Well hi. What's up? How are ya? Welcome to the stream, as always. My name is Jerbo985.
Did you already knew that? You clicked on it. Good afternoon, how are you? Do you? What is that?
Don't do anything cool while the ad is going. Oh my, you know what? That's a really good idea.
That's true. I should not say anything for the first five minutes ever of any stream. That's right.
Because a ton of people are coming in and getting a pre-roll. That's true.
All right, well let's just like do nothing. I do nothing for five to ten minutes anyways for the
first ten minutes of every stream. You're always late in the first place. You know, all right,
let me ask you guys something. Maybe we should poll the community on this because this is important.
If I were to hit the live button, right, at 4 p.m. specific, but I just was not here for at least
10 to 20 minutes, would you prefer that? Or would you prefer for me just to be ready to go
like when the stream comes on, you know within like two to three minutes that we're going to
start? What do you prefer? Would you rather just be late or do you want the stream to turn on at
four and have this screen on for like 15 to 20 minutes? All right, we want you ready to go.
I'd rather you just be late. Okay, be late. All right, second one. Okay, turn it on so we can
listen to the music and watch the planets. Yeah, I'm talking about Monk. That's what I mean.
I was just watching your Thrillville VOD. I get five to ten instead of 20. Well, it is five.
It's 410 right now. I didn't start at 420.
We're going to play Everhood today. We're going to continue the playthrough.
I don't really know that much about... All right, so the last time I played this,
I played it for like 40 minutes and it was really... I was like half a bottle down in wine.
I drank like half a bottle of wine. I was just playing it. I didn't really follow the story
that much that well. I remember it was fun, but people were like,
please, for the love of God, play this game again. I was like, all right, restart the game.
No, start over? No, I mean, I played it for like... I remember the gnome stuff. It was fun.
I remember the guy would be in like the club and the guy's like, we did like a dance battle.
Why do I sound like that? Stop. What's wrong with me? Yeah, but you were drunk.
So what? I started the game a little bit on the drunk side.
So what? I can't continue that playthrough. It needs to be a clean slate.
Well, let me ask you this. How long is this game? Is this game like a four-hour experience?
Is this game like a seven-hour experience? How long is the game?
It's like about seven hours. Okay. It's like six to seven. All right. Well then,
so then I can, I'm guaranteed to be able to finish it tonight then. Like six. Yeah. So then I'm
already like four. Yeah. No, no. We're not starting over. Let's go. You guys ready? I'll give... Okay.
Here's the story so far. Laser beam dance game. They shoot laser beams at you. You have to dodge
it. The music is to the music. There's a beat that plays in the background. You jump over the beat.
You dodge the beat and then you beat enemies based on dodging their musical attacks. That's
pretty much it. That's all you really need. It's pretty fun. I will tell you right now.
Let's get this out of the way as well. There's a, there's a flashing lights warning. I turned on
this thing here. So I, the image sensitivity I turned on because I don't really like getting
my like face like flashed and shit anyways. So, but just be aware this game is pretty,
if you photosensitive, this is like, this is going to be a doozy. Anyways, I'm ready to,
I'm ready to rock and roll. You should put up a warning. I think that, does that warning stay
in the corner? I don't remember. Let's see. I put it on hard? What? I played this on hard? What?
Why did you let me do that? Why would I be on the hardest difficulty guys? What? So this is,
but we're only like 30 minutes into the game. I got into this castle. You're good at it. So
don't worry. I'll be all right. I got into the castle and I'm about to do like a big castle battle.
As expert as well. Yeah, I know. We tried to stop you. You insisted on it. Okay. Well,
you should put a warning on screen. Should I actually, because I will if I, if you think I
should. No, yes. Yeah. I'm getting a lot of yeses. You should. Yes. Put it in the title. My title is
like perfectly carefully comedically crafted. I don't think I want to do that. I'll put it on
screen. I'll just put it like kind of in the corner. Your title sucks. Oh yeah.
I'm sorry. I've been in a weird mood lately. How's that? Can I have it like kind of down here?
Where should it go? Like up here? Is that all right? Is it okay? Put it right in the middle?
I'm not going to put it in the middle, dude. What are you talking about? Responsible Annie.
I think that's okay. Yeah. I think that's, that's all right. Put it in the stream title.
My stream title is perfectly crafted. All right. Well, all right. You guys saw that. Whatever.
Fuck. You guys saw the funny joke in the stream title. Who cares about the title? I'll put it in
the stream title. You guys already saw the funny stream title, right? And everybody laughed and now
all right. Here we go. I, dude, I had this one. It's one of you required to feel the music.
Flashing lights. I put it right here. This title has so many brackets. This is the longest title
I think I've ever had. This title is too long now. Let me see. Is that better? There we go.
Care as somebody said. I don't know. Okay. When I play, people tell me, play Ace Attorney, dude.
Play Ace Attorney. Ace Attorney is like so fucking fun. It's like the funnest game. You're going to
love it. That's, that's great. I tried to play it. I did because I always try to see if I can
record a game or capture it, make sure it doesn't look like shit, right? Um, I can't play Ace Attorney
because every 10 seconds the game decides to go like this and I don't know why it goes,
and it flashes a white light in your face. It happens every 10 seconds.
Anyways, the key to the locked door is somewhere in the maze. I put it there.
Maybe it was for the best. Okay. So I got to find the key. Why can't anyone hear me?
You were playing the game wrong. You should buy, buy a real copy of the game.
It's funny you say that, sir or madam. I actually bought every single version of the game that was
available. I bought it on the iPad to see if it had, if it happened on the iPad. I got it across
every platform, steam, everywhere, consoles. I purchased that game probably four or five times
because I was hoping that one of these versions did not have the flashing white light.
Hi-ho-ha. Fancy seeing you here in such a spooky place. I am notice Freddy here. I've heard that
this castle has a heart and a soul. Hi, Fanta. What that really means? Maybe it has a secret rooms.
Slime. Oh, here we go. Everybody get ready. First banger of the night incoming. You ready?
This is Flynn. Welcome to Slime Brothers Plank Service. My name is Flynn and my brother's name
is Muck. It's me. We provide a plank renting service. What kind of plank are you looking for?
I'm looking for a long plank. Long planks are my favorite, but sadly they are out of stock.
Welcome to Slime Brothers Plank Service. My name is Muck and my brother's name is Flynn.
Talk to my brother if you want to rent a plank. Welcome to Slime. That's not what he said. I forgot
everything about this guy. What was he? I forgot. Well, I don't remember. I'm not kidding. I don't
remember what he sounded like. I have no idea. Well, I don't know. I remember he was kind of
like Otto on the right, but what did he sound like? Hi, welcome to Slime Brothers Plank Service.
My name is Flynn and my brother's name is Muck. It's me. Yes, what do you want? Long plank. Whoa,
you know, very long planks are hard to handle. They come at a price. Are you sure? All right,
actually, for you to rent a very long plank, you also need. Shoot, I forgot. Hey, Goku. Yeah?
What do you need to rent a very long plank? You mean the diploma of certification for
handling very long planks? Right. Do you have a certificate for handling very long planks, sir?
Yes, I do. Hey, don't pull my leg. You don't have a certification. You're a funny guy. Of course,
you're wrong. Don't worry. It's on the house. Hey, Muck. What is it, Flynn? This wood face
wants the diploma of certification for handling very long planks. Oh, really? Get ready, matey.
Let's go. Turn it up. Oh, this is good. I like it. This is a good song. I drank two copies,
by the way, so there's no way I get hit again. Nice. Are they playing? Are they playing like
guitars? Just like wood guitars. Oops. Oops. You are worthy of the diploma of certification
for handling very long planks. Now it's up on the wall. And of course, here's your very long plank.
God. Let's pick it up. You picked up the very long plank as my diploma. The diploma reads
diploma of certification for handling very long planks. One who has earned the certificate has
not only amassed a body of knowledge pursuant to handling very long planks, but also has demonstrated
proficiency in wicked dance moves and an impeccable personal style. Displayed in the medium of groovy
beats, we, the Slime Brothers Plank Service, present with this diploma evidence that they have
fulfilled all necessary requirements as given with confidence that the individual is equipped
by grace of Slime Brothers to meet their challenge in life as a strong, willful, and plank-possessing
individual. What a nice diploma. Please leave your diploma here. I have only five voices.
Okay, so I have a plank now. Where do I put that? Oh, it's this guy. I remember this guy.
Oh, it's you again. What the hell do you want? You'll be annoying somewhere else. I'm busy,
can you tell? Fuck off. Here's the plank right here. Gotta be careful. Certified welder? Oh,
save the game. Right. I forgot the lanterns did that. Save. Hello? Nose-far-ot-choo.
That was a sneeze joke. I warn you red. Amazed monster lurks here. If it finds you,
try to scare it. Monster guards something. If. Sorry, forgot what it was.
Okay, just look around here first. Are there any items in this game or is it just a bunch of
dances? What the fuck was that? Okay. Oh my god. Oh shit. Nice. Gotta stay on the left side after
this. Oh my god. Okay. Jesus. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I'm ready. I'm ready. Holy shit.
Oh my fucking lord. All right. I gotta, I gotta stay on the left side. Definitely.
Could be right. What the fuck am I supposed to do about that one? What was that button? That was
like a Sonic the Hedgehog spring. Nice. All right. Fucking idiot. I need full health for this.
All right. All right. Right. Jesus god. I gotta get that one down. All right. So
what does the red button do? Do I touch the button? I like the song though. I gotta put
both headphones in. That's a problem. Stupid fucking idiot. All right. Stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop. I jumped over the button. I button button. Where's the button? Here it comes. Fuck
you. Fuck. Shut up. Not you. You don't have to shut up. It's me that has to shut up.
Ugh. All right. I swear to god. I'm just, it's, it's just a reaction. It's hitting the jump button
on everything. It's, I have to jump, jump, jump. Oh my god. He's running around. He's running around.
He's running around. What do I do? Where do I go? Oh, you found a crystal key. Give me out.
I hide. Oh, give me out. Can I dodge him when he goes down the hall? I did it. I got it. Maze
monster lurks here. Okay. I got the key. So I got the key. Okay. This is my room. It ain't much.
Sorry. It'd be nice if I had some more furniture. Game console with super racket inserted.
Wanna play some super racket with me? Sure. Okay. I warn you. I'm quite good. Hey. Sega.
Oh, we actually are doing this. Deflect with X. Okay. Someone just did that inside of my head.
That sucked. I don't want to hear that again. I don't want to hear that noise ever again.
Okay. I can just, it's too much. If you ever want to play again, I will be here. That was kind of
cool. You're pretty good at this. I mean, I'm playing, I, I got to give myself credit.
If anything that you require me to press a button at a certain time, I've made this remark before
and some of the new viewers can listen to this as well. If a game has four face buttons and it's
in a control stick, I will be able to do good at that game. If we're talking four buttons,
that's it. If there is like a dodge, a punch, and like a run, I will do good in that game.
Save the game, right? What about Minecraft? Well, no, no, no, no. So I'm sorry.
Minecraft has way more shit to do. There's like a crafting menu. You have to press like a,
you have to combine. No, no, no. If the only thing you do in the game is jump,
dodge and attack and move, I will be, I will win. Careful with that stuff. Doors unlocked.
What about Dark Souls? Well, here's the thing. Dark Souls, you don't, I could literally use the
default weapon in Dark Souls you find in the very beginning and you still get through the game.
You can find like some shitty katana on the ground in Dark Souls and you could,
you could get through the game. It doesn't matter. Hey, did I lose? What happened? Oh,
okay. Okay. What? Okay. It's, I get it. Hey, you got to go up some, it's a joke. Up, up.
How do I go up from here? Yeah. I'm not playing your game. That's down. How do I know which one
goes up? Oh, okay. I got it. You picked up the handle piece of a door. I'm bored. I'm going to
go read Calvin and Hobbes. I mean, I've, I've completely, I put a stamp of approval on that.
Calvin and Hobbes is fucking one of the greatest ever. I, I, I can like say that that's a good
idea. I mean, like we've probably got like German 985, Calvin and Hobbes, and Garfield is like the
best cartoon characters probably ever, right? So that's okay. You have the biggest challenge ahead
of you. This is the mirror of truth and I will allow you to leave my castle, which is probably
up here. John R. Buckle. I am royal guard of castle. My guard important. Very important.
Enter alone only. What? Why? Rules are rules. I don't have any legs and this guy is mute.
Did you really deny us entrance? Hey, were you only? Okay. Hey, how's the mirror? Okay.
I, um, let's walk around it. I think you should keep trying to look at the mirror. Maybe try to
examine it from the other sides. I just did that. This is my first dream. Say hi. What's going on?
Just stare at it? What if I just don't move and look at it? It's not even a mirror.
Okay. I don't, it's not doing anything. What? What's to happen? Oh, look at you. Look at me.
What gives you the right to come here and control me? I wish you would just leave.
You disgust me. This wooden cage. Not always been like this. Divided myself into pieces.
Everyone, once you leave, I have to deal with everything. He's made it a wood. It would be
like creaking and shit. I'm the actor. You're not an actor. I hate you for it. I wish you would just
stop. I want you to leave. I don't want to talk to you again. This guy's so annoying. Okay. I leave.
This is like, this is you and your emo phase. Talk to me. I'm rural guard. I guard important,
very important. I leave now? Well done, little puppet. You are a one step closer to helping us
all. In another time, you will come back and you will slay the beast within and passage will open.
The end is nearing us. You are now free to leave. Oh, hold on. My headphones got tied up. That's
kind of hard to use. This is kind of cool. I should play Noita. I have played Noita and it created a
big problem for me. All right. Yeah. I'm just untying my headphones so they can sit on my ears
better. Okay. What's over here? Come on and experience the race of your lifetime. We let's
go. All right. It's pretty good. Oh, look at them braces go. Someday I hope to win. My sibling is
into fantasy games. All right. I'll tell you, I have both headphones in and it's loud for me because
obviously I want to feel the music. That's a requirement. Otherwise, you know, the exit signs.
So, but I can, I can't hear myself talk. So it's hard to like talk. I don't even know what I sound
like right now. I have no idea what I sound like. You sound like you're drunk. I'm so, I can't hear
myself talk, which means I can't talk well. Why me? Why me? Why me? It's the point of learning
new skills. You'll just get bored and forget all that knowledge over time. Maintaining your driving
skills, for example. What does anyone get out of that anyways? I guess when it comes down to it,
I need to stop thinking about the future. Enjoy what's in front of me instead of what's ahead.
So that's why they've had like 10 wow expansions. The exact reason you're describing.
I have to treat my life like I'm going through a cave full of gems and try to collect as many as
I can because otherwise what's the point? Wow reference minus two. No, no, it wasn't. No,
it wasn't. Hi there, a red rider. Can you smell the gasoline? Can you feel the thrill? Are you
getting pumped? Do you want to participate in the race? Yes. Oh, exciting. Let us get you our cart.
Wait, I actually get to drive this? Welcome all racers. Tonight and all other nights,
we will race until the end of time. Why am I the other way back here? This isn't fair. What?
Brattle is A. Oh my God. Are you serious? I'm so bad at games like this. I thought I had to pick
stuff up. I don't know. I just, I thought I had to pick something up. Oh, this is crazy.
Shit. I'm not going to be able to beat this. I can't win this.
My God, it's too fast. No, I'm just towed. Oh, this is what it feels like to be fucking towed.
I'm in 20th place still. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it.
Fuck. It's hard. Don't get lapped like towed. Don't get lapped like towed on Bowser's cape, please.
It's hard to tell where they're coming at that down the road.
It's too hard. It's no idea. It's too much. Both headphones in visual stimulation.
I'm going at warp speed. I'll get it. I'll get it. Just relax everybody. Hold on.
All right. There we go. There we go. Slow down. Come on. Come on. Right for the middle.
Come on. It's right there. Damn it. How? No, no, it's right here. I, I still got it. I have a chance.
Oh, that was a choke. It was a choke. It's all right. I get it this time.
Okay. Let's go. Let's go. I'm coming to first place now. Let's go. See, now I get it right here.
You pushed me off the road. Fuck you. Don't hold the acceleration the whole time.
In much better position than I was last time. Red is climbing through the ranks.
Who's in first place? It's always Mario and Luigi. It's such poor shit. And if you get even remotely
close to either one of those two assholes, they go. And they don't even have a star. It's so fucking
stupid. That game sucks. All right. Hold on. Don't blow it. Can anybody even hear me? I don't even
know what I'm gonna be talking. Hey, good. Just don't hit anything. I'm right here.
It's right behind me. It's right up ahead. Oh, I just scared the shit out of me. Yes. Yes. Nice.
All right. I guess you can hear what I was saying. Anytime in Mario, uh, Mario Kart Super Nintendo,
you get close to Mario or Luigi. They just have a star. It's so, it's annoying. They're always in
first and second place. Congratulations on finishing in first place. Here is your trophy.
Oh, trophy. You picked up a trophy. What does that do? Do it multiple times. Wait, do the race
multiple times? It doesn't do anything. It does literally nothing. Oh, that's still fun. Hi, ho.
Welcome. Welcome. I am Cassius. Come and run my humble obstacle course. It ain't much, but it's
something. Hi. I will reward you with something yummy. If you beat the universal record,
you want to run the obstacle course? Make sure to stretch first. I'm not muted. Stop. I can see my
indicators. Ready? Three, two, one, action. Oh, this is bad. I got to use analog for this. Or do I?
How do I sprint? Oh, did I do it? I got it. You beat the record. Receive your award outside.
Well done. You'll be rewarded with a homemade, delicious, scrumptious cake. Okay. Maybe you can
give it to a friend. Picked up a cake. I like this kind of little mini games. I like this.
Only VIPs allowed. Oh, no need to eat. I know the taste. Anything else I can do? What's he doing?
Look at them racers go. Okay. Okay. So that's, I got to go in the VIP room. Let's do it.
Who are we theater? Who are we watching? Hello Red. I sometimes come here to relax.
Just to let my mind wander a bit and forget about it all. I got it right. Good. Sorry.
Here comes my favorite part. Wow, that was cool. Look at that. I got to share that with you stranger.
Okay. Anything I can do over here? Dude, this would be so bad for you. Imagine sitting this
close to a screen like this and having your eyes open. Oh, it hurts to think about that.
All right. That was cool. This is fun. Imagine being that close to your stream.
VOD watcher point of view. We had a good time. It didn't. It's not the door we came from.
That was quite a fall. Okay. What's up with this? He picked up a shiny gem. He over here.
Wait, did I look up here? I like the song so far. This is the best song, best character coming up.
Cool. Whoa. What's that? You found my eye. Please give it to me. Sure. Yes, I am finally restored.
I can't believe you have all people saved me. What's that supposed to mean?
Are you here as well, little red nose? Aiding the enemy? What? The enemy? The enemy is gold pig.
I might have been lost to the woods for ages, but you are the one who is truly lost. Anyway,
I am not without honor. You have helped me. So I am in your debt. Now that my vision is restored,
I can use my magic. You seem to be missing an arm. Maybe I can help by removing this giant
boulder in your way. Should we teleport it away? Destroy it? Why not transform it?
Now it's a Mario cube. How delightful. Maze transformed the giant rock into a clay pod.
This is what happens when you do voices for too long. I will now consider the debt repaid.
I am still thankful for you bringing me my eye, red. I will remember that.
You can go now. There is no reason for you to continue to stand there. Apparently. Hey,
hold on a second. Now that the debt has been repaid, you are still the enemy.
Seeing you in such a weakened state, it would be unfortunate if I didn't, you know, exploit the
situation. Oh, I didn't press the button. This might be my favorite song so far. Oh, damn. Seems
you are still strong even without your arm. But you know, I don't really care about any of this.
I just want to have a good time. Thanks to you now I can. I won't forget that you helped me.
I won't bother you anymore unless you bother me. Have fun in the mushroom forest. I have enjoyed
enough here without going insane. That reminds me, I'm extremely late to an appointment. See you
around. Are we in the mushroom forest? Well, this is on hard. There's something about this place I
can't remember. Funny. Wait, this looks like a cave. Oh, oops. I feel like this is about to get weird.
Everything's slowing down. I obviously follow the rabbit, but. I am the guardian of the mushroom
forest. There will come a time when we shall talk, but it will not be tonight.
So unfair. Everyone took the good hiding places. You still have seven to find. Oh, great. You found
me. I don't consider myself so good at hiding as the others. We still have six to find. Whoa,
you found me. You still have to find five more. See you around, dude. Oh, thank God. Are you Swedish?
No. If you spend too much time in the mushroom forest, you might change. What does that mean?
Oh, you found me. I think you should be reevaluating my invisibility spell. You
still have four to find. By the way, we never figured out what that was from. It was not from
that TV show. I don't know what it's from. Oh, you really stepped into something bad now.
Another weirdo. Oh, let me get my weirdo voice ready. One, two, three, me, me, me, weirdo. Incoming.
I have finally caught the wooden pestilence. I'll make sure it won't be able to escape.
With my defibrillatory stun gun, it will hurt. It will take months before we can use that stun gun
again. We'd better make the best out of this opportunity. Grundel, go pick it up and bring
it to the land now, Grundel. What are you doing? Hurry up. I've had enough of a weirdo for you.
You doofus. Here comes the weird guy. Don't you know that Gerber does weird characters
and he loves to do them. Even though they all sound like this. Every single one of them.
It works, I think, though, for most characters. You got to just do the weird guy. That's it.
I thought I was supposed to find mushrooms. Oh, back to the bunny. I mean, I just got
captured. What are you talking about? What happened? Never mind. You can't talk anyway.
Kick me up and let's get out of here. I do anything else here? He's doing anything?
I don't even want to talk about the things I've seen here. You can save your progress here.
Do you want to save? Yes. Good luck getting out of here. Are you going in the light? Get out of the
way. Step away or prepare for trouble. I wonder what this song will be. He's got one huge arm.
Not bad so far. Oh, my lord. Oh, fuck. God damn it. That got hard. Relax, relax, relax, relax, relax,
relax. You got to hug the left side when he does that weird bone. Here we go. You idiot.
That was so easy. You good? All right. That was a good one, too.
I didn't do it. I promise. I didn't do it. No, I didn't. Strange looking machine.
You have awakened just in time. My masterpiece is about to be unleashed.
I have constructed an artificial replication of an ancient creature.
Its raw energy makes it so powerful that it can only exist for a limited time.
The only chance to bring you down and establish peace once and for all. Prepare to face your doom,
red beige. What's wrong? What happened? Did I lose? What? How could you have defeated my masterpiece
so swiftly? It didn't even stand a chance. Even more powerful than I imagined. It must be another
way. We will meet again, red marauder. Okay. The door is shut tight. All right. Go get the
mushrooms. Go back and get the mushrooms. Can I get, can I go back from here? There's no door.
I can't go anywhere from here. Are you enjoying the game? This is great to go down. What the hell
is going on in here? This is freaking me out. Oh, actually, you know what? You're going to think
I'm crazy for a second, but trust me, I'm doing this for a reason. I need to move that over the
dead pixel. Let me get it in the right spot. I have a dead pixel on my monitor. And I think
that actually, if I move it to this right spot, it'll fix it. Right. Let's see. It's like, how do
I move it? I can move it over here. All right. It's, it's on the dead pixel right now. It only
works for some types of, it takes hours for that shit to work. Does it? It's not going to work if
I sit here. Oh, well. Yeah. It's, it's green. The pixels. So it's not a dead pixel. It's a stuck pixel.
All right. Who are you? You're everywhere. What do they want? Let me be. I don't want to make it
stop. I don't want to make it stop. Make it stop. Make it stop. Make it stop. Make it stop. Make it
stop. Make it stop. The TV. How long must I endure? How long has it been? How long has it been? How
long has it been? Who said that? Who's there? Stop laughing at me. It hurts. I just want it to stop.
It hurts. Just want to stop. Rest a bit. Please. I don't want it to just stop. I don't want it to
hurt. Stop it. Don't do it. Stop. Stop it. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop it. All right. I'm getting out
of here. No, I didn't want to do that again. Do I keep talking to them? It never ends. Why won't it
end? Must I suffer forever? It never ends. That damn mage. Why does it torture me? I want to leave.
I don't know where to go. I'm useless. They're everywhere. Okay. Well, I turned off the TV. Can
they leave now? I don't know. It's an average Jerma viewer. You can, you can leave whenever you want.
I don't know. I'm not holding you here. Why do you think we can leave? I don't know because you can.
All the circumstances are optimal. I have analyzed the triggering factors of what is considered a
battle using quantum theory to artificially create a battle that is not considered a battle.
You can't resort to your dirty tricks, red mage. This will be the end of you.
Oh, I can run. There's no jumping. All right. What do you got? What do you got? What do you got?
What's going on? I have to attack it? Yikes. Yikes. Oh, I thought it was over.
Fuck. That was sick. Remarkable. My efforts have proven futile once again. Is there nothing that
can stop you? Hope you find it in your heart to forgive my actions. I just want to find a solution.
This won't be the last time we meet, red mage. That was cool. I can go in there.
We're all being paid by your mother to watch this stream. None of them want to be here.
Nobody wants to be here. Okay. If my mother was paying each of you $1 to be here every stream,
that's almost $17,000 a stream. That's extreme. I stream probably two days a week.
You're talking about like $40,000 a week that my mother is paying to have you all be here.
But that's $160,000 a month. So you're telling me that my mother is spending more than 1.1 or
1.2 million dollars a year just to have you stay here and pretend to like the stream.
And that's only if you were getting $1 to be here. And I'll be honest with you, right? Think about
that. If somebody were to ask you to, hey, I want you to go watch this stream for, you know,
four to six hours, I'll give you a dollar. You'd be like, no fucking way. You'd be like, make it
$50. You're not doing that for a dollar. You're doing that for at least like $30 to $40, at least.
There's no way you're going to do that for that little. Like, if my mother's not giving you at
least like a 20 or like at least about 30 bucks to be there. Uh-uh. There's no way. I want to get
that. Can you imagine? Can you actually imagine if like, I was actually truly paying people to stay
here and you guys are not bots. You're just, I'm actually like hiring people to pretend to be an
audience. That would be so weird. When's the paycheck? Okay. No, no, no, don't go back in.
Happy Saturday. Yeah. Happy Saturday. Okay. Now we're looking for the mushrooms or maybe not.
Professor Orange has sent a message. They have failed to annihilate the doll.
Yes. But then we moved back to our hideout. That doll to the hillside back. It's a grand similar
affection. Orange messages that there is a doll picked at the blue door piece that Orange has
left before it left. What? Sir, the doll has given the kiss, the cursed kiss. Yes. The doll
is still there. The doll can hear us. It's using some sort of telepathic magic.
How long is it with this thing? I can just swap the magic if you desire, golden pig.
Not another word. I'll do it right. I'll do it myself. Are you all right?
Okay. You kind of Zoey's out there for a while. Looking for mushrooms. Can I run down?
I'm not making any sense. I made it to the other side. All right. Mushrooms. Hello there.
Do you want to save? Yes, I do. Change. All right. All right. All right. Hi. I guess you found me.
You still have three to find. Bye. Three more. I think I already went up by this one. Oh, hello.
I guess you did find me. You still have two to find. Well, find the bunny. All right. I'll get
the bunny. I already went up here. Is this one? Oh, you found me. I knew I should have
chosen a better hiding spot. You still have one to find. Oh, don't even start doing more to you,
idiot. All right. I got them all. Hi. It was the last mushroom. We'll be waiting by the forest
guardian far to the west. Whoa. Oh, it's this person. Right. Okay. Right now you are the
annoying audio book voice actor you complained about. I'm not. No, I'm not actually. No, I didn't
complain about audio books. I just said it's hard to be an audio book voice narrator because
you have to do like 60 people's voices over the course of the whole story because even the best
voice actors in the room in the room, I was going to say even the best voice actors in the room.
If you tell them to do all their voices back to back to back to back,
you will be able to tell it's the same person. You will. Nobody can be different people.
For instance, I am the guardian of the Muslim forest. I will open a passage for you. Let me
tell you that this is entirely optional. You're not forced to be here. This is only for those
seeking answers. There will come a time when we shall talk, but it will not be tonight.
Hey, that was me talking. You knew that was me talking. Why? Why can't I go in there? He
found us all. What the hell? Hi there. You found us. Go talk to the divine mushroom.
Look at the divine mushroom. Welcome to my domain. Your efforts in indulging my kin.
For giving them some joy, I cannot offer you much. I can't offer you much, but I can give you
a bathroom break. You need to pee very badly. Enjoy the break while you pee.
Drinking water all day. Be right back before I do another big, big one. Oh,
it's still the Christmas thing. Hey, it's still Christmas in my mind. I'll be right back. I just
want to grab some beef jerky too. I promise that I won't choke on it and inhale it like I did in the
little ring string. Sponsored? I didn't tell you what brand I'm eating. Sponsored by who?
Sponsored by the beef industry. Beef industry sponsor. I'm not in Congress. I don't have
lobbyists. What are you talking about? I really liked his streams. Once the big beef industry
got involved and started lobbying him. What? All right. I'm ready. What'd you say? I like this
comment. I bet your breath always smells like you just ate jerky. It's not garlic. I'm not eating
cloves of garlic. Beef jerky does not stay with you in your clothes and shit. It's just like
fucking, what are you talking about? What are you on about? It still has an aroma. Okay. What
about every other food? Do you have like, like chicken nugget breath? Did you eat a bowl of
cereal? Are you going to have like, like wheat grass on your breath? No, I think your breath
just stinks. That's it. Nobody knows what you had for dinner. They just know that you smell.
Holly's. There you go. There's your proof. Holly literally just said, I don't smell like beef.
Like I don't smell like a meat aroma. Confirmed. My headcanon is that you smell like weed.
Why wouldn't, why are you headcanoning what I smell like? You know what? You know what I do smell
like? I smell like a dryer sheet. I smell like a dryer sheet and motor oil together. You know,
you understand? Like it's just light motor oil and dryer sheet. Maybe like a hint of grilled onions.
What a disgusting smell. Are you willing to risk your soul? Yes. I am neither glad nor sad. You
smell like piss. I do not smell like piss. I'm very, if I'm not going to mess around and be
honest with you, I'm very aware of how I smell. I always am trying to be like clean. I always want
my clothes to be clean. I always want to be able to have a shower before I go anywhere or do anything.
I always am very aware of my like cleanliness of my body. Just go. All right. Settle down. Relax.
I'm just hanging out. Find peace in your endeavors. Take a few steps back, please.
Good. Now let this happen. Things might get strange. Ow. All right. It's a worm fight. Whoa.
Time to get weird. What the fuck? Shit. Whoa. I can't even see that. Hello, human.
And you see us. I don't know what I'm supposed to be looking for. Jesus. Why are you here?
Oh, fuck. This is so wild. You are hurting. Please quit. Never. I'll never quit.
I will give it 100% always and potentially go beyond. 110%. I hurt my throat doing that. Why?
Seems that you are back. Did you know what you were getting yourself into?
You don't have to keep coming back. You're always watching. I hope you're enjoying yourself.
That you have something to do. Being it. It's not always easy. Have you come to hear an absolute
truth? Yes. There is a risk you might change upon hearing it. Sometimes not for the better.
Are you sure you want to hear an absolute truth? It doesn't feel like the machine else come in.
There are several absolute truths. One of them is you are me and I am you.
Even the ones you hate and love remain true to yourself. Your thoughts were never yours anyways.
Take this truth and it is now in your hands to truly interpret. It's humor is how you wanted
to experience this life. I told you many times to not go through with this. I thought it would be
fun and here you are. We look forward to sitting talking and laughing about all this when you
return. You must go forward. We will let you return to your world. We hope you find what
you're looking for. You must now leave. It's turning British. Welcome back. I hope you enjoyed
that experience. You strike me as an adventurous sport. Take this precious gemstone. It might be
useful someday. Maybe not this day. You picked up a ruby. Thanks. All right. New item. Can I go in
here now? Guarding the forest. Do I have to pay him in a ruby? You smell like Sour Patch Kids
and old cigarette butts. So I smell like a movie theater? I smell like the outside of a movie
theater. Now that's an absolute truth. All right. Whatever. Would you like an absolute truth? Yes.
You smell like Sour Patch Kids and cigarette butts. That would be so funny. I wish they would put that
in here. An absolute truth. Your breath is awful. It smells like you just opened up a tuna can
and put it inside of a dog shit bag. I hope you found something extraordinary.
You can now return to your realm. Okay. Damn. All right. That was cool. He's just frog.
Enjoying ourselves? Nope. This is quite a strange world. This realm has a way of
cutting right into the heart. It is natural it becomes this way for immortals. I like it for
what it is. I will be expecting many great things from you. It will get harder in ways
you might not be able to imagine. Voice is bad. Voice is bad. Shitty voice. Worst voice. Okay,
fine. I'll give you one that you like. But I shouldn't let you worry too much. You're ever
lost. Maybe talk to your blue friend. I bet they have a keen sense of direction.
Opposite ends of the spectrum for horrible. And not getting the good one. I know you want it to
be like, all right, if you're ever lost, maybe talk to your blue friend. I bet they have a keen
sense of direction. Now that would have been good, right? Hey, you fine piece of craftsmanship.
Want to swing by Midnight Town. The nicest place around. That was a perfect voice for a frog where
the world wasn't ready for it. Trust me, I know. All right, we've got a lot of places I can go.
Is this kind of like the Mega Man open world screen? Do I just pick a world and go?
Hey Red, instead of going back there, how about we go to Midnight Town? Cool. Time is only temporary.
True. What's this? Casino? What are we playing? Looking forward to playing. It's fun pretending
to be someone else. Oh, it's just, it's like D&D. I can't wait to get started. Hi there, Red. We can
finally start the game. Let's go. Certainly is out of my comfort zone, but I don't have anything else
to do. Sorry, well done, but I do like your company. Okay, Red, there's still room for one
more player if you want to join. I promise you it's going to be blast. All right. Yeah, let's play.
Wait, what's in here? The hatch is shut tight. You can't get it open. Seems we're all finally here.
Now, are you ready? Ready for an epic adventure? Yes. Good. Let me just set the mood. Let the
adventure begin. Once upon a time, in the land of Medallion, there was a village whose name had
been forgotten. The little town was settled with happy, hard-working villagers. But beyond the lake,
deep in the darkness, stood a tower so tall that it reached the clouds. The villagers could see
mysterious lights and shadows moving at the top of the tower, fearing that an evil wizard had
taken hold of the tower. The townspeople hoped for a hero to save them from their presumably ill
fate. Within the village was a temple that protected an ancient relic capable of withstanding evil.
Sword that deflects, Red attacks. Really? That's a really dumb name. I find it quite descriptive.
Guys, please don't interrupt. During a dark, rainy night, a warrior entered the temple.
Oh, great warrior, take this sword, our most valuable relic. Vanquish all the evil and save
our small village. Receive this sword and gain its powers of deflecting red attacks. With this power,
you might be able to face the evil wizard. Now before- what the fuck? Give me all your treasure
or pay with your lives. Oh, great warrior, we're helpless. Save us from this foul bandit.
I can deflect red, deflect his X, okay. Get out of town. You have bested me.
You saved us, oh great warrior. Hooray. Hooray. Hooray. Now make haste to the tower and defeat the
evil wizard. The warrior has a quest. Little did the warrior know what terrible challenges were
ahead. Seems like such a waste of time. We could be doing something more important, Red.
Mermaid man.
No, we need to get into the boat and go get them, SpongeBob.
What are you doing, you old moron?
I am trying to do what it is a superhero must be doing, getting to the bank.
We cast that check two days ago.
What? I have no idea what you're talking about. That wasn't SpongeBob, that was Barnacle Boy.
I have no idea what you're talking about. I'm glad you're the warrior, Red.
All right, get to the tower and fight. Yeah, that was Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
That wasn't SpongeBob. Oh, this is cool. I like this. Mood, yes.
Fake SpongeBob fans. So what, we're playing D&D right now? Is that what this is supposed to be?
Hey there, Red. Are you on your quest to slay the evil wizard? You see, that is also my quest.
That guy's terrorized these villagers too long. I see you got the sword that deflects Red attacks.
I'm not relying on any steel. My weapons are my fists.
Just out of curiosity, would you like to engage in some friendly sparring?
See which one of us is the strongest? Your sword versus my fists?
You want a surprising battle? All right, let's see who truly is the strongest.
Fucking cringe. What? Why did I just cringe?
Wait, why wasn't I ready? Shit, I could be hitting way more of these.
Like that, there we go. Yeah, you gotta string it together.
Cat, our streamer is bad. What? No, I'm not. I mean, I'm not great. I wouldn't say I'm very
good, good, but I think I'm okay. You got impressive moves. I have to practice harder
if I'm gonna beat the evil wizard before you. Let me handle it. I'm the one with the sword.
Oh no. Help me, Red. This game's too hard. I gotta attack my squirrels.
Would you help me? Thanks much. This time I will not fail.
Oh no, get up. Wow, those squirrels don't give up.
Would you help me up again? Thanks. This time I will not fail.
Wow, don't give up. Can I have you help me? Thanks. Thanks for helping me.
If he's dead, he's dead. Whatever.
Dear enter my domain. I have been commanded to not let a soul pass this bridge
if you are to cross. Prepare to pay with your life. Is this the wizard? No.
I think it's about to get serious. Boys and girls, it's about to get serious. What was that?
What the fuck is this? Oh, it takes out the whole row. That's good. No.
I like the song though. It's really chill. Shit. See ya.
Got some dank moves. Such great powers. I sure hope you're a good aligned character.
Warrior had proven their skills twice. Their confidence was high, which would be needed.
The swamp of chaos would challenge the warrior to their very core.
Swamp of chaos? Isn't a swamp level a bit cliche? What's next, the sewer level before the tower?
No. It's actually the badlands of chaos. You don't have to change the entire level because
of the zig. No, it's fine. I was obviously kidding that there was a swamp level. This is better.
The game's like glitching. Do you see that? What's this? Can I get rid of this stuff?
Honestly, the graphics in this level are very ugly. It really looks unfinished.
Well, that's what you get. Just saying you can make it better at the end of the game.
This is fart music. I gotta come forward in the chair. Here we go.
Stop hitting me. Only if you give me all your items.
Land, is that you? Did you see ya? This is my custom made mech character from Gears of
This fantasy game is way easier with a mech. I also noticed that attacking other players gives
me more loot. This must be breaking several game rules. I'll have to check the rule book.
Hold on, you don't play a good character, do you Red?
Oh, in that case, green and over all of your items will feel the wrath of the chaos six.
God, he's like scary looking. B. All right, get it together. Get it together. E.
Fuck. I'm going too far. This game is hard. I play a good guy. I lose. I play a bad guy. I lose.
Here we go. I found the rule about PvP combat. Oh, I guess you guys solved it already. It was
really not what we were concerned about. The show must go on little one. How am I supposed to win
when I keep losing? Muk keeps telling me failure is the progress that pays the world to success.
To me, failure just seems like failure. I guess you just have to think of another way to win the
game. I can't believe I was steamrolled by flan. I should really retire.
Don't skip. I didn't skip anything. Finally, at the foot of the tower,
the lair of the evil wizard. Will you be able to save the village from its ill fate?
It's actually becoming quite exciting. You can do it, Red. I guess if anyone has a chance to win,
it's you. If you defeat the evil wizard, we win the game. I'm the curse save point. There is a
50% chance that I'll delete your save. Lucky for you, you should have several save slots.
Do you take your chances? Oh my god. That actually scared me. Your save was deleted?
Okay. Holy shit, is that real? But seriously, your game was saved. Okay.
Scared me enough to do that. Got all this space back here. I'm assuming you're not going to use it?
Really? Okay. You have come a long way, warrior. I see that you are armed.
You are not the first they have sent to assassinate me. Isn't that right, Rasta beast?
The villagers just fear what they don't understand, you see.
Don't listen to that evil wizard, Red. Oh, shut up, Rasta. I don't have time for this
and you heroes are bothering me. Your death will serve as an example for anyone that would
even consider disturbing me. All right. This is the big one right here.
Oh, they're being blocked. You think you're fighting evil? You are so full of yourself.
I am the one who hears God. How are you so strong? I can't believe I was beaten by a wooden
doll wearing a metal bucket. One day I'll have my revenge. Lots of jump scares in this game.
Thank you for saving me, Red. I wouldn't have made it if it wasn't for you.
You fought valiantly. Let's go back to the village and tell them the good news.
You beat him too fast, you skipped verse two. Really? Oh, shit. Now that the quest has come
to an end, Red and Rasta beast journeyed back to the village, silhouetted by a glorious sunset.
No verse two. Really? Oh, sorry. Once returned, they were received as heroes for defeating the
evil wizard. Plant opened up a bakery where they sold slimy muffins, which proved to be quite a
success. Zig decided to make the tower their home, where Zig lived happily ever after,
or at least for a long time. And Nosferatu- Wait, you weren't in the game at all? I wanted to role
play as one of the mushrooms. Nosferatu continued the unfruitful quest of trying to learn the
secrets of their past. The end. Oh, that was fun. So what did you guys think? That was a good session,
green mage. Oh, I've played better. I enjoyed it, even if it was a bit hard. I guess this is it.
Actually, your great efforts of saving the land of Medallion, Red. Puzzle piece. Take this tributary
piece of wood as a reminder of this epic quest. Oh, wow. I'm sure it will come in handy. We picked
up a piece of a door. Door piece. Very cool. Oh, it's open. Hey, what are you doing? That's private.
The hatch is shut. You can't seem to get it open. What? Are you serious? For that just being one
little section of this area? That was pretty crazy. That was one little house. There's so much
more to do here. What's this? Oh, boy. I'm not doing that yet. Hi, dear. I feel that I am
destined to do great things in my life. I can go down. Who's out there? If anyone is out there,
it's kind of an emergency. Could you get some toilet paper? I'll reward you with a lava lamp
for your troubles. OK, toilet paper. What about the shop? These flowers smell like an old person's
breath. Like Sour Patch Kids and cigarettes. A rigidly locked chest. I smell like childhood.
I smell like barbecue. These flowers smell like paper. They smell like dirt. They smell like
skunky sweet. Wow. What is that clay pot you have? It would fit perfectly for something I had in
mind. I will give you something valuable in return. Could I have the clay pot? Yes.
This feels great. You can take my old hat. Trash can live. You seem interested in that chest.
Are you only Altem? Only the brown mage can unlock the golden lock, so I've heard.
I got a lid. What do I do with the lid now? Hi, small figure. I'm a stone guardian. Really like
eat, but I no move. Oh, you have food. Can I has cake? Yes. Yum. Yum. Yum. Yum. Yum. Yum. Yum. Yum.
Delch. This was a bad cake. Thanks for nothing. What? What do you mean?
Pick up a hook. Do I have a hook? I have a trash can lid. A beautiful metal thing is that. I would
love to trade it. What do you want? Do you want to trade? Yes. Wow. I look so cool. Here, take this.
Um, this nice stick. I don't feel like it's a bad trade. Pick up a nice stick. Okay, stick,
trash can lid. Is there a trash somewhere? Oh, right here. I need a roof for my home. Maybe I
can give you some trash if you find me a roof. I do have some half used toilet paper if that would
be useful. Hey, that thing right there would be great. Perfect. I will trade you for the toilet
paper. Yes. Wait, you're not getting my toilet. I need it too. Haha. What? That's not fair. Ow,
my hand. Damn it. Oh, cool. I like this one. Damn. I think you get your that end, huh? That end?
Oh, what a bother. Fine. Take the toilet paper, but I'm keeping the roof. Got the toilet paper.
I need to be honest. You're really good at this game. You're crazy good at this game. Am I?
Can I find my calling? Who's out there? If anyone is out there, it's kind of an emergency. Yep,
I got toilet paper. Attach it to the hook and I will hoist it up. So what? You're going to
give me the key to the chest, right? Ah, yes. Finally, I can wipe my table clean. Is assholes
a table? Oh, right. I promised you something. A lava lamp, right? Oh, no, I've got bad news.
I seem to have lost it. If you bring me batteries, I promise to make something really, really unique
and special as a super promise. You dick. Bring me batteries. Well, batteries. Batteries in the
clock. I think I went everywhere I can here, right? I think that's it. Hold on. Wait, hold on.
Oh, the door is locked. What is that? All right. Well, I know I can go down. I can do it, Red.
My wife is 350 pounds. Please help me. I don't know. What do you want me to do about it? What
do you want me to do about it, man? Good luck with whatever you're doing. Okay. So I got that
was that door. We've been here. We've been here. Have I been? This is okay. We've been here. This
is the entrance, right? No, I don't want to leave yet. We've not gone in here. I hope you had a
great time. Want to go back dancing? Wait, what? I've gone in here. Knock on in here. How much do
I weigh? 100 and like 150 160. I just want to be someone. I wish I could leave this place someday.
I haven't felt happy in such a long time. 155. Um, I guess I can't do anything here.
Okay. What was that all about? Uh, you should do a golfing stream. I'm not gonna go golf. No,
I don't. I'm bad. I can drive, but I can't do anything else. I can drive and I can putt. That's
it. I would love to drive your ball for you. Wait till you chip it a million times and all the annoying
boring shit. So like I do the, I use the driver and I smash it. And then I just go in the golf
card and get to the green. I just drive to the green and wait for you. And you do all the shitty
boring golf suck stuff from the tee to the green. And then I take the putter and I putt. I do the
fun stuff. Just tell gold pig that you beat me up. If I can count on you saying the same. Yes.
You're a cool guy. All right. I've been, this is the first part, right? I was already here.
I remember doing this and I spit in the, like the one hour that I played this game a couple
weeks ago. I remember playing that part. This implies that I would let myself be within 200 feet
of you. I don't understand. What do you, what do you think? What do you think I'm going to do?
Like start biting you? Door's locked. Did I go in here? I think I already did. Yeah, didn't I?
This door seems broken. Oh, I have all the pieces to this door. All right. Let me save it.
He's rabid. I'm not gonna, why do people think that I'm going to like, I'm going to see you
first of all, how am I going to know who you are? If we're just like out in public somewhere and
we're just doing something, I'm going to know that you're a chatter in my chat. I'm, dude,
if we're just at the grocery store, we're at the grocery store. I'm not going to like ask everybody
in the grocery store if they're a watcher of the channel. First of all, how are you, how am I going
to know who you are from the smell? Okay. Are you sure you want to go in this door?
This journey is long and unforgiving. Do you still want to enter? Yes, of course I do.
And what, like, oh, hey, Jerma. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, just want to say. What, what is it?
I'm a big fan. And when I hear the N in fan, I just grab your fucking arm and start.
Why do you think that's going to happen? No, here's what's going to happen. Hey, Jerma.
Hey, I'm a big fan. Oh, hey, cool, man. Really good to see you.
You're a fan. That's awesome. That's so cool. Yeah, I, this is really fun. This is really cool.
I can't believe somebody recognized me in public. That's insane. Yeah, dude, can I get a selfie?
Of course you can. Of course you can. I'm going to need your credit card, though. And I got my
app here. It has tap. You can tap the phone. It's a little device I plug in. Yeah, sure,
absolutely. You got like a chip in your card, right? Yeah. And then he bites you after you pay.
No. Oh my God. Oh, thanks, man. Yeah, that was $50. Oh, here's a selfie.
I'm just a normal person, guys. I'm not like a rabid weirdo. If you come up to me and say,
Hey dude, how are you? I'm going to be like, Hey, what's up? It's really good to see you.
I'm not like a psycho. I'm not going to like, what are you talking about? Hey, red and blue.
The night is here. Sit down and relax. You still have a long walk ahead.
Please don't bite me. I don't want to turn into a germa. I've been meaning to tell you red.
This path will only lead to more torment. You have come this far. So I guess you've made up
your mind. I'm afraid this will lead to more questions than answers. I fear something
horrible might happen if you continue. Anyway, much has been said. It's time to hit the hay.
Good night. Is it like a bite of a vampire or a zombie? Um, I don't know. Probably,
probably a zombie. If I were to say that I don't have fangs and I don't like drink blood or
anything. So a zombie is just kind of a person's mouth and it's just kind of dirty with unbrushed
teeth. I mean, right? That's the only difference. A bit embarrassing. I don't remember why we are
here. What are we actually trying to do? I don't understand what we are doing. I feel like everyone
is speaking in riddles. There's no clear indication to what's actually going on. You really think we
should continue forward? I trust you. What is going on with this fire? Somebody's just breaking
styrofoam in the background. I can't even concentrate. I just hope you know what you're
doing. I just wanted to say that I trust you. Good night. Tap dancing. Yeah, somebody's practicing
above me in my apartment. That's not what fire sounds like. As good as a day can be, the road
is clear. Good luck. That's the hamburger helper burning in the oven. You don't put a hamburger
helper in the oven. In the oven. It's the sap that's being ignited by the wood.
All right. That's actually kind of interesting. I actually didn't know that. That's kind of cool.
Thanks for the tip. This is nice. This kind of reminds me of Outer Wilds at one planet. Enough,
buddy. Look, pal. I tried stopping you earlier, but you ignored it. I laughed and let it slide,
but now I've really got to put my foot down and tell you, go back and stay out and I won't hurt
you. Oh, I see. So be it. Get ready for a beating, fella. You gonna distract my lightning? I'm
serious. Go back. Come on, mate. What are you gonna be so stubborn? If you won't turn back,
I'll be forced to take you down. All right. You asked for it. I hate to do it. I'm gonna be real
sorry. I shall unleash my fury upon you like the thunder of a thousand lightning storms.
We got a big one coming up. A good song. What am I doing? Why would this work the second time?
All right. Hear me out. If Gold Pig asks, please just say that I fought valiantly, displayed great
acts of heroism and all that jazz. I won't waste any more of your time. I will. Don't worry. I will.
What's that? A car?
Hello? Broken car. There are batteries next to the engine. Do you want to pick up the- Yes, I do.
You picked up the batteries. He's mad. What's the car battle? Go back, turn around. I'm not going
all the way back that way. That's a 10 minute walk. I'm gonna get teleported to that hub world
anyways. Big gate stands ahead. Do you want to open the gate? Yes. What do we got? Oh, you walk
the entire way to the old desert temple and not many visitors come to these parts. It's good to
have multiple saves. Who knows what might happen? Nice. Good luck with whatever you're doing.
Look who finally stumbled in. You just won't give up. As much as I do. I must say I do.
Admiring. Chasing. Like this. At the edge of the mountain. Lucky for you, I have prepared a
welcoming party. Perfect. What I do. What I pay you to do. Hello, Red. I cannot let you continue down
this path. Leave now. I will kill you if you don't. I'm not a very good actor. I'm not a good actor.
Seems that you didn't understand what I meant when I told you to leave.
I regret disobeying my command. This is a Zumbini. I feel pain. I've resurrected you from the dead.
You are to follow my orders until I release you. What is it you ask of me? I want you to disable
the red one. I have something funny to- can't write as well. All right, let's get down to business.
You want to pass, Dolly? That ain't happening. Amigo, you heard what either mage said. I'ma
mess you up. Real bad. Can I still have the sword? Who made all the music for this? That's awesome.
It was Kevin MacLeod. It was not Kevin MacLeod. It's not Kevin MacLeod. It was. No, it was not
Kevin MacLeod. I'm guaranteeing that. Kevin MacLeod is a talented guy. He made a bunch of
great songs for all of us YouTubers. I don't think they had anything to do with this. It's
impossible. Purple, I can't do it. Yes, I see. I did not expect you to be victorious. I expected
you to die. I can't believe I was being used like that. This isn't the first time Purple put me in
a rotting corpse. I could at least have been for something important. Those mages, I don't like
them. I don't like them. I know your secret now. The tactic that lets you win. I found you.
I am Rob, former world champion. Raised from the dead. How to fulfill my deed with my bro Zomp.
But where is that guy? Ah, your green zombie friend there, down the hall.
Oh snap, that slacker knows we've got a job to do. Whoa, whoa, wait. Hold on there. I recognize
your voice. You're the one that summoned me. Oh, I see. You're part of the binding contract.
Seems I've summoned two entities, I guess. Sure seems like it, bro. This guy is loud.
What do you want me to do, boss? Well, since you're here. Yeah. If you defeat it, I will release you
from your bind. Okay, bro. It'll be a piece of cake. Hey, you're going to, yeah, I'm gonna, yeah.
Who's louder, me or them? It's definitely me. It's definitely me. I'm way fucking louder than
this guy. It's not me. It's not me. Holy shit. Oh God, it's distracting. You play good. No,
not sure I could take them down, bro. I didn't expect you to. I expected you to die.
Nothing has changed, Red. Hey, it's me again. I thought I would make things easier for you.
It's good to have multiple saves. Who knows what might happen? Do you want to save? Yes.
Nice. Good luck with whatever you're doing. All right. All right. All right. Okay. I don't,
whatever. Just look up on like the Wikipedia for this game what he said. Dude, my, hey,
my wife is 400 pounds. I don't care how heavy your wife is. I don't care how heavy you are.
I don't care. You're just prancing around in the same spot. I'm surprised you even got this far.
The dead may not be able to stop you. Living seem unable to do as well.
But I will not let you continue. We'll end your journey. This probably seems like a major boss
fighter. Oh boy. I can't get hit there. Why don't they play this kind of shit at the club? I would
go. It's getting quieter. This is freaking me out. They do. They do. They do this in Germany.
It's true. Hold on. Do I find that I like a certain genre of like German club music and I didn't even
know? Impressive. I won't be able to stop you. Understand that I did what I had to do. Let your
choices be merciful. It's literally just EDM. But is it like German EDM or is there a difference?
It's just standard. It's techno. You missed a door? I didn't. Oh, there is a door right here.
You're right. What kind of music do you hear at clubs? I don't know. What's this?
It's been a long time since we arrived in what some call Everhood.
So many years have passed that I've almost forgotten some of us were once humans.
So I thought I would write our history before time fades away. Time fades away our memories.
A long time ago, before we found the rift that would enable us to transport to this realm of
the immortals. When we were a society of millions and a small selection of us had the privilege to
belong to the almost at intestines, we had many debates on how to share this gift, this newfound
miracle. Should we open it for everyone or should only a few be allowed to visit such a place?
We decided it had been far too long that we had kept this gift to ourselves. In the end,
we determined we should allow everyone to meet the entities. The masses were elated. A great
majority decided to become immortals while only a few would remain as mortals, such as the old,
the sick, and unfortunate ones were the reasons of their own. You could experience the most
euphoric moments of your life then completely forgot they ever had happened over and over again.
I still have fond memories of using the earthquake machine during my dance-off battles with pink
mage. They were one of a kind and I truly miss them. Brown Mage. Okay, are we in the metaverse?
Go back, go to talk to Brown Mage. Can I get there from here? I don't think I can get all
the way back there. No, I know. I'm not listening to that one guy. This game's sick. This is a really
good game. I understand why everybody wanted me to finish it. It's very, very good. Very fun.
You need to do the Schrodinger's stream. What's Schrodinger's stream?
You're unbeatable after all. I assume now you feel entitled to have your arm.
I won't let you take it. That's why. You're going to have to take it for my cold,
dead hands. I will end you. Let's go. Final boss. Maybe. Watch it.
Easy. Get your tits out of the way, I can't see. You're blocking my view.
Through the fog. Why did I walk into that? You gotta keep the blood flowing. See what I mean?
Whoa. How do I dodge that? Oh. All right. Fight him. Shoot him. That's not it. I'm prepared.
Typical of you to dodge my attacks.
Why do you keep challenging Red when you know you always lose, Gold Pig? What do you mean?
Don't tell me you've forgotten. Seems you don't remember Red's other side, Blue.
Oh, always being a pawn in someone else's scheme, little gnome.
Gold has been using you all along to get his arm back. Wait, what? I, what?
Didn't know, or? Forgot. You scattle-brained twerp. I noticed you kept forgetting things.
It was just a matter of time before you turned completely useless.
That's why I took your legs. You don't need those.
My legs? You stole my legs? You stole Blue's legs? You let your greed control your actions again,
Gold Pig? Why would you even take Blue's legs? That's why they may be useful as toothpicks.
You give me my toothpicks back. Give me my legs. Give me back my legs.
You should return the legs. Blue is weak. They don't deserve to have anything.
Give back the legs, you hoarder. Fine. Fine. So I'm Red Mage, and that's Blue Mage,
and that's Green Mage, and that's Purple Mage. So we're all like, we all know each other.
We're all friends. Oh, I can finally walk again. I guess I don't need your help anymore.
Thanks for helping me. Now, where's Red's arm? I think you'd better spill the beans, Gold Pig.
These guys don't give up. Do what you want, right? Your precious little arm.
It is no use to try and hide it any longer. I keep it in the treasury. Go and get it and then buzz
off. It's gonna be a trap. They're gonna lock me in like a cell. I know it. There's a trap. It has
to be. Oh, look it. These are all our friends. We know these are all the friends we've made along
the way here. Remember the door? Remember the fish? Remember the goblin? Remember Dr. Robotnik?
Make a second save. Multiple saves. Hurry. Save. Save. Two saves. What? What? Why? Make a new save.
Why am I making a new save? Okay. Make a third save. I'm not doing two. I'm not. I'm doing two
saves. I'm not. I don't. No. Here's my arm. You want to pick up the arm. Leave you scram. Don't.
Are you sure? Yes. You picked up your arm.
What? It's not. This is bullshit. This is a fake end. Yeah, it's a fake ending. It's a fake ending.
I can smell it from a mile away. It's a fake ending. It seems as if the doll has finally
found its arm. You have proven yourself more than worthy to get your arm back.
Now that you have seen what remains of this world, the ones in this world are trapped here in this
realm. They have lived for many, many, many, many eons. Searching for a release for a purpose,
for a meaning. I just freaked out. People said their voice is bad. I must ask of you a huge
favor. Help free us from this eternal wandering. You must find extraordinary courage and determination
as this will be an immense challenge to end this world. We'll show you how to free souls with your
arm. Pair yourself. Human. Oh, this is a real boss. Oh, we got to lock in on this one. Listen
closely now. Reflect my attacks. Whoa. This is a whole new game. It's loud. So you got to get three
notes of the same color in a row. Shit. Oh, this makes it harder. This makes it really hard. You
just need two notes of the same color and now free souls. It's only two notes. Two then X to fire.
Oh shit. Okay. I thought I had to. All right. It'll be a challenging mission, but you do not stand
alone. You're the key, our champion, to free us from the shackles of immortality. Seek out the
spirits if you are in doubt. All right. Go. Am I about to go free these motherfuckers over here?
Interact or kill? What? You want to? Yeah. I want to save. What? Why would I kill the save point?
Great. Good luck. What if I, what if I kill this? What happens? I understand. Oh,
did I free them? Finally, you have your arm back. It's been such a long time. The mages have fled
for they know what is coming, but they don't understand why they must be killed. You must
help them by ending them. If you need help finding the remaining souls, we will be in our court.
Right now. So they're all running from me now. I'm going to head back to the cosmic hub. Wait,
I'm about to go on. I'm about to go kill everybody. I'm going to. Oh no. Don't kill the hub save point
for obvious reasons. All right. Well, let me go to like the circus, the carnival.
So wait a minute. What do you want to do? What's the point of learning new skills?
What do I, what do I do? Hey, what's with the attitude? What are you doing?
I thought we were going to have a dance off. I thought we were going to have a dance off.
I thought we were going to have like a dance off party thing. I don't want to kill everybody.
I thought it was like, oh, I can like grab the different colors and should fire it back.
What? I can just kill people? Hi there red. The cart race is closed. You, I have to?
I didn't want to kill that person. It's releasing them. You're freeing them.
I'm to stamp home. Goodbye. This feels bad. They're immortal. There's 28 more people. Wait,
I have to wipe everybody out? You can go pacifist if you want. I mean, what do I do?
Let's see what kind of wood you're made of. Oh shit. I can't just kill this guy. This guy's
fighting back. Of course. Right. When I changed from yellow to gray, can I just tap, tap, tap,
I'm going to try it. Watch this. Ready? You ready? Ready? Nope. That didn't work. I didn't do
anything. Wait, wait, I didn't kill them. Oh, not so easy to kill a vampire. Is it? Oh, I got it.
All right. I got you. It's, you got to do it before the song ends. This is awesome.
This game just got like five times cooler. Right now. It just did. Shit, you idiot. You idiot.
Can I block these? Oh, I can. I can. I didn't think I could block those.
You fucking idiot. Stop blocking. Get out of here. Oh, you hit hard for looking like a pair of sticks.
Before I go, let the world know. The world know what? I, Disco Jimmy, live to the fullest.
Time for me to perform my final disappearing act. Hey, no need to be so hostile. Let me just
go get a thing. What's he doing? Sucker. Wait, what? Is he hiding?
You don't have to kill them all. There are two routes you locked yourself after murdering the
save point. Oh shit. If you want to see this ending, you can keep going, but if you want to
change your mind, you can slow the save before you kill the lamp post. Shit. Well, we're already
doing this one. I'll do this one. I figured it was probably I didn't have to kill everybody,
but I mean, I want to see what happens. How do I get out of here? Oh wait, there's a sign in there.
Oh, there is a sign. You're right. I have to kill everything? Sign? Use magic eight ball. It will
help in your mission. What is your obsession with me? You are so cool for vandalizing a sign.
True rebel. 26. But what about the robot? The robot hid behind the booth.
I didn't I didn't kill the robot. Let me see. There's actually four endings. That's actually
that's cool. You stand still. The game will give you a guide and who you have to kill. Really?
Oh, it's a lie. Okay. Do the right thing and save them. Wait, that means I have to kill all the
mushrooms. I like the I like the mushrooms, but I'm not killing them. I'm freeing them from the
immortal world where we're all stuck here. Right? Is that just the narrative I'm putting in my head?
I kill this thing? Look, everyone's having a good time here. What about you? Can I? I'm the guardian
of the mushroom forest. Oh, yes. Here it is. The reaper of souls. I've been looking forward
to speaking with you. Have you come for my guidance or for my soul? Let me I'll get you.
You can say some words first. Put it simply. Life is suffering. The living fear death until
it's too late. That is how the mind works. But when life does not have a time span,
becoming immortal is more of a curse than a blessing. It is torture for the soul. There's
nothing to do with all of this time. After thousands of years, you become docile. You
become mute. There are so few things you can do in a physical form. It's almost like a cruel joke.
You must take great strides to realize what must be done. Do you understand what I'm what I'm saying?
Do you understand that I want to die? Um, yes. Good. Good. Do you have what it takes to finish
the quest? I don't know. Like maybe. No. Yes. The weight of the world is in your shoulders.
No one should be forced to bear such a burden. You're the only one that can end this torture.
Now, shall we battle? Yeah. Sure. Yes. Just like that.
That was tricky. Well done. You performed admirably. A true liberator, finally.
You will be received as a true champion when you reach the end. Farewell.
Everybody around here see that? They kind of look, they look kind of sad. Are you all right?
Wow. You found all of us. Oh, what a twist that you would be the one who had such power.
Life sure is full of surprises. So long for now. I don't want to get rid of them all. I like these
guys. I like this guy. I like this guy the most. I don't want to get rid of them. You found us. Yay.
It comes a time for us all. Oh, you have to free them. They're suffering. Death is temporary.
Life is eternal. There's nothing to be afraid of. Oh, God. He looks concerned. I don't think he...
Nothing to be afraid of. Don't miss the point of the whole thing. This is a musical thing.
We are supposed to dance, sing, and enjoy ourselves.
Hi. Hey, little guy. What are you doing? Nothing. Just coming over to say hi to you and check on
you and make sure you're doing okay. I'm doing good. I'm doing very good. Are you struggling?
Are you sure of your actions? You can't kill me in a way that matters. What the fuck, man?
It's not my... I'm freeing them from the immortal torture. Wait, the little worm guy. Get her alive.
For me, it doesn't matter. I can let you kill me without a battle. Or would you prefer a fight?
Do you want to battle? Yeah, I do. You're slaughtering everybody one by one.
Well, oh yeah. This guy does the weird shit. Shit. Hello, human. Oh, he won. No, he didn't.
I have green right now. Why is Dreamer so cracked at this game? I don't know. I just...
I told you. Give me four buttons and I win. That was fun. I admit defeat.
See you on the other side. Are you still on hard mode? Yeah. I haven't changed the difficulty or
anything. I have no idea what extreme would be like. All right. Is anybody still here?
Or did I free everybody? Is this somebody? The tree has a face. It said,
I think your brain might be just wired to be funky. The people in the lab. Oh, that's right.
Where was the lab? Isn't it up here? If you crank it up to extreme, it should be fine. It's not that
much harder, to be honest. Maybe... Once I learned you got your arm back, I reconfigured this entire
lab into an impenetrable death fortress. You're never going to catch me, bloodthirsty marauder.
Run down. Make sure to set all traps to full power. All right, you doofus. Oh,
just got to do it to the beat. That's it. No. Did you just turn it down? You fucked up. All right.
I'll turn it back up. It looked like it was too loud. I'm sorry. I'll turn it back up.
I'm fine. I need to go this way. I need to go over. I need to double. Where is it?
Yes! I'm fine. Oh, my God. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have to turn it down in my head. Oh, I have to do the whole thing again. God damn it.
God, I hate this. I just want to skip it. I hate trap stuff. I have no patience. This is getting
murdered. I don't... I don't... I can't do it. I'm going right down the middle. One, two, three, go.
I hate it. Okay, so I have to wait till it processes each other. One, two, go. My God,
don't even do this to me. All right, so I have to start at the bottom. Just walk with it. Just walk
with it. Just walk with it. All right, I made it. Oh, shit. What does this mean? Can I touch these?
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. I'm fine. I can't believe it. How is it possible that you
got through all those traps? I command you to attack that red marauder. All right, we're ready
to kill. Oh, come on. God damn it. Come on. More volume. But that's a soul, right? 25. All right,
don't move. I'm just going to save the game. Go to extreme difficulty. I don't think I can... Can I?
Makes winning feel good, you will die. Less health regeneration for people who like hard challenges.
You think I can handle it? I'll try it this once. If I can't do it... If I'm not confident on this
doing it once or twice, then yeah, I'll try. I'll try extreme. Seems my luck has run out.
I don't blame you. I did try to eliminate you. There's no point in hiding myself from me now.
This inevitable death is upon me. I didn't even get a chance. He had two souls in his head.
You're orange. Started out as a minor inconvenience as it mostly does. For years and years and years
of endless enjoyment, our physical bodies were simply not keeping up with what our minds desired.
Not a sense of sickness or pain, none of that existed. But through sheer exhaustion,
our bodies from our primordial worlds would not adapt into the freedom of our new home.
This, of course, wasn't the case for every inhabitant. But as a former human, it certainly
was for me. You don't have to do this to yourself. Don't let chat peer pressure you. No, I know.
If it's too much for me, I'm just going right back to hard. And I will not care at all.
Sometimes games go from hard to extreme, and extreme is like impossible. So don't worry.
We usually found quick solutions such as potions, surgery, and artificial limbs.
But our demands grew more ambitious and we continued to evolve ourselves,
all in the name of making our existence as joyful as possible.
Our ways became twisted. We felt the urge to play pranks on each other,
throwing both friends and foes into pits of eternal hell, over and over just to experience
the days and months. In this insane indulgence, this cruel and twisted nightmare,
inhabitants started to disappear altogether. I suspect they found a way to end their immortality.
Brown mage. We're just like pranking each other by killing each other,
just to like know that time passed. That's kind of fucked up.
Oh, this person. What do you want to do? They're everywhere. What do they want? What do they want?
Leave me be. I don't want to. Make it stop. Make it stop. Make it stop. Make it stop.
What are you doing? What are you doing? I'm just, I'm freeing you. That was upsetting.
Back to the entrance. Yes. Build a save. I don't think the save points have a soul.
They don't. Okay. I think that's everybody in the forest. I believe that's everybody.
Interact with the ball. You shake the magic eight ball. It says,
Zig is relaxing in the dance club in a bad mood. Oh, it tells you where to go. Okay.
How the hell do I get out of here? How do I get out of here? I'm a save point and I have a soul.
How do I get out of here? Wait, what's that? You can open that door? Eventually?
Oh, get him out. Get me out of here. Use the door to the right of the lab.
Oh, I went the complete wrong way then. The spirits.
Why the fuck do you eat cauliflower with mustard? Why do you think I do that? Who told you I did
that? I don't, I don't, is there something wrong with that? They never were truly alive.
The mushrooms were never alive. There was the type of guy to watch
anime intro openings and complain that that's not what's put on the radio.
This door is locked. What's going on in here? And what's going on in here?
It's a vicious insult. I mean, is it an insult if it's not even real?
Okay. That's like you saying to me. Oh, German man. Like, God, imagine being the guy that likes
putting fucking call mustard on cauliflower. I've never eaten that before in my life. Right?
Like that doesn't insult me. I've never done that before. I don't like want anime intros on
the radio. Like, I mean, if that were on there, that'd be cool. Fine. But I don't like care.
All E flower. How do you say it? Good music, good people. I lived good.
Goodbye. What is that? What's this? Is it a wanted poster? Oh, it's a robot. Get him.
There's no escape. I always wondered if I was truly conscious. I might finally get some answers.
You want to fight, huh? You act tough, but I've never seen you throw any punches.
This time, I'll teach you a lesson. Yeah, turns out, turns out you didn't have a soul.
No soul in the robot. I know that's sad. Oh, this seems so easy by comparison to everything else.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do. This song was awesome. Let's go. Phase two. Shit. Shit.
Fuck you. I expert. I can do it. I can do it. I can do it. It's easy. I can do it. Come on,
Gwen. Come on, Gwen. All right. You idiot. Can I touch it? I can. Oh, how are you so fast? Last
time. You got lucky. This time. Oh, you won't be so lucky. Oh, shit. I almost lost. I don't feel so
good. Expert makes them have more health and you don't have as much time. I mean, we'll do it for
a little while. Getting kind of creepy. Someone did the math on this game and the people living
in it. They've been living for 12 million years. God. Oh, what about this guy? Worked too much.
Should have done other things. Damn. I've had a great time. I've had a great time. I had a great
time. I had a great time. Does the ATM have a soul? That would be kind of funny. Do not harm the
automatic terror machine or it will harm you. Oh, shit. It does. I thought I could be sneaky. Oh,
I can't grab those. Come on, Gwen. Shoot it. Do not damage evil property. Ice over. It did have a
soul. I guess it did. Rabbit. Way to go. Way to go. No. Oh, what's going on? What the fuck?
What is it? I can't catch these. Speaking a different language? Yikes. Yikes. That's fucking
crazy. All right. Retry, right? I think I can do it. I can do it backwards. The text is backwards.
Last checkpoint. Try again. This one was wacky. I got to focus real hard here. Holy shit in my
fucking diaper. I was told to not say die forever again and I just did. I have more than one person.
I know. I got to roll over those. Oh, fuck you. I had it. Wow. It's impossible. No, it's not.
Damn it. It's so hard. I want to beat around the experts so bad. Same exact spot as last time.
Shit. Difficulty. I know. I know. All right. You need to jump and press the direction.
I know. I know. I know. There's a lot going on on the screen. There's all this candy shit
all over the screen. What's it doing? Oh, where are we going? Don't die. Don't go backwards on
me here, please. It's so hard to tell where the fucking thing is. Was I supposed to touch that?
I jumped over it. Shit. What are you doing? Oh, no. Do you have what it takes? Human? I don't know.
Oh, damn. Damn. That was close. Not required. You all right? You seem distressed. Hey, buddy.
Do you want to save? Yeah. I ran out of time. Like 15% health? No. No, what? You idiot. What happened?
That was your backup. My brother's two, three... All right. Start timing out the people.
Writing about how fat their family members are. Okay. I don't care. What did I just do? I saved
over the backup? We have been. Okay. All right. All right. All right. What happened? Did I blow it?
You saved over the one before you went into kill mode. Oh, that's all right. It's okay.
It's all right. That was wild. I thought I had it. I guess once the kind of neon colored ones,
once I can collect, once those started to come down, I didn't know I was supposed to kill.
Oh, I have to kill you. I'm glad I still remember you. Would I please tell you something? Sure.
You haven't said a word during the time we've known each other. You helped me even when I had
done something bad to you. Without you, I never would have made it to the Gold Pig's temple.
You helped Flan in that game. Even though they attacked you later, you helped Green Mage get
their eye back. Maybe it was all just to get your arm back. I don't know. It feels like there's
something bigger going on here. Maybe like an important cause? Do I have something to tell you?
Green Mage blocked the door to Midnight Town. There's a hidden entrance.
Green Mage told me to keep it hidden. I think Green Mage gave me this job because I would forget
where it was. It would remain hidden for everyone. I trust what you are doing, Red. I think I'm ready
now. Bye, old friend. May we see each other again. In the second eternity where we cannot die.
Immortality in heaven. Where the whole thing starts over again. I won't allow you to go any further.
Last time you had your arm, so many perished. If anyone else dies,
I just cannot stand by and watch it happen again. I'm gonna sneeze during this and I can't mute
because I'm playing. I'm ready. Oh, come on. Bullshit. Give me a break. I tapped it. What the
fuck are you talking about, bro? I was hitting X on the right spot. This is making me really mad.
Get the fuck out of here. God, that was hard. That was crazy. That's a severe
concentration. Whew. It wasn't enough. I can't believe Holly beat that for you. Shh, don't say
that. No, I'm gaming right now. All right, you can go. You can go in the other room. Thank you so
much. Yeah, thank you. I'll see you. All right, who's left in here? Good job, Holly. Come on.
Hey, what are you doing? You do have a pacifist save. It's the second file. Oh, that's right. It's
a little bit before the end of the game though, right? What about this guy? You're asking for
trouble? No trouble making in my shop. Actually get to go against the shopkeeper. Good luck on
this one. Oh man. All right, is this when we turn it down to hard? Find out. Oh, you can't grab those.
You can't grab those either. All right, I get it. I was trying to grab all those in the beginning.
You can only grab the orange ones. Oh, this is crazy. Okay, I'll give it a few more tries.
You got to just sneak in there and sneak out real quick. Come on. What? No. Oh my goodness.
Oh, yeah. All right. Okay. All right. All right. All right. We're going back to hard. That's insane.
Let's go. That's wild. Especially when your left is right, right is left. I don't know about that
one. Oh, did I training wheels myself though? We'll see. No, it's still pretty bad.
Shit. All right. Now we reset. Reset. Oh my God. You idiot. Oh man.
Give me something to throw at him. Shit. Going to be close.
That was probably the best song of the whole game. That was awesome.
Such a shame. Getting down to the final like 10. Getting a little weird. Oh, the chest. Can I still
open this? I don't want to kill the chest. I want to open it. Didn't say the brown mage had it.
This is getting pukey. All right. Here's the brown mage. What do you want? Kill. Who's making
that ruckus? Scram and get out of here. Bring me batteries. Oh, yes. Finally, I can power my
toilet. All right. I promise you. Here's a lava lamp. Oh, no. I seem to have lost it. Bring me
a trampoline. Then I can give you something. That's super promise. All right. Fuck this guy.
Forgive me for my thoughtless requests. I shall reward you greatly for your endeavors.
I will need you to open the secret entrance to my keep. Okay. Please be very discreet. The secret
entrance is located south of the pool of water. You'll find a pile of rocks and a door. I've
unlocked it for you. Okay. So I have to go down there? All right. Wait. What about down here?
Open it with my arm. Yes. You want to go in? Yes. What's all these tally marks? Oh, it's you. Hey
there. I'm a bit surprised that you broke into my cellar. I guess I shouldn't be. Now what is it
that you want? Go down first. Don't kill. Go down first. Did I go down first? Am I going to soft
lock myself out of something? Yes. Yeah. Go down first. Okay. Just wait that way. Just wait that
way. Okay. So go down from here. Okay. What the hell is this? Sign says turn on colorblind mode
in settings. I think I prefer it on, especially in battles. Really? I have to turn it on? You
don't have to. Oh, I thought it was required for this exact mission or something. Wait, this is him.
Dear Brown Mage, you never want to do anything lately. Just sit in your little hole and eat and
eat and eat. There isn't really anyone on my level and I'm bored out of my mind. I might give the
mushrooms a visit and yes, I'll be taking the ruby with me. Marine Mage, welcome friend. I sadly have
some bad news. I seem to have miscalculated my hypothesis. I need a very rare type of stick.
Unless you have a special type of stick. Wait, you do? Give it to me and I'll finish it.
Finally, I give you this as you have given me so much. The golden key. This key will unlock
secrets. I got a golden key. Okay. Is this person alive? A well-maintained porcelain toilet. Looks
expensive. Why are you acting so hostile? What do you want? Wait. Oh no. I've been tricked. It's
you. Even after everything I've done for you. We don't fight him. He just, oh shit, we didn't
even get a, you don't go, you don't get a cool song apparently. Oh shit, okay. All right, let's
go to the chest and then I want to open that other door too with the gold lock. Save the game first.
Save, save, save, save, save, save. All right, chest. What do you want to do? Interact. You want
to use the key? Yes. Something powerful seems to resonate with the golden key. Are you sure? Yes.
All right. Who is it? Dr. Manhattan? Who's in here?
Holy shit. That gets a little, okay, that got a little crazy.
Why is my pee green? I don't know. Go to a doctor. That's a question for a doctor, not me.
What?
I can grab those? I thought I couldn't. I thought I couldn't grab those. I thought I
couldn't grab those. I thought I couldn't. I can't. I can grab those. I thought I couldn't.
Oh, I didn't know I could grab those. I thought I could jump over them.
I can grab them. Shit. I'm an idiot. Oh man. All right. Gamer Fatigue is sitting in. Gamer Fatigue
is sitting in I think. Let me drink some water. Gamer Fatigue is sitting in. I'm ready. This is
one of the hardest battles in the game. I'll get it. It might take me a few more. I got to get
through the Gamer Fatigue and I'll be fine. We're good. God damn it. Motherfucker, that lasts so
long. His brain's overheating. Oh, it is. Oh, I was close. 30%. You ever shower with your socks on?
No, I don't. All right. All right. It's all about you got to move to the edges of the screen.
You can't panic. My nose is burning. Okay. Oh my God. All right. I'm out. I'm out. No, I'm out.
I can't leave. I'm stuck here forever. I think I'm stuck here forever. We'll forgive you if
you lower the difficulty. I think I can do it. I think my brain's starting to get a little
fried from the game though, to be honest. I think we're frying out.
Fuck you. Same exact spot as last time. Same spot as last time. I'm so close though. I can
feel it. I got him to 25% health. I just got to get through that section and I got this shit.
That section is the worst part. If he goes back to the first verse again, oh, it's over. I'll get
him. I'll get him. Take a break. Take a break. All right. We'll take a break for a second. Deep
breathing. Let's go. All right. So when he does the second part of that chorus, everything comes
down. There's two blips where you're safe and you have to collect them both and fire it back.
Everything else is full. Shower with some socks on and eat cauliflower and mustard.
You can just dodge it and do the fight later. Yeah, but I want to kill this motherfucker.
Okay. I'm ready. One more attempt and I'm going to go pee.
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Quiet. Everybody quiet. I'm in the same spot.
It happened the exact same spot again. Okay. We're not upset about anything. We're just
exclaiming the fact that I need to probably move to the left side. I'll move to the left side
instead of the right side. It's mirroring the pattern. I know. I know. Tasmanian devil.
Hold on. Did that actually sound like the Tasmanian devil? Oh my God. Let me see. Let me hear it.
It's okay to be upset. I know. Oh man. It's the same spot. Oh shit. It keeps happening in
the same location. I got to move to the left side. You're going to piss yourself? Oh, I'm good. I'm
good. You can hear it. Okay. You want to know what happened? So right here, I can pinpoint
you the exact place where my brain decided to try to switch this from anger to like,
this is a funny voice, right? Right there. Because then I go like, I'm trying to look at this is a
funny voice now. Like that was me. That was my brain desperately trying to make you guys
think that that was like, oh, a funny voice I was doing. I realized that I was screaming and I had
to like in the middle of the scream, turn it into like a little funny. Oh, what a joke he's making.
Larry David. I'm not fucking going anywhere. This is the one right here. Halfway through that,
I was like, oh, I'm a comedian. Shut up and get it right. This is it. This is the one. This is
actually the one right now. I'm not fucking, I'm not going to get hit once. My face is so itchy.
My face is so itchy. It's ruining everything. Oh God damn it. Why does it itch? Why? Whatever.
I'm fucked. Yeah, I didn't beat him. Oh man. I'm finally free from the shackles. I hope to see you
soon. Goodbye to this wretched world. No. No. No. I failed the DPS check. Reload the save.
You can find them again. Oh, I can fight them again. Okay. Shit, that was crazy. What do I
want to do? What is it? Gems of power and soul bound gems, sometimes known as the fruits of the
gods. Okay. There are different gems in this world. Many are already known, but it's likely
there are still just as many waiting to be discovered. It truly harnessed the gem's full
potential. It just needs to fuse the gem with their body and soul. These are known as soul
binding gems. One should be cautious of soul binding gems as they have a tendency to change
the very nature of the ego once they are truly connected. In essence, it's very unnatural.
The melding process is known to be quite painful. For a gem to become a soul bound gem,
it needs to replace at least one of the five senses. I hate that. I keep thinking about how
much I hated how I said that. One or more need to be sacrificed so the gem can be truly activated.
Especially considering it was like it happened in a sheshma. I hate it. I hate that sound. Oh,
right. Hey, you think you're tough coming in here and making a ruckus? I'll show you ruckus.
Oh, all right. We'll take a break after this. We'll go pee and I'll come back.
Crash can time. Stop farming 2022 awards. I'm not. I promise. All right. Relax, dude. Come on.
Not you, me. This is night and day compared to the last one. Good block. Holy shit. What are you
doing, man? I'm just completely jinxed at you. Not even my shell can protect me from you. We've
had a long time for this. 13. All right. I'll go pee. I will see you guys in two minutes. I'm
going to go pee. I'm going to grab a little bit more water. I'm going to shake around a little bit
my brain in the right place to do the rest of the game, which I'm assuming that we probably
are getting near the end here. I'll be right back. Okay, guys, somebody wants to say something.
They're a little groggy. They've been sleeping for a while. They don't want to be on camera.
Are you doing, Cheeto? Okay. Okay. Yeah, you're a little groggy. Tired. Do you want some coffee
or something? You've been asleep for like two years. Do you want anything? Okay. That's a very,
that's pretty big Burger King order. You want to, you want to shake? Okay. Chocolate? Okay.
You want me to put you back on the shelf? Okay. Back on the shelf. He's not ready for the camera
yet. He's a little tired. He was asleep for a couple of years. He doesn't want to be on camera.
The large Burger King order, McDonald's, whatever he wants. He's just waking up. It takes like a few
days to wake up. All right, let's go. We're going to do a Burger King Cheeto stream. All right,
who do we got left? I already did this stuff. What's Cheeto's order? So Cheeto really only
eats a very, very little. So Cheeto likes nuggets. So what ends up happening is he eats one nugget,
like the half of one nugget takes him like 45 minutes or so. He kind of nibbles at it. And
then I just eat the rest. Blue slime is working hard in the cursed castle. I opened this. Ow!
Thank you for removing the lock. Green mage locked me up to keep you away, I guess. Oh wait,
wasn't green mage like down in the thing? Yeah, hold on. Let's go get green mage. He was down.
Where was he? All right, let's go get him. Hi, green mage. Time to go. From this point forward,
I need 12 more souls. How much time do I think I got left in the game? This is where it ends.
After spending an eternity in mushroom forest. How anticlimactic. Maybe like an hour or two? All
right, cool. An absolute max of maybe two hours. Okay. All right, green. Let's go. I don't know,
I can catch these. Wait, stop. You're serious? Hear me out. If you want a true clash of life
and death, you'll have to spice it up. Come into my playroom. I wouldn't go in there if I were you.
That corridor is endless. Well, technically it isn't endless. There's an end. It'll just take
forever to get there. I know because I made the corridor. Hi, buddy. Main reason why I gave the
ruby to you is to have them separated. Together they are too powerful in wrong hands. The emerald
is locked inside an indestructible chest stored with an acquaintance of mine. For your own sake,
I won't tell you where the aquamarine is located. Take care of yourself, green. It takes four hours
to go down the hallway and there's shit in the hallway so you can't just tape a button down.
Are you kidding me? Welcome to my real playroom. Only a special few know of its existence.
Let us not delay the inevitable. Or are you too scared you might lose?
All right, it's time for you to die, motherfucker. Let's go.
Somebody said Forsen watched Shrek during the walk. Wait, are you serious? Hold on. Really?
That's fucking hilarious. Oh, that's amazing. I was there. I haven't felt this alive in a long
time. Let's go. It'll be the greatest duel ever. I can't pick those up. I'm trying to grab those
and it's too much. All right, sit up. I'm too busy trying to grab those ones and I just avoid them.
What am I doing wrong here? This is not that hard. I'm just overthinking it now.
The last insane electricity man. I need to put my brain back where it was.
Oh, fuck off. Can I catch those? What the fuck? Oh my god, you're killing me here.
I can't grab anything. Oh, shit. No, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Oh my god, you're gonna be kidding me. Pity loop? That's fine.
I got pity looped. It's all right. I'll take it. We'll do the two. I know 11. What characters
were even left? I'm not doing the hallway. I'm not doing that. No, that song was awesome.
That was a really good one. A blue slime in the castle. It's only four hours. That's four hours
too long. I think everybody's dead here. So this way is locked. Favorite type of cheese,
probably Swiss or some kind of cheddar probably. Where should I go? These people are in here,
right? The ghost people? What do you want? I bet what you heard from the forest spirit was not
what you wanted to hear. What are you doing? Oh, again? Oh, whoa. What? The blue slime is
working hard in the cursed castle. My work is not done. Still, I've had my revenge. You must kill
everyone from this immortal world before we allow you to continue. You have 11 souls to liberate.
Cannot kill what is already dead. You must kill everyone before we can close this realm.
I can give you something that will help you. Help you find the souls. Some might say the extra help
isn't necessary, but I say take all the help you can get. Do you want it? Yeah. This lantern,
it will help you find souls. I want to go away, but I can't seem to let go. What do you want?
Wait, what? The beast within the cursed castle protects a spirit.
Get the lantern. If you stand still, a guide will show you where the souls are. Oh,
this is what they were talking about. That person said that. Ah, all right. Cool. No help. No help.
No help. Where are you at? How does that make any sense? Why are you telling me to do that?
Nice GPS. Come here. Why does it run away every time? Annoying. Yeah, there's the night guide.
There's people in the castle too. God, our differences. Both of us had our own goals.
Me trying to stop you, you walking all over me and not showing any sympathy.
Hurt my feelings. It hurt my finances. Right now, my friend, I understand that you're on some kind
of killing spree. You can't just let that slide, you know. All right, dude, let's go.
Match the colors. Huh? Please, can you stop? If I bother. The guy looks like German when he's
streaming. That's true. You sure are a tough guy, you little red twerp. There are 10 souls remaining.
We're gonna find them all. He's as naked as ever. Oh, we have to ride this back.
Probably shoot. What the fuck? There's somebody here. I didn't know that was okay.
There's somebody actually on the train. I can't really read what they're saying.
This is gonna hurt. This is gonna hurt. Yeah. Nine. I guess my days end here. Nobody else to
move the car. It's the only character with a damage animation. There's no music now. This
is weird. Who's next? I had a nap midstream. Why is he killing everyone? You're gonna have to go
back and see what happened. Oh no, not these. You ain't going nowhere. Against both at the same time.
Let's get him, Job. They both have such painful sound effects for noises.
He's gonna be screaming the whole time. It's gonna be so annoying. Oh, they have different health bars.
Oh god, that's too many sounds. Oh, the beat. I can't focus. I'm almost dead. It's too powerful.
Now what? Impossible. So he said, I don't get this combat system at all, but it looks fun.
So the first half of the game, you do not have a combat. You don't have a laser beam that I'm
shooting out. You essentially, well, I'll let you figure it out. It's a fun game. It's good.
Found a loophole in our contract. Kevin McCloud. A two? Yeah, down to seven. Oh no, I don't want
to kill these guys. I like these guys. Hey there, pal. Oh, you seem to have found your arm. Great
news. I like these guys. Hey buddy, great to see you again. You can't come here and cause a ruckus.
I don't like the vibes you're putting out, man. What does she teach you a thing or two about bad
behavior? You think that qualifies us to help, Buck? You got it right, Plant. We won't go easy
on you, kid. I really like these guys. I don't want to kill these guys. That was cool. He's cool.
Oh shit. Oh, he's pissed. What happened? What the fuck? I should have killed the turtle. I should
have killed the turtle first. It's Ornstein and Smog. Oi, oi. That is phase three. I got pity
looped again. No, I didn't. You horrible creature. I hate you. Down to five, right? Okay. Everyone,
they certified me. I feel bad. Okay. Somebody in here? They are in here. Oh, this shit. I remember
this. I got to go down. Just kidding. Up. I remember it. Do you want to stop killing? I don't know. I
feel like I'm doing the mission. I'm on the mission. No. I admire your determination, but I can't stay
in the choices you're making. I can't be part of this murderous crusade. One of your quests
must end now. Faster hand? All right. This game is crazy. Ooh, I like it. Okay, let's go. Damn.
Oh, my colors are blending together in my brain. Shit, I don't think I beat him. Jesus. I barely
got the loop. Come on. I want to see the heart rate. You should have seen the heart rate on
the magical lightning guy. Boy, the hand didn't have a soul, though. Oh, my God. What are you
doing? It was probably really high. All right. We'll lock doors. This is the beginning of the game.
I am free again, thanks to you. The mage has locked me up. Purple mage is in the room with
the mirror of truth. We trust in you to finish the deed. Who's in here? Wait, what? Oh, right.
What is that? Going to the theater? You killed the cursor. That's your hand now. Oh, okay. Oh,
the maze. The spider. That's right. Okay. Wait, why does it want me to go up here? Where was that
spider? Hold on. Let me go to the theater. Somebody in the theater. Who's in the theater?
It's a 50% chance every time you walk in. Where is he? Either you were lying to me or these are
some really stupid ridiculous odds. All right. Where's the spider, though? I want to do spider
first. There's still several people in the castle. Castle near the slime brothers. I'll just go back
down. You're insanely stupid sometimes. How? Because I didn't know that it was, I don't have
a Wikipedia open about how to trigger the event to happen. Oh, you. You're alive. You find pink
spirits and old saying says not to trust them. It'd be quite mischievous. I guess this is as
good as any place to die. It's cold and comfortable. What would you like to die for? What does that
sound? What if I can't? Do I play by myself? Sounds killing me. What is this? I don't.
Okay. Congratulations. There was a type of person to say please to his Alexa. Sure. Find the spider.
I'm here. Where are you? Where are you? Let's go. Favorite album of all time. Probably Demon
Days or Plastic Beach. I like them both equally. No, wait. Oh, right. I have to avoid those.
Right. That's going to be a pain in the ass. Okay. Avoid everything. Just avoid everything.
You stupid idiot. I can't believe it. I can't believe it. I can't believe it. I couldn't press
it before and now you can't avoid it. No. Well, I. All right. No, no, no. Start over. Start over.
Let's just do this right. Shit. Dude, I'm slowing down hard. I feel like I've been looking at a
kaleidoscope for five straight hours. Oh my God. Sensory. Oh, stop. I'm turning it down. Oh my
goodness, dude. Come on. That was unbearable. Okay. Peace returning to the immortal realm.
Follow the pink. I was thinking about it. Up. We're here. Up. Whoa. What is this? Two, two, two.
Two, two, two. What do you want? Hello, red. Keep following the candy canes and you will arrive
at bubble gum land. You sure pack a punch. Okay. It's a long way. It's going to be a pain in the
ass to go back. Vampire guy said don't trust pink spirits. I'm not trusting them. I'm about
to kill them. Come here. Trust them. I'm here to murder them. How long is this? What the fuck?
Am I going to have to put on Shrek while I do this? Something's not right. I don't know what
it is. Something's not right. Something's not right. Oh, please. You just have to walk backwards.
Welcome to bubble gum land. Relax and rest. If I do a job badly, then you can do it well.
Is there a save point anywhere? Here is good to be a bubble gum entity. Welcome to bubble gum land.
The quest is so big. Big bubble gum spirit. Hello, red. By now you should have come across
the powers you wield. Only you can erase the inhabitants of this realm. The incredible power
which only you possess. Some life is supposed to extend into centuries while others are shorter.
If one is in a loop where they cannot die and yet they fear death, that is not a pleasant way to
live. That's why you, as the human, have a gift. You get to experience the world within all its
dualities. Unfairness and chaos. An expiration date. But someday this will all end. It is truly
the most bittersweet feature of your existence. I give you only my words of advice. If you're
doing this for a cause, a cause that is good, do what you think is right. If you do not agree,
then who is to stop a god of death? Much has been said. We must go on.
You didn't have a soul? All right, well, what's your deal? Oh, you found my backup secret hideout.
Now that you found me, what are you going to do? Are you going to finish me off because I
took your arm? Or are you going to stroll out where you came from? You are here to erase my
existence. You've destroyed my empire. You've ruined my reputation. You've forced me to flee
for my life. Your thirst to kill does not end only because I took your arm. You disgust me.
It's my life you want. I won't give it away easily. I will make you walk through hell.
Sure you will. Bubblegum hell. All right, let's go. Dude, it's easy. Just settle down.
You're going to let this shitty stuff hit you? Why do we keep seeing that thing? Someone's
vaping in your room, dude. You put on quite a show, you annoying wooden doll. You have bested me. I
wish thousands and millions of years of torment upon you. Hey, dude, you hit my car yesterday,
dickwad. Are you going to pay? You drove off and I'm going to go bankrupt. You hit my car.
There's two left. I'm assuming that's including me, right? It kind of has to be. Purple mage and me
are the last two people, right? Purple mage is waiting in the mirror of truth, praying.
And the theater only responds when you go back to the hub. Does that guy count? He's optional,
okay. Because I'll be honest with you, I don't know if my brain can handle fighting that guy again.
I could try maybe once or twice. How do I get out of here? Let's peep the horror. I don't have the
horror. All right, let's go up to the mirror, see what he has to say. I'm going to get a big
reveal, I guarantee it, right? Want my GameCube controller back? I don't have your GameCube
controller, man. All right, this is it. One of the final people to grab here. For many years,
I have been told that this mirror tells you the truth. I spent many nights thinking on this.
If you have any decency left, I urge you to leave, to stop this act and leave. You're not a killer.
Refund this game, if you can. Just leave us alone. Are we getting existential here?
You've come here to kill me. Maybe this was meant to be. Although, I won't give up my life easily.
Well, they say that because they know you're already five to six hours into the game,
you can't refund it. They don't put that shit an hour and 45 minutes into the game.
They put it six hours into the game. Oh, stop hitting me. It's all right, start it over again.
Sloppy. He's healing. Okay, stop being so sloppy. He's healing. This is one more.
This is how it ends. You fought well, I never stood a chance. The final gem. Go to the court
of the lost spirits. Back to those guys. All right, it's going to be me. It's definitely
going to be me. It's going to be me. I'm going to punch myself in the face and I'm going to end up
dying. I'm going to wake up somewhere in another world or something. Let me save it.
All right, so it's saved. Fight the light guy first. I don't think I have it in me.
Kill the lamp. Did I? Just do the light guy on easy mode. That's not a bad idea. I'll try that.
I'll turn it down just to see what happens when you win. Let's put it on normal or something.
Yeah, you can do it on normal. Okay, that's lame. Well, I want to see what happens. All right,
50% chance. All right, there it is. All right, this world is a shell. It gives me no pleasure
to witness this twisted experiment. All right, let's go for it. Let me just get the win here.
I'm not an expert. I just want to see the end. I'll put it back.
I can already read the chat messages that say lost on normal, so I can't lose.
All right, relax. Oh, fuck. I did it. That's heavy. Finally, a worthy warrior. Use it well.
That was pretty cool. What about the door in the forest? Is this my only opportunity to see that?
No one's left here. Okay. All right, let me save it here. I'm going to go look at it. That's true.
You can do it after the game, but that's in a while. Okay. Where? Do the right thing.
You're probably going to want to put this on normal again. Well, we'll find out.
That door was here somewhere. This one's okay. All right. What was that door over here? Where is it?
Do you like cucumbers? Yeah. Yeah. He's doing end of the screen voice. I'm kind of tired,
I'll be honest. My brain is... I feel like I've watched six movies. I'm so close here. This is
the final act of the game. I'm not going to stop now. Where is it? I feel like it was right here
somewhere. Oh, it's the thing. Is that professor's junk pile thing? Hello. Hello. Save. Down here.
The ending takes a while. You should probably just do it. How does it take a long time?
A jump rope holds itself up. You accept the challenge. Sure. All right. I'm going to give
this one my all here. I got enough time to do the ending. Attack yet. Whoa. Holy smokes.
I guess you don't kill this thing. Do you want to unlock the door with your arm? Sure.
Is that... All right. I got to just grab this. My head hurts. I got the aqua marine. All right.
Get me out. Get me out of here. Hey, my grandma said you're cute. All right. Well, just put me on
speaker. Put me on speaker. I'm going to assume that I'm on speaker. Put me on speaker now.
Hello there, darling. I just wanted to say I can't believe you think that I learned that I'm a cute
and attractive man. I don't know what you look like. I'm not entirely sure, but your grandson
seems to know quite a few. He's got a good taste. You know, I'm old. I don't know how old you are,
in particular, but I just want to say that your grandson's in good hands here. As he watches me,
I have a lot of good people here, a lot of friends and stuff, and family and everything.
Family's incredibly important, so I just want to let you know that your grandson's in a good place
right now. Do you think I'm cute? Thank you. Okay. Now take me off speakerphone. Dude,
pass the fucking joint. Dude, did you buy it? All right. Let's see the end. Remember, why do
you hate everything? What? I like frogs. All right. I'm ready. I'm going. I'm finishing the game.
I still have a little bit of juice left. I do. You're saying it's about an hour from here?
I have a little bit of gas left. I think I'm good to go. You got all the gems. Go in and out of the
blue door now. Do I actually have all the gems? I have aquamarine, emerald, and ruby. Where's the
diamond? Where's sapphire? Where's quartz? You're very close. The blue door is the true ending.
I gotta get out of here. No help. You've liberated everyone in the forest. The mushrooms are never
truly alive anyways. Okay. Final gem is black tourmaline. Well, then I must be pretty good for
my energy levels then. All right. So you think I can open the blue door? You mean this one here?
There's nothing alive in this part of the realm. Do you still wish to enter? So be it. I tell you
to budget. Oh, why is the game so quiet? Other blue door. Sorry about that. I turned it down from
blue door. The other blue door. In and out of a blue door. And that one? I mean this one here.
I would call that a gray door. Blue trim. Go in and out of it. The green door is better. I'm just
going in here. I'm just going in here. I'm just going in. I mean, there could be some super
secret weird thing. I'm just going for it. You have done a massive task. Everyone is dead except
one. Some of the ones you've slain might not approve of your actions. Those who felt wrong,
there will be reconciliation. It is time for you to come out. Hello, human. Or should I say,
hello, red? You've done well. It is time to go back home now. Close all the doors. Permanently.
Hardest part is coming up. Close all the doors. The door is locked. Okay, just get rid of all the
doors. Thank you for staying persistent and helping us. Finally, some peace in the world.
How do the doors talk? We had some good times. Now it's time to say goodbye. Okay. Finally,
peace blast. We meet again in another plane of existence. It's been awesome, buddy. Why is there
some nonchalant about this? You're doing the right thing. Am I going to come out of a birth canal?
Right? Am I about to like be born? Is this going to be like I'm born or something? It's supposed to be
purgatory. I'm going to wake up in a hospital bed. Stop the waiting room. Well done. This world has
lived for a long time. You have done a tremendous task. You could have quit any time you wanted.
But you pushed through even when it got difficult. This is a great feat that only a few could
accomplish. Use this determination wisely. Now only one remains. I told you it was me. As long
as the last star shines, we can't depart from this world. We shall grant you power to kill our son.
The rabbit? The final battle has begun. We must hurry. The last star needs to die for us to continue.
That was like Peter Griffin plays fucking Undertale. Oh god. Here we go.
Negative 103 Celsius. What? I can't catch that? What the fuck are you talking about?
Excuse me. I'm grabbing them. Do I have this timed wrong because it's stretched out?
Because the perceptions are warped. That's true. Ow. Ow. It's getting closer. It's getting closer.
Fuck you. Oh come on. Uh oh. Can I dodge? Damn. All right. Just blew up a son.
I'm sorry. It was open in the other window. I'm sorry. I had to put Larry David in there at the
very end. Victory screech. Uh oh. It's the absolute truth. Kingdom Hearts. Okay. Oh. I'm just shit so
bad. I'm not even kidding. I don't know what happened in like the 10 seconds that I started
this. Oh my god. What? I don't know why they crept up so hard on me. Oh. Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
The absolute truth. Okay. There's nothing to attack. I can't hurt it. I'm just going to queue
it up. All these lives you have destroyed. Who was wrong? Oh shit. I got to fight this guy.
Uh huh. Whatever you say. I don't know. Don't do that. Not now. Oh you can do better than that.
You can do better than that. Playtime is over. You thought you got away with no physical constraints.
We have the upper hand now. My hands are sweating and I have to shit. I'm going to shit my pants.
What? This has gone too far. Pink? Red has been helping us. We just didn't know. But they killed
us. Yes. They did. They did what I couldn't do. I thought- this person's naked. This person's
naked. I thought by not killing we should not fear death. I've read that so wrong. Look at that. I'm
a little on edge right now. I'm kind of like a lightning bolt. It's been really kind of tricky
to pay attention. I feel like somebody just put a blow dryer in my face for 15 straight minutes.
Do I have to keep going? Are you on Adderall? No. That was crazy. There was too much going on.
Are you still going? I can't understand how you went through with this monstrous act.
You're the only one with powers to kill in a world of immortals. Against their will you took
their lives. That's not true. Half of these people were like, yes please kill me. Hooray. I'm happy.
What do you mean against their will? Like 70% of the people were happy I was doing this.
Was it my purpose to kill everyone? What do you mean that's not true? Half the people were like,
yeah well here it is. I'm happy. Thank you. I was being thanked because I sent her on a mission.
Have I forgotten my destiny? Don't be mistaken. I have thought about this for many years.
So many wanted to end their lives and didn't struggle. Even if they had asked me I didn't-
I don't think I could have killed them. What are you talking about? You were the one that killed us.
What? No. It was the doll. Her body was burned up in the incinerator, pink.
But as always the main problem was that- what was it? The main problem is something- you were in
there. That's the issue. You were inside. To cope with losing your body you create an illusion.
What? Don't go. No. After everything you were still the killer. No it wasn't me. It was not me.
I did not kill you. I was not. I did not do that. I did not hit her. I am stuck here now.
Was this all a test? I cannot do this alone. Please Red, you have to help me. I beg you,
you have to help me. I cannot do it alone. Is Daffy Duck gonna come over here with a pencil
in his hand and be like, don't don't don't erase me. You're an idea. And I'm gonna start like
drawing shit on him. Not the entire body, but it will have to do. Control me like you have always
done. Please guide me. Is that the Konami code? I guess. Where do we go? Is it really all in my
head? It couldn't have been. I know you're out there. What if I- you'll be my eyes. I trusted you,
human. Guide me out of this hellscape. It works. I can't believe it. Sorry. I'll remain silent.
As long as I trust you, you can guide me. Shut up. You just said you were gonna stop talking.
It's a frog. What do you wanna do? The journey is almost over now. Do you wanna save? Yes.
Thanks. What do you wanna do? Hello, Pink. Knowing you've accomplished what I asked of you
makes me a very happy frog. Your biggest challenge is yet to come. Please,
stay and relax until you feel ready. Let me know if you have any questions. Okay. I mean,
I've got quite a lot of questions, actually. What is behind that? Beyond there lies the end of your
journey. I don't understand. I can give you a hundred different explanations for what's behind
that door. But in the end, you're gonna come out the birth canal either way. It don't matter
what I say. You just have to find out. Where are we? We're not in the physical world anymore.
We're not in the end either. We're in a sort of waiting room. Just for you to collect yourself
and come to peace. I'm fine. I don't have to- I'm fine. Like, I heard- I felt the gurgles for a
minute and now I'm fine. Don't worry. Is that how I'm supposed to do that? I'll admit, I did not
expect this. I'm sorry. Don't worry. If you're fine, then gamble on a fart. Why are you just
assuming and implying that I have to do that? I don't need- I don't have to do that. I'm just
kind of walking right now. There's nothing here. Oh, please. So what is the final boss, then?
It's gonna be me. It's- it's gonna be me. It smells horrible. Let it happen. Oh, no. Did I
shit my pants? It's cold. What? It doesn't feel good. It's uncomfortable. I didn't mean to. No,
no. I won't. I just killed him. Age will always get you human, but some of us found a way out.
But it requires immense determination. The only way for you out, Pink, is to surrender yourself.
But I think you already knew that. Have what it takes to save Pink. Yes. Good. You see things
through. That is a good trait, but it's far from looking. Look into the darkness. Face the abyss.
Shit your pants. Just do it. Water's getting deeper. It's cold. It doesn't feel good.
Uncomfortable. It hurts. Everything is burning. I guess I- I forgot a problem. That's- that's way-
that's, uh, a few too many Taco Bell Diablo sauces on that. Eagle funny. I know. Trust me. I get it.
What happened? Uh, I'm coming out of the birth canal. I told you. It's been some time since we
last saw each other. All right. Holy shit. We're all good friends and we all get together sometimes.
When you're feeling down and you're feeling out of luck and out of change, we will work together
and we will have- I'm sorry. I- that's what I expected. That's what I expected. I expected that.
You have to understand. I can't hear anything. I can't even hear my own thoughts.
I have no- I don't know what I sound like right now. I might- I've probably been talking so loud
this whole playthrough because I can't hear anything. There's a vacuum cleaner going behind me
and in front of me and on both sides of my ears. It has not been easy, but you made it into the-
what is this? You have fought- am I Jesus? You've fought well, Jesus. Most important thing.
Coming up here. It's still left.
We're going upside down again. Hey, stop doing that. We are reaching the end of time.
Okay. Okay. Can somebody press the tracking button on the remote, please?
I'm trying to watch The Simpsons from 1990 fucking 3. Give me something to shoot at him.
What the fuck? Will you behave? I don't know. Give me a bow and arrow to shoot at him, please.
Am I the Big Bang or something? My planet? Farewell. Thanks.
Oh my god. What are you doing, game? When you're out of luck and you're out of friends,
let me be the one to show you. So long. It's still going? Is this- am I getting looped?
Am I getting pitied? Oh shit. Don't lose now. Stop shaking the screen. Stop doing this.
Please, I can't see anything. Oh my god. Bro. Bro. Bro. Bro. Come on, bro. Dude, what the fuck?
I can't even like see anymore. I literally can't even see. Somebody's just screaming into my brain.
It's like- it's like somebody hitting me in the back of the head with a hammer every 10 seconds.
There are wow raid bosses that are not as long as this.
I remember like Ragnaros took like 40 minutes. I don't want to re- I don't want to do that again.
All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'm good. I'm good.
I don't want to see it anymore. No. Stop it.
Stop. Dude, I want to do that. It's- oh my god. Hey. Hey, you want to do this again
for another five straight fucking minutes? Stay strong. Stay determined.
Fly into me. Fly out of me. Because you're a baby and you're about to be in the universe.
I don't know whatever the fuck this is. Put it on easy just to see the end of the game.
My face is itchy. I'm losing my mind. All right. Wait. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I got it.
Stop. All right. If I make another sound after this, I'm going to gift a thousand subs
until the end of the fight. Okay. Starting now. I can talk. Okay. I did it. I almost screamed when
it just did that. What happened? Where am I? When it did that second part right there,
when it just threw a bunch of- I almost screamed, but I was like, oh my god, I can't scream.
Am I dead? What am I? And you fart directly in- I'm not going to even say anything because
why do I read those? Do not worry. You have done well. This is the end of this life. Before we
venture forward, I have something to show you. It's going to be earth. I created earth. You're
awake. You did it. Apparently I did it. You freed everyone from the immortal realm. Welcome to the
waiting room. This is the place of reconciliation, the place after death and the end of the game.
This was the good end. It's been an absolute joyful experience to see you on this journey.
Some have waited for you here. Okay. This is the good ending. I actually was supposed to do this.
Look. Thank you for freeing me. You're truly a great warrior, but this world still has secrets
left to uncover. I've lost everything. The world doesn't exist. I'm not really me anymore. All these
things I used to care about, they don't matter. In a strange way, I feel relieved. I believe there
was another world after death. I thought everything would just stop and turn black for all eternity.
Maybe an eternity has already passed. I don't even know anymore. I'm glad it seems there is
more to life than what I thought. I feel stupid. I thought we were already in the afterlife,
but I'm happy there's another journey coming. I'm a bit sad that I've been quite accustomed to my
body. Existed for eons, maybe some change is good. It must have been hard for you to kill everyone.
I'm glad you took the role of Reaper. Here comes the birth canal. I'm telling you. Sometimes when
it gets really quiet, I hear a voice. I can't decide whether it's nice or some whatever. I have
a nice journey. Everyone's getting birthed. I knew you had it in you. It gives me great pleasure that
you were able to free the souls, including his by the way. Everyone did that D face when I did it to
him. Look what I did. Wait, why are you not going? You had a reason for coming here, didn't you?
As we are ending our chapter, I have a strange feeling there is more to this world.
Across to the other realm, I see. It will be a pleasure showing you this world, Red. Unfortunately
for you, human, you will not be joining us tonight. But don't worry. Your time will come soon enough.
Goodbye. You've done well. What a strange place you have brought me to. Kill them all again.
You did well, human. The inhabitants had been there a long time. It's great to finally see
them come back. As for you, Pink, I hope you understood what needed to be done. It was a
hard path, something no one should be forced to do. It is not good for the soul to be immortal.
You need to come home. Yeah, so it seems. Hi, guys. I was shocked with everything that happened,
but I'm happy with how it all turned out. I think Flan is happiest of us all.
You, Red? You've changed quite a bit. How long has it been since we saw each other?
I can't tell. I know we didn't leave on good terms, but I wanted to let you know that I'm
thankful for what you did. Grim is ready for it to end when he stops doing voices.
Yeah, if you're new to the channel, hour number like one, two, and three is like, oh, that's me,
Germa. Oh, hey, that's me. I had a great life and lots of friends. When you get to hour number four
and five and then six and so on, it's like, here, I'm just just me. We're just hanging out.
You can feel the energy levels like sap from my body. I've had a great life with lots of
friends and fun, but when I was alone, I didn't have such a great time. Anyway, happy you helped
me. Yeah, end of the stream voice. That's how you can tell. Do we have to send everybody or?
I did a good job looking forward to reward. This is it, huh? What was the point of that?
I got some thinking to do, Red or whoever you really are. Red, hi, Blue. I'm so happy to see
you again. Once I died, it felt very cold and everything became dark and it got a bit scary.
But after a while, that frightful feeling disappeared. And when I opened my eyes,
I was here. I knew you weren't a bad guy. All these people are respawning in the freezer.
Oh, we're going over. Oh, I didn't know I was an immortal. He's sending us over.
He's sending us over to the next realm. I didn't know I was an immortal. Knowing that there is
more. You still have like a cold up here. Send them to the birth canal. I wonder where we will
appear now. Are they going to like appear as like animals and humans and like bugs and stuff?
How do I know that I'm not just like having them reincarnate as like a beetle? I couldn't believe
that there was more to it all. I'm so thrilled. I assume the world would just cease to exist.
And then nothing, you know, this is truly astonishing. I never got the chance to truly
meet you for so many years. No, for so many decades, I've been living in a world of terror.
I was held prisoner by Professor Orange. They gave me things so I wouldn't couldn't leave.
I'm just happy it's all over now. But I do feel regret regret that I didn't take it into my own
hands and free myself from Professor Orange. I just gathered courage. I don't know. Still,
I'm very happy I'm finally free now. I am thankful. I was hurt. You. You helped me.
Professor Orange. Not so nice. To me. All right, so we're sending this guy to hell, right?
Had theories about there being additional layers of consciousness after death.
The rationalist and materialist in me couldn't let myself truly indulge in that fantasy.
In any case, I'm glad that there is a light beyond death. I'm sorry for my actions of malice
against you. I was technically sent to hell. Anybody else down here? We got everybody down here?
What about the street lamp? Okay. Thank you for everything. Do you want to save? Yes. Right here.
Amazing. Okay. I'm going to save your progress. No. I can't kill him. All right. Only a few more
people up here. I think this is it. Who's that? A Roblox character? This whole game was made in
Roblox? You did well. You can finally know peace. It wouldn't have been possible without you.
Seems like a good place for a fresh start. You can call me Bridge. Oh wait.
Honby. When you killed me, I was like, this is where it all ends. But then I didn't.
I'm ready for something new. I will be honest with you, Pink. I never expected the afterlife
would look like this. It's been nice, but I do feel a bit sad. Are you sad? No. I have a heart of
stone, you know. Maybe that's how you were able to do it all. And we're just, we're sending them
over in their essences and energies. We're going to fire a laser and blow up a planet. That's like
why we did this whole thing was for that. Bye. Get out of here. I'm sorry. He didn't leave. I'm
sorry for attacking pink. I thought I did the right thing. It's both exciting and a bit, uh,
whatever that word is, it starts with an M and ends in ellencolic. Oh, melancholic, like melancholy.
We're going to leave this realm. I've lived for so long that I feel like there's so much more for
me to discover. Thank you for all the good times, Pink. Thank you, Ross the Beast. You're always
looking out for me. You need to get out of here. All right, nothing gets past you. All right,
gotta be gone. All right, we cleared it out. Nobody left. Put everybody on. Now it's time.
Hello, human. Are you ready to end the game? Yes. It's been a spectacle watching you.
Let us say farewell in a way it deserves to end. God, more. Do I have to fight God now?
You kidding me? I don't want to fight God. I don't want to fight God. Everyone's leaving.
Am I going to try to hurt them or are we going to dance over the credits?
How come it's just those guys? I want the whole and I want the whole cast.
All right. All right, guys, guys, guys. Okay. I'm done. I'm done. I'm really tired.
Everyone go live your next life and ship. I don't want to do this anymore. I'm fucking tired.
You don't understand how long I've had to do this for. Goodbye, everybody. Goodbye. Goodbye.
Thanks. Thank you. I swear to God, I'm going to start throwing you outside the side of my window
like a fucking newspaper if you don't leave. Thank you. I hope you found this experience.
Let's try to kill me with that last chord. Oh, okay. Dick. Before we close the curtains,
I'd like to thank all the Kickstarter supporters and everyone on Patreon. I hope it does that.
Please do that. That would be fucking awesome. Let me dance over all the Kickstarter names.
Come on. Thanks for everything. Always to let me get out. Can't leave me alone.
I won't let me rest. Thanks to you, I can finally sleep. Yeah, that'd be great when I get to do that
too. You want room service? Anybody here want room service? Want to call Toshiers? Anybody need
anything? You're always sort of annoying. You know what? Send that guy to hell. Send that guy to
hell. I want that guy dead again. I want that guy to go back to the immortal world. I don't want to
give him eternal fucking beautiful life. Send that guy to hell. It's been a pleasure. Thank you.
Thank you for helping me. Yes. I'm so happy there's more. I'm just waiting for this to cut
and we're in a giant bus and we just go off a cliff. Oh, we're going to venture beyond the
and then it just cuts to like real. We go off like a fucking cliff and the car explodes.
That health bar is huge. That health bar is massive. It's so massive. Thank you for playing my game.
See you later. Please stop thanking me. Yeah, we did. One thank you is enough. I don't need to
hear more than one thank you. Here we are at the end of the road. We have witnessed an eventful
journey. Many words have been said. Thoughts have been shared. Before you leave, do you wish
to hear the last absolute truth? Sure. What is it? There are no absolute truths. Yes, there is.
Chocolate is delicious. That's an absolute truth. Nobody can disagree with that. You're free to
wrap your half truths into whatever. No, that is the true beauty of it. You can make the rest up.
You still have a long time. No, that's not a good idea. That's not a good idea because that's how
Facebook and Twitter got so fucked up. No, no, no. Let's focus on truth, please.
You still have a time left and some time after that. Oh yeah, the thing about truth is you just
make a bunch of shit up. Who cares? Who cares about that truth stuff? I'm not going to skip
the credits. That's not what it means. There's no Facebook dude in heaven. Oh, how do you know that?
You don't know that. You don't know what it is. You don't even know what it looks like.
You want the alien rant again? Take care of yourself. Thank you, friend. What the fuck is
happening? Come and visit us again. It never ends in everhood. New game plus.
All right, I'm going to give you my full my opinion. Played through the whole game. Took
about seven and a half hours. I tell you, I believe that that was very solid. I would say
that was a highly recommend. It's very good. It was definitely worth playing for sure.
That was very good. What would you give? What about a rating? New game plus for the good ending.
I don't think so. Game grew on me a lot after I beat it and thought about it more. Please write
to us and tell us how our game made you feel. Our email is in the store page. I'll tell you right
now. It made me feel I had a lot of emotions. It made me feel all kinds of things like what is
life? What is death? This game contains flashing lights that can be dangerous. No, it's very good.
But this is this is now looks different. What happened? Oh, you can replay battles. That's
cool. All right, I think I'm going to call it here. That was really good. Now I understand
why everybody said, dude, don't just play the don't just like drink half a bottle of wine and
play like the first level. I get it. That was a that was a very, very fantastic time. I had a
great time. Hope you did too. The next time that you see me live, I will see you on the 20th of
the next four or five days. I've got a lot of stuff I need to do, a lot of work to do,
especially on the big stream that's happening on the 1st of February. A lot of stuff to do.
On the 20th, that's Thursday, we're going to play Hitman VR. It releases on the 20th. I'm
very excited for that. I feel like that's going to be a lot of fun. And I will see you guys later.
He's stalling? The stream is over, man. But yeah, Hitman VR will be the 20th. I'm assuming I'll
here's one thing I want to make really clear about the VR streams is because the last time
I did VR, I kind of really had a lot of trouble and a lot of problems afterwards.
So what's going to happen with those streams is I'm probably only going to be in the headset
for like maybe two or three hours each time. I just physically can't do more than like three,
four hours in the headset. I just can't. So yeah, for those of you that don't know,
I have some medical issues with my chest and back. Even seated VR probably would be too much.
Yeah, probably two or three hours. Maybe I'll push it a little more past three if I'm having
a great time. But the 20th, we'll do it again. Maybe on like the 22nd or something, 23rd,
24th. I will do it a few times in a row, but just not a whole lot of time in the headset in a row.
Like I'm in the same setting. It should be fun. I'm looking forward to it. You should go back to
Everett and try the pacifist run. Maybe I'll do that on my own time. But thanks for hanging out.
Hopefully you guys had a good time. And we'll see you again in four or five days on the 20th.
It's man time for that. Let's go. I'm going to say four o'clock Pacific. That might come back
to like two or three, depending on if I can get my sleep schedule in the right spot. But plan on four,
although it could be pulled back to like something as early as two or three. I really want to get
back on that like 2 p.m. Pacific schedule because it is right now pretty late for everybody,
not just East Coast. And that's it. Have a wonderful evening, everybody. Take care of
yourselves. You know, hey, do one good thing today. You know what I mean? Do something good
today. You know what I mean? So you can breathe in the air and breathe it out and go,
that feels good. I did something good. Do it. Just do it. Why not? Do it. No. Okay. Good night.
Well, yeah, it's too late. The day's over. Yeah. Never mind. Do it tomorrow. Do something nice
tomorrow for somebody. I don't know. Yeah. Forget about the rest of the day. Just, you know, you'll
be asleep. It's like negative 30 outside. I'm not going anywhere. Call your mother and say hi.
Mom, it's good to hear from you. I'll see you guys on Thursday. Take care. Have a good night. Goodbye.