Oh, there's no sound. Oops. Hey. That was awkward. Hey, hi guys. Welcome to the stream.
You guys could just hear my mouth open. That's what it sounds like when there's no
background sounds or audio. This is what you hear. That's, no, like, you can't hear that now,
that this is on. Like, I just did it and you didn't hear it. Fucking magic of audio mixing.
Anyways, uh, how you guys doing? Hope you had a good couple of days there,
after the green screen movie night. Hope all is well. My camera's on. Oh, better turn it off.
Tonight we're gonna play Just Cause 4 and then tomorrow, uh, if it's allowed, we're going to
re-stream the game awards and, you know, maybe give a little j- couple of jabs every now and again.
And then after that, the plan is for, uh, potentially this weekend, Saturday and Sunday,
to be Dreamcast. I'm gonna get that ready to go if I can. So that is the plan for this week.
Okay, but what about Lego Island? All things, all things will happen eventually. It can't be
Lego Island every single stream, you know? I would love nothing more than to have it be Lego Island
every stream. But I'm sorry, guys. It's just not the way it works. So let's move over here.
Uh, Just Cause 4, it's just, I heard it was interesting. That's what I heard.
You know, might not be true. It's currently sitting at a very great, mostly negative on
Steam. I don't know why. But it is. And here it is right now. That's because it sucks.
All right, well, let's, well, just how much does it suck? Just Cause you can doesn't mean that you
should. But I mean, look, we have to try stuff. Okay? This stream is a fucking first impressions
journalistic approach to most video games, right? Like, we have to get, we have to do it.
Oh, the game is starting.
Up to this point, his whereabouts have been unknown since our withdrawal from Medici.
I thought that was actually responsible for deposing half a dozen heads of state.
The black hands have encountered them before. Anybody give a shit about any of this? Like,
I could just skip this whole thing, right? I'll give you our own backstory here. Okay. So
we fought him again in Medici where he overthrew Sebastiano Di Ravello,
real journalist. He had some involvement. This is his handler, Tom Sheldon.
Well, we can't skip it. There is no skipping it. We have to sit here.
So first impressions of that cut scene was, um, those animations in there. Hold on. This is so
loud. I actually just skipped that. But how am I supposed to know what happens in this one?
That's too loud. Yeah. You know, you got that right, chat. From my understanding, it's back
and forth here between two forces. Uh, one red, one blue. I'm going to monitor your progress from
a safety point. What kind of fucking system is this? Hold shift to aim down sights? What does run?
You get the grapple. Wait, the grapple is immediately in the game.
How do I suck to that? The road is walled off. Can you get over it? Come on. This is how the
rock used to get strong. Attach me to like four cars. What do I have to do? Okay. Where to now?
By the way, his new show. Those lights across the valley head towards them. Like here come the
Titans, whatever it's called. Jump off and pull the parachute. That's a big tower. Espinosa promises
it will change the world. No more tornadoes or hurricanes. And most of Solis believes him.
Project Diablo won't be a problem after today, Mira.
If your plan works. I don't want to fucking wait for this.
Reach the landing zone. What? Pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up, pull up.
Just like in Mario when you're in Mario world. Wait, I lost the momentum. No, I didn't. I'm good.
I got it. Okay. I made it under the dish. That's what they wanted me. Face to face with a black hand.
We've come face to face before. Heading up. Okay. So I need to go follow the waypoint
to the outpost. Why do I feel like I shouldn't be allowed to do this?
Is this just cheating? I'm cheating in the game. I don't feel like I've been playing a video game.
All right. We're going up here now. I'm so tilted. Wait, why?
Does anybody else feel like they accidentally put me in a save file that was halfway through the game?
Are these bad guys? Okay. It's fucking easy. Yeah. God, I feel just like the Punisher in this game.
How do I, can I grab? Is there a grab button besides that?
So I gotta, I gotta get a juggle here, right? Oh, all right. So, uh, alternate fire, release all tethers.
Fire weapon, alternate fire, tap. Oh, well that's an explosive. Okay. This game sucks.
We haven't even gotten through the halfway into the game tutorial. Come on guys.
What's going to, this is what's going to, I know, listen to me. I know exactly what's going to happen
with this game. This is, we skipped the cut scene. We're in the middle of the game, right? It's going
to do this. This is like the, the flash forward. We're going to go back. We're going to have like
a melee weapon. We're going to have a baseball bat and like brass knuckles.
This is going to take us all the way back. We're playing a mission like in the future.
And I just took that out. That was so mean.
Put a reef on timer on the screen. Not good enough. Why would I do that? Okay. Grapple and open
parachute. You can fly around. I need to land there? Every bone in your body breaks right there.
All right. Made it to the giant speakers. I made it to my show. I can't just pull it out here.
It really is the fucking Mario reference I made. You guys all thought that was
nonsense. All right. Get up there. Okay. I've made it. All right. We're fine. We did it. Wait,
I was supposed to go up there and then jump. Okay. I know what I have to do. Bingo and then
fly over here. This is stupid. There we go. Just use the momentum of the ground.
Are you sure this isn't modded?
No guys, I'm sorry. I downloaded goofy gravity mod. That's my own fault.
Structure. I'll figure it out.
I don't even know what I'm doing. Was that a person? Oh, you can drive? This car,
this car still work? Can I grapple the car? Use nitrous. I've almost made it. Come on.
I feel like I'm playing Spider-Man. This is just the Spider-Man gameplay.
I don't have any grenades left. I don't even know if I'm progressing. Oh, shit.
He just turned into the cookie monster. It's all right. I'll get up. Oh, cookies.
Oh, I don't belong in this part of the game yet.
I'm at project the upper. This physics and the gravity just don't make any sense.
I'll figure it out. How do I get that? Oh, fuck. I have to fight. I mean, the conflict really is
just there. You know what I'm saying? It just is. There's too much going on right now. I need like
a slow beginning. We're never going to get out of the tutorial. We might not. I'm at project the upper.
Okay. There's a console up there. I'll figure it out. What? I just go to the structure, right?
What did I just do to that person? All right. I made it. Okay. That's what I had to do.
Could use this vent to get me up there. And then jump off the edge.
Go down and link the portal level. Come on. What the fuck are you doing, man? Why would I?
Get up there. Release the tethers. Get up here. And then I have to parachute because
I just did that shit. I just did that. You can't tell me I didn't. That's what I'm trying to do.
Oh, fuck. No, we're fine. All right. We're good. Melee attack is Q. Just for anyone that's curious.
This way we got to jump. Okay. This is just like Mario. Another Mario reference. This is
from Mario 64. That's all we do in this channel is make Mario references. Nothing else. We don't
ever do anything else. When you land. That went too far, man. Then get. All right. Reach the console.
I'm going to get behind cover. Is there a cover system? Look, it does explode.
All right. I got it. What did you say? What was that? All right. Shoot the explosives. That's
what I just did. See? Who just gave a hundred dollars? Lorag just gave a hundred bucks.
I don't have any more bullets left. What do you do if you don't have any more bullets?
All right. Ammo. Get it. Shoot the giant exploding Disney balls. All right. I did it.
Anybody else? I think I'm safe. Hold on. Let me get to a safe place so I can talk about it. I
just got a hundred fucking dollars. Hold on. Up there. Watch this one. Can I get some pipe in the
chat, please? Wait, I'm on this. I'm on the structure. I think I got to get off. You know,
I always wondered why. Why do you have to ask for hype? All right. So we reached the console.
All right. Did I make it? No, it's over here. Okay. All right. Weapon case.
A grenade launcher. What should I do with this? Do buildings fall down?
I don't know what I'm doing. I have no idea what's going on. I have to hack this. Okay.
Oh no. Not one of these. Make sure I jump before shooting.
Now you're sure that I don't have mods and stuff. Are we sure about this?
I didn't get like the deluxe edition, right?
They're trying, lady. This person's freaking me out. Can I?
It worked.
All right. Remote hacking progress. Oh, they're on a stupid machine over there.
Take your time. Don't take your time. I severely... Whoa, that was a grenade launcher. I severely
overestimated how far that was going to go. Or underestimated. This is, um,
this is... I can't even tell you what I have to say. I did it. I made it. He's unlikely he has
survived this long. This is not an ordinary mine, Senor Espinosa. See, now we're going to go back
to like 1982 or something.
Let's see what Project Yappa can do, shall we? Uh, lower. Thanks for the hundred dollars,
by the way. I had a cold and wasn't feeling too great, then I watched the green screen movie
stream and I know only do I feel absurdly healthy. I can see perfectly at night and do long division
without a calculator. Thanks, Jeff. You're very welcome. You're incredibly welcome.
All artillery towers. PS2 cutscene. I'm getting, am I getting hit with the explosions?
So do I think it was? See. Deal with that, please. He looks like, uh, he looks like the mask and the
bad guy gets the mask on. What's that guy's name? What's that actor's name? Bogdano. Quick rundown,
quick rundown on the game? It's fucking stupid. Look, the ground, look at the ground is even
like moving around. That cement ain't fucking holding me. Please respond.
See, now I have to start from zero again. See, I told you guys.
Maybe a few reaps. I'll need to make repairs. You guys thought it was going to be a situation where
we weren't halfway through the game. I'm sending you my coordinates. Hope it works.
All right, so that's all we need to know. Skip this fucking whole thing. I'm stuck. Visible cursor.
Yeah, well that's okay. So all you need to know is. Not having my grappling hook is like missing a limb.
Okay, so now we have to go to meet Mira. Pigs. I can't do anything with the pigs. Why?
I can't ride the pig. This could have been a full letter grade. Okay, well, what the hell are you
talking about? Connect, is that, okay. What is that? Thanks for telling me. That looks like the place.
I'm no longer connected to the servers. I've never seen anything like Iapo before.
Mira might be right. All right, everyone's dressed like a Pokemon trainer.
Don't have your graphics on low. The graphics aren't on low. What are you talking about? Two double
anti-scopic filtering. 1080. Fixa. High, high, yes. Medium and medium.
What the hell is this thing? Is this like a bridge?
Okay. All right, let's go meet Mira. Zero percent. Zero percent what? What's on the phone?
What's up? I wanted to see the phone. All right, let's go.
Glowing hair. Oh, this whole game feels like it was made in second life.
Are you sure this isn't a modded version of the game? Are you certain of that?
That would hurt.
What happened? Everything okay? Yeah, fine. It's all over. Oh, yeah, I'm fine. I'm just fine.
Things are going great over here. If you fall from that high and you land, you're going to disintegrate.
Just fine for, yep. I almost didn't make it again. Okay, easy now. Refund and get, yeah,
so this is second life. Where are the people with the elaborate like $400 animated dancing?
That's what I'm worried about.
Is that dog? That dog, that dog is very small. Doesn't look to undersize like it wasn't scaled
properly. Can you pick up dog? It's kind of leaning to the left here. It's leaning to the left.
I don't know. I don't think it's going to make it. I don't think this dog is going to make it.
Oh, well, okay. It's smart. No, maybe it's not. Come on over here. I got something to show you.
Let's find out just how smart you really are. Come on. Come on. Are you peeing over here?
That's really cute of you. Good job, dog.
Is there something else you want to do? You sure? No, all right, fine.
Well, you're very good at handstands. That's for sure. Oh, fuck. All right, meet Mira. The dog was
doing a dog T-pose. That is pretty accurate. Up here. All right, I'm going to bother. Here comes
cutscene in three, two, 30 FPS cutscene. Yes. You look awful. Yeah, so does this game. The black
hand are casing the village. Does that happen often? I'm being unfair. I think I'm being unfair.
It's only been like fucking 20 minutes. Maybe somebody attacked their weather base.
Tools? Jesus fucking Christ. You could just hand it to me. Why would you boot the toolbox over here?
I don't think I can take project the apple alone. We're in the same room. I agree.
I'm saying I was wrong. You were right. Is that a distress signal? I didn't think you were with
the agency anymore. Help me with this. Don't let him fool you. That's just an elaborate fucking
Yu-Gi-Oh toy. What do we do about Yappa? Between the blizzard and those artillery towers?
I can't get close. I have a couple of ideas. Tell me. Wait. Listen. What do we- a helicopter?
Your actions in the next few minutes may determine the fate of this community.
Choices matter? I am Commander Morales. I have tolerated El Abismo for years.
To maintain order and justice in Solis. This game is using the McDonald's happy meal engine.
For the criminal and the disenfranchised. That's what somebody just said. Last night a terrorist
attack was launched against the project Yappa facility. The culprit was abetted by a conspirator
from this village. Who is that? Gabriela. She killed my uncle when I was a girl. Is it my settings?
Maybe I should turn some settings to up or down or something. If Mira Morales is not surrendered
to me immediately, I'll be forced to conduct an exhaustive investigation. Every home will be
searched. Every citizen's identity will be checked. And all transgressions will be harshly prosecuted.
One guy had the gun to the left. You. You know what I mean? Like that guy's not in- that guy on the
right. See that? Everybody had that gun pointing down to our left. He had it pointed to our right.
Where is Mira? That's the fucking hitman right there. That's the guy that's in disguise.
I don't even need to look at the back of the box to find, uh,
Meryl's codec. I already know. Let him go, cousin. At least you aren't a coward.
Your father would be disgusted with the monster you've become.
All right, take the guns away and give him ski poles.
In prison. Why are they in this gear here? Wouldn't it be too hot to be in- that was a jump scare for
them. This is sad. Can we hit two likes? I freeze. Oh, here comes the first decision,
first quick time decision of the game. All right, well, I did- he just- he's dead. He shot- all
right, that's where he's at. So I'm the cause of this. All right, forget about Pokemon. What the
hell? I did that. Okay, I did that. I can't skip this cutscene, you know, we're too far into it.
We need re-
Get over here! Come here! I could have done that, right? You'd like pitch shift me like 5% and let
me fucking scream. I would be a great scorpion. You know, uh, if anyone's watching right now,
that's part of the scorpion dev team. I do consulting work, you know. I think we just
started a rebellion. We didn't have to drag these people into this. They are what we need to put
down, Project Yappa. Well, they'll need more guns. Eso. There's a factory down the road from here.
Abandoned. Cascillos vacios. Fix the graphics. You can't, what? Put every setting to low.
No, not yet. We can't give up yet. Anyone who wants to fight the Black Hand gets to fight.
Sure for it? I promise. Before the stream is over, we will do the Best Buy computer all the way to
the left on the shelf settings. I promise. I promise. Hope everything works. We've already
given up. What? What have I given up yet? We just got started. Look, I can like throw this over here.
He's fine. Just jump. See? See, look at this. I cars out. It already gets a letter grade.
Do you guys understand? There's a letter grade. Holy fuck. Why are you psycho?
What? What? Why is it? What's wrong with their car? Wait, what? Their car was just like eating
somebody. Their car was just chewing on someone. All right. Wingsuit. Oh, it's because I went over
here. God damn it. Hold on. He's fine. Just jump. You can't let me. But you just opened up cars.
Oh, bah. I can't do it yet. All right. Well, we have to wingsuit over here.
Hope everything works. Oh, battle bus.
All right. That's the factory. Oh,
when we drop right here. Oh, there's a guy at the cube. There's a guy at the cube.
That's what you've got. Your AR lens mirror told me already done.
Something like that. Let's get started. I feel like this shouldn't be happening.
Where am I getting the momentum to do this? Do you understand this is not physically fucking
possible? That's not how these work. That's the end.
I'm the hacker. That's what you've got.
You have an AR lens, like a little computer on your eyeball. Can I like shit something like
bird shit on people? Can I like throw rocks? You know what I meant by that. Can I like throw rocks
down at people? Okay, Sargento, you're up. Use the AR scan to find generators. The factory needs to
be powered on, but the doors to the electrical room are being held shut by backup generators.
How many times are you going to make the Fortnite joke? Will it be every time you jump from a
little bit? Or will it? Because that would be funny if you did that.
Okay, so we just gotta find the generators. Well, there's one over here. There's one over there.
This one was the closest one. What the fuck is that thing?
That's somebody's little toy helicopter. What? All right. Well, this one's over here. Let's go
this one first. One, two. I couldn't do it. I was going to do the Yahoo. So here's the generator
right here. I can't have this much power. I'm trying to do like this. All right, we're good.
Use AR scanner. Here's your mission. The factory needs to be powered on. The electrical room are
being held shut by backup generators. We shouldn't accept it.
I need to get on this guy's motorcycle. It's important. No, don't slow down. Oh shit,
I gotta turn around. No, before I lose. Okay, I gotta stop. Let's play.
Here's your mission. The factory needs to be powered on, but the doors to the electrical
room are being held shut by backup generators. Mission accepted, Sergeant. Your AR lens will
show you where to look. It's only a matter of time before Gabriela sends more black
to stop us. Oh my body. This game has got way better, by the way. All right, this is this one
right here. Use it to scan the building. There it is. Okay, there's a generator building.
Very good. Let's go over to it. Fuel barrels. Aim at the barrel and hold to start tether.
Oh, I can do that? Generators well shielded. Oh my god. Can you turn it off? To rip the plating
off. Oh, I can use my grappling hook, but I can't use a fucking rocket launcher.
Oh, I guess I shoot it in the guts. Build, build, build. One generator down. All right, I get it.
Okay, two more to go. You know where to look.
All right, so there's one over here. Am I gonna, am I gonna get minus for that one? Why?
Do you think that was fun? What's closer? 177 to 171. They're both right next to each other.
I won't do that again. I'm fine. Somebody's shooting.
What was that? Zip. Is he alive? Zip. What the fuck? What the fuck is that thing?
Why is this here? Wait. Okay. Okay, Sargento. You're up. Listo. Here's your mission. Wait,
hold on. What about the little school bus? But the doors to the electrical room are being held
shut by backup generators. Mission accepted. I gotta get on the battle bus. Hold on.
It's only a matter of time before Gabriela saves more black man to stop us.
All right, I'm gonna do this quick. We need to get these people guns fast.
There's one here. Just go. I know how to do this. Let's go to this one first.
Fuel barrels. That hurt. Really? Okay, pull this off. Generators well shielded. What the hell are
you doing? I think I can use my grappling hook to rip the plating off.
Destroy the generator. Good. One generator down. What's in here? What is that? Okay, two more to
go. What is this thing? You know where to look. Oh god, don't make me say like another Fortnite
reference. Another Fortnite gun. What? I don't know. Does this thing shoot blades? Toaster gun.
No, this is the halo promotion. Oh, the other one was right there.
Oh. And boink. No, hold it.
And let's use the Fortnite gun. Pretty good actually. I don't want to get rid of this.
I'll get rid of this stupid one. What do you got in this box? Oh, nice double Fortnite gun.
Oh, come on. Seriously, how am I alive? I don't know how I...
Helicopter? No, it didn't. Go for the brain. Got it. Got the brain. Shoot the fucking brain,
guys. Every time. All right, we're good. I think that's it. We have one more to do,
which is down here. Are we still alive in here? No, no one's alive in there. You're behind me.
That was so fucking loud. All right, let's go quickly. This thing is you get to skip so
much nonsense doing this. Okay, I'm gonna kill... I'm gonna die if I keep doing that. I keep thinking
I'm gonna... I keep hitting my fucking head on the wall. That's not good. Almost done. Here's the last
one. Generators are all off. Let's take this and I'm gonna replace this with this. Choppers and troops
headed this way. Choppers heading this way. I'll take him out with one hit. Oh, what about this
thing? Yep. Those are birds. All right. Where they at? Come on. All right, they're not coming.
Time to go. Really? Fuck. Don't do that! No! All right, I gotta slow down. Where is it?
No, that was just... Little Mikey got a fucking toy for Christmas and that just went into the
coffee table and broke. That's what that was. On the first day of Christmas day, really?
Oh, whoops. Sorry, guy. All right, let's go. I was laughing at the stream.
Controller aim. What are you talking about? I gotta flip the switch.
I'll put up the Ghostbusters ghost thing. All right, come on. How do I get rid of these?
Eventually, I'll get it. Yeah! Here's the other one. I swear to God, I'm never gonna be able to get over it.
Breakers are on. And the Black Hand are almost here. Just hit the master override.
I can't. I have to do it every time. It's too much fun.
We're in business. Let's call everyone in. Uh oh, I'm closed in. Just give the order. Open the map.
The front lines... The front line is represented by these lines on your map.
This is where the Army of Chaos is holding back the Black Hand. Okay. The Zykan represents a
deployed squad. Secure regions by advancing or deploying squads. Select the Wachikuni region.
The Wachikuni. Okay. Can I like move the map? I think I just put... I put one in the wrong place,
apparently. I want to move the map. Okay. Well.
Should I just hide in here? Is this my safe bunker here? 60 FPS in-game cutscene.
All right. Is that mine? How long was I in there for?
It's been a few days. There's a bunch of canned soup in there. I felt like I could just stay.
This reminds me of those Kingdom Hearts III cutscene trailers they were showing at E3.
Is that gun gonna be any good? Come on, man. You opened that skin in a basic crate.
Did you see my weapon skin? I bought it on the Steam store. What happened here? I thought that
was music playing for a second. I thought that was a big party going on over there and that was just
music. To advance your front line, you need new squads for your army. To inspire people to join
you, destroy black hand infrastructure and vehicles. This creates chaos. You can notify
when you have enough chaos to recruit new people into squads. I'm part of the party.
All right. We got coordinates. What is going on over here though?
I need to investigate. He's playing the music over here.
What weapon is this? That guy's getting lit up. Where are you going? Oh my god. Watch it. I'm
the leader. Don't shoot me. Oh my lord. This person is destroying the whole bunker. What? I
could fly this? Where the fuck did I go? I'm in space. I'm in space. It put me into space.
Oh no, it didn't. I'm underwater. What's this thing? The blade is still spinning. It's a rare
weapon down here. Look at it. Are they still shooting this thing in the fucking ground?
Is there another helicopter? I don't know what's over here. I'm fucking so confused.
I need to get over here. Okay, so this is an enemy outpost.
They just let me go on here. I'm making so much chaos though, guys. Uh-oh. Speaking of chaos,
they're using the laser gun to burn me. That guy sounded like he's in my bedroom. I gotta get out
of here. I gotta do like something. I gotta do like a mission or something. There's a whole new
game environment over here. Who did that? Who even did that? All right, let's go. Where's my
scanner? I did that. Hostile still active. Hold on. No, hold on. I gotta go to the mission marker.
Lower the settings. This looks too real. They're just gonna do this forever. It's never gonna end.
So, why would I even? Oh, you can. Okay, hold on. Oh, nice. I got the skin. That was a teammate.
Is it a washing machine? This really is fucking Fortnite. Are you fucking serious?
You idiot. Don't do it. Don't do it. I know you want to, but don't do it. I forgot even
what I'm supposed to be doing. All right, we need to go to the mission marker. Weapon crate.
Turn the graphics down. No, not yet. I'm not turning the graphics off yet. Okay, release all
tethers. Where is the mission? I just have to cause chaos for like a little while. It's a chaos meter
up the top, right? How do I get to the map? Okay, there's the chaos meter. This is too much happening.
All right, I'm gonna go over here. M is not bringing up the map. It's not M.
We both shot each other. I win. One? Why is the map one? Okay, so we got this one here.
Sargento says he's got a surprise. Go to the coordinates and see what's going on. All right,
that's it's S. It's right here. I made it. Stupid fucking wingsuit, man.
All right, we're good. Get off this. This is so stupid.
This would be a lot of fun though if this was real life. All right, there's the
where I gotta go. All right, let's wingsuit in. Nice and careful. Air brake is control.
Okay, that's how it works. I'm ready. It feels like GTA with cheats. Yeah, that's exactly what it
feels like. It feels like you shouldn't be able to do this. Load up the truck. We're leaving in 60
seconds. Did you organize the ambush? See, most of the stuff we recovered is standard black
ammunition. But I also found some of these. We're not sure what they do. We didn't want to mess with
this. It's very bright.
There's a bunch more left in the truck. Metal Gear Solid 5.
This could be useful. They won't have a screwdriver. Somebody's had one.
You have to make do with whatever you find. So we didn't metal gear solid 5 people.
You actually can. I mean, that's just like a straight one. They thought that was cool
from Metal Gear Solid. They were like, yeah, I guess we're going here too. Sounds like a fun
mechanic to put in our game. All right, here we go. Grapple onto the truck.
Who's coming? I'm not even on the truck right now. This didn't work.
That balloon thing is pretty cool, huh? I think it'll come in handy.
Where'd you learn to plan an ambush?
I want the cow. I want the cow over here. I don't care about the mission.
Oh yeah, just one.
All right, you're fine.
One, open grappling hook menu. One, three. Okay, air lifter. This is where you can edit your
grappling hook. Currently you have loadout A equipped. You can have multiple loadouts
you can edit independently. Okay, so currently you have loadout A selected. Switch to loadout B.
Edit the empty loadout. This is your loadout edit screen. Columns define what your button presses
do. The auto column will activate mods. I knew it. Automatically when the tether is deployed.
Actions on the tap and hold columns will only activate when you tap or hold F.
Oh, that was a huge amount of money that came in. You're right. Did we even address the last one?
We did, right? Okay, I'm just making sure like I didn't just fucking skip it like an idiot.
Add a medium force air lifter to the auto column. The air lifter will automatically deploy to be
left up to be medium. Okay, it's right click to go back. This is so odd. Now the air lifter is
equipped in this loadout. Use the air lifter to clear the road. Holy shit. Wait, what am I doing?
I can actually stand on this? Oops. That's bad. Okay, hold on. 200 fucking dollars just came in.
100 dollars from D three four D dead C four T. Who fucking died here?
Oops. That guy's alive. Aim at the wreck. Hold on. Okay, aim at the wreck. Who is doing this?
And release. Oh my god, people are giving so much money. Hold on. Give me a second. I need to I need
to address these. Dead C four T just gave 100 dollars. 100 fucking bucks. Who even is Jerma?
Also love the YouTube. YouTube. Thank you. That's me. I am currently Jerma. And I think I will be
for a while. I don't know if I'll have any plans on being anybody else. But thank you so much.
Dead C four T for the 100 fucking dollars. And then right after that, I'm pink gave 100 dollars
to 100. 100. No message. Just 100 bucks. 100 dollars. And then right after that, 50 dollars
from Juno. And they say there's a lovely Easter egg in this game with a link.
Is this a spoiler? I don't understand what it is. I don't know if that's like a spoiler.
Might be a spoiler. It's a gnome. No, it's not. Somebody just drew that on their map and pretended.
But thank you to all three you guys. That's a fucking lot of money.
That's like 300 bucks in fucking an hour. Not even. See, that's what I mean.
Stuff like that. All right. Now escort him to the extraction point. You think I'd make a good agent
like you? Let me get on here. Keep your eyes on the road, Sargento. What the fuck? Because I think I
could do it. I always wanted to do something important. He's complicated, Sargento. He put
cake topper on. All right. What do I need to do? Escort him? That's what I'm doing. See you later.
Why are you not driving? Maybe that's why. Extracted. Oh, that guy was an S-rank. Holy shit,
guys. What else? That it? Who's shooting at us? Where are you? What the fuck are you doing here,
man? What? How are you even holding on to this? I don't have any bullets left.
I attached it? I don't understand. That thing is so heavy. Thanks for spawning me in a great
place with no fucking ammo. Whatever. Fuck it. Okay. Start the tether. Let's go. Get it up.
What have I created? All right, we're good. Is that a grenade?
This is what works for me, Sargento. You'll find what works for you. Get out of here.
For now, just worry about getting us to the extraction point.
On the head. Perfect. All right, I get to have a different weapon. This is the only weapon I have.
I can't even do anything. I don't have any bullets in this gun. And I have no other weapon.
All right, here we go. Here it comes again.
This time, I gotta be at the different... Don't. Don't.
At Bravo Station. We talked about this. Okay, there it is. There it goes. Here comes a helicopter,
right? CC, we'll be waiting. Over and out. What the fuck are you doing? Wait, I have to... Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What the hell? How do I let go? I have to let go
of this. Just focus, Sargento. Drive. They're still coming. All right, I'm going, I'm going.
These people just don't give a fuck. At all. Look at how many people are here.
That guy on the motorcycle just definitely died.
I can't... They just have a balloon on their car. That doesn't do... That didn't do anything.
How have we not ran this guy over?
What am I doing on top of the car? Get out of here. Oh, shit. Give me this. No, get on it.
Oh, I don't know how to drive this. I don't know how to drive this going too fast.
All right, we're fine. Oh, fuck.
You work out those hiccups, Sargento, and you could be a real operations master for the army.
No, I can't. I gotta get out of here. I gotta go, gotta go. I'm almost there.
All right, don't run into them. Watch this. Ready? And somehow that does not kill them.
What? Go, go, go. Hide away. Inflate, inflate. All right, that's gonna take them away, right?
How heavy is this thing? You are so heavy. Grapple them to the ground.
They can't move. Oh, shit. Get the blimp. It's too far away, I think.
Oh, no, he's alive. He's fine.
Lock and load, people. The Black Hand want their supplies back. Everything's fine.
How do we stop this guy from doing this? I don't have any guns.
I need a gun. I need to get like a gun or something. Give me a gun. Give me a gun.
Where's that weapon? Is it a weapon box? Weapon box. Weapon box is everywhere, in every direction.
Who is that? Okay, we're good. It's a shotgun.
This is live. Oh, you guys are alive. These people are fucking insane. I'm in a multiplayer
GTA lobby right now. Come on, secondary fire. Don't ever blow it up. Helicopter. Where is it?
Down there. What is it carrying? Time until extraction.
I'll work behind the lines. Make sure the armies stay stocked and safe.
You need an army. You stick together. Am I this bad? Yeah. Hey, sure.
Why can I not hit this? Oh, wait. Holy fuck, thank god. Help Sargento train the army.
Search the map for training and counterintelligence operations. Help Sargento and the army of chaos
will earn mod points that can unlock airlifter mods. All right, I don't want the stupid sniper
rifle anymore. All right, let's go. Squads received. So this is Garland King's new star. American
filmmaker Garland King has an offer that can't be refused. Meet him, meet with her, and hear what
she has to say. Yeah, let's do that. Close notifications. Oh, this is like the friends list.
One, two, three bullshit. What the hell? Make it M, man. Who's lost the target?
All right, we gotta go to G. I have a stun grenade. So we have to get from here over to there
in one jump. One, two, three.
Almost there. What the fuck was that? That just exploded.
Open the self-reeducation center.
There should be a control panel you can use.
I'm never gonna get that. No, I want to do the G. I had G.
Whatever. I'll just do this one. Open the south center. Fire stun grenade.
So satisfying. Is he stunned? What the hell was that? Oh, it's a grenade launcher.
I didn't kill anyone. Not one fucking person died. Not one person died. I find that hard
to believe. Weapon. Can create? No. What the? What was that? Who are these people?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. These are okay. The army of chaos is breaking you free,
but we'll have to fight our way out.
I don't. Just let him go for a fly.
Drop his gun. What an idiot. What an idiot. He let go of the gun. Ow. Oh, fuck. He's gonna kill me.
All right. Oh, oh, oh, oh. Nice. Did you see that? Somebody saw that. You guys saw that,
right? Did my computer turn off? Or did you see it? I got a rifle now.
I've got a group to the entrance. Send someone to extract him.
Extraction inbound. Objective locked. What? Thanks, Jerm. Very cool. You are so welcome,
man. You're so gosh darn welcome. All right. Now take it back to the instruction point.
That's not the right way. Back it up. Can I get in the car with you?
Oh, I'm the leader of your crew. Get out of the fucking car.
Like, let me drive. Why would you turn this music on?
I'm what? Is this a radio station that's playing right now? This guy's gonna have a really bad day.
Why would you turn into me? All right. Let me drive. Get out of the way.
How do I turn the fucking radio off? Thank God. I don't understand music, man. Let me complain
about something. What is with music now? Where the whole song is just I'm building up a fucking
power level. That's the whole it's just like, here we go. Here we go. It's getting a little
bit bigger. It's getting stronger. Here we go. Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes.
This is the sound. This is the sound. Here it comes. Here it comes. That's every song.
How many songs does it have to come out that are just
he's an out of touch mover? No, it's just everybody's everybody builds music.
Instead of making a song, they build up to a song and then the song ends.
All right, people. It's time to free yourselves. Come on. I can't. How am I going to get them?
We owe you so much. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Let's listen to it.
Isn't it amazing that we are using?
Instead of. Well, you know what I mean, though? It's you know what I mean.
No, no, no, no. I'm trying to get the helicopter over here.
It worked. It worked. Make sure he's dead. All right. Let's go. Where are my friends?
Forgetting this is not a shotgun. Who? What is it? There's a person right here.
All right, let's do it. OK. Can I see a little bit of hype in the chat?
I'll take this. All right, we get it. No, we didn't cover their escape. Oh, look at that. Hold on.
I got it. I got to turn on the fucking music. This doesn't have a radio. OK, that's fun. That's fun.
That was a fucking bit of Legos, apparently. Push it over. Ideas. What do we do?
I was hoping I could see if we could fall this way. Crush everyone. Yell about.
Now we're going to go like this.
Come on, use a grapple and pull the bridge down.
Nice.
Bridge is open.
Imagine how sick this would make you.
You didn't do that. All right, we're going to we're going to go on the tractor.
Can I fit everybody in the in the tractor here? This is just got to fall out of grade, by the way.
How do I pick somebody up?
Wait, hold on.
Oh, no. Battle bots. God damn it.
Oh, thank God it started to be over here. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Here we go. Thank God I can do it again. What? Really? I can't pick them up?
It's just toys. It really is. They just it's just bouncing toys. Just Cause 2 was the same way,
man. It was just fucking toys. Where is everybody? Toy Chest 2. What are you shooting at? I don't
even know. Fine. Take them down. Blow them up. Whatever. Who cares? Nothing even matters.
All right, I can put my face in this.
What? What?
Get out of here. Weapon chest. Oh, long scope. All right. Destroy the infrastructure. There's one
more. Where is it? Up there. Oh, this is going to be an epic moment.
No, I didn't get it. Okay, let's get out of here. Not even fucking close. All right,
cover the escape. All right, you're good. I got all three of us, right?
It's like I got hit in the face with an explosion. I think we lost one.
Lower the bridge. Who is dropping grenades on us? Where are these coming from? Who the
fuck is throwing these? They're disappearing out of the sky.
Where is he? Where is he? Is he on the boat? His face is fucking up the direction.
He comes down. All right, here we go. Okay, one of these guys, I'm going to turn on the fucking
jacks here, guys. Sorry. I had to turn it on for a minute. He's on my ammo, but I would have jacked
him. Oh no, you're going to die. I need something. How much health do you have? Stay okay. No,
no, no. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. No, no, no. Get out of the way. Out of the way.
You idiot. You're almost out. Who's left? I got to make sure at least one guy gets out.
Why are you walking up there? What are you doing? At least get in the car, dude. Get in the car. Can
you get in the car? Get in. That's the last group, Sargento.
He did it. That's the idea. Good work, people. We got one person. All right, so now we can open
the map and we were doing what was the mission we were doing. What the hell? We were doing
something. By clearing 1A extraction, you made it safe for the army to advance and secure the
Tierra del Cuapec region. And by causing chaos, you earned more squads which are now awaiting
your orders in the reserves. Ready to secure. This number indicates how many squads you need
from your reserves to secure the area. One. Two. Lower this cost by securing adjacent regions
and advancing already deployed squads instead of deploying new ones from your reserves.
Okay, let's get it. I win. This is what I was trying to do in the first place, but what is this?
The army of chaos is getting ready to retrieve intel from a black hand radar outpost, but before
they move, Amira needs a favor. All right, hold on a second here. Unlock mods. Gas. Choose different
gases for explosive effects. Helium, explosive, hydrogen. So I can make a balloon and explode it.
Fragile. Change the armor used on the airlifter. Fragile, invulnerable player, invulnerable enemies.
Okay. Float. Change how the airlifter moves. Float. Guided follow. Peak altitude. Change the
maximum altitude of the airlifter. Holy shit. I don't even need to see the other ones. Set what
the lifter will do at its peak altitude. You can hover it or pop. Okay, well, let's try this. Gas,
gas. Step on the gas. We got something new over here. Splash damage. Oh man. Oh, I only got one
kill. Let's go. Your support is on route. What happened? Did I, what did I do? Um, okay.
Got him. You actually made it over there? How the fuck did you do that, man?
I don't believe it. How many of these balloons is it going to take? It's pulling in every direction.
You're still fine up there. How is that even possible? Still just floating around.
Get over there. Still hasn't crashed. All right, it's my turn. I want to see how hard this is.
It's not even fucking hard. You're overreacting.
All right, where am I going? All right, get rid of the tethers. I just have a helicopter. All right,
so I can fire a missile or switch vehicle position. All right, I have 91 missiles.
I should probably call this chaos, right?
Why did that hurt me? You understand? I shot that thing and it blew me up. What's this fucking
thorns damage? I was supposed to do that. All right, cool. Somebody's got on a SAM site, aren't they?
Where?
Holy fuck.
Well, I just was playing around. All right, where am I going? Here, right here. Track it. Right here.
Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes.
If you're sitting down, get up. Dance now. Unless you're driving. In that case, just move your head.
Oh, sorry, cow.
I'm a monster. I'm not. I don't even know how I hit my head on the ground. That didn't make any
sense. Action. Action. Okay, start it. Just seems to happen every single time. You're right.
Hey, go sober up, Charlie. Get him working on some new pages with the frogs.
Hey, look at you, you handsome devil. Garland King, you've heard of me. No, but I've heard you can
help the army of chaos. Let's not worry about that now. Come on, walk with me. Rico. I love everything
about you, man. The look, the swagger, the leather. You're an artist. The Da Vinci of violence,
which is why I need you for this picture. I get to be in the movie. We'll work out the details.
This seems like it's going to be kind of fun. You see that barely floating rust bucket there?
See, I need it to careen through the water. My stuntmen bless their square jaws. They can take
a left hook, but they lack the touch of a true artiste. So here you take these and I want you.
Details. Just plant them on the rust bucket and blow it up, baby. Straight to the great dry dock
in the sky. Turn off motion blur? I don't think you can. Are you in? I suppose I could. Perfect.
We'll get your agent a copy of the contract. You don't have an agent. We'll get you an agent.
We're going to do amazing things together, doll. Okay. Hey, Charlie, fuck your story, all right?
Whoa. All right, I'm ready. I'll try to turn it off in this setting. Let's go to settings. I
thought I didn't see it there. Army of Chaos pilots. We'll pick... that was not long enough.
All right, so hold on. Let me hold on a second here. Edge fade. Is that doing it? That looks awful.
That looks three times worse. Put it on low? What if I do this?
Why is it always... all of it looks bad. Hold on. Global... maybe it's a global illumination.
I don't think it's that. Because everything looks just so ugly. Oh, whatever. All right,
grappling hook menu. Uh-huh. You now have a new loadout. Select loadout number C. Edit the loadout.
Add boosters to the tap column so that it activates when tapping F. Equip a booster with
high boost force. Tap here. Okay. Okay, we're looking for high force. Now the booster is
equipped. He's not reading our suggestions. What are you talking about? Shadow and motion blur is
the biggest FPS hog. No, we're not doing potato mode yet. Tell the boosters to... okay. So...
and then release. Aim at the marked area on the rust bucket and hope... but wait, are these
boosters though? Do I have to tap like F? Oh, okay. There it is. So that's it. Okay.
And that's our cue. Climb aboard, Rico. Out of here, people. Let's move.
Time for Gary's mod. Not even... Stunt on... what? Stunt on the van?
Cover Garland's escape. Wait, what do you mean their escape? What's wrong with you?
Oh, you're so high. I gotta catch you. I can catch you. I'll get you. I'll get you. I'll get you.
I'm gonna catch her. I'll catch her with my hands. I have to get her back over here.
Oh, now we're getting fired at. Where do these people come from? All right, let's go.
Don't let them wreck us. Don't... I won't let them wreck us. Don't worry.
I came here to shoot my next picture. My magnum opus.
It looks like a paradise, but everywhere you go, it's permits.
They only give you permits if you're Espinosa Telecom.
Espinosa Telecom. They got this place locked down tighter than a clam's ass and high tide.
What does that even mean? All right, we're fine.
Wish I had a DP in the car. You're doing beautiful work.
You close stuff up for a living. Most guys just pretend to do it. Let the effects department
handle the rest. Not you and me, Rico. We're a pair. Stick with me, kid.
Starring in my picture. And I get run over by the car.
Solis will love you. The world will love you.
Damn it. Where are we going? I'm gonna go. This game hurts my brain. I'm so sorry.
We just met and I'm already faking your death. Be a sport, sport. You're almost ready for the day.
Oh, no. Let go of that.
Get the black hand's attention. Damn it.
Guess I better find a black hand outpost. Holy shit. All right, I gotta.
That's how I always wanted to go. Are you kidding? I would get about my own death. Make it dramatic.
Should buy me a few hours. Is this far enough away? Is this far enough away?
Actual. Actually Garry's mod. Actually fucking Garry's mod. All right, let's go.
Lure them away. Make it look like they died in a big explosion. That's how I always wanted to go.
I can't talk what I just did, lady. All right, here we are. Make it look bad. All right, lure
them away. Watch it. Watch it. I have to. She's going off into the water. I'm so much cooler.
Well, you somehow with even with nitrous attached, you are faster than.
Now to wreck this van, I guess. Okay, wreck the van. That wasn't enough to wreck the van.
The van is still fine. Not good enough. Get the fuck out of my way. I'm trying to destroy myself.
Oh, I'm supposed to get out of the van. Get out of the van. I did it. I wrecked. I did it.
No, get back there quick. It's me, Dutch Vanderland. Move. Move. Move. That guy was
aiming his wrist completely backwards. All right, I gotta tap it. I'm ready to go over the jump
and then I'm gonna get out. I'm not gonna be inside. Why don't I just skip that? I'm gonna
skip the whole fucking thing. Now to wreck this van, I guess. See, like I just skipped all that
bullshit. It's driving around the mountain. Add thrusters to it. I can't get in the van.
It's gonna land. I'm gonna die. We're good.
All right, it worked.
I want to get on the bus. Help Garland shoot her opus. Search the map for stunts and scene shots.
Pretty cool feature. That's what I was looking for. This bike is fast.
What are you doing? Why are you like this? Why are you like this? I don't even care.
Damn it. Tornado. What do you mean tornado? Tornado. Tornado. Tornado. Oh, there's a tornado over
there. There is a. Cool. Let's take a look. Thanks for the boost. I appreciate it. All right,
let's go to the tornado. I lost control of the bike. Oh, fuck. That is a suicide drive. That
guy still has a fucking... I can't even pay attention. Do you see that bird explosion?
My tire is fucked up. Hold on. I gotta spray it now. I wish you would just get out of the fucking
way. Fine. You want to go to the tornado too? That's fine with me. New bike. This is a fast one.
How far away is the tornado? Looks pretty far away. Oh shit. Okay, it worked. It actually worked.
How do I lose the police? Oh, this is not the way that I want to be going. This way.
No, no, no. Put that away. It's safer to be this way and somehow you are right next to me. Don't
ask me how. Here's the tornado. This guy's still right behind me. I was gonna say. No way. I can
take a second here to make sure I get the right spot. No, he is right behind me. I'm not even
stuck on here. I'm taking them on. Here there's a helicopter. It's still chasing me. I am surprised
you can even get over here. Okay. We're almost at the tornado. It's right here. There it is.
Oh, easy though. I'm safe, right? This is so far away. You actually made it. Well,
all right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We're so close.
What can you even do here? Can I be like a storm chaser? All right. Here it is. Holy shit.
Do these people know there's a tornado on the road? I don't, nobody seems to really give a shit.
If I live, if I go in here. Oh my goodness. This is huge. Okay. I'm in it. I made it.
That's a wingsuit in there. What the fuck was that? Is that a blimp?
Helicopters. Why would you even fly over here? What the hell are you thinking?
Look at all these cars.
Oh no, no, no. Don't die again. All right. I'm going to be flying for this.
All right. Wingsuit activated. Oh, all your organs flying out of your body right now.
No. Shit. Activate the wingsuit again. Quick. Whoa. I just scraped the ground.
Holy shit. I'm going all the way up. How high can I go? Is that it? How high am I?
I'm not even sure where I am. Holy fuck. That's crazy. I'm going up even higher. All right. This
is where we Spider-Man Empire State Building. That's fun. Look at this. All right. Let me do
one more thing. I just want to be all the way at the top. I want to lose control. I don't have a
wingsuit on. I just want to get off this and be flailing around. Like that. I guess it doesn't
matter. Hold on. Can I not get back in like this? I guess not. I'm trying to stay in the ragdoll,
but it looks like you just float. Where do we end up? I'm not sure. This is chaos though,
apparently. I'm causing chaos. Did I get out of the eye of the storm? No. I'm going around again.
There's a helicopter in here now. Where's the helicopter? Where'd the helicopter go?
I have to get a plane into the tornado. Oh, there's a helicopter.
Plane. Plane. We have a problem. We have a big problem. I can't do anything. Control. E. Space.
Alt. Click. Q. I can't do anything. Can I pull a gun out or something? Stay in ragdoll. Hold control.
Hold control. I can't do anything. Can I like eat a grenade or something?
Oye Rico, you meet that guy yet? He might be able to help. No, I didn't meet that guy yet.
I will. All right, I need to get out of this. How do I get... I don't want to like exit the game.
I will. Fish gave me a few minutes. I need to grab onto something. Is this just a table flying
around? Just wait for it to blow over. Will this disappear? Oh wait, here comes a blimp.
The blimp is going to get sucked in. And then I'm going to grapple onto the blimp. It seems
like the only thing I'm able to do. Come on, pull it in close enough. Or even another helicopter.
I gotta... No, it's flying around too erratically. Table. Can I grab the table? Okay, I'm going to go
to... I'm going to try to grapple the table. I can get it. It's going to be close. I just had the
indicator. Okay, hold on. Fuck. I can't grab it. I need to grab that. Fucking god damn it.
I need another table. I need to grapple a table. Or a tree? I had the indicator on the fucking table.
Don't worry, in like another couple minutes a table will come out. Come on, up higher.
I can use the grapple hook though. That's really important. I just need something that I can grab
to fly up here. Like that. That hunk of metal right there. Come on. Go up. Can't grab the tree. This
should be the loading screen of the game. I'm so mad that I couldn't grab that table when I had a
chance. The tornado is moving, so maybe we'll get another opportunity. The tornado is moving. Am I
going towards the direction of this? Pass through the ring faster than 70 miles per hour. I think
I'm going that fast. I hear a noise. Can I grab that? I'm not low enough. That sounds like a table.
Can I booster myself? No, I can't. I wish I could. Debris? Here comes debris. Might have a chance
here in a second. Debris on the way up. You can see a table? Any tables in there? Order a boat?
Can I order something? I'm getting lower to the ground. Get it? I can't grapple it. No, I'm too
high. Almost. I was so close. Press E? I can't do anything. Can't you scrape? I can't do anything.
All I can do is spin around in a circle. Yeah, there is one way to escape this. That's a table
coming up through the vent here. Did I miss the table? Did I really? No, I didn't. What a great
stream. All right, I'm just going to fast travel. Wait, did I just get up? Table right there?
All right, I'm gonna go here. How do I fast travel? I don't think I even can. What the fuck am I?
What's happening? No, I'm not. I have to get out on my own. I can't use voice commands.
What do you mean you can't use voice commands? I just read somebody's chat room message.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. I just saw something right here. Somebody wrote that. We're going over water right now.
There's nothing here. I missed my opportunity like twice. Can't do it to trees. Go into the
tornado. I can't really control where I'm going. I can't. I have to stop this. I have to stop this
right now. Somebody just wrote I'm getting sick to my stomach and that's where I have to. I gotta
like make sure I don't make somebody throw up. I'm making people sick. Wait. I have to get out of
here. I have to get out of here guys. There's no more. This is not fun anymore. This is just
bad. This is not fun. There's no tables to grab onto. We're going over a couple of houses.
There's an opportunity right here when we go over this house. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Right there. Come on. Turn this way. Come on. See it? You see it right? You see it. You see it. You
see it. Come on. You see it. I do. Come on. There comes another blimp. Get to the top.
Give me ins... It didn't get it. What? How did it not get that? I... I'm out. I got out. All right.
We're good. I feel better. Time to respawn in the tornado. Now I need to get a plane
fly into it. That's a really good idea. So let me track down a plane. Are you telling me that guy
gets away? That guy gets away? The guy on the motorcycle gets the fuck away? But not the guy
in the 3000 pound car? I need a plane. How do I get a plane? Is there like an airfield or something
around here? Wingsuit stunt. Car stunt. Speed stunt. You can order it. Get one from your airdrop.
That doesn't exist. There's a plane in the airport. Where's an airport? Airport. That was a plane
just crashing. I feel like if I wait long enough, a plane will just... It's me. I just have to go
somewhere and just look in the sky. All right. What about over here? I just heard a plane. What
if I get up here? Right there. Come here. Come on. Pinpoint fucking accuracy. And was it worth it?
Was it worth it in the end? Give me a fucking plane. He actually got out of that. What a bunch
of dog shit. Get me up here. Will you get up there, dude? What are you doing? You're driving me nuts.
That's really fucking funny. I'm ready for a plane.
Apparently not ready for the plane to drive by me.
Oh, I'm so upset right now. Another one's gonna just drive by, right? This is like the plane drive
by zone. The tornado's gone. There's no more tornado. There's no point to do this right now.
Okay. Come here, you motherfucker. What the fuck? Here's my chance. Get over here. Fly over here.
Do I have... I'm gonna have to... I got a drastic... I'm right here, man. I'm right here.
I did it too, man. I right-clicked. I was gonna drive right into the fucking rock.
What? Did they crash into each other? Why are you driving that close to the water?
What's wrong with you? You're skimming the water right now. There's no reason to be doing what
you're doing. It's gonna go in the water. It's gonna fall in the water. All right, let's go.
Airport. No, it's too far. Just drop. Just respawn. Move on. Okay, let's take a look at the minimap
for a second and see what we got. I need... Okay, so we got some stunt missions.
Cantos. That looks like an airport. Found one. Okay, I just gotta go this way to Cantos.
I need to make a waypoint. That's a really strange waypoint marker that I have to make.
What even button is that? Toggle waypoint. Tap... What is that? It's space. Okay, I was like,
what is that on the keyboard? I thought it was an underscore.
Okay, wait. That guy's a bike. No, forget the bike.
Okay, here we go.
You suck.
There we go. I can't do it. I'm trying to go too fast. There we go.
Straight ahead. Every time he says, here we go, is when he hits the ground.
I was looking at chat. That didn't count. That didn't do anything.
All right, we're almost there. That sounded like an elephant.
Do something cool. I can't. I can't do anything. I fucking swear to God.
What the fuck? All right, so where's the airport? Over here. Almost there. Airport.
I fucking hate myself.
So where the fuck is the airport? It's like right over the bridge here.
So like over here. Behind the hill. All right, let's get a plane.
Is this... Do these things work? Could you actually do this?
All right, plane. There's a plane right there. Can I get in... Can I get... Is that a plane I can get?
What happened to you? It really is just... Oh look, a little guy. Let's take it.
How do you fly planes? I have no idea. Hold C or Z to turn. C or Z? I'm holding E.
Control. Okay, it's control. Off we go. Why am I going backwards?
That doesn't make any logical sense. Why am I going backwards?
Okay, control is reverse. If you were curious. Shift is drive plane. Z is turn.
No, it's not. I know. I'm going to clear it. I'll clear it. Okay, here we go.
So how do I pull up? What's pull up? Oh wow. Apparently that.
Get big plane.
Hey, Rico. Are you talking to me? Okay, so W. Why am I not pulling up? Why is it not working?
That did the complete opposite last time. Can I ding my head? Can I ding my head?
I sure can. I sure can. Let's try it again.
I'm running out of planes. It's okay. Just... So S. Is it S or W? It is W.
Or is it S? Okay, it's S. And then W is...
How in the name of fucking God are you supposed to control? Okay, Z and C is just tilt. Okay,
I got it. All right, we're gonna find a tornado. Switch vehicle position. What does that do for me?
Oh, it puts... Okay, it's still going. Don't worry, it'll come back. It'll come back and I'll get it.
Wait a second. Hold on. All right, fine. Never mind. It just exploded. I don't know where it
exploded, but it did. I'm going very fast. All right. You thought I was gonna bump on the ground,
didn't you? Nope. You can't take the big one. What the fuck was that? What? No, I can take a big,
huge plane. All right, I'm gonna do this in line. Oh, I'm not doing anything. I'm waiting for this
other plane to take off before I do anything. I can't turn the fucking plane. Earth. I'm almost
there. Okay, here we go. Let's go. How do I take this? This thing is so huge. I don't even know
how to go with this. How can I go? I'm losing control. I don't know if I'm... Am I upside down?
Am I up or down? Does anybody know if I'm up or down? I think I'm up. I can't tell which way the
plane is going. I don't know. I think we're on... Which plane are we on? Are we upside down?
I don't know. I am. All right, let's go this way. I am upside down.
Oh, it's still going. Why does it keep zooming out? Do you see what that's doing? Am I at an
unreachable place? I can't even tell. Am I getting closer or further away from this object?
Oh, the world's coming in too quick. Oh, holy shit. Okay, I'm starting to be able to see the
world in a 3D plane. All right, now I get it. Now I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
Oh, give me this fucking thing. All right, well, you got blocked by the sneeze guard.
One thrust. It's hot. All right, I'm ready.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait. Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Why is this tipping over? It's got to be on the edges like here.
Okay, I'm ready.
That's better, right?
Balloons. What do you mean? What are you talking about balloons?
No, no, no. Dude, I want to fly, man. I want to get going. Okay, here we go.
In three, two, one. Let's take it off. Okay, well,
didn't really do what I thought it was going to do. At least I flew.
Jet ski. Thank you. I'll take it. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Okay, come here. Oh, fuck. That was mean. Kind of a mean guy though. How can I? Never mind. I thought
it was a... What? Is somebody in that boat? Oh, what the fuck is this person doing? What's wrong
with you? Why would you drive like this? I need to stay on here. You're still going. Okay. At what
point are you going to be done with this? I should be asking myself the same question.
And I didn't get her. Didn't get her. Nope, sorry. You just turned her boat into wood.
Where's the panel? I want the balloon. Okay, booster. Oh, let's see. So what can I do here for
airlifter? Low, medium, or high airlift? Let's try it. Let's tap. Okay, is this equipped?
Kidding me. We're gonna let that stop you. Let's go, lady. You and me. On a grand adventure.
Oh, there we go. There we go. I need more up here. No, I need him in the back. I mean,
in the back, in the back, in the back. Where is she? Is she still in the... Is she still here? I
can't see her. I gotta get some in the back. She's still here with me. The boat is smoking,
but she's still in here. All right, that levels it up. Why are we falling? There we go.
Look at that. Get some back here. Oh, that hit her in the head. How do I take this off?
How do I take that one off? How do I take this one off her back? Oh, there's two. There are two
inside of her. Is she trying to drive? How do I get that off? Oh, wait, she's attached.
She's attached. I forgot. I can't just... Oh, how do I get out of here? Can I... I gotta,
I gotta like pick her up. I need to get on the bottom of the boat. I want on the bottom of the
boat, please. Oops. Oh, fuck. I gotta... Bring it down. No, bring it down.
Okay, everything's good. All right, just... You just drive the boat again. You were doing
a good job driving. Why are the three helicopters just hanging on over here?
I feel like I need to see this. I need to get over there. I need to understand why they're there.
Ow. What the fuck are they doing? It's so bright, but I need to see. Ah, I can't even look at it.
I need to get over there though. They're shooting at each other. What are they? Why are they firing
at each other? Turn off bloom. Hold on. What is it? Which... Where's bloom? I don't see bloom. That's
the only... All right. Global illumination? Well, that didn't do anything. I need to see how this
plays out. Just don't look at the screen for like five minutes. Somebody got a hit on someone.
The middle one took a little damage. Aren't these all on the same team? Why would they be doing this?
They're invincible somehow. What if I take them down? Well, I was allowed to destroy it somehow.
Fucking idiots. I don't know how to fly this. Dammit! No! Fly it! Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Is it spent? It's shipped! Yeah! All right, back to civilization. Switch the camera a little bit. Is
it like a cinematic camera? No. Propeller isn't moving too slow, but that's a scientific reason
for that. Tornado. You got it. What was the last time we did a mission? I don't remember a mission.
I need to pitch this a little bit so we can start to get some traction here.
Are there no more bullets in anything? What? Don't do the awuga. Go. Oh my fucking god! Why am I
so stupid? Get there. No! Get there, get there. It's still savable. I pressed fucking E and I've
j- oh my god. I hate- I hate it when I do things like that. There's another cover-up. All right,
hijacked vehicle. This one. Okay, let's get it. Grappled to the bottom of the ocean on it. I won't
be able to swim back up, man. We didn't get to fly into this one. Well, to be fair, we probably saved
ourselves at least 45 minutes of nothing. Mm-hmm. I was gonna get all the way there.
Who's the guy that I need to hijack?
Oh fuck. You're good. All right, that was a fun little thing. Now we're all safe.
I got jumped out of the car. Why would you jump out of the car?
Why are you jumping out of the car? Wait a second. Are you gonna jump off the motorcycle?
You idiot. Nice bike. Did he do a wheelie? I was trying to fucking crush that guy.
Ah, just get in the car. I can't take this button. Okay. I'm not looking at chat ever again for the
rest of my life. Never. For the rest of my whole life. That's fair. Airport nearby. No,
I gotta do a mission. I have to do something. We've been doing dog shit for the last like two
straight hours. I don't even know what the first mission of the game is. Is this traversable?
Yep. That's the point of the game. Well, yeah, right? I mean, this road. Have the lady got up?
Whatever. He did so many spins. She didn't even get a hit. She just pretended to get hit.
What exploded? Why was there an explosion? All right, make our way this way. Start the Lapa project.
Why is it telling me to go the other way? I'm going the right way, right? I don't think a Subaru
Outback is gonna make it over here. What? I'm trying to get in the car.
I'm trying to just die. All right, I want the car back. Give it to me. Give me the car back. There's
one balloon popped. Two balloons popped. How many is it gonna take? Last one coming in.
I'm trying to... I don't even know where this is trying to tell me to go. Scripted. Well, yeah,
that one was. It's so much safer to do this. This is all the way across the map. Holy shit. Thank God.
This is really that far away. Oh my fucking God. Why am I going here? Why did I decide that this
was a good idea? Okay. Anyways, I think that instead of that, get there by a plane? Now you're
thinking. Now you're thinking. End of stream voice? What are you talking about? Wait, what the hell
are you guys talking about? I heard it? What do you mean you heard it? I'm not stopping the stream
right now. All right, this time we're gonna get there quick with a plane. All right, plane. Not a
big one. Just a little one. Just one big enough to get us where we want to go. One right here.
No, the stream's not ending. There we go. Let's move. This will get us there very quickly.
There we go. Straight it out. Don't go upside down. Just get there and be fine. No, I'm not gonna fly
upside down again. Press E for turbo. You know, that would be very interesting if that existed,
but it just doesn't. I'm sorry. Fly upside down into the tornado. I know it's a tornado,
but don't get me distracted. Hold E and get on the roof. I'm only gonna try this. No.
Hold E and get on the roof. What does L mean? What do you mean L? L? L. Oh, I had to press up.
All right, that's kind of cool. That's cool. All right. Can I make it through? Do you think I can
get through the tornado? What do you think? Oh, already a struggle. I made it. I'm good. I'm
currently... am I out running it? Yeah, I got through. Pretty good nausea stream. All right,
that was a good stream. All right, time to go home. Just kidding. Okay, almost there. Start
the Elapa project. How come this doesn't have a horn? I'm gonna pee my pants. I should probably
do something about that, right? Press E for horn. E? Can I walk on this? Yeah, you can. Okay,
I can't like walk around out here. Can I go on the wing? This is so dumb. Wow, don't do that.
I gotta go there. See, if this is a real plane, this would just hit me right in the face.
Okay, see you later. We're gonna go... end of the plane voice. Yeah, end of the plane voice.
What did you do? Oh my goodness. Okay, here we are. All right. Okay, so I think... okay.
I... okay, so looks like... I'm just gonna piss. I'll be right back.
All right, back. All right, so that brings us to... that brings us, unfortunately, here
to the... I can't... people are gonna actually leave. A bunch of people are probably gonna leave.
People just see that in the image and they just leave.
I probably shouldn't do that. That's like not even like... okay, so...
how do I do this? Oh, it's over there.
Right here. 40 people just left. Oh, damn it. Whatever. It's all right.
It's all right.
Pilots. You guys... I thought you guys were giving me shit.
Request... home to the free spirit of breathing people have... Request travel. Select an available
pilot. Each pilot will need to refuel after their flight, making them unavailable. Oh.
Really? Okay. Do you know what would be funny right now? If Jerm was like...
didn't open his parachute and he just landed on the ground.
Where the fuck do you want me to go? Oh, no. It need to be Izzy.
I'll get there eventually. Don't worry.
All right. I need a chopper. Open... there really is a supply drop. I can't fucking believe it.
Edit... open the supply drop menu with three. Pick an available pilot and edit their loadout.
Oh my god. Civilian vehicles. Okay. R, please.
Sending you coordinates. I forgot it was...
shipped. Why Izzy? Nice city. Poor city. Always been that way.
Do you think... okay. Do you think I can jump out and then grab and come back in?
All the money is there. So, people in Kuya get by other ways. Like selling... what? I can't fly
this thing. Oh, you turn on the radio. Need music. Read my mind. Who is driving this?
Uh, I can't get back in. I made it. I don't know who was flying that before, but that was weird.
I can't fly it. Can she fly this thing? No. Radio, right?
What does she want for a station? Oh, here it comes. Oh, what does every song ever made in 2010
Beyond? We're dropping fast. Listen. Here it comes. All right, let's go. Nice.
Oh, shit. Can she die? I thought she was immune. This is taking us a long time.
Boosters? No, but that'll ruin everything. Now she's not gonna move. Why have you guys told me
to do this? She'll make it eventually. How's it going, Izzy? Look at all these hackers.
But none of that matters unless we can disable Yappa's defenses. Izzy and I have been working
on that. All of these facilities house prototype weather cores, and each core is connected to
Yappa's defense network. Towers with artillery? Si. If we can plant a virus in those weather cores,
we can send a message up the network causing malfunctions in the tower's machinery.
Inside the server room. You don't have to be in there. You could be like in your bedroom.
It's so hot in there. You know how hot one server gets? They have server farms in fucking
Antarctica because it gets so hot in there. You can't physically be inside this room.
What's that? Information on a place called La Masmora. It's a prison hidden in the desert.
Yeah, that's true. I think my uncle Lanza might still be alive. If he is, he's being held there.
And he can help us get into Zora Uno. He helped your father build project Yappa.
Get out. If he's still alive, I'll find him. Just lower the temperature of the room. Good luck.
Here is Sona 3. According to Izzy, it's not on the network, but I have an old friend Cesar.
He has a theory that might help us. Then let's hear what he has to say. And this is Sona 2.
We don't know much about that facility. Are you ever going to answer this?
I'm not an agency man anymore. Rico, those coordinates are close. Look.
Nice. That can't be a coincidence. Like I was just on a normal NPC room. Check it out.
Just carrying a box. I'm sending you all the data you'll need to your AR lens.
Good. Let's start hitting Oskar when it hurts. I skipped that at the end of the cutscene,
but that's okay. Okay, here we go. Bingo. I accomplished it. Let's take out their satellite.
In fact, that might even be our satellite, but take it out anyways.
Not hacking in that room anymore, are you? All right, so now there's a wingsuit mission right
here. What do I have to do about that? What is this? Wingsuit stunt. How do I do that?
Do I fly through that in the wingsuit? I did it. Oh my leg. I gotta go through the whole thing.
Okay, hold on. So how am I supposed to be able to see that? You know what I mean?
I gotta start from all the way back here then. So turn this way. Here we go. One, two, nope.
I have to activate it up there. I'm not even doing it right. I have to actually be in a
helicopter and activate it up there. Give me five seconds. How the hell?
Wait, what? Chat? No, chat. No, what do you mean chat? No, what happened?
I need to be going way faster than that. What about like this? Can I just...
I have to be up in the air. I just locked myself in a fucking prison.
Can I grab that from here? Don't take your rage out on that guy. Rage? Oh fuck it. I don't even
care. I'm gonna get like 15 points. Where the hell am I going now? I feel like it's something else
I need to do. Request travel. No, wait. What? I can just go there? I gotta get this waypoint marker
off. Go back to the tornado? No. Okay, here we go. Track this one. Fly time. Wing suit. If I crash,
I'll turn the stream off. That's how you know I'm not going to. You guys don't have that much
confidence in my ability at all, huh? Ah, good night everybody. No. Thought I was gonna crash
right there, didn't you? I'm gonna go through this weird valley here. What's this? Oh shit,
he's gonna turn the stream off.
Escape? Who am I being chased by? Oh, here it comes! Here comes the beat!
Who am I escaping from? Who am I chasing?
No, wait! Hey! No! Oh! Fucking E! E! E! E! Oh, I'm so annoyed right now.
Has this whole country lost its mind? Oh, my goodness gracious. Just get over here.
Where the fuck is that J? Get off! Get off! Wait, why is there...
All right, I am gonna press E here because I want to go across.
That's not a crash. Wing suit in the water. I'm just gonna get close enough I can grab the edge.
Okay, we are getting close.
I'm keep trying to just go as fast as I can. How far away is this for real? It's... I'm so fucking
far away. I really might supposed to get in a car and drive there, seriously.
How am I ever gonna traverse this? What the fuck? Jesus! Why? What the fuck are you doing?
What was that? I'm almost there.
There it is! Something exploded. Is this on low settings? No, not yet.
We're so close. This isn't low settings? No, it's not. Made it to your house. I hope that wasn't an NPC
giver. Whatever the fucking quest giver.
All right, so what's the mission here? Reach the waterfall cave.
No, I can't just shoot everybody. It's not funny. All right, I need to get up there.
Reach the waterfall cave. You got it.
What? Oh, I get the stuff down here, right? Nice. Take the retract motor.
What do I get for this? A new unlockable? Do I get to... Is this a tracking device?
Both cave doors.
This is Avi Huerta. I'm sorry we weren't able to meet. Please, better be worthy than you go.
Retract it. I promise you. What the fuck does this do?
Set the retract force to high in the auto column, okay? It'll work automatically after releasing.
All right, open the door. Am I supposed to just pull this? Hold? I don't get it. Aim at the door
and hold to start tether, okay? Aim at the wall and release tether, like this wall.
Oh, it just pulls the... All right, I thought it was gonna do something else.
I was expecting it to be something else. That's just a regular tether.
Aim at the other door. Do I really have to do that?
This is some place, Avi. At least six centuries old. Oh shit, I gotta fly this little go-kart.
Uh-huh. I promise. Ain't everything. There's a map inside the plane. You can get my coordinates
from there. Got your map. Where am I going? This thing's kind of cool, actually.
I'd like to begin with where you're coming from. Back without the hidden behind those doors for a
reason. I had to open both doors to get this little thing out of there. The Espinozas didn't
like anyone challenging their narrative. I was imprisoned. My wife won't speak to me.
My reputation is ruined. Stop blowing things up over there, you dummies.
I made allies in prison, both seen the cracks in the facade. Now they help me uncover the truth.
And what do you need me for? I believe I have discovered the path to the tomb last ruler of
the Prius-Pinoza people of Sols. I wonder what's in there. According to the history books,
Patrongo was executed for countless murders, but I believe the reality is more complex.
Did I just GTA spawn the same car like four times? To who? What the hell was that? The Espinozas.
Their monopoly. If this part of history is not true. All right, should I make it all low settings
and then put the title, everything on ultra? But just cause for gameplay. Ultra settings. PC,
1080p, 60fps. Do I have to land this? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Do I have to land this?
How do I land this? How do I land this? Do I have to land this there? Excuse me.
How do I land my hovercraft? Oh fuck, I have to land this there.
Um, I don't know how am I supposed to land this there. I'll try. This fucking Peewee Herman did
this in one of his movies. I'm certain of it. Oh boy. I thought I just failed the mission.
It was a landing strip? Oh, your stash is safe. Anything else that you'd like to say? Sweat stains.
It's a relic. A figure of Otorongo. Mid 16th century. Wait, is that? There was a
mission here. Okay. Retract the ancient lever. Ancient lever is down here. Okay.
Put the giant cartoon lever down. That sounded like something. I see it.
A giant head. Rico, follow it. I can tell what kind of day this is going to be.
Oh, okay. Can I get on top of it? Can I just run with this thing?
Come on, let me do like the cartoon log thing. Um, I don't- I'm on it. I was.
That wuma is an ancient sculpture of an honored person. This one may be Sumac's visage.
Avi, big guy and I are at the floor of the cave.
What do you see? There's a mechanism in the ground. Looks about the same size as the head.
It's a giant lock, Rico. The wuma is the key. Can you use the retract to get the wuma to the mechanism?
Why not? I'll try.
Rico, use the retract motor to get the wuma to the lock.
I'll get it. It'll get in there. Perfectly fine. Just small injuries.
That hit me right in the fucking head, too.
Fine, I'll do it the dumb way. I'll do it the way that you want me to do it,
video game. Come on over here. Get in there.
If something happened, a door opened up. This is a Nickelodeon game show.
Where Sumac sleeps eternal. Rico, please.
Where he sleeps eternal. There's a human skull with a candle inside. Light it and be ready for anything.
There's text on the wall. What the fuck happened? I'm buried. Only five beds remain.
That mean anything to you? Get this thing open.
It sounds like a single line from a longer text. Get it open. If it's gonna screw over Espanosa, count me in.
Bueno, others close to Otorongo will likely have the other lines. The tombs of his family, his advisors.
I'll keep my eyes open. Help him uncover the truth.
Seek out the hidden tombs of Otorongo's family and advisors helping him, and associates will earn you mod points.
That's good. Everyone thought I was stuck. Sorry, I'm not stuck. I'm absolutely fine, but
you don't think I'm gonna take this thing for a balloon ride. You're out of your mind.
I'd say we probably make sure it's balanced, otherwise this whole thing's gonna start turning around.
I need to just make a circle.
Fire it up with a slingshot.
How many D's can I have? Ten? It's ten maximum.
Away we go. My goodness.
I can't. It's not gonna go. Put boosters underneath it.
I mean, it's gonna fly all over the place, but I'll try it. Can I move it with my hands? No.
All right, so here's what's gonna have to happen. I'm gonna put- let's get up there.
Let's put balloons. Stay up there, dude.
Okay, let's balloon it to get it off the ground.
And then once it's off the ground,
we'll put the crusters underneath.
Okay.
Crusters are A.
Don't hit me, please.
God, this is- this is gonna be hard to do this without getting crushed.
It's reaching the height limit. With these on it, it would- it definitely will not. It'll go flying through fucking air.
What am I doing? Hold on to my spine.
What? I don't get it. What the hell?
Is it not on anymore?
Hold on. Was it- the wrong fucking thing was on. God damn it, really. I thought it was A.
Let's go.
All right, here we go.
Change the height limit? Change height limit?
Does it have- is it on the balloons?
Yeah, but I mean, I have to- I have these things on right now. Shouldn't that not even matter anymore?
Air height limit.
Air lifter.
I mean, it's-
Where do I do that? This is the tractor.
Loadout B controlled. How the fuck do I edit mods, right? Okay.
Peak altitude is at medium.
No limit. Okay.
So then I should just get on top of it then.
No, fuck. I just got hit by the ball.
Whoa.
All right, slow down, slow down, slow down, slow down, slow down, slow down, slow down. Let's just try to do it with balloons now.
Because if the height limit is off, then maybe I can just fly out.
Right? Wouldn't that make sense? Oh fuck. Jesus, I don't know it's gonna happen this quickly. Fuck.
Oh, no!
How high went so high so quickly?
All right, where is it?
Where's the ball? Okay, I deleted all the- there it comes. Okay.
Am I- am I out of the way? I don't know if I'm in the way or not. Nope. I'm good.
It's a fucking asteroid.
All right, let's
settle down, settle down. I didn't know it was gonna happen that quickly. I gotta do it in the right place.
Gonna find like the center of the ball. This is fine right here.
Right in the nose.
Okay, now wait a second before I do anything else. Oh no, right here.
Oh shit.
What?
We're still going up.
We're still going through the clouds. I don't think we've even started a descent. I don't think there is a descent.
No, yes, there is. Oh fuck, it's descending.
It's going fast. Ah, I got another balloon. Another balloon?
We're going really fast.
I don't- we're going so fast. I can't even fucking do anything.
Whoa!
What?
That just went a thousand miles per hour.
Oh my god.
That speed was just increasing the whole time.
Where is it though? Let me see it. Is it- did it fall back down?
No, it's gone. Did it land in the jungle? Fuck, really?
I don't see it anywhere. It's gone.
Oh well, that was fun.
That thing did not have a terminal velocity. It just kept going faster and faster. It's in the hole.
No, it's not.
That's not- that's not it.
It's not in the hole.
Really? I went all the fucking way back down here.
What the fuck? Where did you guys even come from? Why did a fucking hundred animals just spawn?
What are you people doing? What are you doing?
Save him. Oh shit, save- I can save him. You're right. Hold on. I can save him. Where's the balloon? All right, save.
Are you telling me the water is too strong for this?
What's it gonna take to pull you out of here, man? Why are you connected to the-
Get him out! Get him out!
Hold on, is he gonna fall back down?
The theory would be he would be falling back down, right?
Okay, I'm fucking being a psycho. I gotta get out of this cave.
Like, what the fuck am I doing?
What the hell do I even have to do now? Okay, we've got a helicopter stunt.
Speed stunt. Find the rock or riot. All right, hold on. Let me do this first.
This is gonna be un-fucking-bearable, you guys understand that, right? I can't even fit it on here.
Oh my fucking god, it really looks like a Nintendo 64 game. Well, I need to change- hold on, I gotta change the title.
I gotta change the title to, like,
Just Cause 4.
3DS.
This is a lie, though. How long can I keep this up? But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're gonna take this a little bit further. Hold on. I'm gonna put a- I'm gonna put a 3DS on the screen.
Okay, I need just, like, a nice open 3DS image. All right, that looks pretty good. Yeah, this one looks pretty good.
See if we can get it on there. Yeah, okay.
Save image.
Okay.
Did it work?
Can you see it?
Okay.
Just give me a moment.
It needs to be a little bit bigger. It needs to be a little bigger.
You know what I mean? Like, I can't just be that. Like, anyway, like, that's a little bit better.
All right, that looks pretty good. Maybe a little bit lower to get the edge there.
Facecam on the bottom. I don't have my facecam plugged in. Do it. I- I can't.
No, we need, like, a picture of Super Mario.
Man, this actually feels really good on the 3DS. Something I was, uh,
kind of shocked to see.
You know, I've been in games journalism for a long time, but man, the 3DS version, this does hold up.
This is a clean, uh, 60 fps.
Put a one minute delayed video of Just Cause on the bottom.
No, no, no, no. Guys, what are you- what are you talking about here? Hold on.
Why you just- excuse me. If this was- if this was not a fucking bullshit joke.
Print screen, please.
This is- the map is down there. If you- if this is gonna be legitimate, I mean, it's gotta be legitimate then.
Okay, let me just open up paint.
All right.
Too bad. I can't just, like, record.
Me. No, that's gonna- that would take so long. Okay, save as PNG. That looks fine.
We're gonna have to shrink this a little more. Okay, how does that look?
It's a little skewed. It's because this is tilted, so it doesn't fit that well. I need to angle it. I can't.
Tilt it in paint?
You- I can tilt that in paint. What? How the fuck do you do that?
Free transform it into a trapezoid.
The skew tool?
Skew? I see rotate, resize, crop, resize.
Skew? What?
Skew it- how many degrees? Like 10? No, minus five. Vertical? We should go vertical, right? So we need a
vertical skew of, like, five. That kind of fucks it all up, though. What about this at five?
No, that's kind of fucked up looking.
Uh, no, that doesn't work. Can I skew an OBS? Let's see. I don't think I can.
Maybe filter?
No. No, that's just the way it is. Just gonna have to be like this. Just use the 2DS.
Oops-a-daisy. Well, it's just gonna have to be like this. Shift and grab. No, shift grab just does that. It's all right.
Close enough. Wait, oh, I need hands, too, though. What the fuck? Okay, hold on. Save image.
Hand.
Run the desktop. That's fine. Okay, hold on.
Oh fuck, it's not keyed out, though. No, it's not gonna work. Never mind.
Never mind. It's too much.
What did I just do? Oh, did I just delete it? Did I just, like, exit the game?
Uh, this is very hard to play this, but let's play. Here we go.
Holy fuck, I actually got it. He play looking at OBS? No, I'm playing on the big screen that looks like
it's this so much aliasing. It's unbelievable.
Now, let's go do a mission. Is it so hard to point this? I don't even know what the cursor is.
Watch it. 160p for the authentic experience. I need to pick a mission.
Uh, here's one. I can't read that.
Let me try as hard as I can.
Agency distress beacon. An agency distress signal has pinged
who grappling hook over since
the
stufafone at
Ilapa
That can't be
evidence
loves
When the source of the beacon
All right, you got it. Why am I? What happened to my momentum? Oh
Where's my fucking momentum? Whatever
Okay, that was odd. Can I get on your car or is it not gonna let me do this?
Right, okay that you know, sure i'll take this one that sounds like a fun place that sounds good
Like the real the 3ds port really is like just a little too buggy for me. I think
Gotta go this way
Turn on music
The game honestly looks better like this, uh, I'm gonna I'm gonna send a disagree here
That's not authentic though. Hold on. Give me one more second because that's not authentic. It's about to be though
Okay, um
We need
one of these
Hold on a second. Let's see how that sounds
Another a little bit here. Hold on
Okay
Tell me how that changes things
Wow
Go worse. I need I need to know what that sounds like man. Hold on. What did that sound like?
See how that sounds. I'm not gonna put this loud. I just need to know what it sounded like
Okay
It was just
It didn't change anything
It didn't change fucking anything. It just made it
Extremely loud. Hold on. That's why
Okay, let's see what that does. Is that different? Does that sound different?
The link what do you mean the link? What do you want for the link? What are you guys linking me?
Somebody just did it somebody made it
Why
Uh
Well, hold on
All right. Well, let's get rid of everything else but this
Oh my god
How's that a little bit more down?
That looks pretty good. Maybe a little bit up and to the right
How does this sound?
Cap it to 30 frames a second. Oh my god. I don't think I can
I don't think I can do that
Scale resolution. Hold on. I don't think I can do that
filters
Scaling aspect ratio. I can do it in obs but i'm gonna have to turn the stream off
Set my monitor's refresh rate to 30 do it in the game
Do it turn i'm not gonna turn the bit rate down on the stream
No, let me just wait
I think you seriously underestimate how I how much I cannot see what's going on on the screen
Now if this is authentic though, I have to play a little differently. You know what i'm saying?
Oh fucking jesus. Let me do this
Oh my god
Fuck this i'm out of here. I have to use the actual controller. I don't know the controls
What are the controls? Oh use tilt controls
One of the crazy things about this is uh that i'm what is that? Oh, I don't have any more bullets
All right. I figured out how to use the uh, okay hold
Hold what I can't even see what that says left trigger. I don't know what that even says right trigger
How's the battery battery low?
Really, come on. I thought it was already keyed out. It that they already had the channel gone. Whatever keep it
No, it has to be authentic. All right
I don't know how much more longer I can take this before my eyes actually start to hurt
All right, I'm gonna go back to the the controls. I know how to use okay comes the end of the joke voice
I'll do something at back before though. I promise i'm gonna do something fucking epic read chat
No, I
Another link chats going too fast. I can't click. What is this?
Is this supposed to be in my office?
This is my office. How many more layers is gonna are we gonna add to this?
No, I'm like so done with this. No, I'm not gonna put hands on you get the idea you get the you get the idea
Hands is too much. Oh, I just bounced off the ground. That was lucky
No
Take a picture of your desk have to make the screen dirty
I like that idea. All right, i'm gonna get like a transparency of like dirty screen dirty dirty window a dirty screen
Does it add like smears on it? All right, I think I can do I can work with this
Add a crack in it too. It's gonna be broken. Oh, here we go. This is perfect
But how am I I gotta i'm gonna have to do like transparency with this. Let me see if I can get this to work
Okay, did that work? Let's see if I can get this screen dirty
Hold on. I didn't need to
I need to turn the opacity down
Opacity
Hold on. It's that's really dirty. What the fuck did I just put it right here properties?
I gotta go into like
Key it not green. Hold on just key out black. Yeah, that's what i'm doing
Um
It's so dirty
It's really really too dirty. I think is that too dirty capacity is at like 75
That's like fucking puke man. That's that is so dirty. Somebody just dropped it in the mud and put a reflection of my face
Oh for the love of god
All right. Give me a second. This is worth it. It's gonna stay on too. Hold on
I need to make sure this is gonna reach no, it's okay. This will work
It needs to be pointed in the right spot tilted like I may be looking right down at it though
Okay, hold on
I gotta add that as a source now
Okay, this will be worth it when it's done right like right here. Okay. Okay
Let me get I need to key this out now. Jesus. This is gonna be fucking so hard. How's that?
My eyes
Better are we good even less? Oh
How do you think it got so dirty the boy we got hands now
But the stylist my hands not on the stylus the hands on the stylus is I don't have three hands. Okay, that was
one second
All right, we got hands god damn it this is fucking so stupid I love it
Well, whoops whoops whoops. This is I have so many images here. What even is this which one of these is the right one?
Okay, hold on. I need to do this
That's so dirty
Is that really what we were using?
That's disgusting
Okay, that's this one. Where is the dirt coming from right here, right? No, that's this one. There's the dirt
All right
So now I need me turned on as the mirror and this has to be on too
So this has to be able to be up here. So where is there go?
Where's this image? Wait, what the fuck is going on? Why is it doing this? This should be at the top
You know, it's because it's keying it out. Hold on. Hold on less dirt. No, we need like all the dirt we can get
So this one can go it's because it's keying out the background. So hold on. What is this one?
That's the fucking battery now. I'm getting rid of that
Here's this
This is another one that can be removed
This is I don't even know what the fuck is down here. We're almost close to perfect
Okay, here's the game
Why is the game not being captured anymore? Okay. There we go. All right nice and
Nice and dirty
Where's that dirt? There it is
How's that? It's off center
I can fix that
So I need to go here and here
The game needs to go
See what we got here
Okay. Now what is down there though? I need to full screen this
Am I like eyes deceiving me? No, okay. It's fine
Move dirt move dirt move the dirt. No dirt's good. No, we're good. That's it. We're ready to go
Okay. Now I gotta make sure you can see my face, right? Okay. Here we go right here put dirt on your hands, too
No, I think i'm gonna get him. So wait, I think I can go down here. Oh, i'm in the water though. I'm just kidding
Oh whoops, I got I got stuck. Hold on. This is kind of cool looking though. Look out there, man
It actually looks really good on the 3ds
My hands my hands are down here three hands. All right, i'm gonna land on the bridge. I see you guy
Oh shit, I gotta get out of here. I gotta get out of here
Let's fly out of here epic style
Oh, that's all right. I'm still alive. I had bullets. Oh so daisy. What is that on my screen?
My screen's a little dirty. Well, am I supposed to go this way for the uh mission?
Well guys, I don't do you know do you see where the mission is? I think i'm gonna check my map down here
Two maps this two maps
Two maps
Two two maps
Yeah, I really like this pretty yes. It's got these great. It's a great feature
Four hands
All right. I'm gonna find a plane man. I'm gonna find a plane. I don't have any bullets left
All right. There really is so much dirt on here clean my screen. Oh, hold on a minute. Hold on. Let me clean
What's going on here? What's all over the screen? I can't get it off. Somebody said the screen was fucked up the better
I think it looks better
Whoops. Oh, I think yeah, I think we're good. I can't oops
What the fuck happened to this thing? I don't know man. I was trying to
Happened. Oh, let me let me clean my screen. Yeah, all you guys saying my screen is dirty
Here we go
Oh, sorry, let me just clean that up real quick. Oh, whoops
All right, i'm fucking done. Like I played just cause
Sneezing cracks
I sneezed so badly that it cracked my 3ds
Really?
Hold on. No, I can't like I can't like punch it and like I guess I can what the fuck man
I can't control it dude. This game sucks. This game sucks. Okay, let's get crack 3ds voice
Mom
Mom mom, do you know what my charger is? I have one percent battery
Uh
This game sucks
3d
All right. I'm out. That was fun. I'm done with this. It's impossible. I can't play like this
My 3ds is off. My 3ds is broken though. Sorry guys. It's the webcam mic. It shouldn't be
Yes for you. Heard you broke. I also brought the charger for you. Thanks mom
Son take better care
Can I have your 3ds, please? I'm sorry
Broke my 3ds
Two 3ds's are you serious? What's in there? Oh my god
It's just cause it's too far. There's like four 3ds's in this house. How do I go back to normal?
Is it even possible takes the resolution so you can play but please keep the 3ds overlay
Why do you want the 3ds overlay? It's the it's impossible to watch
It's just a lie. It's not even real
Hold on. I let
The dirt on the screen. Let me at least be able to see what i'm doing
Wait, we're on the webcam
Why are we on the webcam mic? That's not the webcam
Oh, you want to be on the webcam mic. I see what you're saying
I get it
Okay, i'm a secret agent
Oh
This game's actually really really good though
It's got mostly negative on steam. I don't I don't know
Maybe it's because it's not on 3ds like this is I mean, that's probably why
Because it's not in the 3ds
keyboard
And that and that's it
And that's it
Immersion is we're done. We're done with this. That was a lot of fun
Now i'm gonna go back to playing just cause 4
I mean, we how this has been like a fucking hour. We've been doing this for an hour
No, i'm not turning the stream off
Don't let the photoshop go to waste
Some guy gave hands to you and you're whose hands are those though? I don't know whose those are
What happened?
Why did that happen?
They're yours
All right, I need to go back to normal that was fucking that was a lot of fun
But I need to put this back into 1080
before I
Literally lose my mind
So tomorrow we're gonna be streaming the game awards if you didn't know
Should be fun. I'm not leaving. I'm not leaving. Why does everybody think i'm leaving?
I can't say well, okay, but until people just think i'm gonna leave the stream. Well, that doesn't look right
This looks completely wrong
Okay, well, let's try maybe this will fix it
Hey, look at that. Wow. This feels very strange
This is this feels incorrect
I really feel like this feels wrong. Okay. Yeah game awards are gonna be streaming it. We're gonna. Oh, we're gonna talk about it
All right, let me give me this car
Actually, I want a bike. Well, I missed the bike like an idiot
All right, how far away is that start agency district?
What the fuck? Why is there a tank here?
Why am I still alive?
Who's playing a fucking rts right now?
Do they think that's me? I guess still alive. He's still trying to drive the car
Okay
Well, not anymore. It seems
Oh my god with the cycles
Destroy the bridge. Okay. Fine. Watch this
You can you can do that. You actually can I thought you kidding
Okay, I gotta get down there this way. How far away is this place?
Actually, not that far you can get there a little lickety split. All right, let me try not to
I said that and I almost did it
I'm so used to playing this on the 3ds that I forget how to play control the game
No, we're pretty far away. I can I like a guy can get some speed here
There we go. I finally figured it out
Now i'm moving fast now i'll move it fast
Yeah
Very fast. Hooray
You just it's transitioning between the two of them that makes it easier like that
What what do you get why is everybody making the I made this face
Everything I love this stream. Why is I made this?
Oh for the love of god, okay
Well, that was uh, okay that looks a little better right? Yeah. Okay. We're fine. Hey, hi i'm back
How long that must have been on there the whole time. It's all right. Did I go buy it? No, it's right here
Go back to the webcam the mic the webcam mic is not still on
I just want to get up to the top of the mountain. Oh the game audio too. Fuck
I forgot there's a shit little filters on this. There's so many the game
Okay now you should it shouldn't be insane
What a terrible fucking stream that would have been webcam mic and a bunch of filters on the audio stream is now ruined
And
Why would you do something like that? Thank god. I didn't kick the goat in the head
Okay, we're gonna do a mission. Hey, would you look at that?
Hey look a mission guys
Can you believe it?
Tom sheldon
Well, I guess you got my message. Yeah
He's all cleared me up. I'm on my way. Who's that?
Why are you here sheldon?
When you went dark after medici, I figured i'd look through some of your old files see where you might end up
It turns out your dad is working with us. He has a really really great something called project
That's like tinsel
Talk of weather modification technology
Did I turn the graphics back right looking at those eopah files I ended up on administrative leave
I guess i'm not the only one who doesn't trust tom sheldon
Maybe I didn't know you're looking to take out eopah rico
I've already done some of the legwork fake snow
You screwed me over more than once in medici
I don't want your help sheldon. Well, you're gonna need man. This looks much better on the 3ds. I agree
Turns out that place is constantly surrounded by a nasty lightning storm
Uh fried poor annabelle here
That seems pretty suspicious to have a standing lightning storm like that. Don't you think?
Is a friend of yours rico?
Not exactly
Nira malales, she's tom sheldon. I'm sorry for the mouth. There's nothing I can do about it. He cannot be trusted
Buenos don't listen to this guy senorita pleased to meet you
Rico and I were just discussing the situation with zona dose and you know
Like a mouse in my coffee for a second. It's an ice cube. I did
Okay, this is a very cool, I can't wait to understand the story
All right, hold on is the water is a beard made out of water
Look better. That looks kind of all right
Apply the 3ds settings
Yeah
I need
I need sasau
I don't think I don't need to turn on sasau
Now do max settings
No, I don't like the way games look with max settings
They look overproduced
You know why there's a lot of your favorite first person shooter?
Streamers play on low settings because of all the lights and graphics and illuminations
No, it's easier to play a game and see when it's not on like maximum settings
Yes, it is type in professional counter-strike player low graphics and you tell me what you find come on
On
Damn it. I didn't get it
Yes, you need to type in professional counter-strike player graphics settings
Why did that guy do it like that? It's rolling. He's right
I know that people play on low graphics so they can see the game better
Just type in computer professional counter-strike graphics
commands
professional csgo player
All right, what a mission am I gonna do before I like turn off the stream? How about that one?
Now just go open with the google search and type in your computer type in
What should I put my graphic settings on if i'm going to play professional counter-strike? What is a pro player's setup?
Do they use low settings type that in your computer?
How do you use turbo jump turbo jump? Oh, no jump jump jump jump jump jump jump
Did it bounce
No, it's turned to shit. Okay, whatever
Oh
He's my grenade launcher sick
Dude, thanks for the fucking heads up man
I need this
Keep at it people
Am I still alive?
Hey, did you hear the song that's why we're next to a bad guy
What the heck is spawning right to a bad guy?
What the heck?
Get out of here. You're gonna hear a bad guy
All right, let's go
I want to do one more thing before I
Well, okay, so you know what I mean? I got one do one more thing
Here take this I can't have that why?
This needs two. I only have one the hell else am I even gonna do here?
I guess I gotta go over here
I want travel to here
Yeah, I mean i'm gonna do one more thing before
all right, so uh
Wing suit stunt dirt is surveillance airship. How do I like want to get forward motion here?
Damn it. Just put on the damn suit
It's a friendly jet. None of them are friendly
I gotta get up there
And oh not quite
I can't get there
Okay, so let's get up here
into the ship
Destroy the airship
Now that's gonna be very easy enough
Okay, so guys, thanks for uh coming to stream and away we go
No, shoot the
That's not gonna destroy the ship. Oh
What are you dropping on me here? What the fuck are these things?
I want to get on that. How do I get
Get inside of it. What the fuck is happening to my character right now?
All right, where's the blimp it's all the way up there
It's so high up at this point
How am I supposed to get up there?
Just go really hot. How am I supposed to get up there?
I have an idea
Fuck you game. I got an idea
All right. I need um
I think a rock or something. Can I stand on a rock?
I'm gonna do the floaty
Okay, now here's the theory can I
Get on top of this
Okay
Now let it go
Okay, hold on now. I'm just trying to make a fucking ladder. Oh my lord. Just let me get on this
Just filled
Okay, here we go and see if I can get this to work and one
And they all fucking explode. Of course they do
Ow my hand
Ow
No, they just both explode. He's coming down. Anyways, fuck this
Not my fucking gamer hands. I know really
Okay, I think I can get it
I gotta activate the chute
Did I get it
I'm right underneath it man. I'm right underneath it
There we go
Okay, so how do I uh
How to activate this
I'm gonna shoot it
Oh, is anybody in here with me?
Who's in the blimp? This is probably like 10 people in here
Me. Oh me
Destroy the blimp and I put it down
I'm going down, right?
I think so
No, i'm just going sideways. What the fuck is that?
Why is there another one?
Crash into it. I can't even turn
These things don't turn
Okay
Sorry, I can get back
C and z it's not doing anything c
No, c is not doing anything z is not doing anything
shift shift is
Whatever I can I do
Control
No, I can't turn this thing
How the fuck are you turning? How are you turning your
to the air whale
q and e
Nice try. How the fuck do you turn for real?
Why is he good to do it?
Number pad four and six. No, that's not doing anything
Num pad num pad doesn't do anything
z and c z c z c c not doing anything arrow keys
Watch the show santiago as i've said before i'm more of a reader
You were saying that the show starts with the boot of an attractive gentleman
planes
What happened planes helicopters cranes planes?
Throttle up. Yeah, it's not doing it c and z aren't doing anything
helicopters
Yaw
Yaw, I don't that didn't do anything either
cranes
Just watch the show. Okay, he meets some of the local people that must be the gacha drive see the gacha
And these are some pretty tough individuals you can tell by just looking at them
But over the course of the first season diego uses his charisma and his intellect
To show the gacha that the espinosas are taking too long i'm taking way too long middle mouse button
So
All right, i'm just destroying this one just drive it into the wall you got one less blimp one less problem
Oh, thanks wait that blimp is freaking out can I now can I steer that one?
Hey kid, we're gonna get through that lightning storm. We need a way to keep from getting sizzled lightning
Best bet still medial
All right, we need a three let's send them to
How about down here man? Go for it
new mission
That we are not going to be playing tonight
unfortunately
But I just want to thank everybody for spending the time here on this stream
Because we've got
Uh, just another second here before it's time to get out of here
You know i'm saying
I'm gonna get on the blimp
Now can I drive this the right way
No, I can't I cannot I can't fucking drive this thing
Is my mind deceiving me here?
Or are we going backwards?
controller
No, that's not I don't know how to hold on
Left bumper and uh, right bumper you think
That's what I would assume it would be
It is okay bingo
Got it
I can do it on the controller
How do I put the blimp? I want to go fight the other blimp
It's time for a head-on collision
If I can even find it comes a blimp fight
I crap. No, there was a there's a blue one right over here
There's a blue blimp over here
I'm already bored
Oh, there's the other blimp. Come on
No
This is gonna fall eventually
I can't get higher like this. Can I?
Not really balloon on a car. It's gone
It's gone
I would love to go
Get off this
It was so loud so unnecessarily loud
No, I would have had it too
Whatever i'm gonna turn the stream off if it hits me turn the stream up if it hits me turn the stream off and it hits me
nice try
Turn the stream off anyways
All right now get in
Why did that not do anything?
Get in get in the car
All right. Where is it?
Looking for the blimp
You don't see a blimp. I'm trying to drive the car. What happened?
All right, I gotta do I gotta do something here. Hold on
Yes
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me
Well, uh, I bet it's time to go to work
All right, this is where I work right here at the gas station
Real sturdy real sturdy car made out of silicone
Okay, I got I let me just pull up to work. There it is. Okay, let's tap this
Oh, no, the car exploded. I can't believe it
my durability
All right, that's the end of the street
uh, this game gets a uh
Whatever you like it if you like it
If you don't then just didn't like it and you don't like it and you buy it if you think it's fun
I don't know. Maybe i'll play it again
I want the 3ds version. It's probably pretty good
so tomorrow
What's gonna happen tomorrow is uh, if it is actually legal then i'm gonna restream the game awards
I'm gonna watch the game awards together
And we're gonna watch fortnight win every single category
It's legal. All right
Game awards are at 12 pst. Well, we're gonna have to be ready for it then
But thanks for sticking around
Just wanted to check out just cause for which i've had fun
I had fun. It was a fun game, but a little on the uh, a little on the weird side
Wait 12. What do you mean?
Wait, wait, wait, wait 12. Hold on a second. Hold on. Let me make sure we get this right before I get out of here
I I don't think that's correct
12 pst. No, it's got to be later than that
game awards
The game awards are
5 30 pst
Okay
So at 5 30 pst is when the stream's gonna be tomorrow and we're just gonna have fun
There'll be a face cam there, you know
Maybe if I feel like turning it on but yeah, uh, let's get to the bits
Let's put the outro on the screen. Thanks for sticking around
Hope you had a good time. I did
And I I did burp a few times on stream, but it's okay
And let's bring ourselves back to just under five and a half hours ago
We had three dollars from divas. Thank you divas with three bucks
Mostly lost gave one dollar. The reason I was tilted earlier is because you always go live five minutes before I need to leave
I'm sorry about that. You know, I'm sorry about that
That's the real end of the stream voice. Yeah, that is
But thank you mostly lost but the two dollars total here obviously you need to operate on my schedule and you can't go live until I say
So it's very difficult. I will tell you
Especially being on pacific time now. It's
When you're on pst, you have to remember
You're essentially back in time
because
noon pacific
Or even like 10 a.m pacific
Is 10 11 12 1
2 3 4 5 6 it's like 6 or 7 o'clock eu
If I got up at like 9 in the morning and streamed at 9 in the morning it'd be like 5 o'clock in the afternoon
That's kind of insane
Sorry if time zones
Uh screw up your viewing habits. I'm sorry that it's like that
Sorry to hear about your the pacific time
Uh lorag 100 dollars lorag 98 100 dollars earlier
Thank you so much sir feline one dollar. Shit. The ground is shaking
It was for a large portion of this stream. Thank you bake me home for the one dollar
Marvish mcgally for the one dollar
Uh, just an eu guy passing by. I hope you had a good time. Good night germa fireman. I think we got
I think we got fun out of this. Maybe we didn't get 60 dollars worth of fun
No, maybe I don't know we got like we got like at least 17 dollars worth of fun
If I had you know, if I keep playing it the next couple days and maybe i'll get like 41 dollars of fun
I'm, not sure
60 dollars for a 3ds game
It's kind of ridiculous, isn't it?
Uh, thank you freddy c for the two bucks. They just say beautiful. Thank you
Sly 161. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey germa. I know chat didn't really like watching it
But two point hospital got new dlc wanted to let you know because I know you enjoyed the game
Yeah, I don't know what it was
What was with okay two I had to turn down two point hospital
and
A lot of you guys were acting as if I was just blowing a fire alarm through your speakers
Like I had to turn that off. It was a bullhorn next to a fire alarm
It was bad. I don't know
Okay, the only I I have like at least three times where i've looked over and been like why is everybody so fucking angry?
um
octogen
octogen stream two
Was another one of those two point hospitals where
Everyone everyone was just hating everything. That's the only two that I could really actually think of where it was like, whoa
Everybody's very mad right now
Yeah, I did two octogen streams
That's the only two times I think I could really pinpoint when I would it was just like well people are very angry with me
Nintendo labo was like that too, but I but I was shit faced so I don't even know what you're talking about
But thank you sly
Uh, thank you
Uh teidolf swiftler. Thank you for the one dollar. Hey germa
It's me. I know i'm asking a lot of you to do this
But I just spent the last of my grocery money on these bits
And i'm gonna starve to the winter if I don't hear you say the magic words, please please
uh
What do you want me to do?
Say the words savory dog smell. I've said that like a hundred times
Thank you dark star 700 000 games for the one dollar, please dear christ fix the graphics
This game looks absolutely gorgeous. Normally. I think your computer is fucked up
Is I
And are you really are you sure?
No, this is not even at the 3ds bit. This is before that
I don't know. I that looked okay except for christmas beard
It was a little janky and ugly
There was a lot of aliasing and it was very bright
Actually, it did look pretty bad. You're right. Never mind, but thank you though
Uh, thank you freudian weapon for these six dollars
Germa heart, that's all they say. Thanks a lot
Appreciate it
Hawkeye of mine gave 4.99
Watching you in an open world game is probably one of the most incredible things to watch this game is your element
Lul
The game is still better looking than you
Ban that guy not only ban that guy for life ban his other accounts, too
Click on like click on like like post history and like finally like and then like ban everything
Don't you guys know that I know dave twitch?
It's actually it's a short name it's short and it's dave it's dave twitch ansky
He's a very close family friend
Easy, but thank you hawkeye of mine. Thank you. I'm pink the 15 dollars. I'm pink
15 bucks
I've watched you on youtube for a while about four years ago is when I started though
I would say how much I love your content for your four years ago is when I started though. It's a long time
Thank you for being here for this long. It's weird because
The 10 year is going to be coming up here in a couple of years
Just over two and a half years, right?
Once we hit 2020
That would be because I started in 2011
So we're talking about only another two to three years before that's that's a full decade that i've been doing youtube and twitch
What am I going to do for the 10 year anniversary?
I have no idea
Need a jar of peanut butter
Offstream and not stream that day, but thank you. I'm pink
Uh dead c4t. Thank you for the hundred dollars
Thank you so much. Thank you. I'm pink again for your hundred dollars
Really appreciate that. It's a fucking lot of money. Thank you guys
You guys are too
Too generous. Thank you
Tingy thanks for the one dollar
I have to say that the other night is some of the most fun i've had on your stream not only watching but just interacting
Nearly 12 000 viewers. I've never seen a better group of chatters on this site. I love being here. It's always a great experience
Yeah that
That was wild
Never never before have I ever had that many people here
The last germa wrestling thing was just about 10 000 and then that was about 12 000
like
In the last week i've never seen anything like that before
That's that's fucking crazy
So if you were part of that you participated
Thank you. You're amazing
Thanks for fucking coming out here
And then uh juno again juno, thanks for the 50 dollars
Five zero huge money. Thank you
Guys, we're always so mean to germa
I don't think so
I don't think you guys are mean. What do you mean mean?
uh tater
tater giving out five community subs
five community subs
From tater somebody's trying to get me to respond. They just said fuck you germa
They're trying to get me to say hey, come on. What the heck. What are you doing? What? Hey, why?
And I just did I know that that's a good tactic now
But thank you so much tater five community subs
Captain worgen, thanks for the two bucks
It's really cool to see you playing just cause four if you like the game
uh
Have you thought about playing?
Oh, they messed up. He said whoops. Sorry. I didn't finish my last bit what I meant to say was have you heard of
it's
called
Uh, hold on a second. There's like you got hold on germa cool to see playing just cause four. This is from captain worgen
Is you like this game have you thought about playing have you heard of playing it's called
I think you may have uh, not done. Oh my god
Maxi kaspersky and kairatobi giving a five minute subs each. Thanks guys
That's ten coming in for maxi kaspersky
and of course
kairatobi pin man has given
five community subs
It's time for slime has given five community subs here. Oh here come the fucking subs
Holy shit guys
Well, that's uh
That's like five ten fifteen twenty. That's like 30 25 30 subs in 15 seconds. Thank you
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you everybody
Jerk tc coming out with five here
jerk tc
five
Community subs. Thank you
God damn
Terma gets rich part two
My lord, oh my god
Peter, uh, peter
P. Oh
peter, uh
Tater came in with 10 more peter came in with 10. That's 20
peter
Peter came in with 10
community subs
tater with 10 community subs
my fucking god
You guys are way too you guys are way too kind to me. I will try to use your money in uh
In a good way
I'll try my absolute damnedest
Buy 12 pounds of eggs. That's a lot of eggs
Much love to you guys. Seriously. Thank you
Trying to get on track with the bits again here after an explosion of subs
Thank you flug boy for the one dollar
I hope you're doing all right germ just want to say the green screen movie night by my entire rest of the year
It was great. I also hope we didn't ruin any chances of you wanting to watch jojo
No, that's okay
I told you 2019 the one anime is gonna be jojo
I'm gonna watch season one
only
Everyone wanted me to do that. They said watch season one season one is the way you should watch i'm like, okay fine
I'll watch season one
Uh, but thank you garfield the monday killer for the one dollar
Garfield thought of a strange scenario if there was a week-long purge
Who are two guys you would trust to protect you?
Stipulation you can pick fictional characters. They can't have any superpowers. So batman would be allowed
But he can only use gadgets
They're not capable of turning against you
So if you hire the joker, he can only protect you
Garfield would choose mr. Rogers and pooh bear
Okay
Um
And that's very easy
God
Wait, is god of super be a good hold on. Wait. No that no, I don't know. Um
What I picked to protect me, you know, I would I would pick garfield i'd pick garfield
And man would we get ourselves in some real dangerous situations?
You know, I picked garfield and like garfield it's like a fucking 100 people coming to get me get out there
Yeah, go get them
There's a hundred of them go get them
You gotta protect me
And the second person I would pick because garfield would it would would just be destroyed in a second
Uh, the second person would be
um
hmm
Doesn't have superpowers
It'd have to be somebody huge
That's really fast. That's really strong
All right. Can I pick can I pick like the mountain from game of thrones?
Does it mean that's like
Okay, so it'd be garfield and then the mountain
Somebody would just shoot him. But this is a world with no guns, right? It's just who do you whatever?
That okay. I would pick a guy that had a gun
And it was very good at it. I'd pick like 47 or something
A gun is not a superpower
Thank you garfield. Thank you captain worgen for the one dollar
Thank you. Listen to all these subs
Thank you
Uh g
duh
G to x
Thank you for the one dollar. Hey germa while you're stuck in the endless table surge
Make sure to change your balloon height to infinity. It's what you paid for
We ended up going in and doing it
thankfully
Pigeon attack. Thanks for the ten dollars pigeon attack. They say big plane
Thanks for the ten bucks
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
big plane
I am monk. Thanks for the one dollar god gamer
I don't think so
um
Okay, you can say like just a fun intermediate level
Intermediately skilled gamer, okay
That beat jevil first try
And beat flame lurker first try and hit all of the targets in point blank two
Which is nearly fucking 100 percent impossible
so
Take that with what you will I guess
Nearly and 100 percent. Thank you. Uh, thank you
Gnostic for the ten dollars
Thank you so much. Hey germa, it's my birthday today. Just wanted to let you know how happy I am that you're streaming tonight
Thanks for all the laughs for the years of laughs here's to another year of fun
2019 is gonna be a lot of fun. I can assure you
We will have fun in 2019
Definitely. Thank you so much for the ten bucks and speaking of ten bucks. Thank you
uh
Thank you
x-chris for the ten dollars
Thank you for the ten dollars
Thank you. Also to
Smug smug jund
For the one dollar a joke truly worth 200
people
Shut it off. Shut it off already
Like this sound the sub sound
Does anybody else feel like it's broken
I think it might be broken
Is it just in a constant never-ending loop?
It might be
Wait, hold on
Wait, okay. It was stuck
I think it actually was stuck
but thank you, uh smug for the
One dollar here
Mostly lost. Thanks for the one dollar again what I can't fly this thing. No, she could for god's sakes man. Shut it up
Coldest fridge. Thanks for a dollar 91. Hey germa. Just want to thank you for all the great streams of late
Don't forget that you saved a lot of people's lives
Like mine
Also, my birthday is tomorrow. So stream a day before is just as rad. Well, we'll be streaming tomorrow, too, man
It'll be live tomorrow as well with our
game awards
uh stream commentary
uh
Peter gave five community subs again and maxi gaspersky gave five again
again
They did it
another time
Five each again. Thank you guys
And speaking of people that have been handing out community subs
In the last 40 30 40 minutes of this stream
Uh tater gave another one another five
Community sub drop here
It is raining subscribers from a handful of incredibly generous individuals. Thank you guys
Thank you so
much
You spend a lot of money on this stream
It means a lot local streamer gets lots of community subs
Yeah
I do not uh, I do not take it for granted
Hopefully you will see where a lot of this money goes
Because it's going pretty much right back in so thank you
Uh a dapper dog by the way, uh, happy birthday
To the coldest fridge tomorrow. It might be tomorrow right now because it's currently
About 1 a.m. Eastern. So happy birthday coldest fridge
Thank you. See you tomorrow on your birthday
Also a dapper dog. Thanks for the two bucks. Thanks for being you germa. Lots of love bday 100. Thank you dapper dog
bday 100 thanks for the two dollars
uh vive
five k toll
c
Thanks for the two bucks. They say fail fish
I must have done something real stupid
There was a point there in the middle of that
before the ds bit
I I think i've ran into the ground like seven times in a row
Thank you springfield for the two dollars fifty cents. Hey germa. I've been wondering for my entire life
What happened to the gift of flight video? It's my favorite video of all time and it's gone missing what gives
I've explained it a few times before
But there was a point when I was trying to clean up the channel
of
terrible
13 and seven fucking call of duty kill confirm videos
That I just hated I was like, I don't want this on the chin and I went through and I was checking boxes
And I was like wait, what's this?
And some of them just got checked that I shouldn't have checked
There was a period where I don't know man. Like I got they get to a point where
There was somebody like videos that I wanted the channel to be more
Focused and I was like embarrassed that people could go back and watch
Some of those terrible fucking videos where I literally just played call of duty for like eight minutes
And uploaded whatever fucking happened
And I only did that like five times so ten times maybe total of the nearly thousand videos that I uploaded on that channel
so
You know, I I mean I was starting to get a little bit more viewership
I was making content that I like to make more than something like that and people were going to go back at the beginning
Of the channel and oh no, here's like what's what are these videos?
I'm going to watch these and be like, well, never mind. Let me unsubscribe this guy. I don't like this
So it would get caught in the crossfires of me trying to clean the channel up
Of like stuff that I thought was bad
bad as in
Like not good to watch
But sorry that some of those videos were removed
But thank you springfield for the 250. Hopefully that is a that is an explanation
That you will be okay with hey kairatobi. Thanks for the
$10
Thank you so much kairatobi
Uh chat can thank snowy on discord for the edit. Here's a fixed version
Oh for the 3ds
Yeah, thank you all of you guys that threw together in less than five minutes
Photoshopped hands and screen skewing
That was a lot of fun. Thank you
Uh smelly boy. Thanks for the one dollar play geoguessr
Not tonight. Uh, thank you pudding for the one dollar 3ds joke fund
Thank you. I put it in my 3ds joke fund
Savior of the dreaming dead. Thanks for the one dollar. How exactly did we get here?
Um, I turned the graphics down
all the way
In just cause and it looked like nintendo 64 or 3ds
So then it was like this is a 3ds game. Oh, okay. Hold on a second and then it just spiraled out of control
That's what happened. It's kind of how it went down
Uh carrot, thank you carrot for the one dollar the fucking 3ds. I can't even type i'm laughing too hard
Glad you thought it was funny. Thanks for the one dollar, dude
Hey shoot man. Thank you shoot me for the one dollar
I feel the need to admit that I watched the green screen movie night for an hour before realizing i'd already seen it
And it wasn't live
Thanks for the free content you smooth
brain stallion
What thank you
Thank you to mostly lost for the one dollar. You're the top just cause four streamer on twitch
By a large margin doesn't I mean that doesn't really surprise me because i'm playing it like three days late
You know what I mean? Didn't this come out like on monday or something?
So anyone that was gonna stream it?
Anyone that was gonna stream it probably already did it right? It came out yesterday. Oh, well
Three three days yesterday ago
Oh
No, that's cool I that's
Really really?
I mean, that's a I don't really know what to say, you know being in the top position on any given game is
This is an honor right because it's like oh, wow. Okay
That's really cool
Hopefully people like the stream
top 3ds streamer
Maybe thank you mostly lost for the one dollar. You're the top. Whoa. Whoa. I already did that. Just did it
Just did it
But thank you mostly lost. Thank you meaty mate for the five dollars meaty matey
Five bucks here. Thank you so much
Blue comet. Thanks for the ten dollars. No message
Just ten bucks. Thanks a lot, dude
Ten bucks. Thank you
Pre-recorded stream skip what?
Uh danda dump. Thanks for the one dollar. I just spent money to tell you
This is the dumbest joke I think you've ever done keep up the good work
Just you fucking wait
Just wait
I would I would just wait before you say that okay
That's all I need to say
but
I thought it was really fun
Uh ren, thank you ren for the five dollars. They just say pogchamp pogchamp pogchamp
Thank you
Uh, thank you there
Or there nor there nor for the one dollar top 3ds gamer
You can you I remember a long time ago. I wanted to capture the 3ds
and it was
Nearly impossible you have don't you have to get a separate device from a third party?
That lets you hook into the hooks in the back of the 3ds and let's you plug it into hdmi or something
You have to actually mod your 3ds
I don't think there's anything I really would want to stream on 3ds. Anyways, maybe the warriorware game
But we already played all the warriorwares a long time ago. That's probably that's really the only thing i'd want to play
Just use the webcam
Go back to like 2007 youtube
Hey dan with wings. Thanks for the ten dollars dan
Hey, germa just want to let you know that the 3ds bit was the hardest i've laughed in a live stream
Uh stuff like this is why you're the only streamer I still watch keep it up slugger
Thank you
I hope you still think that in another week
Another day another month another year
Hope you still have fun. Thank you. Thank you smacklesmore for the one dollar germy
You're the funniest and most creative streamer and also very handsome. I mean
Those are those are like three
Three like super nice adjectives, you know what I mean?
All I can say is thank you
Appreciate it. Kyratopia. Thanks for the one dollar. Uh from snowy again in the discord in case the joke ever comes back
Yeah, it's just like a blank slate
That's so funny. I'm gonna have to hold on to this because if in case that ever comes back I have a perfect image
Thank you
Uh, mr. Wink. Thanks for the dollar 50. They just say
Who who I think that's the that's like the point two second gnome video, right?
Uh mostly lost. Thanks for the one dollar. If you went back and looked at all my bit messages
They probably amount to abuse what?
No, you're fine. Don't worry
Uh, thank you jess for the one dollar smash comes out this week any plans on that?
Um, I think so
But I don't want I don't want to turn on smash on launch day
because
I'd like to unlock the characters and at least get familiar with it before I try to do anything with it
We'll see
There is a possibility that you will see smash brothers
on the channel maybe
Uh stream the story mode. I don't know if that would be I don't know if that's that interesting though
It's just kind of fighting against bots
I'd rather get familiar and then do an actual
Multiplayer stream where I fucking decimate everybody as pac-man
We'll see but yeah, that is exciting does come out soon. Thank you though
Uh maxie kaspersky. Thanks for the one dollar. I'm something of a community sub myself
Well, they sure have given a lot. So
Thank you. Jerk tc gave 15 bucks 15 from jerk tc
I'm here cuddling a kitten and having goosebumps because I like your videos so much
I'm a huge fan of goosebumps, too
I especially love the abominable snowman one
I love
the um
Attack of the dummy in the in the attic
Whatever that one's called
But in all seriousness, thank you
I'm very happy that you think that this is worth watching
I hope I can continue to
Have you feel that way? Thank you for the 15 dollars. Thank you. Timmy tim tan for the one dollar
I didn't show up to the date
A date
to hello
Sandy is that you? Yes. Uh-huh. Who's this? It's gil gil gil who
What do you mean gil who gil dixon, of course? Oh gil dixon. I'm sorry
Yes, we had a date last night. Where were you? I waited for one hour
Oh, i'm sorry gil
I couldn't come
Couldn't come
Why not?
Well, I had to pack my stuff for my trip
Why didn't you call me? I wanted to call you but um
I couldn't remember your phone number my trip and now
I'm going to forget yours
A date
What do you mean gil who gil dixon of course
For one hour
I waited for one hour
I just lost yours
If you want to learn english
Go check it out
Thank you timmy tim tan. Thank you up quark for the one dollar. If you had to bring back one old meme
What would you bring back?
um
None of them. I don't think no i'd rather i'd rather see
And do new stuff
You know, we can always remember the old ones
But there's new ones to make
You understand all your bass are belong to us. No, I don't mean like in in history
Thank you though clueless sniper. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey germa
I was wondering if you plan on doing another movie night
I had a lot of fun making my weather channel video and I hope I have a couple more ideas
I don't really have a plan
to do a second one
but
I might
There's a possibility where we could figure out something fun
Where you have to make something very specific, you know what I mean?
So instead of just literally anything
There's maybe like a few different categories you could put it into
But I don't know this I don't really have like a plan for it certain categories maybe
But i'm very very happy with what happened and how it turned out and i've seen um
A lot of people discussing it and i've seen all the people had a lot of fun
I'm really happy about that. I've also seen a little bit of criticism and I can understand that
uh
It was very very difficult
To because this was never supposed to be a contest, right?
I wanted to try to include as many people as possible
because
If okay, let's say for instance, okay
Uh, oh there was like seven or eight jojo videos, right? That's and then okay
Yeah, that's it's a lot. Well, maybe I think there's actually 15
but
There were people spent a lot of time on them
And I didn't want to have it because at that point it's okay this all these submissions
Well, i've got to get rid of all these and uh, only one of these videos can make it in you know
What I mean at that point it becomes a contest
rather than just like a night of just putting up as much as we possibly can
which is
That was the purpose of
The this last sunday, you know
I didn't want to really exclude very many submissions. It was hard to exclude a bunch of them
But some of them really couldn't be used for various reasons
But it was more of a community night than like a video contest
There is plenty of potential to do a video contest
We'll see but I had a lot of fun
And I said this on the stream before
At the end and at the beginning and midway through
I was absolutely blown away by how just how fucking creative
So many of you guys are so
I loved every second of it. Thank you asha for the five dollars asha 108
You're still the number one pub g streamer on ipad and I will keep my number one chicken dinner slot
As the number one mobile ipad pub g streamer
Thank you though for the five dollars. Thank you. Errol is for the one dollar germa earth. Thank you
Honey chain. Thanks for the one dollar. Thank you all the great videos and streams over the years
Thank you for watching the videos in the streams
Honey chain, thank you
And then finally dubsky dude for one dollar when you were in that pit with the boulder and those random animals spawned
That was very eerily similar to your old space master video. It kind of freaked me out
All you new people need to look that video up you can find it on an ancient website called youtube.com
Animals I just remember the bird flying upside down and around the circle
It was like a parakeet or something
and then the
What a weird fucking game
Uh, that is it for the bits
Let's show the sub credits while we make our way out of here. Let's put them up on the screen. What do you say?
Here they come. I got a feeling there's gonna be a lot of these
Considering the amount of gifted subs that were tonight
Oh, yeah
Holy shit
That's going fast
That type of video is why you started watching in the first place
Yeah, I mean I I always tried
I don't know. I get bored really easily guys
I know that
Uh a lot of people ask. Well, what's your process when you go to make a video or a stream?
It's pretty it's very easy. I I get very bored
And I like to try to do new things every time or play something different or try a different video or try a different idea
Because if I do the same thing for too long, I it'll bore me. I just get bored
Ever put something that you know is fun
off
um
You mean like I was having a good time and then
I know I was having fun, but I turned it off
I don't think so. Maybe um
Like red dead two
No
What the hell does this explain this image?
It's four feet tall
44 54 inches
What are you what are you talking about? You don't know how tall the ceilings in my room are
You don't know how tall my ceilings are
I'm not 54 inches tall
I'm like 68 or something
Don't make me get a stick and stand next to it. Hold on a second here
I i'm like 65. Oh, no, no, no 68 or 69 inches tall
Yeah, i'm 69 inches tall
Look at look at all these subs
That's so many
That's so many in one day
That's the that's the funny number
That's fine
Just because it's the funny number doesn't mean it's the real one
Four and a half feet tall
You know, i'm gonna let you guys have this one. Okay?
sure
Oh bob bob champ we could have it
Don't let them have it. All right guys, i'll see you tomorrow for the game awards
It should be fun
Right at the very end
We had garfield the monday killer with the dollar
Garfield coming into the last second with one question
Uh, do you think the green screen streams and movie night streams would be a good thing to do as a yearly basis?
It felt appropriate to use the green screen stream and movie night to sandwich the rumble because all three streams seemed like a trinity of the
best of all
That i've ever offered
I told I talked about this once
Maybe a little bit more but I I want every since moving to las vegas
The whole point of coming out here
Was to try to dial it up to try to do more
to
every 30 to 45 days
Have something else going on
That was one of the number one reasons for being here
You know what I mean?
So a green screen it doesn't need to be a green screen. There's I have plans to do all kinds of shit
And the next thing that I plan on doing is probably going to be on christmas eve
That's a plan. I have a plan to do something on christmas eve
So they if you have been enjoying the last couple of weeks of the green screen stuff and then
um
The germa wrestling i'm trying to try i'm i'm going to dial it up to like 11, man
I start expecting that once a month 11 out of two
Oh, yeah, here it comes
Turn it up
one
Ah, let's just stay at one one. Let's stay at one. So pretty much i'm dialing it up to a one
At a 10
But that's my time
I have a wonderful rest of your evening. I'll see you tomorrow for the game awards. Have a great night
Thanks for sticking around watching just cause 2
See you soon