Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Playing as the spy tonight with the Ambassador, the Stinger, or the Coniver's Kunai, and of course the Dead Ringer, my default spy setup.
Playing on Gold Rush tonight, defense on Gold Rush, but I don't really want to talk about the gameplay.
I want to talk about something that is very important to a lot of you guys,
and something that I get asked a lot, and this is going to be a great way for me to explain how to keep motivated in things like YouTube,
or really anything universally, anything you're trying to do that you're maybe not succeeding so much at,
or maybe you're just starting something and you really want some advice on where to go from the beginning.
And this is what this video is going to be about. It's going to be about goals.
So let me just start by saying that if you have a particular thing you want to try and do,
let's say you want to be a soccer player, or let's say you want to be a YouTube personality, or you want to do a commentating,
whatever it is you're trying to do, it's going to be quite difficult to do that thing unless you set yourself a realistic goal.
And this goal is constantly going to be updated on I'd say probably like a monthly basis.
Let me start by saying, when I started YouTube, let's just talk about YouTube commentating in general.
When I first started YouTube I had zero subscribers, didn't really know the direction I wanted to take the channel,
but I knew I wanted to do something. And I would look around at all these channels that had 20, 15, 20, 30,000 subscribers,
and I'd say, damn, how did they get to where they, how did they get there? How did you do that? That's ridiculous.
And what I didn't understand back then is all these channels that you're looking at that are really, really popular channels,
they all had to start from zero, and they all had to find a way to work themselves up to where they are.
And a lot of these guys have been doing this for a couple years, sometimes even three or four years.
So it can take a long time. But let me get back to the whole goals thing.
The reason why I bring that up is because if you don't set yourself a goal, here is one of the realistic goals that I set for myself.
When I first started, I said, I want to have 25 subscribers by July. I started this channel in June.
And I knew that if I reached that goal in July, I knew I was going to want to keep going.
And then I would set another goal for myself. So once I got, I think I got to like 60 subscribers in July, I was so happy.
I was like, wow, I put a goal for myself and I shot way past that goal. I'm going to make a new one.
And every month I just added another couple hundred subscribers to that goal. And it really makes you motivated.
It really makes you want to do it. It makes you want to keep pushing for it.
But you can't ever say to yourself, oh, I have 125 subscribers. Next month I want to have 4,000.
It's not going to work that way. Some people get lucky. Some people will get really lucky and you'll get 20,000 subscribers in two days.
But that happens because of circumstances that not everyone's going to see.
So if you are starting out as a new YouTube channel, or even like I said, if you're a new soccer player or you're a go getting into drama at your school or something like that,
try and set yourself a realistic goal, something that you know you can accomplish.
Because if you reach for the stars too early and you don't get to touch them, I like good analogy, right?
If you reach for the stars too early and you get shut down, it really hurts.
And I've been in that position before, guys. Before YouTube, I wanted to be a film director.
I went to college for film. I have a film degree. And I never went anywhere with it.
And I've reached way too high. And I think that a lot of people do the same thing.
They try, they reach way too high into the sky, and they get nowhere.
And I specifically wanted to make this video to try and answer some of the questions that people have for me in PMs when they say,
You know, I just started my YouTube channel. I'm just starting this, just trying to do that.
Where do I go from here? What do I do? I've been doing this for like a couple months.
I only have a couple hundred subscribers. And my only real answer to that is you just got to stick with it.
You got to stick with it. You've got to put a lot of effort into your channel.
Or even if it was something else, it all takes practice, it all takes effort, and it all takes time.
The most important thing that you have to remember about starting anything new
or even if you're already doing it, it takes a lot of time.
I've been doing this for just about a year now. I'm coming up on one year this summertime.
And I'm currently still setting goals. Every month I give myself a new goal and I try to reach it.
And that's what you guys should be trying to do with your stuff, your content, your anything, your flute playing.
It doesn't matter what it is. Set yourself some goals and go for them, man.
So that's going to be the end of this video, guys. Pretty good spy gameplay.
I just wanted to make sure I got this video out to try to help you guys with your new channels or new anything.
If it's something to do with school work or something like that.
But I will see you guys all next time and expect more of these videos where I kind of just talk to you guys.
I'm not going to do them all the time, but expect them every now and then.
So yeah, see you guys all next time. Take care, everybody.