Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Demoman with the lock and lo- that's not the lo- whoa whoa easy.
I'm so used to saying that when I play demo that I just said it. No, this is the Loose Cannon.
Loose Cannon, Islander, and Tideturner, which is pretty standard at this point to have the Tideturner
on because it is so good. But Loose Cannon, just had the urge to play with it. Just felt like throwing
it on, get some kills, get some glorious double dunked Orido double stuffed Oreos.
And it's gonna sit in the background like it typically will when we discuss some things,
in particular in a commentary style like you're seeing right here, which I haven't done
in quite a while, so I figured why not. And today's topic of today's video is when you
find yourself in a situation where you can't think about anything. Your brain is empty
because there's too much stuff to think about. I'm gonna try to make that make sense. What I
just said, I'm gonna try to make it make sense. And that's kind of the point of this video,
is slipping into a mindset where I've been recently, and I'm sure a lot of you guys have
been there as well, where your brain is just constantly, constantly thinking about things,
running at a thousand miles per hour with everything that's going on in your life currently.
And it makes it so difficult for you to focus on really anything at all. And now these things
could be good and bad things at the same time, and they just pull up in a giant caravan.
The mother gets out of the fucking car, pulls open the door, and like a bunch of kids come in and
jump into the public pool that is your brain. And maybe one of the kids, maybe one of the kids is
like, is a problem that you're having. You know, he jumps in the fucking pool. He has his sneakers
on for Christ's sake. What was that? You just heard some crashing noise behind you. Somebody
knocked over the hot dog stand. It's a kid running around the pool. You're like, hey,
no running at the pool, please. Another kid just jumps in and you're like, oh, what was that? What
just happened? Oh, that was a new job opportunity. But wait a second, you just pissed in the pool.
That kid just pissed in the pool. Oh, God damn it. I gotta go, I gotta get like the chlorine,
everybody out of the pool, and then like two more kids jump in. And that's like something else that
could be going on in your life, in your whole brain. Then all of a sudden you close the pool.
You say, everybody out of the fucking pool, because I've got to deal with this. And everybody gets
out of the pool. They all pile back into the caravan and then they all they take off. And then
you're just kind of left with an empty pool. I don't know how much sense that just made.
Probably none at all. But let me translate it in as best way that I possibly can. Instead of emptying
the pool, instead of instead of not doing anything and just kind of drifting back into, I don't know,
I don't give a shit about it. Whatever. Try to ground yourself and deal with each thing as it
comes to you at one at a time. Otherwise, you're just going to drive yourself batshit crazy.
And I can't even tell you how many times I've been in a situation, guys, where I've had a ton
of stuff to deal with and a ton of stuff to think about, that I just, I throw it all off to the side
and I just, I'm too overwhelmed to even think about doing any of the things that I've wanted
to do or wanted to say or deal with the bad things that are happening. You never want to
tackle everything at the same time. And as much as sometimes that can be unavoidable,
and that's one of the main problems with life in general, guys, is sometimes it's unavoidable.
Sometimes you just have a bunch of shit that is going on at the exact same time that you're just,
you don't, it's hard to not just open the pool and let everybody jump in. And like I said before,
if this made no sense at all, I'm going to listen to this back and I'm going to be like,
why do they, why would they ever want to take advice from me? I just told them there was a
fucking pool party going on in my brain. Like they're going to think I'm crazy.
No, all right. Ground yourself, get grounded. We're going to move on from that. I just wanted
to throw that out there because there's been a whole lot of stuff going on in my head recently,
both good and bad. But remember, this is not talking about like, oh, how everything is so bad,
everything is so bad. No, no, no. It's just when you have too much to think about and too many
things going on at the same time, you can, it can rack your brain. And that was the point
of what I just said. Don't worry. I'm fine. I hope all you guys are fine as well. How have you all
been? Hopefully great. But let's move on. We're going to talk about PAX Prime now because I'm
going to PAX Prime. I will be there all four days. I can't believe it's actually four days. It was
four days last year too, which is crazy to think about that they're going on like almost a full
work week, five days almost for PAX. And some people show up days earlier and stay days later.
And that's like almost an entire week. And it's, it's a lot, but I'll be there. I will see you guys
there. If you are going and you want to come say hello, please do not hesitate to say hello. I say
this every time a PAX comes around that I'm going to, but please, if you see me and you want to say
hello, please do it. Please. I'm telling you, I will sit there and we'll talk for a little bit.
I'll chat with you and I'll do a meetup too. Check my Twitter, probably on Sunday afternoon.
That's when it'll be happening. And that's pretty much all I got to say about PAX. It's going to be
fun. It's going to be exciting. Could you guess that's one of the things that's currently on my
mind right now? Probably, but that's going to wrap the video up guys. Thank you all so much for
watching. I really do appreciate it and take care of your pools. Take care of your pools. Make sure
there's no like algae growing at the bottom of your pool. Cause then you got to get that vacuum
and you got to scrub with them. It never really works that well scrubbing like the
vacuum at the bottom of the algae and the, and then there's like the bugs that get in there.
Get those bugs out of that pool. Get the bugs out of there. I mean, that's gross. Nobody wants those
little bugs in the pool. And hey, before you come in the pool, just step in that little gross bucket
of water to wash your feet up. By the way, before this video ends, what is that? How come that,
why do we have that bucket of gross like sewage water that never seems to get cleaned that you're
supposed to step into and then go into the pool? That's like, that's like making you more dirty
before you get in the pool, isn't it? Like somebody clean that fucking sewage water. It's disgusting.