Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2.
It's been a while since I've seen some Facecam Fortress 2, and I do apologize about that.
What the hell? What? What? Whoa, hey! That guy's like glitching through the gate!
Uh, this is Balloon Race, by the way, if you didn't know.
How did that guy, like, get through the gate? What a freak show.
Gonna do some Facecam Fortress on Balloon Race.
What the hell? Music is playing in the background right now.
Get back on that ship.
What's up, everybody?
Oh, oh, oh!
What? Did they spawn, like...
What? What?
I have no idea how this mode really, like, works.
Oh, Scout!
They're just, like, appearing on our ship?
BS.
What the? Get what? Pyro, get the hell out of here, man!
How are they getting on our boat? I wish I, like, played this for, like, 15 seconds before recording.
Oh, get that medic.
Give me an overheal, baby. Give me an overheal.
Get out of here, Scout!
Get out of here, Pyro! People are just, like, glitching onto the boat.
Help me! Help me!
Oh, sick dispenser, baby.
Right now, bang.
Oh, you can't... Oh, you can shoot through. Good.
Good, good, good. I was gonna say, that would suck.
Give me more health. This guy's trying to shoot in the window.
Oh, I gotta lead my targets a little bit here.
Try and get it in the window.
I got it in the window.
This is ridiculous.
They're gonna win!
Oh, get crit!
All right, seriously, I need some, uh... I need a medic.
I need a medic right now.
Heal me, man. Heal me.
Come on, heal me.
Come on!
Oh, man!
Let's get up there. I don't have enough health to get up there, actually.
Damn it. Oh, I'm so scared.
It's all right. Get out of here, Heavy.
Get the hell... bang!
Bang!
Can I climb the ladder?
Oh, my God, I can climb the ladder!
I ca...
Apparently, I killed two people.
So, that's how people are getting on the boat. All right.
Here we go, baby. Rocket jump!
Get out of my face!
Uh...
I kinda wanna climb up this thing again. I'm gonna die instantly.
Ah!
I did it again. I killed myself again.
All right, I'm not going over there just yet.
I'm gonna get, uh... I'm gonna get my rage up a little bit here.
So, how the hell do you, uh...
How the hell do you move the boat from here?
What? What? Hey, whoa!
Whoa, what is this guy doing in here?
What? This guy's in our spawn!
That's the glitching demo man from the beginning.
What a son of a bitch.
The guy's just, like, hanging out in the spawn with his, like, glitches.
Let me just hit a tree real quick.
All right, here we go.
What's up, everybody?
Mini Sentry, screw you!
Come here, you...
We don't even have the first point capped.
How do you cap points?
I have no idea what's happening.
I got him.
Pyro coming down the stairs.
Oh, so we have to cap that?
We just, like, stand on the treasure chest?
All right, I think I get it now.
I think... What? Oh.
Get... I seriously have no clue.
It's definitely the treasure chest.
All right, now knowing that, I'm hanging out up here.
Come here.
Oh, let me help this heavy out.
Let's get it! Let's cap it!
Come on!
Come on, everybody! Come on!
Ugh! Dammit!
This is point number one.
There's so much going on right now for my tiny brain to handle.
Oh, we got it. We got it.
Good, good, good. Good job. Good job.
Shoot it back in that window, baby.
Let's get this boat moving.
Oh, ship. I keep calling it different things.
Get back down here.
Let's hide down here.
Ah...
This heavy's freaking out.
That's a good thing.
Oh, long shot. Long shot.
I'm standing still right now.
This is not gonna be good.
There we go.
This huntsman right is just in his glory mode.
They're all swimming.
They're all swimming over here.
Oh, let's beach it. Let's beach it.
Oh, yeah, we're beaching it.
This guy's toast right here.
He died before I could even get to him.
Oh, no, you don't.
Oh, boy.
I'm in trouble.
Are they teleporters?
I am so confused right now.
I'm going in a teleporter.
Can I destroy these?
No, let's go in.
Can I go in?
Dammit, you can't go in.
Get out of town here.
Oh, I can go...
Apparently, I died.
Don't know how.
Apparently, a mini-century.
Who knows?
Whoa.
Dude.
Oh, somebody get hit by that crit.
No, I didn't do good enough.
Well, we're way behind right now.
Shoot it.
Let me shoot through that thing.
This guy's got a wrangled mini-century.
All right, let's go.
I'm going to cause absolute carnage right here.
You ready for this?
Carnage mode activated.
Stickies.
You're pushing me off.
Let's push.
The thing, the boat pushed me off the frigging...
Let's go here.
Is he going to get hit by that crit?
He's standing still.
Oh, I killed two people.
I killed two people with that.
Are you kidding me?
No, you're pushing me off.
That big fat bastion heavy just shoved me off of it.
Oh, you...
Oh my God, that was crazy.
We are so far behind.
I don't know where I'm going,
but apparently, we're going down here.
Get everybody.
Give me like a triple kill right here.
Heal me, Medic.
Come here, you...
He's dead.
Ugh.
Balloon Race is out of control.
Holy crap.
Nobody on...
All right, get on that point.
I got to land some shots.
Oh, they're all coming up here right now.
That guy's got crits.
He can't hit me.
Aha, he can't hit me.
Oh, get it.
Get it, baby.
They capped that point, too.
I'm going to kill that...
No, I got him.
Oh, yeah.
I'm so happy about that shot.
Yeah.
Wait for me.
Wait for me, please.
Please.
Yeah, okay.
Janka.
El Doctor.
Dying, I'm dying.
I'm dying.
Oh, you got to heal me, Medic.
You got to heal me.
Damn it.
We are getting beat pretty bad right now,
I'm assuming.
Judging by the fact that we crit.
Didn't kill anybody with it, though.
And apparently, I still have the rage.
Oh, we're about to lose.
Oh, you scorch shot, son of a bitch.
That guy's got the right idea.
He's got the scorch shot.
You bastard.
Oh, it's over.
It is over right now.
It's over.
It is so over.
We can't...
I keep hitting those people in the back.
All right, we're going for an epic rocket jump super kill.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
I'm on the king of the mountain.
The killer.
I'm just going to stop whipping people.
Are we actually going to cap this?
No, we're not.
Oh, man.
I got to stay alive up here.
Crap.
This is just complete chaos.
Is anybody even going to be able to get this point?
I don't think anyone's going to be able to even cap this point.
It is too chaotic.
Get out of here.
See you later.
I'm gone.
Wow, blue's actually on it.
We're going to cap it.
Is this going to be a tie?
This is going to be a tie, right?
It has to be.
Time has been added.
There's more time left?
What else are we going to do?
No, don't leave without me.
I missed the boat.
So do we just go in a circle?
When does this end?
How do you like beat?
Oh, no vote.
I don't know.
How do you win?
I think we're...
This is just like an open field over here.
I've only played Balloon Race like a couple times,
and maybe like three or four times,
and I loved it,
but I just never really understand what the hell is going on in this game mode.
I'm jumping off the boat.
We're going to try and pick some people off.
Let me get a couple of long-range beauty shots.
Just going to clean people up as they come down.
What's up?
I got crushed.
You're wrangling a sentry from all the way back there.
Holy crap, man.
No, no, no.
Way too many people.
Get rid of this heavy.
Thank you.
And get rid of this guy.
This guy right here.
Get rid of him.
And this guy.
No.
Yay, we did it.
And I got on the top of the scoreboard somehow.
Well, that's going to be it, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching.
Really do appreciate it.
Balloon Race for the return of Facecam Fortress 2.
I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course...
Wait, we won again?
Is that a double victory?
Sweet, dude.
Well, I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
See you all soon.