Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. How's it going? The title is wrong? Yeah, it's bad, isn't it?
Autocorrect and spell check have ruined society. Hold on, I'm about to burp. This is, you hear this?
This is like I'm about to burp voice. I'm holding on to it for a minute. That sounds like I'm about
to cry. Autocorrect and spell check have ruined society. Let me tell you why. Honestly, I just
typed shit and if it's going to be completely wrong, I don't even care. The computer is going
to tell me what I need to fix. I just didn't right click it and fix it. I don't care, leave it.
This looks like I was shit faced. Oh yeah, let's do some science experiments, I guess.
Tweet that out. All right. Hello. Hi. I haven't seen you in four days or so. I haven't seen you
in a while. Chat immediately forgives him after chanting kill for five minutes straight.
You guys, what would you guys do with chanting kill? What's wrong with you guys? You guys need
to relax. Kill? I mean, I could understand be incredibly upset with, you know, why didn't you
write, we're upset with you. We're upset with you. We're okay from now on, right? We're upset with
you. Not kill. Welcome to a little late night stream. Be just hanging out late night. There
was an announcement from a game that I like, which we'll be checking that out this coming week here,
I think on Thursday. Gizmo is in multiverses. He's coming to multiverses. This is literally
one of my favorite movie franchises ever made. I am going to main Gizmo. I don't care how bad
the character is with me. I don't care how bad I am with it. Gizmo from Gremlins is in multiverses.
It's coming this week. Yeah, everybody's like, oh, yeah, I can't wait for Rick. Dude, I can't
wait. Oh, man. Oh, Walter White, maybe. Gizmo got in before all of your favorite characters.
My favorite character got in and none of you even know who it is. No, I'm very, I'm curious.
By the way, yeah, this game has mostly negative reviews on Steam. I don't, I don't, I just,
we were in pre-stream and I was like, you know what, fine, I'll put it, how about Mythbusters?
This is a mostly negative game. Is it going to be, is it that bad? I don't think so. Wait,
let's check it out. Mostly negative. The other options were worse. Excuse me.
Cult of the Lamb and 20 minutes till dawn. Excuse me. I'm very curious. Let's try it.
What if this is amazing? What if you guys, okay, what if this is really fun?
I'm ready. I'm ready to do some experiments. A bad review game usually is a good game for you.
For you. All right. Let's go. I'm ready to play. I think I have it set to go. Bane. Yep. Oh,
hold on a second. Wait. No, I'm not going to say it. There's a ton of new people in the community
over the last year or so. Should we get a new opinion on the Bane voice? I feel like there's
a lot of new people here over the last 24 months. I feel like it's going to be,
I think people are going to like it. I think people will think it's good. There's so much
more people here. There's so much more of a sample. All right. Let's go. Here it is. And
snap my fingers. Snap. There I am too. I wasn't naked in that frame, but whatever. I don't care.
All right. Let's go. Mythbusters crazy experiments simulator. Are we all here? Should I go? Oh,
you need to hear the music. All right. Let's go. So what do you do? We pick an X. Whoa,
this is crashing my computer. Hold on. Welcome to Mythbusters the game. Soon you'll be able to play
the role of a real Mythbuster. Each myth will have its own unique gameplay mechanics, which
you will encounter during the finalization and testing of the experiment. Have fun. Let's go.
This is okay. Hold on. It's 1.0. God damn it. I can't make it lower than this. I got to go
into my actual mouse DPI. Is it mouse settings? Right? Mouse settings. Cursor speed. Let's put it
at, I don't know, like here. Myth busted. Yeah. Okay. Let me see if that helps. All right. I don't
know what to do. I just turned my mouse sensitivity at a hardware level down. Can I? How do I fix this?
How do I fix this? Lower your DPI? Isn't that what I just did? Hold on. Is this DPI? Hold on.
Hardware. Wheel pointer options. Pointer speed. How do I turn the DPI down on my fucking mouse?
Cursor speed is not DPI. Well, where's DPI? It's not in Windows. Where is it? Wait, it's not Windows
mouse speed? Whatever. Okay. I'll deal with it. Can I use the controller? Okay. Go to the myth board
in order to choose a myth. Not a whole lot going on here. That's like we, we got one. It's our,
put it on, stick it on the wall. We're about to make our first $40. Okay. Heroes Gambit.
Action movie heroes tend to find ways to survive a grenade blast within seconds.
Is it possible to survive a grenade explosion by covering it with an object
and hiding behind a suitable cover? Bucket? A barrel? Or maybe a wooden box? What would be
the best way to stop the explosion? Why are we jumping on grenades? Oh, plug with the Mythbusters,
man. First myth of the day. Gary's going to jump on a grenade and fucking explode. And we'll see
how many, what's the point of this? It's going to be one episode of this show. Um, okay. Uh, okay.
Unlock experience. Run for your life. Test the firepower of a grenade. Save the mock-up from...
Okay. So I accept it. Now you're going to pick the first myth for testing. The goal of the game is
to get as popular as possible while still having enough budget for your experiments. During the
game, you will get cards to assemble episodes. Wait, we have to actually make the show?
Appropriate usage of those cards in the episode will allow you to gain higher popularity and budget.
All right. All right. Let's go. Here's my, here's my team. Okay. This is celebrities can make the
audience stick around. His knowledge will be an immense help during your endeavors. And he has
been working with guns and explosives for years. Well, I mean, it's going to be this guy. You bring
the explosives expert. You don't, I mean, yeah, that's correct. Right. Let's go. So how do we do
the experiment? How to survive a grenade. It's called pick it up off the ground and throw it back.
Let's see. How's that? Okay. Test the firepower of a grenade. What's going on? Wait, hold on. My
brain is confused. Where are we? Test the firepower of a grenade. Save the mock-up from,
All right. Click and drag to throw the ball. There's drop it on my leg. What happened?
This is a long cook time on this grenade. Did I do it? It was a grenade. Determine the area
percentage. Click within a body to fill it. What? What happened? Wait, what? I don't understand
what's happening. Click within a body to fill it. Select apply button. How, it has to be at 5%.
I'm so confused. What's happening? The right side. What does it want me to do? Are you sure? I don't
know what it's asking. Read the number on the right. Fill 36%. I mean, this is like 36.
Okay. Oh, all right. I get it. I get it. Okay. Wait. Oh, we're making the grenade. I get it. All
right. Oh, this is easy. I get it. Oh my God. I just, I don't like this. Okay. We need to move.
Oh my, what? I thought I was going to be playing with, I thought I was going to be playing,
whatever. You know what I'm trying to say. Move the tiles. I have 44 moves left. Oh Jesus Christ.
Okay. Hold on. I just have to do it, right? That's it. I don't have to do anything fancy.
All right. Let's go. Solve the equation by moving the specified number of sticks.
I don't think they did this on the show. Okay. Seven times three equals nine plus I can move
two sticks. This is just those, the book of bathroom brain teasers that I used to have.
What's the answer? I don't even care. One times three, one times three equals seven times three
equals nine, 10 to the 12, 13, 14, 15. That's not, that's not 21. 78. What is it? Seven times two.
All right. Seven times two. How do I do that? No. All right. We made the grenade. All right. I made
the grenade. I got it. Okay. Time to do it. Run for, prepare the grenade and build a test mockup.
When you are ready, place everything on the testing grounds. The test mockup does not get
destroyed. Okay. Additional objectives. All right. Okay. Page number, shooting range. Oh, okay. Throw
the grenade. Yeah. Whatever. Whatever. I don't fucking care. Let's go. Let's go to the, let's
go to the fun part where I can experiment. All right. Assembly mode. Look, I just want to be the
fucking celebrity that walks on and just has the safety goggles and is like,
that's all my lines. I don't do anything. I have my own air conditioned trailer.
What are the two songs playing? $150 for a hammer. What? I have to build the grenade?
No, we just buy the grenade. I don't want to build a grenade. Okay. I need nails. One nail. I need
six planks. Oh my God. This looks like I don't want to even be in this room. I need a wood saw.
Where's my actual money? My popularity is a thousand. Okay. Buy a grenade. Buy this thing.
I need six wooden planks. How many do these do I need? How many nails?
Seven nails. How many do I have? Okay. What is this? Why would I buy saws? Spending all my money.
By the way, isn't this my workshop? Why would I need to buy things in my own workshop?
All right. Wooden plank. I need six. They don't show this process on TV.
All right. Check your notebooks on page three. Okay. Oh, okay. Let's build it. Well,
this is where the music is coming from. Craft. A piezoelectric grenade. Remove the grenade fuse.
I want to remove the grenade fuse. Okay. Mount a grenade to mount a grenade.
How you so fused by holding down? I would not want to be in this room. Okay. Okay. This is my
grenade. This is my Molotov grenade. All right. So now what do I do with this? Move wrench to the
tool belt. Where's the wrench? Oh, okay. And hammer on the tool belt too, right? Is this a detonator?
All right. Let's go. I got that. Close backpack. Tab. Choose wrench. You bet your ass I'm trying
to throw it. I can't throw it. All right. What do I do now? No, no, I don't want another one.
So check your notebook page four. Assemble the saw. Page four. Please refer to page five.
Okay. Assemble the saw. I think that I just have to get this stuff ready, right? Prepare the saw for
cutting. All right. Let's go. Wrong tool. I need a wrench. Okay. Ooh. Satisfying sound effects.
Okay. The machine's ready to work. So what do I do now?
Don't lie down. Don't like put your neck under here. All right. I'm ready to work.
That's not good. Get me out of this. Okay. Cool. So it's assembled, right? We're good. Using the saw,
get wooden beam piece. Okay. How do I use it? What the fuck was that? Oh, okay. I get it.
Wooden plank piece. You don't want to be going fast in this environment. There should be points
for speed. Okay. So I got everything. Check your notebook. What's wrong with my drugs? What's wrong
with my face? All right. Now what? What page am I on? All right. So I need a hammer.
Okay. I need a hammer. I got a hammer. Hammer. Go to the big workshop and make a mock-up.
Oh, all right. Here we go. Test mock-up. I don't want to. I just, I'll be honest,
I just didn't want to read any of that. I didn't want to read any of it. Any of it. I didn't read
a sentence. It's good, right? Okay. It's in. Now we, what the fuck am I making? What is this?
I'm making a shitty mailbox for like my second grade class. What is this supposed to be? Um,
middle with bonnet, middle with cowboy hat. Oh, you bet your ass. If I was on this episode,
I would be like, yeah, let me do it. I'd be like hitting it with the hammer and I would hit it hard
and put, pretend my thumb got hit and go like, oh, and put it like into my mouth and shit. What
am I doing? Why? What am I doing with this? Okay. Put it on the truck. Okay. Head to the shooting
range. How? Oh, okay. Shooting range. Okay. The cleanup crew is coming. So what? Check your
notebook on page six. Start the myth and activate explosives. Use to reduce the radius of the
explosion with shields. Used to reduce the radius of the explosion and space for all large tests.
What do you, what do you want? Lethal zone. Okay. Here you will start the experiment and start the
test sequence. You will need to have an appropriate tool in order to start. I need a button. Okay.
Take the test mock up to the say, all right, let's go. Where is it? It's on the truck. Okay.
We didn't really need to bring the whole truck for this. I got to put this in the back of
somebody's car. We didn't need to bring the truck for one item. Where is it? Where's my cardboard
cutout? Take the test mock up to the safe zone. Where is it? I loaded it in the truck. What
happened? It escaped. What? Dude, you're the test. Is it in my inventory? No. Where is it?
What happened? It's behind the truck. What? No, it's not. Where is it? Hey, where is it?
Uh, is it, is it not there? Did I, is it, am I soft-locked? I have to make a new one, loser.
Go to the shooting range. It was on the stand there. Was it? Well, I told me,
I didn't have to take it out of the truck. Who do you think drove you there?
That's funny. Where is he? Where is this thing? Where is this guy? I'm serious. Where is he?
The grenade's still on the shop's table. No, it's not. I have it in my inventory.
That guy didn't want to die. Where is he? Look behind you on a stand. It's not here.
No, behind you. Check the box, maybe. I think I have, I think it's fucked up. I think it's
screwed up. I think I have to restart it. Large menu items. It's in the house. It's where the
arrow is pointing. Yeah, there's nothing there. I can't do anything about it. Yeah, take the
test mock-up to the safe zone, which is here. Walks in front of the truck. Shit! Wait, what's
this? What's this? No. Wait, was it really? It was not there. I think it's gone. I just think it's
gone. Okay. I don't know what, I don't even know what items those were. Did I actually lose it?
Fuck. I actually think it's screwed up. Oh, that's not good. What do I do? Should I start over?
I don't think I want to start. Should I start over, man? I feel like all you guys are going to
leave. Who raided? Is it Raid? I don't even see who, I can't see who raided. Who didn't rejoin?
Wait, who? Slime? Slimesicle Raid, what's up? Hey, we just started the stream. Thanks a lot.
Slimesicle, appreciate it. Welcome everybody from Slimesicle's stream. We're just getting started
here. Gonna be busting some myths. Just turned the stream on for the first time. You joined at the
perfect opportunity. Time to bust some myths. What do we got today for our first one? Run for
your life? What, I have to make a grenade? This is fucking different than last time. What? What?
Did I win? Skip it. Skip. I don't care. Why can't I move this one? Fuck. Just skip it.
Fail it over and over again. Look, I'm too stupid. See? All right, we got the grenade. We're good.
Okay, cool. Yep. Well, got it. All right, let's go get the items. How many nails? Seven? One?
Wasn't it seven? It was seven nails last time. I'm so confused. What's wrong with my guy? This
fucking music is fucked. How many do I? Wooden, three wooden planks. I need the start button.
Okay, cool. Yep, I got it. I won't laugh. You laugh, you lose. If I laugh, I have to turn the
stream off. Why turn the music down? This doesn't count. This doesn't count. The music is at fucking
zero percent. Okay, it was the radio. No, starting now. That doesn't count. Starting now. Starting
now. If I laugh, I'll turn the stream off. Where's the sound? Why is there no sound? This is going
to get DMCA. Whatever. I don't really care. We're just doing just generic. Just generic. I'm not
adding anything weird. Just right side, left. Just generic. Okay, take item. I'm holding it in my
hands right now. Into the truck. Bring it to the truck. Okay, I'm in the truck. Drop in the truck.
That didn't do that last time. I don't know what it did last time, but not that. I'm ready. I'm
running to the beat. Let's go. There we go. Yes. What? Hey, hey, hey. What do I do? I don't know
what to do. What's the point of this guy? What's the point of this guy? Leave it on the board?
Put the Tessa objects in the appropriate slots and protect them from the explosion. I can't
fucking take it anymore. It's been six minutes. I've turned it off. Wow. Whoa. Wait, I can edit
the episode? Okay, go to your laptop. There's shit everywhere. Okay, I can edit the video.
That scared me. I didn't know what that was. That was actually terrifying. Okay,
find nice messages from fans. Okay. Progress and then the Mythmaker Studio. All right, let's go
for it. Each episode has five empty slots that can be filled with collected cards. All right,
we had Sergeant. We said Sergeant Daniel is there. Each episode is 45 minutes. Wait,
we're going to spend 20 minutes targeting Sergeant Daniel? Sounds pretty good to me.
Good afternoon. We have a great idea for an experiment. Consider this. Can a chair with
enough balloons fly? I hope we understand each other. Waiting for some good material. That means
they don't like the show. Your show is really nice. I like it very much. I like it. Good show. Good
luck in your future endeavors. Hey, thanks. Thanks, Michael Brown. Cool. All right. Do I sleep in
this? Go to the myth board. All right. Where's the myth board? Oh, right here. Of course. Balloon
chair. All right. I'm doing balloon chair and then I'm never playing this game again. Yeah,
sure. I don't want to make a go. I don't want to make a grenade for the balloon chair. I don't.
I don't. What do you want me to do? Oh, I got it. All right. Cool. Sick. This game's sick.
How many degrees does a right angle have? 90. All right, we got it. Okay. Time to go and check my
notebook. This game's cute. This game's cute. Come on. This is cute. Okay. Pork. Wait, why am I
getting pork for? Is the Mythbuster to make like a pork chop sandwich for somebody? How many bottles?
He loathes it. I didn't say that. How many more bottles of water do I need? Water times one. Water
times one. How many waters do? Oh, this is a bottle. Never mind. I thought it was blue. I thought
they were water bottles. Whatever. Where's the? Oh, okay. Cool. Let's assemble it. This is my
favorite part. Go to the pump station. Gelatin in the bucket? No, not cement. What do I do?
Press the valve? Press and hold the valve. I like the way this sounds. How do I do it?
Where's the press and hold the valve? Check the ballistic gel proportions. What does that mean?
I need 10 to 20 percent pork gelatin and 80 to 90 percent water. Oh, shit. Hold on. Whoa! That's way
too much. Oops. Everybody all right? Everybody move. Nobody's got glass in them or anything?
No, I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do. I do.
Hold on. Let's go. 20 percent. Oh, come on. 20 percent. And then 80 percent water. Like that,
right? We good? Oh, dude. Fucking science. Ballistic gel hand? Oh, dude. Science! Do we have a
ballistic gel hand? Dude, that's only possible with freaking science. Make a second hand? Well,
why did you tell me to make? Science actually is pretty cool. It is. It's fun. Look, I will take
science over math. I will take science over social studies. I will take science over English
class every single time. No matter what. Every time. Make a second hand? Oh, that's wrong. What
about geography? No, I would have liked school a lot more if it was 40 percent science class. Like,
20 percent gym. And then 40 percent. All right. 30 percent science. 20 percent gym. 20 percent
lunch. And then like 30 percent like who invented stuff. That would be cool to me. Like,
inventor is 101. Like, oh, we learn about like every invention that ever was invented and who
made it and what their patents are and shit. Kind of fucking cool, don't you think? Oh, and what
credit score is and how to write a check and what like taxes are. Would have been kind of nice if
they told us that. You know, just saying. All right. Let's open the notebook. All right. So,
here we go. It's time to do this. I need the wrench. We're going to put the things together.
I'm not this cute. OK, item checklist. Let's go. I'm ready. You're 40. You should know by now.
I do now. And I have for the last probably five to 10 years. I did not know this until I was
probably in my early to mid 20s. It took way too long. It shouldn't have. I should. It shouldn't
have waited until I was like 25 to understand all this stuff. Like 23, 24, 25, 26. I knew what it
was, but I didn't understand how it worked. And you know what? Sometimes I still kind of don't
understand how the fuck that works because it's different everywhere. All right. I need the parts.
The craft. The buster. Collect all the needed. Aren't they all here?
Teenagers don't know to know credit scores. No, but teenagers that grow into adults need to know
what a credit score is. And teenagers that grow into adults need to know about like financial
literacy and all the things that come with it. I don't know why we wait so long. OK, cool.
Where do I get this stuff? Collect all the needed parts. What is it? I need steel rod 15. Oh,
they're not going to help me anymore. The tutorial is over. OK, I need 15 steel rods. Where are those?
Oh, just spend all my money on cement. You got it. I don't know why it feels like a Mr. Beast video.
I filled this bowl with cement up to my neck. Uh, where is it? Steel rods. Oh, here we go.
Steel pipe. Steel rod piece. I don't know what any of this means. Steel rod piece. Just buy five of
them. This is what I would do. I would just buy five of these and just bring it to the contract
and go. This might be way more, but just keep whatever you keep and use whatever you don't need.
Like for another project, you don't have to pay me. I don't care. I just want to make sure
it's right. All right, so 15. Oh, I need more than that. 15. Well, how many did I buy? Five. OK, 13
screws. Any buster head, buster torso, buster pelvis, buster limb, buster hand, buster foot.
What is that? All right, 13 screws. OK, where's buster? Buster head? Buster hand? What is that in
construction terms? What is a buster head, a buster torso, buster arm? What is that? Buster. Wait,
where is this? Oh, it's the dummy. Where do I find the dummy? It's the name of the dummy. Well,
OK. Oh, buster. I got to cut up the steel rod. Where's the saw bench? Where's the saw bench?
I forget where it is. There it is. All right, I need steel rod piece.
Saw blade damaged? What are you talking about? The wrong material was cut. What? I broke this?
Oh, it's a wood saw. God damn it. City boy. You know why? OK, I don't know how to change
a tire either. Very, very important thing to know because I could know and I could learn,
but I know I would screw it up. I would screw it up. And my fear of knowing that when I put that
tire on, I'm going to get back on the fucking highway and my car is going to flip over like
GTA. Somebody that knows what they're doing has to do that, not me. I just have this crazy fear.
Oh, yeah, man. No, you're fine. Just pop the hood and connect this and then take that out
and put this back in. My car is going to explode if I do it. I will put everything and I'll follow
the YouTube tutorial instructions or whatever, and I'll be like, OK, pause the video. Rewind 10
seconds. Watch it again to make sure I'm doing exactly what that guy just did. Verbatim with his
hands. OK, done. When I close the lid to the engine, the car is going to explode the second
that it latches in the front. I can't. I just can't do it. I'm too afraid of it. Change a tire on
stream. I wouldn't be able to. YouTube University. No, you don't pop the hood to change the tire.
I'm just saying, like, in general, mechanical stuff like that I'm terrified of. It's not hard
to change a tire. I know it doesn't matter. So, yeah, you pop the trunk, pop the hood to get to
the tire. Yeah, I'm telling you, I'm going to have the wrench in my hand. I'm going to be sitting
there like, all right, pop the tub. Pop the top of it. Yeah. Looks like that screw is loose in there.
Yeah, kill the engine, mate. Kill the engine. Go, go, go, go, go, go. All right, let me get in there.
And I'm going to get in there and I'm going to put the wrench around the nut or whatever.
And I'm going to go and I'm going to wake up in front of the pearly gates. It's going to be like,
yeah, man, I'm good to go. Yeah, no, this looks good. I think this is correct. I'm awake.
Something killed me. I just wake up at the pearly gates and fucking Peter's going to be like, wow,
man, you don't even know how to change a tire. He just fires me down to hell. I look over and I see
over like the pearly gates, I see like all the mechanics. They're all sitting there and they're
all like, yeah, waving to me. It's just like a shitload of mechanics and like electricians.
What do I need? Peter Griffin is dead because bad. Wait, but hold on. It doesn't mean like
Sekiro on stream means I get to go to heaven. And that's logic. Hold on. Why are we tying?
Oh, why am I tying like professional skill to you go to heaven? That doesn't make any sense.
These guys were all car mechanics. If you're not a car mechanic, you go to fucking hell.
What am I talking about? That doesn't make any sense. This game must be pretty boring for you
to talk about this. Playing video games with the skill is not worthy of heaven. Hey, all dogs go
to heaven. Some dogs go to hell. Can you imagine that's the sequel? Oh, Disney presents some dogs
go to hell. Rated PG. There is a sequel. What? Do I even have this thing? No, I don't. What was
the name? Was it all dogs go to heaven too? Colon, some dogs go to hell. Where? Okay,
I need the saw blade. I'm good. I'm good. I'm on it. I'm back on it. I'm back on it.
Do I have enough screws to put this on? Okay. Let's get back to this, please. He thinks he's
so funny. No, I think that was funny. I don't think everything I say is funny. I think that
was genuinely humorous. Typo in the title, hee hee. You know what? Yeah, fuck that. That just sucks.
We're getting rid of it. I'm changing it to some dogs go to hell. No, that's like weird at a context.
Um, how about just like, science. Okay. I mean, it's only going to be the title for like another
15 minutes, if I'm honest. Play something else. Why are you playing this and not gloom wood?
I don't know. I'll play gloom wood eventually. Is it out? I thought it wasn't out yet.
Oh, it came out in early access. Okay. There are three all dogs go to heaven movies?
How many of these do I need? How many? Did I? How many of those do I need? All dogs go to heaven.
Hold on. Wait, there's three movies? All dogs go to heaven. The series friends to the rescue
and all dogs Christmas carol. All dogs go to heaven too. What's the main character's name?
The dog from all dogs go to heaven. Charlie. All dogs go to heaven three. Charlie's inferno.
Why is there a countdown? Okay. So now I need I have steel rod pieces. I need the
I gotta hit those put Buster's head together. Buster. Here we go. Press the F, dude, please.
What? I just did. What do you mean? What's wrong? This feels weird. Something about this just says
this feels weird, but like somehow wrong. How do I make this? Um, okay. I need to make the head
with the no. I need to make ballistic goo. Okay. Ballistic gel head. I need. Okay. Ballistic goo.
How do I need? What is this? Not cement or whatever it is. I don't know how much this. I
don't know. I'm just gonna get it though. Water tank. I need a few of these. Okay. Um, is it a
ballistic Buster's torso? But is it ballistic torso? Am I missing that? Oh, there's already
one here. All right. Um, no bottle to fill. Here we go. Okay. 20%. 90%. Is Buster already made?
What happened to it? Okay. 20%. That's it, right? 20 and what's going on? How do I get it?
It's going to blow. Just take it. Unknown substance added to backpack. That how is this
making any sense? What am I doing wrong? It's 20% and 80% or 10% and 90%. Right? 10% 90%.
How am I doing this wrong? 20% 80%. I did stop it at a hundred. It didn't do anything. 20%.
I can't. If I go any more further, it's going to explode. Ballistic gel. Okay. I need poly
polypropylene granules or ballistic gel. That's what I'm trying to make right now. Ballistic gel.
I'm trying to make ballistic gel right now. Okay. 10 to 20% gel and 80, 90%. How is this wrong?
Potion of helium. Is this Harry Potter? A portion of helium. Okay. Ballistic gel is I'm going to do
15%. That's 15% right there, right in the middle. And I'm going to do 85%. I would help me. What's
happening? 15% 80, 85%. Science is magic. That's not 85. Yes, it is. Take the bottle now. It doesn't
know what it. All right. All right. I've, I've, I've had it 15 plus 85 is a hundred. Okay. I'm doing
10, 10 and 90, 10 and 90%. It has to be correct. Didn't you want all classes to be science?
I actually don't know what's happening. Neither do I. Imagine how gross it is if you get splashed
with pork, gelatin and water. Yeah. This keeps hitting me right in the face. Okay. Here we go.
I'm going to do 10 and 90. Should I do 20? 10 plus 80 is 90. Put the water in first.
How? What am I doing wrong? Water first. I'm going to do 80%. 80% water. Now gelatin.
I'm going to get kicked out of this place. 10 and 80. Don't fill the hole away.
Dude, this is genuinely worse than the clock. How is this worse than the clock? I'm doing what it
says is I'm supposed to be doing. There's your 10 and 80%. It doesn't work. Look, 15 gelatin
and then water up to 90. Bro, none of your hypothesis works. 10 plus 70. Hey, I got a
hypothesis. Flip the recipe. How does that sound? Didn't work. Is that pork? Yeah, it's pork gelatin.
These jello shots. Yeah, I made jello shots with bone broth and vodka. First one to puke loses.
Um, does anyone understand what's going on? Cause I think we've tried every combination.
It's the wrong gelatin. Pork gelatin and water. This is pork gelatin down here.
Take the bottle off before it explodes. Holy shit. I already did that. Why? Unknown substance.
Oh my God. How much bullshit is in here? Please tell me he's pretending. Um, all right. I am
going to hover over gelatin and I want everyone to scream the stop sign when they want me to stop.
I'm going to do it very slow. Yeah. Yeah. Fuck that. Look at all these people saying this shit.
I don't get it. Oh my God. I'm screaming. Okay. How about this? This is like 15%.
80. Like this is correct. That's correct. This is correct. More water. More water. More water. No,
no, no, no, no. A bit more water. It's not there. The white circle is the gelatin combined. Yeah,
I know. 80 to 90% water. That is, that is legitimately what we are looking at right now.
This is legitimately, legitimately what we're looking at. He's definitely not sober. Yes,
I am. Take it. Why do I have four of these? What didn't it say? Uh, now I got a clay mass.
I don't wait. So I need to make a bunch of clay. I need clay and water. All right. So I need clay.
This is a pain in the ass. Is there salami? Can I make salami water? Worst gamer moment. That no,
it was not. I, that's horse shit. If you say that actual horse shit, don't say that. I,
I tried it like five different ways. Okay. Here we go. What is it? What's the combination?
20 to 50% clay, 20 to 50% water. All right. What's going half and half? Here we go again.
40 and 40. That's perfect. Yeah. That's, that's it. 40, 40 and 40. That's it. It's done. See? See,
a lot of you guys got that wrong, apparently. Yeah. You apparently got that wrong. Okay. I got
clay. Now I need helium. Try to just make more. I'm going to make one more. Probably need it.
All right. Now I need to, let's see if I can put this together. I got to put the
in here, right? Um, where's the head? This is a torso, right? Okay. Ballistic torso. Uh, okay.
So, okay. We need ballistic. What else? Ballistic feet? Oh my God. It takes so much of this stupid
ass gel. I need to make more. I need to make way more then. All right. Throw this away.
Gel and water is fine. What was it again? 15 and I need more bottles. Why are you wasting so much
stuff? Um, because it's not real. Oh, balloons. 20 balloons is 630 fucking dollars. And what are
you talking about? Oh, right. Okay. All right. Let's get it. This is 15%. 80%. That should do it
right there. I, what, what happened? What happened? 15 and what's going on? 15, 80%. That's 10, 20,
30, 40, 50, 60, 70, 80. Yay. Is that your real, real voice? Yeah. Here we go. Oh, let's do, let's
just do, I'm gonna just make a ton of them. This is worse than school. No, it, it isn't. No, it is
not. Oh, also a lot of you would be interested. Um, I have to change my Dark Souls tier list.
I have to change my Dark Souls, you know, what I find to be, what's the best Dark Souls? What's the
best Prime software game? I have to change it. I played Dark Souls 3 recently. I was just kind
of messing around on the couch. You're like, oh, why not? I'll play Dark Souls 3 for no reason.
I don't like that game. I don't like that game. I don't like it. Demon's Souls is better. God,
I knew it was going to pop and it scared me. The skill issue. No, you know what I figured out about
Dark Souls 3 that I didn't really pay attention to? There, every area has just the annoying group
of people that are firing projectiles at you from across the map. Think of all the areas in Dark
Souls 3 and think of how many times you go, wow, this is really fucking annoying. Somebody's just
firing missiles at me. What's up with that? What's up with that? Hey, guess what? Bloodborne's a
perfect game. Besides the fact that it's 30 FPS and it's only on PlayStation. Why won't they just,
just release it for the love of God? You know, they could, Sony could probably say,
oh, we're increasing the price of Bloodborne Remastered to a hundred dollars and we'd all
still buy it, right? Like they would, I would buy it. A lot of you would buy it. I mean,
it would be bullshit. It would be absolute horse shit, but we would. Rich Andy. I would hate it.
Whatever. I have enough. I need two of these. It has shit graphics, but that's what I mean,
a remaster. It doesn't have shit graphics. It's just older, like almost 10 years old.
You're enabling the company to do that in the future. Yeah, that's true. Nevermind.
Bloodborne sucks. It doesn't. I played literally Bloodborne in Dark Souls 3 back to back,
just messing around. Polly had never played Bloodborne before. So it was like, holy shit,
this is amazing. All right. When somebody has not played a From Software game and you know they
haven't and they're into the series, that's like bringing, that's like your friend and you go watch
all the Marvel movies back to back and they've never seen it. Or like the Lord of the Rings
movies. It's just, I can't wait to watch you watch Lord of the Rings, right? It's a better game. I
don't need to make three of these. No, Marvel was a bad, okay. Yeah, sure. Marvel was a bad example.
I would have said the same thing about Game of Thrones, but after like season five or six of
Game of Thrones, it was kind of just like, ah, no, don't, you don't, don't watch it. I remember
people being like, oh man, Game of Thrones, season seven and season eight are coming out.
Should I start? Oh, I should definitely start. Should I watch it? And I'm just like, well,
yeah, yeah. I mean, it's a, it's great. It's a great series. Oh, I can't wait to see what happens.
Yeah, I know. Me too. Me too. And they're like, what are you talking about? Ah, you know,
when was the last time you watched the Varys scene? Oh my God. That's right. It's been a while.
Oh, did I not make any other? What did I, what did I make? How many? I have to make so much of this?
Okay, so I made, I didn't make any arms. This is good enough though, I think. This, I think this
is fine. Do we really need to make it? Oh no, I made the torso. Okay, so I need legs. Where's,
where's that? What is this? I think this is a leg, right? Yeah, I need two of these, but yeah.
Game of Thrones, we'll see. Wait, isn't there, I said Lord of the Rings, isn't it? Doesn't Lord
of the Rings and Game of Thrones both have new shit that's available to watch right now? Is it
worth it? Should I watch it? Is it all right? No, they suck. Do they? I don't know. Do they?
I think I can make four of these. I haven't heard great things about it. I like Rings of Power.
Rings of Power is good? Okay. The Lord of the Rings one is good. They suck. Don't let the fan
boys tell you otherwise. I mean, I don't know. It's so difficult to do that though. I honestly,
at some point it's like, okay, Lord of the Rings was a thing. They made the Hobbit series and people
kind of said, mm, these are all right. It's like after the, these are all right. And it was Peter
Jackson that did that. I don't know. I feel like it's hard to make anything else. I don't know.
I could be wrong. Is it worse? This guy's got so many. Okay. Hold on. I need one, two, three,
four. I need four more limbs and two hands. This is elaborate. House of the Dragon is the Hobbit
of Game of Thrones. Okay. Okay. I actually didn't really hate the Hobbit movies that much. I thought
they were a little stretched out and a little weird. Some of the CG in the Hobbit movies was
kind of odd. I remember there was one in particular. There was, there was a lot of CG that kind of just
felt strange in those movies. It was like really, yeah, it was weird. I need to make more of that
fluid. House of the Dragon is actually good. This is pretty divided then. I need more pork. Is there
pork in here? Because they filmed it at 48 instead of 24 FPS. Yeah. It's something like that, right?
Give it time. I am absolutely not dogging the show. Settle down. It's fine. Would you sell your soul
for infinite money? No. There's only so much you can buy with money before. It's just like,
what the fuck else do you, what do you do now? You know what I mean? It's like, oh dude, infinite
money. Infinite money. All right. So I could get a plane, a boat, and like five houses. Then it's not,
what else? Okay. What else? Dude, you have infinite money. All right. Can I rebuild it? Okay. Can I
rebuild every school in America? Can I spend it on other people? Because that might be worth it.
If I sold my soul for infinite money and I literally fixed every problem in the world,
and then I would just be essentially the one that had to get sacrificed. I mean that,
all right. Do I get to have a cool life for like the next 40 or 50 years? Uh, two more, right? I
mean, if I had infinite money, I would, I don't know, I'd, I'd go all out. I'd go baller mode
on myself, right? For like, okay, for like five years, you would not hear from me at all, ever.
I would just disappear and do a bunch of crazy shit as like a billionaire. And then I would come
back. I had fucking bags under my eyes. Be like, all right, it's time to fix this shit. And I would
rebuild every school in America. I'd make, I would plant like fucking hundreds of miles worth of
crops. I would redo our entire education system. I, okay, at that point I'm back and I'm ready to
go. But you, I get, I get a few years where I'm just going to just fuck off and just, I don't know,
live on an island and eat like coconuts and shit. And have like, have like 5G internet on the island.
Just give me, give me like five years for me just to like be a fucking nutcase. And then I'm back
with like a golden suit and a golden top hat and a golden cane. Who am I kidding? I'd be dead.
Are you serious? I would, I'd be dead. Oh dude, what would you do with the, with infinite money?
Well, I would be, I would like bungee jump in a gold suit and way too much and snap the thing and
die. I mean, you know, I'm being honest. We're just getting assassinated. But, but hold on,
but what hap, wait, but what about the money? Is it, okay, we got to clarify a few things here.
Is it a genie scenario where I have to, I have to essentially be alive, right? Like it's me.
And if I'm not around, I can't just like go like this and wave the gold cane around.
So, so it's the devil. Is it the devil? Is it a genie? Is it a, how am I coming? What's my
motivation? Give me some direction here. You get kidnapped. Yeah, but, but that's my point. Like,
but do I, listen, does, do I have to be like, oh, great powerful sorcerer, I would like a hundred
dollars to pay for my bar tab. Like, how does this work? We need some context. It's just a credit
card with no limit and then you don't ever have to pay it back. Okay, but do I have to swipe it or
can somebody take my infinite credit card thing and use it? Because then, yeah, I am making it
24 hours. Okay. Oh, breaking news. It seems that this man, Jeremy Albertson from Las Vegas, Nevada,
has in his possession, crazy enough, the infinite money credit card. Anyone who possesses this card
can purchase anything in an infinite amount with no repercussions. I would go to the grocery store
and there'd be a million people waiting for me. No, no, I don't want that thing. It's a golden
McDonald's card. No, yeah, no fucking way. No, thanks. But if I really had infinite money, yeah,
I would just disappear. I'd go on a five-year bender and that's not what you guys think it is.
You know what I mean? That's getting wicked high on the couch for like a week or two straight
sometimes watching like tool videos, right? You know what I mean? It's not what you think it is.
Where's the hands? It's clearly exactly what I think it is. No, no, tool, like actual tool videos.
I'm not going to be sitting there just high, just like,
it's being like, I know the piece is bent because I watched it. I'm just sitting there like,
I'm talking, well, I mean, I would probably, I may watch a few of those.
It wouldn't be the only thing I did. It's taking me like 40 minutes to make this.
Okay, now we just have to hammer. Oh, it's a hammer. What? Oh, come on. What about a
McDonald's life pass? What if someone offered you a McDonald's life pass, but to get it one year,
you have to eat McDonald's every day and nothing else. No, why would I do that? That's not,
that's not, that isn't, no thanks. How much is a McDonald's meal?
Okay, if I had to eat three meals at McDonald's a day, that would be, what is a, what's like a
number, number one or number two, 10, 15 bucks, like 20 bucks, maybe like $16 maybe
for like two meals or something. All right, so let's just say it's $30 a day. So you're telling
me, so this is effectively what you were saying and this is why it's not worth it. So $30 a day
turns into 30 times, uh, seven, right? So that's $210 a week times four. That's $840 a month
times 12. So you are giving me effectively $10,000 to eat McDonald's every single day.
No, that's not even close to being enough money. That's $10,000 for a year's worth of McDonald's.
No, you add two zeros to that. I ain't eating McDonald's every single day for a year for 10
grand worth of McDonald's. No way. Are you kidding me? Make that, make that 10 million,
make that a million, then I'll do it. No, actually I wouldn't. No, I wouldn't. I would not eat
McDonald's every day for a year for a million dollars. You just die. It wasn't, okay, what,
supersize me was like 30 days. Imagine if it supersized me. He was like, yeah, I'm going to
eat McDonald's three meals a day every single day for a year. I think he, I don't know if he,
would he be alive every day? Who is he talking to? You, of course. Who do you think I'm talking to?
And don't get me wrong. McDonald's is one of my favorite places on earth. And I genuinely mean
that. I love that place. I wouldn't want to eat it every single day. I wouldn't want to eat ice cream
every day either. Too much of a good thing kind of sucks. All right, what do I do with this? Would
you eat ice cream every single day for 10 grand? You have to eat it like twice a day. Would you
though? No, you wouldn't. I don't, after like a month or two, you'd be like, I feel sick every day.
And we're talking full fat ice cream. None of this, none of this like oat milk ice cream. None of
this like lactose free ice cream. We're talking ice cream, ice cream, milk, fat, whole milk,
cream, ice cream. You have to eat it three times a day. I didn't already do this. Ballast in the
fountain. What is a ballast? Oh, clay mass and a jerry can. All right, so I need more clay, clay
mass. Wait, is this pork in here? What's going on? Okay, clay and it's just the same thing I was doing
before. If they paid for the ice cream, then yes. I feel like it would be the same thing as McDonald's.
It would be too much. How are you busting myths right now? That's actually a really good question.
Yeah, what myth am I busting? Oh, right. See if you fly away with balloons. That's what it was.
What would your, what would your brand of ice cream be? Wait, if I had ice cream, like an ice cream.
Oh, shit. What would my ice cream flavor be if I would have an ice cream? Shut up. It'd be,
it'd be a chocolate ice cream. And they would be gobs of cookie dough in it. And I'm talking a
smooth chocolate ice cream. Not this like, not like the kind of cocoa dark kind of chocolate. No,
no, no, no, no, no. Smooth milk chocolate ice cream with marshmallow swirls, swirls of like a
marshmallow fluff, like swirls in it. Cookie dough, not chocolate chips. They get, they're annoying.
And like cookie, like cookie crumbles, soft cookie crumbles. Wait, that's cookie dough.
All right. Take out the cookie dough and add like soft cookie, chocolate chip cookie crumbles,
soft, chewy, and graham crackers. And it would be called the fat fuck. $120 for a chair.
Wait, this exists? It's called cookie cobblestone? Oh, no, it already exists.
Cookie cobblestone. What? What this? I need this. Where do I get this? Look at this. This is called
cookie cobblestone. Where is it? Check this out. Okay. Let me see. Chocolate ice cream,
cookie dough, marshmallow swirls, and crushed cookie pieces. What? How come they stole this from me?
This is amazing. I want this right now. This is rocky. You know it's not rocky road. I don't know
what rocky road tastes like. They must've made this like 10 minutes ago. They must've just made
this. Okay. Cookie cobblestone. That's my jam right there. I want this. Is this something like,
it was back in like 2002. It doesn't exist anymore. That looks damn good. Nice job, Eddie's.
Seriously. We connect on stuff, you and I. Eddie's, you and I get it. I mean, some of the world's best
ice cream since, you know, since 1928. I'm just saying. I mean, it's the world's, one of the
world's most tastiest ice creams. Why am I buying bullets? Why am I buying a gun? Stop fighting,
stop fighting your lip. You want that sponsor so bad? Hey, Eddie's, got a couple of streams coming
up. Why would anybody sponsor? Why would an ice cream company sponsor this stream? They would open
up the stream for five minutes and go, nope. Eddie's, I'm available. We're a sponsor. Eddie's
went out of business. No, it didn't. No, it didn't. Eddie's ice cream. What are you talking about?
It exists. No, it's not. They have a tweet from 12 hours ago, guys. They're fine. How dare you
fucking say that? I've actually had them before. I, you know, I love, you know what my favorite,
let's get, you know, ice cream tier list, ice cream from the grocery store tealers.
That word tier. You know who I think makes the best in the grocery store ice cream? What do you
think it is? What do you guys think? You got, you're close. Some of you guys are close. That's right.
Blue Bunny. Blue Bunny makes the best grocery store ice cream without a doubt. It's by a mile.
I mean, it's by, it's by a fucking mile. It's not even, it's, I'm not kidding. It's not even close.
Hold on. Don't even start. Yes, Ben and Jerry's does make the best ice cream,
but Ben and Jerry's does not really have in the grocery store strawberry ice cream or just
chocolate ice cream. It's like Jerry Lewis's tonight dough. It's a bunch of wacky shit and
it's amazing, but I'm talking just straight up chocolate ice cream or strawberry ice cream.
It's, Blue Bunny makes the best. For anything else, it's Ben and Jerry's. So I know I've said
that before. It is the best thing you buy at the grocery store. Hands down. Okay. So I think I'm
ready to do this. I need a potion of helium at the pumping station. This has been a fine chill game.
We're just, we're just hanging out, having a good time. Blue Bunny only makes novelties. No, they
don't. I have, I literally have Blue Bunny chocolate ice cream, just chocolate in my freezer right now
and I eat it all the time. Hillamook is better. Blue Bunny is better. That's my opinion. You have
to, you're making me prove this. Why would I prove that in ice cream? I just go look it up, type
Google Blue Bunny chocolate ice cream. I don't have to prove it to you. You don't have it.
I have it. Okay. I don't know why I have to prove this to everybody. Why does this matter? Why do
you have to know this? Okay. Blue Bunny chocolate, chocolate ice cream. It's just the standard Blue
Bunny chocolate ice cream. It's delicious. It's perfect. It's smooth, pillowy. When you scoop it
out, it makes this like, it's fluffy. It's pillowy. I was anticipating to show you a smooth pillowy.
I just may have been in there for a while. This may, hold on. Was it exploration? Fuck. I fucked
it up. I fucked it up. I fucked it up. I fucked it up. I fucked it up. No, it's not. It's freezer
bird. My freezer is fucked up. That's my fault. That's my fault for showing that to you. That is
not fresh. That I had a freezer problem. That I had to fuck up with my freezer settings. And
that's what did that. My freezer screwed up. So we're good. Too cold. I don't know. I just,
I messed up something with my freezer. That looked like, no, it was free. All right. Anyways,
Blue Bunny is incredibly fluffy. It's smooth. It has an amazing texture. And I know I look really
odd saying that to you right now, but it's true. It's got a pillowy texture. It's, the mouthfeel
is perfect. It like disintegrates in the back of your mouth. And it's just, it's perfect. It's
the best ice cream you can buy. Don't look at what I just showed you. That was, I shouldn't have done
that. I should have showed it to you when it was ready. Play the game. Do you, you don't care about
this game. I know you don't. What am I doing? All right. Water. All right. So now I need helium.
I need, where do I get helium? This looks like helium, right? Where would I get helium? Oh,
here we go. By the way, I want to say this really clearly too. Strawberry ice cream.
I like it when there's some strawberries in it. My favorite kind of strawberry ice cream is
no chunks, just smooth strawberry flavor. How do I make this? Just 90 to 100% helium. That's it.
Okay. You know, plastic bottle. I need 10 of these. What? Why do I need so much shit? Oh,
it's three for each one. I get it. All right. It's time to start the experiment. Now I need a chair.
Page 11. Oh my God. Okay. Get the right pieces for the chair frame. Yeah, I'm done after this.
We're going to change games. This is cool. This is fine. But I, we gotta change this.
We're on experiment two. Yeah, but we've paused and had like a stupid shitty podcast
for at least like 40 minutes of this stream. All right. So I need to do rectangular steel.
Okay. Wooden beam and wooden cylinder. Wooden beam and wooden cylinder. I gotta change the saw too.
Really? I would love a German podcast. Um, I, I wouldn't. I wouldn't. This is, we already do it.
I'm doing it right now. We just do it. This is what we do. Half the streams are just that.
They, you know, I don't know. Why would I do a podcast? Like we're just already doing it.
I don't, I would, going on someone's podcast is fine. I think that's fun, but I feel like I
wouldn't be able to do very much on my podcast. God damn it. This better be worth it. Can I cut?
Wait, can I? Oh, it's the wrong one. How a metal cutting saw can cut a wooden
piece of furniture. Okay. I'm sorry. Take it out. How do I unscrew this wrench?
How do I get rid of this? Oh, this, there we go. Would you play heroes three? Like heroes might
magic three. I want, wait, back it up. I want to, I want to, what is this? This is a wooden saw.
Okay. I need to buy it. Um, I wouldn't, if people wanted to see it, I'd probably play it again.
It was fun. You'd have to want it, right? You have to want to see it. What about Subnautica?
I, didn't I play Subnautica? I did. Didn't I? I played so many games. I feel like I have played
it on stream. Haven't I? Play it again. Damn. Okay. That was almost like quadruple. All right,
we're good. All right. Get the right pieces in the chair frame. I think I got it. Right. I did it.
I did. Head to the rocket launch site. Let's go. I got to turn the music on. All right. Take Buster
to the safe zone. Let's go. Where should I play after this? How come this one's the radio? The
other one wasn't the radio. There you go. Okay. Assemble the chair. Roblox? Oh no. Mount the chair
and wait, what are you talking about? What's wrong with this? Ah, install six balloons. Well,
don't go, don't leave yet. Okay. I don't, where is it? I don't have a button anymore. Where's the,
where's my button? Where's the truck? It's in my fucking pocket. God damn it. See, in that scenario,
I do not tell anybody that. In that scenario, I drive all the way there. I walk into the warehouse.
I put my hand in my pocket and I go, oh my God, it's in my pocket. And then I text whoever is on,
out in the, in the field. And I go, oh yeah, man, still looking for it. Did you, did you touch it?
You might, I think I saw you have it for like 10 minutes. And then they go, yeah, dude, I had it
for 10 minutes. Oh fuck. I'm still looking for it, man. I'll find it. And then I text the person
again in five minutes, selfie under a desk and with a thumbs up, like, got it. Like this is where
it was. I found it. And everyone's like, yeah. Oh, thank God, Jeremy, you saved the day. You saved,
you saved the experiment. Let's go. What land on the island? While I'm trying to get points,
who is that? Why am I doing this? How do I slow down? We're going way too fast. I don't have a
gun. Wait, what happened? Why? All right, hold on. Unlock the chair. A-W-A-S-D. How am I supposed to
fly up there? Um, that doesn't make any sense. How am I, how do I do that? Shit. Do it again.
I can't shoot the- I don't, whatever. Throw it away. Wait, I didn't do it. Yeah, I did. It's fine.
That was fun. What are we doing next? What should we do now? What do you think? How you guys feel?
What should we play? I got a few things. Let's do, we can do 20 minutes till dawn. That game was a ton
of fun. Play Driver. How am I going to, where's, how am I going to get access to Driver? Is Driver
on Steam? I'll give you some options. You want to do a vote? Yeah, we'll, we'll throw some options
in there. Okay, let's see. We could do, uh, let's see here. Let me move this. All right, we could do,
what should I put on the poll? I could put on, call the lamb. Put on, uh, 20 minutes till dawn.
Put on, what was the other thing you just said? You just said one. What was it? Ultrakill. I feel
like my, I don't think my brain can handle Ultrakill. I need to really be into it. Driver's not on
Steam. Where am I going to get access to Driver? Is Driver on Steam? No, it's not. What was the
thing you just said? Somebody just said something cool. You said, somebody said something cool.
What was it? All right, let me get the poll going. All right, so we could do, no, not, uh, Gloomwood.
I'll do Gloomwood on its own stream. Okay, uh, Cult of the Lamb. 20 minutes till dawn. Yeah,
I can't see. Yeah, we gotta have a third game. No, Sorcerer will be its own day. What else,
what else can I do? There was something else I wanted to play and I don't remember what it was.
Somebody said something cool and I forget what the hell it was. Superliminal. All right, or
what do you think? Oh, it's already active. Wait, wait, what? Oh, the poll, no, no, no,
the third game is Superliminal. We gotta, we gotta do it with Superliminal on there.
Superliminal sounds interesting. Uh, stream's gonna be, uh, it's gonna F for a minute while I
download it. Yeah, kill the poll. We gotta put Superliminal on there. Play Pepsi Man? I would.
Superliminal is awesome. All right, well, let's do it. Try to do it and forget about the rest of
the poll. Let's just do it. I'm gonna play Superliminal. Whatever. Things like people
are into that. Yeah, I'll play it. No, I'm not gonna play Disco Elcium. That game's like 150
hours long. I'll get 10 minutes into it and be like, oh, I'll play it off stream, guys.
All right, Superliminal is downloading. Do I, let me refill my drink. I'll be right back
while it downloads. Superliminal is what we're playing. Get out of, Jesus Christ.
All right, give me one second. I'll be right back.