Oh yeah, friendly fire. You want to do like some like medic pyro jumps?
Let's go over here. Come over here, let's jump like into this thing.
This would be amazing if it was an actual mechanic.
Like friendly fire regardless.
Buff the third degree so you can hit your own medic and like jump with him.
This is awesome.
Alright, let's try to get up there. Ready, so...
Ready, go.
Just up, straight up here. Yeah!
Yes!
Okay, so the rule here is,
everyone get as close to the middle as you can.
Like everyone's stuff on that point.
Okay, now at the count of three,
literally everybody in here called you like your mother a bitch.
Alright, go! One, two, three, go!
Why have a Natasha?
Why? Who has flames?
Who has fire?
Who had the fire?
Oh, it's the healer.
Oh, god.
Are you kidding me?
That guy's the last one standing.
I had the worst one.
I didn't know what your plan was. I went in with the Natasha.
Yeah, yeah, you did. That sucked.
Alright, again. Do it again. Do it again.
Do it again. Do it again.
Don't kill each other. Hold on, wait a second.
The guy that just
flew up right here.
You got destroyed.
Alright, don't kill each other.
Do not kill each other.
Oh, I know what I'm coming with.
Make sure we get everybody inside here.
Everyone stuff inside the middle.
By the way, whoever is in the very middle, you're dead.
Like, you're gonna die instantly.
Drebin, you are going to die instantly.
It's gonna be ridiculous.
Alright, so everyone clump around him.
Get as close to the middle point as you possibly can.
If you're not like in the gray,
then something's wrong.
I can't even fit.
Alright, so hold on.
On the count of three,
Alright, go. It's too late. Just go.
Oh, I'm gone.
I got taunt killed.
I got kicked off by a taunt.
You really did.
It's down to two.
Oh, there's one more contestant.
Oh, he's got a holiday punch.
Get him.
The crits are down.
What's gonna happen here is somebody's gonna detonate it first
when I say three.
And every single person in the room is gonna explode.
And then the crits server is gonna crash.
I'm looking forward to that.
Alright, that's it.
Alright, so everybody get in here.
Everybody get in here and don't move.
Don't do anything. Just marvel.
Marvel at the marbles that are all over the ground.
Everybody in here.
On the count of three,
somebody detonate their sticky bombs.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
There's nobody.
I don't even know what happened.
The game, I couldn't handle that.
It just didn't understand.
Three, two, one.
Alright.
That's just too much.
What?
Oh, he keeps on getting healed.
I'm going heavy. Everybody's a threat.
I don't even care.
If I see person, I'm shooting person.
I think I just killed my own spy.
See,
trying to heal yourself with a power jack
is not, it doesn't work.
I love the chat.
This is dumb.
Somebody has to try to win the game.
But everybody's in there.
The second I say that, of course,
somebody just puts a shotgun
in somebody's face.
Look at these two going at it.
Get him. Get him.
Oh, there's a caper.
You capped it.
Somebody capped it.
I need to heal. I need to heal.
He just tried to kill you.
This sniper, you're so dead.
Two snipers.
Right now, this guy is going to shoot the first person.
Oh, he doesn't realize.
He doesn't realize the Huntsman doesn't hit teammates.
And these are just the flames from her.
GG.
I'm taking off the Tommy Slav.
I'm just going Brass Beast.
You can't light me on fire. It doesn't work.
Exit.
That was my exit strategy.
Make sure no one's following me.
All you son of a bitches are a threat.
Oh, no, no.
You were on the point.
I was like, where is everybody?
I'm walking outside. There's like three red soldiers trying to kill each other.
No!
Yes!
I'm getting told off by the AFK manager for not moving from spawn.
I can't get out of my spawn.
Why can't I not hit this guy?
What the hell was going on?
Wait, the AFK manager.
Seriously.
He's like, if you don't move from spawn soon,
you'll be moved to Specter.
I can't physically get out.
I can't get out.
You're going to get booted from the server because you can't move.
That's bullshit.
Oh, Pyro is the worst class to play.
Honestly, I don't even know why I'm disguising.
There's no point in disguising.
Oh, yeah, dude.
Your dead ringer will pop from teammates.
They can look kind of convincing, actually.
Good.
We got somebody on the cap.
What the hell is going on over here?
Why is this guy's clothing just over here?
No!
I got 7 HP. I'm good.
As long as one of my teammates doesn't show up,
I'll be okay.