Oh, you didn't you didn't think we were gonna play every single wonder book game? Let's make a potion.
We have the ideal guinea pig there. That is a poor soul. The cure for boils.
Alright, so I'm gonna make this potion that he's gonna drink it.
If you can make it correctly.
Pungent onions.
Crushed snake fangs.
Pungent onions. Dry nettles, a dash of flubber worm.
Nucous and sprinkle of ginger. This is a lot of ingredients.
Dude, why don't you just go to CVS and get fucking boil cream. Why do I have to do all this?
They make like Neosporin.
We have the ideal guinea pig there. That is a poor soul.
Oh shit, no, no, no. Go this way.
We have the ideal guinea pig there. That is a poor soul. That is a poor soul.
Get out of here, Dobby.
You're tracking mud all over my wonder book. Get out of here, dude.
Turn to page three.
Dobby, get off the book.
Dobby, get out of here.
What, page three?
Keep an eye on those pictures. They'll always tell you what we're doing next.
Ah, a hopping cauldron.
A faithful friend.
Dobby, get out of the potion.
At least until you try mixing flux weed.
I don't think he's supposed to be here.
Right at it, then hold the move button to start lifting it up.
Okay.
Am I making a potion?
Or am I Looney Tunes-style cooking Dobby in a pot?
This is fucked up.
This is evil.
Get him out. Get him out.
Dobby, get out. Get out of the...get out, please.
Ooh. Ooh.
Say the same line again, please.
Oh, that's fine.
Scatter those lovingly gathered ingredients everywhere, not to worry.
What a mess. Try to get some of it in the cauldron.
Oh, that's fine.
Scatter those lovingly gathered ingredients everywhere, not to worry.
What is in this?
Try to get some of it in the cauldron.
This thing is still going.
You need to be really careful when you're using your chopping tools.
Because there's a chance that you might cut yourself.
Ooh!
Hey, buddy. Who's holding the knife?
Okay, I did it right.
Yes!
...to clip off some of the nettle.
Hold the clipper's clue.
For a cure for boils.
We still need that ingredient. Pick it up again.
It'll cure him.
If you don't get him in there, just dunk him a little bit.
Come on, Dobby, get in there.
Dobby, we're curing your fucking warts.
Stop there. That's two figs worth of juice.
Put my hand down.
There.
Oh, dude, he's sucking my blood.
Quite ingenious.
Oh, how much is he gonna drink?
After that close encounter, time to learn more.
Okay.
I just let these things drink a bunch of my blood.
Now I'm gonna kill him, mash him up, and put my blood in this potion.
You wanna get arrested?
That's how you get arrested.
That's how you get the health inspector to be like,
You're putting blood in your fucking food? Your blood?
My restaurant's gonna be closed.
Give them another bash.
My blood wasn't green?
Go to it!
Why is this implying that I had green blood?
I don't have green blood?
My blood's red.
Now we've got a cauldron full of ingredients.
All you need is a wave of the wand.
To make it into a fish potion.
That's it.
Your wand, pick up the fish and fling it towards him.
Stupid, that's covered in shrinking solution.
He's just a little baby.
Well, he certainly won't stop us passing by now.
Can this chop?
You're too hard.
But here it is again, flighty thing.
Just keep quiet still now.
You know what the most fucked up thing is this entire time?
I haven't even had a chance to sample my own material.
I haven't even had a chance to drink my own fucking potions?
That's changing right now.
Whoa, that's spicy.
Whoo!
At first, I really didn't think I was going to like that.
But man, that was pretty tasty.