Are you sure you don't want to join Berg?
Wait, what are we offering? What is my deal?
For every video that you upload with the clan tag Berg,
the Berg CEO of Berg Industries gives you $5,000.
$5,000?
Now, we're talking about the CEO of Berg Associates.
This is one of the biggest corporations in the world.
Yeah, I can clearly tell that this is serious stuff.
But...
But you have to give me time. I have to talk this over with my agent.
Well, in each upload, I forgot to mention this is part of the stipulation,
in each upload you have to be completely naked.
And there has to be a face cam on you.
Like on your naked butt.
I'm totally fine with that.
Even if it got flagged and you got removed?
No, but I mean, can I do the uploads on livejasmine.com? Is that okay?
No, it has to be on YouTube.
And you can make like separate accounts.
Yeah, I guess I'll have to do that.
Dude, you'd get arrested.
Somebody actually has.
No, already.
Somebody actually has the McDonald's logo.
I don't find that hilarious.
No!
It's been too long since I've played this game.
He is going big. Going ham.
I'm in the middle, guys.
I keep forgetting that left click is not like melee.
I keep trying to left click and I throw a friggin' blade at the wall.
How does that make you feel?
You're getting excited now, but you're going to...
I am getting very excited.
Oh, I missed him!
Oh, you didn't even throw it.
On my screen I did.
No, not on my screen.
I was holding it for really long.
Sweden ping, bro.
Okay, so now the ping game starts.
Yeah, it's like, dude, come on. My ping sucks, dude.
My controller's broken.
Totally, dude.
My A button on my controller doesn't work.
Like, I don't know.
My controller's like broken.
That's the oldest excuse in the book.
You actually invented that excuse.
Back in the day.
Oh, hey, dude.
Oh, I thought you backed me.
I thought you backed me first.
You're shit.
It's so back, too, because I'm doing the climb maneuver.
So I can't do anything.
Okay, meet me, listen.
Meet me at the statue at 12 o'clock, okay?
I don't know where the statue is that will play this game.
Oh, wait, I'm going to bank.
What was that? You were going to bank what?
What were you going to do? You were going to bank me?
Okay, I'm coming for you.
Oh, there we go.
Okay, now meet me at the statue.
Meet me at the statue.
I'm at the statue.
You said meet me at the statue.
You didn't say I'm going to kill you at the statue.
I'm like, just stand here.
Okay, I'm on the statue.
That means we're going to hang out,
not you're going to throw a knife at my head.
All right, where are you?
Look at that kill cam.
What did I just do to you?
I came to the statue.
I'm still trying to be your friend.
What are you doing?
You're the best opponent ever.
Now you see, when you break the friendship trust,
meet at the statue queue,
now you're getting bankrupted.
It's going to happen in this game.
I thought we were going to be weird.
All right, you know what?
Watch this.
Is there another guy right here?
Oh, it's you.
Oh, you slag.
Somebody was behind you too.
All right, boo, we're going to have to kill him.
Well, once again, Orb is going to lead here
with quite a solid 125 points.
It looks like another victory here for Orb.
He is going to try and not really play it cool
because he doesn't really...
Oh, only Orb will shell cast his own live gameplay
about how good he is.
Oh, shit, very shortly.
Boo, are you ready for this one?
Oh, that wasn't even him.
Now I'm ready.
I'm going to slap you with my axe.
No, I'm sorry, boo.
What?
I thought it was him.
Okay, come to the statue now.
It's not.
Hey, boo, don't shoot me.
Don't shoot me, I didn't mean to.
Come here, guys.
I'm by the statue, guys. Where are you guys?
Me and boo have a mission right now
to come destroy you.
You're really pre-aiming me?
Really?
Okay, I see how it is.
I see how we're going to play this.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no.
I don't have anything. Where is he?
No, no.
Behind you, what are you doing?
I don't know where he is.
I was behind you for the longest time.
I missed everything.
Hey, well, that shows.
Well, 145 points, guys.
I'm going to put this hatchet up your asshole.
I believe we have another W
in the vicinity of this game.
Jerma, we got 40 seconds.
Please make him count.
I'm not even throwing, I'm trying to find him.
Okay, so we've come to that part of the game again
where I like to talk.
Where is he?
145 points on the scoreboard here
and we're going to play another victory here
for Orb. He's been playing consistently
throughout this tournament
and he is going to
you know, not really try
because it's already 10 seconds.
It's got to be a victory here.
He's going to walk around and try to
let the opponent back him here.
No, my Jesus!
Oh, yes, you got him.
What an evil guy.
Listen, I don't believe
it lagged.
Oh, yeah.
Dude, I played like shit in this game
and I got second place.
Nice host.
I lag, guys.
I got banged right here.
Are you going to DDoS
me right now, guys?
Are you that amped to win?
Are you going to DDoS me?
See you guys.
I think I went right at the end and then I got
bankrupt with one second left.
Jerma, what happened to Orb?
Don't you remember all the times we met
at the statue?
Yeah, I remember meet me at the statue so I can punch you in the face.
That's like what happened.
Meet me at the flagpole after school.
I'm going to put like an icicle up your ass.