Hey, what's up? How are you a little early? It's okay. I it's a little early. Yeah,
it's supposed to start tomorrow at like four. We're a little early. I figured I'd start like
at least a couple hours early. Give me a minute. I don't know where my phone is.
Be right back. Send a tweet out real quick. And we can get started. What about have you seen our
place I have been very aware of the ongoing various battles going on in our place. Make
this really clear. The germamite army is incredibly incredibly strong. I'm observing
I'm observing and I'm calculating. I have no commands for you. We're observing. Let's see what
happens. Who gave this lunatic an army? I will be I'm telling you right now that I've got a
I've got a strong community. What are the orders? I don't have orders for you.
Your orders are to observe, calculate, passionate, empathize, strike when necessary.
There's those are your orders. Give us something. I am observing. I have nowhere to strike. And
that's the thing. That's the thing, right? Oh, German. Where are we? Where are we striking?
I don't have I there are no targets for me here. Where are we landing? You need to defend you need
to defend the sus face. Well, I'm aware of his existence. I'm aware. I'm very aware. Worst
general ever. General, what are your orders? Very aware. And I want you to be compassionate. And I
want you to be aware. Sir, they're flanking us. Just be aware of it. I want you to be aware of it.
And just keep your eye on it. What a bad general. But I don't have anything for you yet. Okay.
I am actually trying to see where the hell this plays out. I don't want to make an alliance with
somebody. And then here's the Okay, here's the thing about the our play stuff. So if I make an
alliance with somebody, that person has a battle or a war going on with somebody else that now hates
me that wants to get rid of my shit. And then I come forward and I go off. Let's go after that
fucking person. I break that alliance that I have with that person. That person that has two more
alliances. Then those people are mad at me. And then somebody from the top right corner
it starts posting and saying, Hey, germamites, we need you in top right corner to defend the
shovel knight. It's like, dude, I broke like five alliances. And I have like two wars going on down
here. I don't know. I don't it's hard to get involved. But if we need to, oh, we will if we
need to. We will. What is he talking about? Okay. I will show you in just a second. These are just
like the delusions of some random guy. No. Okay, listen to me. I didn't even tweet the stream. Just
hold on. Give me a sec. Okay, I'm back. So yeah, let me explain what this is. This is easy for me
to do this. I'll just show you. Come back over here. Hi, how are you? Okay, so this is our slash
place. I've been made aware of this. Every single pixel here, every single one is placed by an
individual user. So for instance, like, like pirates, right? Like somebody one person had to
click that square right there. It is huge. I believe it's every five to 10 minutes. It
your cooldown refreshes is a dick on the screen. Okay, whatever. What do you want me to do about?
Oh, no. Okay, refresh in five to 10 minutes and show me where the show me where the where's Waldo
dick is. Because that's just going to happen for the rest of the time. This is here. So the craziest
part about this is, oh, okay, we've got there's a little of this, this, I think that's supposed
to be me. I think I think that's me. I've been told it's me. I don't know. I'm like, kind of
don't want it to be what it is. I don't I have no stake in this. I have no idea how what happened.
I didn't tell anybody to do this. But that is, I guess, where you guys have collected yourselves,
I guess. But let me tell you, I there are no alliances here. And let if the germamites need
to be called in, maybe it depends. I am totally okay with this being right here. I don't I don't
we don't need to go anywhere else when I do do anything else. I'm just observing. Check the
chessboard. Where's the chessboard? chessboard? Right side. Jesus Christ. Okay, chessboard.
Left. Why did you say right? Everyone just started saying right. Chessboard. Down near this
sus face. Left in the middle. Okay, in relation to Star Wars, where is it? Directly above sus.
Oh, right here. Oh, okay. Okay. All right. This is cool. I'm okay with that, right? Can we can
just like concentrate in this little spot? I don't I don't need more than one cube. Okay.
Let me tell you, very cleanly, don't need much. We need a square this big. If you attack,
germamites are ready. And they always will be. And they're some of the strongest, most I said vile,
the most vile. They are very strong and they know and they know how to they know how to draw.
This community is incredibly artistic. Like you guys could get the amount of art the amount of
creativity that I see here. Trust me when I say I'm all we need is a little we need a little cube
and that's it. There are no allegiances. There are no alliances. Everybody is we have a creative
community here. So I what I'm not going to do is I'm not going to what I'm not going to say this
because I know what the second I say this it's going to be like, there it goes, right? Let's
observe. I'll look back in a little bit and see what it looks like. We're incredibly uncoordinated
but strong. Vile artists. No, you're a community of incredibly intelligent doctors, scientists,
and he's along and I got to cut them. Like with it. I just saw it over here. Okay, I got to
fucking turn this preview off. I distract myself with my own preview. I'm reading what you guys
are saying. Then I go there's a guy right there and I look at it. I fucking hate it. I don't want
to look at this. I'm going to move the face cam to the other side of the screen. Oh, yeah. Oh,
I know there are other streamers that are doing this. I've been watching some of them and it's
been fucking crazy. It's been actually pretty entertaining if I'm honest. Change your talismans.
Thank you. Now let's get to the real thing here. Well, I yes, I'm supposed to stream tomorrow,
but I kind of I just I wanted to do it and I said people were saying some stuff to me.
I'm going to take it to I'm going to take it to heart now. They said, German,
these last few encounters are ridiculous. They're hard. They're frustrating. They make people angry
and you need to do whatever means necessary to try to kill them. So I know that there are a few
spells that I don't have that people keep telling me about and I want to go get those spells and
just see what they do. Yeah, it's our slash place. It's really looking even if we're not going to
participate all that much. I mean, I know a lot of you guys already are. It's just really cool.
They do it every what every year every every few years. It's it's really cool. It's been awesome
to see just the communities kind of even across the world watching all these different communities,
like kind of if a fun way, right, kind of battle for this kind of land and like territory almost.
It's like, all right, like I've seen like people have treaties. All right, I'll get we'll give up
this the quarter of this part of our of our territory here, but we want an alliance.
It's like everyone's playing risk. It's a game of risk with like 60 million people.
You're a beta male chapstick user. No, I'm older and my lips are dry. Yeah, it's just they're
playing everyone's playing like risk or like Crusader Kings or something, right? You're
speaking with Elden Ring vocabulary. What is he talking about? It's just our whatever. You know
what I'm doing. So I'm at the end of the game. So this is literally the finale, but I'm not going
to go through this door. I want to go get the spell because everyone was talking about there's
a spell. There's two of them, three of them. I want the crazy spells and I want to do the crazy
shit. What opportunity am I going to have after this? So I know people go get the comet, comet,
comet, comet, comet, right? Where is it? Do I know where it is? Should you get the spell that turns
you into a toaster? That would be fucking Monka Lol. Go to the Volcano Manor. Okay, that's stop
number one. Volcano Manor. You should do a long rip. Go through the Windham Ruins in Atlas Plateau.
Dude, I didn't do like anything in this bottom part of Atlas Plateau. Do I have it? Or is it down
here somewhere? Where's this move? Right here? After Caleb, you just started zooming by the tree,
like up here, over here somewhere, maybe here. You're missing a lot of bonfires.
Like three in this whole entire zone. There's a dungeon along the wall, like here or here.
I don't think I even walked. I don't think I even went over here or the cringe village
at mine you highlighted earlier. So like over here, like in this area. So if I go over here,
am I gonna be like in the right spot? Is that correct? South of Volcano Manor. So like down
here. Should I go from abandoned coffin this way? I guess I could just look this up, right? Do I
really? I could just look it up. Well, we'll start here. I'm just gonna look it up. What's the spell
called? Comet Azur. Okay, Comet Azur. Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. Where to find it?
Uh, it's in the Hermit Village in Mount Gelmer. Okay, so where's that? It looks like... Yeah,
so it's right... This is actually probably not a bad place to be. It's actually literally right
below that, the tree there. I gotta go like to... How do I get over there? It's like here. So from,
probably from this grave here? It's like right here. Not even close. What are you talking? Yes,
it is. It's right there. I'm gonna go from... Should I just go from the... Should I walk this
way or should I walk down from here? It's the village on the map. Right here. All right,
I'm gonna try to find my way over there. Starting from... I have to go this way. I'm just gonna go
from here. Need to see dance. Oh, that's all right then. Wait, wrong one. Go from the... This
actually... Because this is probably down. Can I get there from here? There's a discord for the
r slash place. Yeah, you guys can do whatever you want. I'm not sending you anywhere. All right,
I'm ready. But I ain't... I got nowhere for you to go. I've already played Genshin Impact. Um,
I played it a little bit when it first came out. Put like six or seven thousand dollars into it.
Then I was like, ah, I'm not really into it. And then I uninstalled it and I broke the iPad
over my knee. That's what happened. Fuck, forgot. That was so long ago though. It was like a few
months ago. Okay, can I get there from here? Probably. Or is it too low? Is it high or up
or is it lower? Shit, it's right there. It's literally right there. The way you guys are
telling me to go. Is there a jump over here? All right, I'm gonna have to go from here and then go
left. Yeah, what I'm doing right now is I'm trying... I'm getting the... I'm going to get the best
spell in the game apparently. This is apparently the best sorcery in the whole game from what I've
been told. It just melts people. It's ridiculous, apparently. Okay, now is there a way I can go
around? What is attacking me? Oh shit, I didn't even do Atlas Plateau. I just like snoozed through
this place. I didn't do any of this. All right, be strong, I'll do it. Okay, is this whole area
Perfumer's Ruins? I mean, let's see what's here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm looking...
I'm facing the wrong way. I'm just trying to get a spell here because you stink.
Ta-da. So, from here, where do I go? Oh, a chest. Oh, nice! I'm from this cookbook.
Holy shit! Is there a place to go down? Cave moss. Cool, okay. There's probably a way to go down.
Maybe that's it. Perfume bottle. Those are like the flasks. I haven't used them the whole game.
Anywhere to go down, like a dungeon or something? Or another. What's that? Yep, very nice.
Perfumer's Talisman. The perfume bottle thing, I don't... Raises potency of perfume items.
I don't know. This is a lot. Me strong, I'll take care of it. Why do your lips look so greasy?
Did you eat KFC recently? Oh, man, I love that. I love that extra crispy combo.
It's... God, I fucking love KFC more than anything. After you eat KFC, you can smell it on your face
for at least an hour, even if you wipe your mouth and wash your face and stuff.
That's disgusting, by the way. It is. Okay, I think I got everything here. Let's keep going.
I need to go over this way. I actually don't want to get zits on my chin.
All right, we're going to four. How can I get to four? Around here?
No, around here. Shit! How do I get over there? This guy's a bit greasy. I think I have to go
from the lava place, yeah. Unless is there a... Can I go through here? Is it like a dungeon or
something? There's definitely something here. Here we go. All right, let's go. Yep. Sage's Cave.
I don't have a... You know the move. KFC Manor. There it is. Not like...
Yeah, so there's this move. There's a spell. There's a fake wall. So I know that there are
a few more spells. And I need your help. This is the backseat stream. This is the stream where
it's a late night stream. And we're trying to get to the end. Trying to get as powerful as we can.
I'm ready to be backseated. All right, I can go this way. Wait, what about down here?
Every stream so far has been a backseat stream. Yeah. All right, I can't make that. There's two
bosses in this dungeon. Really? Pretty cool. There's a very useful chess piece here. Okay.
Because... All right. Everyone tells me about this laser beam move. I know it exists. They're
saying, dude, just go get the laser beam, please. For the love of God, just go get the laser beam.
It's cool. And I'm like, all right. So that's... I want to use the laser beam on Millennium.
Understand? And if it is what I think it's going to do, I have an idea. Can I actually not make
that? Whatever. I'm scared. There's two chests? Dude. Lost Ashes of War. Rejuvenating Ballaces.
It sucks. It's cheese. Um, that's fine. I know that there's at least three spells that I... And
plus I want to... I've gone the whole game without using any of the ridiculous, like, dump 80 points
into sorcery and just do the beam at every boss. I haven't done that. And you know I haven't.
I haven't done that. So if there's one opportunity I'm going to take
to do that move to someone, it's going to be Millennium. I'm gonna hold on to it. And I'm
gonna just... I'm gonna keep it in the back pocket. Mr. Wall. Back here. Hello. My God, there's a lot
of you in this room. This will be good for these guys because it'll hit them when they're on the
ground. God, I can't see. Come on, Starlight Kid. Do it already. Bandit's Curve Sword. I don't even
need to look at it. Oh my God, what the fuck? This feels, um, this feels like Mario Party.
Like, I feel like if I, like, we're all gonna take a turn and then it's gonna blow up in our face.
Okay. Black Hood. Candle Tree Wooden Shield. And Butterfly. Is it? What is the Candle Tree
Wooden Shield? Light for its eyes, easy to handle. About to represent a sur- surrepetitious prophecy
of cardinal sin. The lit candle tree design was forbidden. Lit candle tree? A burning urtree?
How did you just pronounce that? I don't know. I just guessed. Looks like I got it right.
Hey, chat. Did you tell Jerm about the thing? I think they did. The R place. Very aware.
I have no orders. There are no orders for you. This guy still doesn't have a lantern. Nope.
This is lantern, uh, any percent. No lantern, any percent. Star and Sword key.
Very cool. You beat Godfrey with no lantern. Yeah. And wood again, my lord.
Raptor Talons? What is that? Why are there so many chests everywhere?
This is the most chests that I've ever been in a dungeon. Baseline of deck scaling C.
Claw? What is it? Claw comprised of two sharp thin blades
built by the assassins of Ravenmount to imitate the death birds. That's really good for PvP.
Golden Great Arrow. Why are there so many chests here? This is getting the shit out of me.
Uh, over here? There's so much stuff. Skeletal Mask and Raptor's Black Feathers. Whoa.
Where's the mask? Skeletal Mask. Where is it? Skeletal Mask that tightly grips the face,
worn by the assassins of Ravenmount. This ritual implement relentlessly digs into the wearer's face,
preserving one's human instincts while dressed in imitation of the death birds.
That's interesting. What is this? I have so much stuff. A Raptor's Black Feathers focus and vitality
really high. Transforming into ritual? We're transforming into a death bird, if only by
imitation. Strengthens jump attacks. That's kind of cool. That's really cool. It's bloodborne armor.
It does kind of look like bloodborne armor. You're right. The boss. I'm so unbelievably
overleveled for this. Like, come on, I can do it, right? Necromancer Garrus. Necromancer
Garrus is gonna fucking die in another one hit. All right, I got him. Doesn't come back, right?
Family heads? What the hell is that? I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Garrus. I was way more overprepared.
It's a staff. Three bludgeoning copper heads attached to it. It's a flail. The heads were
made to resemble those of his wife and two children. Gently rattle the copper heads to
summon vengeful spirits that chase down foes. The anguish of a spouse and children.
Invites a cursed wrath. Let me see this thing. Oh my god, this thing's fucking morbid.
What does it do? Oh, that's kind of cool. Interesting. All right. Well, that's cool.
I don't think I want to go to the beginning of the dungeon. That is an act. That's an actual
rat. It's a baby rattle. Well, it's a it's a it's a flail that has some stuff. It's attached to
this. This is the baby rattle. Hurry up and fucking stall like it. All right, that was cool. In
the necromancer, I'm sure 70 to 80 levels ago may have been a tad more difficult, but you know,
this is what it is. I'm here for the spell. Okay, we're already here. Black knife assassin.
It's I can see the footprints. Okay, I would be really scared right now if I couldn't just do this.
Hmm. I don't have any mana left. Oh shit. Fuck. Oh, I just got him. That would have been so awful
back at like level 60 or 80. Concealing veil. Conceals wear while crouching. What? What do you
mean? It's invisible? Am I invisible? How can I tell if I'm invisible? Well, that's really cool.
Is it bizarre? Let's put this back on. What's here? Oh, the damage. The damage one.
All right, so that is not what I wanted. I wanted to go over here. This is not the way I wanted to
go. Can I get out of here somewhere else? Can I keep going? You need to go to volcano manor and
then around the volcano. You have to go around the entire mountain. All right, well, so if I go here,
I can, can I go like this way? Instructions to find comet Azor in alert channel. Oh shit.
Directions. Around Mount Gelmer through a canyon. Start from the abandoned coffin bonfire and go
uphill to the northeast. This is VR Josh, by the way. He's just got my back on this one. Start from
the abandoned coffin. Start from the abandoned coffin bonfire and go uphill to the northeast.
Then go north slash northwest through a canyon. Hug the canyon's left wall and it will loop
around Mount Gelmer counterclockwise. You'll come to a castle, go left from that castle,
pass some lava fields and through some rocks. You'll go past some advanced shacks.
Beyond those is a magic boss. Oh my god, this is a lot. I'm going to do this step by step. Okay.
Go uphill to the northeast. Northeast. Uphill. VR Josh would beat Jerma in a fight, I think.
Probably. Okay, I haven't gone this way. Why, okay, oh wait a minute. Being able to take out,
what the fuck is that? Being able to have, to be able to give somebody directions means I can beat
you up? What are you talking about? Ancient dragon lancex? Oh my god, good thing I'm here way early.
Late. Just eat all this damage. I'm so powerful. I'm, I'm sorry, uh, lancex, but you're dealing
with somebody that is about to fight, that's been fighting the final, all right, you got the hint.
You took, you took the hint. Okay, uh, so north, north, yeah, I would leave too. Lancex just landed
and was like, oh, what's this new area? Oh no, no, no, no, no, I'm way, I'm way too underleveled for
this. I'm way too underleveled. This game's fucking stupid. How was I supposed to know I wasn't
supposed to be here? And he turned around. He's complaining to his chat right now. How the fuck
was I ever supposed to know that? What level are these guys? That's so fucking stupid. Okay, that
was cool. Hug the canyon's left wall and then loop around Mount Gelmer. Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, this is crazy. I wasn't even over here. Okay, there's the tibia mariner. This is an
elaborate April's rules joke to get me to come over here. All right, can I kill the tibia mariner
in three hits? What do you guys think? Where do you go? There you are. Three hits. Here we go.
One. Nope, not gonna happen. You got a lot more. You got a ton of health this time.
Oh, he must be resistant to cold. I thought he just knocked him over. I thought that was
way too much of like a wave that the skeleton made. Could be a mariner. Dead. It's gonna be.
Deathroot and tibia's summons. Easy class. Tibia's summons. It's a sorcery. Oh, it's an
int and faith. 28 int 20 faith. Summons a group of those lost in death. Three skeletons will appear
from some distance from the caster. Are they huge? I don't want the faith. That's cool though.
Okay, wait. I don't want to fuck the instructions. We'll come to a castle. Go left from that castle
past some lava fields. Shit. Fuck. I messed it up. Where were we? Not near the castle yet. Okay,
so I just keep going this way? Over here? Oh, this is grace. I think this is it.
Yes. Okay, this is definitely it. But how do I get up there? Stay at the bottom.
Over here. Following the instructions, monkey. Mirage. At the end of the canyon is the castle.
God. Oh my god. Fucking lava bursts. Watch out. I think I have. I have five. I can do another
flask upgrade. That hurts. Come on. What's up? Oh, he doesn't know. He doesn't know. What do I
not know? Can you please be nicer? My little brother is watching. I'll say 50% less swears
for the next 30 minutes. See the water. So getting it off there. I want to yell it so bad.
I want to just put like epic music and just do the intro as hard as I can.
Well, this is a dungeon. Wait, that is. No, there's actually nothing in here. Please do it.
That's like, that's just me. That's just, I'm, you want me to do what you want to do a fan,
like a fan dub. You want me to do a dub like a fan dub on stream. Poison. I'll think about it.
What if I get it wrong though? I might not get it right. Who cares? Okay, you will get it wrong.
I probably will get it right. Actually, cause I've seen the intro of fucking absolute shit.
I'm going to get poisoned. Who gives a shit. All right. I got to pay attention because I
can't talk about that right now. No illusory walls.
When will you learn it's illusory, illusory, illusory, illusory wall, illusory.
You do it phonetically like bump dash bump, death dash bump.
Illusory, illusory, illusory, illusory. That sucks. That's not, that's, I don't like it.
Illusory, illusory, illusory. No, no, no. It's illusory. It's illusory. It sounds way cooler
that way. Illusory wall. Oh, there's an illusory wall. That doesn't sound right. An illusory wall.
An illusory wall. An illusion. Not an illusion. Illusion. Stop reinventing English.
Illusory. I don't even know how it was said. Somebody said it and I just don't remember.
Okay. Well, this is a bunch of re shit right here.
Oh, I actually could have just walked in and done that. I'm too flashy for flashy sake.
Uh, I had a mana? What? Fuck up. Fuck up. I, there's no way I don't have mana.
Mushroom body, mushroom arms, mushroom legs. Mushroom body. Mushrooms found growing all over
the body. These overgrown mushrooms have colonized the torso. Those enraptured by the scarlet rot,
they are holy vestments that root one to the earth. It just looks like, hold on,
put my like weapons away. Just like sit on the ground. Okay. I, I now have a rune arc on me.
I like just sit here in the corner and just have like an item on me.
We're taking that off. Oh no. The bull goat armor. Holy shit. That's actually, I'm not at heavy,
right? As long as I say medium, I'm fine. Dragon gauntlets. I could put the bull,
the bull goat stuff on. Almost the whole thing. Can I put the whole thing on?
No. Nope. My pants have to be, uh, light. Oh no, I can't wear pants at all. I can wear these
trousers. I actually, I don't hate this. This is actually, I didn't realize what that, I didn't
realize that. I didn't realize that they came out like that. Clipping through the hat. Damn it.
I can't wear it. That'll drive me fucking crazy. I like this the most, I think. No, the blue one.
This one. Yeah. This is my favorite so far. I want like blue. Yeah. I like that.
That's really cool. That matches really well. The whole thing matches now. Okay. Well, now where?
Now where else to go? Where am I supposed to go from here? Uh, that way? Honest to God, dude.
He can't even cast. There's four people. It doesn't matter how much HP that I have.
There's four people shooting at me. You know what I mean? No, dickhead. I already went this way.
We're gonna go that way. Yeah, because this is, this is like the end of the waterfall or something.
Or can I go here? Oh no, I can't go here. Or unloved. Thief to the Badlands. What? Why did
that happen? Oh, thank God. It was one of those right there. That's actually not a bad thing.
That was a good thing. I got a refill of my flask. Okay, so be careful because it keeps going.
I got kind of unlucky, didn't I? I got really unlucky. This is safe. Sir Gideon Andy?
Oraloo Andy. Thief to the Badlands. The effa brilliant gold mask Andy. The lonesome
dung eater Andy. You guys really know how to ruin things. Oh, okay. All right. Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Okay. I have to hit you once. Oh my God. I'm so glad I'm not doing you at the correct level
because this would suck. I almost killed him in one hit. That was pretty cool. All right, cool.
Hindered of rot's exultation. Yeah, it's definitely okay. Poisoning or rot in vicinity increases
attack power. Raise attack power when poisoning or rot occurs in the vicinity. Raise attack power
when blood loss occurs in the vicinity. Would be good for millennia. Holy shit. How's that person
gonna get VIP'd and then don't do it? You know what I mean? Like the thought is there.
The lonesome Andy. Sir Gideon Andy. Oh my God. Like that's so, I hate it. Okay, so I was,
that was kind of cool. I didn't do any of this shit. Lonesome ass eater. Ew, ew, ew, ew.
I'm sorry. I'm overdoing it. Lonesome ass eater. Stop. This thing's stupid.
The lonesome ass. Imagine that was his name. Oh, hey, I can see it. That's the castle that,
uh, that, that, that VRJaws said. This is a fucking long way to get over here. Okay.
Wait, what the fuck? What? This, this is not right. I'm all the way across the whole thing now.
Is this the, wait, what does it say? When you get to the castle, go left from that castle,
pass some lava fields and through some rocks. You circle around the whole thing.
And Sir Gideon ass eater. The lonesome dung eater. I'm sorry. This is this it? What the
fuck is with all these random bosses? Another, okay. Magma worm. Don't even get up. Just stay
here. Do not go into the lava. Frost him. Come on. Frost him. There it is. Yeah. Let's end it
with a flashy move. All right. I'm slowly cleaning up all this shit that I didn't do.
Dragon heart. New draconic power is available. Okay. So you come to a castle, go left.
Sir, that circle, pass some lava fields and through some rocks. You'll go past some abandoned shacks.
So you want to go through the lava like this way. What about Alexander? What? This hurts.
You need the boots.
He's still alive. Jar.
Okay. Anything else? No. What did he say? Icy giant's peak. Lame of ruin.
I burnt the urtree though. He still do that. The jar on. Hold on. Torrent's like dead.
Is it a helmet? Jar. Jar that fits cleanly over the head when upturned. Made with pride by iron
fist Alexander. In a uniquely jar-like gesture of friendship, it boosts the power of throwing pot
items. That's so dumb. You could summon him for the fire giant. Really? That's cool. That's really
cool. All right. So I keep going. And then it says finally abandoned shacks. What is this?
I missed when the jar was yelling.
Okay. I don't want to. This route sucks by the way. You gave me directions through three bosses.
It's the only way? Why is this place riddled with fucking animals and bosses? I think that hurt a
lot. This is literally the only way. All right. Well, now I have to fight one of these.
Oh, that was rude. What I just did. It didn't even hurt him. Why did all these people come from?
What the fuck? All right. I have to actually pay attention to this. Oh my God. Why are you?
I want to get me out of here. I'm going to go up the fucking cliff. I know it.
I don't know where I am. Where did I go? God damn it. I'm running by it. I don't want to
fight that. I was already going too fast. I could have just the thing jumped from like stage left
and I saw like the corner of it. I should have just kept going. I should have. I got way too
overconfident because I killed every boss in like less than 10 seconds. And that bear was not easy.
That was horrible. Go around the lava. I'm already here. I don't care about this. Just go
this way. Where is he? Wait, what's in here? What? Roiling magma. Okay. That's kind of cool.
Okay. There he is. Items spraying his ankle. What was that? Don't you fucking dare. Get the
fuck out of here. How did they even get up here? How did they get up here? They can't, you can't
jump up here. Do you see how you can't do that? I had to use the horse. I didn't want to do that
dumb fucking move. You can't get up there, right? Oh my god. This is not possible. You can not jump
up here. He's so menacing. Did he shit out a little bear? What was that? Where did that other bear
come from? That was so terrible. That was so weird. That was just so sad. It rolled so far.
It rolled from here slowly all the way over there in tiny revolutions. That was so awful.
Oh my god. I feel awful. My whole body feels bad. It rolled for a full two minutes.
Okay. So now we're here. That's slow. Pulley crossbow. Wow. Pulley crossbow. Let me see it.
Okay. Cool. Crossbow made with pulleys and power springs. One in the chat if anyone's fired this
weapon. Liars. I think I have enough to roll up. 140. I need 139. I think I got it.
Okay. That's actually kind of nice. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait a minute. Wait. Hold on.
Wait. I have horror. Horror lose. I do. Did I look at this? Why did I not break that?
139 is what I need. Did you beat that boss? Nope. Nope. I'm preparing for that boss.
Because she kicked the ever-living shit out of me a day and a half ago. I turned purple.
All right. I was horrible. Why do I really not have enough? I don't know. No. Dude. How could
you even consider it? I just saw a huge bunch, like a big crowd of enemies. And I'm like, all
right. And then I realized what it was. And I was just for a second, I was like, this sheep.
Okay. I thought these were sheep. Get away from the sheep. Sheep. Get out of here.
I don't want to accidentally kill the entire fucking family. 139 is what I need. It's bones.
130. Okay. I need 139 for God's sakes. Whatever. I don't. We're on the right track.
Now, last time I did like a sheep sound, everybody fucking freaked out and like people left the
scream. Well, like, shut the fuck up. It wasn't funny. It was like, I'm leaving. Don't fucking do
like a dumb sheep sound. Do you remember that? I don't think you guys remember like the sheep
that I did. And everyone got really mad. It wasn't like funny mad. It was like, don't fucking do that
again, dude. That wasn't funny. That sucked. I distinctly remember that. And I was like,
holy shit. People really didn't like that. And again, I'm not messing around. It wasn't like,
oh, dude. What the fuck? It was like a don't fucking do that again. Okay. What the fuck is
happening in this game today? Even though he died. He just got cut in half long ways. Like,
he was like, I'm ready. Okay, here we go. Yeah. Like, he's one of those, he's going to go like this.
He's going to go in half. He's not even going to know why they all so fucked up today.
Don't you feel like they're like, the enemies are weird today?
Something's weird is going on. What's happening? Why is everyone so fucked up?
Go level up. You're living eternally in a 1900 slapstick movie. You know, I miss like the piano
playing. Like the classic piano. Like. With people just getting hit and like hitting each other and
stuff and like falling down stairs and stuff. Like that's fucking hilarious. Endurance probably,
right? Or 60. Yeah. There's a scene in Leslie Nielsen in one of the naked gun movies where like
he's in an apartment, like doing an investigation, looking for like a clue. And he like bumps into
an automatic, he bumps into a piano. Like he falls over and like hits bumps into a piano
and starts playing this like classical, like automatic piano music. And he starts like
falling into the walls and breaking shit. And they like ends up burning the whole place down
or something. I remember just laughing at the piano. I don't know. Pianos do it to me.
I think we're really missing like the old high school theater old lady that plays the piano.
Do you guys remember that? I don't know what it's like in like high school now or like middle school
now. But there was one old lady that did the entire soundtrack of the entire play. And it was
it was a little scuffed. It was always a little bit scuffed. But this lady worked it all night.
All night. Every song, every tense moment, all the tense music. I was that I just got a cool weapon.
This boss alley. It's this literally is boss alley. They all decided to hang out here.
This probably would have taken like 15 in game hours to go through this place.
Like at level 60 or 70 when you're supposed to be here.
This where they there's casters here. Get out of here. How many people are here?
I can imagine like the old lady playing the piano right now.
I think sometimes you can hear her like say a fucking really really bad swear too.
Fuck. She'd be like ah this piece of shit. Like she'd turn her music over and she'd swear.
It was like Jesus. Okay so what did I just get? Oh a memory stone. That's all right.
I'm not going over there yet. Most OP spell in the game. This is well all right so
Homet Azur. Can you talk? Okay well can I do anything else? All right I want to see what this
does. Play ragtime music. Oh wait I got something over here too. Roiling magma in faith. Okay a lot
of these fire spells are in faith. Kind of interesting. Okay where is it? Fire is a
tremendous comment within Astari Torm. It takes three slots. Shit. Wow. Oh okay I have the- wait
a minute. So theoretically I already have this on. If I do this. Oh my goodness. It's not going to
work versus them. There's a hair in here and I got to get it out. I got it. Oh oh my god this is
one of my hairs. This is long. This is like one of my hairs. That's what the fuck. It was in there.
Like coiled up. That's disgusting. Okay so um you say that's not going to work versus. All right
where is the other spell? Somebody said they were- I see there's a few super spells. I want to get
them because this is it. It's not- I'm not- this is it. This is it. Is there another one? Oh talk to
Selen in limb grave. Rocksling is really good. The other one. Talk to Selen about this guy. I have
it already. It's swarm of flies. Selen's quest. Use that when you dodge the big flower in phase two.
Oh man. Can we just do it now? Let's just go do it now. Let's go do it right now. Let's go kill her
right now. What do you guys think? What do you guys think? First try? We go do it first try?
We do it right now? You think? Linestone pebble is better. Okay last charges. Uh I'm gonna say
10 and 4. Let's just see. We gotta get to phase two. I'm not using this until phase two. If I
beat this. If I drink that flask and melt her. Probably gonna get a lot of shit for it because
you didn't beat Melania the way that I did which was soul level 80 and uh a short sword.
Well I'm sorry but let's go. Bombo you ready? All right Melania. Begin the process. Come on
Bombo. Old headphones gotta go in otherwise this ain't happening. Stagger! Where's the Stagger?
Oh my god. Do it right away? No fucking chance man. I gotta get her phase two. She stands still
in phase two for like five to ten straight seconds when she lands. And you know what?
We're going rune arc as well. Let's do it. Bombo! Let's do it. Can I get two moons off? No. I don't
think so. Let's fuck who cares. Let's do it. Got it. All right let's go. Come on Bombo. Fire!
Hit her in the fire. No!
You tried dodging that attack? I don't think you can. By the time you dodge the first part of it
she's still the animation is still happening. You can. It's just hard. This boss is dumb. I can't
wait to burn her face off with this fucking spell. In the fire. Good good good. Stagger up.
All right back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Run run run run run run run. I'm paranoid that she's
gonna do it again. I'm so paranoid. She's gonna do it again. She's gonna do it again. Right? Like
she's gonna do it again right now. My god I can't even see. I don't want to use the laser spell yet.
She never does it twice in a row. I feel like I've seen her do it twice in a row.
Use the moon blade? Bro that's the only move I'm doing this whole entire fight.
You know what? Fuck it. Let's just see what happens. I'm just doing it right now. Go!
What? Doesn't work. It's gonna work in phase two because she stands still for like five straight
seconds in phase two. I just have to get her to phase two. Just kill me. I don't want to waste
blasts. No reason. Just kill me. She's really weak to bleed. I can get her down. I've gotten her to
phase two plenty of times. It's just doing it. You need to play ragtime piano. It's the only way.
You know I've considered it. I considered it. Ragtime piano music royalty free?
Whatever.
Come on Bombo. Let's go.
Please. Bombo aggro. She's full health again. Oh god damn it. There's no fucking way.
Not anymore. Not without Bombo. Bombo. She just. Okay. You live by the summon, you die by the
summon. She generates almost a hundred percent of her health back if she does that to the summon.
She just ate him fucking alive. That was stupid. She shouldn't be able to gain health from the
summon if the summon didn't have any blood. This is gonna be so hard without Bombo. I'm so afraid
she's gonna do it. Just do it already. Just do it. I know you're gonna do it. Just do it already.
Do it already. I got the black and white filter. And I'll top it with one of these accents.
That sounds like a good idea. Okay. That sounds fun to me. That's like fucking grainy. All right.
Hold on. The whole thing. What if I beat her? It's gonna be ruined. The clip is gonna be fucking
ruined. Hold on. Hold on. I need to. I wish I had a cigarette. I need like a suit jacket,
too. You know what I mean? This could be a cigarette. This clean lady down here. I'm
really not gonna try. A new tactic, I think. Alice. Alice, listen to me. The new tactic is gonna go
like this. I'm thinking we wait till we get to the bottom. Radio filter. Yep. That's true.
Actually, good call. Let me make sure I get this right. Okay. So, okay. So, what we're gonna do
here is we're gonna make sure I get this right. Let's go ahead and bring this up a little bit here.
Does that sound better? Does that sound good? How does that sound? Maybe a little bit. That's
a little too much. I think that's a little too much. Yeah, I think so. Now, you see? How's that?
Okay. That sounds pretty good to me. Now, let's go ahead and get this started, I say. You know,
I say. I'll tell you, I'm gonna be hollering here. I'm gonna be hollering here. Get down here.
I'm gonna make sure that we take care of this as soon as possible. I'm thinking summoning Mambo
for the first quadrant of this fight. Mambo, why don't you come sailing out here, please?
That sounds good to me. Show of the moon. Show of the moon. What do you say? Show of the moon.
What do you think, Mambo? Sure thing. Absolutely. Oh, rats. Rats, rats, rats. Rats.
That looked a little hairy there. I say, I say, you get your hands off him. That's my friend,
Mambo, and he's a good friend of mine. I say, you get your, you lay your hands off him right now.
Get your hands off him this instant. Oh, great. Now, she's doing that move. Gotta stay very far
away from that one. Oh, look at her. She's, she's sapping the ball as hell. I say, I say, I don't
agree with that, and you're gonna make, I'm gonna get real sore with you. I'm saying right now,
I'm gonna get real cross with you. If you keep that up. Hey, you listen, Butcher. You listen here,
Jack. Here we go, Mambo. Now, I don't get that move at all. That move is absolutely unbelievable.
It's one of those moves that you can't do anything about, and as ridiculous as that,
get playing soon. They're gonna be like, I can fly eventually, too. No chance. We'll never fly.
All these people talking about getting in the air like a bird. That makes absolutely no sense to me.
Not at all. Hold talk if I've ever heard it. Satanist flying around. What are they thinking?
All right, Mambo, come on. What happened to the music? I had some good music on here,
and I don't know what happened to it. Not exactly sure. I don't know. I don't know where it went.
Excuse me for one second. Now, that's better.
Okay.
Let's get in here, and let's get, let's, let's, let's go ahead, let's stop, stop the bully.
Run away from that. Mambo behind. Come on. No, no. Not that close, Mambo, please.
Fuck, no. Excuse me. Looks like she's gonna, I say looks like she's gonna heal the whole thing now,
because she did that to Mambo.
I think this could be long here. I'm very certain this could be it. Hey, it's possible.
And then we have to break that glass immediately and try to get over there as fast as we can.
See, what you don't know is back in the 1930s, we never exhaled it. It stayed in.
Permanently. We absorbed it into our bloodstream as the second we sucked it in.
And as some facts for you. Now, come on now.
Fuck you. Seriously, that's stupid. What? How many fucking moves do you get before you?
I'm sorry about that, folks, but what I meant to say was how many moves do you get to do in a row
before, gosh darn it, you, how many moves do you get to do, gosh darn it, before fucking, wrong
thing. Wrong thing. And now the whole thing's fucked up, folks, so we may as well just do this
and say, fuck you, die. I blew the whole thing. Locked in, she sat down at my desk.
I said, lady, what are you doing in here? He gave me one look, one quick look in my eye.
And I knew, sorry, I knew right then when she came and sat out of my office, what, it was going to
be quite an evening. I knew right there that the next few days of my life were situated, they were
stuck. Gosh, I could get through this. The local paper the next day, yeah, so all the other people
that have died at this moment. So I ripped it up, and I'm fucking mad, and this is the only thing
keeping me from fucking strangling myself. Like, just strangling. So she walked in.
Can I turn it off now, please? It doesn't work. It makes everything sound horrible and it sucks.
I say, here's, okay, here we are. I'm gonna paint this piece of shit. Oh, I lost my hat.
It's the only thing that's keeping my brain in. Oh! It's okay. Everything's fine. Don't worry about
it. Everything seems to be going very smoothly, as smoothly as it could. Just don't want her to do
that to Mambo. How long is he going to keep this up? Probably until he wins. Or he runs out of mana.
This is bad. I don't fucking know.
I gotta turn this off. It's fucking with me. It's fucking with me. I gotta turn it off now.
I hate this fucking fight, and I hate this piece of shit behind this door.
Let's bring it back. 1995.
Okay, let's try this again. This time I'm gonna try. I haven't gotten her to phase two.
I can't, why can I not get this piece of fucking shit to phase?
Fuck this fight. I hope I get to cheese the fuck out of this. I hope I kill it instantly.
I hope I kill her instantly in phase two. I hope so. Get in there. Come on. Just go.
Bully, bully, bully, bully, bully, bully. It's the only fucking way to fight this.
Bully! Where's the bully? Get it. Come on. Go, go, go, go, go, go, back up, back up, back up.
God damn it. Everything that we just did. What a pain in the fucking ass. Keep it up. Go,
go, go, go, go, go, more, more, more, more, more, more, more. She's gonna go up. She's gonna go up.
I just know she's gonna go up like right now. She's going up. She's going up. She's going up.
When is she gonna, she's gonna go up like right now.
Is she going up? I'm so fucking paranoid. She's gonna do it, right? What is going on?
Okay, she's almost there now. Oh, fuck. This is it. This is it. All right. Fuck this fight.
Let's go. Drink? Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. I didn't drink it. What? What happened?
Why didn't I drink it? I don't care. Fuck it. We're doing it anyway. What did I drink? Talking
about, dude? What are you talking? God, this is un-fucking-bearable. This is the worst fight
they've ever made without a question. Without a solitary question. I think you can just run.
That's the one you gotta, all right. No, no, no. Okay, there's two? Two of the thrusts.
Jesus Christ. At least that's the longest I've been able to see what the fuck this piece of shit
even does. Like you're so slow, but your moves are so fucking awful. This is what happens when
you don't have 99 arcane. Okay, testing. If I sprint away, I can sprint away and it won't get me.
Oh my God. Okay. I can run away from that move. That's confirmed. That's confirmed. I can run.
I mean, at this point, I'm just. That's one, two, three. You can't dodge it. This fight sucks. See
you in two weeks when they fucking come out with patch 1.04 and they're like, well, you know, we
always, we nerfed it a little. They got a patch 1.04. The first tagline is going to be in bold.
Linear damage output and healing has been reduced by 25%.
I'm not going to waste man on the moons. I don't think they're worth it. Maybe one moon. Let's go.
I didn't, why did I not drink the flask? I literally pressed fucking swear.
That's a broken fucking move. Even if you dodge it, like even if you dodge that shit perfectly,
it doing. I have fucking 52 vigor, 53 vigor. It does my entire health bar. You have to roll in.
It's like she keeps going. This is stupid. This is fucking stupid. This is stupid.
This is stupid. Stupid. It's stupid. It's stupid. This is stupid. This is stupid.
It's stupid. This is stupid. I just want to make sure you understood.
I can hate that move too. That's awful. It's the heal shit. Just don't let the character here.
Why is the only character ever that heals? You've made fucking 200 bosses from software.
You have to have it with the heal. I got back up, back up. She's going to do it. Is she going up?
Yep. Nope. She's going up now, right? She's going up. Yes, she is. Come on.
Mababababababambo. Don't fuck it up this time. What? You motherfucker. You motherfucker.
I'm so mad. Jesus Christ, please. Drink that flesh right now. Drink it. Shoot it.
It doesn't fucking do anything. It doesn't fucking do anything. Fucking Jesus. I thought
didn't know it was going to go that far. God, worst fucking fight they've ever fucking made
in the history of all of their fucking games. I don't want the gargoyles, black blades. I'm
talking about this fucking thing. I'm going back. You want to be a broken boss? I'm going to use
the broken katana. How does that sound? Let's just go to the... Now you're fucked because now I'm
angry. Now I'm angry. I'm like... Hugh, put every ounce of your strength into this fucking thing.
Every ounce. I'm going to... Seriously, code it in everything you could... What the fuck do you have
back there? Poison, rot, blood, magic stuff. Just dump the whole thing on it. Dump everything on it.
I'll pay you extra. I don't have any runes. This sucks, man. Give me the other rune because
this rune's stupid. Everything's stupid in this game, apparently. You don't understand
everything's stupid. Seven and seven. I'll pay extra. I will pay extra. I'll pay an extra
10,000 runes. I don't care what you put in that. I want it to be able to kill her. I don't care
what it is. All right, we're putting Godric's rune on. I just better work or I'm going to be
even more mad. I'm going to... I'm going to break. I think I have to... I'm going to... What am I...
I'm so mad. I'm trying to hold it so hard. You know what I mean? I feel like I'm like...
I feel like you're holding in a fucking fart and it hurts your stomach, but you're
surrounded by people and you're like, I'm not going to just fart and ruin everybody's day.
You know what I mean? I'm holding it in right now.
It's like if you're in a room with like 10 people and like, oh my God, I got a big gas problem,
right? Like I'm not just going to fucking rip ass at like something. No, I'm holding it. I'm
holding it and I'm fucking going to go in the bathroom. It's 1800 and then probably 2000.
I can't cool down. So angry. I need to cool down. I need to cool down. I got to cool it.
Let's take a rune arc. Pretty cool. All right. Very cool.
Use the mimic tier. No, the mimic tier is the last resort. Moonvale is the beta 0.8 last resort.
I need to sell some shit. I wish I could just fucking relax. There's like a demon right now
that's like, just start screaming. That's what we want to do. Just scream. And I'm like, no,
stop, man. Relax. And he's like, no, we're going to scream in a minute. What can I get rid of?
Okay. Just, just go to the bog spot. Stupid fucking boss. You know, and the music is so good,
but it's making me hate that song. You know what I'm saying? Like when I hear that, like,
I'm just like, fucking hate this. I hate this area. You're reminding me how much I hate this.
I got the 2000 rooms. I need to shoot it at somebody. I thought I killed him.
And this thing has bleed too. Fucking baby rattle. I gotta remember how to play with this.
I feel like this is going to be even better. I feel like this is not going to even be better.
Just kill the bird. Yeah, you're right. But I gotta remember how to play with this stuff.
L1 is the sideways and R1 is the overhead. It'll be significantly better. Use the FP talisman.
Stop telling me what to do. Stop. Fine. I gotta stop like putting the fourth of the
thing where like, oh, you're the, you are the most unhinged Elden ring streamer. I have to keep that
in mind. I have to make sure I'm like somewhere like in the middle, right? Like I can't be number
one. I can't be like the guy that everybody points to like, oh yeah, go to history. He's a fucking
psycho. No, I'm fine. And I'm not going to say anything else. That's nine. Bingo. Plus 10 moon
veil. I'm ready. I am so pissed. All right. All right. All right. I'm ready to at least give this
a try. This has bleed as well. Do you know about the Wraith Bell cheese? I don't. So what, so you
saying I should just get up there and just start whacking. Just like, wham, wham, wham, wham. Is
that, is that the idea? Let's see how this works. I feel like I'm gripping the sword way harder.
Fucking hell. What a great mechanic. I'm somewhere. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Dude,
it's the camera. Okay. Like I know I'm supposed to like dodge thrower, but like the camera just
fucking fucking rips around. Walk the first flurry. You should have a do well to shield.
Mine's going to come here with two fucking shields. I just hope I win. Let me just see if I can.
There's no fucking way I'm going to be able to do a toe to toe. Not a chance of hell.
Dude, you don't stop, but you don't stop fucking attacking. She does not stop attacking. Is this
intended? This, is this intended? I feel like there's just like a bunch of zeros and ones in
the code of millennia. Like somebody just fucking put them there and like forgot to get rid of them.
I feel like there's just a bunch of zeros and ones that they just like to put there. Somebody
copying and pasting a thousand of them and they like forgot to get rid of them. Like, oh shit.
There's like all this. We got to delete that. Like this shouldn't be there. That's fucked up.
Why is it there? I don't think this is better. I don't think this is helping me out at all.
That's not doing it that much. Dude, I do that much damage with this more than that. Way more.
And it takes the same amount of time. Yeah. Like that's, this is, this is why would I, I'm not,
it's awful. Look, I look at this. That's 2000 damage if I get the frost. I don't think this
thing's worth using. I'm just kind of taking mana that I need. I'm dead. Use rivers of blood.
Bombo's not helping. Use the staff spin. You got to use it close range to hit with a sword.
You have to dodge her moves. I have a hundred hours in this game. I've beaten every single boss
except for this one and the next one. What are you talking about? I didn't run here from the first
bonfire. Damn it. It's just so hard. It's just like, she's got so many different time moves.
It's like, it's like the worst of every part of every boss game. It just really is. She's the
worst of every single encounter in Elden Ring and she heals when she fucking hits you. Are you
shitting me? Why was I crouching? Stop attacking. Just look at her health. Are you fucking kidding
me? I don't think this is supposed to be like this. This is a plus 10 fucking weapon, bro.
Why can you do this? I feel like the people are like, oh, get good. Get good. They pick up
their controller and they're here too. You're here too. You've died 200 times too. Hey, get good,
man. I haven't gotten good either. No, you get good. Why do you not attack her? There's almost
no opportunity to attack this boss. Every other boss in the whole game, even old Radan. Old Radan
pre-patch. It was like, I mean, you could at least get away. You can't get away from this motherfucker.
This motherfucker is so awful. You can't get away from this and if you get hit, she just heals back
to full fucking health. This makes old Radan look like a children's coloring book. This boss is in
the wrong game. I get it. I've never lost a battle. I'm undefeated. From software, you don't
have to make that actually real. Just put it in a fucking note somewhere. Put it in a tag.
Have a helmet you pick up. Be like, oh, by the way, Millennia was really good and she lost
not that much. Don't make it real. God, fuck. No, don't drink that potion. She's got full fucking
health again. I can't, man. I'm about to summon fucking five of you and I don't even care.
But do I really need the accolade that I lost like 15% of my hair? I don't give a shit. Who cares?
What though? I don't give a fuck. Oh, Xbox achievement. Like 25% hair loss.
Oh, shit. Oh, fuck. Oh, what the fuck? Last boss in Sekiro, I could like reliably like play against.
I think they just mashed. I think they just put every slider to 100. Just said, fuck it. Let's
just see what happens. From software, they were like, just take every single slider and just put
it to 100 and just see what happens. Just see what happens to the world. Some like world event.
Yeah, just like put it all at 100, max everything out. Who cares? And let's see
what the internet says. And oh, we're talking. They don't even give it when you drink.
Please stop doing that. He's too upset to focus. There is no focusing. Just get lucky or sit here
for 50 hours and fucking just grind this until you burn it into your fucking frontal cortex
to understand. I'm so mad. I played, I played every single boss in this whole game.
And let me tell you something. This is the worst thing they've ever done.
Even that dumb ass dragon in Dark Souls 3 was better than this. That stupid huge dragon with
500 million health was at least like, was like, okay, I just kill me fucking instantly. That
just didn't happen. No, Kos was not even close. Kos had so much, no, there was so much intel
on Kos. Kos was a walk of the park in comparison. There was so much intel on Kos. Kos took forever
to do anything. The reason why Kos was annoying was because he went with every fucking move that
he did. You could dodge Kos pretty easily with the intel. Just running in circles. Bomb up. I
thought you said dodge through the second one. Fuck you. Oh my God. Was that too far away?
I think running is just the honestly like the most reliable way. It's so hard to perfect dodge
like 16 things in a row. Gotta stem it up. Shit. Oh God, she's gonna fucking heal everything now.
Combo just to hit her. Oh shit, come on. I tried to fucking dodge through it, man. It's just so
precise. It's so awful. So awful. It's so awful. It's so awful. I'm so fucking dead. Are you?
No. Oh God, I can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. Fuck. This is unbearable, dude.
Why am I eating the poison? Because I don't have any flasks. This is horrendous.
A poison. I don't have any flasks left. That's heals. I had to try to get at least some health.
Guys, do you think I really give a shit of my health bar going like this?
When she can take this much health in one second? Don't make fun of my fucking big
fingernails. They give me strength. Weapons dagger. You guys, okay. It's really easy to sit there and
be like, do do do do do do do do do. Do you understand that? This is the most unbearable
thing they've ever made. Ever. I'm trying. Don't you get it? Just add a fucking stamina, man.
You have to move so many times. You have to move so much more than she does. It's holy shit. I
don't fucking expect people to actually reliably do this fucking stupid ass fight. Holy fuck.
I fucking hate this game. This is a two. This fight brought this game down to a one and a half.
I don't even want this game to come free in the cereal box anymore. You understand?
That's how awful this is. This is a two. Two out of two. Two out of six. I don't even want
free in the cereal box anymore. How much? I'm trying to get her to bleed. I just want to see
what the bleed damage looks like, but it won't fucking proc. I give it a 2.6 GPA. Like, bleed.
Okay. That does a lot, but holy shit, you have to hit her so many times and she's going to get it
all back because nobody's perfect. Not you. Not even you. Stop pretending like you did this perfectly,
by the way. Nope. No way. It's close to the mimic tier. We're getting close to the mimic tier. We are.
What? Like, I'm level 145. What the fuck? How are you supposed to do this?
What the fuck are you talking about? Phase two shit, man. Like, you have to fight her.
You have to fight like three or four health bars worth if she fucking heals off of anything.
Don't get up there in fucking time. Oh my god. I wonder how many people in chat here
summoned a friend to beat this. And they're all sitting here and talking. All this
and they probably summoned three friends to beat this. And this sitting here, Pepe laughing at me,
and you fucking people here definitely summoned two of your friends.
I'm telling you. I'd love to see. I want to see your game files. Show me the game files.
Show me the game files, okay? That you beat this guy to summon.
Show me the files. I want it. I want it. Nvidia shall play of you beating this by yourself for
the first time. I want to see the documentation. I want you to use the power of friendship.
Dude, for the one person in chat here that beat this without fucking summoning people,
right now you are just like, you have huge balls. You know what I mean? That's great.
That's awesome. It must be fucking annoying, right? Like, but like, okay, some of us people here
can't do this shit. You know what I mean? And you could have that forever. You know, oh yeah,
millennia. That's like wicked fucking hard, kid. But I mean, I beat it like on my fourth try.
It's like, okay, dude, cool. That's awesome, man. But like, you must be, you are an alien.
You're a fucking alien from outer space. You're an alien. You were dropped off here in spaceship
and you have like a 10% higher intelligence than everybody else on earth. Use millennia's
shackle. That item doesn't exist. We're going to relax. I mean, I got it a halfway at phase two
before. Let's just do what we were doing before. The reliable thing we were doing.
Getting better. Getting better. Kind of listening to these negative Andes in the chat that are
telling me that I'm, that I can't do it. None of these negative Andes are going to get me,
get me down. All right. Is there a shield that blocks anything? I'm going to put a shield on.
I'm going to put a huge fucking shield on. I'm going to put a giant, what's the biggest shield
in the game? And I'm just going to just put it on and hold it with two hands. It's my favorite
kind of dessert. Tiramisu. Can't hold any of these. These are a hundred physical though.
Okay, here we go. Does it matter if it's on, how do I block? Why can't I fucking block like this?
God damn it. I thought, just fucking killed me already. We just find like a glitch or something.
I'm going to find, I'm going to get stuck in the wall and it's going to fucking kill her.
She's going to go like walk through and die. Let me find some scrap. I'm going to clip into the
fucking wall and she's going to follow me and die. I got to fix this like, just can't wait.
I love what takes you forever to kill me when I'm just standing around.
Use the lie down emote. Try to parry her. Don't drink a potion, you idiot. You idiot. I need to
see, we're going to, this is weird testing. We're just, I want to test and see if I can eat that
whole whirlwind move, whatever it is. Oh, damn it, man. I hate this.
This is the most I've ever struggled on from software was I'm telling you without a doubt,
like not even nothing comes close. And I have 5,000 hours in all the from software games. And let
me tell you something Reddit, right? Like, yeah, I know I've seen it. I've seen, I've heard about it.
I just want to see if I can block this. This is just a wash. This is a test.
Just do it so I can just see if this is worth doing. Go up and please,
please just let me see if I can block the move. Why won't you fucking do it?
Go in the air. Six mana flasks. I didn't, I, dude, we've been trying so many strategies to beat this
stupid ass boss. Am I actually going to be one of these streamers that sits here for like 10
fucking hours to do this? Like, oh, I took me eight hours of two straight streams to beat her.
Go in the fucking air. Okay, you can block the first one. Who cares? It doesn't matter. You're
going to get by the next two. Do the power stands on the Katana. What about Blackknife,
Teesh? Do I have enough, uh, whatever they are? Do I have enough warts for that?
Summon your friend. Is Teesh actually good here? He says so much. Just so much.
Blackknife, Teesh will help a ton. I gotta do something, but it can't be the Mimic tier yet.
The Mimic tier is like, I'm going to like turn on the game show. I don't want to do that yet,
but trust me when I say I'm, I'm willing to. Oh, stop this bullshit. I didn't want to drink that.
I'm okay. Can't see anything. Oh, come on. You're doing it again. I can't hold it. I can't hold it.
I can't hold it. I can't block you when she does that. Oh, I'm trying to parry.
The end of this video is going to be opening up the trash can and dropping the Elden Ring disc
case into the trash. Boom. Plus like for more. Look at this fucking thing. Things are plus seven,
dude. All right. I'm going to try this one more. Where's Teesh? I don't think I do. I don't even
have Teesh. I don't have it. The jail. Oh, it's a jail. All right. Let's go do it. I'm fucking
putting up with this anymore. I don't care. I'm not doing it. I don't care. Whatever. I,
I, I'll, I'll summon Teesh and win. I don't give a shit. Who cares? It's just pixels on the screen.
You know what I mean? It's just like pixels that have been mushed together to look like an image.
Well, I don't care. Where? An area. This one here. Is that it? No. Is that one? No. Is it right here?
This one? Southwest. Right here? Okay. Right here. All right. We need to go to one. Let's go. Oh my
God. He's going to use Teesh. You know, for the last couple of days, I was thinking like, oh fuck,
maybe I'm going to try to beat this. I beat like the last boss in Sekiro and like I streamed it
and I didn't like get like help or anything. And I did it after seeing this for the last,
the last like four hours or so game wise. No, I don't fucking care. If I could summon a giant
omega lull that just came and just bit her head off and just killed her instantly, I would do it
and like everyone would be like, oh my God, he used the giant omega lull. And I'd be like,
I don't care. Yeah, I did. Good. Okay. I don't care. That was supposed to be so angry. Use the
mimic tear. The mimic tear is worse than the omega lull. You'd puke. Mimic tear is not an
instrument. I know I'm just kidding around. All right. Where are you? Let's go.
What's that? Oh, that's slow. Hey, shit. What killed me? What happened? What happened? What
happened? What happened? There's a dot. Oh, fuck it. I thought it was just like magical juice.
I didn't think it was a dot. This is hard too. This thing is in Lunaria. Holy shit, dude.
You can jump over it. Maybe not. That hurts a lot. Whoa. Got caught. Drink. Why the fuck
the input bullshit? 80,000 souls. Holy shit. Okay. You got the omega lull spell. How dare you?
What's wrong with you? Okay. Why don't you use common Azure? Common Azure does not hurt her really
at all. I did it on the phase two transition and it was like, I held it on there for five full
seconds and it was not worth doing. Okay. Where are you? Black knife teach. I can buy those.
You should do rivers of blood while you're here. Are there any more? Yeah. I need ghost glove
ward five. Hey, do I need six, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. Let's go. Not the right build for rivers
of blood. You got to respect. It won't work on an in-build. Let's give this another like hour.
We got teach. I've heard this is the omega lull bite millennials head off person. We're going to
do it. Arcane index, but that's like the whole, another character. I have a plus 10 teach. I'm
ready to fuck around. I'm ready to fuck somebody up. 132, man. Holy shit. All right. Bombo actually
was really good. Everybody loves Bombo. How could you not? I'm sorry. I have to put game genie in
mumbo. Okay. Let's see what happens here. Disrespecting best girl with cheese. Andy's
grass shaking my head. I don't care. All right. Get her. Let's just kill her. Holy shit. That was
insane. Oh, what was that heal? Oh my God. Teach. Why are you healing so much more? All right. You're
going to die on you now. I'm just, that should never do that much damage. I don't care how strong
the boss is. That's fucked up, man. Don't you think that's fucked up? You did one slash and it's
just a good 90% of my health. Come on, Gary. Cheese Andy. Oh, correct. I'm back. I'm already a G.
How did you miss that? God, you should never do that much damage. Oh, it's that cheesy Reedy
Brody. I hate this fight. I just want to get, I just want to get out of this fight. You know
what I mean? Like I just, I'm going to go to my game files and just where it says millennia dead
dash space exclamation point quotes, true quotes and bracket. You know what I mean? Like I was
going to put it in there. No, not mumbo. Fuck. Mumbo prove everybody wrong. Juice? What? How am I
out of juice already? She's just farming. Like she's being farmed. Oh shit. I just, I just can't,
man. I'm just so done with this bullshit. I need you to. Oh, fuck off with that from software.
What is with this code? Oh my God. You got to be fucking kidding me, dude. I can't fucking believe
that move. Like you guys put a training dummy on the ground that just like absorbs threat.
All that work gone in one move. Isn't it, isn't it fun? Isn't it, isn't it, isn't it fun for you to
spend all this time fighting this fucking goddamn motherfucker down here is all wiped away. She has
the stupidest move ever across every single video game. Every single one, every single video
game. And I'm even talking about the holy hand grenade from fucking worms. Armageddon. Oh,
you should have gotten staggered. It's so hard. Do you understand how hard it is to dodge that?
Because when you dodge, the camera fucking goes crazy. Sometimes you dodge like the wrong way
because she moves so quickly. I'm not going over there. Fuck that. Oh, I can't. I got no fucking.
I actually can't believe that's in the game. I was out of stamina. I couldn't run. I couldn't run.
I was too busy playing the game right now. Like the from software devs are watching the stream.
They're watching the stream right now and they're going like, oh, here it goes again.
Oh, that move that we turned up to a hundred and fucking a hundred times to just watch, watch,
watch him. Watch him. He's going to lose again. Yeah. Idiot, idiot, idiot. God,
he just never prepared for it. Oh my God. Oh, what the fuck was that? What just happened?
He just like did a full one hundred and three hundred and eighty. He just fucking did a 360
return. Fucking run. Just run away. Look at her health again. The healing is fucking stupid.
What is the, what's the, what's the fucking magical lore reason for her heal?
Oh, let's go read the description. Am I in the rot? Fuck you. I am.
Okay. Let's go. Fuck it. Just do it. Do it. No. Oh my God. Please don't do it.
Get away from me. Please teach me something. Please do something.
I fucking ran out of stamina, man. I have no stamina. I have no stamina. Oh my God.
Oh my fucking God, dude. How the fuck are you supposed to do this at a second phase?
She's got full health. I've got, I've got, I can't, the stamina kicked down. I can't even attack her.
I can't even, she's going to kill me. She's going to sneeze in one direction. I'm going to die.
This sucks. I'm dead. I'm just fucking screwed. Oh, okay. She shouldn't be able to heal in phase
two, right? That's not fair. Relocate flasks. How many health flasks? I don't know, man. This
seems like fucking crazy. Maybe like nine. How about the boys? The boys are going to fill her
health bar five times. What about your armor? I feel like I'm wearing some of the best armor in
the game. You need to cheese harder. How, how? Where's the other, where's the ultimate cheese move?
Just summon people and spam moons. All the people saying get good. I'd like, I want to see your
fucking clocked game time on this fight. And no, I'm sorry. If you came in here at soul level 500,
that's not what I'm talking about. Why does dude twice the fucking like delayed input shit?
I don't want to fucking do that. I want to, I don't want to do, I didn't want to do that move again.
Teach us under ones, please. Oh my God. This is it. This is the one. This is the one. This is the
one he's just got full fucking health boys and girls. Oh, fuck. No way. That's so insane.
That's just like, what the fuck are you supposed to do? If you, okay. I understand. Just run,
but just run, bro. Run. What if you're already there? Like when you, if you're already there,
if she goes in the air like that, it's like, you're fucked. The timings, it's like one, two,
three, four, five, six. It's just like, holy shit in my face. Get the bloodhound step.
Do I have to seriously just go get every overpowered fucking move in the whole game
to beat a boss in the whole? Just give yourself an arm cannon, a mega man legends, fucking eyepiece.
By the way, go get like the, the promoted, like captain Morgan fucking handle of alcohol.
You drink that. Well, you shouldn't have to do all that shit. The fucking moon,
it's right in front of you. You gotta be fucking kidding me. Just, I don't, just kill me. I don't
even care. Tisha's player one. Good. Good. I hope you do. I hope you beat it Tisha. Please beat the
game for me. Just beat it for me. I don't want to suck. Cause if I don't, if I summon somebody,
that's extra embarrassing, right? Quote, end quotes. It's extra, you can't summon somebody,
it's embarrassing. You beat Sekiro last boss first try. Oh, we like to jump.
That's impossible. That's impossible to do that reliably. You can't do that reliably. It's
impossible. I just only did that because I turned into Tigger. That's the only reason why I did that.
Okay. This is stupid, but it's going to work. This is really stupid. This is stupid. Turn around,
Tisha. It's impossible, man. They come up at such weird timings and they go across the whole game.
It's like, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, stab, stab, stab. It's like, you gotta fuck. Are you supposed
to do this? This, the tuning on this fight is like, holy fuck, they broke off the volume. All they
broke, at least this goes to 11. It goes to 11. It goes to 11. Roll to the right. Dude, what do you
think I was doing? Are you shitting me? I was, what the fuck? Just dodge. Oh, I can't even fucking
take it seriously anymore. I got missed the move. Oh, whatever. Oopsie daisy. Oh, the brilliant minds
that brought you fucking Sekiro and dark souls. Comes the ever, the fight of a lifetime.
Melania, some call it, she's never lost. Yeah. Oh, yeah. I have no insults. I'm just angry.
I could have, I was going to just go off, but like, you know what? No, I'm not going to,
I'm not going to go off. I'm not going to be the guy that everybody points to as the streamer that
looks like a fucking weirdo. I'm just going to play and I'm going to dodge this perfectly once.
Now I get that input. Dodge one second later. I can play it on an Xbox 360 sometimes. Like,
the input lag is like a full second sometimes. Don't let her do any moves. Either she goes in
the air killer. Do it quick before she gets this. The game hit her. Didn't that look like her back
was turned? No, I need that person to fight for the rest of the game. What the, what is that?
I thought she was doing the other one.
I thought she was doing a move guys. I thought she was doing another move. I thought that was
the big sweeping one. Oh my God. Fuck this fight. Fuck this game. Return it. I don't have a hundred
hours in it, but I'm returning it. I'm going up to the counter with these eyes like this. The
fucking GameStop that I got this piece of shit from. I'm going to be like, hey, yeah, I would
like to make a, I'd like to make a return please. Oh yeah. You want to make a return? Yeah. It's
been, uh, I know that like your policy is seven days. Uh, it's been 38, but I want a refund. No,
this is the way you suck. And you're gay. Your game sucks. It's like the guys at GameStop had
nothing to do with this game. Come on. No, no. I don't know where you are.
Fuck what happened? Why did she not move? That was weird. No, she had to fucking do that move
right there. Oh my God. She had to do that right there. You see what I mean?
It's like, if you're, if you're within like five to 10 feet of her, you're just fucked.
Oh, why? Oh, why? Why? The scarlet rot killed me, but fuck man. This sucks such a dick.
That sucks. I can't believe she did that fucking move of all the things. It's just like, come the
fuck on. And I was so, I was right next to her too. That's the worst part. Oh, you pain in the ass.
I can't believe that fucking move is in there. Like that move existing just fucking ruins the
fight sometimes. Like it just does. It just ruins the fight. That fucking move existing,
just throws, it fucking just shreds her and throws the whole run into the air.
That's what makes the fight fun. I don't like going to the dentist, do you? The dentist sucks.
The dentist is not fun. You don't go to the dentist chair and go like, yeah, I'm ready.
I can't wait for you to drill in. I'm not going to say it. I was so fucking close. It was one
fucking hit away, but she healed off of the stupid dance thing that she does. She healed like 20% of
her fucking health pool off of the summon. This sucks. I can't wait to be done with this. I'm
going to do it and I can't, I'm fucking, I'm not doing this on Me Strong. Me Strong is just going
to get high and fucking enjoy his life. He's not coming in here. I don't give a shit about secret
fucking ending. Me Strong is going to just suck a fucking ball. He's going to just,
whatever is the term that the fucking kids use. He's coming in here and he's literally
not coming in this door. I don't give a shit how cool this is. No, and it's not even cool.
It's not even that cool. This fight's not cool. Me Strong is going to get wicked high and he's
going to walk around limb graved. That's it. I'm looking forward to that. I'm just looking
forward to like going to limb grave and like fucking just like spelling the ocean and shit.
I don't want to be here. My God, you fucking seriously. God damn it, man. I'm trying not
to lock on that move. It breaks this whole encounter. It's a broken fucking move. It is
broken. It's a, it's broken. It needs to be corrected. They need to get in there and they
need to correct the mistake. It is a mistake. It is a mistake. Why are there so many people here?
I need to relax. It's like people like telling them fucking threads and shit.
Don't tell people to come here. Don't tell people to come here. Why? No, I don't have
access to teach. I fucking hate this. You gotta be fucking kidding me. I'm doing it. I'm doing it
with my original friend. I'm fucking furious right now. What is happening? Do the magic move. Do the
magic move. It's a glowing shit that she has all over. What's going on there? Why would I attack
Mambo? What was the point of that? I ran out of fucking stamina. I'm going to go put 50 endurance
in after this. I'm going to put 50 endurance in it. Then it's 70 intelligence and that's it.
And here comes the fucking
This piece of fucking garbage needed one hit. You had to do that move out of every move.
You were dead in one swing but you are so unbearable that like the the player base
does not even want to fight. They are afraid to engage because a few of the moves are disengageable.
Like that you just disengage the whole fight. Nobody wants to fight you. You're just annoying.
You're an annoying piece of shit. I'm taking one of these right now. I'm taking these fucking
ruined drugs right now. No, I'm not. So watch. Take one now. Quick. The only reason why everybody
fucking does this fight is so they can. It's a vicious cycle. I need to beat this because
everyone's gonna make fun of me if I don't. Everybody, all your like discord groups and
all your friend groups and shit. All you guys are sitting around going like fuck I have to beat her.
Otherwise like I'm gonna be the one person in the fucking friend group that doesn't beat her.
And like everyone's gonna make fun of me. It's a social experiment. Fucking social experiment.
It's a fucking from software. It's a from software like social mind experiment.
There were like government officials just sitting there with clipboards watching me right now.
And they're taking notes about my fucking behavior. They've got like microscopes.
Somebody's watching like this part of my face right here under a microscope.
This goddamn door and fuck this area. Can I change? Can I change? Let me ask you guys a question.
Can I change my ending? Can I burn this fucking tree to the ground? Can I go get an extinguisher
and can I go put out the urtree and can I torch this fucking goddamn tree right now?
Can I burn this tree? Tell me that I if I can I want to. I want to burn this this fucking tree.
I want to burn this place. I'm gonna go back to the urtree. Did my spell even land?
They have to fix this. Can you imagine somebody that doesn't really play from software games
walking in here? From software is going to send millions of people to church.
Like you're gonna you're gonna like make people go like ask god for fucking help here.
I want to see the uptick in like new religion applications after this game came out. I want
to see how many people like went to fucking church. Like went to like their local church
and was like you know what I'm gonna try. Yeah yeah bullshit. I knew you were gonna do that dumb
move. That's the meaning of this. I didn't I I did not press R2 a second time. I did not press R2
a second time. Why did it queue up another fucking R2? Why? I swear to god dude sometimes like if
you press a button in this game and you're in mid animation the fact that it like does that right
after. I want to check checkbox to make that fucking not happen. I want like a dozen checkboxes
for these quality of life things. Just fuck you.
Healing it again. All that fucking free health from that. You don't want. Okay it's it's like
seriously I feel like a speed runner. Like if she does that to the summons just start the whole
thing over. You don't want her to do that move to the summon. She regains like 30 40 percent her
health back. Just kill me. It's like shit. It's like I've had to kill her like fucking three
times already. Fuck you. God damn it man. Look at Tisha's health. It's just throw just throw dice
in the air. That's what this whole fucking fight is. Just throw a hundred fucking dice
into the air. Did you get 10 sixes? Okay good. Congratulations. What? I fucking dodged. Oh fuck.
No. Get away from me. I was so like intensely paying attention to all the fucking moves she
was doing that I fucking wasn't ready for that shit. Oh my god. I don't fucking even know where
the camera is. Oh my god. No I almost I needed one more hit to kill her which means I can do it.
Oh I still got one of the words are like fucking right here and I want to just spew them out.
Oh I want it like I want to say shit. You have no idea. It's taking it's taking like like stone
level concentration. Like I'm a goddamn stone. Not like spew out just this just just talking shit.
You know I'm watching so bad. I gotta I gotta bring myself down. What you're about to hear
is encouragement and praise with cheering applause just for you. Acknowledging you for a variety of
reasons. Because there's a situation that does not apply to you. Just listen.
So sit back. Get ready. Here it comes. We want to thank you for all your hard work. You're the one
who steps up and gets things done around here. You keep your word what you promise and then you
go the extra mile. Job. Job. As Bill Tellum. Job.
You're probably wondering why we have asked you here today. We want to tell you that we have faith
and we know you can do it. We know you've got everything it takes to accomplish whatever your
heart desires. The dream mission you're seeking. I bet it is yours.
Just listen. Everyone agrees. Your side. We're here for you.
Why? She had no health. What the fuck? You've got to be fucking kidding me.
I had to heal. I had scarlet rot. All it took was one fucking, if she had hit me with one move.
Oh my god. This is the worst thing in any video game that's ever come out. Without a doubt it
sucks. This is pure pain. It's just misery. This is miserable. Miyazaki, look what you're doing to
us. Why are you doing this to us Miyazaki? Please let me out. Let me out of here Miyazaki. I don't
want to do it anymore. I don't get it and I don't think I ever fucking will. Is there any rhyme or
reason how to dodge that reliably? I feel like it's fucking impossible. The hitbox is fucking
gigantic. And then she comes at you so fast. Like fuck that move. It's fucking terrible. It's stupid.
I can understand it twice. The third fucking time. Bro, fuck you. And fuck the horse you rode in on.
Fuck you and the horse you rode in on. Did I put the black and white filter back on?
Get her. And this time we're not fucking around. Put it back on. Cheers to you quick.
We believe in you. Dude, I don't get it. I don't understand. It's impossible. What the fuck? You
just dodge. It's not possible, dude. She goes fucking crazy. What the fuck? You have to run?
That's what I'm saying. Okay, how am I supposed to close gaps with having this permanent
terrification of like this piece of shit is just going to go in the air and just Tasmanian devil
across the whole game for fucking a full 10 seconds. What a stupid fucking boss. Did anybody
play test this? What was the game about to release? My fucking hand. That fucking hurt a lot.
Oh, fingers. Okay. My fingers. All right. That hurt a lot. That fucking hurt. They were probably
up against the fucking release. Miyazaki is like, I don't I don't know, man. Just fucking release
it. We'll fix it in a patch. It's like fucking six months later. You know what I mean? Like,
I'm just you're fucked. You are fucked. If you are fighting this boss, right, you're like,
let's go let's go this fucking educationally, right? If I'm supposed to fucking attack the boss,
if I'm attacking the boss, and she just starts Tasmanian deviling homing you across every
you need to run away from her first two, that's dude, but that's what I'm saying.
If you're if you're like, attacking the boss, and this and all of a sudden, like, okay, here we go.
Here she goes. You're it's too late. It's already too late. It's already too late. Unlock the cam.
Last time I did that, I dodged through the first one and I didn't know what the fuck she was.
Holy shit, man. I can't believe she she was dead. I got her down to one centimeter phase two,
three times now. Oh my god, this is the worst fucking thing I've ever played.
Oh my god. And everybody's saying that. Don't you when everybody says the same thing. Don't
we all agree that it's true? When everybody's saying, oh, yeah, this is the fucking shittiest
thing I've ever done in a video game. It's not accurate. 99.9999.9% of people. That's so many
people. I feel like I'm fucking like a radio host. Spider-Man and when we get those photos of
Spider-Man at 99.9999% of people hate Spider-Man. And that's why I think that they should nerf
Spider-Man like I'm turning the J Jonah fucking Jameson. I knew that sucks. Look at the health
teach his health now. It's just like, fuck you. Now teach is going to be dead in phase two and
I'm going to have to fuck around on my own. I ran and I still get hit by the second she went
near I fucking ran away. It's still hit me. I still got fucking hit by it. God fuck you.
Worst goddamn boss. Please don't. Please just fucking get hit one more time. And I'm such a
bad fucking position. You guys wanted me to make my tier list. Put this boss at the very bottom.
Like F, F, F, F, F, F, F, F, F, F, F, F, F tier. I mean like F like I want it deleted from the game.
F tier. Like F. Worst, worst ever. And put Horror Lou up at S because that was fun. This sucks.
Horror Lou is a fun fight. Horror Lou is the best, one of the best fights I think I've done in the
whole game so far. F. You got an F. You got an F. Oh my God. It's so fucking slow. Oh my God.
Eat the poison thing. Eat the poison. Eat the poison. Eat the poison. Eat the poison.
What the fuck. What. What. Hit me. It went that far. It went that fucking far. And the rot dude.
Use Comet. Dude Comet sucks dick here. Sucks dick. Quiet. Don't stand in the floor.
We got all these game expert Andys. Game. We got these expert Andys. Okay,
I appreciate all the help everybody. I really do. I appreciate it. I appreciate it. I like everyone's
trying to help. I brought her down to one fucking hit remaining and she does something stupid
that covers the whole fucking game world. I've done it like four times now. And it's just trying
to get even remotely close. It's just so painful. The game just doesn't want you to fight the boss.
The game is telling you to fight these bosses. They don't want you to fight this one.
They want you to run across the fucking game. I don't want it to turn and run. Run. Run. Run.
Okay. Now, oh, here we go. Another run, run, run. Run. Run. Play touch your shit before you put it live.
So our place checking out what happened with our place.
Just run from the bomb attack. Have you played this game? I don't think you've
played. I don't think I don't think that I don't think that person's played the game.
It's so fucking stupid for what for me to lose hair who cares
But German go get the one fucking move ability. You have to get to fight this boss to make it better
You shouldn't have to make do 99 arcane to fight this boss
No other boss in the whole game has been like this is the only one
It's the only boss of the whole game that has been like oh dude
What you gotta do is you got a respected 99 arcane and get the blood move. I don't have to do that with anybody else
Fuck this. I ran a fucking stamina. I couldn't dodge
Did I just beat millennia and show my dick on camera
Please no, I didn't right
No, oh my god, I'm in trouble. I think I'm in trouble. I actually think
This this fly is open and I stood up and I like nothing. Oh my god. That was so many emotions in a row
I'm wearing fucking like pajama pants and these are wide open. I mean, I'm yeah, I'm wearing obviously my god
I thought I was fucked. Why is it open cut? They're just pajamas. It's just pajamas
You remember the dream that I had I thought it happened and whatever I was about to just lean into it
And I whatever I don't know what it would happen to me
I would have gotten like banned and I don't know what I would have leaned into it
It would I would be like talking about like oh my god
We shot German's fucking dick on camera and like whatever. I whatever okay, like I honestly what would I have done?
I would have been like whatever fine. I do cares. So well, yeah, you saw it. I don't care
What I have done?
No, it's the fucking worst thing ever that was actually the worst thing ever
Even with like cheese strats that was seriously like my teeth were falling out. That was the fucking worst
Holy shit, that was so bad
What a shit show. All right, let me I got so lucky at the end there being able to just spam like three moons in a row
We saw a ball
Honestly, what am I gonna say if that ever happened? I did that it'd be like, okay
Well, what do you guys think that one move ruins the fight?
Honestly, it does it does and I know you you'll get it eventually, but I know you could probably dodge it
Okay, if you time if you timed anybody out for like telling me to dodge those and I was like ban that person for a
Day, I'm being everybody
If I if I'd said that
Do endurance 30? I guess I have of course I have underwear on but it was like, I don't know
Well, I'm happy that happened, but we're not done. I still have to do the other thing
I have to do the last boss
So what what does that does that just what does that do for me? Does that do anything for me?
Does that open anything up or ruin?
Take the pot. Okay
Remembrance of millennia goddess of the worst boss in the game and should be deleted from the game and no one would be mad
If she was gone hewn into the urn tree
Power of its namesake can be unlocked by the finger reader
alternatively views yeah
Micola and millennia of both the children of a single god as such they are both
Imperions but suffered afflictions from birth one was cursed with eternal childhood and the other harbored rot within
eternal childhood
Check the mod chat for the clip
If you guys examined it the mods examine it
Okay, not the mods have examined it. There's no no balls were showing good. So what eternal childhood? That's weird
Cursed with eternal who cursed very cool
So now let's go to the roundtable hold check that great run
Isolated divine tower which stands beyond the lost great bridge
Stupid-ass boss has a stupid-ass fucking tower. Where is it?
Beyond the great bridge like up here
Mm-hmm. You need to teleport you already have it
Wait, what it's fun divine. Where's
Isolated my father stands beyond the lost great bridge teleporter at divine bridge grace
Why not have it anymore because the capitals need to teleport there go to the self limb grave and teleport to the trap with the
trap chest
Self limb beer teleport via what?
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where's that tower of return? Oh, yeah
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh
Yeah. Oh
Yeah
All right. Let's tell people I didn't beat it and like everyone be calming me down
Having a plus
Having 15 flies having one extra class is not gonna do anything one extra class is not gonna do anything fucking stupid
I really really like this game up until the last like fucking 10 to 20 fucking minutes
It's hard and this fucking just broken and stupid and like I take a break. That's not gonna fucking do anything
We'll get 99 arcane if I that you shouldn't have to fucking do that. I'm just not doing it
Not gonna summon people. No, I don't I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck. Okay
I don't give a fuck. Stop telling me to fucking summon. I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck
Stop telling me to do that. I never get angry on these streams
I really don't but like I'm fucking seriously, it's so mad right now. I'm never gonna beat it
And it sucks because the game is actually really fucking fun beside this. It's like an eight now
I give this like a fucking seven point nine
Are you telling me to go all the way to the fucking you want me to go get this fucking item?
That's gonna help
Didn't be like that
We got you
You that just came in you probably really concerned there. We got you. We got you. Yep. We got you. Mm-hmm
I'm sorry. I hate myself. Okay, uh
It's down here. L didn't ring L didn't ring L didn't ring L didn't ring. All right
Let's start the chant
Elden ring sucks. Elden ring sucks. Elden ring sucks. Elden ring sucks. Elden ring sucks. Elden ring sucks. Elden ring sucks
Imagine coming into the screen and just seeing the chat just like just spamming Elden ring sucks
It's like no, it doesn't what why is everybody hated here?
Sucks like that's what makes me feel better. Just get everybody to say Elden ring sucks
Yeah, that'll be I that makes me feel so it's like it's midnight. Holy shit
Extreme you should show us. You should show us crushing watermelons with your thighs
Do you imagine if I act if I did that like oh today guys, I'm gonna crush watermelons with my thighs
He's a stupid. What's stopping you? Um a lot of things actually. Oh this thing
Wow, that's actually kind of cool. So this thing's turned on. I
What the hell so that's how you get the guy I've looked at this before
Least on the map isolated to mine tower. This guy doesn't even own a watermelon. I mean, they're not really in season right now
What was that? What's that? I just like play-doh when you like the play-doh mush things
Are you push the play-doh through the thing? I?
Ain't not supposed to do this you fall down. You'll fall backwards, right?
What would you do if there was another millennia at the top of this tower?
Um, I would probably turn around and walk away and go fight the last boss
It's fucked up somebody's who would mean who spoiled it who spoiled it. Oh really? Okay
Are you guys full of crap? You guys are full of shit. Whoa, you can see a zoo
I thought that Azula existed in a time like outside of reality or something. Whoa
So what the hell is going on here? I thought that Azula existed like somewhere way out and not here
Just the center of the vortex does what happened?
What happened? Why is that place just destroyed? What I don't understand what happened. I'm in the future
This thing's in the past. All right. So what is for a boss that was that horrendous?
What does your rune do attacks recover HP after damage is taken?
So blood-borne acts made immediately after receiving damage will partially yeah, it's the rally from blood-borne
That's kind of cool, but I don't really need it. Do I have all the ruins?
I have I have the entire I have the whole Elden Ring don't I?
Lenny is daughter to Queen America and Radegon and her great rune should have been the most sacred of all
I have the whole thing. Okay, where's Mickela's rune? I don't know. Oh the remembrance, right?
Okay, you need to get the other I don't know and of millennia decks and strength causes blood loss
Decks 48 laid built into Millennia's prosthetic arm
Millennia's war prosthesis symbolized her victories some claim to have seen wings when the weapon was raised aloft
Wings of fierce determination that have been never known to feed until I did it
Waterfall dance perform a series of one-footed leaps in the manner of a waterfowl
When Lisa Swift you agree, that's the move. It's the bullshit move. Well, this is I don't have 50 decks
I'm not gonna get it. This is a faith move
It's a giant flower that explodes with scarlet rot each time the scarlet flower blooms Millennia's rot advances
That's bloomed twice already with the third bloom. She will become a true goddess
We do that
This whore this whore Lou. Oh, yeah, this is the super. Yeah, I don't we're not gonna do any either of these
Although this move could be cool
It's an ash of war which I don't think I can use on either of my weapons get it for you collection
Melee is usable on all melee assume her soul and buy 500 throwing knives
What about the equipment you can get the winged helm?
Winged helm made of unallied gold worn by millennia blade of Michaela
Millennia awaited Michaela at the foot of the husk
My brother will keep his promise. He possesses the wisdom the allure of a god. He's the most fearsome Empyrean of all
I don't want this cuz I hate this boss. I hate this person
This could give you this could deposit five dollars a second into my bank account and I would still not fucking wear it in principle
What a dumbass like that's fucking stupid. Oh
Just put it on and go idle and just go fucking go to the store. Just relax. I just leave it on
I would even play the game
five five dollars a second is
Let me see how much of a dumbass. I really am how many seconds were in a day. There are 60 seconds in a minute
8,000 660 time 60 times 24
86,000 it's about 50,000 dollars a day
50,000
Day is it a day
$18,000 an hour and I wouldn't do that
Holy shit. I did not I must have hated this
If I got $18,000 a day for putting this armor on and leaving my computer idle
Fucking dumb. Well now I can't do that. Now the power is taken from me, right?
I already said I wouldn't so I can't have it cool armor
Never buying it. Never putting it on. That's cool. So now
I'm gonna smash them. I'm gonna smash. I'm not gonna use this so I'm gonna smash it
Plus it means I get to kill her again
shit, uh
Maybe I'll get the move for fun. Can I level up? I can't just to level up one more time
140 I'll get the move try it. I mean why not? It's not like leveling up is gonna do very much anymore. Anyways
You missed an entire underground area
How much longer you plan on screaming? Um, I'm gonna try to beat the game tonight
Or at least get close enough where I have like one more thing to do
Where's the you actually did I did not do deep root do the underground you missed a boss
Didn't fight check out the bottom left of our place
Where's my mouse?
Is there is there another boss I can do?
Don't beat it tonight what happened? Oh, it's not loading. Okay, the bottom left bottom left
Hold on. Uh
Can you see I don't want to do that? Okay, so it looks fine. What's wrong with it? It's fine
We've got we've got our little corner over here. I mean, I I'd be honest. I wish you picked a different picture
I wish you picked a different photo and I do I why do I have to have why do I have to be kidding?
Why am I among us? I'm not this hair
Why am I eyes bleeding this boogers coming?
That's so okay. I can understand the boogers. I understand the boogers I do
We don't need to move. We don't need to go anywhere. We can stay right here. Wow. What else is going on here? Let's see
Oh, no, look at the
the United States
Going it's going under what else is going on here? Whoa
It's like spilling out. That's crazy. Yeah, we don't have to go anywhere
We're fine where we are hop left. Oh, that's oh, it's Aaron. Look at this. This is what's what's happening here
It's like a start menu. That's funny girl for the chessboard. Yeah, I saw the chessboard. Very cool. Oh, this is cute
This is cool. That's so cool. Yeah, we don't again. We don't gotta go anywhere
I'm not I'm just observing TK. Well, I can't wait to see the time-lapse
Is that is that a giga Chad cool, all right
That's like a photo. This is like a there's a photograph. This is insanely detailed. That's actually crazy
Star Wars. Oh
That's awesome. All right. Well, that's fun. Oh
forcing
Buggers what oh you took away
Buggers cool. All right, let's get out of here second. I said it. I spent all day looking at that
I mean, it's really really fucking cool
Did you kill the boss at the end of Fia's quest? I did not I don't even know what you mean
All right. So where am I going? What a deep deep root. Oh lie down and I did that boss already
Okay, so people saying go to knock Ron. It's over. Just go to your OBS and end the stream
Hold on. Wait, I think I know what this is. I think I watched Holly do this
I think I know what this is is it this is that place right probably so it's a I think I know what I think
I know what this is. I think I know how to get her you spoiled it. No, I just I like watching my girlfriend play
I was almost just hit Hollow Knight. Why why did I just say that?
I think I know how to get her you can get there from the mog as well. Okay over here
I think I know where to go. I think that might go the right way. Yes. Yep. Shut up
I got really mad not you guys shut up then
Here you jump off a cliff. That's what I remember. That's not it. There it is. Okay. I got it
Yeah, I remember watching her do this. I remember watching her at least go through this
Yeah, you supposed to kill these because like she was slaughtering these things. He was just like what what?
And I was like, you don't need souls or you don't have to oh, that's what she was doing
Right now. She's probably just like you motherfucker. I did not do that
Yeah
She's like don't say that
Yeah, she's just like slot is everything in this game. It's it's like actually kind of fucked up. All right, so
That's the dude that raged. All right
There's a difference between being very upset at millennia the first night of Mickela. Okay
No, Jerma, this boss is too hard. Nothing is harder than millennia. No way
No doubt, I don't think I do not believe a word you're saying I just killed somebody very far away
You afraid of awkward up? You're no joke
Nothing is even remotely as hard as millennia. This whole game is gonna feel like a cakewalk for the rest of time
I play it. I press the button you can have an Xbox controls sucks
No, poor one shield, of course. Oh, he's not killing the jellyfish. She actually loves the jellyfish
I find it to be really cute. Was he talking to I don't know. I think there's like fucking tons of people around me
Ancient holiness dwells within first bullhorn skewers blows and performing shield bash epic
Where is he? Okay. Is it aqua ducked or aqua ducked? I say aqua duck
aqua ducked that like it
What are the Nintendo switch to come out old gold gold gold gold?
Order healing death flight int and faith. That's really low
I can cast I can cast this spell you should do it. Please gaslight me. Oh, I want you to like have a good time
I don't want you to fucked up or anything. You but I come from here did where do I go?
Is there another way you missed an item? I need to stop like looking over here at chat
Like I'm just like oh right there. Well, thanks guys. You guys the best. Thanks. Appreciate it. You guys the best
Golden rune who cares got a brain up there
Remember a golden rune. I can go this way and I can't jump to there
You can see Mogs house from here. Can you oh
Shit, you can that's cool. It is right there. I wasn't in time
It's pretty it is really pretty look at the stars to see a secret boss. I don't think that exists
Let's try gaslighter
What down here forgot how fucking good this weapon was I haven't used it the whole time this thing is insane. Ah
About the baby rattle baby rattle. It did it didn't do as bad wrong or anything
But I guess it plus 10. Let me at least enjoy it for a little while. He's known for I am NOT supposed to be here
You're doing a YouTube build. I wasn't before you know what? No, I'll stick with it for now
I want to play with it. I should kill this very easily
Well, there's a glitch wait is it okay, there's another one I'm gonna kill you right now. Oh, he's getting close. That's scary
Whoa, send it with a flash
Our girls great sword gargoyles twin blade
Pretty sick. He's over leveled. Oh, oh
Yes, I'm very over leveled I'm like a hundred and like 50 just going back as people said I missed a great room
I want to see those words gargoyles great sword
vacuum slice
Just like the wielder the missing parts have been mended with corpse wax patchwork of champions
see strength that
Venom slice I just read that it was vacuum slice
What happened gargoyles twin blade see strength? I would actually be really fun to use the strength build
Okay, let me see. Oh
There's got to be something here some kind of thing that I'm this
mmm, I can't tell
Missed an NPC. I mean guys at this stage. There's literally one boss left. I I
Don't I'm not doing a quest line right now. I think actually I can go back you little runt. He's you
He's me. Are you gonna fight the final boss tonight? Um
It's getting really late. So, I don't know. How is it one o'clock?
Well, uh, we'll see I should probably take a break
Water you need to go say sorry to Holly night. I did didn't I I'm sorry Holly
Didn't mean to tell everybody that you were like murderer
Okay
Talk to the NPC you get a blood-borne reference
My mic has been pointed the wrong direction since I punched it like three hours ago
Have I sounded weird for the last like two or three hours?
eat brute depths
Okay, that's actually good for people that are that big. Oh
No, you know, you can start with it. You cannot finish with it
These guys were so hard the first like 10 to 20 hours of game. They were terrifying
staff of the avatar
C-strength D faith. I
Actually would probably want to use this
Bird tree slam. Oh that says the golden shockwaves everywhere shit
Use the most broken sword the game and says the bosses are easy
Dude
This weapon has been equipped for like 4% of my playtime
Okay, this is the weapon that I'm only using this just because I want to get my plus 10 out of it
This is what I was using before
You like I understand that like when people see the moon veil
They just go rabid because everybody in PvP just like spams it and everyone just hates it and it's an overpowered weapon
No, I I get it
But you really gonna do that to me?
This is my weapon, it's the baby rattle
I've only used that moon veil or like 2% of the game. So can't level up my axe and my bow
My bow and my bow. Oh, I'm use the horse
What flavor of axe body spray do you like do it when they did the chocolate one?
Yeah, they did it. Yeah, they did a chocolate like body wash and body spray and it was kind of
Weird it was awful smelling. But at the same time you kind of got used to it and you liked it
Kind of sounds felt like like like burnt sugar or something. You missed it
But did I miss you missed it? What did I miss? There's a dung beetle. Whatever be strong. I'll get it
Yeah, it was really weird. It smelled like
shit, it was one of those cases where be very careful when you go shopping for body wash
Because sometimes you'll be there and you'll you pop it open you and whatever you'd like to smell right or like
How's this one's does this one smell? Okay, right? Don't trust that
Don't ever trust that you get at home and it smells terrible. Oh my god
Okay
Within the hot shower that gets gross go there you liked it because it's felt like shit. Oh
It's concentrated form smelled. Okay
When it was heated up, it smelled pretty awful. That's a legendary item. By the way, look at that. That's legendary beam
I'm gonna have to come from another way. Oh my god scared me
Okay. Well, whatever am I gonna beat the final boss this stream? Probably not
One of these okay. Whoa, my goodness. That was okay. That was like in real life when a bug flies next your head
I was about to just dash out of the room
Are you gonna at least attempt it?
Yeah, I don't want to go to too late
Right, I don't want to just I don't want to go so late
Depending how long this takes me. I might try like once or twice
then now I'll actually only have one thing left to do in the game and then we'll do that and then I'll start the like
PvP night like the invasion night
Where I invade your game potentially or maybe you summon me and I help you beat
That piece of shit boss
You probably combine those creeps together
River of blood exploit night. No, we'll have rules
We will ban weapons and if you use them
You are excommunicated from the community fuck. That's like a minecraft chunk error
Whoa
There's a finger reader here. You're good
I
What are the two fingers oh
I think I can level up. They're just an alien radio antenna. Why make them a hand? Why make them
They're markers down here. What markers do I have here? I don't have any markers. What's that weird? Oh
Nope ghost level up work five could have used that
Why let go?
Oh shit, that's a that's that's quite a congregation of those
Right so hard, but i'm just way stronger than you. Good try though
Is it only one?
That breathes fire. Whatever fucking i'm over leveled
Astro for vacuum slice. I already have that
There's not much down here climb the tree
Let's check
He's the guy live
He beat millennia. I did
I got very lucky. I used a very powerful summon. I didn't use the mimicked here, but I used like the second best
Summon for that boss
Oh, there's a map oh shit cool fisha is better than the mimic
Okay, go all the way west. Yeah
Is that a
Three sentinel
Oh, he's up there. All right
Oh, come on
What's happening with the sound
What's wrong? What was harder millennia or the last little of simpsons hit and run millennia?
A hundred times and I mean I mean 100 out of 100 times. It's bullshit. No, it's not
That's the truth
last level the two towers
That was fucking awful, too
So what tree is this if this is here then this is the ur tree, right? These are the
It's like the roots of the ur tree
Right, this is the ur tree. Why does it look all fucked up down here?
Everything looks like all poisoned shitty
cool
Because you burnt it
I didn't a lot of ruins over here
clarifying clarified butter
You have to get in that
Well, there's an omega knight in here fresh on his mind. I wonder if he'll change his mind about it being 100 times harder
Past your bedtime it is but i'm close to completing
elden ring
We'll see how tired i'm i'll take a break after this fight
This is definitely a fight down here. Why would you tell me to come down here if there wasn't let me look over here
Oh my god, it's a boss. Oh, I did not think you were you're gonna be here
Get it
Got you
Celurias tree so this is this is another person's tree
Celuria
Whoa crucible tree armor. Holy shit come with the crucible knights who served godfrey the first elden lord
the great tree
ornamentation is the knight celurias mark
Displayed also by her men
Holds the power of the crucible of life the primordial form of the urd tree strengthens aspects of the crucible incantations
This is pretty good
You only read mean messages. No, I don't think so
It's like 4 a.m. I am pacific
Yes, t
I'm gonna take a quick gander over here
And we'll go in the coffin. Well, I thought that was a turtle
There's a bell
There's one of those bell things here
down there
Damn, I don't have an item. All right, be careful
Oh shit. Cool. All right
They give you a lot of those uh resemblances
I don't really care for it right now, but it's cool
Interesting
very interesting
Okay
What's that part of this mausoleum soldier ashes? Okay, that's cool. I actually want to look at those
All right coffin time
A lot of spitting stones here if you're looking for spitting stones five six four five six. There's a shitload here
Back to the coffin, please don't
I hear a twinkle
Uh-huh
So spitting those I'm not spitting so whatever
I know the words i'm trying to say it's not coming out right
Often no, no, no coffin. No not in the coffin
Up the roots like up here. This is where i'm going
We're losing them. Am I going the right way?
Other roots up the roots near the coffin
Back where the gargoyle was spitting fire at you. Okay
Don't go in the coffin
go over there
backseaters, that's okay, uh, i'm
actually thankful for the backseaters
because
It's getting late and not that I want I don't want to rush through the game. Not a million years
But it's getting late and I kind of want to see what's down here
You're saying over here
there
Don't help him. No help
Probably go from here. Um
I don't think so
You're
No, no, no nodders. Don't cough in my face
Didn't mean to
Oh up there
Two fingers stand for peace
Well, hi, Mr. Litherin
I don't want that ending
Oh shit
How far do I have to go?
There oh shit
All the way
All the way i'm going all the way
Oh boy
Oh shit
Okay
Why don't I get off the horse?
This looks like a boss area. What the hell is this?
That wouldn't happen in real life. If you step on a
Branch it doesn't explode
How close do I have to get to this thing?
What the fuck?
Oh, no
It's
A little shit guy
Oh, no
You know i'm gonna let you hit me three times
two
Three, okay
That was four
That's about enough for you
So you let a dickhead
burn
Got a better idea
Roger
What is he doing here? What?
I don't want to fight roger
Why bro, they hate you. What did I do? I didn't do anything wrong
Roger you're still using spells with my level 15 buddy
It seems the student has become the master
I hate the way my face looks sometimes
This guy worked for fear. No way
All right. Who's next in like the fucking?
gauntlet
This is okay
bro, why
What if lionel the lionheart?
Fias champ, why am I what's happening? Why is everybody ganging up on me?
That guy in one swing
That was somebody's little brother
You could tell he was wearing the pumpkin head
Nobody puts that on unless you're like you unless you're like 14
He's away from me. I might have to kind of like five people at the same time. Lionel is fat rolling
Is that it?
He is missed
Honest to god, what the fuck is that?
This looks like me
That's horrifying
Pumpkin heads actually like pretty good item
That was rude
What is it you intend to deny us golden order? I don't even know what they want
I actually don't know what they want
Everybody speaks in riddles in these games. Oh, does thou want thy golden finger?
What is what do you what do you want?
My lord doth how destined death?
Okay, I want to be held
They call yet. You still wish to be held by me. Well, I want the item you're gonna give me then i'm gonna kill you
Fuckin secret. Have you ever seen a hand when the first demigods flesh was marked with the half-wheel wound of the centipede?
Godwin's halibrand has since been recovered at the round table
But there is another halibrand somewhere before the time comes we receive our lord when godwin died
A halibrand scored his flesh
But another exists
Another mark in the shape of the half-wheel wound of the centipede
Must find it before the time comes we receive our lord
My hands will be dirtied once more by the deed will you still let me hold you
Oh, I have I have this
Give curse mark of death
This is the this is ranny's curse mark
This is the other halibrand how did you most thanks?
with this
Godwin can take his rightful place as first of the dead to get up and claim a second
Illustrious life wait i'm about i'm about to bring godwin back to life our true champion
Radiant baldichin's blessing
The new life of those who live in death
And take for yourself the throne stay the persecution of those who live in death
By becoming I will soon to conceal my own stay the ruin
I become
They get a rune
How are you gonna lay with godwin?
He's like a big
He's like a big cheeseburger
You grow hair
No, no, that's just sap. That's just sap. That's sap
What would be golden?
Us killed this is goodbye. I choose to lie with god or a child
What greater blessing could there be to be born? What are you gonna?
This is goodbye, but I am sad I choose and I will be willing what greater
How how
What is that?
That looks like a like dragon
scales
Enter the deathbed dream. This is fucking weird
Let's dragon portis axe
What
He's so overleveled for this feels pretty good after millennia. I'll tell you
Shit
Wow. Oh, that's death flight. That's hell
remembrance of the lich dragon
Holy shit that was yeah, that was 3k a swing
Mending rune of the death prince
Excuse me
Can be used to mend the shattered elden ring formed of the two hallowbrand half wheels combined
It will embed the principle of life within death
into order
That feels like an ai generated sentence. Let me read that again
Formed of the two hallowbrand half wheels combined
It will embed the principle of life within death into order
Golden order was created by confining destined death
Thus this new order will be one of death restored
What does that mean?
I now have the whole elden ring. I should be able just to put it all together and just eat it
That's cold. Oh that fight
Would have been a how come this is not on cannot be used
Why not this guy I swear to god?
Okay
He is hood. He is robe
Very confused
He is hood
Put a black cloth that covers the whole head one by fear the deathbed companion on her journey after being exiled from her home
The fabric itself is a soft silk
It was a shit
Curse mark is your baby
Put away those baldkins blessings
Yeah, I got a super one
Used to use fp to temporarily boost poise
Okay
Blessings of the utmost rarity
It said a deathbed companion will only produce a blessing of this kind for a champion, but once in her entire life
Soul blessing which she imbues of her own volition
This is just the shitty one
I can't be used
Gives it more max hp forever
Is it actually
Are you fuck are you fucking?
Are you kidding me kidding me? Let's get to 60. Oh
Daddy's here. No way really
Daddy's here
What's up, man? I love your videos
Time to get all your lore questions answered
Daddy daddy
I'll just tell you take your time. Take your time. It's probably an incredible amount of pressure
Uh need to come out with some of these videos
Take your time
We'll wait
We'll wait the amount of shit to piece together that i've been seeing from tons of people in the community
People are still kind of trying to guess what things even mean or what this place actually means
So this is oh, I found this I found that it's still happening a month later
Don't feel too much pressure. Seriously, like we can wait
Very excited though
Truly truly love your videos. I really do
Thanks for um stopping by. Can you give us a sneak peek? What the
the hornblowers
What are those?
aliens
What are the hornblowers?
Whose fingers are those whose fingers are those?
Can you give us a little um, give us up small
Why is there gold shit everywhere this gold dung?
Everything's gold is the gold ship. Why is there two fingers?
Okay
No, i'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding
He probably gets this shit everywhere
Like all that he's here
Explain in in minute detail, uh incredibly intricate stuff that takes like an hour to explain in five seconds
What does that mean daddy? Like he probably gets his fucking everywhere
No, uh, it's cool to see you here
He left
All right. Well, uh, should I try to beat the last boss? Should I go for it?
Let's do it. Let's see if I can do it. Oh the coffin. Where does the coffin go?
Ah the
remembrances
right
If I can pick this up
After godwin the golden became the prince of death the ancient dragon fought long and hard against the death within its companion
Alas victory was victory was never achieved and its only reward was corruption
I think those two fingers are giants. I think they're a giant species of giants and they were killed
And they only have like hands remaining and they try and they can communicate with the golden order
I also think that there's two fingers and there's apparently three fingers
Excuse me. Excuse me. How much does that make?
Excuse me
One two, three, four five. Excuse me. That was a whole hand at some point. That's five fingers
and why did these
Why did these fuck off and never come back?
You would think that the whole world being changed. They'd be like, you know what come out of sleep mode. I don't understand
odd really
Fortisax lightning spear and death lightning
47 faith
That's probably so cool
They said this golden lightning was wielded by godwin who befriended fortisax. So why do we just kill fortisax?
Just eat it. You know, you're going to anyways
What level am I?
I am 150 exactly
We have we are going to probably end the game at 150
It depends on how if I can actually beat this or not
All right. Let me give it a good try
It is late. I don't have to beat it tonight. I am going to
You're gonna remember the
Radigan fight because you have to do that first
Let's go
Can we break? Here comes the cool music
Here we go
final fight
tarnished
In search of the elden ring
Must extinguish thy flame
of ambition
begin
Oh you do another one fuck
Oh my god, I thought I'd punch me in the face
I thought I could
All right. Well, that's been a while. I haven't played this in a while. I haven't played against fucking
Radigan in a while. I'm so busy fighting millennia of just panicking and dodging every five seconds
I'll get it. I'll get it. Does that mean
That happens really quickly
I try jump if he does that
You know, I never learned his entire move set
I literally just summoned somebody and freaked up
I think you just have to stay close to him
This also is definitely not a place to have
Like seven flasks. I need all of them
also
Why am I not just using this?
That was real dumb
How would I ever use that on the move? It takes way too long
What can happen? What the fuck happened?
What happened? He's deflecting. Oh, that's what's going on
He's deflecting the magic and throwing it back
Okay
All right. All right
I'll get it. So let's just beat the shit out of him. He can't do that to the moon
Use the laser beam
What if he just deflects a thousand open row and kills me one hit?
Try it
Hold y and press r1
It's too late now. No, I'm just gonna beat him up
I did I didn't shoot any spells at him. What the fuck was that bullshit?
God damn it
I think I fucking expelled every ounce of gamer juice on on four hours of millennia
Where are you?
piece of shit
Fucking baby route sucks absolute balls like oh my god that hits with every other weapon in the game
What he's I gotta get around him behind him. I'm dead
Yeah, you gotta get behind him
Dude, fuck off
I didn't want to jump my fat fucking fingers hit it
You gotta get
Flail sucks the flail has like a hitbox of like
here
it's like
Here it's literally the hitbox of the flail is like fucking four inches in front of you. It's like
Elden ring sucks elden ring sucks
Get this fucking item off. It's the goddamn last boss of the game. You know, who cares?
He caught it almost all of that. Oh my goodness. He did it twice
It really makes you feel like you know, did bring you know
I mean really makes you feel like everything actually was a good strap you can summon
I want to summon it at the second phase. I think that actually kind of worked. No
I don't fucking know what to do. Oh my god
I gotta go behind him. Stop dodging back you fucking idiot
I didn't mean to press that button and damn it. Fuck the last three bosses of this game
I gotta start off
But you don't like aoe spam bosses
No
No, I don't no, I don't
Underleveled what i'm level 150. What do you it's easy to dodge all of his attacks
Just fucking didn't bring tish in your pocket. What are you talking about?
What I dodged it
Teach you and I are good friends
I've never seen this part
I know what happens here l plus over level plus still losing plus using the katana plus using comet azor plus ratio
Let's go, let's do it again. This is fucking who cares
Where where what's going on? Oh my god, what how do I do this? What do I do?
I'm being such a fucking idiot right now. He's confirmed better player by the way. Oh my god. What does that mean?
Whoa
What the fuck man? It's like i'm on the highway and i'm walking the opposite side of the highway
This is a car's driving at me 100 miles per hour
Oh god, damn it
You just run
Holy shit
I'm just doing it. I don't even care
Is this hitting?
Holy fuck oh fuck
Get it away from me
What the fuck have the from software devs been playing overwatch recently?
Do they like that game? Is that a is that a with their favorite game?
I just like you're just filling my screen with just colors
It's like what the fuck is happening this is five people altered at the same time
Oh, I didn't even fucking go this way
My fucking hand is so sweaty. You can sometimes you can't even press the button
Don't hit me. Don't hit me. Don't hit me. Don't hit me
I thought he was dead
All right, let's go. How do you get sweaty from pressing buttons? I've been holding this control over six straight hours. Oh god
I'm gonna get behind him
No, i'm not what I don't know what to do about this
God, I can't fucking hit animation shit
Can I get on the horse? Of course not
I just don't get in that right? Don't let it get inside
I don't
Am I in it?
Do I have to jump over it?
I think you have to jump over it. I don't know. Oh damn it run. Oh, it's right on my heels
You really have to go all the fucking way over there
Out of stamina
What the fuck let me over there
Bastard, sorry for the language. You just I don't fucking know
Why do you keep fucking going away fight me?
Jesus christ
I don't
What the fuck come over here?
All right, my heels
I have one heel
Oh my goodness this fucking swing animation. All of you motherfuckers are in slow motion in this goddamn game
It's like everybody's in slow motion and everybody just explodes the whole fucking boss room
This motherfucker run. He's like, okay you get close and then he just teleports across the whole game. Where's my horse?
Guess what?
The game crashed
What a surprise this fucking six out of ten
Teleport see it run it, please come chase me. I'm gonna beat it right now. I know the game didn't I know I understand
I need rest. I almost just did it get rid of this fucking thing. I don't want this. I'm just using it
I don't want this thing in my inventory
Me strong exposed. Ah, damn it. I wasn't close enough. You're gonna fucking do it three times
Thank you tish
Let's go. Oh my god from software. What the fuck is that? I tried to lock on and it's
This is the ring. I don't get this fucking key. I think I jump. I'm gonna try jumping over it
I'm gonna jump over it. I'm gonna jump over it
Ah
What is what the fuck is in the way? What the fuck is go? I can't see shit
What get this fucking mist out of here?
What the hell?
I couldn't fucking see anything
Was that actually the end of the look at how huge this place is
He dodged it. Yeah tish didn't have like gold vapor in his eyes
Or in her eyes. So I can't who are you? What's your name?
She uh, yeah
Fucking idiot put elden beast in the meat grinder just like they just decided to just
Uh, I got it. I got a pigman's but we'll talk about him later
my man
Oh, I fucking messed it up
A lot of aoe spam bosses just they just shoot it and brought the whole fucking road
What if I happen to swinging swords at each other?
Does every last like three or four bosses in this game have to have a fucking
bomb that a bomb
An over and over again fucking missile. I can't even hear the music over it
You're just dropping fucking missiles, man
I didn't think he had another attack, but how the fuck can you tell in this game?
You're going explosions
Oh fuck
Shaking my god damn shaking my head shaking my ss-ing my head
Shake shaking my head
I'm curious. Does this do any damage?
I can't even tell how far away I am from this motherfucker. I swear to god
All right jump over it thought I could go through it
Get away from me
You're such a fucking missile
Get this fucking thing away from me
What the fuck man, leave me. Oh my god. It's on the elden ring
No, what the fuck I attack him
I didn't want to roll that way
Please kill it. Please kill it. Please kill it. Please kill it
That was horrible
fractured america
summon ronnie
Oh, let me do this first
You know, I haven't I actually I haven't uh, there's a couple little dungeons
I want to do in limb grave because I didn't see what this was. I think i'm gonna go check that out
Summon ronnie battle is over. I see
He has four hands
I do solemnly swear
To every living being and every living soul now cometh the age of the stars
Did I make a mistake here a thousand year voyage under the wisdom of the moon
Here begineth the chill night that encompasses all
Reaching the great beyond
into fear
Doubtliness path stretcheth into darkness
Let us go together
My dear consort eternal
I
Beat the boss if I was stupid
He blacked out. Yeah. Wow. What did I say six out of ten? That's um, that was me being angry
It's way better than that. It happens what I don't get it. Heesh is the true elden lord
Rainy all right, what happened? Heesh literally killed the boss for you good. I'm glad
It's complicated
Rainy started a thousand years of night killing the tree and freeing the souls then okay
Basically give her the power and she decides to fuck off into space with you leaving the planet without a mean god to rule over it
No more gods people control their own lives
Started a new age. No more elden ring
You just gave them self-government
Huh? No more greater. No more bullshit greater will and two fingers
Oh who care? Yeah, fuck them. They they they they fucked off
halfway through the game
Which I don't get that either. Why do they leave?
They just like they went like they lost the connection to the router
Everyone gets free will now
Seems pretty good
the rating for the game, uh
It was nine point seven
After the millennia fight and after that fight, it's a nine point
nine point six
nine point six five
Nine no
That's not that's horseshit. It's it's higher
Okay, I honestly I thought these I thought this was like a kickstarter. I thought these like kickstarter people
There's so many names just here. I thought this was like thanking like the kickstarter people
um
Holy shit, that's a lot of names
Uh, it's a nine
It's a nine
The nine point eight is so simple. It's so easy
nine seven feels
Correct, but I feel like it's low
nine point seven eight
There it is a nine. It's a nine point seven eight
Bloodborne was a nine point four. This is better than bloodborne
I I think so that's slander
This is coming from somebody whose bloodborne has been their favorite
Well, it's bloodborne has been my favorite game ever all of all time since it came out
If bloodborne was 60 fps
It might be it might be a lot closer
nine point seven eight
It's it's this is so close to being a perfect game
And like what's the theory you think there is no such thing as a perfect thing?
Ten does not exist. It doesn't there's no such thing as a ten
And like a nine point nine feels like like horseshit, right? Like, okay, really?
You gave it a nine point nine
And doesn't mean perfect
It probably is a ten ask me tomorrow
Sekiro, I did not I was not a big fan of Sekiro
I thought Sekiro was good, but I I did not think it holds up to this
All right, ask me tomorrow. It's probably like a nine point eight seven
But wow, what a fucking app as a masterpiece it is
He said half-life alex was a nine point six
Yeah, and this is better
By a small amount. I think it is better than now half-life alex
Half-life alex is in a different kind of category for me though, but this this is better than half-life alex
Was bloodborne worse than half-life alex?
No, it just ran like shit
It just ran like shit and we can all pretend like it didn't
Bloodborne seriously runs like crap
And they did okay
It was on ps4
And they didn't even give a ps4 pro version or some anything anything to get it away from like the 28 to 30
FPS that it was in 25 fps
I just wish there was even a ps5 version for it anything anything to make that game not like 25 fps
This game is heavily flawed. I think you've heard me complain about half of the things that we've yeah
But even with a lot of this game's issues when I was like, oh, we'll talk about that later
for open world games
Nothing comes remotely close the last open
Look at the last open world game that you played that you gave a shit about like really beside don't say breath of the wild
We all know what you're gonna say
Forget about breath of the wild
I haven't given a absolute fuck about any open world game. They're all dog shit
I haven't played a truly good open world game in a long time red dead redemption 2 was good
but red dead redemption 2 felt
Didn't feel like this. I loved red dead redemption 2 story and its world
But I think this trumps it in sort of
gameplay
kind of immersion
red dead redemption 2 is very good don't get me wrong, but
I don't think it it I don't think they even compare
Red dead redemption 2 is a good movie
Yeah, I okay. I sat there with red dead redemption 2 and loved every second of it. But yeah, I was kind of just
trotting around on the horse and
talking to like dutch and
Crafting food and gunslinging. It was a lot different
Did you begin journey 2?
Oh, okay
You can do it from the round table a war open world game has not done that to me how I feel about this
since
God, I don't know
gta 4 maybe
maybe gta 5
But even gta 5. Yeah, I remember playing gta 5 and I was fucking floored
GTA 4 maybe a little bit more because that was the first time where it was like a new engine
It's been about 10 years
Fingers still gone check the remembrances. Yeah, I will
Yeah, I got to look at
Yeah, and of course, okay look for all my frustrations with this game
For all the times you heard me say like this sucks. It's dog shit. It's coke
This truly is one of the best games that's ever been made. I think everybody can agree on that even if you don't like it
This is without a single doubt in my mind will will go down
As one of the single greatest pieces of playable media ever
I really do feel that way
Let me show you something about god of war god of war
I yeah
When I walked out here for the first time
And knew that I had no directions
And I saw this
It was a feeling
That was just like right here that I haven't felt since I was like fucking probably 20 like 19
That's how I gauge whether or not a game is like like holy shit. This is crazy
uh
Walking down here and realizing like how much is here going even to these first this first like kind of shack
Realizing that you can find things on the map
find little dungeons
It's terrifying it is an overwhelming horrifying experience
Nothing has done that since probably I don't know maybe like
eat the engineer video
Game is very front-loaded. I will
I will say the this the game is very front-loaded. I think that this area here
leading into k-lid
and then a little bit probably I but hold on I did love um, I did really like the
kind of capital area
Elmer was really cool, too
I I can't say that this was particularly like incredible
It's kind of just snow and fog
but
I don't think
This first like 10 to 20 hours of the game
Maybe even the first 30 to 40 hours
And ray lucaria was crazy too like walking in these front doors
And making dlc as well. Yeah
Like when you do this, I did it on stream. You saw how I reacted to it
You go through here
And you get to see the ray lucaria building
Yeah, azula was yeah
There's way more good zones than bad zones. Let's put it that way
The game does fall off a little bit at the end. I I have to admit that
Kind of feels like they just throw a bunch of shit at you in the last like 10 hours
Like seeing this in the distance
Seeing like azula in the distance being here seeing the ur trees
But the first 40 hours of this game
Makes up for the last five to ten hours a hundred times over
Is the
Where's the it's is it right here? Where's the the we can see the building the end bosses ain't aren't bad though
I just I feel like the last couple bosses just felt like just very
spammy and annoying
And you know what? Here's a complaint
We have this really cool horse
We don't get like a final like epic
Battle where we can use the horse in that last area against the elden beast. That would be cool
Like torrent's been with us the whole game and we don't get to kind of have that ending with horn
I feel like that's that's a big ball drop
Especially because the boss moves around so much
I wanted to take torrent to the end but torrent really kind of felt like a real afterthought in the last like 10 hours or so
The fire giant was the last time that I really think thought I really needed to use it
But that's not why that's why I don't think it's 10. I think it's like one of the best games ever made
I think it's like a nine seven nine eight nine nine, maybe
Who gives a shit about scores? That's stupid. Anyways
Who cares about like me have I got to give you like a score. No, this is one of the best games ever made
That's all you need to know
Stamp it recommended best game one of the best games of all time. That's it. That's all I need to know
Who cares about like an arbitrary? Well nine point seven eight like
Why am I even having that number?
I'm making that number up that number makes no sense. I'm going to the same place
Better than bloodborne. Yeah, it is but just because it's just a newer game newer technology not on a playstation 4
And you know, it's kind of depressing in a way, you know that post
Uh best masterpiece game ever made kind of depression here
I'm like sad the game is over. That's why I haven't gone to bed yet
Yeah, like look at this like this is just this was so awe-inspiring
It's like this will be explained really well
What the fuck is in there?
You don't know
You know, it's gonna be really you're gonna be you're probably gonna be in that room somehow
You're gonna be all over this place i'm seeing it at a macro kind of scale
It hits you in this weird way where you just don't
You're so confused. You're so terrified of this thing. You're so awe inspired
You know, you're gonna walk around every room in this place
And you know, it's gonna be hard and you know, it's gonna be scary
But like let's fucking go
Is this the honeymoon period or do you actually really like it?
I mean, it's been almost like 40 days. I don't think there's much more time for a honeymoon phase
Yeah
A lot of places like in the game did that especially in limb grave, especially here
There's a fake wall in there
And let me find let me find my favorite spot
but
I'll I know i'm kind of stalling to end the stream here, but still
um, I know i'm stalling but
having that area
Where you can see this? Let me see if I can find it here. It's from a cliff
And it's just you can't even believe that you can see it
Where is it? It's kind of far away. Maybe here
Is one spot where you can see the lacaria and a couple other things
North of stormville. Okay. Yeah, I know it's like up here somewhere
This is it right here. Yeah, I mean the stream's over but I mean we're just hanging out
Yeah, this is it here. It's just
You know, all right, you just saw it up close
from far away
it seems
The journey seems so awesome from here to there
Mount gallimard is right there. You got one of the churches you got ready. Look harry a lot of the it
It's just I love it. It's sad that it's over
But that's what means
I'm about to r1
Hello, there's someone there. My name is hietta
And i'm journeying in search of the distant light
I wish the ruins weren't so repetitive
Some of those done. All right
If we're gonna okay you just heard me gush about the game some of those dungeons were dogs of shit
Some of those dungeons were just awful. It's truly terrible just complete afterthoughts
It was
I want to say maybe five to maybe like 10 of them were pretty awful
But that's not that there's so much in the game though
It's so easy for me to sit here and not for us to be like that was fucking stupid. Those dungeons were terrible
but I mean like
Look at all this
You don't have to do them
That's why it's not a perfect game, but it's pretty damn fucking close and I know i've been swearing a lot
But I just i'm exhausted
There's a bunch of disappointing triple a releases. It's pretty great
Yeah, that too that too. Let's be let's let's get no let's talk no more criticism
I think this
shows
That you can still make incredible experiences that people
That people will the jaw will hit the floor still
I know a god of war it was an I told you the first like two or three hours of god of war
I thought were fucking unbelievable
um
I feel like that game dropped off for me a little bit though. But again that first like hour
God of war especially that first major fight
Was like it did the same thing it hit me in the same place. I was like, holy shit. This is cool
Uh, it's still it's still here and anybody that tells you that like oh gaming is fucking dead
Every all games suck. It's fucking awful what the industry is in this in the shitter right now
It's like I mean this look at this
this exists
um
And my god what a journey it was
What are we at for time?
105 well, let's say 104 104 hours
I've i've never put 100 hours into a single campaign ever
I don't think that's that's never happened
I have to be real
that has
Never happened my whole life
Never
I played through bloodborne a bunch of times, but all those playthroughs were like 40 hours
40 to 50 hours dark souls 3 was like 50 hours, right 40 to 60 hours maybe
GTA 5 would probably come close somewhere around probably like 70 or 80 not 100 one more for the road
How many times did I die in total what's the total death count
736 times
Oh my god
But yeah, all right. Let me tell you my plans for the future of this game because i'm not done with it
Because i'm sad and I don't want it to end so it's not going to
We are going to do
a like community night
I am going to you can summon me. We'll do i'll put my sign down without a password. We'll do summons
You guys are having trouble with something. Maybe I can come help
Me strong needs to do his first like 10 hours first five hours
Maybe first two hours
I want to do like a pvp like invasion night. At least maybe we'll come down the whole thing
So it's not over
But it's not going to be a priority anymore considering. I just beat it
Elden ring
Is now it's not going to be every single stream
It will be
In once in a while, maybe maybe the next stream will probably be something else. We'll probably move to some. Uh, well, we'll see
But it's not a priority anymore
And that's the end of the stream. Thanks for staying up late
Thanks for putting up with my anger and my bullshit. I really appreciate it as always of course
Wrong thing. That was an incredible journey
Game is unbelievably good
And I am incredibly happy to have shared it with you
Let's just be real
That was uh, uh, really fun
I'll be uh, let's be let me be really honest
That was some of the most fun just kind of playing a video game and hanging out with you guys i've had in a long time
Dad to see it go. I didn't even look at the remembrances. It's true. That was amazing
so, uh
See, uh, see another 10 years when another like fucking masterpiece comes out. God damn it
America's hammer
Stone hammer made in the lands of the newman
outside the lands between
The tool with which queen marika shattered the elden ring and radigan attempted to repair it
Wait, the hammer partially broke upon shattering the ring becoming splintered with ruined fragments
This is not a masterpiece
I think it is
We can have different opinions. That's all right
I don't think it's perfect, but I do think it's a masterpiece
sacred relic sword
Thoughts on what the weapon
Or tens are many and varied some consider it the mark of a great sin or a sign of great devastation
Some think it is at the end of an age while others the beginning
Can view the sword with bygone golden glory then fire at foes a wide golden wave fans out sweeping through all enemies caught in its path
Another faith dex faith. It's the farming sword
There's masterpieces you haven't played yet
I okay, let's announce it
I'll play breath of the wild
I will not immediately but we'll cue it up
I will cue up breath of the wild and we'll play it
You can't play breath of the wild after this. I'm not gonna we're gonna wait a little bit
I'm not gonna just like oh, hey guys, uh
Wednesday stream is breath of the wild now. I'll give it some time. This is really cool though
I'm not gonna do any of that right now
All right
enough stalling
Thanks for staying up with me
Uh, that was a wild one. I feel like I fucking
Had a meltdown
Accepted the meltdown had another meltdown and then had an end to the stream. That was like three meltdowns in a row
Wasn't I like when they're like a black and white like i'm smoking on camera routine
I don't remember any of that
Almost accidental cock reveal. That's right. What a fucked up stream
I oh i'm okay. I almost showed my dick on stream
Let's just be let's call it what it was
That's unbelievably that's awful
I'm fucking wearing jeans from now on every stream
That's fucked up
No, i'm kidding. It didn't
I have pants on I have undergarments on i'm kidding
But like my fly is open
Just wear I have pants on I was kidding camera got barely below your chest. Yeah, but I didn't know that
I love it. People just like what is he talking about? What is what the fuck are you talking about?
Wait
Is hugh still here?
I didn't even check
They're still here. I don't feel too bad about this being over. There are many masterpieces. You never played from the last 30 years
Yeah, that's true. That's a that's a good way to think about it. It is
But i'm sad to have like because you know, it's that everybody's into it
Everybody's trying to piece together the lore and
everybody's
So happy about it. I don't know. It just feels cool
big giant gaming community events like this are always awesome
seeing like all the gifts and all the people funny ways they've died all the
Funny stories people have people can tell
Doesn't happen that often once every like three or four years we get something like this
So the next stream
Let's take a look at a calendar here because it's not gonna be tomorrow or today. Whatever
Um, let's go
Let's go for tuesday
tuesday the 5th
What's your favorite boss?
uh horror lu
Let me think
Uh horror lu slash godfrey is probably my favorite of the whole game
I could do a tier list eventually here
total play time 105 hours and 47 minutes
I think the big centipede
what
the void big centipede void thing was really just
terrifying and awe inspiring
Probably that one was pretty high astell. Yeah
rykard was cool, but rykard was kind of a gimmick though
It was a fun gimmick, but it was still kind of a gimmick
If I had a top three it'd be horror lu
astell
and
Maybe godric
Even though I talked a lot of shit
the music for godric
It was awesome. The scene where he takes the dragon was really cool
Mogg was cool
Favorite non-boss
Oh, that's right placida placida sax was pretty cool as well. That's right
Yeah, I would put that in the top five
It'd be mariner. Yeah
What about the baseball stream?
I don't have any updates for you for the baseball stream. I do have a very vague update for you
That it's going to happen
probably in
july
Couldn't get it done in time
Uh, so july i'm gonna have a hard date for you probably in the next few weeks
Um
Look for a hard date. You'll get it soon
It'll be in the summer
It's gonna know it is gonna happen. That's gonna be one of my favorite streams ever
any updates on grotto beast
grotto beast is another one of those things that I
Need to put a lot more of my brain power into
My brain has been very focused on like one thing the last month
um
But yeah, it's also that is still a thing
Um
All things ceased to exist while elden ring was a thing. I was kind of afraid of that but
How many more stream events are we going to have this year?
I would say at least two
Baseball is guaranteed and then there might be one more. There might be one more big one. It might be very big
Good night, everybody
See you again on tuesday
4 pm
pacific
Take care of yourselves
Those of you that have been here for the entirety of elden ring
Thanks for sticking around and uh and going on the journey with me
Did it before but i'll say it again. Have a great night. I'll see you tuesday