Today is a very special day. Every 25 years, the barbarian village of Elvenwood celebrates what they call the Warrior's Harvest.
A fruitful, wonderful celebration of honor, where the finest soldier in the village is chosen to venture out far away from camp and potentially to never return.
I am that man, and I will accept the task to find out what happened to my old family's house, Castle Griffinsteed, long since abandoned and corrupted by dark magic.
I must find out what happened. I must uncover the secrets of my old family name, for I am Carl Griffinsteed, and my adventure begins.
I give my final farewells and loom towards the path near the castle. There she stands, nearly 200 feet from our encampment.
I see to my left there could be a broken down caravan, but I leave it. There may be a scary animal inside, and I don't want to deal with that.
So as I move forward down the path, I think to myself, there's potential for bandits. The castle has been seized many times by many different forces, and my suspicions are correct.
Bandits are waiting for me at an outpost, and we will see who will die today. It will not be me.
I ready my sword, and I charge forward, or I wait, I wait for them to charge. They charge forward, and I take my swing with my blade.
I knock one of them down, and their blades have no effect on me because they are just idiots, and almost totally unscaled.
I walk away from this encounter. What war will lie ahead? What treachery? What deceit will lie ahead of me in Castle Griffinsteed?
When I stand right now, no man has stood, no man enters, no man returns. When you step in, you are there forever.
So I hear from my old grandmother's stories, and here we go. A castle in ruin, once great, standing tall, is now a former fraction of what it used to be.
But this is not the test. The test is the catacombs below. That was a checkpoint. The test is the catacombs below.
One can only imagine the secrets and the horrible dungeons that lie ahead of me, but I will press on.
I must find out what happened to my house, and I will bring back news to the tribe. A dead end, a choice.
One can go left, or one could possibly go right. Oh, coins. Coins, I need these. Cool.
And what is this? What is going on in my father's dungeon? Are those? No, it can't be. Wizards! Evil wizards!
I must dispose of them. They might be conjuring up some type of demon underneath my family's house. There's too many of them.
I'm being overwhelmed. I need to find it. Oh, give me that shotgun. That works. Shoot him with the shotgun.
I must cleanse them all. No dark, black magic must be performed under here, and there could be hundreds, if not thousands of them.
And the final one is dead. Hopefully, I have stopped their ritual. My stomach is full of all kinds of fluid.
I'm getting sick to my stomach, very nervous. There's only one way to go, and it's straight on.
Through my old family's prisons. You can tell it's a prison because, look, there's bars on the wall.
Through the corridor, into the next room, where there are coins. All right. Okay, well, we got our supplies here, too.
Got a couple of healing potions. What's that, an Uzi? I'm going to take the Uzi. A magnum and a flail.
I don't want to use this. We're going to go with the, uh, we're going to go with the Uzi.
I think that's the best for this current situation, considering it shoots the most bullets. Nothing in there.
Let's keep going on. See what we find upstairs in the dungeon. It's the military. I should have known.
The secrets. They must want to sell them to some private industrial man. Not in my watch.
You're not going to take me. I'll get pretty shocking out here. Pick these coins, too. It's all about the coins, guys.
Got to get as many coins as you can, so then people know how high your score is.
What? Okay. They must be at least one. We're going to go with the more finesse weapon. Magnum.
There's one down. Yep, I know that. I can see him. He was peeking over. He thought he was sneaky. He's not sneaky.
I'll show you sneaky. That's a one-two. One-two, baby. That's a rocket.
Get rid of this guy. Don't let him shoot another one.
I should probably take this. You never know when you're going to need a rocket launcher, my old grandmother used to say.
So, on to the cave system. Seems to have been dug out rather recently.
The fresh smell of dirt is... I can't go downstairs. I may have put these in wrong.
But the mold and mildew caking the walls, and the slight crackling underneath my feet...
It's one of the lesser demons! That is Algorro, the third lieutenant of the underworld!
I don't stand a warrior's chance!
That was really easy. Okay. I think we may have won. We may have beaten Castle Griffithsteed.
I would assume that there's nothing left. That must have been the source of all the power, so let's make our exit.
What the fuck is this? This is underneath Castle Griffithsteed?
A whole land of strange things. Creatures and wildlife and vegetation I've never seen before.
A harmless creature, it seems. But I must keep my wits about me if I'm to uncover the demonic presence.
Underneath my old family's house. What's in here? Having lunch, I see. Creepy.
We're going to continue on. Another place, another building. What is in this one?
Oh, a shop. Oh, cool. I told you guys I was going to need those coins.
Okay, so we're going to get... I'll take some potions from you, good sir. Your radar gun.
I'm going to switch to the shotgun. Okay, it's time to go. I'm going to go now.
I don't really want to be here anymore. You guys are seriously creeping me out.
We're going to leave. One more door to check, just for good measure, you know. We're going to open it up.
Get away from me! Get away from me, you vile creatures! You're not going to catch me!
Get me out of here! I don't even want to be here anymore!
Laser beams! How dare you shoot at me! I gotta go. Time to run. It's time to get out of here.
Another dungeon! It never ends! What else could I find under here?
I thought I killed with demonic presence. But of course not, it's a zombie game now!
Don't you know every game has to have zombies in 2015? What the hell is going on there?
Alright, I can't be much further away from the final secret. I wonder...
What is that? I just saw a hand. That must be Algulu! The giant demon!
Stuck in the wall for all eternity! I've only heard stories about this! I must hide!
Look at all these creatures! What the fuck was that? Oh my god, a barrel exploded!
There's exploding barrels! There's bunnies! Laser beams everywhere!
I've got to be careful. Aim down sights, just like in Call of Duty.
I remember my grandmother taught me that secret of aim down sights.
She would be so proud of me if she knew I was using it now.
Must clear the rest. A few more soldiers. A few more zombies.
What's that I hear? Oh no! He's getting ready to cast a giant spell! I must stop him!
I must have fucked up his health, because he wasn't supposed to die like that.
But that's it! The zombies are no longer pursuing.
Have I made it to the final room? The final door? Will I uncover the secrets of my family name?
What is in here? Who is this?
Welcome, Carl. It is I, your great times eighteen great grandfather.
I can teach you all the secrets, for you are the only person to ever make it through the dungeon.
So your choice is this. Come with me, or take this at least two months supply of chips.
The choice is yours. I stand you will make the correct one.
What do you want to know about your father? What about your grand...
I kinda want the chips. That's a lot of chips.