How are you doing?
How are we? Hold on, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, now we're good.
What's going on? Happy New Year, everybody.
Officially, right? Last time I saw you, it was still December 31st, Pacific time.
Catboy. Yeah, I know, I know. Look. Look.
I didn't tell you when I had that- I didn't say,
hey guys, the next stream is gonna be me in a catboy outfit.
I just said, at some point, over the years,
over the years, I was gonna get into a catboy costume.
No, it has to happen this year. Don't worry.
It's gonna happen in the next- Okay, I'll give you a-
Look, it's gonna happen in the next, like, three to six months, okay?
I didn't say I'm gonna wear a catboy costume next weekend.
You won't even know when it's gonna happen.
It's just going to one day. And I don't want you to know the date.
Scammed? Dude, chat is in shambles right now.
But yeah, hopefully you had a good New Year's Eve.
I bought you for Eastern time, but took off around 10 or 11 PM Pacific.
And today, we're gonna do something that I haven't really done on this channel before.
I mean, I've kind of done a version of it, but I saw this little device,
and I had to have it, and I have to play it.
This is a knockoff Nintendo. It's shaped like the Nintendo.
It looks like the Nintendo. I just had to own it.
There are 620 fake Nintendo games on this console.
I don't know how many of them are real. I just saw this and I had to get it.
I've seen Vinny do this shit before. I've seen Joel do this shit before.
And these are usually a fucking mess.
They are the kings of these devices, I would say.
I'm just a measly peasant in their presence.
So I have no idea what this one is. I just saw it and I had to buy it.
Yeah, I've done the 700,000 games before, but never a-
Never like one you just plug into your TV.
Eat a Whopper? Tomorrow's the Whopper stream.
I gotta tweet this stream out. Hold on.
Yeah, this is called the Family Computer System.
Yeah, tomorrow is Whopper's stream.
A few weeks ago, I played that game, Black Masses,
and that joke is gonna happen tomorrow.
So a bunch of people probably have no idea what's gonna happen with that
routine, in quotes.
But for those of you that were there, cool.
I think I'm gonna have fun. I don't even care.
Oh, my God.
I can't fucking wait.
That's gonna be like my favorite stream of the year.
Part of me only wants that stream to be an hour long.
It's just the whole thing.
But we'll see. I don't know.
Let's see how much that makes me laugh.
Catboy stream.
You'll get the Catboy stream.
Okay, guys, okay, let me just break this down for you.
So yesterday, two days ago was New Year's Day.
But you expected me to go get an entire Catboy costume
and have Catboy makeup put on me in 24 hours?
No, I'm doing this legit.
I'm not just gonna go get a pair of ears at the dollar store, okay?
Just hold on, give me some time.
He's dedicated.
Yeah, well, it's gonna be my version of that image.
All right, let's go.
Let's play.
It's time to play.
So this is gonna be an interesting thing we do here.
I'm just gonna play this the way that I'm gonna play it on the screen right now,
or two random number generators.
Remember, there are 620 on this console.
And how this is gonna work is I'm going to roll this.
This is just whatever this lands on.
This is what I'm gonna play.
And whatever one this is on,
this is the amount of time I have to play it in minutes, okay?
People say, show the console, sure.
I'll show the family computer system.
So here it is.
Is it right here?
Can you see it?
Not the Nintendo Entertainment System,
the family computer system.
So, you know, well, hopefully this is fun.
I have to delay my audio by almost two and a half full seconds, by the way,
to be able to stream this and capture it.
So we might be completely out of sync right now.
I have no idea.
I tried desperately.
Let's test it.
One, two, three, four, five.
How's that?
Do I have to adjust it?
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four, one.
Good?
All right, let's go.
All right, good, good, good, good.
All right, so what do we got first?
The first one we're going to play, we're going to go to 162.
And I have to play 162 for two minutes.
Okay, good.
That's good.
All right, let's go to 162.
By the way, Mortal Kombat 4 with a C.
That's, I mean, there's a lot here.
Oh, what is it?
162?
162.
This one's called Duck.
This might be just Duck Hunt.
Oh, I'll show the controller too.
The controller's funny.
Look at this fucking thing.
So it looks kind of normal until they decided to add, like, mirror buttons.
They'll look here.
Oh, what the fuck?
There's just four buttons.
And it's A, B, T, A, and T, B.
And I tried to read the instruction manual to find out what the fuck that meant.
I have no idea what that means.
It gives, like, an incredibly unclear explanation of what that actually is.
Turbo?
Yeah, but it doesn't do anything.
All right, let's go to Duck.
It's time for Duck, and I got to play this for two minutes.
By the way, when I get to a point where I want to see
times up spammed in chat, please.
When I get the time, I probably shouldn't have told you to do that.
Whatever, Duck.
I already love it.
It's like Dig Dug?
Oh, shit, I got to get these off screen.
Stage one.
Duck.
How do you play?
I win?
Oh, okay, you have to bring the egg to the bottom.
Oh, it is like Dig Dug.
Did I lose?
Oh, shit, okay, hold on.
This is cute, man.
This is not even, like, bad.
This is, like, fun.
What is it?
Is it a dog?
It's times up.
It's not times up yet.
Oh, the egg broke.
Okay, you can't drop that far.
I got one more minute.
I have one minute left in Duck.
All right, don't touch the green stuff.
Wait, does it matter?
Because it can't fall that far.
All right, let's get a heart.
Oops, oops.
I didn't know Jerma was a retro gamer.
Oh, I think I blew it.
Did I blow it?
No, I'm not done with Duck yet.
I'm not done, I'm not done, I'm not done.
I want to get to the bottom of Duck.
Hold on.
I like this one.
Times up.
It doesn't matter.
Oh my god, I get times up.
Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, fine, time's up.
God damn it.
I wanted to play that one.
Maybe I'll go back.
Okay, keep Duck on the list.
All right, what's up?
What's next?
All right, 169 for seven minutes.
169.
What the hell is random number generator?
169 is gyrodine.
And I see right now it is almost 11 minutes.
So at 18 minutes is when I have to stop playing this.
This is, I probably should have made it five minutes,
but whatever, I have to sleep in the bed that I made.
Okay, gyrodine in three, two, one, go.
Okay, gyrodine.
Whatever, what's going on?
Oh, it's a helicopter auto-scroller.
Shit.
How do I kill things?
I can't hurt anything?
What?
Why can't, why do my bullets not hurt stuff?
Is it over?
That sucks.
It's like a laser tag weapon.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Okay, I was pressing, wait.
There's two guns.
There's this one, this is just lights,
and this one is real bullets.
No, it's not.
Oh, that's the ground.
Holy shit, okay, this is air and this is ground.
How am I shooting the cars?
Oh, fuck man, gyrodine's pretty good.
I'm liking gyrodine so far.
They just look like crumpled up pieces of paper.
I wonder if this is a boss.
I mean, this is just somebody sketched these in five seconds.
I can do this.
I can sketch these tanks.
They're not even symmetrical either.
Oh shit, watch out, jets.
I can't fucking believe I just lost right there.
God damn it.
Please spawn right here.
Oh my God.
Wait, no, no, it's like a checkpoint.
Just play Ace Combat instead.
You can't really compare gyrodine to Ace Combat.
Oh my fucking God.
No, it's the control is hard.
Why can't you, why can't, why not?
Well, because the Ace Combat is a,
this game was made in probably 30 minutes.
Ace Combat has a team of like 200 people that worked on it.
For like four years.
You don't just take raw hamburger meat out of the refrigerator.
Put it on a plate and say,
this is the same thing as the five-star restaurant.
Eat my fucking hamburger meat instead.
I have literally no idea what that meant, by the way.
Like I have no idea what that meant.
I said what I, the sentence I just said,
I'm saying it like internally in my head now.
And like the point I was trying to make is kind of there somewhere,
but like I don't know where it was.
It was in there somewhere.
If you deconstruct that whole sentence,
you'll be able to like find out what I was trying to say.
It was in there somewhere.
He's zonked.
No, I'm not, not today.
Stop drinking bong water.
All right, if I don't get to the end,
I'm going to be very mad.
This is not even hard.
Like I played like 4,000 hours of Binding of Isaac.
I can't beat Gyrodyne.
I mean, the controller is kind of hard to use.
Oh my God, give me a break.
Fuck this game.
It sucks.
Never mind.
It's funny.
These are excuses.
No, they're not.
They're...
Look, all right, the controller sucks.
I press left and sometimes it doesn't go left.
Sometimes it just sits there.
They 3D printed these controllers, like a thousand of them.
It's hard to use.
It's fucking hard to do.
How much more time is left on this one?
Two minutes?
All right, whatever.
I got it.
You know what?
Right works fine.
Up works fine.
Down works fine.
It's left.
Left like doesn't want to...
If you have to push hard.
There's a dev in the chat.
Well, I highly doubt that.
I'm trying to pick up the mermaid and it got me killed.
I can't even get past the first two screens of Gyrodyne.
This is making me angry.
Dev of Gyrodyne.
Why am I tapping when I could just be holding?
Stop pretending.
I'm not pretending.
It's hard.
You get on General Mills presents Gyrodyne,
and you tell me how difficult it is to move around.
There you go.
Watch out, watch out.
Hurry, do the famous Gyrodyne cheat code.
Oh, you're right.
Up, up, down, down, down, up, up, up, down, down, down.
B, A, B, B, B, B, B, B, B, B, B, B, A, B, A.
Left, right, left, right, left, right.
B, A, B, B, A, back, B, I, B, O, B, O, B, O, B.
Did I get it?
No, I was too slow.
I really don't want to be playing Gyrodyne anymore.
We're going to follow the rules.
I can't break the rules.
I have to keep playing.
30 seconds.
All right.
This is going to be the last life, so I better make it count.
I'm just going to dodge and not care about anything but dodging.
But I move slower than they do.
That's why this is so difficult.
I move slower than the bullets.
I move slower than all the other things.
And I made it.
I made it, I'm good.
I feel like I'm looking at the Chrono Trigger overworld map.
God, that makes me want to play that game. Let's just play that game tomorrow. No, no, no, no, no
No, don't lie to them. Don't lie to them. They'll fucking sniff you out. Don't lie to them. Where are these cars driving?
Why are they driving up here?
Off-road, I guess. All right. Oh, I made it. It's the first I've ever been in Jaredine. I can't even see the bullets
Wow, it looks so much better on your guy's screen. I'm not even kidding from my monitor
It looks like dog shit, but on your on your screen. It looks wicked good on my screen
It looks like shit when it's why is it? Why is that? How can your screen look so much better than my screen?
Whatever. No, it really does. I couldn't see those bullets. I looked over at my preview monitor
I can see them clearly and we're going next. It was Jaredine. It was pretty sick. There we go. 299 for
Three minutes. Okay, I can do that. 299 pong pong for three minutes. All right, let's play pong pong
I'm gonna start the uh, so 1930. Let's start and I'm gonna guess this is pong
If it's not pong then I don't know what it is pong pong stage one
Um, what the fuck is happening? What am I driving? Am I a car? Okay. I'm orange car
I have a bullets or guns or anything. Is it just bumper cars?
Wait a minute. Is this just a mario party game where you have to bump like yoshi and luigi off the edge
I think that's what this is. I don't
I don't know what the goal is
I have to just dump them into the corners
I don't have no fucking idea of it
Uh, what if I drive into one?
Oh, I was killed but I can't look at when I bump into them they don't go the direction you think they're gonna go
This doesn't make any fucking sense
I don't have any bullets or anything either
See like you think they would they would bounce backwards
But i'm I go for much
Why did I switch with him? What the what how is that even fucking possible?
What?
We switched places
Get in there
Oh, I don't have to do it. Wait, there's two more left. Hey jerma, i'm the dev of what is what is this?
I look honestly. I don't care what's happening in the game right now. I'm gonna read this
Hey, i'm the dev of jarodon. This game was the work of two years of work with myself another dev
He ended up with my wife and I lost custody of my children. Okay. Well
I'm the dev of jarodon. All right, it's not even careful. How much time is left 19
20 21 22. I have like 40 seconds
This is by far the worst one yet. This is the worst one yet
I cannot bump them when I get close enough. I just I switch places with them 22 30, right? All right
I don't even care. I'm just gonna wait
This was I don't even with pong
ping pong pong pong
Worst two out of three. All right, let's go
What we got coming up next is 223 for five minutes. Just get rid of the timer
That was not three minutes. Yeah, it was 19 20 21 22. All right, 223 for five minutes
Don't get rid of the timer. I'm just gonna leave it for now. There's like 600 games
I figured we'd do something interesting for the first like hour or two. All right, 223 is
Spy versus I want to play spy versus spy right now
223 is called five days. I'll have five minutes to do five days
So we're at i'm looking at the stream time right now. We're at 23 minutes and just about 30 seconds
So five minutes from right now five days
Okay, five nights at freddy's. All right. Do I okay? I'm just shooting. I can't really aim at them
I feel like this is how I end up playing x-com
Oh my fucking god. Okay
I can't shoot them at an angle. I have to do this for five full days
How come I just turned them green?
I can't even aim that direction
I can only aim aim at specific angles
I'm not doing that bad
Drive me fucking crazy
I feel like i'm playing like an old nintendo scary horror game like maniac mansion
And the title screen glitched out and it's just repeating
The cd just is skipping
Oh, wait, this guy's uh red
orange
He was one hit
Is he just faster?
This is penis music
No
All right
I'm gonna do i'm done. This is stupid
Just stop. Yeah, i'm down with this one. I don't even care. I don't care. I can't take this one anymore. I don't care
Now where we going next?
The tire no the time. Yeah, fuck the tire the tires. I don't care
Broke the rules already. I don't care like fuck the timer if it sucks. I don't want to burn my brain
seven minutes
All right
397 is what is it?
You have to follow the rules 397
Dr mario, this is a classic. This actually might just be dr mario, by the way
So do not be surprised if it's just just they just ripped it and put it on here. They did I think
virus level
speed music type
um, okay
I have a confession to make for all of you watching
I have no idea how to play dr mario. I don't even I don't understand it. I don't get it at all
I don't i've never played it more than five seconds at a time
I have to match like the colors right somehow
And you get rid of the aliens. I think that's how you play
And then I can attach it to here and then kill right?
Is this the game? This is actually dr mario or is it like a weird bootleg version of it?
Um, oops, there you go. That's fucking best gamer moment. Fuck 2020 moment right there if I ever see one
I have to attach this to oops. Oh, I fucked it up. It's over. What am I? Oh my god
I can't I hate these kind of games. I can't I do not like tetris style games
I can't do them. I get so impatient because the thing goes so slow
It just trickles down like one two three, but i'm like hurry get the fuck down there
I have to like think on the fly. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I don't want to do that. Oh fuck. I'm in trouble
No, I can't I can't do it gotta go fast. There's no car I can drive. I don't like it
I don't like it. There's no car to drive. I don't like it. I'm so impatient. I'm so fucked up
I can't do it. I'm too fucked up to play these games. I can't do it
I can't do it. I'm too fucked. This is why I got like an f in geometry and shit like every year
I can't play these games, but I can sing though. Okay, that's worth something
Fuck i'm so screwed
Imagine being in like
Junior high school or high school or something and you get your your test back from the teacher and they're like, oh, uh, jeremy
Yeah, you didn't like you messed this all up. You didn't like do this correctly. The the angles are all wrong
Um, maybe could you come after class? Maybe like we could do some tutoring. Excuse me teacher. I can sing though
That's how you get to the office. Oh, I can sing though. Okay teachers like I don't care cool. That's like great
I'll get it this time. What a horrible excuse for every scenario
Mr. Albertson just want to let you know your blood pressure is a little high and your cholesterol is a little high too
Hey doc, I can sing though. Okay
uh
Good good
Start eating Cheerios and stop ordering fucking hamburgers from uber eats every day. I've made no progress. What's happening?
But I don't understand like what you're supposed to do in dr
Mario I get the concept but like I don't I don't care like, you know when you just don't care
And that's why you can't do it because I just don't care. You know what I mean?
How many you guys like do you like you staticians and should have looked at this going like oh man
You see this like wait, you gotta put them right over there
You could have been over there the blue could have gone over that way
I don't care. I can sing
I'm done
80 uh 88 what's 88? Uh bomber man. Okay, so it's bomber man for a maximum amount of
Two. All right. No, fuck the timer. I don't care. I was playing until I don't care anymore bomber man
Is it actual bomber man? Let's see
um
Kind of I want to say kind of
Is this what the original one looks like?
It's dead
This is what the original game looks like. Is it I don't think i've ever played the original
This is actually literally just bomber man. Is it? Oh, holy shit. Cool. This one's fun. I like bomber man
You know, I used to play bomber man 64
And bomber man 64 had a very surprisingly fun party game mode where you could have like four people
It was like a battle system. It was awesome
Come on go get him. I just didn't kill myself today. Okay good. Oh, why are you avoiding me so well?
There it is. Got him. Oh my god
This guy sucks at bomber man
It doesn't care
Does that really matter? Okay in in the year 2020
Does it matter if I can't do the original bomber man very well? I'm gonna die get out what?
It's funny. Whatever. It's been two days
You have a certain amount of time to be able to say it's still 2020. Yeah, you get that you get some leeway there
It's been two days three thirty six. What's three thirty six? It's been three days. Yeah, but whatever it's three days
So people are oh, yeah, man still saying 2020 shit people still do that shit in march
Okay
How many times people when they sign in somewhere or they write something and they have to look up to the clerk or right?
I look up to the cashier and go, uh
I don't have any idea what today is or what day it is what time it is and the person has to go
Oh, it's um, yeah, it's one four twenty twenty one guys every single time
I filled out a piece of paper where there was a clerk in front of me
They had to tell me what the date was every single time
I never know what day it is and sometimes they have to tell me twice because they'll say that. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, four five twenty twenty. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Cool. Thank you and I fill out the paper and then I have to go
four
Five five twenty twenty. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Thank you. Oh, yeah, that's I thought
So, come on this is battleship. Oh, is this actually this is the real battleship where you have to like
guess where uh
People's boats are and stuff
I told you this already
You know, I talked about like the next twitch thing
Let me call it for you. I'm calling it for you right now. We had like
It was all kinds of different trends on twitch right over the last few years
among us
Chess was huge for a while
Rust is getting big right now. The next one's gonna be battleship. It's gonna be fucking battleship
It will be huge drama around battleship
Within the next six months. I guarantee it
100 guarantee it
You come to me you come to me when i'm correct. I don't care. It doesn't matter how long it is
It could be six months
Hey, you want the absolute best tip for battleship put every single boat
Right next to each other in the exact same corner
Your friends will sit all over that top left part of the map and be like I have no fucking idea where this dude is
Here we go. All right, where are they? That's right here. Oh you've sunk you did I miss
Wait, what are we gonna? You're not gonna find shit. Oh, I don't know where it is over here, dude. Nope wrong
Don't get it wrong every time
How about right here?
Oh bear just missed
You're never gonna find it
Okay, what about what if he's doing the same thing?
Did I get it?
Is that a hit?
No
Either this strategy or all four corners is the best strategy because people just don't think you're ever gonna do that
Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? What was that?
What is this?
How does he have a four shot?
Um, excuse me. That's not fair
And where's mine that shoots four times?
That's fucking ridiculous
Why did he get that?
That's absolutely unfair
That was a hit. Okay, that's a hit. I know where he is
Yeah, good luck finding the rest of them
Right now he's oh right. He can do basic math
Found yeah, but that's so unfair. You found me because you had the four shooter. That's unbelievable
He's doing the same thing
This would have taken him at least four or five more turns
All right, that's one destroyer. I sunk the destroyer
All right, so i'm technically in the lead
I hope he's doing the exact same strat. Ah damn it
Pre-recorded what what are you talking about?
Um, i'm gonna say right here. Oh shit
Is it gonna be close?
No, but the computer has a bunch of algorithms inside of its head
It can do that math
A human does not a human has no idea what's going on
And then by the time they figure it out
They look up at you from across the table. They're like dude. No, you did not do that
No, you didn't
And I said like
You didn't know I did
Dude, no, you didn't
This computer knows where these are because it's gotta it's literally doing a math problem right now to know what these are
Music's a banger. Yes, it's pretty good
Okay, but he technically doesn't know where the other one is
Right here
Nope, he does. No, but he can't he doesn't know
He's still gonna take him. Uh
It's over. I lose
but wait, no, no, that was the the
Can we stop talking about how bad I am at battleship and start talking about how?
Unbelievable it is that you got to shoot four times in one turn
Um, I come we're not talking about that and change your weapon
how
press select
Oh my god, what? Why?
Mine's even better
I missed all of them. But whatever it doesn't matter because you know where to come. You know who to talk to
When all the top streamers are going back and forth in a huge drama on battleship
You missed all it doesn't whatever who cares next he lost in 20 turns
Yeah, but doesn't matter
Oh, I pressed. It's number 10
Sorry, I pressed it before you can see it. 10 is robocop 4. We're gonna skip robocop 1 2 and 3
Which okay, that's fine
robocopa 4
in 1992
1992 presents the year a production of some sort. This was made somehow
Robocop with a baby or a child. What why does the child have a machine gun?
What the fuck?
Okay
uh
Let's play how come I can't
I can't press any buttons
On the shoulder. Yeah, what the hell is going? I can't press anything
No buttons do anything. We just get to see the high scores of robocop 4. Okay, there we go
start
Command.com load bios memory system. That is okay crime in progress penal code is 139.1
voice analysis officer lewis and current position esposito and charlmers i'm on my way lewis
Cadillac heights dusk rescue your trapped colleagues from the clutches of the evil splatter punks things may go
Things are gonna go on behind closed doors. What?
Why was I like leaning back his robocop? He was just like leaning back in the car
He's just like
Okay, so do I how do I select weapons?
Oh missile
Hiding the trash watch out. We got a cyberpunk over there
Is that a mario power thing?
p-block
I'm i'm actually that's what that is. I'm just being completely honest with you
How do I get it?
Oh, give me a break. It's one of these. Whatever
And this is this is actual song
I'm gonna get in come and get it scum
Time's up. No, it's not what are you talking about?
Oh, this is wario block firepower upgraded. Holy shit. Nice
rapid fire
Time's up
No, I took the timer off
What does the p-block do?
Efficiency increased
Oh, okay. Cool. Oh my god. Actually, I like this one. This one's really fun
I mean, it's very illegal very illegal but like fun
It's time to wake up. No, i'm not getting out of bed yet five more minutes
How many robocop movies were there two?
I don't remember three
No, i'm not done yet with robocop. I'm playing it still we don't have timers anymore
This game has upgrades
Warning armed units damaged
What my arms are damaged? Okay, whatever
This is grand finale right here. You just walked up and you have a gun dude. Why are you walking up to kick me?
missiles
Yes
Well done officer prepared to enter repair laboratory. Oh nice
Why am I strapped in?
They have my ankles bound
And my arms bound why?
All right. Didn't say my arms were damaged. All right
0.005 percent
Is that 22? Okay, this is yeah, we got to repair this
Oh look how damaged this is. All right body
Here we go
Please confirm repairs press a to accept or b to relocate
rocket motors factory
Nice. All right. I'm going till I die. I don't care. I like this one
I like this one a lot
I haven't died yet. I'm going till I die
I don't care if this is a 24-hour stream. I'm not stopping till I die one time in robocop 4
This one's fun as fuck dude
Was unit my head malfunctioned. I just walked
Okay, um, my controls are backwards now
When I hold right it goes left because my head unit is malfunctioning. Okay, that's so stupid
Anytime it says head unit malfunction my controls are backwards
Hi missiles upgraded sick
Nice
Shit, I need that p-block
Oh a ninja
missiles are jammed
What missiles jammed again? Why is robocop such a fucking tin can?
Gotta get those auto attacks. I have eight percent health bad very bad. I'm dead
Get away from me
Wait, he's at 33 if I just land these I get it
Uh, fuck that was robocop 4193. I like the sound this makes
It's pretty nice
193 tetris 2 they don't like tetris. You saw dr mario not a fan at all
He lost to the ninja omega lull
That's not even a big deal
tetris 2
Level zero handicap zero music select silence
Loginska bradinskay
Karinka trika, which one where's the
Which one is it is it this one
That's not even right I like this one the best it's going on the right side of the screen
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Here it goes. Oh
It's just tetris, okay cool, I guess no ooey gooey
All right, can I do this can I do something crazy here? No, I can't um, which way which way over here?
Uh over here. Um, which way over here? Wait, I got I I have an idea
Oh my god, what do I do? Um, okay. This one's fine. I gotta snake one of those uh ones in there
I don't I don't know. I guys I don't play tetris ever
Um
I need that one. That's what I want
Yes, okay
No, I need the other z what do I do with this one?
I don't know
That's what I want. There it is. Can I snake this in there? Can I let's see
Fuck, okay. I can't I keep snaking it. I can't do it
I'm okay. I'm okay. Okay. Okay. Everything's fine. That was a double double double
Mm-hmm still on level zero. I can't think of something. I would rather not do than play
tetris
Some of you guys are so into this i'm not at all and I mean really at all
I never was even when I was younger this game came out when I was a kid
This is a big deal when this came out. I remember
Everyone was obsessed with it. Not me
I don't care at all about this
It's classic. I have to respect it right because I mean, come on. It's a classic
That's like what you can't but you're gonna hate donkey kong. How?
can't
That I just like the way that looks that's why I did that
Give me the one the l that goes that way. Is that the one is it the l gonna go that way?
Shit, come on, dude. Really?
Oh my god. Damn it. I need the l that I need the l to coast the other way
Oh now i'm in trouble
This is bad, this is bad. I didn't play this game. I didn't I don't care about this game
I told you a thousand times. You know how many times I have to tell you. I don't do I have to tell you another time
Saved
Oh, yeah
You didn't see me lose therefore. I didn't 453. I didn't play tetris. I didn't like it
I reacted the same way when I was eight
mo ya
Jin, um, I don't know what that says stage one rest three. Okay, what I can jump I have to collect these
Holy shit mo ya jin is the best game on here. Are you serious? This is awesome. Oops. Okay. I I
I don't know where I was. All right, let's do it again
This I like this one mo ya jin. Can I jump up so then I whack it while i'm on it, right?
What I can't jump on top. Don't you think I'd have to hit this and then jump on it, right?
No, can I roll it?
I all right. Give me a break
I you have to hold it for like three seconds to roll it
Is that a bald head with like hair on the back? I can't tell roll it
Yeah, I tried to and it didn't work when I went. Oh, it didn't work. I can't move it. That doesn't work
I must have to do something else
See you have to hold it for like a full second or two
Is it fall damage?
All right, there is
Dude, fuck this. Fuck mo ya jin. How dare you say something like that?
Can I get a few people in the dru crew to uh go out and just tell that person that they're not?
Come on godwin
What am I doing?
I so desperately wanted to call you guys the dru crew
So, uh, how do I get out down here? Oh shit. I might have just screwed that up
What is this?
Oh, it's like a pow block. Is it can I?
Just like in mario. Cool. All right
I can't get that guy
Oh, this is my favorite one so far, but hold on. Let me think this through
So I have to
Get the guy up top
Get the guy on the left
And then the guy on the right. How do I how do I do that?
How do I get this?
Times up not yet. Hold on because i'll die if I fall from here. I can fall down here
I can't I can't make the jump across
The screen what's wrong with the screen? What?
Screen is warping just walk to the right. What?
Are you serious?
Get away from holy shit. The timer is on crack
It really is
Oh, is this supposed to be 10 times slower than it's going?
Every fucking time I play it. It just makes me fucking angrier every single time
Um, how do I can't move it?
Oh, okay
How can I aim down?
What I just do
I just got really sad and the thing exploded
What?
Oh shit. Okay. Hold on. Oh my god. What do I do?
I I screwed it up
I cannot get this
Okay, wait, somebody kill me
It's off locked. Oh, it's because it's a bomb. Okay. I have a bomb now. I get you
So do it
Okay
now
Roll get away from me
Roll this over here
I can go up collect you
Go back this way
and
How do I get this guy walk the other? Oh
shit
Um, wait
Oh, it's off lock. This one was fun. I like that one. That was a good one
We already do 372
372 venice beach vol i'm assuming this is volleyball
Venice beach volley by super mega copyright reserved by who exactly?
Who owns the copyright to this?
No one that just wrote that
Configuration game mode one player point. Uh, let's do five set one rules
normal, okay
Tom george
Roquey james
What does that say?
weight 230 height 200 age 20
re
su
jage
resummage
Okay, he has 85 resummage
70 smash 80 speed
There's just 26
Okay
Uh, I want to go first. Who has the most resummage?
All right, you got the most resummage
All right, we're gonna go with james
All right, let's go
Pick it up and do it again
Uh, it's now, you know, it's because I don't have 100 for sewage. How do you holy shit? Okay
nice stuff
Stop it
Isn't idea tech is that a real company? Let's just just hit not jump. There it is. Okay
Oh my fucking god. I don't
What do I do wrong?
Is it it's a real company?
There it is
What are you doing? That's my partner. What are you doing?
I was setting you up
Do I have to control the partner?
All right, set this shit up ready
up or spike
This game sucks
Just seeing somebody jump twice
To hit the ball coming down
I'm gonna get it right here
There it is. All right. Now I got a block
Nice. That's point. It's idea tech versus super mega
The ball goes so slow and I said I want to stuff is that what yeah, this is an actual console on uh,
Composite video but it's going well. Hold on. It's going through. Well, not
It's currently going through a retro tink
2x pro
Highly recommended piece of uh hardware
Things incredible
Can take anything can take s video composite component
Upscale it run it through a good filter looks awesome
I highly recommend the retro tink get it today if you want to have an upscaled experience
on an hd tv
Never give up. We lost. Oh, i'm not trying again
There's no way i'm going to try that again
I mean we we're going to play these so don't worry
Well, you don't you think i'm gonna skip at you think i'm gonna skip hot blood basketball. No, we'll do it. Hold on
What's 113?
raid on
bungling raid on
bungling bay
Is a bungling round one factory six left four
This is another helicopter shooter. This is another this is two dollars
Oh, that's five fifty two
Oh my god. Okay
Is this this is this is like it's asteroids
Well, you're in a helicopter
This one's gonna make me sick. I'm gonna this one makes me sick. I have to stop right now. I'm done. I'm done
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done off off off off off times up. Nope not happen. That one is just instant headache number four
We get to play contra six. All right, I gonna why do they do this by the way? Is there a reason why?
There's a link. How come like why can't you just why does it have to be just numbered contras?
What's the link when a battleship match for one billion off the debt lose the match and one extra day of catboy?
Excuse me
No, no, excuse me
No deal. No deal. I got I got I can't make deals like that unless I can
All right contra six super contra six. This is neo city 1992. A lot of these take place in 1992
Hi, it's me fox
Is that you burns?
Yeah
ahead of intelligence
Is in serious trouble
We need your help
Okay
I'll be in the old warehouse
at the edge of the harbor
fox
Now we must eliminate
you burns
Wait burns as in like was that a fire? Wait, what's going on?
player select
Hey contra
Rambo guile ryu or bill
Oh boy. Oh boy
Couldn't they couldn't put anybody else here
I mean it kind of has to but bill looks like he has shitty equipment
Bill has a pistol or Roomba and a can of fucking butt light
Uh, I don't think bill's gonna be very good
Everybody else has like machine guns and flamethrowers. All right, let's play bill bill
Let's go bill
And it just is contra but not somehow
Bottom of the screen is just blinking
Rambo
Don't that copyright don't matter
It really doesn't
Like if I made a game right now
That was called contra six
And I sold it on steam and like rambo was the main character like how quickly would that get removed from steam
Why am I fighting a tractor?
What?
Why doesn't have a mind?
Forklift, yeah, but there's nobody in it
What bullshit?
Why am I going so holy shit i'm going so slow
Give me a fucking break. All right, just damage boost through it. Oh, all right. We're good
Yeah, I knew you were gonna spawn a guy right in front of me
Yeah, I was pretty good at contra when I was younger
Hey, what's the best contra times up? It's contra three for super nintendo. You got it wrong. Sorry
what
excuse me
Okay, it even has the
regular nintendo slow down
I gotta get more. Okay. There we go. That's better
Can I land on that? Can I step on it?
Go on I want to see what contra five is like. Let's see if it's any different
There is no five. There's one two three six seven eight
Oh, let's do contra three
This is the best contra so let's see this one takes place in neo city 2100 neo city's been around for a long time
That was 1992
It was the first neo city wait
Hey, it's me fox. Is that you burns? Wait the hell
Yeah
The head of intelligence
Is in serious trouble
We need your help. Wait, this is like 200 years in the future
Well, what?
Okay, i'll be in the old warehouse at the edge of the harbor
They must always be a fox and it must always be a burns
fox
No, we must
That's just my face
Who am I iron it's the same exact game with just different people
It's the same game. There's no difference at all
Okay, I want to look at all the contras. I want to see all the copyright characters. They put in
Dude, don't be surprised if like fucking mario is on one of these
I really wouldn't be surprised
I don't know if like ross from friends was on here, too
Cookie monster might even be on here
It could be anybody
Okay, i've already I don't care. I just want to know who the other characters are. I want to see the cutscene
Let's go to contra one. We've seen three and we've seen six. Let's see what contra one is
uh
Wait, what?
So inside of the contra one folder was like contra two through eight
This is just how a ton of folders on my desktop are right now. It's just poor folder management. Uh,
Okay, we're gonna do contra two
Contra one folder into subdirectory contra two and now this is just contra
a 100 rip
Uh completely I would say absolutely fucking against the law completely illegal. This is contra one
Um, okay, whatever
I I guess that's what this is contra one. No, it's not wait. Why do I have a spreader automatically?
This is like level three in contra one
But I have upgraded weapons
That is
Oh, okay
And they made it really simple. They gave you the spreader
Why would you do this?
It's just different scenes from contra one
So am I correct when I think that when they say contra two they mean level two in contra one
We need to investigate a little further here
This is gonna take some full investigation. He's so smart. Hey, thanks, man
You know what that boss used to scare the shit out of me in contra
It was the boss in I believe it was this exact same kind of style
Super contra, right?
Like that weird skeleton guy
That hangs around the room when he jumps on he hangs from the ceiling and shit and then his face pops out of the middle
And super contra was terrifying. It made every time you fought a boss. It played this horrible scary music
It was like
It was like fuck the boss is kind of scary
Kill it off. I forgot how fun these games were
You know the sad part about this
I'm gonna say something right now and you guys can tell me. Oh, no. No. Yeah, that's right, dude. That happened already
um, is it too bad that
I would love a new contra but the one definitely came out that was an ipad pay to win game probably right?
I'm sure they redid contra for ios and it's probably just complete just dog shit pay to win like weird shitty game or something, right?
That's so sad, I feel like that would be the thing. All right stage three waterfall. I have 26 lives
26 lives
was this in
I don't remember any of this
I don't I don't remember this being the game
Did I ever never get this far as a kid?
All right, I want to investigate contra one. Okay, so that was contra two. Here's contra three
It's definitely just the level select
Yeah, it's the level select. Yeah, of course it is. Oh my fucking god. So what's the other ones then?
So if that's that so what is contra 30p?
Shotgun what's shotgun?
This is just letting you start with the shotgun. That's so dumb
Okay
It's just just a game shark. Okay. No, no, no, I don't want to do contra. No stop doing contras
12 in one
so bogus
Click the link. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What's this link?
I'm gonna click the link. Okay, it's pretty good. It's pretty good. Not bad. It's not bad. It's pretty good
Uh, by the way, that is eight oh five eight. Oh six see I can read that today
Uh, how come it's not showing up there it is. All right, let's go. I want to see what contra two is
This is a debug menu
All right contra 30s contra four a this is not what that's not contra super
What arena four play is this contra it is
So this is just contra two
The contra three is not contra three. It's a made-up contra three
So what would contra six or seven be? Um, I've no I don't know what's going on
Not bad
But all right. I I don't I need to see so if that's contra two con we've seen contra six
What is contra seven super contra seven? I hope fox I hope burns is in trouble
Oh, this is uh, definitely a made-up one
uh
You can tell because how badly this one runs and I can't even pick this item up
It's just a rom hack of the first one
All the enemy spawning is just so wrong and off
two room
Two room sail
Look at this enemy spawning
Oh
Tototel
otototel
Sail sail sail
Everything's on sale. The whole world is on sale
The otto hotel. Oh, it's otto hotel
Love you. Love you. Love you. Love you
I think two room is my favorite
Although otto totel is probably is good. This is impossible to play by the way. This is impossible
And if you noticed we have not made any progress
We keep doing the exact same screens
This is never ending just keep walking to the right same thing
Okay, what's contra eight? Here we go
It's somehow just worse font version of the last one. In fact, it's pasted over
It's superimposed over the last one. It's just pasted on
Okay, let's see same exact game. No difference at all
And what's with this music?
I feel like I only have like 100 seconds left in any old nintendo game
Oh hurry up
Yeah, if you slowed this down it might actually be like a good nintendo like regular nintendo song
Done i'm done with this. It's over. Oh, that was super crunch at eight
All right. Now, where are we going? I mean, let's I mean let's do the robocop like fuck it. Whatever
We saw robocop four. Let's do robocop one
License from ocean software and then a real company the future of law enforcement
nice
Load up that gun
same exact thing
arrest mode second street
Nash avenue crime in progress. Oh, it's it's different. It's a different game
Okay, there's a punch. I just have a punch. I don't have anything else
Select doesn't do anything
Okay
These are these are who are these people? Okay. That's not fair. I don't have nothing. I know button select this block
Start doesn't do anything
All the buttons don't do it
That person just drop kicked out of the fucking window and hit me that was incredibly impressive that was unbelievable
Oh, yeah, I didn't even hit him he missed and he died
I want to go up. It's castlevania. Oh my god
Off the top rope. I can't go down
I don't understand how I still have a gun that I can't use
Oh
He decided to take out the gun. It's a scripted. Wait, what?
I don't want to I just shot a dog. I don't want to I don't like hate that sound. I don't like that
I don't want to hear that. I don't like that
Why there's so many fucking rabid dogs?
Why am I aiming like this too?
Okay
Here's what's going on right now
Uh this game they had some kind of model. This is pulling back a bow and arrow
And they just didn't care to change it
This is a different model for some other game that they made probably and it's pulling back a bow and arrow
What on earth is that doctor robotnik? Okay?
uh
Data east got him in the air. All right, I made it through. Oh shit
He's blocking the bullets with his hand
Come on, okay
Hey
Why would you shoot a flamethrower out your window down, you know, the flames would come back up and hit you right in the fucking face
Aiming a flamethrower down wouldn't the flames just come back up and hit you
Wouldn't the heat like come back when like the flames check back up backwards and like hit you in the face
That's not how fire works. What some of those flames would come back and hit you in the face
Can I go in?
Oh, all right. I gotta put the put the gun away
Now it's just fighting
There's liquid in there
It's simply hot
And plus wouldn't you burn the like building down too if you got like right?
I'm just going this is not somebody's room, right?
Why is there a gun on the ground?
Thought equals up. Yeah heat rises
Have you guys ever heard that famous fucking quote by that famous actor that famous role in that famous movie with that famous comic book
Character and that famous director
Oh, no prepare everyone's oh, no. No. No. No. Oh, no. No. No
Fire rises
I had to open up my iced coffee to do that and I got it all over my face
It's like a cover. It's all over my mouth and my chin and my nose and stuff
Remember, you're so stupid ban that guy for life ban that guy for life. Don't ever want to see that guy's name again
I'm just kidding vip them for 10 minutes. I'm just kidding. Don't do that either
Who I don't know
They're gone already
Like I I feel like see like your chat license plates
You guys will drive you guys will just drive by and scream like you're a fucking loser
Like what's that guy's name? But he's gone. He's gone. He's already gone. Fuck
I'm going up I think and some of you guys have a lot of numbers after your names, too
So I can get you know, it's like well, okay. I I see
One, uh g. Oh, no, there's a bunch of the numbers after
Like if your name is like greg
six
But there's like a seven or two a nine and a one after that, too
I
I can't mark if you don't know who the fuck you are
I'll get the greg part
Uh, I can't I can't do anything in here. Oh shit. Wait, this is like the this is the boss
Brother
I love when people at at okay
Robocop has never discouraged. Let's challenge again. No, let's see. The next one is
Every time I say a fake person's name you guys at the fake person
Until somebody makes the fake person's name remember you made my little sister cry when you made the pig noise that time
What do you mean?
What was your little sister watching me?
Yeah, don't that's not a good idea. All right, that was Robocop one. Let's see Robocop two
1981 is that 1881?
That's 1881
Got quite a few bullets in that uh handgun Robocop
Only supposed to be I believe 12 rounds in there
Gatling gun
All right, let's go
dark
What why is he wolverine?
A nuke laboratory has been located destroy all nukes on the premises
What target villains to be arrested are indicated by a flashing icon a select nuke a store is reported in this area
Why would I blow up the nukes in the nuke lab?
I don't know who that was but they've walked out here and I just shot them. I don't know who that was
I have no idea who you were
This moment i'm on ice
Why is there ice momentum in this?
This is fucking horrible
Why is it like
It's just skiing around
This is a huge dog fire hydrant, too
How do I arrest people wait shouldn't I be arresting these people instead? There's an arrest icon over there for the flashing indicator
So how do I arrest them?
Do I have an arrest button or something to select arrest?
So I have to destroy the nukes here
If you don't get enough momentum, by the way, you're not going to make these jumps. So I need to
Am I knocking on the door now?
I'm deciding to knock on this door
You have 22 of the nuke you've destroyed 22 you have arrested 40 of the target villains what
Report you have not destroyed enough nuke in your last mission proceed to the firing range for testing and calibration
There weren't any nukes and what do you mean arrested? I killed everyone
uh
This is just another game for the nintendo
By the way, what are you doing up there?
This is what's this game called?
for time
How many people have to kill?
This is actually in the robocop game
oops
Oops, this I this hurts to do
38 how many people do I have to kill 37? I have to kill. Oh my god. I killed so many more people
All right, does it matter if I miss and hit somebody?
How much more time do I have not very much
There's so many just random civilians here
There's more civilians than the bad guys
Come on
What hey what's going on
Hello incoming message
report
You failed to attain enough points in the firing range. You must return to your previous assignment
I don't think so
All right, we saw robocop, uh four right? So we need to see robocop three super rescue
This is in a different language robocop
That's not robocop. Oh dear
Okay
stamina
I took it's a three like a four hit combo
Okay
This is kind of fun, but not really at all, but i'm gonna give it two minutes
I'll give this the one minute it deserves. You know what I mean?
It's a p station. It is right
What happens if I spell the word robocop three
Too many robocops
Uh, let go let go of the grave
like flappy bird
Pete get it
Robocop four is three. This is shatter hand
Wait, this is a different this is a different is a game
What the fuck is that?
All right, this is awesome. Yeah, this is a game. Oh, I'm so just ripped off. Okay
Okay
They must have just seen the cyborg and just said you know what I don't just put it as robocop three
This is good
It actually is pretty fun
Shatter hand is an actually good game
Kind of feels that way
All right
Play ace combat
Will you stop with the ace combat?
I'm not gonna play ace combat
Lost time. All right, let's go
Shit, okay, he swings the gun at you when he gets when you get close
Can't shoot him with anything
That hurt what was that hitbox you serious?
Actually good game. Yeah, dude
That's fun. All right. We did the whole first page
So anything one through ten is done. Let's get a random one. Why not? Let's go random again
and 482
shockwave shockwave by american game cartridges
I would probably put at least a hundred dollars on the fact that this was not made by an american game cartridge company
I think that would be a safe bet
But you know
Do your name? Um
X who cares doesn't matter shockwave man left men left five code hti level one minor work
But I don't
Oh cool
That's cool
Can I dig through these?
Nice, this is awesome. All right. I like this one
Do I have a certain amount of ammo?
Oh, this reminds me of
Shubabrab
Yeah, the music is absolute dogshit you're right
This one's not bad though. Oh, wait a minute. This has got weird
um
Oh, no, I don't
This has got it complicated. I don't I does it
because it moves it
up or down or
405 405 is
Seaport guarl seaport guarl seaport guarl. What is guarl?
guarl
That's not supposed to be war right seaport war
Seaport guarl guarl. This one looks like it could be kind of fun support guard. That makes sense
Oh this sucks
This is awful
Space invaders, but way slower way more clunky and not fun at all
It's so bad, I can't even tolerate that for more than one second 5 26. I can't even tolerate it
Load runner. All right, this will be interesting load runner load runner. Let's go stage one. It's bomber man
Wait what?
It's burger time
It's burger time and mario original donkey kong
Can I do is there a jump?
Wait, what do I do? Wait?
I have to trap them
Okay, i'm gonna try
But what does the sand do?
I was looking the other direction dude
All right bury this guy
Yeah, bury what i'm looking the other way. I don't honestly you see what i'm doing. I was looking to the right and I
Moved my cursor. What was that?
He dug to the left when I was facing to the right
I'm going this way. Fuck it. Can I pick this up? Okay, I think you can pick the gold up
Check this shit out ready
Yeah, get out of here fucking dead
digs depending on the button you press
Oh, okay, that makes some sense
got the gold
Didn't spelunky based on this
I need to pick up like a bunch of gold bars and then leave
He can't do that. Okay. He can
what
Excuse me. Excuse me
How are you climbing out of that?
Excuse me. I'm not done. Hold on. I have to fill it in
Didn't I do that?
You can walk on their heads
I need to see what the fuck's going on here. Hold on come here
And fill it in and kill him
Uh
Die my fucking god just get out 475
475 is
sky kid
baron sky kid
Baron or baron and max let's do baron first mission one bomb the target. This is very bright
This is like this is very childlike for me like shooting at a bunch of like people
Am I like a little kid?
There's a dodge
Let's go
No wrong button
There's a dodge. I think there's iframes on that I could be wrong, but I think there is
I have to bomb the target and hopefully I get there good at a fast enough time. Is it a bomb?
Oh, I do I have the bomb
oops
What the fuck like ladies dancing
Was that the target was that the mansion with the mounted guns on it, okay, give me the bomb
I know it hurts my eyes, too. I promise god damn it. They're gonna come back now
Come on family computer system. All right, don't I got it. Okay, i'm gonna drop the bomb on it
I'm ready target ready target acquired here it comes
What is this? Okay, here we go drop drop
It's not it. I like this one. Actually, if it wasn't so bright and horrible on the eyes, I would actually like this
Oh fuck. I missed the bomb. Whatever
Okay, just dodge
Fuck. Oh god, you can't it's impossible. It's impossible
baron and max
Let's go. It's two people
He didn't make it off the runway didn't even make it off the runway max
Well, I still gotta do the mission man
I I still we have a contract here
Oh my fucking god, what just happened? What i'm still alive
What happened land here?
I did it. Let's go
Good start max. I'm really glad that
I'm really glad you came along
The absolute just double cross
I want to play this another one one more time. I don't get max anymore. He's gone
Oh
Jesus christ, that's impossible. It's too hard. It's a fun one, but that's
You move so slow. All right. What's next 415 go backwards. It'll be faster
four one five is
Holy shit, dude. This one is not just warfare. Not just a great war not just constant war the
utmost warfare there's no other warfare that will be more
Uh, that'll be higher than this that'll be more dangerous and and this is the size this is the top
This is high as you can go in war
And they've already got planets and shit. So we're talking planetary level of destruction
I don't know what i'm hitting
There's so many particles on the screen. I don't know which one is an enemy which is part of the background
Okay, I think I understand
Remember the asterisk
Oh double triple spreader
And you have so much screen real estate that you're only going to use the middle part of the screen and down
You really had to have that big planet the big marble in the background had to take up the entire third of the screen
Because they weren't spawning in the middle. This would be a lot easier and way more fun
And I don't know what's coming at us. Something is coming towards us
I feel like i'm watching
When somebody uploads an entire television show to youtube
And they put it in a square in the middle of the screen and they surround it with a bunch of other bullshit
It's like dude, that's like you think it's gonna help
Oh, there's no never be a war that will be more than this
I've had enough. What's next?
Boot cat. I got a good feeling about boot cat boot cat
Oh, it's just that's a cat inside of a boot. This couldn't get any more fun
scene one england
Uh, that's not where england is
That was uh, that was california
Is it cat boy boot cat
What's going on with these other cats?
Oh boy
uh
You have to start it just stands still to shoot
Uh, it's like four seconds left. What?
Why is the timer counting up instead of down? That's kind of weird, right?
Why is it a 14 seconds?
Uh, this is a real game. What do they make this up?
Is that the time of day? Is that gonna reset at zero? Let's see. Yeah, that's the time of day
That's what time it is right now
They decided to add a full cycling block
Why?
Honey, I can't shoot
There's a giant shark under there and i'm can barely concern
Oh my eyes
Why?
What is the point? Why would you put this in the game? What are you doing? Why would you do this?
Oh my god, the sun just exploded
This is a long level one, by the way, it just doesn't stop
We could have done mario
one one
10 times by now
It never ends dragon
Okay, let's go to the atlantic, uh ocean
Cool. All right. I'm beating this whole game. Let's go
It's even doing the mario song
The urine the water level. Oh, I love it boot cat is perfect
Is that wait that's supposed to be water?
What wait why is the water go into like a mountain
Get out of here
What is this? Can I go in this?
How many different paint tools are you going to use?
You can't just change the thickness of the pen halfway through your ms paint
Drawing you can't do that
But what happened to the consistency?
Well, okay
I can't wait to see yeah. Here's another water mountain
This lightning now coming down from the sky
I think these are supposed to be waves if oh really
What the fuck is that thing what just stole me something just came and took me it was a rat or a mouse or something. Yeah
It's the best one so far bootcats the best. It's just
It's I love it. It's so good
Almost got hit by that shit
I have to do well enough to beat this level because I need to see what's next
All right, watch out here comes the lightning
What the fuck was that? All right, easy easy
Don't get struck. Don't get struck. Don't get struck. Go go go go
Right at the same exact spot too. Come on
All right, last try last try last try last try
We have to go up the water mountain and the lightning is right above you
No, but I have to jump. I can't just
This thing's not gonna hurt you. What am I concerned about?
All right, don't blow it. Have we figured out what the timer is actually for?
Or is it just there for some reason what's the 73 in the top?
Wait
It's not 73 lives. Is it?
What's the p?
All right, don't go fast because you have the ability to
There comes the lightning
Slow down
They look at the mat movement pattern. They move with the screen faster when you hit right
Oh my god
Stop doing that. Stop doing that. Stop doing that. Stop doing that. Stop doing that. I can't show that
I can't fucking show that. Um, I can't do that. No, I ain't gonna show this
I can't even look at the screen. I'm trying as hard as I can to get to the end
Oh my god, this is so this is impossible
You have no idea how hard this is
These things just started spawning from the right side of the screen and they're hitting me over and over again
I'm gonna die. I can't look at the screen. I'm doing this my eyes closed kind of i'm opening them every five. Okay, we're good
We're back here. We're good. So many things are attacking me at the same time. I can't believe you couldn't see that
My head hurts now
Oh my god, he just comes out of nowhere. He just comes out of nowhere. He just appears on the side of the screen
It starts shooting fire
What the fuck?
No, I wanted to do I want to see the
I ain't doing that flash the screen thing again. No way
Sorry
That was boot cat and after boot cat we're gonna go here
375 is pond pond volley pond pond volley
You got a link for me. I guess i'll give it a look and see what it is important. There's a dead update
Okay. Well, i'll give it a look see it's getting spammed. Um, it's just it's just cat boy germa. So be on the select screen
All right. Well, all right. No more links. No more links links are banned for now on pond volley boy. I like the background animals
pretty cute
Uh, that's this is hello kitty. That's uh
Carol the frog frog that's uh snoopy the dog and then that's little boy. Oh, it's a different language
We're gonna have to do the first option
I want to be uh caro
Yes, the computer is going to be snoopy
Yes
sure
Sure
There's a lot of menu options. Where are we?
Uh, all right. It's my turn
Just I just got killed. It just hurt me
Is that uh, for a second? I thought that was spelling i c u p at the bottom
I thought it was like our spell i c u p i cup. What did I that's what I thought that was
Where's the net? Isn't there usually a net? This isn't it's actually really not that bad. It's like cute but
Functionality wise it's kind of at a zero. Nice jumping hit. Okay. All right. There's a good volley
Oh
It's a baby game. There are no nets
This is actually a hello kitty game. I'm sure it is
One come on
Nope that hit me in the face fucking left. I
He's gonna wait. Why is there another player?
And it was allowed to bounce on his side
It was allowed to bounce on his side
Excuse me
Where's my point? Do I not get points for this?
Come on land and I still land twice on his side. That's unfair
the fairy
Yeah, she just dropped it on she just helped him
Oh, whatever. I don't care. I'm done with this fucking game. This game's stupid
Uh, this is called water pip
Water a water pip game idea by
Wait, that didn't say game develop by that said this is this person's idea. Um, what's that mean though game idea by
Holy shit, are you kidding me?
What a horrible idea what a terrible idea
It's tetris and that pipe shit. What an awful idea
It's a bad idea
Uh, I need to go. Oh my god. I lost wait. There's another
I don't like this
You guys know how much I hate this game. This game has haunted me since I was
This is actually a pretty cool idea if you think about it, but I can't do it. It's too much for me. I can't do it
I have 27 lunar ball go do a coffee break coffee break coffee break. What?
Coffee break coffee break what's going on? You guys want to go on a coffee break coffee break coffee break
It was it was one of the games. It said coffee break. Um
Oh pause button said coffee break. I didn't I didn't even look at the screen because I didn't even care
lunar ball
Up down round left right friction
Sure, it's pool. Um friction is
Oh, come on
I'm just playing but you have to get it in the order
I have to do this in one shot with two shots
How's that possible?
There it is. I don't get to
Resident sleeper. Yeah, I know you with a love pool or you hate pool. There's no in between
There's not like I oh I kind of like pool
No, no, no, you either love this and do this a lot or you hate doing this
And the idea of somebody saying hey, do you want to go like play pool is like god?
Please don't fucking ever ask me. Please. I hope no one ever asks me so I don't have to say yes
Uh, this game i'm done. I just wanted to hang out. Jesus
466 what do we got karaki the the karate kid
Licensed by nintendo of america karate tournament first round chances remaining free. Oh my god. I fucking annihilated this guy
Was how old were they? What's the who am I what?
Holy shit, this is unfair
This is like a 30 year old in like the 12 year old competition. You got to get this guy out of here
semi-final round
Final round of the tournament this person's in a suit
Holy shit, they're strong. Fuck. I lost
Okay, let's go
Oh, yeah
Hey, you want to get fucking original mortal combat strategy to make your friends fucking scream in your face and leave the house
You let you you you you you i'm fucking leaving like i'm not coming back. Wait side scroller
I thought it was just a tournament. How many guys had uh the
Here's all right
There's a few just a few you know ground rules that are played that are put in place when you play video against your friends, right?
Anybody ever played a sports game like a baseball with their friends?
one-on-one
And you have to make the rule you are only allowed to throw strikes because throwing balls
Was impossible to read and you would miss every time if they threw it way far away
No leg sweeps in mortal combat or you automatically lose
Like if you if you do a leg sweep in mortal combat I win the match
If you throw a ball in like some of those old nintendo super nintendo games
That were baseball you automatically lose like because you they're unhittable and you can't even tell that they're coming in as ball
Uh, uh golden eye
Nobody is allowed to play odd job
You gotta put down the video game ground rules
Oh, i'm all of a sudden i'm gonna get trued on that one. Where's that? Why's that lady up in a tree? What?
I'm gonna get trued on that one. You're gonna true that one
Not the other one
i'm dead
Daniel san in okinawa chance. Oh, okay. I got one more life
This one's actually pretty fun
This is probably just the actual game
but
uh
Did they do the movie backwards?
Doesn't the tournament happen like in the end of the movie the popular one to not seem like a mortal combat scrub
um, i'm sorry, but
The leg sweep in mortal combat like one two and three
Swing the hammer. All right, if anybody trains like that, that's what wouldn't happen
I know you like to watch that in movies and tv shows all the extreme training regiment
Well, you have to like dodge like all these things. Look at all. It's a knife. It's gonna kill you
You're dead. You're gonna die
dodge the pendulum
I'm gonna like you're gonna go through like the fucking football training thing and smash into stuff
No, just fucking do push-ups and like kick into the mirror
Please relax
Kick no kick into the mirror not kick the mirror like watch yourself kicking
To see how good the form is
I need to be level one at least come on
You broke the mirror. I didn't say to kick the mirror ice block break. Oh, I gotta go to the hospital
I gotta go to the hospital. Oh, why did I do that?
Why do we do this shit? I could have just fucking done push-ups and kicked in the mirror
Can I take like six to eight weeks for this to heal?
maybe longer
This person throwing I like the bonus games are more fun than the actual game. I just want to play those
Get out of my fucking way, please
bonus game
Damn it
one enemy
Get out of here typhoon strikes
The bird's flying backwards
Okay, I can't
Oh wait, it's supposed to be windy. I'm doing okay. I'm okay. I'm doing all right. I wanted a mini game
Is this guy okay?
He's got full health for that
Mini game in the middle of a typhoon. Yeah. Well, it'll be all right. You guys said coffee break now
I like want to take a coffee break
Get some water or something and pee. What's the last time I peed? Anybody know?
When I when was last time I peed which one he knows
Four hours ago. I don't know
Something like that
Just came back 30 minutes ago. He's still playing this. I haven't been in this for 30 minutes. I've been in this like 12
Mini game right here. It's an open door. Let me in
Yes, okay chopsticks fly catch
Come on get over here
Oh, I didn't get one shit. I got them all I've had enough of the uh, the yeah, okay
That's enough. I had enough the karate kid
All right, let's take a quick break. I'll be right back
Get some water. I'll see you guys in like two or three minutes. How do you do?
You guys ready for some more uh classic video games?
Uh, me too. How what happened one guy germ of fireman. My cousin drew this last christmas and I just found it
That's so cool. Yeah, that's cool. All right, let's get back to it. Hope you enjoyed the artwork head to it
We'll check that one after
Okay, uh, where are we gonna go?
Hmm
I think we'll do a couple more generated ones and then we'll pick some out too
So we'll do five sixty five and then we'll uh, we'll go through and pick some up five six five is destroy
dig dog two
All right, destroy destroy one
uh
This is wrecking crew. This is just wrecking crew, but
Not at all. It's this vines and money it
Yeah, it's even the same it's just I mean it's the music it's the exact same music
Wrecking crew. I mean, how's the drew crew doing nowadays? I try really you can just jump on me like that. Oh, fuck you
That's so stupid
How's that drew crew doing got six months? I I I can climb down they are
whack
All right, I can I know what to do now come over here win go in go in go in go in
Why he's a wrench in the background you see that wait there was what's going on?
What am I what am I missing? Do I have to destroy the top left ones? I blew up the pillar
It's just wrecking crew. Who cares 256. I think we already did this one. We did 250. No, we did not we did not do
Animal contest i'm looking forward to it animal contest stage one
Oh cool. All right. Do we use like a there's a big animal talent show dog
Cool dog and cat and now this one's dog and squirrel
Okay, next up is dog and lion lion beats dog. Okay, I get it
Cat versus rhinoceros rhinoceros beats cat. How do I choose what animals I have though? Um lion versus cat
Lion beats cat lion versus lion. Okay, we gotta go again pig versus
As a tie warthog versus uh lion. No, it's not I win them all but I can't select my animals though elephant versus tiger
Yeah lion versus rhinoceros
Warthog versus cat lion versus tiger
Really? I don't know about that one mouse versus warthog. Yeah
Elephant versus rhinoceros really elephant versus rhinoceros again mouse versus lion
Now that wouldn't happen
I would pull a splinter out of his foot and we'd become best friends and I would win
Mouse versus dog mouse is the worst. Why do I have so many mice lion versus? Oh, here we go
This is gonna be big warthog versus elephant elephant fucking wins dog versus lion. This game is stupid
So you just have to just hit a until but how is somebody gonna win if we can't decide what our deck is?
Yes, I just said deck but how else would you like me to describe this?
It's just rng. He's won so many hands in a row never played war. Yeah. Uh, oh, this is big
Elephant versus warthog. I'll take them all
So the mouse doesn't win so okay, so the mouse is like a two this is gonna come back this way now
It's never gonna end. I'm invested now
Uh, I was invested until we saw all the different animals and now it's just
Unwinnable war because it's gonna go back and forth forever. Somebody said what a truly terrible game
No, you know why I feel bad for all the people in the audience
Especially the people in the front row because those tickets were a thousand dollars you guys us. No, I mean in the game
Yeah, there's no winner. It's not gonna happen. It's just flipping a coin over and over again until you win the 20 times in a row
We'll see you next one, please. That was animal war 331. All right after this one. We're gonna pick some
We'll find what it looks good
331 I
Just I want to play I can remember. Okay, let's do this one first alpha mission octo shield cannon homing paralyzer and nuclear fire thunder
Uh, i'm i'm not playing the game sid three so far so good. This is actually seems pretty elaborate
This doesn't seem bad l e I got e I'm gonna play I can remember. I don't care. I
Can remember copyright night to do fisher price fisher price
I can remember the awning design and little people characters and designs are trademarks of that's a lot of fisher price trademarks for
A fake video game. No, it's just memory. I can remember
Instructions make your selection
Let's see
The object is to uncover and match the hidden fisher price toys the player with the highest score after three rounds wins
Okay, I know how to do that. They are I get it. Okay. Oh my god
Holy shit the amount of instructions two plus one player play alone. They wouldn't use the controller to spell your name
It shocked me. I just got electrocuted level one. All right match the fisher price toys. We have legos and
Furby that's not correct. Furby around back them cool sunglasses and a camera
Toilet paper and Furby. Wait, where's the other Furby? Is it a what is that a bicycle?
All right, toilet paper toilet paper toilet paper toilet paper four nine
Twinkle twinkle little star
Beautiful singing. All right, where's a camera?
Three. All right, three and twelve. Wait, we're gonna make a making a picture
Furby and Furby. Yeah, I told you I could sing
Yeah, everyone's like oh my god. I like this first dream i've ever been here
He said he could sing and then he sung that twinkle twinkle little star and I fucking had chills throughout my entire body
What are we are we building a cash register?
What is this? I don't know what i'm looking at. Is this like a grocery checkout?
You did very well
round two
All right standing mixer and cash register. All right standing mixer is on
Eight uh four six and eight. So what do we got two?
Here we go
Cash register cash register a musical note in the background. Cool. All right step
pretty good we're making a ouija board horsey and
one of those
Push machines that has the balls in it that pretends to be a lawnmower and it goes
There's a little thing in the middle pops the balls up. I love those. It's like my favorite toy. Okay, uh,
I don't know what that is bathtub. There it is. This is it's so loud. No, it's not
Mary had a little lamb and made as I was
I don't know. How do you what is mary had a little lamb what a lyrics
Mary had it's like three words in the whole song
It's mary had a little lamb mary had a little lamb and the sheep's wool was what?
It's a real lawnmower
His fur was soft as snow
That's not it whose fur was soft as snow. You got it wrong, too
That's incorrect
Little lamb it's probably funny when people sing nursery rhymes like that
and
Look when you sing mary had a little lamb or twinkle twinkle little star
It's just so simple and basic in the syllables and the way that you say it is broken up so deliberately like
Mary had a little lamb little lamb little lamb
But when you have a singer that gets a hold of those it's no longer simple anymore. It's like
mary had a little lamb
Little lamb little lamb. It's like you just fucking sing the song normally for god's sake
Mary had a little lamb whose snow was half as large
I'm getting old
Okay, i'm done with this one. This one sucks
You're gonna read the time. I am not high right now. Okay, leave me alone. I love you. Just enjoy
fruit pig
Milk nuts
Nuts and milk nut. What does that say?
Get away from me
I'm dead. We just both died. All right, i'm done with milk nuts. I'm not playing nuts
What's the fruit pig?
Mary had a little lamb little lamb
Holy shit, this one looks awesome catch the fruit. I feel like this is part of the end credits of sing
They would do something like this right like the pig dancing with like retro graphics and stuff. I think that did happen didn't it
What is the song the song at the end of that song? It's like try
Hold on try everything
Try everything right? What does it get? What does it go?
Try everything it's wrong movie about animals. Whatever. It's this
Sorry, two animal movies came out that were 3d and had animals in three dimensions and they had like fun
And they like was the lessons that they learned. Okay, sorry. I got it wrong
How did I lose? I got like what a harvest that was
You're one of the only you're one of seven people that actually watched sing
um
That movie's insanely popular. I have no idea what you're talking about
I need to okay. I need to catch more than 11 of each one. Sure. Let's go
It's gotta stay in the middle
Try everything don't try everything that that song implies to try cigarettes. Don't do that
I'm gonna lose again
Not enough lemons have dropped. There's only been like 10 lemons total in the entire playthrough
Come on. I need lemons only lemons lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon lemon two more lemons lemon lemon lemon
lemon 13 12 11 10
Nine, I got it
I win you're disappointing the banana bros. That's not what you guys are called. Excuse me. I've had enough of fruit pig
Uh, what we got? Let's do uh
How about uh
Let's see. How about chubby? How about dough boy? Hey
Uh, why is dough boy?
Okay
Nope
Okay, dough boy. I don't know what the hell you were doing there, but a dough boy is blowing up like houses
What am I looking at here?
uh
Do I not have a gun? I got a wrench
Who is fighting?
none
tnt
binds
Left free I touched a rock and died
I'm just gonna try to get to the end
views
mines
These trees are in the way. I can't move
Okay, not enough for 12
Submarine and then i'm gonna play toy factory after isn't a submarine under the water
Not floating on top of the water. That's why it's called submarine
Oh like I like this one. This one's good. This one's really good. I really like it
I won. Okay level two where the sky is a different color
That guy that's worth a million points probably
No
Sing this for a billion off the debt
Just because one person says it doesn't mean it's gonna happen
It needs to be at least a 50 to 60 percent
Agreeance with everybody in chat here. You got to get at least 10 people on board
And then those 10 people have to get 20 people on board and those 20 people have to get 100 people on board
Those 100 people
Have to get another 500 people on board
and that's how you get
10 percent of people in this chat that liked the catboy shit to like 70 percent because now I have to dress up this month
I'm gonna beat this game. I'm actually gonna get to the end
This reminds me of a gamer v portable game. I thought it was a question mark. All right, that was fun. Let's pick one try harder
I don't really do you think a flappy is this flappy bird? You think let's try
Okay
Flappy push select button
keyword and music
input keyword
What's keyword mean?
Fun and we'll do music
uh
Definitely be I don't care what the other ones are
This is the bar song
in undertale
Okay, what's how you play? It's kind of freaking me out. I have people just locked up in like a cage up there
And we make them do this shit
um
I don't know how this works
I have to get the ball on the
I have to get that. Okay, I get it. Well, just kill me. I didn't get it right
Okay, so we have to move this out of the way
Can I go over here? Um
All right, it's one of the it's one of those it's one of these dumbass puzzle games
Chippendale 2
All right, let's i'm gonna start picking them. Let's do chip and dale
We'll start chip and dale 2 and then we'll go to chip and dale 1 and then 3
Let's do it like the star wars movies. They take capcom off the top of that. By the way, they just deleted it
They just put a black over it. That says probably capcom presents. That was a capcom font chip and dale rescue rangers
Yeah, now it's legal. Yeah, they they removed who made it on the splash screen. Therefore. It's now completely legal to just sell it
Yeah
Lots of singing today. All right, I want to be I think I have more connection with dale. I'll be honest
Uh-oh
Fat cat has infiltrated the gold facility and took 10 bars of gold
Chip and dale get on the case
He just broke in here and went that way. You must get him and get our gold back
I'm ready. I'll get the gold back
Me and dale will get it
I don't know what she says
I wish I could read this
I thought she thought he's gonna jump right on her head
All right, let's go. We have to introduce every single character that's in the show
Like get jimmy cricket out of here
There he is. There's dale
So dale is uh, if I remember I haven't seen the show or seen them talk in probably 10 years or so
Dale is like a high-pitched goofy, right?
It's goofy but higher pitched. Okay, I can read that one
It's like wow. I
Hold on. I'll try to get it
I think it's like goofy. It's like goofy, but it's high pitched. It's like this. It's kind of like goofy, but kind of like this
It's like that
Oh, I don't know about this dale chip
Let me let me think but it's really it's like the alphan and chipmunks. They pitch it up, right?
Hold on see if I can get it. I do this. Oh, it's me
Shit, we gotta get down there and save that gold if we don't get it
We're gonna be in bad trouble. Is that close goku?
No
Now, let me see what it actually sounds like uh chip and dale. Let me hold on
All right. Okay chip and dale. There's a gadget scene. I just want to hear the voice for a second. I hear it
Why can I not hear this? I should be able to hear this. Why can I not hear it? Oh
See how close I was here he comes. Come on dale talk talk dale. Does dale not talk? Did I get it completely wrong?
I'll admit they do seem to have he doesn't talk
To contribute some
Dale doesn't talk. I met I fucked the whole thing up dale doesn't talk. This is chip
I told you it was pitched up like crazy. Dale doesn't talk at all chip and dale rescue rangers. Hold on. I was close
Yeah, it was close. It was not high pitched enough
All right, let me get back to play this game
Please i'm still on the chair what I mean i'm still on the chair a bit. What are you talking about? Oh a burger
Why these blocks don't exist I tried to jump game is not even fucking fun game is fucking stupid
I feel like those blocks are not supposed to be like the p question mark. All right
I'm gonna drop us on his head
We need a cat puke. All right first cat puke of the year. You got it
You want to I'll give you a first cat puke of the year
How to go down
Get that in super mario, uh old material. All right. Um, how do I can't go down?
That's chip and dale 2
Let's see what chip and dale 1 is
He swallowed food the same time that I did that's a little weird i'll say all right chip and dale 1
Walt disney company produced by capcom forgot to scratch that one out
This actually just is the chip and dale game, isn't it?
Yeah, this is just this is just the game. I've played it before chip and dale 3
All right
Okay
hip ale 3
That's definitely that is definitely not chip and dale
Destroy enemies underground artillery base chip and dale
What are you talking about?
No chip and dale you're gonna go to a foreign fucking land and you're gonna start shooting at stuff
Well, that's too bad dale gotta start firing
Why would they do this
My speakers what happened?
How bad does that sound?
Holy shit the flamethrower
It was that bad. Was it I I just tried to put the pitch up a little
Firing missiles
It was extremely bad
It was the what hold on. How's this? Is this different? Is this better? How's this one?
This is like a little this is this is what I was supposed to be right?
Yeah, so what happened? I think my like my device like fucked up
Chip and dale go to like war with fucking flamethrowers and machine guns
But who are these like other bears? There's like these are bears
Okay, i'm just gonna fire a tank
Do
Maybe you did do you think they just didn't know that like chip and dale was like a kid's cartoon
Oh, yeah chip and dale. Uh, I guess just
Just put that I mean that people know who that is
Got it. Got it. Got it. Nice job dale. He took out that enemy tank
Let me in out of the front door of the base
Dale relax. This is like the big smile on your face. This is this is fucked up. Uh,
Oh stop so waste ammo
So what game is this actually that they put chip and dale on?
Of all the things
Don't waste bullets
I'll be all right. I mean, this is so many things on the screen
The chip and dale rescue rangers. I want to get to the boss. This is just chip and dale 3 dude
What are you talking about?
Play ace combat get out of here
This is a hack of heavy barrel
It's so funny because they have the other real chip and dale games why even put this one on
What's the process to add chip and dale 3 but make it a like kill people game?
grenades
What keys do I need?
It's for you to scream
I do not think whoever made this console was concerned about me streaming this console
If they were
Uh, I think they would be a little more careful
Of all the uh
Copywritten content that is in it. I'm enjoying chip and dale 3 though. It's actually kind of fun
Yeah, I can't look at that floor anymore. It hurts so bad
I can't open those
I don't get killed by my my own grenade, right? All right. All right. Come on. Let's get a boss
I'm gonna laugh my ass off
if it's that
guy with the mustache
Come on other chip and dale characters
other disney characters just just
pumped in please
Who's the bad guy in chip and dale?
I've not seen that show in a long time. Who's the act who's the antagonist?
What's her name?
Fat cat, right? Okay, it better be fat cat
Dale is the antagonist antagonist pov right now. Is that what you're saying?
When there's danger
All right, let's go
Who's the boss fat cat? Come on. No, it's the truck
i'm done
What's next? That's uh, wait, let's stay on the chip chip and dale page. There's something else. I want to see
Hot blood wrestle hot blood story. I think is what we start with first
It's just river city ransom, which is an incredible game for the ns. Is it though?
It is it's just river city ransom
This game used to scare the shit out of me because these ever when they start chasing you with weapons
It's terrifying
I love this game. Uh, best part of the game
Is when you eat the plates
I'm getting deja vu right now. We did this already didn't we didn't I talk about like oh my god when you eat the plate
It's so funny
Did we do this?
I played this on stream, didn't I?
Have I never played river city ransom on stream?
Yeah, you go and you buy food and stuff. It's awesome because you eat the whole plate
It doesn't matter what it is. It could be a coffee. It could be
A sushi or like a hamburger doesn't matter
You eat the entire plate
Oh, sorry, just like spoiled something fun. I thought you already saw it
Boss time. I remember boss comes out of here, right? Nobody comes out of here. I hate that
This game is so good though. Oh shit, please
I need to try new trash can
All right, here comes the boss
He pops out right here
Is it right here? Is it after?
Oh, here we go. Okay. Yeah. All right ready to see the fun part
watch this
okay, so I can't see what i'm buying but
uh
This
I love that so much. It's so cool
Oh, it's the best you eat the whole thing in one bite even if it's a plate
I love it. Where's a coffee?
Or like tea or something. Can anybody somebody can somebody read this? I need a coffee
All right. Well, it's just river city ransom, which i'll play it on your own time
It's like one of the best nes games ever made. All right, so what's that? What's the next one?
It's hot blood wrestle. I mean we have to do that
um
Was there another river city ransom?
I I don't remember this. What is this? This is the
Do you guys ever play dodgeball for the nes?
I love that game so much. I hope it's on here
Uh, it doesn't matter what my name is
It doesn't matter. Let's go
Only in japan. Oh, okay. I see
No, just I wanted to be my name. Let's go end
Yes, okay
I want to be
Because it was this fighter brawler
Uh like scrapper
All right. I'm gonna be scrapper
scrapper
Scrapper four
I have no idea what just happened fight
Okay
I don't even know what character I am
Why did you start off with a lightning move?
How do I do a lightning move?
Get away from my friend
I can't tell who's winning, but I think we're doing okay
Oh my god, somebody's gave a shitload of subs. I just gave 50 community subs
Zap x gave 50 subs
That's a fucking ton
Too many too many subs. What's this weapon?
We sort of pin him
Oh his friend is gone. All right
Yeah, get him. I just killed my own friend. Oops
What do you like he left health?
Holy shit. I just got absolutely fucking destroyed
Okay, let me let me get up
please
Oh, the the spam is what the game actually is. Okay
That's it. It's a huge pog face. That's an omega pog
Two omega pods
This is made by the guilty gear devs. That's interesting
All right, let's get a random one
I'm having fun. I love this. This is like a bunch of fun
It's just a shitty game loot box. You just open up a random number
Some of them are actually real games
Hexapoo man. No hexapoo new
All right, it's poo new
Exo pod presents to start level one
Uh, is this spray paint? What is this?
It's like a water can do I have to shoot the ladybug. This is kind of cool. I like this
All right, i'm gonna be here for a minute
And one level one complete presents to start hexapod
level two
Is this like just centipede but not a centipede I guess. Okay. I cool. I guess. Oh shit. They're getting close
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What am I preventing them from turning into flowers? Why is this cool? This is like bad
This is bug spray
All right, one more level and i'm done last one
I can't
I can't i'm gonna say I hit the escape right off. It's not escape. It's reset actually
It's like
Yeah, every this hurts
You ever play a game or something and it's just you just need to move your body around because blah you just hate
I can't stop
All right. How about um, let's pick a good one
Mortal Kombat 4
Superman
Okay
There's how many I don't even know how many characters is this a match three game or is this the character selector?
I thought it was a match three game. Okay, this is Sonya
What the fuck?
Sonya versus nightwolf
It actually is mortal kombat but not
at all
I'm getting destroyed
Okay. So hold on if this is Sonya, who's the other Sonya?
Because there's like five Sonya's on that character select pick the green sub zero
You know what? The best part about this is this blood
They tried to keep it as authentic as possible with member original blood in mortal kombat
All the parents all the legislation that was like this is bad. There's blood in this video games people. That's just it's disgusting. It's horrible
They kept that
I lost. All right. Hold on reset. I i'm going to pick another character
I want to pick green sub zero and see what it is. Where is
What even is this? This is uh cano
This is sub zero, right?
Is this striker?
It's kratos
Um, where's that's sub zero, right?
Is it don't johnny cage? No, johnny case has sunglasses
We're gonna be red sub zero
Liu kang versus nightwolf
No, it wasn't
I gotta see if I can do the kick
What's the button combination to do the actual kick move?
Just keep him in the corner. Wait, can I do the sweep?
This game doesn't wait. It doesn't have a sweep
Is there wait, we need to see if there's a finisher if there's fatalities in this i'm gonna laugh my ass off
Up down kick
Fuck he's supposed to be in the face. All right. I want to try to get fatality dude
Wait
Is that shao khan?
That's not nightwolf
That hasn't been nightwolf this whole time
I was wondering something fell off about him. That's a lot of blood
Did I won?
Just had to make sure he was extra dead fatality
All right. This is striker red striker is who it's just striker. Okay. Oh wait, is that the bicycle kick?
Forward punch forward forward kick forward forward kick back forward kick back back kick back back kick
Back back kick back back forward kick back back forward kick back back forward kick
Back back forward kick
Just kill me. Whatever
Another 15 subs from scrumpleton scrumpleton. Thanks for the 15th sub. It's a fucking lot of stuff
A lot of subs right now. All right. Uh, I don't know what this is, but i'm gonna pick it
It's just shang seng. All right. No, it's not
Wait, no, it's not
I'm gonna get perfect. I'm literally about to get perfected. I can't even attack him. Wait. Wait, am I striker? What's happening?
I just was pressing buttons strikers
Who am I? I'm not even playing the game. I'm not playing I was not playing I was not playing the game
They were big bits too. Oh, there was a hundred bucks. Holy shit. Okay, uh valemi. Thanks for the hundred dollars
Although I don't read bits anymore
I do not read bit messages anymore. We talked about how I
wanted to move away from that and
Uh, that's kind of the way it is
So for those of you that don't know if you might not have been here for a while
I do I no longer read bits because it got to a point where I took bits away from the end of the stream
I stopped reading them, but I still was reading like a hundred dollar bits and I find that to be a precedent
I do not want to set people to uh, try to
Essentially, I don't want to have it be a thing where people give me money and I i'm gonna like read it out loud
And I don't want to set that precedence for people
To like feel like they have to pay me money like an insane amount of money
To try to get me to like read something
I don't want that precedence to be set at all
So I stopped reading bits of the uh, it used to be 250
And if somebody wants to me to read something, I don't want to be like I have to give this guy a hundred fucking dollars
So he will not read it. So that's something I don't want to have happen. That's why I kind of stopped reading bits completely
Please god read this
You're a wholesome fucker
No, I just don't want people to have to drop that kind of money to have me read something
You know, I'd rather just pick it out of chat and I still if somebody gives community subs
I still read them. I still just read the fact that they were given but there's no message attached to the community subs or anything
It's just sort of um, and people get the subs. It's not just me receiving like a hundred dollars in bits
So that's why the kind of the idea
I just don't ever want it to get to a point where people need to spend an insane amount of money to
And i'll read it he doesn't know how to read no, but I I do know how to read bird week study the game
All right. I need to study the game was there to study. How is this just not playing the game?
How is this different than just playing the what about how is this studying the game
You have to eat the butterflies
Why do I keep running into that bird? I'm so stupid
Speaking of subs, we got 10 from anonymous and then 10 from shock too. So thanks both you guys. Oh my god. I'm fucking
Bird week sucks
Although I wish there was a bird week on that shark week channel discovery
We get shark week. I don't care about shark week. I would want bird week
I'm more interested in birds time for mario 10 super mario super brothers kung fu mari
super mario
kung fu mario
When he just jumps up, he's got like a human body
Like a wait, he has he has a human body, doesn't he?
That's just this mario 2 mario mario 3
He's huge. Yeah, he's like six five
There's a knight
A lot of random assets in this game
You know what's bizarre about this though? I really could I really feel like this could be one of those mario games that came out
25 years ago or just regular nintendo or super nintendo that nobody talks about nobody hears about anymore
What was that one mario and time like luigi stuck in time or something?
If there was a mario yahtzee game like this could be real
Mario is missing. Yeah, that's one right. Yeah, that's one
A giant tiger
Just getting mauled by a tiger in mario
Very hyper realistic tiger. Yeah
I wish there were mario sounds in this
they're like
Losing focus. Yeah, i'm i'm i've my brain has one road
It's a one lane highway
It just goes in a straight line and if you if you tell me I need to take a turn off that highway. Nope
I can't have more lanes. It can't be more than one car on that road. It's just one fucking road
And it's long and it's huge
But that car can go 500 miles per hour
It's a it's a lamborghini on that road
What mario character is this?
It's actually not even that it's actually kind of a fun game
That was it was toad
Krillin
Wait, was it who was that? That person was so small
That person was like three times smaller than me and he's jacked who i've just realized
oh
No, I thought it was a boss
Auto scroller, of course, it'd be an auto scroll in a mario game. Why not?
All right for all the shit talking. It's not even that bad of a designed video game
It's not bad
It's just a little weird
Oh shit. Okay. I'm good
It's scrolling very fast. Yeah, it is
They even put the ah, ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha in the game
I love mario 10. It's my favorite mario
Vertical scroll now. Wow change it up. I'm impressed
I'm impressed
That was a football player or soccer players have to play mario 7
what uh
Boss fight
Oh, it's it's the it's the thing in mario 64 in the in the middle of the pyramid
With the hands you have to stomp on the hands
Come on get him
Got it level two
All right. I'm gonna go till I die one more time and then we'll try the other marios
Oh shit. Okay. I thought it was gonna be a faller
Webcam is on what?
What are you talking about? What happened usb unplugged?
Something just unplugged. I have no idea what that could have been
We didn't look at the cutscene what is this mario is that mario peach
Are you okay? I have no idea what we just watched but whatever mario like a donkey kong jr. Man
Uh, hold on donkey kong jr. Ma
Donkey kong jr. Math
Oh shit. Okay
All right. What do you mean math?
what two plus
eight
plus what's going on eight plus eight plus
Uh four eight plus twelve plus twelve
um
Is four I I I just accidentally did that. I have no idea what just happened what happened eight plus what four times
Five is 20 plus seven is two. I one two
three plus
four times
Nine is plus thirty six
Okay, seven times
Nine is plus I have to do. Oh, I have to get to sixty six. Okay, six times ten
Eight times. Uh, what is it? Sixty five plus one
Six times eleven. Can I do that?
Six times eleven. No eight times six is what what is eight times six sixty six. I don't know six
Times I can't do more than one digit guys eight times eight is eight. So I don't know
Eleven times six. I can't do more than one digit eight times eight
Sixty four. I can't do more than one digit eight times eight plus two
Eight. Oh fucking idiot. Jeremy just gotta get the time symbol eight times eight is sixty four plus two
No, what no stop. I I didn't want to touch that reset it reset reset reset seven times seven
Plus it's weird how you have to touch these things and pick them up chugging the bong water
No, no, I just the game is weird if you if I touch a symbol if I hit x it clear. It's weird
It's a weird it's weird mario 12 push start music type round one the match game
Holy shit. I just destroyed the entire thing chef mario
You guys ever think that if nintendo ever decided to make a theme park think about all the marios
They would be if you go to disneyland or disney world. There's chef mickey. There's rodeo mickey. There's magic mickey magician mickey
There's library and glasses mickey now imagine how many marios they would be you can have a mario for every occasion chef mario
They could be like archaeologist mario. Why would they not do that? I know there is one but
Is it like licensed officially by nintendo? It is yeah
But what it wasn't like it's like two rides and like one little pop-up thing or something
I'm talking about like a disney world for nintendo like an entire theme park. That's nintendo. Look it up
I I feel like that i'm getting lied to
Nintendo land or nintendo park nintendo theme park super nintendo world is an upcoming theme park
So this doesn't exist yet. Okay. Thank you
Uh under construction at universal studios japan. Oh, it's opening like next week
It opens in like less than 30 days plans exist to bring it to universal studios hollywood in california
What the fuck this super nintendo world? It's opening in like three weeks
The theme park is based on the nintendo video game franchise
What at universal studios japan super nintendo world is wedged in the wedged. Mmm
I'd like the whole thing mario kart koopa's challenge an interactive dark ride attraction housed in a recreation
Of bowser's castle based on the mario kart franchise. Oh my god
Yoshi's island a yoshi themed omni mover with yoshis
Power up band key challenges a power up band and the official app are both required to experience the attraction
This is going to be the one up factory for dining hino pio's cafe for a little bit of shopping
Oh my fucking god under
Nintendo i'm nintendo. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, it's all about nintendo coming up nintendo is going to be the next disney
I just want to make that really clear for you guys nintendo next disney next disney fucking world next huge attractions huge everywhere
Not just video games. It's taking a long time for this to come down. They come from wait
What fuck disney and nintendo capitalist scum?
All right, i'm not gonna play mario anymore
scum jerry
George I don't understand why you're still playing mario
No, they're capital of scum over there and and he's he's on he's on like he's got like two
He's got 199 george has 199 moons out of 200. His eyes are fucking dark
He's in the corner. There's like mountain duke hands all over the place. I just need one more moon and then i'm done with this
little bastard forever
Recreate an episode of seinfeld on stream with doctor schmeichsen. Why doctor schmeichsen?
But why does he have to be on that stream? I guess he could be but I mean why
Why I guess why not? Yeah, that's true
All right. This one was fun, but i'm done. Do you guys understand that as we get older?
sitcoms are going to be that they're going to make these jokes because
When our parents were watching these sitcoms from you know, 20 30 years ago
It was exactly what was kind of kind of big and in at the time
Whatever was currently like the thing that people cared about
10 to 20 years later
They try to hit the nostalgia on it too because they know they're going for what there's a certain audience. There's going to be
Sitcom like gamer stuff. It's going to be everywhere. They already do
Oh, no, but it's going to be it's going to be a major part of almost every single tv show
They do now a few do maybe a few mario 14. This looks like a continuation from
Uh
Neither of these are mario. That's not mario either. Is that it's mario's messenger
He transformed that's his transformation
1993 wario
That was he grew a little bit. It just gave they just gave him a mario head
They didn't even try with this one. They did not give a fuck with this one at all
This is superimposed on this whatever game this actually is
What this is so powerful?
What's wrong with my guy?
Why am I what's happening?
Why am I blinking?
Wario made this
Oh
Hey, good luck mario. You'll never beat my wario game
This is a double jump
You'll never beat my wario game goku. I can't just add goku to everything with that voice. It's gonna get old
I can't do that
I can't you I don't want to burn that
That transformation though is unbelievable
At least I mean this is very much the
The turtles are here these ice creams
I okay that you see that that's what it was just all the cracks a little bit there
We saw the crack in the armor
Literal different character can I get under there forgot to put the sprite in on that one man
Get up there
This music could be in a mario game and I would like it wouldn't you
They're gonna serve alcohol at nintendo land
Very very important question
No
I want like a mushroom drink like it's a big mushroom glass and it's like I like some
Kaluha and and uh like mint and strawberry and like syrup and stuff. I I they don't not gonna do that
You can't go one day without drinking
I drink like three times a year
Um interesting interesting how uh when you hold b down for long enough
Mario's mustache goes on the back of his head
Fucking hard
All that for that don't die from this
No keys what?
Shit, did I miss a key? What'd I miss one?
Did I did I jump over it? Did I miss it completely?
I was busy. Oh, I was busy. I was busy
God damn it. I was busy
I was busy
I was busy and I didn't see it
What were you doing? I I was busy. I was looking at something
It's two different songs playing at the same time. It's freaking me out. This game's awesome though. I like this game
Just the actual video game whatever they're
Copyrighted stealing. Oh jesus. I'm in trouble
Uh, okay, he comes back up to get his I haven't heard him. I can't hurt him. I guess I can
I can't even
I'll watch it. He's shooting the fireballs. You can't how he's supposed to dodge those. You cannot get away from that
Why are these not hurting him to be standing in this corner? I can't hurt him
Jump over them. Yeah, but like why can't I hurt him? God damn it. Just jump over him. Just jump over him
Just just jump over those jeremy jump them
Jump those wall jump. Wait, I wait I can hold this in the air
I have no idea what's going on, dude
This might look simple to you, but it's requiring like seven million math problems for me to not get hit by this stuff
Remember the controller hitting left doesn't work like 45 percent of the time
I don't care. It's her it's terrible being the controller blame the controller. Not the game, right?
Yeah, I will blame the controller when I hit left
Case closed pro wrestling time player ready
Well, he just shot me with a gun. Okay
Am I dead
I'm just running away from this guy
Wait, we're both are we both gonna get disqualified. What's the count?
Ah
um
Okay, I thought the referee just laid down
No shit, come on
Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up. Get up
Okay, I lose whatever
Ow
Ow, ow, ow, ow enough
um
What should we do next? How about?
Is somebody to choose from still?
Astonax wait a minute
I've played this game a ton
I'm getting an insane wave of memories
Wait, i've played this
Astonax am I insane? This is real, right?
Astonax game
Yeah
For nes
The name is from greek mythology
I think
I'm a freshman
here
at green view high
I don't understand
What the dream means?
And who is that girl?
The other day
I was walking to school. Can we speak the teleprompter up a little bit, please? I sound like an idiot
Astonax
Where am I
This is Remilia. My name is cutie
I brought you
to this world
What?
A talking butterfly very clearly that's like a person with wings on
Listen carefully
To what i'm going to tell you
the girl who appears
in your dreams
is princess
Rosebud of Remilia
She is being held captive
by the evil wizard
Blackhorn
Astonax
Please save our princess. This is just that this is just Astonax
But i'm only six
I thought I was gonna say only six feet tall like what is how what does that matter? That's like good. What are you talking about?
Astonax
You are the warrior
chosen by this world
You possess the wonderful miracle power within you
And also
Only the princess
Can send you back
To your world
I can't do it myself
Oh my fucking god
Take this magic
axe
bash
This is
The only way you can get back
to your world
Thank you
Blackhorn has many monsters at his command
You have no choice
I'm sorry
Okay, then
Lead the way
Astonax let's go
Astonax
This does not look anything like the person that was just talking
Um, it's pretty sick gameplay. I like it. Yeah, it lost me. It lost me really quickly. Let's generate one 314
Oh, yeah, we've seen utmost warfare already. We've already done one 205. Let's see
205 is air alert
You watched more cutscene than played. Yeah
Just another one. It's just one of these
so many of these
That was a planet that was just coming in why was I glitching
This is quite the invasion this is a full-on invasion mario 7 waiting room
I think this is it. This is all there is to it. That's yeah, that's all there is to that one
How about uh, what about double dragon? Let's see if it's just actually double dragon
I think so
um
No, press start. Okay mode one. Yeah, it's just double dragon. I think mario's giant. I whatever i'm not reading that one
Uh valemi, thanks for the 20 subs valemi 20 community subs from valemi
Thank you. Hey, congrats to those that got the stuff
game sucks, it's just double dragon but
Kind of weird looking
Yeah, we've seen it already. We don't want real games. We need
Weird bootleg strange games. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait final mission. What do you think batman? Is the game? All right?
Oh, okay
She just looks like the cardboard cutout that's at every
Spencer gifts
There he goes
That's city the background. Let's go batman. He's why is he purple?
Is batman purple
No, wait. No, there isn't there a vert. No, the original batman was kind of purple, wasn't he?
They talked about in the 60s with adam west. He was purple right purple and black and gray
Yeah, he was
They just didn't add the other two colors. That's fine. Does that say meat eat?
eat
re
Eat re whatever
You want to bet?
um
I don't why do I think that batman's like purple? No, he had like purple underwear
Yeah, pat batman had purple underwear. He's like a purple speedo, right?
No robin had a red speedo on
um
He had purple somewhere
He's like legs his boots or something purple boots
No batgirl is purple. Is it?
Wait a minute. Hold on. Are you freaking me out?
batman
60s
And I swear to god he had like purple something
Um
No, he's not purple. Well, yeah, he kind of is. Yeah. Yeah, it is it is it's yeah it is he's purple
Yeah, he is
Why is everybody gaslighting me?
He's purple like he's completely purple
There ain't nothing here but purple
He's going completely fucking purple
Except for the yellow in the middle
And why is he on an elmo phone?
That's blue. That is
That's not blue. That's purple
That's purple. How is that blue? You think that's blue? Yeah, you say get your screen check
Some of you guys need to get your eyeglasses examined
That's purple
That's lilac. Okay. All right. I've heard about enough
I've heard just about enough
It's lilac
Lilac
No, it's not purple. It's fuchsia
No, it's lavender jeremy
Take the colorblind test already did and I got 100 on it
I got one of the highest scores you could possibly possibly get on that test. It was like a 150
100 percent colorblind. No
Silent
Hi, who's the where's the boss? I want to see the first boss penguin, right?
Don't die. Oh, you're actually you guys are listening. Well, very very you guys are very very good listeners right now
That guy was just smoking a cigarette. I'm not even sure he's a bad guy
But whatever you're in batman's way get out of the way
If you see batman fucking sprinting down
You get out of his way
um, I don't know who this is but
They got me
I think this is just a uh, extra bad guy. This is not like a batman character
All right
It's so it's fucking so hard
fake fan
Am I a fake fan? We're not knowing who that is star force
astro robo sasa
Yes
sasa
Live-action batman television series of the 1960s starring adam west featured a blue purple and gray version of the batsuit with the cape shortened
Thank you
Uh, what is it? What am I doing?
Um, this doesn't reach
I did it. This is kind of cool. Look at that cow down there. Look at how cool that cow is
Oh my god. I love this one
Look at he's like hello. It should be mr. Cow
I love that cow
I get the cow too. It was a detective comics
Yeah, he's purple. It's purple dude. Oops
This is the same level. Did I not do it stage four? I didn't they get all these e's
Destroy the balls leading up to the knock the tower down
And I just fly in there
Uh, I don't know. What do I do? I don't know what that does
Give me like powers
destroy the wall
powers
Oh wait, I can what's the point of the balls then if I can just break this? What was the point of the walls?
the store p
Oh
Come on dude, why of all the things do I have to think about that one?
Nice, ah, yeah, that was that was good. That was very good. You get that one. Absolutely
That was that was very good. All right, this one's cute, but I think i'm done
What the hell?
Yeah, that was fun. Let's get a random one
Two three four. We're going four. Oh nine
spider-man one
Okay stage one three lives spider-man. Oh, what did I think I lost? Okay, I can
All right. I get it. I get it. So you got to climb around. This is definitely, uh green goblins
Design work. I know it
The song is awful for a spider-man. This should be way more upbeat
This does not feel like spider-man music at all. And when does this end the enemy has full health?
What enemy am I supposed to be shooting at enemy full health? Well, I want to see spider-man too for oh, sorry
Different pose and this time we're climbing on the wall. Okay
That's doll. That's dr. Octopus
Okay, I have homing missiles
If he touches me, I
Okay, just spam a and you'll win. All right, beat him stage two dr. Octopus again
I guess
Oh my god, this is painful stop doing that
Stage three dr. Octopus again
Are we ever going to see another character?
There's a glitch right if you get to the top left part of his shoulder you can spam it
It's the only place you can do that. Let's get right to the top left shoulder area here
If he would stop doing that
Stage five dr. Octopus
I don't think there's anything else. I don't think this one has anything else in it
Every time he touches you it resets the whole game. Holy shit. This is awful
I'm gonna after stage 10 if it's still dr. Octopus. I'm leaving
Nope. All right stage eight
He has so much health as this goes forward. Oh my god
Okay stage 10. This is gonna be it. It's gotta be the last one
It looks like a stink bug. He yeah, he does
It's that one spot on the shoulder though. All right, what if I'm still here just i'm gonna turn the volume down
I need to see what happens after 15
Let me get i'll use 20 once I get to 20. That's it. Fuck. He's he's shooting more
It's 20 i'll get 20 when it gets 20 20 is over
25 well
Hold on. Oh, by the way, I don't have to tap it. Hold on if I hold it. It does it too. Wait a minute
And if I hit the turbo button what happens? No, it's faster without turbo
19 last one. Okay, let's say is it is it last one? I promise you lost a thousand years. I'm sorry
I wanted to see what was gonna happen. I want to see if we got another boss or is it do 420?
All right, fine. I'll do the funny meme number wonder ball. A lot of them have the same format here. Okay wonder ball
I think i'm winning
Absolutely. No idea what's going on. I'm not controlling anything. I'm not shooting that i'm not firing it. It's just doing it on its own
This is randomly ai generated music. I think this is just a little toy. That's fun to look at for kids or something
I don't have control of this. I don't have control of this
I can pause the game
How's your sunday going? It's doing pretty good. Hope your sunday's going well. I can't this is not a video game
I can't play it
Sing wonder wall
I don't know the lyrics. I just know how it goes
Hmm chubby cherub. Yeah, let's do chubby chubby cherub
uh, um
This must be cupid. I don't get it
What's about the dogs? Holy shit. The baby got stuck on the power line. Oh, no
No, no, no
dead fox gorilla war gobble bobble. This is bubble bubble tube
Now it is beginning of a fantastic story. Let's make a journey to the cave of monsters. Good luck
Oh, hell. Yeah
It's just bubble bubble too
Oh, man, I cannot contain
The pogs that are coming out of my mouth right now
See in six hours
When i'm not streaming
I'm probably lying down in my bed
I in fact probably an hour from now. I probably will be doing that as well
So i'm not gonna see you though. The stream will have been completely ended by then
For at least a few hours at least
Come on, I gotta get up there
Come on, get up there
Get up there
Oh wait, do a bed stream to erase the debt
I'm not gonna do a bed stream
How can you not like it? It's got candies
What would I do though? Like what do you want me to do for that?
Just lie down in bed
Sleep, I don't think you can do that. I maybe wait. Yeah, I can do that if I don't like give a notification out, right?
And you're not allowed to sleep on twitch
With uh as long as you don't
Something like that
You would play on the ipad until you get really sleepy
Oh, I love the thing. Yeah the slide best part
You watch somebody sleep on twitch. Yeah, but this is that that's like
Five and a half years ago or something before like all these rules were in place
Yeah, I told you that this dude was sleeping on stream and somebody was spamming this wicked loud piano
In his ears and he wasn't awake. It was like the most ridiculous thing i've ever seen in my life
He had headphones on
and somebody was just spamming this loud smashing on the piano music just like
It was so loud
And this dude's just sitting there with his eyes closed sleeping with the headphones on
I remember just sitting there laughing my ass off going like what is what is going on?
Like what happened?
How did we get here?
That really is fireman in there. He's a jump. Come on jump
There we go. No
No
Can I get can I kill? Oh my fucking god actually getting annoyed by this getting actually kind of annoyed by this one
How do I kill him? How do I get him? You don't well, how do I clear the stage?
Jump into that
other side with the bubbles
Yeah, I think I can I get them to
He sucks. Oh the controller sucks
I know I an inefficient guy blames his tools
No, you blame the shitty controller
This is how I control the avatar
If you were using a toothbrush to hammer a nail in you would blame the tool
I don't understand what's going on jump from below
Just press left six times and I didn't move left
All right, it's time. It's time. It's time. It's time to get very angry
Can I go up this way?
I'm done. I'm gonna smash something. No, I don't know. They just the the left on this I I whatever
I could say that like it doesn't matter doesn't matter. We're playing wampum now
Wampum dreamer can't beat bubble bobble and thinks batman is purple
He is he is purple
This one's kind of I like this one though
Can I jump on them?
Lilac lilac lilac lilac
I just love computer games
Anybody else love computers? What's your guys favorite color of blue?
Mine's teal
Aqua
Aqua's my favorite
I don't think that's the actual color. I think that's me saying that I like aqua
Royal. Yeah, royal blue is good, too
Good call
Electric blue. What is electric blue?
and health
batman blue
All right fire test ice ritual secret cliff water test
Magic forest or sacred woods. I think we have to go to secret cliff. This is just a good nintendo game
No frills or anything
No weird shit
fine good
Um, I don't know why these up. Oh these tnts. That's got full health somehow how it's buzzwords
Can I hit somebody going up?
Move left. Oh
Making me very upset that this left doesn't work when I want it move
Oh boy
Here comes the goblin define left
Okay, I will define left starboard there you go
bow mast starboard port what's what's right
Starboard is right. What's left?
What actually is left?
port port side starboard side
Oh my god
I still love seeing the uh dev in chat
stuff
People are still just writing it
It's like dude. He's not here man. He's not here
They're not here. They're not here
Fuck this thing sucks
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm gonna get it. This feels like the rage part of a mario maker level
Epic rage. All right, we're gonna go through we're gonna do
Oh shit. Hold on
Against the enemy ball
Oh, no, it's a guy
83 what's 83?
arab arabian l
Uh, it's just to collect the word the letters. All right. I'll just dump them over starboard side. You guys know what I mean?
Come on
What what was so wrong with that? It was a callback to 10 minutes ago
bonus horse
This guy's kind of fun. You get a bonus if you spell the word right. Oh, okay
This one hurts my head
um
Okay, that was fun. All right. What do you guys think chat's choice? What do you think? Let's go
I know you guys have seen some that you want me to play pikachu pikachu pikachu pikachu pikachu
Where's pikachu? I see rocking cats though. I see banana prints. Let me override you real quick
Dice is died top
And I didn't would um, is this german chose with a height?
war
And it's it's banana klar
Yeah, and die banana in sin act good quack quack
Oh nine
It is poverty college. Oh, no
banana prince
Oh nine
How do what do I do? The screen is shaking this hurts to look at
So they took the big banana
I'm getting a shitload of artifacting
But now here come the banana bros
somebody speaks german and it was just
In a tab somewhere and they're just like why is he speaking fucking german?
vending machine
Hmm. Welcome
Nim it's den
I'll take the bananas, please. It's been weirder. Da mit allen bananen
you asked
niched
a good good new good range
You asked you should get new range
You have to I I don't have enough money. I think this is that says
Okay ish wages
Why is this in german though of all things?
Code wart how do I get up there? That's such a hard jump
Excuse me
You can't this impossible jump. This doesn't work switch characters
Uh select start
select
up down
The sign says b
b
b taste
What does that sign say down and b?
Yep. Holy shit. All right. Nice
Ja ja ich hab die stuf
geshaft
spryron the waft the casino
Wait a minute. What do you got over here?
What do you have over here in this game?
Welcoming i'm banana man casino in spiel in casino cost is 20 wrench. Is that okay?
Yeah, can't do direll redlin. Yeah
I'm gonna wear an was with the stew
uh
mere
Here, huh? Nishwar?
uh
six
two one
Shad tut me lead
Which do ish notch in limelwerschwin?
um
You don't go to a casino if you don't know how to speak the language
Like I have a 19 here
Uh, do you want to hit?
Yeah
I oh I okay. I don't know what you're saying, but sure
You're asking who didn't wrench. I lost
Oh my god, I gotta get more rings for the casino
I don't care about anything else. Let's not those rings get up here. Definitely hidden rings over here
Yep
Shit, I want those
You killed pickle rick
Stop, okay. Okay. I got 56 rings time to go to the casino. Oh no
prince
dubest
ver let's each
He'll dust veil gluck
who's
Ray
I got a kiss or something. I don't know
Oh my god, damn it
ring
Welcome, uh, do I want stein axed coney gaxed stern axed or maggie? Uh, how about maggie?
60 rings for maggie, uh nine
only gaxed
Only gaxed this war does much 50 rings
Yeah
villain dine
It come wider
Did I just spend 50 bucks not gambling?
Are you kidding me? What did I what did anyone translate? What does that mean?
Become wider. I don't think that's what that means. I crawl
Oh shit. Nice
That's right. It's have decided to stuff it. Fuck. I can't go to the casino. All right waf
No, I don't want I don't want to stay next
No, no, no, I don't want any waf. I don't want any waf
oh, yeah
Wafen
Wafen geshaft wafen geshaft
What is wafen geshaft?
Is a weapon store?
Wafen geshaft
weapons
Weapons store. Oh, okay. Cool. This is fun. I like like learning german with you guys. This is cool
All right. I like this one. I'm gonna play this a little bit
I don't know why it's in german, but i'm not gonna ask that question. I'm just gonna play
This dude's a true banana bro. Thanks, man
It's in here. Oh, what's the guy do? I feel like he has powers
of some sort
Oh, fuck. Come on. Come on. Come on. Whatever
I think I have infinite continues, but I want at least I want 100 rings
No, he's a corn comrade
You guys have been ridiculous. How do I get?
Oh no
All right. I don't care if there's a casino. This is my last try
And i'm playing a different one
Wait, I want these. Oh shit. I just did it get in there
Whatever glitched out pixels are getting to me. Yeah me too
Now is that because this thing's like overheating or what burbles awful rushing? Yeah
When do you say this one is it's a car one. Okay. All right
Well, it sure is awful. It's very bad. It's very awful
Play pikachu. All right. Yeah, what number was it? Where's pikachu mystery friday the 13th. Oh, hold on
Circus charlie
Where's pikachu just find it bugs war mighty final fight our banger
I didn't even play rocking cats yet. I'm playing rocking cats. Which channel will you choose?
Uh, I mean five looks really kind of like it's been pressed many times
You cannot choose this channel yet. I don't have that subscription. Okay, how about one downtown street? Is this channel? Okay?
Uh, no, how about two sky ace? Is this channel? Okay? No playland. Is this channel? Okay?
Yeah
What is this channel? Is this somebody just being just kidnapped on every channel? Okay, we're gonna do chimp sky ace
Oh boy. All right. I have a I have like a comedy glove. I like it. Let's go
This looks like um
This looks like michael meyers's cat in the hat actual game. How do I get up there?
Oh, you do a super jump cool
What the fuck just happened? I just did a swing
I hate this
I genuinely don't like this at all. I genuinely hate this
I'm gonna just try to get to the end as fast I can
I don't like this
I hate it
nice
Nice. All right. Is this the end this game was made for you, dude
I mean it was is it time to fly on is a shooting level side scroller
Well, I can't fly the plane though. All I can do is jump
You fly and put a load of the ground
He's direct hitting the plane. Isn't that bad?
What the fuck is that?
All right, pikachu
Injugate in one two three
Spider-man
Just spider-man with no number peek-a-choo. Let me look for it. Pikachu binary land. Ah
Luke lu land, uh
Hyper olympics
I don't care. I'm playing hyper olympics
Okay, who am I?
100 meter dash. How do you run? Okay, it's b. I cheated
I don't know which character I am. I don't know what character I am long jump. All right, can everybody just
Settle down and I didn't go very far, but I went real high
That has to account for something that breaks a vertical record. It's not bad. The angle's too high. Is that it hurdles? Oh fuck
My fucking hand hurts
I can't do it anymore. I can't my hand hurts. I have to play one player b. What's that mean?
Am I up top now? I wonder if it's two can I do a and b hit the turbo button?
Oh, that's right. I could just hit the I could just hold turbo
That's so unfair
See you later everyone. Hey, I qualified this time. I came back with
He's doing drugs long jump. Sure. Fuck. I'm going too fast slow down a little just a little
It's so hard to get that when you're going this fast
I'm gonna not qualify because i'm too like roided out. Oh my god. Come on, man
Really disqualified go home you lose. Hold on. I'll get it. Pikachu is 582. All right, i'll get it after this
I promise play b wings. Okay. I broke all the records. They don't even have a indicator back here
I just wanted to show you how high I could go
Better than the first one
Nope long jump completed. What's the next one hurdles? Right? Okay, I might fuck this up because i'm gonna do it
I'm gonna go too fast. Even still he's right behind me. Stop letting lizard people play in the olympics
Javelin throw. Okay, it's still going up. Stop letting lizard people play in the olympics
All right. I'm gonna do this one for real didn't even use turbo for that one. I still got it
Oh, that's gonna be good. That's a line drive, dude
Over 100. Yep. I win. Wait, why was I just running?
Wait, why am I i'm not in first place? How another 100 meter dash? Let's get the world record
Oh, I got the world record like 10 minutes ago. Okay. Oh, this is all they have
All right
Oh, he looks like he went he went down into the clubhouse and uh, we didn't see him for about 25 minutes
He came back. He beat his previous record
oh
Damn it. Oh, well, okay. Who cares? All right, pikachu
582 you say
pikachu
It's uh, it it's like tetris or something
It's fucking tetris this one it's just tetris with pikachu in the shower. What's the sound?
Not bad
Not bad guys. This is gonna be huge
It's gonna be unbelievable
Oh, it's gonna be unbelievable
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? Oh my god, it's gonna be unbelievable
Um, and then we're gonna get an L and drop it in there. Watch this shit
This is oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god
Oh my god, relax
Children play this game
Oh shit, I blew it. Oh
My god
We're doing we're doing that tomorrow
People had did question marks. Okay, that's fine. If you have no idea what i'm talking about. That's fine. We'll see you tomorrow
Yeah, the burger king whopper eat video
Remember well, even if you don't remember it doesn't matter. That's what we're doing tomorrow
Every time I take a bite. I have to do the thing. You'll just you'll see you'll see you'll see i'll see you tomorrow
I don't know what to do with this
Shit, I need a long stick
I need a long stick, please
There it is
finally
Took you long enough
idiot
All right, so is pikachu playing or is pikachu watching me play? Which one is it? Oh
I'm so upset about that. I'm moving. All right. So now what we're doing now
I have a question for you guys. Do you guys want to see this again?
I feel like there's still like two or three hundred we have not seen you guys want to see this again
I think we could tap back into this for fun. There's uh, there's a lot more to do
Maybe like later this week or next week or something. I gotta play Popeye. Is it just donkey kong?
Maybe do it after the burger tomorrow. Um
Okay, he just throws bottles at you. Um, mate, we'll see I can't punch
Uh the guy I can't punch him in the face. What's the point of being Popeye if I can't punch guys in faces
I need spinach. I do oh if you collect the hearts and it's over here. It's just pac-man
Get back here
You didn't look up the stairs
He didn't know where to go
How holy shit? I just got the ultimate bonus. I can't I didn't know what I was doing
What happened? I've been having fun with this though. It's like this. It's just like a it's just a
Jakutery board. I love it. All right, let's do a few more. What do you think? Where should we go?
We gotta do spy versus spy. We looked at that five hours ago mario 7
Didn't I already do mario 7?
Training bag anyone the others bag papers key passport and money
Um, um, no, I don't know what's going on. I think I thought that was funny. I guess
I'm gonna put a bomb in the dresser. That was funny that I moved to the I put a bomb in the painting
When he goes to the painting now, he's gonna get exploded. I have the bombs
I really don't have really any idea what's going on. But that was fun. Hmm. How about
Scoot squoon
How about just mario? I mean
This looks like mario
It is mario. Yeah. Okay, so this is
Just mar but it's not though. It's off
The colors are wrong
What's the it's gonna be a big kicker here somewhere at the end. Oh, it's just mario
Sound is a little weird, too
It's got a purple background. It's got a nice batman background
Yeah, it looks really like it looks really frosty too
DMCA
Okay. What's the okay? Hold on a minute here
What's the legality here?
We're getting lawyers in chat
So I bought this this was a a console that I purchased and i'm streaming it on twitch
I technically bought this and it was sold to me
And i'm playing this console that I purchased on stream, but it's super mario brothers, which is definitely not licensed by nintendo
I have no idea
What's the legality?
This is the fbi you're in deep shit
It's just mario brothers one. It's just super mario brothers
You're gonna get the electric chair
Yeah, i'm sitting in the electric chair of like god, dude
No, i'm sorry. I'm sorry everybody
I didn't mean to stream super mario brothers on the bootleg family computer system
Tell everybody tell my mother I love them
Phone rings the governor calls
Ended up letting me go because the governor's favorite video is the spi video
Thank god, I was a big fan of that spi nest video give me laugh
You get to live as long as you make the spi nest free
After auto's big adventure three on the main channel
He slams the fucking phone down
And I had look I look over at the executioner and I go flip the fucking thing and he goes
Stop playing bad mario
It does look so bad
I'm looking at the preview because mine's what I get through the feed is a little different. It looks really bad for you guys
Okay, b wings. All right b wings b wings. I'm just playing mario brothers
Yeah, let's do something about b wings. You got a number turn off the upscaler. Um, that's that's definitely not the problem
It just looks horrible mario 7 mario. All right, mario 7. Let's mario 7. Give me we got a number for mario 7
What about mario brothers? Uh, we all know this one mario 7 is 66. It's a dead fox. He's naked
Um, okay
Okay, this is uh, is this still america? Am I actually naked?
No, why are they disintegrating?
They're crumbling
They just disappear. What am I shooting them with? I'm trying to get better aerodynamics by jumping like this
I saw this on some fucking youtube video
Oh, i'm done with this one. Where is mario 7 air wolf power blade?
bruce lee 2, uh
Three hundred something three thirty three. No, that's I can remember
3 3 4 no
Aladdin 3 this mickey mouse mystery friday the 13th. There's so many more to play. I have to play this again
3 3 4 3 3 4
Hakuto no ken. Oh I can move in what world does any video game go right to left?
What's that? What's that? What's that little guy?
The the building behind me looks like when you take an nes cartridge that's dirty
Put it in not far enough into the nes
And then turn any game on looks horrible
It's a good boomer jok. Okay. Thanks, man. Appreciate it. I got a lot of those
Okay, why did you want me to play this this game sucks?
That guy even come from he's a falling out of the sky now. Okay
This game gets good. Okay
I'll take your word for it here
And what should I eat tonight? What do you guys think?
Is this like a pizza like a cookie like I like to call that a cookie. So, you know
Oh meet a whopper tomorrow
real cheese now
How about pasta?
Hmm, how does this game get good? I feel like it's the same things going on here
What is there to get good here?
And how would you even know that you've never played this? I guarantee you've never played this nobody here's played this game. I guarantee it
How would you know?
All right, it got good. It got better
Got good. All right. Let me find mario 7 wherever that is
Mario 7 mario said i'm going i'm going for it. I'm not going to play anything else
Besides mario 7. I promise
10 yard fight though. Come on mario brothers
muscle
pac-man
Fruit pig. I remember fruit pig. It was awesome
mag max root 16
Tetris volleyball
I don't know
Three where's it 388 that's not it lima shindian. No, it's not it 278
Reads that's not it either. That's not but there is no mario 7 you guys are liars. There's no mario 7
Now i'm gonna punish you with fruit gift. I already lost some I don't know how I did but I already lost
um, oh
I understand. Okay. Remember you only read a thousand dollar donations now. Oh, that would be horrible if that were true
No, the strawberry
Apple no, I keep going over them. I'm done. All right, let's do one more
What's the last one? We'll i'm gonna play this again. Don't worry. We'll see eventually we'll see all
At least maybe two-thirds of these
What's the last one?
Mystery. Oh, no, no, I won't do friday the 13th. You're right. We're doing two more
And then i'm just gonna spam it and then close my eyes and then open them and press a
All right, where's uh friday the 13th?
Yeah, it was way earlier than this one. No, that's mario 331
Alpha mission. No, no, no, no, no, no, it's alphabetical. Uh, it's not it's alphabetical for the first two pages
And then it does not this does not look alphabetical to me friday the 13th
Uh, I believe this is just the game. Yeah, it is
Crystal lake camp. I actually remember this game being really good
Use the torch to light the fireplace. Yeah, it's like maniac mansion, right? This game's awesome. Actually
Torch children fifth room and children. Yeah. Wait, can't jason be in these rooms and stuff
It's scary. This is a scary game
Purple jason, he might be I have the torch
There it is
Like the torch
All right. I lit it, right?
Now what tr?
change
change change
Why can't I change?
He's in the chimney
This is an insanely awful fucking game. What are you talking about? I just remember jason
How do I get out of here?
Change i'm pressing change and won't let me change
Start select
What happened at the door?
They weren't zombies
I ain't getting lost in another one of these i'm gonna just go find jason and throw cds at his head
Where is he this game was developed by atlas?
Is that jason right there?
Oh, I just got a knife. I thought he was hiding in the bush in the tree with a knife in his hand
So many hours wasted on this damn game
Where the hell is this?
Oh, I found the children
I saved the children
How do I save them cure take?
How do I take them? How do I help them?
I don't know. Good luck
That got scarier for no reason
I just want to find jason. I don't even I just want to see him
Purple jason, he better be i'm gonna be really pissed off 388 is a casino game. Let's check it out
Like this, okay. I lit it. So now what what the hell?
I did what you told me to do. I played your dumb little game now
What do I do now?
Keep going. Keep going. Keep going. You're stuck. I feel like I am
He's fucking purple
He's purple. I thought you guys were kidding. He actually is purple. All right, one more one more one
What was it? What was it? There's gonna be something
388 okay, fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Free it. Leave my shin dian. Oh boy
It's like you're wrecking mario together
What the hell is going on what I land on you win I didn't bet anything I win zero
What wait, hold on going all in on cherry. What's even what's going on with his teeth?
All right, all in on cherry. Let's go. All right, let's go cherry. I I did it
I just how much I just win. Well, this is not worth anything. That's just times two. What?
We're gonna go on on bar all in on bar. I I got an ace
Okay, what is
Let's see the seven. I don't even know which one of these is gonna these are all tied to a different button on the controller
I want to find bar. There is no bar. We're just gonna have to go all in on seven. Oh apples. Fuck
So I understand that you get money for doing this but this is just it
There's nothing to do with this there's no goal or anything. It's just something to strive for it sucks. All right 453
All right, we'll end on 453. What's 453?
We're doing we do this already. We already did this one. No, all right
I'm gonna pick a random one. Here we go
Close my eyes and spam in the button two three four five six seven eight nine ten one two
Three four and then i'm gonna go down one two three four five six
secret castle
Milan's secret castle this looks pretty good
Uh, I can go in the door sort of my eye
These windows are in really really weird places
This game is very cryptic
Hepe hands
I jump on these guys
No, how do I get up there? This game is confusing as shit. Good luck. Okay
Maybe I need an extra power. I didn't play b-wings. You're right
Two dollars can't leave
Um, so I have to get up there somehow
That has to be away from me get up here. Is this a spring? Looks like it could be a spring
I don't understand
I guess I did higher jump. I kind of wanted to die
um, all right, that was
A game that I don't want to ever play again. I would play the final game on the list. That's true
Okay, the final game is baseball new and then b-wings and then i'll see you guys tomorrow
I just pitched the ball back to him. I don't know if it's me at the plate who's
Is me hitting? No, i'm pitching. Okay, so get it back to the pitcher. Why does he put on pajamas? Get it
Why would the pitcher go field that ball?
Did they they they wait till the ball is done before they start to field the ball?
I will never get an out. I cannot move
I all right b-wings. You had a number for b-wings, but let me see what bruce lee too is first 1991 re
Levels like normal
I am you get an instant message. It's me. There's a crime afoot
You just stop those bad guys in the street sure thing a lot of health. There's no jump
All right, and this is only walk. I love this already. It's very fluid. Oh shit. Okay, we're good
Let's guys do a dash
Remember that I guess a knife
But this guy's gonna stand up
No, okay
Uh that guy is because he's purple
I wonder who's gonna stand up
Not the guy that was gray, of course
Yeah, I love this game boss battle. All right, let's go with the lead singer from kiss
That was very very brutal. Okay. Well, i'm gonna try that one more time
fair
Yeah, they all run away where the big guy shows up. All right, let's go. I'll take it. I did it
No, it's not that's not richard simmons. No another text message
You can do a full playthrough. No way
I'm about to turn it off in five seconds
There is a jump I was wasn't pressing it
I can't kick him in the air
Play milk nuts already. I did
Time's up time's up. All right b wings. I need a number and then we're gonna end this room
B wings b wings b wings. What was it? What number two? What was it? I'm wearing the 500s
Okay b wings
golf
ghost
four-player mahjong
mario
Othello pac-man
B wings there it is. Okay
select cannon fire dina jump
hammer
anti-side van
I'm gonna do uh, i'm gonna go with dina. Oh shit. This looks fun. Ooh
Whoa
Where'd they go?
Where my sides go?
I lost my sides
Is the plane falling down?
Oh my god my sides
It looks like it's probably a dodge. It's pretty fun. This is a real game. I would assume right?
Kind of has to be
Oh my god, dude my sides
This is the most powerful weapon in the whole game
Um, it seems pretty good
Nice ship. Hey, thanks. Ooh, this is cool
No, no, no, no get back get back get back. I just let I let it go and there's probably a boss right here
uh
shit
All right. I want to do wide
Yeah, I like wide
This is a fun shooter though. I got two there was a lot going on there. Uh, what about hammer? It's hammer
A little shield. That's cool
Kind of annoying sound but it's all right
If I do play this again, i'm gonna plug the other controller and i'm gonna have to I might get like another controller for this somehow
It's two controllers, but I tried them both. They both have the same left issue
Hammer's pretty sick
Shield around you is actually pretty useful
Excuses. I know
Excuses andy
What happened to my ship?
Don't get killed now. He's almost dead
Get it. Come on
Nice. This is a good game
Can't select
Oh
D'oh
That's all right. All right. That was fun. That was an actually good game to end too
Okay
This is
What happened? All right. That's it. That's it. That's it. That was the last one
We'll get into this some other time. I do like this little console though. We can play more stuff
Thanks everybody for watching. I'll see you tomorrow
Tomorrow, uh, we're gonna open up. It's gonna be the burger king stream
I have an absolutely no affiliation with burger king zero none. I just have to do this
Tomorrow i'm gonna eat a whopper on stream and I don't know
We thought it was funny like two or three weeks ago when we first talked about it
I you might not think it's funny at all, but I kind of do
I'm gonna eat a whopper on stream and just do like a pretend like look i'm trying out whopper burger king stuff video
I don't know. We thought it was funny like three weeks ago. We'll see if it's still funny tomorrow whopper watch it
Whatever. It doesn't matter
Uh, what we're gonna do after that. I have no idea. This was the plan for today
Maybe I will just jump back on this tomorrow. It's already set up. We'll see then we can kind of close the book on this thing
Maybe we'll see
What time tomorrow? Uh, probably around the same time probably around two at three o'clock pacific three p.m pacific's probably better bet
I'll see you tomorrow. Thanks for watching guys as always. Hope you had a good new year's my new year has started pretty well
so
Uh wayne radio tv. All right, let's go. Let's let's we're gonna raid wayne
We're gonna raid what I can't say the r and then w we're gonna raid wayne radio tv tonight
I saw the fridge joke and I was like, that's fucking funny. Okay, I saw the fridge joke
I did and it was fucking it was beautiful. So let's uh, let's do that
I did say I was kind of raid wayne like four and a half months ago
Here we are four and a half months late. Did I spell that right? I did right? It's wayne radio tv, right?
He missed his fucking birthday. I didn't I don't know what his birthday is
All right. Good night guys. See you tomorrow around three o'clock pacific. Take care of yourselves. Go raid wayne. Say hello
Say happy birthday to him. Say happy belated birthday. See you later. Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves. See you soon