Oh, get away from me soldier. I'm doing my introduction. Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with face cam
Fortress 2 Monday's edition playing as the Scout on King the Hill nucleus
Hold on. I'm just trying to sneak up on him. You got to sneak up on him. Oh
He went falling down into hell. Yay. I didn't even tell you the setup. Whoa, this devil man is gonna get me
No, he's not
Hmm almost with the direct shot almost got me twice. Did he kill himself? No, he didn't
strange scatter gun the Mad Milk and the oh
I would have hit him so easily
And the Sandman I'm being all kinds of weird right now guys. We are we have the point we have the poor
God man, I almost got stuck. You are spy. Whoo
Alright, my heart just exploded. I thought the spy
Bumped into me and insta killed me. That was very very weird
Oh, but there's something I wanted to bring up in this video. I'm gonna talk about the gray man stuff
Not really into that much detail, but still it's it's pretty ridiculous
I can't wait to see what's going on with that if they introduce a new team into team fortress the gray team
Can you imagine the lunacy that that is going to accomplish like how much insanity is gonna happen with this game?
It's going to be unbelievable. Oh
No, I don't have the ball I just used it Oh nice shot with the ball you ball bag
There we are I needed that but there's a lot all kinds of theories going around
My particular theory if you want my theory on the gray man stuff. I think what's gonna happen. It's gonna be bots
It's gonna be non player controlled characters
Brand new player models that are not controlled by anybody and there's gonna be a massive amount of them
Hey, sorry for barging in like this interrupting face cam fortress 2. Sorry Jerma
We'll get back to you in a second, but this literally just came out less than one second ago
I rendered this video this face cam fortress video right after talking about the man versus machine stuff and the gray man stuff
This just came out. This is exactly what I was thinking was going to happen guys
It is the man versus machine update and it is going to be a brand new game mode
And it's going to be a huge huge huge deal
Now I there's a whole lot of information that I do not know right now
But I just wanted to let you guys know if you head over to the TF2 website TF2 calm
It's right on the front page
And yes, it is going to be a mode where you fight against waves and waves of a gray robot team
This is ridiculous and and depending on how many missions you complete and how many waves you survive you get probably hats
I think you're gonna be able to get this probably gonna be new weapons
It is going to be unreal and there's also a new movie too. There's a new source filmmaker movie
So I just wanted to butt in here for a second
I'll let you guys know about this because this is brand new information that I did not see or hear of
Until less than like 30 seconds ago, so we'll get back to face cam fortress 2 now
Hopefully man versus machine is going to be incredible
You can read all the biographies of all the new enemies all the new robots. There are giants
There are giant robot heavies in this update if you couldn't ask for anything more than that
I don't know what else you could ask for but you can see all the information in the links in the description
So yeah guys, we'll go back to team fortress face cam fortress 2 and I'll see you guys all soon. Take it away
Gerber so that's my theory if you want it if you want to hear what I have to say
About that same sniper. Oh, I'm coming for you, man. I'm coming for young. You're gonna have a bad day in a second
I'm gonna come eat you alive. Is he still there? No, he's not. He's dead. He's dead regardless
I'm gonna go the other way though. But yeah, I think it's gonna be bots. We shall see
I am anxiously awaiting what it possibly is. It's gonna be so much fun. Oh
There is there's a sniper bastard and he's dead. Yeah
We're gonna win I think we're gonna win. I really think we're going to win. Hey, man, you've got that invincibility on that's not fair
Whatever. I'll just go have fun. I feel like your birthday party. Did it not hit him? What is?
What's going on with this dude guy was acting really fishy. Hey, what's up? Hey, what's up sniper down?
Let us go again. The scout thinks he's gonna get me. He almost did though. That was the thing
He almost did get me. No, no, no, no, no get this pyro out of here. Nice job heavy. Nice job
you
Pyro, mr. Pyro
Cap it cap it. Let me help you. Let me help you with that. I got it. I got it
What's going on up here anything any any potty's going on any snipers any snipers that I can kill
Oh this guy down air spy
Landed right in his face. He's not dead. I would have got healed by that. That's not cool. That's not cool, man
Hey heavy, where's your like sandwich? Can I like swallow some of it? Oh
I just freaked that guy out. I bet you that guy really just said into it like
That's not good, that's not good. Oh my good good job
Good job, dude. That was a nice kill. You saw the opportunity saw what I was doing and you didn't let me do it
That's a good medic. Is this guy just like sniping people with the bison?
Yeah, he's killing people look at the top right. He is actually killing people with that. That's so awesome. Just sniping
Scout first scout. Oh
spy behind me, too
Don't want anyone I don't I just want to kill this heavy because he's the biggest threat and he's scary
Do get me out of there. Get me out of there. Hello. Oh, I don't gonna throw up. I hate this
Girardi now, I didn't hit him. No. Oh
Soviet potato dot exe
Almost out of coffee. That's not a good thing. Wow. This guy has really been up here the whole time
He is just a sniper soldier. I don't think I'd ever muddle those words in my life sniper soldier heavy up there
Thank you for the heels my friend. He don't headshot me. Don't headshot me. Don't headshot me. Thank you for not headshotting me
Walk into that. Mmm
Did I thought he almost fell off? I'm about to fall off to be honest with you
Get oh get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Hello
Oh
What just happened what why am I seeing like an advertisement, what was that?
Alright, I was like in the middle of shooting that guy and an ad popped up. What the hell was that?
All right, I think that's it. You know, hold on. Come on
Oh, I want to like switch to blue and try to like help but that's gonna wrap it up here guys. We won nice
I'm gonna take another sip of this
Mmm, and now it's gone
You know, I start when face game fortress 2 or any video of mine is coming to a close when I run out of something
To drink because that's when I have to go get more. Well, technically it's like upstairs. You know what?
I'm gonna I'm gonna do one more life just for fun. There is there it is. Oh
Please
Gonna be really sneaky here. He does not know I'm right here. Oh, yeah, he does. Yeah, he does. Yeah, he does
How we looking how is this heavy magically standing on nothing? What is going on with this guy?
He's just floating there like a specter. Oh my god. All right. Well, that's it guys. I'll see you all next time
Thank you so much for watching really do appreciate it and I'll see you guys all soon. And of course, take care everybody