Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Battlefield 3 gameplay commentary.
Only the second Battlefield 3 video on this channel, and I'm gonna try and change that.
I'm trying to get better at this game, trying to find my groove playing with Shibby2142 and a couple other guys.
They helped me out. They were pretty good seasoned veterans at this game.
So, enjoy the live commentary guys starting right now.
Oh, no. Oh, it's a bad idea.
Whoa. Hey, he just went right by me. I'm cool with that.
Oh, where's this guy?
Alright, everyone join Charlie.
Wait, can't, can't just like kick this person?
Yeah, I can just kick. Oh, okay.
Cause I don't like him anyways. How did I not get that guy?
One second. Oh, he just died.
Jerma, watch it around the corner. Nice. Yeah, I got him.
One more. Oh, Jesus.
Alright, join up Shibs. Oh my God, he's trying to knife me.
Nice dude, that was nice.
Thank you for just saving my life.
Anybody else?
No, I think that's it.
Oh, no, there's somebody. Oh, no, there's an AA.
He's like on the opposite side of two walls.
Oh, God. No, he got me.
So far away. He got me.
I don't know. Sniper, two guys.
Nice, good job.
There's another guy though, his buddy.
Got health back, Shibya, get some health on him.
I'm down, down.
Can I revive him? Yeah, we traded so he's dead.
Oh, I'm dead, dead? Yeah.
The green meaning.
Like the green monster.
Jerma knows all about that.
Oh, come on.
What do you know about suppressing fire right there?
Oh my God. Oh, God, no.
Is that you in the helicopter right there?
Dude, the helicopter.
Nice.
I tried to come in and just flank him with a helicopter.
Oh, come on.
No, I have no ammo left.
I have absolutely no ammo left.
Done?
Oh my God, it's a helicopter.
The sun is so bright.
Too bright.
Like notify that the building's falling.
Yeah, that's probably the rarest way to die in this game is by destruction because, you know, Frostbite 2.
So much destruction, guys.
Less destruction than Bad Company 2.
Makes sense, right?
Destruction.
Yeah, so getting killed by destruction, that's like an honor.
Oh, boy.
Oh, God, that's a helicopter.
Hit the helicopter face on with a rocket.
What do I get?
Nothing. Nothing from it.
Nope. Nope.
Alright, let's take BA's also getting capped.
Coming right behind you, Shibby.
Alright.
Because I'm trying to take out element choppers with rockets and it doesn't work.
Minus the left. Minus Shibby.
Yep, two of them.
I got killed.
I don't even know where he was.
Working on him. Got one.
I saw that.
Ooh, with the revive clutch.
Not a lot of people do that.
Can't switch revive.
It's a roll.
Okay, A's clean, B's clean, C's clean.
Wait, C's flashing. Let's go.
Why did I do that?
Hold on to my chopper.
He's on the roof.
Oh, eat this.
Eat this, baby.
Alright, let's go.
Vote next map.
Oh, I got your RPG.
Got him.
Got this.
We got this.
Where are we going?
I don't know. I accidentally pushed E out of the helicopter.
Shibby, I like this...
I like this scope you got.
This thing's good.
I like this little...
The Cobra.
So that's considered one of the red dots.
And then there's the red dot, red dot, which is the American version.
Why are we going to E?
Oh, in front of us, in front of us.
Got him.
Where did he spawn from?
Let's just go take A, if you want to go on foot.
Yeah, I'm coming with you.
Alright, I'm going to take this corner right here.
Oh, we're going to shot from behind.
Oh my stupid little bird.
I hate that.
He came out of nowhere.
Anybody in the building?
That thing's so overpowered.
Alright.
Hopefully our car is still there.
I kind of paid her a lot for that one.
Yeah, we had valet pocket.
Uh oh.
Don't push E.
Woohoo!
No, it disappeared.
Guy on the road.
You guys are going B?
We're going B, B, E, E.
There's a car at B, so watch it.
We're in a ram it.
Germa, it's all you.
This guy's down.
Oh, where was he?
I'm dead.
That was a poor decision.
Because we were bumping the Jurassic Park tune and I just got all jacked up.
T?
I did it!
Am I even capping this damn thing?
Protecting it.
Spawning on the T of space.
Oh no, little bird.
Aw yeah.
We're about to win.
These guys got crushed.
Secured, flag cap.
Oh, you need some heals, you need some heals.
Who's that guy?
Give me a sec.
Shoot him, just shoot him, just shoot him all, no!
Your team has won.
So that is going to wrap up the video guys.
Thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it.
And I will see you guys all next time, trying to get better at Battlefield.
I promise you.
See you guys all next time.
Take care, everybody.