I just like broke. Hello. Let's try and do stunts now. Oh, it's too funny. Stop killing
people. I got I have to kill that guy. I have to die so I can have no stars. Come on. Come
on. We got to get that bike. Have to get that bike. That bike is like completely necessary.
I have a bike. Get out of the way. Bike. No, I want like a fast bike. God, this car sucks.
You're chasing down that bike. I'm listening to like screamer music right now. No, that
you can't get away. God damn it. He got away. You are not getting away. I'm getting this
stupid bike so we can do horrible things with it. Oh, dad. It's so funny. I'm sorry. I'm
sorry, sir or ma'am. All right, sir. I got a fast bike. What I want to do. All right.
So listen, stop getting the police over here. You're like ruining everything. I'm trying
to let them kill me so I can like restart. Oh, okay. All right. What I want to do. I
want somebody to get a car and I want to start at the opposite ends of the spectrum. I want
to go on the highway. Oh, I got to weave through traffic here. Okay, so today we're going to
go on a fun adventure with. You were on our screen for like a split second. Where did
I even go? I like went underneath you guys. Did you not go flying upwards? Coming. I
want to watch this even happen. So start driving. Make sure you're in my right lane.
Turn around. Stay right there. Hold on. Stay right there. Stay there. No, no.
Stop it. I'm going to try to do something. Let me get this bike. Okay. Stay there.
No, are you in the right lane or the left lane? Left. So you're in your left lane. Okay. Yeah.
Ready? As soon as you bumped into that car, the radio just blew up.
Oh my God.
Are you guys dead? Yeah. Oh God. Oh my God.
Shit. Look at this mess. All right. Screw this. We're getting a helicopter.
All right. Helicopter time.
It's a massacre. What the hell's going on? Oh my God. All right. We went the wrong way.
We're going to turn around. There was an off ramp we didn't take.
Shit. I'm pretty close. What's handbrake space? Oh God. That's definitely handbrake. There we go.
Oh my God. Okay. I landed. I'm okay. Just happened to be in like an alley.
God. For the love of God. At least I got whatever this is. Pick me up.
You're orange.
Like I didn't realize the guns are so strong and it looks like the floor is shaking under me.
Oh my God. All right. I'm coming to get you. When I get you, I mean die.
Where the hell are you? I got a big open space where I'm standing right now. You can make it.
Just don't hit any trees. All right. Where are you? Above you.
Oh, there you are. All right. Now nice and easy. Come and land right here.
And where are you going? What are you doing?
Okay. What happened?
Just seen a car.
Dude, a car. A car.
It shot. It shot like a million feet into the air.
Oh, my head hurts from laughing at that.
My blades fell off. Oh my God. I just gave myself an aneurysm laughing at that.
Really flew like into space. What am I doing?
Why am I not seeing these amazing things? Why am I never present at the good stuff?
I remember turning beautiful. Oh my God.
It's been too long since I played this game, man. I'm crying.