Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some more...what the hell was that?
Some more Call of Duty Black Ops 2 party games. This one is actually called Sticks and Stones.
Where you only get to use ballistic knives, knives, and the crossbow. This thing.
Oh, get stuck. This is on that boat map again. For a second I thought that was an actual plate.
Get stuck. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Guy right here. Come here.
Just double tap him. Whoa. Whoa. Those things explode. Yikes.
I'm going up there. I'm coming up there, man. I'm going to give you a Christmas card that you're going to want to send back.
Iron explosion. Yeah, melee kill. Can I jump down there?
Oh, you also get the tomahawk too with a throwing knife. I'm going to throw this guy right in the back.
Or in the front. Or in his face. That works too. Pull this back out. This thing.
Oh, I don't know where to go. Shoot down. Let's just shoot down that hallway just to scare him.
Oh man. Did I get a double? Oh, I thought it went through the guy. Wow. Oh my.
Dude, my face. I just planted my face into the wall. That was ridiculous.
Holy crap. That was insanity. Get tomahawked. Nobody was even there.
There's a dude in there. He's sitting right here.
Screw this. No. That thing is terrifying. I'm just going to use the ballistic knives, man. These things are deadly.
Oh, come on. No, please don't kill me. No. Stab him. Reload.
What's this? Oh, you got smashed. I'm going to take this out.
I don't like that thing. That thing's... I'm not good with that thing.
Skewered. I don't have any more bullets with it though. Or ammo.
Oh, with the knives. Not this thing. Now I've got to use this thing. I don't even want to use this thing.
Got him. Oh, bang. Hello. Oh boy. Screw it. I got one of them.
At least I got my ballistics back. These things are where it's at. Oh, someone's going to get it.
I'm just going to throw it over the whole map and see what happens.
If I get a kill for that, that would be so hilarious.
Dammit. Whoa. Whoa. Easy. Easy, buddy. Easy. Easy.
What? That guy was running...
When does this end? How long are the rounds? These things are pretty damn long.
You're wrapping back around. Are you? Oh, get bankrupted.
This guy's got that explosive scary thing.
What on earth is happening right now? Oh, get blown up. Get blown up.
You son of a bitch. It was... people surrounded me.
Get tomahawked. I don't even know if I'm winning or not. Am I? Apparently I'm winning.
Geez. There's a lot of human beings over here. I would have had that kill too. Bastard.
Dammit. Should have paid more attention. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Oh, hit him with that. You're just going to get stabbed. What? What?
All right. That works too. Seven seconds. Six, five, four, three, two, one.
Oh, is that it? Hey, I won. Fruit snacks, baby. That was crazy.
That was absolutely crazy. But let's do one more. Let's do another one.
Let's get off this boat level. Connection interrupted. What the hell? Bang.
I have some delivery for you. Extra special package.
I don't want to run into these... I love these things, man. I don't want to run out of them.
Bankrupt. Bankrupt. I'll just run around with these damn things.
Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. He's still behind me.
Holy crap. Just... Oh. What are these? Shoot me in the face?
What the hell was that? It's all good. Let's come out here and do it again.
I'm going to stab you in your face. You're going to get stabbed right in your face.
I'm going to stab. I'm going to stab. You're going to get freaking...
Where is this guy? Oh, he's over here. Get him.
No. No. Watch it. Please don't hurt me. Please don't kill me.
Geez Louise with a piece of cheese. Oh, that guy's alive. That guy's dead, I mean.
Chaos. There's another guy. Did I get him? Oh my God. Run.
Oh, did I get... I didn't get anybody. Damn it.
At least I got the tomahawk. Wow. Somebody behind me trying to kill me.
How did that not work? Who did I just kill?
Apparently one of them got killed. Keep running. Keep moving. Keep moving.
Keep moving. What? No. No. What do we got? I'm winning?
I was winning. Skewered. I'm so scared.
Try using this thing again. At least for a minute or two or three or four.
Sticks and stones will break my bones, but words will never hurt me.
What? Some dude was just like up my ass. Maybe not. Where the hell was that guy?
That was weird. Sticks and stones. Sticks and stones.
Damn. Right here. This guy. Right here.
Ow. I'm losing. I gotta pull this together here. Come on.
Come on. Pull it together. You laggy son of a bitch. Come here.
Come on. Keep going. Keep going. Keep going. Keep it going. Keep it going.
Still losing. Still losing. But can I pull it through?
How in the name of Jehoshaphat did I not kill that guy?
I was sticking the knife in the back of his head. Nothing happened.
You know what? Screw it Tomahawk. Explosions. Anybody over here?
Yeah there is. Take down that guy. No idea where I am.
I'm like freaking Superman. It's tied. It's tied. I gotta pull ahead.
No. No. No. No. I gotta pull ahead. I only have a few seconds.
No. I gotta get this guy. Gotta get him. What? What? What was that?
The guy just like... Really bro? You're gonna drop shot in sticks and stones?
Oh my god. I won. I actually won. Well there you go. Nice.
I didn't get the last kill though. But yeah that's gonna wrap it up I guess guys.
So thank you so much for watching. Really do appreciate it. Sticks and stones baby.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care everybody.