Hello, how you doing? Do you have a lot of new emotes? You're right. What's up? Let's go already.
Let's get been I'm not late. I was here at 330. It's like this I said, I said Resident Evil six
is a banger. Resident Evil six is the worst Resident Evil game. Wait, hold on. Worst numbered
Resident Evil game, I think. Wait, hold on. It might be better than the first one. I know
everybody. Look, I don't like the tank controls. 20 years ago, I didn't like tank controls.
It automatically is like in a different category for me. Resident Evil. Yeah, they're all good.
And controls. I it's just it just ruins it for me. It ruins it just does. Anyways,
we got some stuff to talk about. We've got some exciting things to talk about. Well,
I mean, kind of exciting. First most important thing is tonight is the night where the New Year's
Eve nomination categories are going up. You'll be able to nominate for each category. Make
sure you follow the rules. They're going to be very, very clearly posted. I'm going to give you
guys probably 10 days, 12 days to nominate stuff. And a day after the nominations close,
I'm going to go through, make the list, and you'll be able to vote on the worst and best
stings of the year. Really important to note. Very important. The dollhouse is not nominatable
in a handful of categories. So to make it so dollhouse doesn't like inhale 10 different
categories, it is not eligible for best stream of the year. It's not eligible for best joke taking
more than five minutes to set up because I know a lot of people probably nominate stuff for that.
So just imagine dollhouse is grayed out in its own world and there's a new category that's
best dollhouse moment. So dollhouse has its own category. You're probably also probably
wondering if worst Peter's on there. Of course it is. I don't think I said it once. I think that's
the only time I said it the whole year. It's just on there. It has to be on there. I don't even care.
There's, yeah, there's one right there. I don't know. I was going to take it off,
but I was like, you know what? I don't care. Wait. Oh, I gotta make sure I didn't get kicked
in the lobby, which I may have. We kicked. No, he's here. Just making sure that he wasn't kicked.
You gotta move around a little bit. Okay. Currently me and it's Alex are currently in
Resident Evil 6. We're in a lobby. We're going to play. This is the Resident Evil 6 stream that
I've been literally like just putting off and just not doing for like the last three weeks,
three and a half, four weeks. Here we are. Good question. When is tomorrow's stream? Oh,
no, that's when is Toontown stream. I don't know. But would you like to hear the series of events
that is going to be pretty exciting stuff? They were playing Resident Evil 6, never going to
play this again. I would assume after like three or four hours, maybe five hours tops, I'm just
like, I fucking have to leave. I don't want to play this anymore. I'm going to be very surprised
if that's not the case. So you'll never see this ever again. In fact, I can't wait to uninstall it
from steam. Secondly, on the eighth, guess what comes out on the eighth? I didn't even know this
until a week ago. That's right. Monster Rancher one and two remake. It's not a remake. It's just a port.
We're going to play it. You bet your ass. And then on the ninth, game awards, obviously,
I'll be streaming the game awards like I always do. Then that's it. That's all I have planned for
this week. I'm very excited. I'm very excited to play Monster Rancher one and two. Beanbag Sonic
lives again. I'm really glad the game awards are at like four o'clock in the afternoon or five in
the afternoon. You want some lore? Remember the Nintendo Direct that was at 9am Pacific?
That was I don't think I even showered. I just ripped myself out of bed, ran in the room,
put my bathrobe on, put some water in my hair and turned it on. I felt like shit during that stream.
Nothing happens before noon here. It just does. It's been like that since I was like 12,
15. Doesn't matter. I, I, guys, I can't even eat before noon. I get up in the morning and it's like,
nope, nothing. I can't, I'm useless until 12 o'clock. And then at 2pm, I'm at peak readiness. Here
we go. From two to 10 or two to eight is like, I got the most energy. I'm ready to go. I'm hungry.
I'm ready to go. I don't know. Why is that? Why is my body reject food for two or three hours
after I wake up? I don't get it. I don't, I'm not, my hunger reflex is gone. I'm like, it makes me
kind of nauseous. It's an ADHD thing. Is it really? That's interesting. Somebody said you're gaining
viewers. Uh, yeah. I just turned the stream on. Yeah. Of course it's going to be gaining viewers.
It's the first five minutes of the stream. What you need to do is you need to wait till like the
end of the stream or after like a few hours of Resident Evil 6 and like 4,000 people that are
here. They say like POG a bunch of times and then they just leave because this game sucks.
I, I'm ready. That's when you say viewers plummeting, right? You got to be ready for that
one. What? How many people are here now? Oh shit. Oh shit. The six K all ready. We haven't even
started. I, you know what? I'll tell you. I have not even been paying attention to my view count.
I haven't even been looking at it. It's just something that I know exists.
Nine K. No, no, I don't care. Don't get me looking at the view count. I don't even want to look at
it. They could be a hundred people here or like a hundred thousand. I don't even want to know.
Don't tell me what I mean. If we hit 20 K, then I got to celebrate that one already. Well, I already
did. You're going to do a face reveal. Yeah. You're a pot. You've got a positive outlook. No, I just,
all right. I just want, I'm just not, I don't want to pay attention to it. Why would I?
Let me check and see if he's here. Not. But yeah, I have, while there's more people trickling in,
just listen. End of the year awards. There's a lot of new people since the last time we did this. So
let's make this really clear. This is, I believe the fourth annual worst shit of the year awards
where it's not like a typical award stream that you may be used to. We go over, over the course
of 2021. All the worst shit, all like the cringiest, weirdest shit that I, that apparently I've done.
There's also best stream of the year. There's also like best joke of the year.
It's things like worst face, worst sound I made, worst singing, worst impressions,
best impression, best noise. It's, it's fun. Irma and cringe never. Worst shit 2021.
Yeah. Best one guy. We take what's something that one guy in the community did.
The emote, right? When are you going to do a Neanderthal collab? Let's go Neanderthal. Let's go.
I somebody, every time. All right. Listen, anytime anybody ever says like, Oh dude,
what, when are you going to do collab with this person? Oh, hold on. Let me call them right now.
Oh, hey, hey, before you say any words. Hey, do you want to do a collab stream on Monday? Yeah.
I got time. You got time? Okay. Now, now say hello. What do you want to do? It's just if it happens,
it happens. It depends. There's a project that I think is interesting. If I want to collaborate
with somebody, then we collaborate. I think Neanderthal is, Neanderthal is fucking hilarious.
Of course that would be fun. Maybe, but like you, you, it just, it's, if it's gonna happen,
maybe it, it could. I would say that about anybody. Literally anyone.
Everyone calling me anti-social Andy. I'm about to do a collaboration in 10 minutes. Like I'm in
the call right now with somebody. It don't matter. I'm, I'm open to collaborations, but I'm closed
to everything. That's really weird to say, but it's, it's accurate.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold on a minute. I'm open to collaborations.
I am closed to solicitations. Okay. That's perfect way to say it. When are you going to do 1080p
streams? Um, I don't know when, when I, I'm not going to know. I don't know. Okay. I think we're
ready. Hey, did we get kicked out of the lobby? I hope not. I haven't been looking. Okay. You're,
you're actually in. Okay. Cool. Yeah. So tapping freaks me out though. Yeah. I don't like it.
Let's see. The camera's not on the camera on. Please don't be on. Don't be on. All right.
That's a freeze frame. It's good. I don't have one camera. All right. So we're going to play
resident evil six. It's going to be a fun time. It's going to be fun. Yeah. Like I would, like
I was telling Chaz, it's, this is the best, most critically acclaimed resident evil. This is the
worst one. What does your title say? It's my title says, uh, I got a, yeah, maybe I'll tap.
My title says picking the best resident evil for the Halloween co-op stream. You're going to tell
mine says this is the worst. My sense, my, my stream title, I swear to God actually says
literally the worst one. So, I mean, we'll find out that's that's yin and yang energy right there.
All right. So when we skip the opening cut scene, cause who really cares? There's a virus on the
loose and we have to track down the fucking tyrant or whatever. All right, let's go.
You ready? I'm walking as fast as I can towards this door. I don't, there's no sprint in resident
evil six, right? I didn't see one. There's a dash. There's a dash. There's a dash. Yeah. There's a
dash button. I don't know what it is. Cause I did the tutorial with a controller. Oh, that's right.
You're on controller. I'm on keyboard. I switched the keyboard and mouse cause you made me feel
insecure. You were like, I gotta, I gotta up my accuracy. So I was like, well, I gotta compete.
I gotta up my accuracy. So then I switched the mouse. Well, but the whole point is that
I would have more accuracy than you. Cause you're on controller and now you're going to make me look
bad. Turn on an ass cam. How would that work? Where would the cams on by default? If you haven't
changed the FOV, it's pretty zoomed in. Yeah. I did. I moved the FOV. What? Yeah. You have to do
that from the main menu. I was told. What do you, no, you don't. Oh yeah. You do. How do you wait?
Why am I just standing here? Cause it's a co-op moment. Oh, it's a co-op thing. I don't know how
to. Okay. There we go. Hey, press V. It's your best bet. Aim for the head. If somebody's, if you
want to toggle sprint, you have to go to the main menu and press the hilarious joke that everyone's
heard a thousand times back in like 2010. All right. I think sprint is all F4. Is that what
they're saying? You got it. All right. So this is how it works. We have to. I hope so. Okay. It's
actually, I think it's double tap W or shift. Is it? I've shift doesn't do anything. All right.
That feels good. But just, I want to make this really clear to everybody watching right now.
I have a script running in the background to make it so I can toggle right click. How do you think
streams happen? There's a script. No, but listen, like you think the humor comes off top of the
head. There's a script. There's probably something that's going to need. There's probably something
that's going to need me to just tap right click. And you have to do it because I have a script.
Neither of us have responded to a single individual chatter on the entire streams. I did. I did like
five seconds ago. You just don't pay attention to your chat. Like I do. You don't know. I'm like
me and my chat get together. We know each other. All right. Follow the shot. We can actually run.
This is good. Oh, happy birthday. Is it your birthday? Holy shit. Thanks. Why did I say thanks?
Hey, is it your birthday? Yeah. Thanks dude. I'm so glad that you were born and you live.
All right. So I'll be honest with you. I got to be really honest with you.
Uh huh. I don't care about any of this. You don't care about my birthday?
Okay. Of course I care about your birthday. What? Why is everybody saying? Oh, the game's quiet.
Yeah, I know. I'm a quiet game, Andy. We're chasing somebody. So we missed the opening cut scene.
Yeah. Wait, this is in media res. This is going to be one of those. Okay. Really though? That's how
the real game opens. They start with like a badass action scene because they're afraid they're not
going to like catch your attention in time. So a helicopter is like scraping a train and then
the bad guy drops in and then they go, Oh, it's you again. And then it cuts to like three weeks
earlier and that's where we're at now. I thought I was playing the stacker game at the who's puking.
Did you see the birthday cake? I mean, I don't turn that up. All right. Is that better? I was
like, that was like grocery store birthday cake. It probably just in the bathroom.
Is that better? I can hear you now. Well, I just for the end game. I have it low.
Why can't I not fire my gun? Did you try to shoot me at the same time? No, I'm sure. I, why do we
have any body? We don't have bullets in our weapons that we brought here. I'm going to put an orange
tip on the muzzle of this gun. This is giving me a headache because of how like shitty the frame
rate is for this. I don't know why. I'm sorry. Is your, uh, is your 30 80 not qualified for this
2012 video game? Does this look as bad as it does? It just looks awful. I mean, it looks like 2012,
but the frame rate's fine. My frame rate's all over the place. It's just really zoomed in.
Wait, you dropped your phone. I think it's off. I turned the V sync on and I capped frames to 60.
I did that too. Maybe it's trying to render 120. That's weird. I might have to fix this
eventually. All right. What, once we get like into this, cause you need to, let's fix it now.
Well, no, cause we need to save point cause I don't want to do this again. Let's get to like a point.
We call them checkpoints as cameras. All right. Search the campus for Liz.
I, I don't understand why we have our guns out holding it like this.
We don't have bullets. Why would we have them out? There we go. That's a book and that's what
I'm talking about. How do you melee? Um, take out a knife and you can swing the knife. I think
you can kick without that. You, there's like, there's like a, there's like a melee dedicate.
That guy didn't get scared at all. Why did he not get scared?
Should we be looking for weapons? The lights are on. Oh, in here.
Wait, I did. I do have ammo. It says I have 18. I have what? Oh, oh, okay. Now, now we have 17.
Where do you even see 17 coming out of my eyeballs? Oh no, we have a, we have an ear mounted.
Where do you see set? Like you have to physically count the bullets over there.
I don't know. I just took the number that you said. I think it's in the inventory.
All right. Don't do anything. Cool. I'm going to, I'm going to all tap for a second.
Hope you don't get booted. Okay. All right. This guy does not, nothing phases this guy.
He's the main character. That's quite a draft. He's leading us like we're the NPC on the follow
mission. He's escorting us. Why is he not reacting to any of this? I've seen some shit.
Yeah. You have a hole in your head. I feel like somebody drilled a hole like that.
Demons are escaping you. Like your soul is escaping. Oh, from the light. You've got a light too.
Yeah. But it's, it's like a weird hole in your head. Like a luscious locks. Oh, you got Leon.
You got no brain in there, man. I can shine a flashlight in there and just see light.
Personal attacks. I'm your partner. I'm your resident partner for like the last 10 years in
this game. How are we going? I have some respect for the most popular resident evil character of
all time. Helena. Who is everybody knows Helena from the opening cut scene of this game. I don't
like the fact that we can't do just what happened. I thought he shot me. Does that hurt me? Uh,
that was a balloon jump scare. Oh, that was bad. I missed every shot. It's your daddy controller
has auto. He just say it's your daddy. I think we're looking for his daughter or something. I
don't know. Okay. Can we just kill him now? He's clearly infected. You don't know that though.
You're going to shoot him that you're going to do what I just tried to do. It didn't work.
Wait, is he running for president of the United States? Is this the same president?
Adam Benford. It's this guy. Okay. I just scared him. All right. The chandelier dropping and like
a fire starting in front of him is not scary, but he's like looking at like the constitution
of whatever this is. And it scared the shit out of him. Get ready to kill him. I will be once I
find my daughter. Hang on. Are you saying a politician is scared of the constitution
of the United States? Oh, that's so relevant. I think we have to open this. No, he's just opening
it. How do you reload? I have no idea. Wait, do we, we can't even reload. No extra ammo. Oh,
by the way, it's his fault if we die because he put, he said we should put it on veteran.
It's your fault. If we'd lose the medium difficulty, there's five difficulties.
Veterans, the third one, but I worked. That's just enough to not lose gamer points, but it's
also not enough to gain gamer points. I mean, I'm just saying we, we could have said we were on
veteran and plan easy. All right. So wait, wait, wait. So he, we have to make the elevator work.
Okay, wait, we need to, he's gliding over here. Okay. This is cool.
Resident Evil six is actually a walking simulator. The guns are kind of like in
universal studios when you go on ride, you know, they're just little laser points that you can
tally up at the end of the game. It is weird to not have the flashlight on the gun. It's like on
the side of our heads. 2012, that wasn't invented yet. You're not paying attention. Like extra
dynamic light. Careful as it doesn't really matter if I'm paying attention. I have watched like at
least one or two Will Ferrell movies with no sound on and just like, I can know what's happening by
the movements that he's doing on screen. I got, it doesn't matter. Why do you have to take the left?
I don't know. I don't like your mother, like mom calls and like I want to talk to mom for like an
hour and a half, which is just the exact runtime of like Will Ferrell's last movie. I didn't even
aim and it did it for me. Yeah. How long, how long is it like a phone call with mom? It's usually
like an hour or two, right? Yeah. Exactly. That's what I'm saying. Why is everyone question marking?
Are you saying that playing this game is like, call it reminds you of calling your mom?
No, I'm just saying a Will Ferrell movie is the exact length of time for a phone call with mom.
Yeah. So next time you're watching a Will Ferrell movie, just think about the last time you called
your mom and then mute the Will Ferrell movie. 10 minutes. Excuse me. You got to talk to mom longer
than that. That depends on if you, if, okay, but here's the thing you're talking to a bunch of
people who still live with mom. So they can't fathom calling her because she's in the other room.
I would, I would agree with that maybe a little bit, but we did a poll, we did like a census on
the channel and it's like 40% doctor, 20% scientist. Um, there's like 10% uh, like
firefighter and shit. Like these people, they're not just like at home. Okay. You got, you got like
a large proportion of firefighting moms in chat. When do we get to play the game?
The one they're waiting for. Oh, they're waiting for us to go to the elevator.
Hold on. We're going to have to move this. It's going to take both of our combined strength.
Is it really? Oh, it does. We're here. This whole game so far has been just like
your annoying upstairs neighbor in your apartment. It's just been the fucking sounds like the walking
sounds. Oh, the creaking boards. Okay. Oh, this is so ugly. I'm really sorry for everybody that has
to put up with this for now. There was entire fan base is milked. I can't imagine like that.
Like, no magic doing like a meet and greet. It's like all like older women. It's all like,
just do they are for the meet and greet. If you stay a streamer long enough,
make that a reality. I mean, I'm almost 40, man. That's called daytime TV.
What cry is that? I thought that, I thought that was the game. He just like freaked me out.
I was like, why are they leaning so hard into that? Got to do the puking off screen. This is
a hard. So let's, let's, let's get this ready. I'm going to shoot, I'm going to shoot them in
the head. You shoot them in the chest. We're going to shoot them five times each. Now I'm going to
shoot. I'm going to shoot once in the head. All right. I don't think you have a choice.
What the fuck is this one? What was that? What was that? Like DDR? Like 300. It was just DDR.
Why is the camera? I thought that was her doing that to you for a second.
It's like, why did you have the gun? Did you pull the trigger or was that all of me? I shot,
I shot him. I shot her in the back. Is it arrow keys? I think, I think it's just WASD correlates.
We'll get used to it. This is going to get really difficult with the QTs on keyboard.
How could this? I was about to scream it, but I, you're in, I don't, I feel like. It's like a yawn.
Now I want to. I was about to scream it, but there's a lot of people that were really pissed
off about that. So I'm glad. What do you mean don't let them in? There is. Don't let this guy in.
Oh, there's too many people on the elevator. I can't. All right. We have to get this way.
Bang. Bingo. Boink. How do you reload? I don't have any bullets left. Run. We have no other
bullets yet. Oh, that guy's got a pipe. How do you, how do you dash? I don't think there is one.
Definitely. That's our cue to get the hell out of here. Oh, it's space. Space? What do you mean
space? Hold space. Oh, that's weird. Okay. I feel like this is somebody pretending to run.
It's not somebody actually running. Okay. That actually
reminds me after this cut scene, I'll show you. Dude, does like security guards actually have this
many screens? Yeah, I think so. Are those two people who've been banned from your channel?
Let us back in. I promise. I promise. I won't ask to see your shit filled diaper again. I promise.
Get him. Get him, Marge. Leon, it's too late. We can do.
Or space twice when you're aimed in. Okay. Oh, I was explicitly told to not talk about diapers.
Explicitly. Yeah. Like, I'm not even kidding. Probably at least three or four people. Get the
hell out of here. You must have struck a nerve. I just was told don't do that. It's like fucking
weird. It's been at least, at least three people have told me that. All right. Pause for a sec.
Okay. I need turn sensitivity like. Yes. All the way down.
Somebody said you can, if you double tap space. What the hell are you doing? Oh, it's like a dodge.
Oh, holy shit. What? Are you seeing this? I can't focus on the settings because I'm stupid.
This is like the easiest way to get a bunch of like splinters all over your body.
Okay, that's cool. I wonder, do we share stuff on the ground? I wonder.
Oh, yeah, I can see that from my perspective. All right. Do we share what? Do we share items
like on the ground? Because I just picked up ammo and if there's no ammo on the ground,
then this is bad. Oh, look. Control settings. Can I break boxes? I don't think so. Is it camera
speed? It's, yeah. Camera speed is, and then there's aim speed too. Aim speed? Okay. Aim
speed is when you're aimed down sights and camera speed is just you walking around. There we go.
And if you put it at zero, don't worry. It's every video game ever made.
It's still horrible. You have to go, you have to go from zero to two out of sometimes potentially
a hundred. I still don't understand why that's a thing. All right. It is a PC video game.
Double tap space when not aiming. My run looks like I'm about to like go on stage at a Broadway.
Okay. Now I think you have to be, okay. So when you're aiming, if you hold the direction in
space, you'll dive and then you can get back up. All right. You ready? Overly complex, but yep.
Wait, hold on. Oh shit. That's actually kind of cool. Why do people say this is the worst one?
Jump down the stairs. They need to bring back the matrix games. I think they just kind of,
they overdid it with every video game having like a jump slow down that ever it just became
taboo to ever do it again. Even I have items too. I feel like we're just skipping everything.
Oh yeah. You got, you picked up the ammo. I didn't get any, you didn't get any ammo. Oh,
that's not good. Unless, uh, unless I just didn't look where you look about this.
We break the stuff. Bad feeling about this. Is that, is that the, be honest,
is that the voice actor for Levi? I don't know. It might be. Is that the, is that the,
I'm not going to do it because it's, it's hollowed ground, but uh, you know, the potentials there
to do like to do captain Levi from attack on Titan.
Don't you fucking dare to get that into my blood. How dare you do that. There's two things that
you were told when we in the private discord together is do not mention attack on Titan,
especially any of the main characters. That was one of the things that, and you, and you did,
you clicked, you did like the thumbs up emote on the fucking text on discord too. So I know you
saw it. Where we go? We got to go to, we got to go to class. Oh, press E while aiming. Sorry.
Oh shit. You can do double pistol. Why would we be hiding? Oh, somebody fell asleep on the stream
again. Oh, dual welding. Yep. Dual welding. I'm just picking up all the ammo. Is that,
I hope you're not mad about that. Uh, I got ammo on that one. Do you get ammo on this guy?
Those skill points. Do you get skill points on this guy? I think there actually is skills
in this game. I really do. Wait, do we have like a, do we have like a tree?
I actually think we do. All right. So what, we're in the wrong place here.
Resident sleeper six. Yep. It made it is good one chat. No, that, that actually is a good one
because this one is the worst one. Was that probably just ambient sound effect. Oh, I thought the
soda machine just broke. I was okay. All right. You know what? Can I just talk about how stupid
video games are? We can just walk over that. Help me. I've wasted so much ammo. I don't know why.
How do you do a wheel? Why can't we just walk over this? Video games are dumb. I hate them.
Look out. I have to stop fucking around because I'm seriously going to not have enough. You shoot
for, okay, you're going to have to shoot for another hour because I just used an hour of ammo.
Please do good because that was probably the next 45 minutes of in-game ammo.
What's the melee button? Uh, you've got a knife. I think you can just do the,
I've got a shotgun. Wait, why do you have a shotgun? Because we're different people.
Okay. You don't, you don't have to be like me. Well, you get a shotgun and I get a knife. Oh,
it's because I've paid for Capcom plus. Yeah. Yeah. I, by the way, I know you still were paying
for that. Uh-huh. Go ahead. Everybody tell you can, it's a confession here. Go ahead. Tell them.
I am still paying for Ubisoft plus. I forgot to cancel it and I still paid less for far cry than
you did. But I didn't look like a geek with all the, I paid for the items shit. So who really won?
Oh my God. I had like, help. I have neon. I have neon armor. Are you really, are you going to help
me with a knife? Holy shit. Okay. Wait, there's herbs. Don't forget to pick those up. I got them.
Do you want me to craft you a heel? Um, what's like the, is it an eye? How do you get to the
inventory? E. Okay. What the fuck is this inventory? I don't know how to scroll over.
How do you go down? Oh, it's mouse wheel. Okay. Mouse wheel and what's on the, what's down the
bottom? What's all this weird shit here? It's probably like, uh, actual usables. Oh, okay.
Like materials up top, full product down below. Um, all right. That's probably the, I really
don't want to be like a dick or anything. And I hate to say this. This is 2012. It was a different
time. They were doing the resident evils had the same UIs since like fucking 1996. So I don't buy
that. They were trying to get creative. They wanted everything to be in game. This is a fucking
horizontal metal gear, solid inventory and a holy shit. I hate that inventory system. I'm sorry.
Oh yeah. No, it's bad. It's bad. You got any dual wield? Okay. How do you do that?
Just a melee. Holy shit. I said a diamond cutter to somebody. I literally just RKO that person.
What? That was awesome. Yeah. Do it again. Um, no reason for me to waste any ammo.
That metal gear. So it was an amazing game. I just, I don't like the inventory.
This is a three shot double barrel shotgun. No, it's a triple barrel shotgun. Oh, incendiary
grenade. Cool. Go to the security gate. It'll lead you off the campus. Go. Resident evil five is the
Mona Lisa of video games compared to this. Um, well when Mona Lisa of video games,
but when you have to understand something, this is like, this is the same tier of games that come
in the cereal box. So that's not fair. Well, you can say, he said, first of all, I want to know.
I've seen Mona Lisa in real life and honestly, it wasn't that impressive.
It's smaller than you think. What the fuck? Yeah. Okay. There's like a spam button. Uh,
PT. Sorry. Does that hit me? Yeah. Body is falling apart. And I actually can, I want that.
And I picked that up. The sledgehammer that just disappeared. No, I don't think you can.
That's an unforgivable sin in video games when there's items that people are using and you can't
have them. You've just played too much, uh, dead rising. It was unforgivable. If there's a swinging
animation that the character is using and that falls on the ground, it's an actual, its own object.
It's a piece, it's a placement of graphical input, unity, whatever it is. If it was made with unity.
No, I'm just saying like if it's in the engine, then why can't I use it?
I want to fight with balloons and this flagpole. Why can't I use that? Graphical and input unity.
Graphical input user. How do I get to the grenade? Is this a college? G? It's not G. Does it not look
like I am doing some kind of like stage dance when I run? Okay. You stand, no, no, stand right
there at the door, but like turn around. I can't. I can see everything you're doing though. Okay.
Hold on. Am I, am I off screen? You are off screen stage left for me. Okay. Hold on. Does
it's like the, the motion of my arms, not. You just look like you're running around.
I'm so patiently waiting for you at the door. I'm just looking. I see everything you're doing,
but I'm not going to acknowledge it for some reason. This is so normal that I'm just going
to give you a minute and then you're eventually going to come over here. Okay. That was very
normal. Keep that trigger finger ready. Okay. There were no, what's around the next corner.
Wait. Okay. Ammo. We stopped doing that. We need those to like distract them. No,
cause we're, this is a fighting hall. We're going to try the door. Something's going to be jammed.
We're going to turn around. They're all going to come to life and we have to fight out the door.
So Alex, it's just going to open. Watch. Oh yeah. Then again, the door's locked. I told you I called
this a hundred percent. That's corner pocket. All right. This is, which is, this is just literally
like left for dead right now. All right. Skill points. Just wait till they come in. Who cares?
Don't even shoot. Actually, we probably should shoot them. I mean, yeah, they're going to,
they're going to commit. How was it? You half your head has gone. Wait till they get in at
least so you can get skill points. Just threw a bottle at me. The melee is better than shooting
a gun. I'm just telling you. I'm tripping over their body.
The Bailey's better. I have a shotgun. If I can upgrade this, I will. Why am I just falling down?
Okay. But an FOV is actually pretty bad. That person just,
okay. So this is what you're talking about. The X pick up the X and you pick it up.
Wow. Sick wrestling move. You're going to die?
What just happened? Did you just kill me? You just hit me in the face with something.
What'd you hit me with? You shot me in the head. You shot me directly in the face.
I'm dead again. What's happening? Where's my health meter?
You died again. But wait, we're dead. What? I feel like this is an arcade game we've put coins into.
It's like deliberately shitty and bad and hard. We'll find out where the checkpoint is,
I guess. Oh, it's right here. It's right here. Keep that trigger finger ready.
Know what's around the next corner. Oh, foreshadowing. By the way, that's totally
Levi. Probably is. There's a stamina meter. Okay. So the right top bar is health and the bar
underneath that is stamina. All right. We know what this does. Let's skip this.
We can't skip this. We have to live it. And again, the door's locked. There's no way out.
Zombies don't know how to do that. I'm it's so dumb. Like zombies that like dodge,
like juke a bullet gun shooting at them. It's like that's stupid.
I don't know. Maybe the first 45 minutes. Okay. Well, prepare yourself.
Are you prepared? What's that from? I don't know. Oh, you didn't play any of those.
Yes. You're right. Yeah, I'm good. We probably should like just stay back.
Just stay back here. You're too close. They're surrounding you right now.
It's surrounding the cool melee. We just have to live. We're in veteran. You made us do this.
Yeah, it's not even that hard. Okay. I'm not the one that died. How do I throw a grenade?
Holy shit. What the hell happened? Her head. But her head like melted off. You like slowly
simmered her head until it came off. That was like, like a tender like pork roast.
All right. You got, you got it. Reload it. Concentrate.
Kill points. It's like actually a hundred lootables on the ground.
Yeah, I know. Get rid of the Diablo to this. Nope. What? Sorry. You wanted all that stuff.
Oh my God. Are you kidding me? What am I supposed to do?
I think you just WASD really fast. I want to throw the grenade.
Fortified windows of that hallway could not hold them. This single wooden plank will.
What the fuck? How? Why can I not? I don't know how to pick up the grenade.
Define pickup. Like it's in your pocket already. It's F. What the fuck? First A. Oh, okay.
All right. So I have it. Cool. How do you like, we need to get the key card.
Yeah. How do you equip a heel? Oh, you have to manually do it. Press E. And then click it.
Combine with R for some God forsaken reason. Well, because you, one of each color is a mega
herb. So combine this with, I'll do this with red. So that's a, I made a six. All right.
You also then have to highlight the herb. Yeah. Press space, then press space again to store it
in your case. And then once it's stored in your case, then I don't know. It's gone. It's there
though. I was just, I almost just threw away bullets. All right. Um, there's also like,
you can hold Q to turn the entire game. Press one. Oh, what the fuck dude? Don't say that. I
just made an herb. Why did you say, what are you doing? Don't tell me to do that. What the fuck?
Are you healthy now? I, I already was. I'm not pressing two. There's something here. Oh,
free stuff. There's a key over this way somewhere. Oh, nice. Not alive. They changed.
They changed it. When's the next rock out break? I just want to chill. Um, this is not a thing.
This is not something you can pick up. I just opened this drawer. That looks like an item that
you put in a door resident evil style. Right? Why, what, what is it? Why can't we not
collect serpent? I just broke it. Oh, that's the thing you destroy and you eventually get to
unlock stuff. Okay. Okay. I don't do the rock outs anymore. The last time I did it,
the rock outs. Yeah. Just like, I used to do this thing where I would just like put a song on and
like air drum and shit, but people thought it was like we could cringy and I got a lot of shit for
it. So what are you doing down there? What the fuck was that? Oh, okay. There was a zombie in
this room. I, I just stabbed. I just stabbed him in the face. Why am I? It'd be nice if I had a
heel. That'd be fantastic. Oh my fucking God. Whatever. Okay. So we're looking for a, uh,
we have to escape now. We're going to go this way through the fridge, through the refrigerator,
secret trap door fridge. Nope. You hold Q, you hold Q. Yeah. You get, you get a little thing where
it shows you where to go. Nice try. Nice try. Their bodies are still physical objects even
after they're dead. So hang on. No, I didn't touch them. Resident evil does the thing.
He's going to get you. Shoot him. Thank you. Well, you call it out. What have you ever played a first
person? You go loading, you go reloading. E3 has already happened. I don't think they're going to
do the Ubisoft thing on the game awards. That's literally the worst thing they put in the game.
It's like the, the like super smash brothers brawl trip that they put in here for no reason.
Why is it in the game? What? All right. What is happening? Comic book falls. I felt like I had
so many times. Yeah. It's resident evil. I'm just going to be spamming R like, look, it's just
hit our, our, our, our, our. Nice try. Cause this skill points on the ground.
It's the room we were just in before, right? We can pick this stuff up. Yeah. Did you,
did you not, while we were walking back through, I kind of wait a minute. So you,
so you picked everything up already. You see a single thing on the ground. No, I did. So I
think we do have separate stuff. What if, what if, what if one of us picks it up and it gives it to
both of us, but also I have a shotgun. So you're not going to get like a shotgun ammo. I love
sandwiches like this, like the triangle sandwiches at like a party. Did you know
that all sandwiches can be triangles? If you just, if you just cut them the right way in half.
Yeah, but that's fine. But I'm saying I like when it's that style.
I did not, I did not purpose that by saying all sandwiches are triangles.
Yeah. But you said I love this kind of sandwich. Like you could have that every time.
Yeah. But it's a kind of pain in the ass sandwiches do taste better if you cut them in half though.
No, I hit you. They're very good. I love sandwiches. Sandwiches like probably one of my top three.
What are you doing? You still over there? I can't see what's going on behind me.
I just know that you're in some trouble. I'm just a one V wanting the strongest blue collar
zombie in the entire game. I can't, I actually can't get out of this. Oh, there we go. There is a
stamina. What about what are your top sandwich shapes? Um, sub role probably number one. Sure.
I'd say also up at S tier is it's a euro a sandwich. Um, yeah, probably. Okay. Probably
for this argument, maybe you just walk through a metal detector. Well, we're going to put our
weapons in there. We can't like, you have to go through it. Oh, we got to run. Oh,
that's what I was getting. This game does the thing like an unforgivable survival horror sin,
where there's people who you think are not alive. Oh my God. That guy hit me in the fucking head
with that axe. Why does my entire screen go white and blue when that happens? What is going on with
me? But that's when you got hit. I don't know what happened. I got hit with an accident. Am I dead?
Are we like symbiotically linked or something? Why? Why do I feel your pain? Because my entire
screen flashes white and blue and it happens to you. I don't know. Is this specific rimming
right now? Are we, are we, uh, getting drift compatible? I need to heal. I have a red,
I still don't understand what I'm looking at here. Okay. All right. This is the third,
that was the third try. They give you zombies on the ground, but you're not allowed to shoot them
until the game lets you. Oh, I see what you mean. Right. The play dead zombies, but you could in a
bunch of other survival horror games, you can, if you shoot them, they go and die. Yeah. Yeah.
I feel like we've been watching the trailer for this game the whole time we've been playing.
I feel like we haven't started playing. It's a long trailer. Watch out, watch out, watch out.
What the fuck? Oh, he was a fucking hunter from left for dead. I don't know how many more of these
I have. I have an unlimited number. I need to eat more of these like pills.
How much do I have to eat? Wait, I have a grenade. What's the grenade button again? F.
All right. Watch out. What the fuck, dude? I'm dead again. I think you're shooting me with the
shotgun. I did a kick. I did like a melee to try to help you. The top bar is your health.
Don't shoot me, please. Watch out behind you. Do I have any more pills?
Just go, go, go, go, go. Just go, go, go. You all right? Oh, that was a big, that was a big
jumping somersault to make it to the car in time. How do I drive?
Are you sure? I'm looking for the keys to the car. Yeah, find the keys. They're breaking in.
They're not in the glove box. Why is this door the fucking explorer? Like, where are they?
You turn the windshield wipers on? Are they? Look up, look up.
Gamers never look up. Oh my god. I can't help you. I am a spectator in this hellscape.
We drove, we drove 10 feet. Oh my god. All right, everyone's buckled. Can I drive the car?
I'm like in the, I'm like above the middle console right now. I just got to get through town.
Made it off campus. This is actually like a realistic college simulator. It's the RA.
Okay, so that was, that was fun. We're dead. Shit. What are you doing, man? Don't put the
bong under the covers. What if he looks at your bed? Helena, are you two all right?
All right, hang on, hang on. We need another way to the cathedral. How do we get out of here?
Turn on subtitles. Did that work? And then the really funny thing happens where like,
I took a huge hit from the bong before. I thought you were gonna say shit.
Yeah, I took a huge shit before the RA comes in. Oh my god, it's cleaning day.
No, it's cleaning day. There's a huge shit. I can't flush it. We have to go to,
you're disgusting. Stop it. Um, like the comedy movie thing where like I take a huge bong rip
and like the RA knock, knock, knock at the door and then I have to hold that in because like,
oh my god, what if the comedy smoke will come out of my mouth and will he'll know?
And then you do like a huge guffaw like, like right after they leave.
Yep. You stole that joke. Okay. Every joke is stolen. It's called life experience.
What's the matter? You stole that.
Matthew Mercer is the voice of Leon here. Yeah, it's him. It's been confirmed.
I would want, I do gotta have some shades there. I hate that when the sun's just beaming through.
You gotta get the glasses that have both little flip ups.
Holy shit, it would suck to be in this room. Yeah, honestly, they need to fix the electricity
in the White House. This is unacceptable. Natural lighting only. He's old enough,
but he would definitely be one of those like, turn the lights on or you're going to like
burn your eyes out trying to read that book. You know, my fucking dad's stuff.
Natural lighting is based. Yeah, that's what every magazine told you. And then you actually
have it. And once you get so much natural light into a room and like your head hurts.
Let's get moving. We don't have much time. Certainly got our work cut out for us.
Oh, halogen lamps only. I know. No, I'm not those either.
Florescence. I have just like those, you know, those like fluorescent bulbs that the long tubes.
Yeah, you know, the ones that go
Yeah, no, they're all of my whole movie lights. Yes. I like my house to maintain the abandoned
warehouse. Look, we'll be at a contact. I know exactly what you mean. Actually, I need heels,
but be careful. Oh, hold on. I think I figured it out. So the the number of the dots that are on
the herb is how many times you can take the pill, right? Is it? I think that's what that means.
He finally gets it. This is a dumb feature. Yeah, like, okay, the number at the bottom
right with the green leap. What's what's your number? Zero. I have nine. You do? Uh huh.
Can I have one? Yeah. Can we actually trade or no? I was about to unload the whole clip into your
head. All right. Let's we need to go to the cathedral. Taking the train to church. There
is no sprint. Yeah, you're right. There's no sprint. I'm just I'm just like twice as fast as you
deal with that zombie. How do I do it? What's sprint? It's space. Why is it space? That's right.
Why is it space? Why? Why is it space? Exactly what I just sounded like. And I did that for a
funny comedic joke thing. So you got it. Chad voice. Watch out. Watch out.
You got to save bullets. Watch out behind you. Watch out. Actually, let's just keep going.
Yeah. Why? There's no reason to stop. There really isn't.
All right. How do you heal? One. It'll take one pill and you can take one pip. You heal. You heal
one pip at a time and I think you can just spam it. Oh, there's a train coming by the way.
Space plus R.
I was hitting space and D. Space and R. What is it? What do you mean R? Why is it? Oh, that's
reload. I don't think I got it either. I think it just clipped you first. Space and hold on.
That's the canon ending. The thing is, isn't space and D dive? Why is it space and R? All right,
just run. How do you tell like this story by the way, like Leon, the professional zombie hunter?
All right. Space plus R. I swear to God, I did it. I actually did it. I don't get it.
It's because I have the script. I have to tell that story. Helena is a survivor in one of these
timelines. You go find your family. Oh, okay. Well, you do it. You do it. I did do it. Space
and R. And I think my script that I have is fucking up this whole thing. Okay. Space and R.
Okay. I got it. I was doing like space then R. No, I wasn't doing it at the same exact time. I
tried to, but dying restores your health. Oh shit. It actually does. That's a strat.
There's a zombie dog. Where? Dead, dead ahead. Oh, well, do we know if it's friendly?
It's got red eyes. He could be barking at somebody behind us. I, okay. Yeah. Oh my
jeez. He's probably barking at the train. Okay. What do we do with the skill point stuff?
I have no idea. Why are you guys doing this? They're attacking us. It's like a mutated zombie
dog. I did it. I released the pathogen. Well, who's something going on here? Why are there
so many people in the subway? That's the question. Oh fuck. I think I killed that guy.
What do you mean? There's a train. Oh my God. Okay. I don't, I think we, maybe we could have
saved that. All right. You have so much health. Let me take this one. Take what? Get high. You
guys should get high. No. Is that why they have so many herbs? Well, they want me to be high,
like in play. And I, I have, but I have sworn that off forever. Ever since I couldn't read the
analog clock on camera. Oh, good shot. Why is that one on fire? I think, uh, yeah, I think we have
to turn that off. Um, what, what happened? What did I just get hit with? They're throwing shit.
What do you mean they throw shit? They just get stuck and then they throw their, look, they
throw it again. You just hit the guy in front of them. Well, they're going to, we don't even
waste ammo on the guys in the back. Cool stuff. I'm just trying to conserve ammo because I'm
terrible. Oh, you can. Oh, so if they have a weapon, you do it for your finish move. It's,
I want to carry it around. So how do we, I'm so sorry. How do we turn that off? I thought
that was in the game. Was that, that wasn't in the game. That was a coffee leg kick up. Uh,
I think I, do we destroy it? I can't tell. I don't know. Co-op moment up here. Can I reach this
with the range? I think. Yeah, I can. I, I don't know why I don't know this about this game. I
feel like we still not playing the game yet. That's probably because we did not see the prologue or
the first cut scene. Is that explode? That's a red barrel. See, look, this, this is a pretend zombie
over on the wall. Yeah, I know. And we can't exactly see him now. You're right. Yeah, that's,
that's stupid. Was there anything in this? No. Yeah, I had something. Uh, use your knife so you
don't waste, uh, bullets. I don't have a knife. I have, uh. Okay. Come on. Are there items here for
you? Yeah. Okay. So we, we, we do both get our own stuff. Is there a train here? You go first.
It is, it is a rail. Yeah, but I don't know if it's going to be an immediate. Oh, there's a secret.
Is there? All right. I got it. I got this. All right. So we're a hundred percent in this or else,
how many gifts ups? Um, zero. Careful. Okay. I'll give you a, I'll give you zero gifts. So do you
just see how far you can get over the electricity? No, I don't know. No gift subs. No gifts. That was
the point. Yeah. Is it zero shadows? Yeah. Do you have grenades? Oh, I don't moving in humanly fast.
And I, I mean, even for like zombies. They are. All right. Is there a barrel? Does that explode?
All right. I think we just have to run, take out the first. Yeah. We just run, just run, run, run,
run. They are really good at predicting movement. Are you good? Oh, you don't look good. Are you good?
Are you good? I'm good. I'm just waiting. You're most grumpy. I'm not a grub. What are you talking
about? I'm very, I'm happy right now. This is train coming, train coming, which would from its
wrecking. It's behind us. It's behind us. It's behind us. I didn't get a prompt. What?
I think you have to be looking at it or no, you get to be on the other side of the track.
There's two tracks. Where's the prompt? Oh, we didn't get a prompt. It's been giving us prompts.
Whatever. I was sitting there waiting with, I was, okay. I was hovering. I was hovering my hand over
space and are just ready to press it. Yeah. I was too. You're not going to get the collectible again.
Not even a real game. Oh, I thought, I thought we shared that. Okay. So now we just have to go to
the other side. Yeah. So just who cares? It's going to do the dumb puppet show where it shows
those scary things and we just run by it. This is a nightmare. I keep having this vision of you
getting splattered by a train at high speed. It trains on the other side. Yep. Okay. It's definitely
going to switch. So just stay in the middle. What happened? Why? I think you got caught in
between the cars. I did not. You went into the middle prematurely. Hold on. Too much air just
came out of my fucking mouth. It was so stupid. Honest to God, I'm not, what happened? I did not
even come close. The train was already by dude. I swear to God. It was like over halfway by.
That's so stupid. This game sucks. It's the cut scene trigger. Yep. But that's the best part.
But I did not understand the cut scene trigger was going to be here. Right? Like right on the
edge. The train is like a boss and you can touch the boss and you die. No, the hitbox is huge.
I'm telling you, just stay really far to the left. The hitbox is monumental. I want to know
what it looks like when I get hit by the train. You might see it because the hitbox is huge.
Okay. Now we can just, I thought it was going to happen again. I thought it happened to you.
Apparently this is our ride. Okay. Very good. Can't open it. We're not getting that open.
There's a illuminated latch on top. Boost me up on top. Somebody just said I've got stuck at this
part for 45 minutes. Good luck. I can't wait. What the hell did I shoot you? Yeah,
directly in the fucking back of the head. The shotgun spread is insane.
Also, I can't believe friendly fire is on by default. Okay. Are you going to boost me?
Hold on. I hate this inventory. It sucks. Okay. So click on this, say send to, how do I send this
to my? You send it to desktop and then you're going to want to right click, zip it, and then
email it to me. But how, how do I do that? You're a hater. I hate this game. Well, who can, yes.
It's space. Okay. How do I get up? I'm not grumpy. I hate this game. What, there's a difference.
I'm just kidding. I like this game. Okay. So there's, why can I not send this to my inventory?
It doesn't say I have one heel. Mannequins that are definitely come to life.
Open this. Did I just use keys? I think I have to wait for you. Yeah. As soon as I dropped in,
keep your car. Oh, nice. Here comes a rage stream. Watch out.
Maybe those ones are actually. I tell you guys that somebody said that they heard that in a game
and they like freaked out that sound. They heard that sound that I always do. And they were like,
it fucking ruined the whole game for me. I couldn't even play it again. What quiet screaming? No, the
you didn't. Why would you tell me that? That was, was that the whole story? Someone played a game.
They heard that noise and didn't play it again. Yes. No, why would you tell me? I'm talking to
all of you. Not the only person here at town is like 150,000 other people here.
Watch out. They like the meltdown animation. The sludge zombie. Yeah, that's crazy.
Be careful. Be careful. Give me, I need a minute. What are you guys talking about?
There's a raid. Are you lying to me? I can't. Probably the most realistic bit about this game
is you have to do everything on your phone. Is there actually a raid? I can't see it.
Mod. Tell me the raid. You know, that actually looks like, um, who is that actual raid right now?
I need a mod. Blade Runner 2049. Uh, Lala land. I don't know. I don't think there was. That's
Ryan Gosling. Okay. That's all right. I got, I got lied to. Tell me that's not Ryan Gosling.
I see, I see Jared Leto more than Ryan Gosling. Yeah, I see that too. It's the hair and the,
and the mustache, but the face is Ryan Gosling. What the fuck happened? The guy was camping with
an X. It's just, they're just gas lighting you. Okay. Because you're using this gas can.
That's my, that is my name. Yeah. I swear to God, this is going to turn on. Isn't it?
Here comes it. Are you ready? I'm ready for space R. The train's not turning on. I mean, it's on.
No, we're just going to have, this is actually the matrix subway station. So you got to do
the backwards. That's a, that's a person, right? I feel like I fell asleep on the couch like this
last night. And that's like my whole body hurts now. Like this is how I slept. I hate that. I
fell asleep before the stream woke up and I'm like, like you said, there's no chapter.
It's got like a bomb. We're in like an extended trailer for this game. How do you switch to bomb?
It's a weird combination in the inventory. I have no idea. Cause I can see it from mouse wheel.
It's like E then like F or something. E, E. You can throw it away. So be careful.
There's literally a way to destroy it. Oh, okay. It's F and then F, F. Oh my God. This sucks.
Asshole. F is scroll vertically. And what'd you just do? You just put down, get away. Don't you
dare. Don't do it. Well, can you pick it back up? This entire station hostage. Just pick it back up.
It's fine. As long as you don't press the button. Shoot me. My like death reflex may accidentally
trigger the bomb, but you don't know that. All right. He's dead.
No, now you have to heal. We did it where I'm veteran right now. No, you can't do like
comedy references. It's okay. I got some. I thought that was part of the cut scene.
Come on. We're going to pull this all open with our bare hands. Oh, you idiot. You idiot.
You idiot.
I didn't mean to use that many. Use it. Use a bomb. Yeah. Use a bomb. Somebody's
for something in my face. Watch out. There's like a spitter. Watch out. Plant a bomb.
All right. Watch out. Yep. I didn't even see it. Cool guys. Don't look at explosions. I saw it though.
It's very cool. They're alive. All right. The worst part is switching guns. The entire gun
inventory like crosses over the crosshair. Like if you mouse wheel while you're aiming down sights.
I mean you can just say it. You can just say it. It's this game is actually not as bad as
everyone said it was. It's awful, but I would not give this an F. I'd give it like a D so far.
I would never. I would never recommend this game to my friends, but like if somebody. Yeah.
As far as like co-op games though, there's just a lot of. You can reach the street level from there.
What are conditions like up there? It's the worst Resident Evil game. It's gotten pretty bad.
If you don't like this by yourself. Yeah. This is not a game I would play solo Resident Evil.
Oh, let me turn you up. But like that. A person using the turnstile and then just leaping. Yeah.
It's fucked up. That's good content. I have no idea. I don't even know what you just said. I
just said that's fucked up after what you said because I wasn't paying any attention. I thought
you're talking about like the zombies or whatever. I was trying to fill dead air while you were in
the settings again. I did the thing where you're like on the phone and like you're just talking
to somebody and you're like that's fucked up and you don't even know what the last sentence they
said. I was talking about diapers. It's fucked up. You two will have to cross that. It's crazy.
What the fuck dude. Save him. Whoa. You can continue on. I guess. Did I punch you again?
Yes. Shoot the thing on the back. Shoot his back. Oh, a bishop. Thanks. Space R. Holy shit.
Okay. I got it. I'm good. I feel like this is just a bad feeling about this.
Okay. Those are not zombies. This guy. Get out of here dude. Run. I don't know. Why are you just
waiting for one of them to do like the thing where they're running and holding their asshole like
they're going to shit their pants. Okay. I haven't heard that reference in like four years. Just like
walking really quickly, holding your butt, shitting your pants. These are just two people
who lock themselves out of the trunk. And why the fuck does that happen in any movie or TV show?
You know what I'm talking about? Like why is it like a funny reference? Nobody like does like the
quick walk holding butt. I've never seen anybody do that. You got to be the the visionary. What is
this game's fucking broken. Just keep going. You weren't allowed to shoot them yet. They
were doing the cinematic thing. We're going to help this guy. Okay. I'll cover you.
Oh, both of us have to help this guy. Use your motherly strength. Oh yeah. This is GTA.
That was a stream sniper. What the fuck? We don't have time to deal with this. We need
ammo and shit though, dude. Yeah. So that's why they first of all, there's a military zombie
with like an assault rifle and they are shooting at us. This is too loud. Everyone always asks why
I might. The zombies have guns now in there. Oh, the zombies have guns. That's what it was. That's
why everybody hates this game. I remember I'm first. I always have the game really quiet
because that's easy to pay attention. I feel like my game's loud. I think my game is a little too
loud. The audio is good. Oh, perfect. I have, I don't know. You should. Okay. I have one bomb.
You want to put it down there? No, no, no. You just got to jump across. Okay. I couldn't put it down
there. Well, see if I can kill them. They didn't work. It did hurt me though. Why did you have a
cut scene? I didn't. You just kind of like leapt across. Okay. All right. That was all right.
What's wrong with my camera? I'm like permanently left-handed in this game because my
camera gets reset every time we do a co-op. Yeah. You're hitting caps lock. We got to run.
Ron, this way. Okay. Ron, Ron, do you know that guy? I've, I've, that's fine. We're good. What the
fuck is happening? I didn't even want to do that. Get up the ladder. Artists spend a lot of time
on these custom kills. Who, who got that there? We just like, I don't know. We just fucked up
somebody's car. Go. What the fuck is happening to me? What's going on? I just got lit up through
the grate. I can't move. I don't even understand what just happened. Why can't we get? Oh,
go. Now where? Over here? Okay. They were opening the new like path for us.
Leon is so cool. He's so cool. It looks like this way is blocked.
They're always so cool. A family of three just died. I guess we're not going that way.
And catch our breath. That'd be kind of cool if you could. I'd be really happy about that.
They should make a, they should make Resident Evil games like mini game games.
This should be a Resident Evil party game, like Mario party. What about Resident Evil, like
soccer? That'd be kind of cool. You can shoot them. What do you mean? Shoot what? I don't know. What
are you referring to? I don't know what he was saying. Well, yeah, I talked to the people over
here in my brain. The pool balls. Oh, you can shoot the pool balls. Did they do anything?
They're saying that it does. Oh my God. It works. Okay. So here's the thing. I got it.
My ball point. Oh, I was going to, we're going to call balls. And yeah, but if you play pool,
the person, if you, if you, if you get it, like I got solids, um, I've got the first one,
which is really stupid by the way, it went like it, that means that somebody can just literally
win and I don't get to play. Now I got to get the eight ball. If you get good at, you can get
to the point where you're, you physically don't. I should have just bet you something for that one
because that was pretty good. Wait, were you seeing pool balls different? Stop tripping over
there. Okay. There we go. Oh, what was that? Hold on. I want to hear that again. You said,
you said something very specific because alive is a gun client side. Uh, where'd he go? I'll go.
It's too scary in here. I'll go. Oh, I thought they were alive. Yeah. I was going to say they're
not even zombies. They are. They're going to stand out. There's one behind us. It's going to,
it's going to change to the fucking, to our Twitch channels and they're going to get up and
fucking flip out the man that'd be changed. No, these are people already watching our
Twitch channels. This is just what they look like. That's no, the entire city is on fire.
I hate that so much. So wait, do we, do we both get this? What do you mean it's locked? Find the
key. Kick it open. So where's the key? Oh, you have to, you have to carefully reach to grab the key
and then you not get grabbed. You, you want to grab key? I'll be ready. Tell me when you get it.
Going in. I'm going in for the sparkle. I have become afraid. We picked the wrong person to be
worried about. All right. We're good. Oh, I have, I have the key. There wasn't even an animation for
me grabbing it. Oh, come on. This stupid game. Of course, like you said, they are not real until
the game decides they are. Uh huh. Are you, are you healthy? Are you good? I'm not okay.
I need help. You want to talk about it? I need to talk about you having healing potions to give me.
I have four. Oh, a shotgun. Nope. Mine. Oh, you got it too. That's not cool anymore. I want my other
one bag. Do you have two shotguns? I do have two now. Yeah. Oh, that's kind of convenient. I think
we got the same one. I got like a triple barrel with no stock and then the, the tactical one.
Sorry. I have, I can't hear a thing you're saying. I'm a little screaming.
Okay. I want to use this combined with my backpack. Eat only one heel. That sucks.
Oh, this door's locked. Find the house key. Oh, this metal door is locked.
Kick their bosses. This is a boss. It's resident evil. You have to mix it with another herb. All
right. I see. Uh huh. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. He's just afraid of us. I got him. Watch out.
That guy's a bomb. They're coming in behind behind us. Why can't we just shut the door?
He's fucking head. Wait, I'm just going to play through the rest of the game like this.
What do you, why can I not trip over you? That's the weird thing.
Are they different? Okay. Is it just red and green herbs or is there more?
Uh, I've only seen the two so far. They're like the turkeys over here, wherever it is.
I'm not going to explore. Yeah. I'm not going near that. He didn't, he didn't explore. That
was anticlimactic. Yes. Red and green. It became a trophy. We have skills.
Hey, green. All right. I got to, we need to do a skill thing here. It hasn't been a quiet moment
to really do anything. It's just been like constant conflict. Are you playing house of the dead?
It kind of does have that vibe. Doesn't it? Yeah. It even has the game over when one partner dies
repeatedly. Oh, we got, that is absolutely a red barrel. I'm ready for it.
You, what do you, why would, I don't understand why you do that. That's you.
You were this close to saying you fuck. You were this close.
That was, that was, there's nothing funny about that. You just ruined our experience.
You didn't, no, no, no, you just ruined my experience because I wanted to shoot that
and kill some people. You just ruined my experience. No one's even there.
We're not even going to be over there. It's not how that is strong.
All right. So you just jumped down. What would have been right there?
That would have been great. Are you supposed to be doing something?
Yeah, I'm doing it. I'm doing it. You just got to stay alive. Pushing this giant heap of trash
as fast as I can. And I don't mean the video game. I love, I have no, I'm the guy with no ammo and no
health and I'm the one that has to take care of this. Can I go now? No, I'm still looking
for an exit. You're still looking for the exit. I'm actually just going to leave you behind.
That guy got cracked. What? I'm waiting for you currently to do a co-op moment.
What? I can't even get down the stairs. How are you waiting for a co-op?
How am I supposed to free you? Wait, hold on. Oh, right here.
Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up.
I'm helping.
Now you really got to help me. Okay. I'm coming. Oh, I can heal you with the number one instead of
pushing V. I've apparently been choosing not to heal you. What is? Okay. I'm going to run.
Do I have any heels? No, I'm not going to combine this. Oh God. Why is V back? Oh,
too green. No, I want to do green and red. Just do it. I want to a green and red though.
I want to do red starburst. I do. Those are the best ones. It's only three. What the fuck?
You look like you're passing out right now. I probably am. Your hands are on your knees.
You're holding your gut. Don't call me menu Andy. These guys really take a lot. They pop a lot of
pills. Come on. You have to help them. Are these survivors? Is this humanity? What the fuck?
That was the only non. That was the only NPC in the whole goddamn group.
Boo. He's standing in front of me on purpose. Watch out. The guy on the top of the guy on top
of the truck. We have to shoot. We have to shoot his like growth. Oh yeah. That guy that you
already killed him in like four bullets and then he screams and then what happens? I think we get
more. What the hell? I guess that ambulance came out of nowhere and ran directly into me.
That was that car was going 80 miles per hour. That was not even like 30. The car was going
100 miles. Can an ambulance even go like 150 miles per hour? All right. This time we're going to get
this right. Come on. We have to help them. Deus ex drivers. It's actually easier to be on the
ground. All right. So wait, are you not on the ground? It's easier to lie on the ground and shoot.
Okay. But watch out for the. Oh, please. Really? Oh, he screams at us. Here it comes again. Oh,
it got you. All right. Clipped you on the back tire. All right. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Cleric beast noise. Yeah,
it is going like I thought I was going to be out of the way. Oh, survivors. Come on. We have to
help. How do you do? How do you do this? Bad ass slide. Just stand over here. There's no reason
to be in that direction. Yeah, we don't need to save these people. They're fine. But we can.
We're going to get ambulance in like 10 seconds. Oh no, there really are. Take that guy out right
now. He's on top of right here. Oh my God. You idiots. I want to get all that stuff before
the cut scene gets us. I want to get, let's go quick. Oh, go, go, go, go fast. Oh, what's wrong
with my body? I wasn't even close. I actually wasn't even close. I was over near you. What the
fuck? I'm serious. That I was actually not even close. I was over. This is the Leon campaign.
So bad. I, you know, I'm turning on the fucking tryhard right now. I always think that's the
ambulance. I know. All right. Fuck that guy. I don't. Did you see that? Watch out ambulance.
It's already ambulance. Just go over to the left. Okay. All right. My goodness. There's more.
There's more inside and they have body armor. He's got guns too. Okay. We're good. When do we,
when do we actually pick skills? Shoot the gas. Wait, don't shoot it yet with this stuff.
It's like a, there's like an omega thing over here. Okay. I'm, I'm ready. What are the second
ambulance? I don't know, but all the NPCs are over here. So it's definitely this far away.
We're good. I think we're okay. Yep. It's safe. We're here. We can rearm there.
Probably finding more people there too. I'm walking like I'm injured, but I have full health.
I think it's stamina. I don't see any other options. Oh yeah. Well, I think I'm just being
dramatic. It's Alex. We've been playing this game for an hour and a half. Yeah. It's the same level.
I feel, I, I, my brain is stuck. But also I don't think turning the difficulty down would have
stopped the one hit train kills. No. I'll just take all of his cool stuff. Who does he think
we are? Exterminators? God. It's nonstop. So just want to make it really clear. We could have just
seen an entire Will Ferrell movie. It already played. Like one of the new ones or one of the
older ones? Probably one of the new ones. That's the ones I would have muted. All right. We just
have to eliminate enemies. Yeah. That's a, did you just read that off the screen? I would just
make sure we didn't have to go upstairs. You never know. There's no way to tell. Don't worry.
Somebody doesn't already have this window. Hey, there's probably at least three people
in one of the chats making some zombies. Cod zombies jokes here. I just want to say,
I know who you are at the Cola. This Cola somewhere did not laugh. Minus two.
Okay. I have the incendiary grenade. Oh, I thought he was breaking her neck.
I thought he was going to get like a snap. Um, what the fuck? I didn't. I thought I threw that
I had to throw the incendiary onto. I had full health. Not anymore. But I was saving you. See,
the zombie that was on you died. Very funny. Very funny. These are, these are enemies from
dead rising. That guy had a golf club, clubs, axes, hammers. Somebody said this game feels
like mockery. Are they like an art critic? What? He's trying to kill them. I think that's the gun
shuffle. Oh, all right. We still have to kill enemies. Is the car shooting at us? I'm so
panicked. All right. That, that, that zombie's neck just became stretch Armstrong for a half
second and by an ambulance. Yep. Why would you wait? Was he going to monologue? Oh, it turned
into a different animal. Oh, Peter. Peter was my favorite side character, but we can go outside.
Peter was my favorite guy dressed in summer Sims clothing. He's in, he's in venom is in.
Is he dead? Nice. I still have no health. Whoa. We should be pretty close. Are we alive? Can we,
are you sure we're not supposed to just leave? Does eliminate all enemies? Yeah. Yeah. It does
say that we can go outside. I wouldn't if I were you. That doesn't sound very safe.
You're a, please tell italics to watch his six. Elbow drop that zombie. Please tell what I watch
your six. Okay. Yeah, I got it. I got it. When do we get to stop doing this? Hang on. Is it,
is that the like six when you're high or like the six when you're not high? What was the analog
clock joke? Oh, I probably couldn't even do that right now. Wait, you had a lockdown button.
I think I picked everything up off. You're all right. He said to come up. We have to go
upstairs now. Hey, I accidentally alt tab. There's bullets everywhere. Do you need help?
You let me know if you need help. Do you need help? What are you shooting at? Oh, hold on. I
need to heal. I'm going to combine some shit. How do you get out of here? I like, okay. So there
was a lot of action going on. I accidentally alt tab. How do I use this? I tab back in and everyone's
gone. Yeah. We went upstairs, bro. Oh, it's this. Yeah. Oh, now the door's locked. We're safe. I got
some folks coming for me in a bus. Any minute now, make it on board. It's a straight shot to
tall Oaks cathedral. People are evacuating there. Heard it on the radio, but that's a big if it's
a shit storm out there. We ain't waiting for any stragglers. Okay. Is this, is this dude like old
man explaining to us how bad the situation is outside? He just started shooting at that guy. Oh,
what the fuck? Why would you get the shutters? No. What door do I look out from this with this
window right here? How? Why even shoot the gun? They get, they're all going to do it outside with
a flashlight just ran across stage 11. Somebody has out there with a light. I don't see any. Oh,
somebody is out there. Who is it? This is just the game. Okay. The game was not made for more
than four players, but we modded it and like ruined the whole experience.
That's one of the big red guys. It's so loud. It is. Yeah, I guess.
That actually would be kind of funny. Imagine having 10 people in this room.
This guy is kicking the shit out of me. Please somebody help me. The carnage is attacking me.
This lady is just her AI has stopped working. What are we huddling? I don't know who I'm attacking.
I guess I'm what the hell is going on? This is so stupid. I drop it in from the ceiling.
Are you alive? I'm dying over on the corner here. Have a have a mental. Oh, thanks. You'll feel
better. I guess I feel all right. I don't know that this guy's supposed to be closing the shutters.
Why? Why is there a drop kick? This is very strangely aiming. Oh shit. All right.
Finally. Oh, why did that take so long? I don't know. This game is not good. It's not good at all.
Were we supposed to do that? No, I think it's just time based, but it's like this is weird.
We all don't tell me to do that again. We did it again. No, we don't. What the fuck? I'm just
trying to be my inventory. Okay. Okay. Don't just run out of. All right. All right. I'm in the corner.
I'm not good. I'm going to help you up while the giant monster is breathing over. Where is
he? He's just stepped on my head, dude. Why does the entire screen just flash white? There are too
many people in this room for what we're doing. This is so stupid. I can't even get up. All right.
I'm just going to drop some remote bombs. Why is he running at me? In the stomach? Lead it back
over here. It's the guy from Saints Row. Yeah. Good work. Good work, officer. You guys aren't even
helping. Frank disconnected. We need to add skills. I'm stopping right here. Where's skill
points? Equip skills. Finally. I just heard something. I got you six. Where do you equip skills?
I think it's between missions. This has been the same mission the entire time. Okay. Hold on.
Let me combine some stuff. I got this. So I want to put this in my inventory. Okay. Shut up. Wow.
All right. Hang on. I'm combining some stuff too. There is one mouse wheel scroll between store
in case and delete from game. Yeah. I don't think you've had fun for a single time. I think I've
been having fun. I think we're having a good time. Yeah. This is the kind of shitty that you have fun
with. Yeah. So we made it outside. They're waiting for us. Not like Resident Evil 3,
which was just shitty. Yeah. Resident Evil 3 was pretty bad. It just didn't do it for anybody. I
don't think this is like watching the Far Cry movie on Netflix. We're going to help this guy.
Now let him fall. Help him up. I'll cover you. Oh, watch out. Another big guy. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. I didn't even want to do that. Why did it do that? I didn't. I swear to God. I didn't
want to do that. Do we both? Do we both have the same plan? Yes, we did. I think it worked.
Are you dead? Wait, where are you? I'm dead. Yeah, I did. Have a tic tac. Yeah. I keep eating
your tic tacs. Honest to fucking God. Why are you going for you? There's 10 people. Is this a bit?
No, he does 10 people here. Why do you have to attack me? I was all the way in the back.
Are you sure you're not doing like a see how long it takes to notice that he's the only one
shooting zombies? No. Oh my God. I'm going to die. It's bad. I'm going to die. I'm lying on the
ground. Just one more of those. I'm the dick that keeps asking you for tic tacs and you only
have like a few left and you don't want to give me all of them. Hey, can I borrow a pencil? Hey,
you have any gum? Can we go? I know you have two pieces of gum left and I've asked for two.
All right, let's get out of here. Do we have to go? I'm going to stay here and shoot zombies
forever because I have so much fun up on this roof. Get to the bus. They've been waiting for
us down here. It's about to have a new character. Well, you can tell this game takes place in New
York because none of these people have their own personal car. We're going to take public
transportation. I'm just going to I'm just going to pretend like I didn't hear it. Oh,
wait, they're sucking that guy out. Why can't I shoot this gun? I'm get you dead. No, I'm not.
I'm fine. Okay, but what did I just what? Oh, no. Oh, no. Back up. He was so close to me.
I did. Oh, give me a break. So excessive. We're going to crash immediately too. What's with the
end horror movies? People just driving a straight line into walls. That was that was one mission.
What was your accuracy? 64 percent. Oh, I was 79. Well, hold on. That's bullshit because you
had a shotgun. Rank A. You had a shotgun from the very beginning, which means you don't even
have to fucking aim. I had a pistol from the beginning. First hour was skewed. You had three
times as many pistols as I did. It doesn't matter. You have your shotgun will hit something. I have
to actually pinpoint the laser on people's heads. That's unfair. In fact, I think that mine's
probably better than yours. Okay, but that doesn't explain the extra nine enemies routed.
End game. By the way, can we just stop for a second and acknowledge that we apparently killed,
I assume, four hundred and fifty seven. What? Enemies in one mission. Is that am I doing the
math right there? Yeah, that's a lot. That seems like a lot. I don't think we did that.
I don't think we killed more than 30 or 40 people. 30 or 40. Maybe like 50. All right.
Hold on. Do we? This is literally a timer at the top. Can you hit? Okay. Oh, it's a timer for me.
Oh, we have to make sure we do this right because I don't want you to have the same
thing that I have so we can be different character classes. Okay. How many skill points do you have?
I have twelve thousand seven hundred experience. You got I got eleven three.
So even though I did more of the work, I got less skill points. That just means I did better work.
Okay. Melee level one defense lock on level two ritz Java killer. Slight melee damage is like all
points. Two of them are twelve thousand. So I'm like just shy of the big. I think I want crits.
You can scroll down. Oh shit. You can scroll. Oh, quick reload. Oh, greatly increases the strength
of your final remaining shot. I'm not going to pay attention to that one. The five removes your
targeting site, but increases your firepower. Oh, that's cool. Break free easily from enemy's
grasp. Yeah, that seems like that seems easy to pick. Oh, wait a minute. Hold on, dude. You
only get to have three of these active at once. Oh, yeah. There's a single player only one hundred
points. Okay, hold on. Wait, can I do a double? No. What does team up? No. Fuck that. There's a
lot of question marks at the bottom. Oh, that's single player only. Yeah, that's stupid.
Keeps your partner from helping you. Oh, God. Getting in the way. We have to pick weapons to.
Did you already pick your skills? I picked breakout, which I feel like was pretty useful.
Arrow pickup allows you to pick up an increased number of normal and pipe bombs.
Lone wolf field medic team up item drop increase. Yeah, you got to pick the item drop, right?
I feel like that's really important. Yeah. All right, we're going to be exact same build. Oh,
we're going to have the exact same build, but those are gimmies. But here's the thing, though.
It's that's really that's very useful. A lot get a zombie hunter level one. Yeah, but fuck that
lock on level one. What is it? What you want? Aim assist. Please shoot somebody. Please start
shooting people on board. I'm we're going to do this. We just killed like 500, 500 enemies killed
defense. I think I'll I'll try the lock steady's hand when shooting. Who cares?
All right, I'm going for it. I'm going to be Mr. Melee. Okay, I'm going to be crit. And
now this is locked because I used. Oh, god damn it. Whatever. Okay, I'm going to save my points.
I have enough points. All right, that's fine. Okay, let's go. Hey, I'm going to get item drop.
All right, ready? I think I'm ready. I got item drop breakout and lock on. I want the melee one,
though. How do you go to the next screen? Do you have to hit escape? I think we just have to hit
escape or something out of here. We're going to have to kill 70,000 people that an organization
This is a weird phone. That's like what people thought technology was going to look like
in 2012. You know, like we had just invented iPhones like five years prior. That's actually
kind of true. And then they did Google Glass anyways. You know, we all knew it was going to
fail, but they did it anyways. This is what graphics will be like in 2016. You know what
the difference in graphics is between this game and a modern game? There was no reason to go that
fast. It's just a person like I why what you just really wanted to show off that you're going to
ram this guy going like 80. We could have you could have just ran them over slowly and killed
them. There was no point to go that one guy and nearly drove us to our death. Yeah, there was no
reason to do that. All right, I actually need the alt tab to turn the volume down. So you got to
protect me. Okay, I'm gonna watch the cutscene first though. Hey, watch this. Watch this.
All right, protect me. Um, I don't have any bullets in my gun. Why is that guy floating?
This is making me sick. All right, I'm coming back in. I'm here. What the hell? Stop ignoring.
Are we dead? I think we're okay. Good job. Oh, here's another guy that said watch this before
he got behind the wheel. Why are they doing this? Why? Hey, check this out. See that school bus
over there? Watch this. Hold my beard joke. They just all go so fast. You don't have to go this
fast. What what if they're all like other players and we're their objective marker. So they're just
like driving and they think they're going to their objective but they're all beelining to ram into
us. Why are people saying I'm ignoring everybody? What do I do? What happened?
Read. It's important. I'm literally, I'm staring at the chat right now. I'm reading.
We're the main characters so that's how we survived and everyone else died?
Literally every other character is dead at this point I think. Read this. Read this.
Are you still the Among Us guy? Not anymore? No, not anymore. I'm the serial killer guy now.
Did you see that? Did I see what? Were you doing something like serial killer-esque?
No. So on the front page of all Reddit with 50,000 fucking upvotes. I'm not even kidding. 50,000
upvotes. Wow. They um. 50,000 upvotes. 50,000. That's like these three Reddit golds for the
first like top comment. Yeah um actually you know what if you don't even want to like breathe life
back into this just know that they put an image of me on the front page of Reddit somehow and it was
like every serial killer combined into AI and like people believed it and it spread everywhere. Did
you uh thank the kind strangers? No I actually screamed at them and said stop fucking ruining my
life. I'm just going to bury myself. Watch out this is a fucking Dark Souls enemy.
I am in a grave. I just drop kicked a zombie in a flooding grave.
I'm just going to I'm just going to play down here. These guys are actually pretty weak.
Are you are you stuck or are you can you get up? You actually need help or is this a routine?
Yeah. Don't take care of your business. That was that was from my stream. Oh. That was for you.
Oh that's right. You you've got to do some comedy routines for your stream.
That's because if you go down there you'll see what happens. Oh that is kind of funny.
It's not funny. I just got bit. Get me the fuck out of here. How do you actually oh um
lightning just struck. Okay we're fine. I sensed a disturbance in the force. Oh dad.
Because it doesn't it doesn't do anything crazy when I get hit.
Only when you do. I guess it's supposed to be like a hey your partner's in trouble.
Oh that's probably what it is. Did you get the emblem over the entire screen? I can't believe
you haven't seen it. Did you get the emblem over here? Maybe it's because I never get attacked or
die. Did you get the emblem over here? I did yeah. Idiot. The big the giant blue one. I got it yeah.
I got it like 10 seconds ago. No no that that was it. What how is that it? I think this is
lightning. Oh it's trying to scare us. I get it. When the lightning strikes we have new monsters
on the screen. Are the other monsters riding the lightning? I think they're just here when
it's to scare you I think. Is the final boss Zeus? I don't know. Can we get mythological
in Resident Evil? I don't I have no idea where this sits in the timeline. I have no idea.
Okay be more efficient with this because these guys actually take like three hits from a knife.
Oh thank you Vectro for the 20 immunity subs. Appreciate it now. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah one
two three yeah it's three hits with the knife. I was using shotgun bullets on these idiots.
Getting ready to speed run this game? I've been watching speed runs. I've become I've become a
huge fan of Mario 64 speed run. Do you need help? There you go. I literally watched Box Box get his
PB last night it was fucking awesome. Did he cut the sandwich into triangles? No I was gonna I was
gonna like gift a bunch of subs but like my credit card got declined so and he was like ended the
stream right after so I would look like an idiot. I missed every shot god damn it. I don't think
you were supposed to kill it anyways. Oh yeah we were. He's got the key in his mouth. I've seen
this movie. It could be chasing us. Where's the uh where's the drunk pirate? Where'd you go? I'm
right here. Are you doing like a your invisible joke? No no no I just I thought I saw the indicator
I didn't know if you were down here. Sprinting is like five percent faster than just moving.
Don't even attack. What's the point? Just go we gotta get the dog. What all right but that's like
actual zombie okay zombie apocalypse day 14 you just go outside your house you see a bunch
of zombies and just what's the point there's two million more like what's the point just
all right there it is there is go it's probably gonna run all right get that key
key hello what are you looking at get out of here me no this guy was just looking off my shoulder
is italics a friend or a foe foe absolutely 100 percent what which one oh 100 percent
fro oh 100 that and this is the reason why i don't have to explain anymore what the
fuck if i was a foe would i do this uh yeah i think so uh i said we run you got it i'm running
what happened i was doing some overkill you okay yeah i'm coming i'm running all the way back up
the winding path that guy it was so weird all right we're at the door of the cemetery
is this the haunted house portion of the game okay we're in probably pressing v nothing's happening
e press v what okay bye god damn it no one can revive you down there and the stupid what the
you can't attack anybody until they have this spawn protection is removed i what what is this
we met we're both running from the same thing no i'm in like a i'm in the mausoleum thing what
do you call it what do you call them there's a big stone what i can't go that way it's a maze
there's at least two blue he's got like i think he's a gut in my head there's two collectibles
what are you doing to me what the hell dude is that are you doing that why are you taking
like a disposable flash in my face is he coming back all right i think i'm about to save you
i'm at the thing i got it oh i need you
okay maybe i'm in trouble now what would that over here why am i why do i have your image
that's strange why am i seeing this over here
alay you're just like voice calming i got two screamers
i know over here i'm i'm working on it i can watch your perspective if you hold v oh
shit i'm all right oh come on don't even if you hold v hang on you're in i might be dead
i can help you i'm here i can literally throw a grenade over there i'm just running by how do
you see me you're on the map but i can hold v when i'm in the middle of the waiting for you
they are man you're a cypher sore eyes oh my god shut up leon thanks
this game is scary literally okay checkpoint you could have come back there and help me at any time
i was in my own problem i was stuck over there on the other side you were stuck
on the gates holding v and telling me about spectator but that's before that i beat you
in the race to get to that point because i just made my way through i was in a problem area as well
as you were i was hanging back so i can get more kills at the end of the mission
i have more kills than you and what if it helps you fucking sleep in my bro
hello it's in there look it's just us did you show something that sounds like i just swallowed
like a fucking bug okay there's a lot i think we just have to kill this really is the closest game
to house of the dead yeah yeah they they do the throw thing too i gotta collect items man i'm
just being i'm just i gotta get ready here comes company ready
what's that from and i'll give you fucking 100 i swear to god uh that was a good animal crossing
voice nope wrong i mean you were doing mortal combat at first that was saber wolf that was
saber wolf stuck in an ultra combo in killer instinct you don't get 100 i only played killer
instinct on gameboy how is that how did that kill me you're a furry jesus would you call me
get him away oh what what oh you're super dead what does that even how you know this game really
is it's just making us do waves of enemies this is not even resident evil this is just a wave
shooter this is the extra game mode to a resident evil game that's out they did do that like in
resident evil 5 that was the the multiplayer like what did they call it this is just a regular
campaign yeah this is a regular campaign okay well let's go for it again the special multiplayer
mode where you like do this look it's just us all right i'm going for headshots here
were you not before sometimes guys that are the people that are running make sure they go down
first like that guy all right i got an idea you take those guys out i'm gonna set up some bombs
i'm gonna set up bomb there you can only do one bomb at a time never mind i think we're all right
it's not very there's not that many don't get overwhelmed get ready here comes company okay
back it up now actually this is probably a good place to plant a bomb i did not want to do that
i this is i can't press any buttons you watch that way i'll watch this way i want to get up
but i can't left click okay i hope you're okay oh what the fuck that dude just fell off did you
shoot him are we just seriously for this one person the scream guys are coming in all right
i'm about to i'm gonna i got a bomb over there on the left side i can take them out in i'm going
for it i'm gonna blow them up right now he's on the ground nice job we did it dude you fell off
ratio whatever l l o l we good he's gonna scream are you okay i want why are the red ones drunk
i know they shit they shimmy around can we go inside they won't let us in until it's safe
i got bit three times reloading okay we're both okay i just opened the inventory
am i dead what happened i'm on the ground what did oh i tell them to wait run you have to run
there's too many oh no are you actually dead dead run though i did run i don't have any tic tacs
don't worry we got a checkpoint did we actually i don't think we did just kidding got him l plus
ratio hold on i we have to have a better strategy here because this is just this is not going to
work this seems too long have to wait till every single enemy is dead yeah have that let me get
this is not this is not there's no jokes in this scene we just have to win i hate that f is to do
that all right um it's okay no more messing around i'm messing around this is freaking stupid
what no stop what are you doing now what you doing my wellington no stop it
no gross what you doing what you doing my wellington you don't know what that is and
everybody everybody in my chat i don't know what that is no but you don't i know who gordon ramsey
no but you don't know what that is though i don't know it's his youtube videos no no no it's his
tiktok okay but he posts them to youtube oh does he yeah he posts them to youtube and he does a
review people send him oh you do know what it is you do yeah i do know i mean that's what he does
yeah he goes stop what you doing everyone the last two i watched though they did it like really
good and he was impressed was he actually impressed i never seen him impressed okay all right good
looks looks very moist yeah but then they put the m&m's in it and he goes no oh stop it what you
doing how am i gonna blow that up is it just me it was gordon ramsey like as he gets older starting
to look like daniel crick i think gordon ramsey is like one of the probably one of the coolest
people on television yeah i missed every shot i love the way gordon ramsey like talks with his
body have you noticed that when he says words you'll notice it he kind of bounces and his like arms
come up his arms come down and he goes like on his tippy toes down his shoulders while his like
facial expressions i love it to disdain i love his cadences they're so cool i'm not i'm not
kidding around all right be careful
all right guy with the bullfrog all right you have the bomb there let me know if you're gonna blow
it up oh shit you can knock the guys off the edges it's actually perfect you can shoot them
down yeah they're on fire it's good like they they drop their torch i mean like starts a fire
can i climb over there all right let them let them actually get over so we can get the items
because we want to make sure you get the items all right now wait you're still shooting okay
i'm ready i got i got i got a bomb right here oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i
would like to get more than one guy but i'll take not that kill do it fuck all right let us in he
said all right all right in in in in in in in in what oh what happened i can't see anything
i can't see anything he screamed are you all right
i'm gonna pass out i'm gonna pass out i think i actually might pass out
i might actually pass out i'm not kidding come to the door come to the door come to the door
come to the door i'm gonna pass out no you're gonna live right oh no man oh no oh no okay so
once you get raised off the ground you can't sprint i don't know so i have to jog
this is the whole game by the way i didn't find a level i did not ditch him i heard the call for
help i saw that he was surrounded by people i got over there i granaded and i almost passed out but
i'm okay yeah that was that was the last thing i heard is i'm gonna pass out it sounded like
it sounded like you tried to like make your trauma like more than my almost
okay buddy why did you almost pass out because i thought it was funny and like i didn't breathe
look it's just us i got really tense and then laughed and then like my brain was like it's time
for you to shut off we're just trying to get more gameplay out of this this is like a hundred
percent run today by the way we have to stay just stay back and just shoot from afar there's no
reason to even go for the whole thing was like keep them on the just forget about the loot just
shoot them and just shoot them and let them die you're walking in circles jump behind you
here comes company i okay here's the thing oh wait do i have any like herbs
i do i can combine this is game changer okay now we actually who gives a shit just kill them on the
other side i didn't have any tic-tacs before he better not okay you know you know no no no
fuck it fuck this where did that even go what where did that go you just shot me in the head
i did i was saving you from this guy watch out watch out watch out watch out i'm throwing a bomb
oh that was a good bomb with two bombs yes i had to do it all right now it's almost ready
teamwork make sure you collect all the items goodness heads gone all right this is where
we get just absolutely messed hold on all right all right just go and press now thank goodness
that was so bad to be fair the level we were just on is representative of the entire game so i mean
we could just pretend like those were different levels we could this game gets dramatically easier
if you're bad sorry guy rescue worker so which one of these guys is gonna say watch this and
drive the school bus with all of us in it and kill everybody here wait i think if you die
they reduce enemies on the next life or is that like just a meme down there i that sounds like a
meme to me i show you there were definitely no scream guys that time all right search the cathedral
okay question if you were in a zombie apocalypse and you were in this cathedral and there were two
people outside begging for help do you open the door uh well there's that that's very very much
very contextual based because it does this fake scenario if you're a bit do you get infected
uh i was open the last time i was here i don't know because the heroes get bit all the time
in this but when people get bit they turn right like if you're not a main character let's take
a look around i mean it's it's it's tricky i would say that you'd probably bring them in
and they they we'd have we'd make a place like maybe pile up a bunch of these uh church benches
and like put make like a cube that we put that person in and they stay in there for like a week
okay so we like quarantine people yes like even if at least like a day or two and look it's not
like we're gonna you can we'll feed you we'll make sure you're okay but like just to make sure
you don't turn in 24 hours all right uh zombie ethics question do you wait until somebody like
turns into a zombie to shoot them if they're guaranteed like infected no absolutely not
absolutely no this isn't just part of the decor because that that person can be useful until they
turn okay but do you tell them that you're gonna do it before you do it or or you like rip the
it depends on how their immunity is like right some people might get bit and they're
infected on their attitude like if they suck i'm just gonna do it right now if they're like nice
there's a lot going on i'll give them a little time there's a lot going on there i think but yes
if somebody is new they go into the just the cube will make like a little cube so like if they turn
to a zombie that it can't do anything and then after that and if it's like okay i haven't been
bitter anything i'm fine and we go all right soldier we like throw like a big gun and they
catch it and it's like okay geez where are you i'm at the co-op moment we're both at a different
co-op moment by the way oh are we oh i'll come over there literally the other side yeah the exact
same ladder well now what do you have to do i have the key item so i put the key item there
there is a uh over in like the weird um clock holes thing over on the top kind of right side
there's one of those we have to have two orange slices some some no two grapefruits
and if we put both the grapefruits the motherly smile will shine upon us and the path will be
revealed is really important in the old telephone like the old like 19 like 20s telephone up in the
top with like the good glasses there's one of those blue things to shoot shoot it okay up at
the top up at the top on like where i'm facing it's on your side it's above you it's on the
balcony it looks like an old telephone it's a big window with like big telephone holes
and there's a blue thing to shoot thank you now my uh achievements can be complete i have one
bullet it's not good all right so then you have to do the puzzle oh you have to knock that down
my son marco he's in the psaa so am i not supposed to be exploring these rooms you think you're
supposed to knock down like the candy cane ladder i think okay well i'm gonna take all the loot
first actually i might be able to i might be able to solve the puzzle actually no you have to pick
this one up no i can i can do everything it says that you have two it looks just like the other
statue the question is what are they for i did kick down one okay you got it yep yep but you
said this stuff up here so i want to get it i think we both have to put a statue on like at
the same time but on opposite sides okay okay i'm gonna go to this one so i am putting one here
as he that was huge we probably shouldn't have opened this isn't this supposed to be a safe place
this is the equipment i'm not gonna no i'm not gonna do it i refuse to
there's a scene in pop culture media from the not too distant past this reminds me of
well don't ruin the don't spawn anything all right just checking to save uh we got everything we can
go i mean uh a media property with undead where the heroes go into the belly of the crypt in
order to get away from the other is nothing it's not referencing anything how do you well how do
you dive all right it's like space we have to be aimed at we said i'm sick of you um uh there that
why is it i thought that was you that didn't i can't i can't shoot this no this is you do
i what am i supposed to do just dive what am i supposed to how what do i do about this can you
help what do you do i i'm stuck on the other side is there something you can shoot oh i think i can
just i like how your first order of business was to immediately blame me well i don't know
what now it's your turn you just you just saw me do it you now you know what to do
didn't even get hit once why did they both come out at the same time when that wouldn't have caused
some chaos in the comms like oh my god what's this oh you got it too oh this is shooting both
like we could have had a little pain yeah let me get a little yeah this games time for this all
right it's me versus you we're gonna see point scores i guess you can't decide that in the middle
oh yeah oh somebody got hit i see somebody got hit oh it looks like somebody's gonna get hit
twice okay get a fucking close-up stop me just keep moving why is the activation button suddenly
space when before it was always v for the entire rest of the game it's fair when do you are they
even happening on your side or am i the only one doing this no they're happening are you just
watching me it's probably gonna be three now okay now it's your turn okay that one wasn't fair
oh shit all right this one's this one's kind of unfair fucking move after yeah exactly
why can i hit this one oh got him get up oh uh-oh a little having a little trouble over here on this
side looks like i was fine until you came over oh my god dude oh the rule of threes
you gotta have three separate sessions of the same event the developers of this game played
too much mario okay we're good okay let's go who is he talking to i i have no idea
i think you have to aim at this i'm just one of the voices inside your head
watch out what watch out for what i think you have to aim this or do i have to aim this
why is it heating up uh i don't i think you have to aim it there's no way for me to move it
oh hey dude aim your gun at mine aim your gun at mine aim your laser at mine okay okay
why is it not working oh you meant like at the thing behind you yeah yeah listen uh
grammatically speaking the nearest antecedent you said aim your laser at mine so i was aiming
my laser at your laser and then our lasers touch your words are using it too big dumb it down
where are you i'm coming up there's a guy on my side i think i have to wait for you
why is it here can we not open this there's a there's a door there's a door but it doesn't
it doesn't have a prompt is there a laser oh yeah there is you're gonna have a laser on your side
uh kind of overlooking the did you throw a grenade at me did you did did you throw a
grenade at me just yes or no it's a very simple question yes okay your honor okay aim your laser
at the thing back there what over the look oh that way here no yeah it's not throw grenade at friend
and kill friend i'm just trying to increase my chances for the scorecard at the end i had like
full health too what the fuck uh yeah there's a dude again oh this one's a mirror oh my goodness
please just die dude all right so this one's a mirror yeah okay looks yeah so i'm aiming at one
oh yeah doing it right and we're free very good the madonna of sorrow this is no puzzles in this
game the rilling somebody said this is thrilling oh yeah and shit talking the streams yeah that's
a sniper rifle i'm gonna get the sniper if you didn't oh yeah yep did you shoot this
key oh you have to shoot something to open the gate for the key item or the bells all right so
you look like you got this down but to do them like all this this three they're fourth uh they
might be a fourth all the way at the end yeah there's one more down there is there even a bell
i don't yeah i don't see anything over there uh uh there's no there's definitely nowhere to go
over here it's a it's a secret hidden bell can we go up oh it's definitely there uh told the five
bells loud and clear and that's the truth i see it cheeky it's on the uh oops did that work where
is it spin i don't know if i just made this way harder to do oh wait is this supposed to you see
it is spinning this is that five uh not quite i think i shot the actual weather
vein instead of the bell and made it spin faster i think that's ringing is there a fifth bell
one two three four on the oh yeah there's one back there yep i know where it is i get it teamwork
it was another rooster feels bad man very nice somebody said god this game sucks
wait you don't like you don't like two straight hours of non-stop action followed by two straight
hours of puzzles no did you hear that it's perfectly balanced i think i want to be the
sniper of the group you can't you picked melee i got crit yeah i didn't unlock melee i said i was
thinking about doing melee but i could be sniper rifle actually i don't think you said i think you
said i'm gonna be the melee guy it's very definitive get the fuck over there and do what
you're supposed to do this is what you're supposed to do you can't shoot the chandelier down why
not all right you can be the sniper sniper sucks and uh also everyone's just gonna make fun you
know if you miss because the the shaky cam is is so extreme while zooming in it's actually not bad
did you turn your um turn your aiming down did she stop drinking so much oh boss okay so when
they listen i understand umbrella umbrellas everywhere but how do people trapped in ancient
crypt chambers get infected like this like that yeah but like nobody nobody had opened that
potentially for centuries you know i'm saying yeah we just did it so who put the zombie there
and then resealed it no no you're not you're not doing protocol put them over in the cube
first saving them put them in the cube rifles put them in the cube first that's protocol
no put what the fuck somebody just attacked me oh look up for the girl i'm actually on the ground
here's tic tac gotcha oh god i'm still all right i think i'm are you on the ground yeah i can't get
up i couldn't move he was standing right over us while i was healing you we just want to see
that death animation oh man well at least we'll have full health remember when you threw the
fucking incendiary grenade at me as a joke and took off six cubes of health maybe you should have
begun the inventory in the practice rules all right if you have a trypophobia you should probably
look away from this all right oh shit time to get some distance i'm gonna put a bomb down here be
careful i'm gonna try to get aggro hey look over here you big stupid alien hey clear comms clear
comms get over here where is it going why is it running away from us it's like up it's climbing
why it's climbing the stairs yeah wait why is it up there i put a bomb there's someone i did too
the other survivors are up there oh shit this guy over here this guy's fucked
i don't okay careful that wait right now which is like we're playing a moba
and getting pissed at the other players on the team for like not doing their job
i've got bombs set up in the middle of the church oh my god leave me alone
it's still up there what did i just do i have no idea what just happened i think i combined
something accidentally all right there's here bomb my bomb right here all right blow it up
he didn't go this way you you got aggro i got a bomb i got a bomb over here
it run towards me and i got one right here they're like climbing the stairs very slowly
all right come this way detonate the bomb excuse me what it won't press it won't press
oh my all right just move away that was such a weird scream it won't press it won't press
i got it i got it it's just like popping bubble wrap boss right in the stomach it's gonna scream
run no help me i'm on the ground okay i'm coming this is gonna thanks why is it making baby noises
why is it climbing again get down it's like a new puppy you're going to want to explore the
whole house okay we got it it was like a pipe organ of one person survived okay i honestly thought
an npc came up and looted the key item that would be so funny it just runs away make sure
we don't miss anything this is important their blood is on your hands no their blood is on this
thing's hands this thing came in we think about how many more people would have died if we weren't
here i just tried to do it all right it doesn't work do it i just i tried it doesn't work do it
okay how about um is there any sniper ammo anywhere yeah i just picked it up okay uh we
need to just leave very cool what about up top i'm checking up top too i don't miss anything
okay all right stuff died up here right technically it's probably it's probably
civilians that died i don't know if they drop anything by the way have you noticed any significant
increase in stuff that's dropped on the ground because i have not and we have both have that
perk i feel like it's not doing anything it's kind of hard to say it felt like there was a bunch of
stuff but that was also a boss fight so they kind of have to like litter the floor with things to
yeah not soft lock you all right we're uh ready to move perk does so little hard compatibility
yeah yeah hey come on don't miss this stuff oh there's a chest oh 4000 nice all right very nice
you're just gonna leave that person yes they're safer here than wherever we're going as the main
characters we have a magnet like attraction to progressively more difficult enemies they're
literally safer the further they are away from us have you seen all the vehicular explosions
and you need to be general chaos looking out for us right now i need to blow my nose
that's like peeing through your nose all right well i peed do you want to blow your nose we'll
take a two minute break yeah we could take we could take a pee break all right but if we're
taking a break then i gotta take the dog out okay uh five minutes ten minutes you can resident
sleep with me okay i'll be back that's all right i'll come back and just talk let me know when
you're ready right all right i'll be right back i'm gonna go pee uh it's fun i'm having a good time
i'll be right back uh warrior all right i think uh i wonder if he is back we'll find out uh are
you uh you back i don't think uh alix is back yet find out okay we have not been kicked out of the
game that's good dude you made a pecan pie are you serious hope it's good man oh by the way one
while there's a most people are here now tonight's the night nominations are opening up in discord
for the new year's eve worst of the year awards there's a bunch of categories this year some of
them don't make any sense and i have not done any of the things that are on the list but whatever
uh nominations will be open for about the next 10 days if you have something that's part of that
category that you know you want make sure you get it in the nominations and then somewhere around
december 15th december 16th we will put up the official poll and you can vote essentially all
the way through into the end of december so keep an eye on the discord over the next 24 hours that
channel will be up it will be very specific rules so make sure you follow the rules advertising on
my stream you're supposed to i'm supposed to be muted on you why am i even on your stream you're
supposed to have muted me you unmuted to talk yeah but i should be deafened on your stream
yeah but i turned it on in case you wanted to like i don't know
be entertaining or something i don't know that's not my responsibility what the fuck dude listen i
just oh all right i won't be able to force this one open now what's your favorite pie
uh put me on the spot depends sometimes sometimes it's key line but not often
sometimes whoa you're a key lime pie that's why it's a context that's actually that's very
surprising pecan pecan would be like always okay or pecan depending on your regional preferences
key lime is an interesting choice though i don't know if i'd put that up there
that's why i said sometimes we have to go this way somehow if i if i had like a coffee i feel like
key lime is pretty good key lime and coffee what the fuck are you drugs are you on uh all right
how do we get in there it's key key lime may just be like a leftover memory from like a nostalgic
like olive garden experience or something do they have key lime pie at olive garden
they probably do i was somebody's go this way somebody's in here you have to shoot a lock open
homemade key lime with graham cracker crust yeah that's that's a combo the key lime has way too
big of a range for me of being awful to being very good it it really varies sometimes i've had
key lime pie before and it just tasted like fucking acid it just tastes like it's great okay but we
have to weigh everything at their best right okay all right like pumpkin pie at its best is still
worse well hold on pecan pie i would have agreed with you but i recently had pumpkin pie and
it was cold it was not hot and i think that changed everything for me uh how do we what
are we supposed to be doing here can we shoot that we're supposed to be looking we can look
in through these there was the blue box that you broke over here that was just loot why would you
eat a hot pumpkin pie i don't know do you eat pumpkin pie hot who eats pumpkin pie hot because
like the only right way to eat pumpkin pie is with whipped cream on top like whip uh i just
pressed bunch of i just pressed a bunch of buttons oh there's a guy kill that guy okay you got it
okay how about now that one's open what's the one on the on the end you're right yeah there's just
a second guy his head fell off whipped cream is not gross why would you say that whipped cream is
amazing whipped cream is disgusting i am fucking pissed right now what i'm seeing that a lot i'm
seeing people that keep saying it it's because they're uh they're wrong is it what what do they
just want to get they just want to get try zero uh oh no we have to guess the number it's a
combination there's a zero one and two in different orders so it's not the two is not at the end all
right 102 this that's a bad guy uh i'll open the other one what was it probably 201 he was taking
he was he was on the pee break too all right they're all open yeah whipped cream is great
it's really light it can go with anything if he's dead or not whipped cream really goes with
everything how am i getting hit by your pistol right now i don't know nobody behind us right
no yeah there is one thing listen if i have to say something good about this game it's that if
they're gonna throw 600 enemies at least headshots actually kill unlike every other resident evil
game dude i okay real whipped cream is great i agree did i strike a nerve i think all whipped
cream is great i don't know what what's the hate to whip cream am i muted right now oh hey you are
you a muted for a second sorry what were you saying yeah i was just saying actually get the
thing the only right way to eat whipped cream is uh 60 40 ratio 60 percent whipped cream
okay all right it's oh it's two okay it's two i don't know two one zero okay we're gonna i'm
gonna help you the two is not at the end actually could be no it's definitely it's two one it's two
one zero yeah it is c what would you say like that like i didn't i wasn't disputing anything
no no i'm talking about chat too chat is really being they're saying that that whipped cream is
not that great real what's the best the best pie what's the best pie um it's banana cream pie
that's a good pie but you already know where i stand on this and it doesn't matter
banana pudding is superior no it there's no crust though don't open one something too don't open
one all right i'm gonna open zero two one i think that was the right one it's a banana cream pie
banana cream pie and um chocolate cream pie and my favorites okay i can respect the chocolate
cream pie what about one two zero these are gonna if we want to get the loot we have to open all
the doors okay well let's do it but let me put a bomb in front of the the big boys one what was
that about headshots a second ago oh he morphed chocolate cream pie actually dodged that's what
you're supposed to do i think don't worry i got this no i'm laughing at the fact that auto mod
is deleting cream pie auto mod does not want you guys to say that word apparently oh i come
listen we're not allowed to have whipped cream anymore we're not allowed to have cream pie
anymore we can't all the words are being stolen from us i'm so sorry mods i just i find that very
humorous all right two uh two oh one i'm gonna put a bomb right in front of this guy because
this is like big boy okay if you open that one i'm ready one zero two uh that opened up something
else it's not even where we are 102 okay is he coming uh here he's coming nice there we go
and then 201 or 210 what do you think 201 um he didn't die 210 okay hey i got a cut scene
problem hold on you're right wait you can take cover but why is what's the point is this mechanic
oh because we're gonna run into all the shooting zombies i do more than no well what have i not
done 201 what oh two one no i think no gates because that one on the left can be two codes
yeah it's probably it's oh one two that's all of them yeah banana cream pie is at the top chocolate
cream pie is at the top as well somewhere there but i would not pick pie as a dessert i think it's
like pretty low for me wow what about cobbler that's kind of gross whatever i don't think
that's i think that's gross what you just said cobbler like alamode um like i don't like fruits
i don't like warm fruit like people think i'm crazy but not like an apple pie that's why
alamo you get the hot and cold no no it's not that's just i don't like it i didn't know i was
i didn't know i was friends with a cobbler hater it changes the dynamic oh nice um yeah i don't
like apple pie it seems like a messier pie what pie just seems like a messier cake so where do we
draw the line but i don't like turnovers either though you just don't like you don't like anything
with fruit no i don't like warm fruit it's like warm fruit filling it kind of just reminds me it's
like a dog vomit or something candy apple it's like human puke it's i don't like it human puke
you have the appetite of a five-year-old because i don't like apple pie maybe you just haven't had
a good one okay apple pie is only good with ice cream but then so is cobbler and most fruit based
yeah but are we going to judge the merits of a dessert based on adding another dessert to make
it better i think if you allow whipped cream you have to no i don't think so that's a secondary
thing you have to then we have to judge everything with no whipped cream that's fine banana cream
pie without the whipped cream is fine oh wait a minute cream in it wait a minute it's actually
not yeah first of all it's not second of all it cream is in the name cobbler alamo is that's
that's a whole ass dessert why do you order five of those from mcdonald's i don't i don't
order five apple pies wait yeah but mcdonald's apple pie is good must be close a good banana
cream pie is important it's very simple to make but it's impossible to master people go oh i i've
got the best banana cream pie son have it and it's dog shit it's fucking disgusting i i've had ramsey
of banana cream pie i'm serious like yeah i've had banana cream pie that was like mealy and mushy and
it was supposed to be my secret recipe it was awful that's true what does tiramisu fit in this
um i like it but i wouldn't put it that high i think that's i think tiramisu and the banana
cream pie share a kinship which is a million different tiramisu exists but really like one
percent of them are are like 10 out of 10 but that's what i mean like it's it's really hard to
gauge some of these desserts because sometimes they can be made so poorly it's also it's also
like you know that's how i judge streams like 99 percent of them are shit but like the one percent
that are good you know those are the ones that get me i'll be talking about this one are we in
the one percent who knows time will tell i'm just waiting for people to
i'm gonna make them you can go ahead and make the don't make the joke if you want
germa for fuck's sake manage your inventory i don't there's an audit where's there an
inventory what are you talking about manage my inventory where over there are they pointing
at the screen i don't know that people someone got really mad i don't like there is no inventory
this is resident evil six i just made i just made some more crunchies
to resurrect you if later hold on ice manage it elbow drop oh shit
imagine i thought that was a person whoa real-time reflections in 2012
oh there's actually treasure in the sink you missed it so i can i just put a shit load of
this and i have 12 of these now what did you say oh shit i did miss that i had to drain the sink
hey watch out don't blow that up when i'm standing next to it like that but you i thought you're far
enough away to not get hurt i i actually shot it it could have been me someone just asked me if i
saw the dollhouse strings i'm currently hey dude you see those trees man did you see those dollhouse
streams well what if you didn't you maybe you didn't you may have been busy i don't know
is an item over here i think don't ask what i'm doing over here i don't want to talk about it
you have to activate a thing avoiding what am i looking at of course i did who do you think i am
oh you watched dollhouse stream okay name every dollhouse character the princess diana one
i can't even he can't even he doesn't even know the only characters i saw were the uh the staff
really they're the only ones who showed up the people uh in the blackout suits
not even a real fan gatekeeping somebody said put an emote only quick i don't care about this
story you can spoil the whole thing for me right now happy birthday i told i said happy birthday
it is a happy birthday yeah now we get to watch somebody else watching
home videos the c virus all right we have to be quiet this is important why did you add
germa wild two but not one three and four because it's a four-part emote and it would just be
annoying to look at it's too much it's like my arm plus you would probably use four as a dick
so why you do i really have to tell you why i have no idea what you're talking about
tell me one three and four is not a big dick and fine and then i will concede we're talking
about an emote oh my god it's i don't know how that is do you know that is um no i that's not
ada was it ada is it ada this is what you wanted to show me wait are we having like a turn on each
other moment like that's fucked up we went through all wait a minute to watch this birthday video
oh my god look at these things they're gonna break open tell me you're playing a resident evil
game without telling me you're playing a resident evil game okay things in tubes
did i wear did i win is that helene helena impression no pick me up i'm dead again heal me
please that was just this is duke nukem you just did duke that was just literally duke nukem talking
oh sorry i i think i won that one i think we're supposed to go over here i'm following you
oh why is it this way is there anything in here listen it's me matthew mercer we have to go this
way no say like we're all in a bubble gum but i'm gonna kick your ass anyways kid whatever it is
say you know the one open the door i can't why can't you open this door i can't what the hell
oh it's two it's a staff hold on it's 201 i'll be right back oh you gotta you gotta punch the
code in there's a computer thing or the room key there it is that's not why is this dude covered in
honey they're gonna get up but we have to go back to that kiosk thing are they gonna get up or is
this like a setup for the enemies you're gonna fight later thing oh no i can't open this so i
need the computer going back leon somebody give me a duke nukem line in chat please he needs to
say it it's 201 but we don't have a i'm here to kick ass and chew bubble gum and i'm all out
of fucking time let's get the fuck out of here you know if you if you committed to that it would
have been great that was close that was very good yeah but you lost commitment near the middle in
the end because i'm ready i'm just pam i got a phone call with oh there we go during a will
feral movie we're just walking back and forth in the same room 201 got it that was a callback
do you remember you're being an asshole no i'm not i think uh some people are just soft okay so
let's work together hang on i can jump over this you are cool wax projects this is a really long
will feral movie when does it end it's like three yeah it's been four hours okay i'm starting to
think you're right about the fighting all these guys no netflix just kept playing the next will
feral movie in your queue and it was dad's home too get ready for a real god real
exciting movie it's well i think we activate the passageways uh we can go through here i think
how do you crouch uh i think you can i think yeah you can i think i can't all goes but
they're just gonna fight us later for sure okay it's on the other side of this great
yeah well i can't go in here i don't you feel like you can go in there hallway over here
did i just pull you you did not i'm still looking at the vent scene you are yeah it's showing me
where to go i know where to go come up here there's a whole hallway we just looked past
like right here oh all right and there's two levers on the on this level on the opposite side
over there okay but i have to pull this lever which has a high probability of causing problems
so that gets us back out here i get it we have to stretch this level out
because we spend a lot of time on the art assets watch out god oh my goodness
oh my god oh my goodness oh my gosh it's getting crazy uh you're where are you pulling the next
lever and you just you just i'm locked in here now you locked me in here i'm not locked in here
with you etc no no no no no stop being such a sussy baka why what if i want to be is that
something that's something a sussy baka would say ban that person and ban their entire family
i want to make sure nobody from their entire family shows up because they're gonna be kind
of like that person and i don't want to ever see them or anybody that's like them
why am i sniping you will not silence us all right i looped around i'm back on your side
these people can just take a million bullets why what the fuck so now we can go this way
yeah we gotta go across which gives us the up thank you got to reload okay how you doing
they are definitely getting stronger okay it's not what a sniper's for what lever is that i just
pulled it i think it's the way to get across all right okay i love how self-referential this
game is why does everything seem so complicated that's what i'm saying as a player like the
developers know it's very oh right here why don't we wait i need to help you get in the elevator
oh okay there are people up there yeah sorry i kind of just left them oh now we got a big guy
i think i'll snipe see if i can help you that's a shotgun
shit sniping oh you okay yep out out i'm trying to help when did the electricity there's electricity
i guess is it i think you activated it maybe yeah you shoot you shoot the transformer what do i
have to there's two levers so i think that now lets me come over to your side oh boy i think
you're in trouble dear you're in trouble that's your side i think no it's my side
i had the same idea i'll throw mine those are credited to me no kill stealing i there's no
timer right i feel like this i hear a blinking like dun dun dun all right nice let's go a lot
of shit over here and get it very cool nice job dude nice work we did yeah we did it first try
how long is this game uh this is the leon section so it's pretty long the 30 hour game it's like 40
hours why that's way too long they just started developing and then couldn't stop and then just
added 16 waves to each arena that they made i was gonna shoot you too that's horseshit
there are four different campaigns and you will be able to see those campaigns if you decide to
buy this game when it goes on steam every year for like three dollars screamer really i thought he
was dead sniped over your shoulder you're welcome thanks uh-oh help me out whoa turned to ice he had
a nitrogen tank or whatever it was i'm clearly the sniper of the group that's fine i'll be the
melee guy i think we have to open this door yep is it like a duel it's a double yeah this campaign
has the best story what's the story i like the part where they release the virus and the entire
city engulfs in flames you know what who has a harder life a civilian in a resident evil
franchise or like in the marvel universe because i feel like in both the city is constantly exploded
and nobody ever has to like actually clean up i've seen marvel for sure because like like somebody
can literally just drop like a kamehameha on you and kill like a million people yeah i like that
part in spider-man why can't you fill me in yet i mean literally the plot of infinity war is it
all right spoilers for infinity war if you haven't seen the fucking goddamn movie by this point
but like the whole plot of infinity war is that everybody dies right no no no no like i in i'm
the spoiler for if you haven't seen infinity where then okay you don't watch television
all right but i got i got an idea what about time travel though look if you put me into like a
grocery store and i have like 500 cans of shit boyardee and i put boards up
like mr mr like electricity man is not gonna be able to get into the building
right like i'll be fine like i just worry about zombies yeah but this is a this is a pathogen that
infects everybody possibly in the entire world like there's four campaigns you don't know this
could be like a globetrotting yeah but okay who's that little that guy that's like yes oh you're a
wizard too i am me as well oh i'm going to torture you and professor coral no no no he's
in the marvel movies is that guy like oh yeah he puts his hands up and he moves his hands around
people fly around and shit is like the doctor strange fight oh yes thanos i am your most
lovely lieutenant what's this they call him like the ma right i'm afraid of that guy i'm not afraid
of a zombie what about resident evil 2 zombies though what about mr x maybe but i can run away
from mr x if just run away from thanos if the if ma puts his hand up and points at me 500 light
poles are going to stab me through the chest like it's different we don't we don't have space
bearing technology that i know of in resident evil but like in in marvel they could just run
away like thanos still can't go faster than light he has to like catch you you could just
you ever see the the best star wars movie the last jedi you know how the ships are just constantly
like uh running away from each other it's just one long spaceship chase it could be like that
you just really have to say star wars my brain just shrank to the size of a pea
let's just get her out of here and then i'll tell you everything i promise communication between the
two main characters will be great anos has the stones that's what i mean anos has some big stones
leave any hostiles to me all right so wait i have to you have to carry and i have to fight
do i have bullets okay i got enough let me set up for this i feel like it's gonna be hard
can you hear me didn't you say something like the hardest of choices requires the largest
of stones stones yes i will get the stones yes stones what movie is that from i give you
a hundred dollars say it again the stones yes i'll get the stones don't look at chat better
don't look at chat you have 10 seconds oh wait you can't fight
i can i can i can like can you help me i'm on the ground
uh you need to turn around right now otherwise we have to start over
can you not help precarious stream position i'm dead okay i don't he killed me i'm gonna okay i'm
in a very bad stream position like i don't you need to come over here and help me yeah but
you know i can't just click on me there's enough how do i put this person down just dump them
jump over the edge i thought you actually went over i can't i literally don't know how to put
this person down and also do i have a heal oh shit i just healed i'm fine i can't left click
right so you can't okay so i can't go down again good to know it's very important that i
don't left click okay as much as possible so where are we heading this way this person
really should have thought about their wardrobe before they came into the sewers beneath the
church get over here i also can't pick any items up where the fuck are you i'm right behind you i'm
following i'm not paying a single attention to anything that you've said in like the last 10 to
30 seconds the roof is caving in i said don't worry turn around me i'm following you i thought
you're going the other way i've been right behind you okay there's a guy right behind you i base
where you are based on gunshots like when i hear them whoa yeah that's the guy the guy's got a
machete all right are we good nope this guy good few people in the knees for fast melee finishers
that's actually a good idea does it bother you when people say like mali i used to say it like
that but then you change like mealy yeah mealy that actually is a great idea i'm gonna start
doing that nobody nobody nobody nobody wait did you play did you play resonate late yeah
what is the uh big vampire lady's name lady dimitrescu okay never mind got him i thought
it was dimitrescu yeah you didn't watch the developer vlogs like i did lady to meet lady
dimitrescu was i supposed to push it for that long he just wouldn't stop there's a person here
and i am useless well you're you're carrying very strong you're helping and i'm not doing
this you with the second person on my shoulders i'm not doing the thing that the person in chat
said to do usually a good idea lady tiramisu it's it looks like dimitrescu there's a boss arena
i just assume everyone's effect infected she's the boss oh shit she is the boss you're right
never mind okay possible still possible losing losing probability right now
yeah coming back swinging back around oh whoa someone's been watching too many ridley scott
movies it's actually kind of cool i'm not kidding when i say that's kind of cool
it's like the skeleton kind of gets like born it's like a snake shedding its skin hey it's
ada ada can you speak up i can't hear you i watched your birthday video ada and i didn't like it it
feels like you wouldn't want to wear like a bright colored clothes here wouldn't you be able to get
seen like really easily it's to avoid friendly fire zombies visions based on movement is it ada
hell is going on it's complicated i could explain or we could go to the next set piece your choice
but this isn't the time or the place these walkways won't hold we need to get to the lower
levels so sorry what the fuck helena get away from her helena she's still the boss
what helena please whoa break dancing boss um okay all right you gotta shoot the edges
zombie boobs i gotta are you alive what am i not gonna say anything what did you just do to us
oh i got i get ada on my team i'll be good it's okay i don't need any help everybody knows in
resident evil games friendly npcs only hold you back is ada just kill like three people
wait i need to combine some shit jump to this cutscene but that was a grenade
okay coming down she gave you a ring putting out my fanfic later if you shoot
it if you don't shoot it or whatever what are you doing down there i am at a lever that i can now
pull because it's going to help this is actually a demon souls drop down this is the demon souls
round tunnel oh shit all right defeat mutated debra let's go we've got her
well never said she had superpowers she was just slightly mutated
when you're mutant you can take five bullets instead of one like a normal wimpy here
in the back shoot you should put her down i love how in the cutscene i'm like no please spare her
but like now i'm playing and i'm just shooting her oh shit all right now we're gonna get the uh the
edges now don't shoot the glowy bits massive damage i actually can't shit what the fuck
they're not holding still okay there's there's explosive barrels on the ground there are
there are barrels in the ground you're right nice let's get those when we have a chance here
because she's standing right next to one nice nice dude nice got one more leg to get
nice one more right there nice nice dude keep going keep going keep going reloading
go if you stand next to one of the other barrels she'll jump to the barrel
and nice dude that's a good idea back it up maybe maybe not okay she's not really doing it but
oh that's a great idea definitely weak to fire big dps there's more there's always more i think
they separated us are you in health i'm a full health with uh 10 heels nice
hey lana a little help here i'm coming levi let me lay on i missed that so close i don't understand
i actually can't help you how the how am i doing that oh there's a lot of i got that one
you you threw it at me i didn't throw anything i was i have a sniper rifle all right most of the
bottom 41 extra bullets why do you have so many bullets why that's a ton of sniper bullets use
them well i just noticed that i had them even afk this whole time oh my god i don't know what
you did but it hurt i didn't do it i'm blaming everything i'm blaming everything on you i'm
this close just come on down where i can reach you all right but then i'll show you i'm afraid
to move you gotta hurry i'm like two stories below you you're supposed to be running around
while i stand here on the elevator you're the guy that kicked the stairs i the ceiling collapsed
on my head i gotta get my steps in ada is just shooting what the hell she's shooting crossbow
bolts at seeming random there's so much of width i have so much ground i need to cover don't shoot
the guy when he's in the middle of his cutscene to animate to stand up like everything's just
shaking i'm coming i'm here supposed to be stopped i'm about to turn it off all right i'm turning it
off thank you please thank you for moving me okay you're the guy that just went out it's raining
and you're like i'll go get the car don't worry you guys stay here hey i got it didn't i got it
didn't i i mean oh you have to jump in ah no goodness this is not good
why did that not hit you oh my fucking god okay what is the space what i'm just staying
down fuck it stay down i'm staying down how do i see what hit me the second time
i'm getting too angry how do you safety team out here on this new universal ride this is dangerous
it's so low we're gonna have to duck again aren't we thank god we both all fell wait get her off the
front 50 sniper bullets less than ideal all right runner over shotgun i'm sitting down i'm not gonna
hit the head be good i love this indian jones ride um shoot that yes there's a spider-man
situation coming up you got it we're gonna the tracks are gonna run out i would say that's
probably a good a good assessment of what's gonna happen here god's bank green gods what the shit
it's dead down i'm staying down i'm not getting up i don't care explosion hurt less than the
i say to good job because you didn't defeat all right defeat deborah is she defeated oh she's here
no i want to combine that good job you're doing great just have you ever been hitting the head
this way have you been hitting the head as a child oh where are you supposed to shoot i think i have
to save help me thank you i think i just chose to save you and just let ada die i don't even see
ada i can't be the one that kills her it would be a question of conscience i have to save you
i know she's fine now it's fine if you just okay everybody knows that the way to defeat the virus
is enough bullets you just if you shoot this person long enough they'll turn back from zombie into
human please i know you're in there that was the dumbest thing i've ever heard
this is resident evil it's like just i was gonna think of something funny to say after that to
like make it look like that was me like saying that was funny but like i just couldn't think of
anything afterwards so i just made it just sounded like i just said you were dumb i'm i did not mean
it like that i was trying to think of something funny to say yeah but i was just making fun of
the game so you just said the game is because that's what happened that's what's happening right
now just keep your eyes on me this is the hidden backstory lore of these two characters we didn't
even know knew each other before now all right let's see what they have to say oh they're related
see that changes the whole dynamic no we knew that before didn't we i i didn't was i supposed
to i think we knew that before i have amnesia i helped simmons breach the president's security
name five characters in the game okay um leon debora ada debora helena lana long story is what
i don't think wesker's in this he's he's in every game isn't he he's definitely in like a lord
document at least we're up against the people who really run in a very dangerous game and if you
don't well that's not fair because there's only five characters in the game simmons there's five
hunnigan simmons okay we were in a voice call with someone but someone on video call overheard us
i guess by the way leon uh what happened um well we have a rank so i you know good job
double that's double a well what was the weapon that you were using for the most part
i mean i was a sniper remember nice you get to zoom in and just put it on somebody's back
yeah that that sucked that chapter was awful all right but i liked it better than being stuck
outside the mansion five times in a row because at least we got like a cool minecart segment
i actually have um all jokes aside i'm actually having this is actually a fun game i actually
don't care i mean it's not a good game but i'm having fun with the game as far as like resident
evils go i think this game aged better because it came on the heels of resident evil five
i mean resident evil five is way better by like a thousand percent that's what i mean there's
been time to breathe and we can acknowledge that it's shitty and like play it on purpose and
enjoy it in spite of itself all right we i got money we got money what's important here
it's not melee melees actually maybe it is here's the thing you have to decide whether to drop one
of your three or upgrade one of the existing ones for like more like i have crit that i can upgrade
oh i would probably want to break out no no no no no no how much more damage does the melee do
is it significant that's a lot of money not significant it only affects the knife oh that's
awful uh honestly defense level one kind of a new perk but feels like it'd be strong you're seeing
a critical hit sounds good rock steady no eagle eye if i'm gonna do sniper there's a
that magnification i only have eight thousand i spent all my money i don't know what to do i'm
dropping breakout we're just not getting grabbed how do you get rid of it uh you have to mount
you have to like escape or did we do oh i hit escape how do i unescape i didn't oh shit you
just did the cut the timer's gone oh no i only have two skills because game is using the escape
key both to progress and also to go back to like change the skills out i'm doing crits level two
i can't cancel the countdown i'm just stuck here okay um i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm i'm
firearm no i don't know what to do about quick reload that sounds good to me quick reload sounds
good to me all right i think i'm okay with this i still have 8 000 points good so now one second
okay i think i'm good the president spoke highly of you agent kennedy like which one's agent kennedy
told me you were the only ones present at the time of his death what are you saying how do you know
a character is evil when they talk like you must be aware i'm the bad guy of this game at the time
of the attack um there's other characters that have talked like that in that tone that were good
although i can see this actor leaning into the microphone with his hand up
curling his fingers around while he says every line he's he's gripping the microphone
but just yeah he has like glasses on down at his nose looking down at the script his hand is up
someone said dude we can't even hear the game we don't know what you're talking about
is it really that low the the dialogue's low but the action's loud it's one of the it's not even
specific to this game that's like every video game and movie is it that hard to mix audio yeah like
sound effects mean gunshots and like footsteps and when the gunshots literally blow out your
eardrums and like everything else is too low yeah i know what you mean like you can't watch a movie
at home without having the remote in your hand the entire movie to just make micro adjustments
up and down yeah it's like you sit there and you just go like plus plus plus plus plus plus
during dialogue scenes and then when you know an explosion it sucks because you've been in that
position where like you're the quarterback of the television of the living room of the experience
you have to anticipate the next explosion and go down down down down down it sucks and you have to
get good at guessing what other people you may be watching with if you're watching like a party or
something yeah like how comfortable is another person with the audio being loud or quiet you
know like i have to i have to gauge that and it kind of like fucks up your viewing experience
because you have to think of two steps ahead of the movie oh there you go
bus lemon say yes you can you get all those things yeah i'm getting some loot you get it do you need
help how do you oh i got it i think i actually have to help you do this or something can you is
it like a co-op moment because it's like i'm i'm i'm pushing can you like v next to it yo you're
lied he's lied okay yeah oh there's a snake in there it was a jump kill that it has a golden
thing right that was actually pointless oh wait i thought that all the snakes in resident evil if
you kill them they have like money will drop and stuff annoying all the only things scarier
than zombies are skeletons it's called skyrim level this is kind of look like a skyrim dungeon
oh oh look what you found i walked right by this salt rifle nice so does every campaign reset your
entire loadout to zero i guess it does it's two different characters each time so yeah probably
down what you had down watch it watch it i think we have to slide on it crawling me
this people a lot of people over there follow them back here
we don't even use bullets pull them up pull them back here just let them die this is gonna be so
cinematic in about 30 seconds when they get over here each campaign has different weapons so that's
cool uh one of them learns to crawl oh i'm trying to help you well that was dumb i hate when zombies
are smart in media okay just make them dumb they're more scary that way because if they have
intelligence then what if you're eliminating a new intelligent life form that you're simply
too intimidated by dameron to stand up dameron to stand up and go back down i think you're good
i think i could probably get i'll tell you right now this is very important
that's strike two you got one more throw incendiary grenade at jeremy when he's doing
something you got one more you got one more that's strike three catch me if you can
okay i almost walked into if i if there was a drop kick button i could confirm would have
drop kicked you into it i may have done it why would you do he was just he's he likes fire he's
a pirate we have to go over here not going that way unless like playing with fire first person
to run into the blades gets ten dollars what do i look like a like a streamer uh the deal is
out me out for ten dollars i think i have to boost you so i good luck okay i think i have to just sit
down here what is happening do i have to do some oh oh it is a fast crawl so i just have to defend
because they're just going to be coming around the corner i'm waiting i'm crawling as fast as i can
erma don't go into the fire you'll burn your wellington thanks that's a good idea
i probably shouldn't wellington i want that person to like know that i loved that one
that was awesome am i supposed to do this as fast as i can or am i like helping you
ah there's probably kiss and kin kiss and kin simon's family tree i didn't bring any other how
do you get off of this there we go not related oh we have to aim it i'm gonna sneeze i think they
left any one let you know uh i sneeze all the time but do it give you a ring your stream not
on mine do it it was on your stream not on mine i'm sorry i can't mute both wasn't even a sneeze
it was just like i accidentally startled you when you fell asleep during a movie or something
the gift data so now should we get ready just changes the fire oh but we can just we have to
do it uh maybe turn the fire back on though okay i'll tell you when to stop there stop there
stop actually oh i don't know does it i can do it as many times i want uh they're coming they're
coming they're thinking about it here comes a good job toasted roasted i'm gonna wait okay more
are we doing there's uh ones on fire one fell down literally nothing tripped them they just
fell down what's what happened to you there's people coming out of crypts the okay there's
people are you all right yeah i'm good don't back up too far i'll be good um soon uh especially
after i heal oh there's a lot of people here oh they have armor ow that hit you somehow yeah
that was a finisher move like we have to collect all the shit on the bridge man come on
all right there's about you get on the thing there's a bunch coming i think you're closer
well now i'm closer i was getting all the stuff on the bridge all right i'm gonna spin it uh-huh
okay you spin it and i'll just stand next to you yeah and take care of the people that fall down
i'm trying but like i'm running out of shotgun shells and that's how i get my accuracy up
survive the zombie attack i don't even know if there's anybody else coming
it's where i wish probably take a look and make sure okay you need to do a stream where you try
to copy gordon ramsey's recipes i don't think i want to do that i've made gordon ramsey's eggs
before in the pan seer delicious coriander two delicious two two coriander please egg
crack simmer delicious it always says in by itself looks like we gotta get our feet wet
oh water oh we're going all over the place they're already using the like they use the
minecraft boss you got the water boss and this is just in the first chapter stewie griffin no
that was a gordon ramsey impression that was not stewie griffin i feel like there's something we
can whatever um okay just keep going that was the reveal for the boss later called foreshadowing
that means the same thing okay i'll just be doing the crawl animation again i probably have to get
ready to attack so i'm gonna make sure i'm ready there's someone in here i'm ready for i saw it i
just saw it i saw it it's coming closer what is that there's something coming closer there's
something here did i get it kind of on your own i don't know i don't know if i got it i think i
got it that's kind of hard there was one enemy in that entire tunnel it was just one enemy that's
weird why you blew up a fish uh there's items i don't have time for items i'm opening the door
right now what happened uh i have been grabbed and i am being drowned and the fish is got both
of us actually can you see this yeah okay i don't know if that was a me cut scene or a both of us
cut scene it sounded like you hit the uh the edge in operation that was just an office camera angle
of you it was it was the office there's a lot going on i'm oh there's literally no way out we're
gonna have to reload what there's another zero way out i can't even come to find you yeah i know
that's why i'm that wasn't me the game just spawned enemies on top of me after i did that
i hope we have a checkpoint right there oh my god are you okay no this is this is the worst
okay so i have to snipe that's what it wants me to do all right i'm back keep moving forward
keep moving forward you got it all right cover me run oh shit okay all right i got you good
reloading that cannot kill you shut up really your turn it's my turn now you have to help me
you gotta snipe my side i can't even see you snipe my side please i'm down here all right you you
seem fine i think i am can you get through now uh there's like an unnecessarily stand up on this
i'm sorry i'm freaking out for no reason jesus jeremy's just relax how are you supposed to get
through this why won't i stay on the ground do you turn this off um i think we have to just get
through both of our like gauntlets i don't think i can turn yours off there's another step jump
scared me the snake ran into the blue trap okay now just go forward oh it's because i have the
sniper rifle out that's why okay i'm just warning you there's a non-zero chance of me instant dying
over here uh i would say the same thing over here too this is incredibly fast and that's
definitely the way i'm supposed to go um you oh there's a guy there's a guy doing it i stopped
did i stop yours you stopped him yeah okay nice now i can do yours i think find the crank
what do you mean it's not even in here you think the developers forgot
uh this guy went to find a crank um did you find it you what did you just do
why did you do that i guess that okay there was no reason for you to turn it on yeah yeah there is
yeah there was this is the only time in the entire game that we've played up to this point
where a crank didn't do something beneficial i didn't know that was the crank you killed the
guy that was turning because i just turned a crank over here that opened the door why would
why would i think that the next crank that looks identical to that would all right well here's you
with uh sharp objects wait till i get across from this i didn't know what it was i just listen in
this game up till now you see a lever you pull it and something good happens okay i got baited by
the devs okay i i don't think i can do anything until you turn this that's not no that's not
strike three that was not an incendiary grenade close though almost he's close that was a that
was a foul tip no yeah no that means you caught it okay what do i do now the game tells you
to pull this why did i put that down oh my god reunite with your partner i'd love to
why does this not work okay you could just back oh shit he dropped something he dropped something
there's a key over here or something i shot that guy in the face three times oh man oh man oh man oh
man oh man oh man oh man all right uh i'm still just kind of chilling over here with the lever
that kills you why the fuck can i hurt these guys can you pull a lever on your side over there
there's a lever over here i need to get but it go pull that one but it's protected by these stupid
spitting guys that's just won't stop and i can't hit them with anything behind you no there's a
key on the ground over here oh my fucking god what i'm gonna scream at this game if you die
before i get over there why can i not hit this guy because they're waiting they're waiting for me
i shot that guy this night what do you have a clay helmet on oh i've got a clay helmet on i'm
immune to all damage that's that's just basic minecraft progression all right i need to i need
to get that all right am i really gonna sit here and watch you through the sniper as you slowly
crawl under the blades when i am near steps away from being on the same exact level as you
don't understand i have to go that way anyway i have to i have to get the crank you're gonna go
get the key i got the crank i got it um are you okay why did that happen okay don't look i am
ready to turn the crank here we go thank you there's nobody coming after me right i hear
screaming but i don't see anybody all right i am through it's because he was below your line of
sight ah all right is this crank gonna murder you or i hope not i think it's gonna open this
oh shit how that there's no okay that was a movie action movie uh how did the bad guy hit only the
small thin piece of metal with the ricochet but not the person that they were aiming at and now
i'm now i'm not going to criticize that in a movie ever again i said if resident evil 6 is so bad
why are you playing it i think it's fun hey if the stream is so bad why are you watching it
so no don't say that looks like we're finally making it out of here i think i'm having a good
time this is really fun no yeah this is actually pretty fun game i'm at i'm not messing around i
really do think this is fun why can we not that was my i was on yours oh well sorry get the levers
confused somber music you're having fun playing explain the plot then it's a resident evil game
yeah but like i've played all the dark souls games i have no idea what's going on in the
dark souls games either or kingdom hearts i still played those you can't jump off the edge i was
testing you played kingdom hearts back up you didn't play kingdom hearts i mean i yeah i i
played kingdom hearts so i could watch when you walk away like six times in a row and then that's
pretty much the only reason i started a new game so i could watch the music video there was more
after that kingdom hearts one and two we're good there you go i would no i wanted to do that okay
so how much time is left in this campaign the leon campaign okay is it is it just me it feels like
listen we're having so much fun but i feel like we've been playing for seven hours but we've only
been playing for like three and a half just well no longer than that well i mean like the story
for like four hours but i promise you we're not gonna let simmons get away with all this okay
i was gonna do a cool snipe and i came out of the cutscene and they're going to kill me
they're not you just like playing kingdom hearts because when goofy goes
then that's true when he does what when he says boy i would kill to watch you play gears of work
co-op i don't think that would have the same charm i don't want to play gears of war i'd say
it's a the game it's it's cool i played it a lot like a long time ago but no i don't really think
so that would be like it would be so boring in comparison somebody said yeah i don't that really
is just to take cover and shoot there's nothing else going on especially like the first two of
them maybe they changed with the formula and like the last ones but i need help it's like okay
it doesn't have quite the same level of goofy cutscenes
are we supposed to just go i hate the guys that have the armor it's not fair
the rts is very good though i did play that the gears of war uh x-com game was actually good
was it yeah surprisingly here's one and two rule i don't even remember which one i played
because i definitely only played one of them i did not play like gears of war i don't remember i
think i feel like it's three they're pretty similar he's still not dead i don't know how
he's alive i just got inspired to make a beef wellington this christmas did you i thought
you were saying that i got really inspired i guess i know where i'm gonna be oops oops
yep it'd be a shame if i didn't click me there thanks for the assist partner i don't want to
make a beef wellington because beef wellington to me just looks like a weird corn dog hot dog
raw meat thing i don't want it it's just like a gigantic corn dog but it's raw in the middle
right out of the freezer but like thought watch out he's blending in okay i got you back okay
don't know what exploded can we knock the weight limit um i guess this is a cut scene we can't do
it what is he doing you got this um maybe i don't know nope he turned like 90 i may have planted a
bomb just wait till we can move away please he's gonna kill you he's gonna hit you right now i
knew it was gonna happen i knew it was gonna all right i'm in i'm in it we were supposed to
shoot the bridge oh i you killed me i didn't but i have you ever had a supposed to shoot the bridge
have you ever had a beef wellington before no okay i know everyone here's like everyone else
eat vicariously through gordon ramsay videos yeah but people kept kept just kept saying that's a
shit take worse take has anyone in this chat eaten a beef wellington before i feel like it's like
three of you i don't think anyone's even had this before listen there's not macaroni and cheese in
it they probably haven't tasted it i mean macaroni and cheese is based so all right let's get him to
run all right hurry because there's other guys so now we've when he's on the bridge we that was a
guy that wasn't me there was a guy to the bridge shoot the bridge shoot the bridge shoot the bridge
let's just run across the bridge run across the bridge i'm going as fast as i can here he comes
wait oh god oh fuck okay just how long do you have uh i have a little bit i've got like at least
five to ten seconds not he's he'll kill me if he gets another go across the bridge
run up can you get around it we don't just keep going this way there's nothing over here
this way he's coming he's coming he's coming all right another bridge we get him another place
there's two what do you mean there's two why is there two this is unfair what we're sandwiched in
oh my god we're not gonna be able to do this it did like a cut scene i could have revived you
well yeah this is bullshit because look at how much weight is currently on this thing and it
didn't fall are you serious listen umbrella uses only the best structural engineers okay how do
you think they made such a successful mutating campaign they had to start with let's not shoot
the bridge that didn't do anything okay why don't we just kill i got an idea just both of us plant
a bomb i'll just plant a bomb right here okay i'm gonna we'll just we'll plant one there don't
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait he's coming he's coming so i'm gonna run
oh no i'm gonna put my what the it won't let it won't let me run don't blow yours up yet
three two one blow it up wow all right we got dead i'm wasting so much ammo like an idiot
okay we need to do that again yep but that one's that guy's dead i got incendiary grenades i'm
just gonna throw it all right he's not coming this way oh god watch out thank you anytime okay get
some ammo is it this bridge i think it's the next one the one that goes up wait do we go down this
bridge um yeah it's the other way yeah it's the one that goes up it's easy to get turned around
in this particular wait area hold on are we stupid here no this is the right way but i think since we
died they took one of the big boys away to make it easy no he's here here he is i think he's here
yeah there's a guy behind us careful i'll go you you wait i'll go get him don't go too okay i hit
him with that throw that i did that guy has a bunch of fucking bombs all over him did it work
all right i kind of did closer that should be good oh my god die already he's dead okay that's
not bad watch there be a third one i'm gonna get a grenade out because i feel like this is gonna be
a third one i get a checkpoint though that's good i don't see another one devs uh can i get some new
content i need something to react to uh here's somebody i can't i honestly can't the guy just
spit in my eyes and turned me into rayman okay what's going on you spit in my eyes and turn me
into rayman just get over here i'm stuck in the animation what he spit on you at the exact moment
i confirmed that the co-op moment so i'm just over here i'm in the like running crouch animation
ready to cross are you good thank you you snap me out yeah yeah nice not nice i saw the scene
of resident evil 5 uh is this the part where i punch the rock while you uh i think you have
to lower the bridge uh do you see any of these people over here that are crawling up behind me
i got you i got you i got you i'm not even kidding i seriously do okay this four of them though
keep crawling crawl crawl go go go go go go go go go i'm crawling is okay i actually just saved
your life i just that trust me when i say that you actually would have died if i did not do that
i mean i have full health but sure there were four of them grabbing you i thought you just
jumped off the edge i feel like i need this oh boy watch out i got big i am i can just snipe
i'm gonna shoot the big guy just worry about the other guys big guys going down
shut the hell up that's my character said the guy is still alive he's i've been he's taking a lot
of damage though all right big guy dead okay cool looking good looks pretty good i want all that
stuff too though oh there's some there's some juicy skill points i think somebody behind me
no i am where are you i have you have to put the bridge down here okay i'm going the right way
i am currently sniping there's people coming over are your way um what the fuck was that
dynamite what guy had who had dynamite it's like i don't know they're just trapped with dynamite
for some reason but why did it blow up near me that was i don't understand that we're gonna get
an auto check he's doing all right he's in the other room this is extremely slow like
there's nobody coming after you yet oh they are now they're on your side oh i got like 85
you got a guy right behind you 95 it's over okay now don't be mad at me for running down the whole
bridge because i want to get all that stuff kill the zigzag he's still alive oh i need bullets
that was actually really cool yeah the drop kick's fun um but you have to like queue it up let me go
get this i can't go get this stuff that's so unfair what all i can't get it skill points
i don't think you do are we as literally a huge rock they had to know let's push it
derma lost auto in his huge mansion right behind you
that was very scary did you shoot that guy no he fell all right hold on i need to do this i mean
we it took both leon and helena to push a rock whereas chris pushed it by itself so i guess he's
at least as strong as both of us combined first redfield yeah that's the other that's the fifth
character in this game i wouldn't be surprised he's show i think he has a whole campaign help me
i don't know what i did can you tell the people behind me to wait oh boy all right watch out
behind us hey uh manage your inventory real quick and then heal i got it thank you thank
your name was red it was bothering me oh on the wrong side so okay uh yeah there are noises
this progress bar i would say we should probably stop right now stop i okay and
fight how do we get off we're just one person oh come on it falls all the way back
was that like a developer meme i think that was just like a gotcha moment i was like oh you thought
you were gonna have to do the entire bridge or we or we fucked it somehow and we like
fucked it up somehow we gotta go fast i think we fucked it up oh shit are you okay yeah are you
are you i think so thanks for your concern big boy gotta go um b that was a sonic losing all
the rings moment you good yep okay you somehow landed there's way too it's too many okay there's
too much going on are you good i think so jesus are you all right yeah this is ground shaking
we keep just going you good are you okay oh are you okay man you good you think okay you good
someone put another two person boulder here that those are the like indiana jones the ones who
got squashed we made it did you ever think about how difficult it would be to reset the traps in
those temples they give you just one guy in the trigger all they only have to happen once
if you're good enough to get into the temple then you're like the earnest level threat yeah but what
i'm saying is like what if you get what if you like 80 of the way through but the last one gets
you like they have someone has to go in and reset all the other traps before the next guy comes in
are we supposed to i know is this a screen saver like what's happening it's just a cut scene
stop trying to make that a thing no i'm going to continue to try to make that a thing what what
thing uh earnest um all right so we have to swim earnest christmas special yeah all the earnest
movies are required reading yeah they're pretty good there's a space bar thing here yeah it says
perform stroke right oh there's like an air pocket i think wait there's an air pocket yeah you swam
past it i press spacebar so i get breath well hopefully i find an air pocket up here found an
air pocket good all right which would you rather do this whole section again or um i give you a
like ocarina of time water temple save and you have to start there i'd rather do this a thousand
more times 80 meters all right where's the air pocket i did you which i don't know which way
did you go i'm i'm like behind you i think i still got half air yeah i have a lot of air too
oh he's fucking choking me well i don't have a lot of air now that's great oh there's one right
here can we share i think see if we can share do you pop up yeah it's a lot of like blood and
guts in here for some reason a lot way too like halloween decorations even the underwater
segments have to look spooky they have to okay i'm getting choked down too i'm doing a great
job holding my breath in spite of it though okay it's just getting me again i'm gonna die
what no i just it won't let are you okay trying to get away yeah i got i got 40 here i'm trying to
like where do you go i'm going back to the air pocket i can't man i'm just fucking going i'm
i'm literally just gonna go to the end because it's right here i hope you uh lord grabbed me
over there fucking god dude i hope i can cut seeing you over here this is gonna be bad in
a second i think um i need you over here uh i'm i'm working my way over i'm gonna drown is there
an air pocket anywhere right here i'm almost there are you here yep what am i what do i need
to be looking at where are you what are you looking at is this mouse bullshit i'll go up to the
ceiling quick quick quick i hit vvv up the ceiling via the ceiling quick via the ceiling via the
ceiling yeah i'm gonna die i'm dead in 10 seconds oh thank god i think we're good
please tell me we don't have to swim up okay oh i hope your earpiece is still working no he
said something cool again here comes the boss i think that's not funny you're gonna make the
dog jump in the water to come rescue you way down you just have to survive i am in the mouth
where are you you're in them are you in the mouth i thought i was i thought it was this
you're not gonna let i'm getting bit i thought i was up his ass
uh i don't know why i thought that okay let's go it's space and r the two dumbest combinations
i kind of i actually just wanted to see what would happen it's incredible that my human strength
capable of stopping that okay here we go space and r i'm ready space plus r you fell off fine okay
uh i got it mine's just mash keys all right i got space plus r ready shiny bit in the in the middle
all right i'll get it it's like a are we holding our breath this long is what i want
uh don't worry about that just stab the weak spot together probably probably both of us using a
spear at the same time i think so are you okay i'm good i'd spam i'm up in the mouth and shadow
the colossus are you at the stomach i don't know i think i was just like waiting for you
i was in there hanging out oh now you got the office camera now oh you're in the water with it
okay find a place to climb up find a place to climb up okay where we're here uh there's a tunnel
that you can swim through that's over towards me i think they just want you to go through the tunnel
oh and then i will get jump scared i said i find a thing to climb up i didn't know
we'd like go through the tunnel and around the whole level i'm looking for like a little ladder
on the edge oh you thought this was over this we're only like a third of the way through this
level i think i you you have to open this helena can you do something about these bars i'm working
on it leave me alone try hold on what if i just left you uh you would die oh you want i see this
this is testing past mechanics thank you i tried looks like i can get up over there but the fish
is probably going to jump up is that going to be ready there it is they make it uh are you live
yes you're welcome i'm telling you mario boss okay one more time we're gonna jump on its head one
more time uh okay weird spot and what am i supposed to do about this i didn't do anything
yeah i shot it why is it on the bridge i'm on the bridge above you watching you gotta start
swimming it's giving me all these prompts and then to take it away from me okay very nice time to
actually fight the fish right i imagine that's what's happening here hello how are you i made
it and i am ready to not crawl through this but rather use our combined strength to push it
okay um defeat the b.o.w why it's slow wait feed it barrels it's got this explosive barrels
um apparently the edges of the screen i feel like we're going into hyperspace i can't even
look at this this is a warp gate yeah this sucks um we're good wait for a barrel oh barrel yep
right now i'm reloading um right i think we're good not kill us i think we're okay did we just
beat it this is what it's like to get stuck in the water park i feel like we weren't supposed
to win that fast nice bit rate yeah bit rate is dead yeah i'm in the same we were sliding down
there for like 45 how did we get outside we were falling through a very long tunnel we would be
like a thousand meters underground there's a nuke that just went off so they're destroying the place
you do an impression of daniel day lewis in um where there would be blood sure i actually
haven't seen that movie
that's why you are all right that's a good one for when they're attacking leon can we get
another one with a little bit more uh energy i think that's pretty accurate
somebody said i that was a bad impression because i hate that movie that's not how it works
you're farming nominations over the end of the year
the bsaa confirmed it was so many bioterrorism attacks we just can't contain them all
it's nothing we can do umbrella is rated a plus by the better business bureau out of our hands
and right now you two are on the top of their list of suspects that sounded like a pokemon
no what pokemon sounds like that listen no it didn't what pokemon are you talking about
is this the end of his chapter we may have just beat this yeah oh look at all these accolades
s rank i got gold though you got silver now this is platinum mine has a crown my metal has a
royal crown on it and a wreath your your wreath is wilting mine is flexing you're getting outgamed
oh shit okay okay i can actually put a third skill in now we have 30 000 bucks i want to
know how bad that was i'm gonna watch the vlog later and say how bad it was i can't buy anything
how i had 8 000 left over from last time but well because you got kicked out remember
you hit like escape so you should have a lot of money right now i got 30k you should have like
20k at least no 13 there's a lot of single player only ones speeds up recovery time when dying what
does that even mean maybe i'll do firearm what's combat gauge is that a mechanic we should know
item drop thing i don't know not into i uh i'm good okay uh trying to i got 28 000 more points
i'm dropping items how many chapters are left um i would assume it's probably five or two in leon's
campaign or in the whole game in this campaign games oh i don't know there are two more for leon's
story okay i thought the daniel day lewis impression was good but i have not seen the movie
i've only seen one clip that's what my impression was based off of where's the thing i unlocked
what is happening uh what's wrong i'm trying to like there we go all right the ui is the problem
everything okay the item drop skills probably why you have so much more we got some item drop skill
users oh i had item drop on oh no because you you got to run that whole section
i yeah i did get like a big bridge with a lot of stuff you can hit escape anytime by the way
oh i thought i didn't know this plane is dead it's already dead on our way to china okay we're gonna
have a skydiving segment we might look how much space there is what are we have like a
passenger jet i don't know if somebody asked me if i'm an organ donor why is that why are you asking
what's your blood type i have no idea wouldn't stop Simmons do you know your blood type i actually
don't i have no idea no i actually don't know telling you find a boss zeus i'm very curious
what the boss will be on this campaign where's the emp in here no they turned into these things
we nuked it but what one of these things is in here yeah it's the dark souls uh you thought this
was a boss but now it's a normal elite enemy oh he's doing this on the plane oh my goodness
just open up the door back up throwing it back up just suck them out we can't go back any further
okay uh oh that's a new gun lightning hawk uh deagle that's actually pretty cool hey do you
know how to fly this thing there's something wrong with you're gonna go back to the tail of the plane
find out what's wrong it's the magnum nice i'm saving this to the last 10 seconds of the game
there's a lot of fairly calm people who are about to turn into zombies yeah
they're like already sitting yeah they're already they've been sitting calm down everyone relax
don't panic we're just two heavily armed civilians running through the plane looking for the zombie
it's just men in black music i mean there's a lot of people in suits with sunglasses so
might be onto something here i can't even hear it i'm going down how deep does this plane go i
i don't know here we go five grand do i have to help you i got it the big red valve nobody's
coming so hold on there's nobody flying the plane right now right correct this is kind of weird i
assume it's on autopilot but also there's a hole in the ceiling of the plane and uh hot steam
pouring out of some oddly placed i think we just have to be quick about it did you just shoot the
lap this is the part where wesker comes in and says uruburus i don't think the uruburus thing
was in this game was it i thought they got rid of that and it didn't they move to something else
like i just like saying it because the resident five and they're also in a plane like this one
when he says it he comes in through like the back i think we made it in time
oh god what if what if uh the monster in alien looked like that crawling
that would be kind of cool like 79 i don't even open the hatch we gotta get the gas out of here
it's just it's that's just a that's just a how do we open the hatch oh shit right here super soaker
all right protect me i gotta open this he's getting closer
oh i'm gonna try again all right let's dump him get dumped uh we're lighter than it he's gone
we would have wouldn't be flown off already holy shit see you later i was not ready for the space
r you've had more practice with that than me just curl up into a ball and hope for the best
hey anytime you wonder what happened to your luggage next time you take a flight just remember
this could be your passenger flight and you just don't know space plus r judge
dude you fucking fell off who's going through i almost got hit by that one i'm gonna win i'm
gonna win you just spread the virus that's true we just dumped that thing on top of the city
not my problem anymore oh okay elena we have to go i have zero shotgun left oh great everybody
everybody turned plane is infected yeah i'm just gonna i'm just running i okay i'm
guys i already used so much like of my don't ever make that joke again shit it's alex i need you to
say something for me uh-huh i want you to say that i say i and we injected and we ejected
ejected somebody that is like pretending to be somebody else what would you call that person
we ejected somebody that was trying to be somebody else like somebody that was
you know putting on like a costume to pretend to be somebody what would what would you call that
person um call that a really really badass halloween party no it's i can't shoot the gun
is it kind of like uh in the thing where there's like a crew of people but one of them
is not actually a person yeah i think we took too long this thing's going down man um so what do we
do hold on all right is it is it like when when they're being too noisy and you have to go
shush i have to you do something no okay i have to first switch off the autopilot to restore um
and where is that third button i didn't hear anything that she just said i think i started
a fire i said no i did that just pressing button try it again okay i think i got it
all right i am just hold the lever the people we ran past i guess are you steering this or is
it i'm flying the plane technically now what uh what are you talking about two different things
900 feet i'm doing it you're making the zombies fall down they like couldn't stand up oh we got
like this is rendered it's cinematic we should have taken the train like ada actually possibly
like tens of thousands dead and that would have they just kept them to up the ante first they
were crashing ambulances now we're crashing uh subways then trains then uh going straight
to like double decker planes what are we gonna crash next you can't keep one up on yourself
i see a ladder i wouldn't go we're gonna go there and get the item who's that that's no that's um
that's the president's daughter from the fourth game chief security advisor simmons why they're
so quiet there must be some sort of mistake i report to simmons it's wrong he's your supervisor
okay uh challenge read the dialogue as they say it in step of who what character are you
no you like oh me okay let me handle this what you thought is to avoid contact with anyone
leon's not just anyone he saved my life back in raccoon city okay it's it started with like
inflection and it just became like a like a regular reading oh look out evil three boss
i hope it hereditaries her you're a psycho it's an overwatch character the big monster
yeah looks like junkrat up close no it's not far away kind of looked like that it's not
overwatch two characters all right here we go ready i have my magnum out and i'm going to use it
i bumped i no i didn't shoot i don't want to miss what the hell where did this guy even come from
he's got a he's this is just a new dead by daylight guy what is this he's like got one
of the civilians he's gonna go put him on a hook okay i'm trying to dodge first you right click
then you hit space and then you hit a l or d no why dodge needs to be just like space
if i have to come over there i'm just gonna heal myself no oh she's got me
me get up he why can i heal what's happening i have three heels use them
nobody's indestructible okay we have a party again you just have to find the cutscene oh wait
yeah we want to go up here it was uh something up here was there yeah i don't think i even have
any bullets wait was this to fight him uh that looks very useful uh-huh too too late possibly
i think so maybe if i did you do that i if you did that that strikes free yeah i mean i had you
okay it was right in the middle so that's it you struck out that's game over you're right it was
right in the middle that's actually strike three though so now now i i don't know what to do hold
on that's game over no look look look hang on here just breathe if that doesn't heal me then i'm
hang on just don't move okay now what's something's happening what's happening here
now i'm about to leave again who is who is jumping over who what that was strike three
we need the barrels we did we did need the barrels he came back
look my my bad my bad all right we can do something here come back here the npc is
is like helping me more than you are all right i got tired of like carrying the team so i just
wanted to have some fun also they're supposed to i'm fighting the big guy and you're i don't
know what you're doing i got i am getting the car to work again that's very cool and it's gonna
watch out because we're coming through that wall we're coming through that wall right now
do it we're about to just charging here we go watch out oh my you did how did you miss
you missed the guy and it hit me well because she missed oh my god man if only you had health
if only somebody didn't throw grenades at their friends in games okay actually i'm gonna need
oh you need help no not yet not yet to combine this with i was just trying to get him right there
i'm down here if he comes down here i can blow him up all right watch out
wait he's like hugging the wall get down here why won't he just drop oh we both just like all
for we all forgot our lines every character including the monster okay um we just all standing
up here he's like is he down finally all right get over here what okay i'm seriously sick of this
this is like a cat he's like keeps climbing up the like shelves in the house he's up there now
he's he's just you can't tell him what to do because it's a cat he's on the other side of the
map he might just kill himself he might actually like run into like the tower maybe have we just
tried asking him what's wrong we may have just gotten a lot of trouble here we let him upgrade
his arm he found his case who made the scissor hand upgrade though all right now i'm pulling this
out here we go watch out i was hoping you were back up here it comes yes i mean we gotta make
things easy for him come on get over here he knows okay here he waits i'm holding i'm holding
is that a grenade yeah here he comes all right did it work uh you got it he hit him
it definitely did is she down or is she just i think he's all right
he just like football kicked it piece of shit yeah he did it was little kid in action scene
staring at thing falling on them sherry
still alive maybe phase one
charlie brown by lucy well the difference is i was standing right there and it hurt me too so i put
the football down and charlie brown kicked it into my face how did that hit you a minute ago
but you weren't picked your current route okay the bird convention thanks all right amily guy did
that this actually looks like to the outdoor market up ahead what does this look like um
this place we're in right now like this scene uh-huh right here yeah right this exact place
right here yeah um another co-op game darkness another co-op game another co-op game um yeah
i don't know neon lights two characters they get naked oh canaan linch canaan linch
it looks like canaan linch somebody said this part this part sucks oh yeah get some plus
fives in the chat we don't nobody remembers plus fives best of fruit three separate locks no not
this i've updated your map okay i just found like if there's like a steam data thing this is where
like the most amount of people that quit the game just all happened right there on comments
just based on like data of like in-game time and like in-game moments stuff this is where everybody
stopped that was creepy my god well this one is different that's a new trick i'm assuming
we have to shoot that stuff i don't know he seems armored we break the armor oh okay then you're
gonna shoot the guts fire probably it's probably fire uh the keys are just scattered around yeah
the keys are kind of in here all right i'm going i'm going for uh that's that's electricity
just go for the keys it's the two of them are basically blocked i got one back here
did he come yeah you have to split him up and shoot the goo inside what the
fuck holy shit i didn't know he was there hey i got a secret door open i got one uh this way
there's one back here somewhere the electricity okay that's the three keys we open this we have
to like it oh i can turn this off ah the electricity all right electricity's off it's like a minor
annoyance we both have to do that that's annoying okay there's two one more key left he's kind of
crawling in here um which way should we go i'm kind of panicking i don't know which way to go
i'm stuck in here now with both of them and i'm gonna die you can come out oh okay i need to go
my inventory and heal it's like there's more okay how do we get the key over there under man
notes right now when we pick up a new key there's another guy well how do we get we gotta go around
yeah let's go like around this way no not quite no wait boxes can't okay uh this way probably
we jump this what there's a little jumpy arms can we not go this way either no it's like it's
behind them kind of in the middle oh god oh okay we're here we need to unlock it from the other
oh please oh please uh are you all right yeah yeah this level's just this is kind of just annoying
okay um where we've done locked from the other side follow i'm just gonna follow damn arrow
maze level okay okay i found a ladder coming you have to go over the roof and you have to throw me
move it move it i'm trying to do that last one now we can get the door right laura croft jump
isn't it i don't think i can make it over there why did i go down that was really dumb i think
i'm gonna open the door for you actually his hand is coming at me is it this door here okay
they're here it's over here it's over here i'm pointing at the screen uh help oh wade where are
you oh there's another door you can go you can go around or you can go through this one
you're uh well they're coming in in there now so i'm just gonna follow them well uh i kind of okay
so that just became more difficult can you just get the key
i'm sure because if you just grab the key because i'll just go over to the door
no you have to open this door oh god damn it really yep just threw something in my face
what's on me it's probably a little jumpy hands oh this is bad please don't kill me
i just one of my keys just came off i lost my q my q is not on the keyboard anymore it's gone
is he killing you i dude key is not on my keyboard anymore what is i can't
unnecessarily intricate if it's a death animation it's a guy i lost my key my actually my q key is
gone please for the love of god don't even tell me this is like a 60 second death screen
thank god hey you want to come in here we have the three keys
no this is actually the last the one that i couldn't get in they're coming down the hall
grab the key i'll try and teleported oh my oh my okay i got the eagle is really powerful on them
let's get is it good yeah all right actually like killed one wait let's go turn let's go let's go to
stop farming i didn't i actually was doing that what am i help i'm too weak to open this door
unless we double roundhouse kick it simultaneous how did you flip off the q key it's because i'm
hitting wasd really fast and my finger got underneath q while i was doing it okay um you
might i actually can't i think you just screwed that up because i my bar went back down to zero
you just watching in shock and horror i was shooting you can just look i was definitely
shooting the whole time why would you grab my ankles and yank me out of there
okay all right let's go i gotta reload but but wait it failed i'm dead again dude do you have a qt
yes i'm getting some serious trauma of why i gotta like steady myself against the wall
like how do you report back with a debriefing uh yes my superior officer i i know you're not
gonna believe me but one of the ones that regenerates himself went head over heels into
a meat grinder sir i don't really know why the meat grinder was turned on in this abandoned
facility really what the purpose of it is but you have to believe me he went in his whole body
ride his ass
looks all clear now let's hurry from miss simons okay well we got it somebody's gonna eat that
like that's going into a meal yeah just the fact that your character is just standing there
with a blank stare while just with getting double grinded you think there'd be a little
bit more of a reaction from that person doesn't know weaponized meat grinders it clearly worked
like why don't we just get like a transportable meat grinder to fight those zombies with
it ada just leave the door please just leave the door unlocked so we don't have to go around
and find three more keys i hope that doesn't happen i'll be so mad let's get some answers
yeah you go oh my you got it you yeah check for ammo i got a lot of assault rifle let me
take inventory for a second i have a lot of handgun i haven't found any heels in this entire level
i have had one red herb i could use my handgun for a little while all right down scared you
yeah i almost did you what uh run i i was wrong just run wait is this ada's facility
oh shit um oh we gotta get up it's coming back uh okay that spawned it doesn't hurt that bad
it doesn't really hurt that bad it doesn't hurt that bad we have to kick the edges oh these real
people they look real i thought we broke them we'll take the stairs we'll slowly open the door
that was way too slow way too slow what's with this camera oh it's president evil one i hated
that yeah that's more accurate wait boxes i'm sorry strike one let's strike one no you don't
get to give me strikes bro your behavior this stream it's minus one strike this is definitely
a boss here not yet getting there well start it's not big enough they just they're giving
us a lot of stuff yeah this isn't the room though we might see it i would love to walk a little
faster okay it's definitely like it's just to survive the room probably robots oh weaponized
room bus do they explode or is that what it is i don't know one of them one of them did
they are oh they they explode if you don't shoot them first yes you gotta you gotta kick them away
kick them away okay well like i mean like just knock them away the stay in the corner
you run interference oh oh this
whatever i hope i hit yes i think i just pressed no oh uh they got to it first no we're good
double zero leon knowing that i'm the great leo the strike two let me skip this
all right we actually should just sit in the corner and just use pistol i have to hack a
computer okay so i will make sure i'm going to defend you with my pistols with your pistols
all right don't we have like five better weapons than that by now you can shoot you only need to
shoot them as once they take one hit then they go away and they blow up i got it where's the panel
is it right here okay i'm ready i will protect you all right we'll try i really thought things
were going to come out of the tube just not like the infinite robot on me god damn it i'm relaxed
i'm fine i like since something was wrong and just dodged out of the way watch out behind you
i can't actually hack yet so what about what happened that you have to shoot them once
you do they bounce back oh okay but you have to kill them all right i'm hacking now i'm
actually playing dead by daylight okay security breach detected in room zero
why is it taking the generator right now it's uh why do i need to see that cut scene
why are you shooting me i'm not shooting you i have not shot you once blood was coming out
how's it going uh it's going great actually i think we're through i'm like faster than the
voice is over
oh we got stuff here 5k 10k nice oh this is the loot room this has to be like we have to be near
the end of the game right have to be uh yeah i think we're catching up to the prologue the
prologue was definite it was like a i imagine the final chapter is probably just like a final
we're gonna have to kill the unkillable guy which is very resident evil the guy that like we've
dropped the metal tower on who's up there is the big bad shoot me i mean i was so many voice lines
we would shoot you she just did a magician smoke she has a grapple hook gun and smoke bombs are
we supposed to jump over here she keeps getting these little cutscenes that oh it's how
can we just fight her no you can't shoot her she's one of the main characters
she has a campaign it's probably her perspective there she is cut her off who the fuck is that
is that chris who is this person one of us is chris oh it's which brown hair hero
oh why have you seen like the gift of chris redfield like naked with like a banana in his
hand and he's like get out of here and like it's like dad whatever it is but now i'm gonna have
chris redfield naked in my search okay there's it there's a gif where it's like chris redfield
is underwear and it's like when you like try to get dad's food and it's like get out here
like he has like a banana in his hand now i'm gonna have to search chris redfield mostly
naked in my searches no he's like he's like he's like bike shorts i swear to god this is a gift
chris redfield in bike shorts it's like chris redfield he's he's putting his clothes on is that
it is that the gift like progressively more clothes he's like in the kitchen and he's like
he's got like a banana and it's like it zooms up and he's like uh okay what's he doing with
he's just holding it and he's just he said you should have left it alone ethan you sure
he's not like eating it i need to look this up because i swear to god this is real it's not a
nude mod well i gotta make sure this is real chris chris redfield okay chris redfield is she immune
to smoke and flash bangs is that her superpower chris redfield banana kitchen gift he's playing
with the controller i swear to god i'm not insane i can't write this you take care of simon i can't
type this yeah you have to search for it that's what i mean how are you gonna search for it i
don't want to type in chris redfield naked with banana in hand that's what i'm saying
hopefully the game doesn't crash have you been alt tabbed this whole time i got it i got it i got
it i got it i got it hold on hold on i need to this is not t.o.s i don't think i might get
hold on just wait i promise it's gonna be worth it i promise scene's over we're just chilling
nothing nothing scary is happening my side will be for the story the subtitles are still on your
side will be for uh naked chris redfield with a banana balanced co-op content is it showing
hold on what do you mean i can't show you i don't i don't know he's he's got the link okay i got it
has anybody seen this you've never have you seen that before talix no but like this this is the
first thing that came up for me why can't i get this to turn off sailor boy chris disarms daddy
ethan banana we have to move on we have to move on now but that's what i found talix we're gonna
move on right now before like this this is gonna get this is gonna get really bad i don't he's
holding like a can of food i thought i thought it was a banana i can't turn this off why
i'm really sorry but like i let's go i i think i found my own can of worms are you good i'm back
i found the i found a different banana yeah be careful apparently there's a series of them
don't write that don't type in chris redfield's banana i please don't write that nobody
i'm serious that like not it's not what i was looking for i was looking for that gift you good
uh-huh yeah i i've now seen chris redfield in a very tight uh sailor costume taking a
banana from daddy ethan i'm so sorry and so has everybody else simon should be just up ahead
be careful did we just get raided from vinnie oh my god i'm so sorry our target is simons
always has been we'll have to worry about thank you so much for the raid welcome everybody i'll
make sure to like follow and subscribe i'm we i did i did not expect we were going to show that
but i had to i had to show that yeah thanks but you understand like it's how to listen this is
really important if i didn't show that then people would have thought i was fucking nuts you know
what i mean yeah no no no that was that was the deciding characteristic that had to be shown
otherwise like how would people how could i ever describe that you described that i found something
apparently tangentially related and i still think you i put you on a wild goose chase and
you you ended up somewhere else i'm sorry this is unexpelled agent birkin impeccable timing kindly
take these two and hopefully hopefully that's not bad to show that are they running down the
streets he's in bike shorts it's fine it's for the benefit of the united states and global security
can't see how killing the president is good for the country well dispose it was a thong all
bullets missed it's a speedo it's fine he that's a guy in a speedo people wear that shit to the
beach guys okay you want me to show you the one that i found maybe in private need to be more
careful okay i'm gonna start a new folder no i mean like on not on stream oh yeah yeah yeah
no i i get you i understand we're talking over the cutscene we have to listen what are you two gonna
do finish simmons there's information on here that could stop the c-virus simmons wants it
thanks i'll put a call into fos give you some protection now move i can't believe i'm the only
person that knew about that i thought it was a like a funny meme that everybody knew it's a it's
about to get a big boost in popularity there are already at least like five artists hard at work
right now it's living rent-free in my head right now i'm sorry what am i did we do it i think we
did it doesn't i like that scene from matrix reloaded it's cool i hope they do another matrix
in like 25 years and they're all like agent smith everybody's in the old folks home that's i would
watch it keanu reeves reprises it they're playing bingo we can't go on top you can't start on top
of the train in the train sequence you end up there you can start up there there's nothing well
look what something's gonna break through the door it's gonna be a couple of zombies we should just
run can we please no i'm just saying this is wasting a lot of taxpayer money keeping these
public transportation rails open when no one's using them we're coming for you simmons wait
i'm this is the i have to read this out loud listen chat i had to show you the gif i had to show you
first redfield's banana otherwise everyone would think i was insane yeah i yes pretty in line with
what you said yeah yes but do you not agree that because people didn't know what i was talking
about i have to prove that it existed here's the thing about chris redfield's banana you can't show
me a banana without expecting me not to peel it i'm gonna peel the banana oh you need to stop
what a waste of a sequence right why didn't we just show up on top of the train we just walked
through the train we didn't even need to do that now we're gonna be on top we're trying to get to
the next story area this is real time travel that is just teleport to the next like fighting zone
the bad guy's on top of the train in the front we're catching him right here
we've got you the hair a traitor 801 i recognize this guy who's his voice actor
yeah i i recognize it too oh i know and he disclosed the truth behind i know who it is
you the u.s would have lost all its authority it's right on the tip of my tongue he's an anime voice
actor and he's in the dub of jujutsu kaisen among other things oh is it um tuna salmon he's the he's
the teddy bear guy bonita flakes i still don't have a q key by the way we don't need to use it
did you pop the cap off or something yeah all right
looks like a pokemon back up we know there's nowhere to go oh shit okay
sure that was a really bad cut in a movie but i tell you though we had to end up on top
of the train and then oh man we gotta get up i can't honest to god i can't think of a worse
thing to put in the game than to have it be like a slide if you press the button like who wants
the slide nobody wanted the slide the slide just causes problems what do we do when we get to this
end of the train all right he's on top he's gonna smash through i already pushed space see if you
can push space on the door um no i just i'd look like i could defeat mutated derrick i think oh
boy are all the characters in this game like brian oh wait wait come here come here eric
i i could just put you up why do they want me to push you up damage damage i'm doing damage
holy shit all right um that's some big damage that bottle some time i don't know why i'm up here
i don't know can you do anything interesting he's coming up to you there's a bunch of ammo up here
someone just scattered like sniper rounds there's a remote bomb i'm shooting him in a very i'm
shooting him somewhere where's the remote i can't why can't i pick up the remote bomb
he can you do that thing when you punch him again uh now i can actually all right you're i stop no
this movie this movie sucks by the way when did you say will ferrell shows up in this
um does he have his own campaign i have to just run away from him i can't believe the eternals
copied the villain from resident evil 6 i didn't see that i don't know what's happening uh
uh we're in the middle of i don't know what's going on i've teleported three times so i really
don't know he's on the other side of the train he's got bone shooting power we are playing
the jump cuts of a movie that's actually what's going on oh thank god okay i'm gonna hang on just
tell him to wait i'm gonna combine some herbs he just annihilated me
your sister hold on all right locking on oh you can take cover somehow what are we supposed to
be shooting him oh you have more bullets though you might have a duck uh he's coming back in
dude in space he's got a face god fucking damn it i hate this game i hate it so much i think i
missed it uh it wouldn't be space r if we were playing on controller where's my space r who's
even has their hands over there nobody all right mutant derek we're coming for you all right
let's go let's go all right let's uh make some herbs there's a green herb back here
you need to make some deals why am i not allowed to pick it up let's go oh your inventory can get
full can it so i just have 300 pistol rounds all right can you just keep killing the boss
i gotta get some i'm putting damage on him i just learned about this let's go all right i'm helping
okay he's gonna do the thing space r be ready here he comes okay i just shot you like six times
because you walked in front of me okay i thought he got you no i got that i picked up the smash
item all right he's up here other train all right wait there was no one on that train
it gave us control for a second um yeah what um did we win i don't i don't know i shot him with
a sniper rifle i shot him like two or three times with a sniper this is really this is the worst
boss fight of any resident evil game i think yeah but that's why it's kind of why i actually like it
we didn't even really get a chance to fight him like it was just kind of shoot him a little bit
and then there's a cutscene where we teleport around and he gets hit by a train i just love
how much time went into the like seven different cutscenes that are mostly uninteractable that lead
up to this point this is very bizarre there's actually more the world will be a better place
oh that's what it reminds me of the edge of tomorrow enemies except with more bones
yo that was sick good thing didn't even move yeah you shot the metal away from my face so i could
land between the eyes uh who's this there's no way we're on the tracks okay that's gotta be wesker
like who whoever suit guy is there they've put a bunch in the games when i said dude this game
sucks yeah yeah that does yeah would you even say you know well but i mean i i mean if you said
the game difference in this game sucks and game sucks there yeah there is a difference are we still
in the same chapter head for the mission objective we're absolutely at the finale coming up here
did we finish it we did what we could let's go excuse me excuse me the next chapter is the finale
i've got to complete the objective i've got to obtain the data remember just wants the game to
end yes do you though yeah all right well i better check to see if i have any fire bombs left
now we're gonna get one big giant finale in the last chapter but we haven't gotten the rocket
launcher yet that's how you know the game's almost over they give you a rocket launcher
with like three shots in it and they say end the game definitely infected people
who are just going to go to some safe house and mutate it's not it's not over the prologue
literally has an unfinished business here we go is it we gotta get the data what i tell you we
didn't get the data this is the key to stopping the sea virus it's jake is naked chris redfield
it's the chris redfield gift hey leave it alone ethan that's uh we're going to space
i don't yeah who is who is jake i've never heard of jake game is he from i don't think we have what
now the question is is this a traditional or is this a mutation bomb this is yeah this is a
infection where it makes everybody a zombie it's that same gas if i were a world superpower in
this universe i would invest a lot more in like air defense like anti-missile and he said why
don't they why don't they just make a big peepee virus i mean i don't know that's not i guess
that's i mean they you could just like turn the pills into a gas and then release that so are we
about to just kind of turn our backs on this and just be like well we tried oh shit's fucked oh
come on i thought i was gonna have 82 accuracy you haven't bought high deaths a new high score
yeah and how many of those deaths were you killing me intentionally we we need to remember that
that's important each chapter i have been killed deliberately by him at least two or three times
four at least two or three a chapter no no yeah chapter a chapter at least two or three now you're
ready to put this thing to bed uh i got 30 000 points not enough for crit two yeah i all right
can i can look at can i just make it like a uh actual rant about resident evil
unpopular opinion you have the floor i'm gonna before you say anything though i'm gonna say i do
not like condone or um agree with anything that he's about to say so but you have the floor okay
all right here we go i actually hate how in every resident evil they lock the super fun weapons
behind multi playthroughs just give me all the cool shit let me play i got a 60 game i kind of
don't want to play through three times just to unlock the in-game dlc just let me have all the
fun stuff scattered throughout the campaign so i can enjoy it and i'm fine paying that money for
a good experience and then i want to put it to bed i don't think that's that unpopular i feel like
the people who are like i want my extra value so i have reason to play through again and get like
quote unquote 60 dollars worth well i want this damn it i thought it was gonna be cheaper what the
3000 to 28 000 for level two get out of here that's what i mean like some of these are clearly
not going to be earnable in one campaign i thought i was gonna be able to do level two
twice whatever this one's 70k for the next one yeah i can't really afford anything i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna go playing this game with a friend is worth it yeah that's the only reason why i
play this there's no reason to play this unless you're playing with somebody else co-op makes
everything more fun that's the only reason why borderland still exists all right you're good to
go yep let's let's seal the deal on this thing i was burying the lead uh i just have a timer uh
yeah i hit escape first so what's going on here okay i think we both clicked at the same time
borderland solo can be fun i feel like you're just looking to shoot stuff and pick up items
it can be fun just to have in the background depends oh borderlands can be fun solo that's
someone that uh bought it with their friends they all got together to play one time and then none
of their friends were ever available to play a second time so they just kept playing because
no one else would and they're trying to feel good about their purchase i didn't say that i just want
to make sure everyone knows i'm the guy that did like the drink my milkshake horrible noise
everybody hated before that's not that was him that said that hate me for the other thing but not that
wesker now she ain't no one dies in this universe not ada no no way
which characters have more plot armor evil my dragon ball my girlfriend no my girlfriend
google my girlfriend wesker let's see what comes up
killed off screen yeah
we did not give a shit of what that guy had to say dialogue
this guy gonna talk all right okay took you that was very long for you to do that
uh go near the gas don't go near that gas did you already said don't go to the gas i was hoping
for something funnier but i'll take i'll take the hit on that one don't go to the gas it'll
it'll turn you embossed don't go near the gas or you're gonna have to subscribe to adobe to
figure out how to do the rest of this tutorial by clicking the link below
oh go go go go go go go go go metal mario
all right watch it turn right oh god it's everywhere okay genuinely the building oh thank
you we're good you did that stephen king presents are you trying to break the glass and let the
gas in i didn't know what was gonna happen when do we get the rocket launcher oh shit we gotta go
up a plate up there plate one of those blue players filling with gas oh come on i didn't
know it's gonna be that fast we're tied good see like i just walked on me for the final credit
don't worry i won't i won't walk into the gas okay so we just have to move okay just run
oh i can see the shit storm and i don't think that's the half plate on the shelf check on the
evacuation plate on the shelf the blue plate is that is that something like school christmas thing
uh the i can't even talk i'm sorry dude are you still down there i'm stuck on the stairs
what i'm the the glass blew open you gotta move man we're coming all right in the elevator all
right let's go where's our ride it's just outside go but i gotta get some loot but don't put all
these like trinkets everywhere sick when the camera's going but it's going somewhere
we're not getting followed by the gas all right oh my god we gotta go this dude we just run
which way just the double doors oh hang on hang on there's a million people here
what a hero good luck it wasn't that guy we don't win if only he didn't have a mask on he would
have survived he need you can't live in this universe if you cover up your face yeah you need
to be on camera yep you have to have lines you have to be able to see your face wearing helmets
are forbidden face coverings forbidden you gotta have full visual or your character can actually
die is your sensitivity insanely high right now uh it's pretty it's pretty high we can't risk
any more men in there and make sure you turn the air conditioner on to like recycle air
and put on some can you reach down the front put on some fucking spotify dude this is boring
like who drives around without music fucking weirdo i think you got the like silent uber
did you ask for like total silence i actually don't listen to music either i would listen to
music but i only have a cd player in my car i'm just gonna come out of the smoke all right
what was the last time you burned a cd
oh i don't remember i have no idea it's been a while i got defeat 500 zombies because this
dude ran one over that's funny okay so the fun fact we actually have to drive um across mainland
china this does all the way this does feel like a haunted hayride though we're just kind of slowly
driving by all the actors this is as far as i can get you why the smoke clear is right up ahead
you two keep going i'm gonna head back and try to find what's left of my team yeah we could have
gone faster if we just ran yeah but we can't breathe we could have held our breath and sprinted
and gotten there faster what if it's like skin reactive it's not it's when you breathe it in
all right going up good thing zombies can't climb sometimes they can that guy's dead why
didn't he just come with us yeah that's weird the gas is still going still having to run out of
vehicles you know on a kill it's the same you can't that there's other miles per hour you can go
that are not 100 or zero people need to tell the resident evil people just you don't have to push
down all the way on the gas it's not we're not playing like cruising usa commentary too
they're driving like they're in an arcade it goes from like you're going five miles an hour
in a humvee too watch out there's a gas tanker coming right at you and it's gonna explode
yeah the mill the guy that guy was going five miles per hour he's going like zero
you only go zero or a hundred in resident evil oh okay this is the prologue i played this part
what there's a callback the prologue of the game starts here and uh helena's wounded so how do we
do this leon it's maybe i'm not wounded yet but i'm gonna be wounded so watch out wait are we
about to like fight dr robotnik is that what this ending is no no no like i get wounded somehow and
you have to carry me and then uh returning enemy shows back up at the end this way leon leon do
you hear me are you all right am i talking to you uh maybe wait i we've changed we've changed
history at the beginning of the game leon carries helena through this part oh okay we've
found destinations all right we got something in here i've got that all right over here why did i
do that why did i just check pulse he dead that was really easy oh dinner plate but at the beginning
of the game you only have like three bullets you wouldn't understand i did the tutorial too
log doesn't have any continuity at all why do i need toggling aimed on sites um it's more
comfortable for me i just like it better action express magnum ammo why can i pick that up
i can't pick that up hold on my inventory is beautiful you have to like delete something
you end up picking up hundreds of pistol bullets over the course of the game okay got it do you
ever randomly get nervous about being like an extra on a movie set and they're doing some kind
of like you know being one of the zombies and the main characters are spraying bullets
and then all the zombies have to dive at the same time to pretend to be dead and you're the one that
like is off oh like jump to the ground first yeah like last before everybody else does well the thing
the director is sitting behind that's saying like okay down down down down down they cut the director
out he's got like his own they usually edit mount would you be one of the people that like dives to
the ground like falls backward or does like the shoulder shimmy where you do left shoulder right
shoulder left shoulder right like you got hit peppered like six times why can i oh well i would
have direction because the director would be talking but they were just like you know feeling
your vibe and they're just letting you pick the vibe all right guys just want you to feel the
vibe and just do whatever you want well then the movie would never get made they'd have to take
a hundred takes yeah but that's how it's gonna go when the zoomers finally start making movies
where are we now just do whatever your vibe is um i'm trying just to okay yep spoiler alert
there's a helicopter and this oh yeah i remember this why can i move
that's more realistic all right that's how it would probably actually happen okay was i supposed
to hold w or d because i was holding i don't know i was holding i'm sorry s right walk towards the
camera that's what i was doing but i don't know maybe it's w because it's a w it might be w i
don't know i get was i running looked like you were running i was holding s let me try it again
you're holding s like before after monka always after okay i'm holding s holding s
this is easier with a controller like i don't get it it's s yeah but you they he stops and
he just starts walking you have to hold space this is this is actually the sprint tutorial like
in the beginning of the game oh shit it's because my i'm still toggled on for my aim
you're still aiming down sights i'm character the character is still aiming because i have a script
right okay well it should be off now yeah we're good all right everybody reset take four this
stunt has cost us 18 million dollars oh way more than that this is like a 10 billion dollar stuff
you're just like flickering onto my screen that was like hey the zombie just standing there yeah
why was that guy shooting you're shooting at the cars i thought that was in the game for a second
i was like that was loud and it was weird all right you've trained how to fly a plane how about
a helicopter you got a chemistry final tomorrow well good luck i'm getting dizzy yeah i was gonna
like laugh out loud not do it but i want to get out of this it's making me sick all right i'm
gonna catch this guy and when i catch him i really he's a zombie and then oh no it's a zombie and
then i have to let him go oh that's right i'm good thank you i missed so don't worry i missed
again focus on flying i got it you're doing great all right you know okay are you like not you're
just not entertained at all right now right like me i i am but for the wrong reasons i say when
you do too much of this shit like i'm i'm not entertained anymore i'm just kind of like
i want you to breathe i want i want this game to remember this is like concurrent with uh the
uncharted games coming up so it was kind of like hot you know like the super detailed elaborate
action set pieces yeah that's that's fine but i want the game to breathe i wanted to fail that
but also i didn't know if it was going to do the whole chopper scene again or not yeah that would
have been painful that's very good call uh we got a lot of boxes here oh i think it's important this
is probably the final boxes of the game i don't have any space yeah neither do i um i don't want
this anymore did you do that yeah i want to combine these yeah you got 12 healings make sure your guns
are live whatever you know what i mean just make sure your guns work uh-huh there's a plate too
do you like upgrading guns sometimes would that make this would that be like a good feature in
this game oh yeah that that is missing that you upgrade your character in a weird way right okay
so we're about to find out who it is because he's like you're back all right if wesker comes walks
around that pillar i'll give you 50 bucks all right i i bet it's either wesker or the unkillable guy
we dropped the metal thing on there's a lot of explosives in that truck bed why do we care about
that guy like we've walked over a thousand corpses it's not wesker is it just the suited
war villain it is from the train yeah well it's uh oh eight is gonna throw us the rocket launcher
like she does in every game right looks like jake gillenhall and william defoe
that's cool i just said that's cool oh that's cool i was reading chat i'm sorry
okay here we go let's defeat derrick just explode this it's right next to him
big red tanker does not explode okay is this a dinosaur holy shit literally a t-rex this is
the coolest part of the whole game this is awesome wow with the helicopters
oh you're gonna shoot him in the eye he's got an eye in front of his mouth oh yeah i played horizon
oh now we get on we get down we start stepping on his head get him you're closer
melee him go melee him yeah yeah derrick all right unload that'll teach you to jump the turn
style at the subway station derrick oh i gotta get the fuck away from him i can't his boxes
are on the edges too i got an explosion another car is 100 miles an hour oh yeah pet the dog
all right get it it's a turret section i stopped working yes i think it overheated
okay this whole game sucked until this last 30 seconds did we not do it yeah we did it he's got
eyes in his chest too whoever's driving this thing deserves a deserves some applause they're
working with very limited space and they're honestly doing a pretty great job
can they stop doing cutscenes well that guy died he was in the driver's seat when it fell
oh we did we got like running at like 120 fps and like the game's like shit's happening too fast
or something all right he's going back into his uh into his form you want to get this one yeah i
got i got this one get it get him i'm trying get off you fucking dumbass can i get that use that
machine gun oh i think i just blew up a can by you i'm okay i'll get this one that's strike four
by the way i just want to make sure you're aware i haven't i haven't done anything yet see what you
don't know is once you get up he's going to transform then you're going to move out of the
way and then i'm going to blow it see all right now now move away what not yet wait wait wait he's
probably invulnerable now okay he screamed and i can't do it there we go i didn't like didn't
affect him at all i'm gonna come down there wait is there any magnum bullets come on we get the
and shoot the mini bird he's going down right in his face okay now we're gonna have to like
mag dump hey to relax all this will she won't she tension well this is we shoot it from the
we're not done what's wrong there's nothing let's go but that was not the last boss it just keeps
going you guys have to carve him you only have 60 seconds carve him but like a yeah like monster
hunter well the thing is that would have been actually really funny if we had done that boss
for 45 straight minutes she's more than just and we did it without cats yeah feelings for her and
then we uh retried it like five times it's only 45 minutes if you suck ass yeah i didn't say the
quality of our gameplay i just said hold on it's probably a qt
um i just took your place you have to climb first so we have to do this together
okay um i feel like i'm going too slow
i'm afraid i didn't want to overtake you uh-huh he's moving over there who else is up there ada
uh it's ada oh that's probably like the ada boss fight oh wait don't you kind of want to
see what happens i think they probably are both in god mode are they in god mode do you think
this is she's why she'd knock off spider-man in this game i don't know but i think she
wait she's probably gonna die um we have sniper rifle ammo oh now she gets to beat him up we
cannot reliably do anything from back here how i can't even we just did you have any sniper
rifle ammo yeah but i have nothing do we even have to shoot it what is it what's the objective
it just protect ada did it reach ada can you come fight over here ada just grapple literally
just grapple away okay she finally is doing the beat down uh she she has to do it three times too
oh the zombie that comes to our side is so we can they're like delivering ammo who designed
this segment but let's go like hurry up zero or 100 we have to climb again
i can't relax well i thought i i had whatever all right hang on hang on
just get two or three in front of me one two one two get in front of me why i there was no
prompt that was just you have to catch me i think i just have to get you okay go ahead one two one
two one two one all right i'm moving i think you have enough space am i too close oh shit
shoot him now uh i had this space in our hair be careful have you seen videos of like bears
climbing trees okay they can do they can do some crazy shit that's what this reminds me of
it's like they sampled clips of random orchestrated music from a hundred different
games and movies and just slapped them all together it's like it's like every marvel movie
every horror movie are you down there go punch him in the face all right i'm gonna i'm i can't move
i actually can't do anything hey where are you i'm like up here giving support i guess
ada you maybe waste every single magnum shot i don't you next you gotta be next to ada and then
do the revive movie revive i was making that up i don't know this is a waste of goddamn time
what the fuck am i doing is this what it feels like to be like a regular marine in a godzilla
movie all right i hopefully we can get you back here are you across no i'm like up in the tower
up here this is dangerous but i need that ammo he just changed he was not that he did not look
like that a second ago i'll tell you i'm just gonna use those should it be shoot him in the head
or where i'm shooting him in the ass he do got some big cheeks like big bulbous oh god damn it man
i haven't had a loaded gun in 30 to 40 straight seconds i'm doing my am i supposed to do something
up here i think we just have to do this wait oh there's a whole level up here why have the
zombies not even been attacking me defeat mutants dare all right good luck down
oh who the fuck is i thought there's just a random citizen up here
innocent oh it's my opportunity get up i'm showing body shots because i don't know where to shoot
them from down here dude having the dodge roll will you stay on the ground i'm not so sure if
that's a good idea get the fuck up all right come on is this zombie even host okay
come on you can do that the whole time knock him down what the fuck primary mechanic in the game
okay please i get us out of here you having fun down there no i zero to do something what
am i supposed to do i'm gonna fucking die did we finally do it it's in the window okay um
you had to get into the cutscene spawn
he only fell from like 100 feet it was locked until you got to zero health is that really what
that was i was so far away from all that that i had no effect on that fight
the t-rex brought this a full letter grade up but the rest of this brought it three letter grades
down i wish i could stay longer shooter we're sticking together oh leon how sweet how much
more it was there to do i feel like we've killed the same boss three times like we keep killing
these two guys guy on all fours in the t-rex yeah she texted you so you would have her number
that's right yes we see the helicopter that means the end is in sight let's just pretend
to be a zombie just walking dead all right here we go this is the puppet master zombie
this is the lady what's her name that's the it's this guy again that's it's the guy yep
are you gonna do the other playthroughs this is the whole premise of resident evil 2 though
and leon's wait no uh we're gonna do the other playthroughs no i'm going to burn the copy of my
cd i have no health i'm like dead hold on can i heal you let's do something about it
hey yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i got it i'm good nice what do we have to shoot here i think
it's just him i think he goes pretty good now he's gonna what this ex-zombie saved us this time
well there's the now he comes back again we have to be in the helicopter for him to spawn though
yeah we're gonna get in the helicopter he's gonna jump at us or like learn to fly even yep he's
gonna jump up he's gonna grab the helicopter with a tendril and then we are gonna have to shoot him
with the rocket launcher it's a good time to reload every gun yes that's what i am doing that
right now you guys should play the jake campaign i'd rather eat a ghost pepper oh more stuff that
was actually like five deagle rounds i feel like we should have had more opportunity to
upgrade our character or something not between chapters that's meh lame co-op moment eating a
ghost pepper not clickbait he turned into a fly did you see that hold on we got one more like
separated get me out of here i'm just like shooting at this guy climb down this is
what's up are you fighting the guy i'm just shooting this big fly in the face i think i'm
winning oh hold on did i do something you you moved it like i'm i'm far enough away from king
kong this is not scary i'm far enough away from him now like i'm not i'm not in any danger he's
one of the like haunted house uh workers like he can't touch he's always moving
what is happening oh i he's gotten angry oh i have to move this again i'm out of ammo and a lot of
weapons i have no bullets all right just hang in there i'll be with you do i have any bullets in
any gun no i have nothing i don't i can i have nothing i have no i don't know what i'm doing
i'm playing like a game show over here i don't think it matters he can't hurt me are you dead
uh i guess so i feel like okay something was wrong there something was wrong there i
used every weapon i think can you move me faster probably me but i could i could be a little faster
this time yeah i didn't know exactly what it's supposed to do first because you were just like
the giant flies over there except reunite with your partner he's very vague i used every bullet i had
i'm not even gonna shoot at him what a waste i could definitely jump to you
just kind of like a pog he's like okay so i'm not gonna do anything all right there's like four
zombies i gotta kill the zombies move them over somewhere all right you're moving i'm moving you
okay this is where he jumps now over that was pretty good shot i can't activate it again yet
all right here he comes he's coming over to the uh lift thing there he is all right now i can do
it again working on it oh shit hold on you have to be out of the way i got at least 10 seconds okay
got it okay are you moving me yeah am i moving i gotta it has to reset there's like a timer
okay i i'm out of bullets again looks like he's can i leave already yet i don't know what
oh shit okay all right you're all clear oh there's a lot of shit up here yeah okay so i've
been pushing buttons on this little device okay so now we where do we go to go through this
okay flies are so fucking ugly i hope they all die who somebody said that they think flies are
ugly and they should all die i'd be okay with that don't flies actually do something very
important like decomposition and stuff i'm sure the whole ecosystem does but like that assumes
that i'm willing to spare the ecosystem you've gotten to a bigger fly and i would rather delete
all like ants flies and wasps we're not going anywhere in that chopper all right so
so time to fight where should we shoot him with the legs
dude his arms yeah i don't know his legs his belly he's protecting his eyes so we have to make him
unheated and then shoot him in the eyes when possible all right what else is left to shoot
he just peekabooed i shot it
he just peeked yeah
what okay he zeus he's got zeus thank you you were right the lightning rod
in the head sniper bullets in there all right i'm gonna take out the ads yeah we need we need ammo
well he absorbs one zombie and oh my god there's some ammo back here yeah this crates
this is not the time for points i want bullets oh shit wait we can touch this
what okay i just stabbed this guy oh he has to eat it we're trying to make him eat the lightning
bolt so he gets electrocuted um so this guy's stabbed how do we move this guy now can i move
him can i kick him we just have to keep doing damage to his like body do the do the yellow
orbs and then shoot him in the face when he falls down we're shooting his legs off or something
need ammo okay here he goes this guy's been lightning defied now what shoot him in the eyes
all right then what about it send it how he's gonna grab it how zeus activate the power
my god it's still going like that callback actually is potentially what took down the
final boss it just won't it won't stop okay there's so much content in this game think
about how many like 20 minute youtube videos i could have made no all right here we are
we made it oh oh there it is oh there it is the bazooka the rpg
this better be a good explosion we both take the shot or do i fly into you shoot i wonder
you got up we both got i just i shot him that fall over there's a guy in a costume
one rpg that was not what i thought all right i thought we were gonna like fly the chopper and
yeah yeah i love this scene in simon so i'm ality that's not zombie movie the other one
hot fuzz it's probably not over like you said he's gonna grab the helicopter we're gonna have
to do something else yes but that one was made of dragon glass okay that's gonna make the umbrella
simple isn't it lightning couldn't kill him but an rpg could that exactly what they wanted to have
happen the plan is all in place only with the blood of the ancient one i guess not ancient he
was like born in like 1975 or something he said let's get to the chopper all right you still have
a shot let's get out of here it's because i didn't i didn't even get to shoot the final boss with
the rpg i had to do i had to do something it's gonna put us all the way back isn't it i think
you just fucked us i think you just fucked us over we have to watch that again all right at the same
time now at the same time now i think we can skip cutscenes oh shit can you escape i can't i'm in
oh my god dude we were out of it we were done just time it at the same time three two one shoot it
okay no no we both do it at the same time pick it up are you ready get in the spot one two three
okay good now escape we can skip this all right we're good let's go don't you i know you shot
yours so yep i shot mine this time it actually remembers that may have been my only chance to
shoot the rpg in the whole game it probably was oh i thought this was a smoke detector the data
you have to get the data intel the reports we're gonna break this case wide open we already know
what happened now we can make it public we already know what happened we have to clear leon's name
because everyone thinks that you killed the president exactly oh shit that's right you're
right you got it oh that's it all right i have a new i have a new game for us to play
okay uh let's go after this is over who can uninstall this game faster oh sorry uh this is
going to be the new yearly halloween co-op we got three more years because there's three more
campaigns i'm playing this ever again all right how about this you play and i'll like eat a ghost
pepper on your screen and i'll just leave who said that this one's even over what if it what
if he comes back all right well the shit all this shit talking it actually was it wasn't that bad
it was bad but it wasn't it was awful but it wasn't like awful enough to not play let's be
honest it was not good but it was not if you have a friend you can just laugh through it like we
just did all right stay for the after credit scene player has left the game uninstalled i win got it
nice i'm honestly shocked that it didn't like yank me back to the did you force quit it because
i can't even hit escape on this menu i i just literally all tabbed and just force quit it wow
okay the game's now uninstalled wow all right nice okay how much of that is related to me like
the throwing a bomb on you and how much of it is just the game well i did we had a i just figured
that it would be like a funny thing to who can uninstall it faster okay now delete the banana
gif i didn't make i didn't do upload it i've watched it and laughed at it i still have a
google image for chris redfield with a banana open i don't want to see it all right that's it
that was fun that was resident evil 6 and it was a fun game and we played it was fun yeah show
and we're going to play the next three chapters on a stream near you everyone just didn't want
to see his final score probably true oh wait did you see it did you get that actually no i i quit
too i didn't want to be left behind uh how long we've been how long has the stream been
uh six hours and 40 minutes probably like an hour of that was just the one outside the house
segment i forgot that we started at 330 in my brain this started at two but no we started
at 330 pretty cool well i hope you guys enjoyed that hope it was fun i actually had a great time
like regardless of the game was bad it was fun to do that is that supposed to be the best campaign
is that the best one in the game that's the main campaign from what i understand because look you
saw like ada i you're gonna oh ada's across the bridge she's fighting the monster you do
i think you just do their version yeah because you yeah you see them that's them in a boss fight
like later when you play that campaign and i'm sure you'll turn around as ada you'll look over
your shoulder you'll turn you'll see oh there they are there's the other two players there's leon and
yeah there was a good story moment wait you said the game was bad and you lost 500 viewers what
are you talking no i did not say that oh you're talking about right now no um people are leaving
because the stream is ending yeah yeah there's not gonna be another six and a half hour campaign
right now it's over i thought okay i thought you see you mean all right well that's uh i think
that's gonna be it thanks italics for playing it's always a pleasure it was very fun we'll uh
we'll see you soon i will indeed thank you the germamites yep for having me uh you know where
to find italics if you don't i hope you're keeping an active tally of all my plus twos
but yeah that was fun and we'll see you again thanks for playing dude it was a good time
thanks everybody bye take care so where does that leave us the plan here is on wednesday
the monster rancher they're not remakes and they're not remasters so i'm not going to call them that
they're reports they're ports i'm gonna play at least monster rancher 2 i'm trying to think
if i should do them both but i don't think so i think we're just gonna do two because two is the
best one so we'll play monster rancher 2 get back into it and then on thursday is the game awards
so i'm gonna stream the game awards and depending how long the game awards is we'll probably just
go back to monster rancher 2 again and then from there that will be thursday after that i really
want to get the the baby sensory you laugh you lose kind of just chatting stream ready so that'll
probably be somewhere early in the next week i can't believe you're doing i mean i'm gonna
i'm gonna do it so this is a chill week um i don't think so maybe the monster rancher streams will be
lower energy i'm not we'll see i say that but it always ends up being the opposite
but hope you had a good time thanks for watching everybody we are out i'll see you guys on wednesday
for monster rancher you have never seen monster rancher it is it's very good it's there's a lot
of pog moments for sure and we will go okay why can i hear myself oh there we go all right
see you later everybody good night goodbye have a great rest of your evening we'll see you wednesday
take care of yourselves good night