What is going on? How are you doing? Too early? It's a little early. You ever like make a sound
and you get caught on your own words? And it makes a sound you've never made before?
That is what just happened. Can I refill my coffee? Of course I can. Give me two seconds.
Okay, I'm back. Hello. Sorry, it took me so long. I had to sprint really, really fast.
Yeah, but the coffee that I have in the fridge, it's like, um, oof. It's like maybe like two or
three minute run from here. That would suck. Can I just say, when you think about like big houses
or like big places. Oh yeah, 17,000 square foot house. I would never want to live in one of those.
Ever. I would think that there were ghosts in every room. No way. Then why do you? Dude, if you
have them, if you have room for a bowling alley in your house, I don't want to live there.
I appreciate smaller spaces. I think you can do way more with a smaller space. I don't like big
spaces. I lose shit. You know, how many times I pace around the living room, just like under my
breath going like, where the fuck are they? How is it fucking possible to lose, to lose my wallet
again? How is it even possible? I'll pace around. I'll go into the bathroom. Was it in here?
It's not even possible. And then, you know, end up finding it in the couch,
but imagine that times like 10. It would be so awful. I would have to have 10 or 20 wallets.
I'd have to have like 10 phones just in every room. It's a skill issue. Oh, that's wow. Yeah,
it is. Absolutely. I love this. Have you, have you been to Greek chicken? They got a new location.
Food slaps. I'll check it out if it's up. See, I'm always into new food. Stop bragging about
your phones and wallets. I don't have 10 phones in 10 wallets. I'm saying if I lived in a big,
huge house, I would need to have like five or 10 different wallets. No, I would have,
I would have a landline. I'd have a landline that I know where the phone is at all times.
I don't need to think about it. I don't need to. I know I want a landline. So many of us that have
so many problems remembering where our phone is. I want to bring the landline back. Anyways,
let's talk. We got a few things to go over here. The first one is what we're doing today. Dave,
the diver is in 1.0. It's been on the list for a long time. Sorry about the milk voice.
Ah, trying to get rid of it with some coffee. So game is really good. I have heard it's very good.
I've been told this is right up my alley. I've been told, Jeremy, you got to try this out. You
got to check it out. And yeah, it's in 1.0 now. So why not? Let's give it a go. Second important
thing is this stream is only going to be for about maybe just about three hours because we're going
to raid Connor's stream, Sea Dog. Connor is doing a charity stream today, a charity auction stream,
which I have a couple of bundles in. There are two bundles. There is a raffle bundle,
and then there is an auction bundle. So you'll have to bear with me here while I explain what
they are. The first one, the raffle item, which the Grotto Beast Twitter, obviously I already
talked about this, but if you want, but I can give you more details. The raffle item is four
of the OG archaeology stream cards, and I believe they're all holographic.
So if you remember the archaeology stream, the fake packs that I opened, four of those cards
are going to be in this charity raffle. Also, there's going to be a copy of the map.
Remember the map prop? They were fake. Yeah, Holly made a ton of those cards here,
so we picked out the ones that kind of looked the best, felt the best out of all the ones that were
made for the original stream, and each one is from each individual artist, the four original team
of the original stream. It's a pretty cool item, but you also get the map too. So that prop map,
maybe the one with the grandpa, like, oh, he left me the map, and it was all burnt.
We made a copy of that map just in case something happened to the original one,
and I've had that here for a couple of years, so you get that too. That's part of the bundle.
And it's a raffle too, so this is not the auction item. I know a lot of people were saying like,
oh shit, okay, some germamite's going to come in and drop tons of money, and I'm not going to
have a chance at all. Well, the raffle is for you then. The auction is two Grotto Beasts
holographic test sheets. So they're holographic print sheets that the printer sent us to approve
the second print, and I signed both of them. And it's really interesting because the two sheets
that are in this auction, their holographics don't exist in the real game. It's a different
holographic type that is on these because they were tests, so they don't exist in the regular
game. There's also a postcard that we sent to friends and family, so holographic postcard as
well. They're holographic testies. They're uncut. Yes, they are uncut sheets. Are you going to auction
the ass baseball? Uh, no. That's for me. But those are two different bundles. One's a raffle,
one's an auction, and we did it that way because I wanted more people to participate. I wanted
more people to see it and be able to, you know, throw, you know, less than five, ten bucks at
an item and potentially get it rather than an auction that could go up into the hundreds,
if not maybe the thousands. I have no idea what's going to happen, but I think a lot of money is
going to get raised. There's a lot of really cool items. Tons of streamers and YouTubers have given
stuff, so we'll rate it in a few hours. You sound constipated. I know, I've got my like voice and
throat and body. Everything's a little jumbled today, the last few days I'd say. I'm kind of
jumbled and having stomach intestinal problems too. I'm all jumbled up. I'll be all right,
though. Don't worry. Let's get a little bit more coffee in me. I'll be good. Did he say testicles?
It's not a testicle problem, okay? Oh my god. All right, you guys ready to play Dave the Diva?
Let's play it. I'm interested. Hey, what's on the agenda today? You're gonna play this one game,
you're gonna be playing anything else after? Just this for probably two and a half hours or so,
and then I'm gonna dump you all on Connor's stream. I think the, I think one of the items,
I think the raffle item, I think is happening pretty early. So, I would, you know, he's stalling?
I mean, yeah, very importantly. I'm gonna give you guys some info. Can you shout out my cat? Hey,
Mr. Fuzzy! Thanks for watching the stream. You didn't say where your cat's name was,
so I just assumed what it was. All right, let's go. This is gonna chill out. I'm gonna play Dave
the Diva and then we'll continue. It's Mr. Fuzzy, Mr. Fuzzle, what is it? I didn't see it.
That's a valid assumption. Yeah, I think it was. What's the charity? The charity,
hold on. Yeah, there's, shit, hold on. Let me, hold on. Give me a second. It's the Immune
Deficiency Foundation. Hold on, I gotta write something. Immune Deficiency Foundation. No,
I knew what it was. I just, I have to talk to somebody. Give me one second. How do you raffle?
Hold on, give me one second. Okay, you don't want a notification, but I can't even talk today. You
know when a notification pops up in your phone and it just kind of ruins your entire train of
thought? That's what just happened. That doesn't happen to anybody. He had to take a bong rip.
That does not happen to anybody else. Come on. All right, let's go. I get distracted incredibly
easily. We know. Facecam? No, not today. Not right now. I feel terrible. You know what I mean? Like,
this is, this is not facecam days. The last like four or five days, I'd say. These are very much
anti-facecam days. Well, terrible is the wrong word. Terrible would imply that I, you know,
I'd feel, I just feel like, ugh. That's the best way to describe it. What about the classic no-cam
germa era? Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Okay, I don't know very much about this game. I just
know that I wanted to play it. Is this a roguelike? Is this a trinket collector? Is this a, you fight
stuff? It's a granny-like. I doubt this is a granny-like. What's the last granny-like that
came out? Hello Neighbor? It's, I don't, Hello Neighbor came out like seven years ago. This has
definitely been one since then. Oh, Dave, you got here quickly. Hello? Oh, there we go. Well, I was
told to hurry here. I was on vacation, you know. So where's the sushi at? Don't rush yourself. Have
a look around. Look at this giant blue hole. I've never seen anything like this. It's not just the
size. Every time you enter the giant blue hole, the terrain and ecology changes, which means
this could be an incredible business opportunity. What kind of business? Well, we can discuss that
later. I heard you took a break from diving. How about warming up? I'll guide you from here. Go
ahead and go in. I don't have a good feeling about this. Okay. A sushi bar. Try moving with,
oh, which one is, what is that? I have X, Y, A, and B. Is it a bumper? Left bumper?
A shitload of you just screamed at the screen. I'm just relaxed. Okay. That was a test. That was a
test to see how patient you really are. And a lot of you aren't. Move to the marked area. So this is
like a boost. How's the volume? Good? Okay. The dive knife. Use the dive knife. Ooh, smooth and quick.
Finally, you haven't forgotten how to use the harpoon, have you? Harpoon? Well, I haven't used
one in a long time. I came first. It looks like you need some practice. Try the harpoon to catch,
let's say, three fish. Got a huge announcement, by the way. I have an unbelievably massive
announcement, and I waited until this many people were here to tell you it. Massive announcement.
Unbelievably massive. Ladies and gentlemen, the first ever House Flipper Invitational,
where a bunch of streamers make a house and I have to grade it, is officially on Monday.
Monday at 4 o'clock Pacific. Time might change, but Monday the 3rd is the House Flipper Invitational.
Well, that's what I'm calling it. There's no official, nothing official with House Flipper,
but I think that's going to be a ton of fun. Whoa. Aim with A and press right trigger to fire. Oh,
I get it. That's sick. I will announce who is going to be in it, probably on Twitter and on
Discord and everything, and they'll probably talk about it too, but so far I've been reaching
out to people. So far we've got, we've got a good group so far. And just in case anything comes up
and the kind of roster changes, I'll wait like another day or two. But yeah, we got some good,
good people coming up. It's going to be a lot of fun. I'll have different grading criteria.
Everybody gets, and here, this is actually, here, hear me out. Is 60 minutes, if everybody starts at
the same time, is his ass has no plan. I got a whole document written. I have 60 minutes.
Everybody starts at the same time and everybody's graded on five different criteria.
Do you think 60 minutes is enough time? You're stuttering today. Yeah, I know. I'm a stuttering
guy. I'm usually like that. And when I don't feel that great, it's like amplified. So you're going
to get like triple the stutters today. Is 90 better? I feel like 90 was what it was originally,
but I'm kind of afraid to have it be 90. I feel like 90 might be a little too long.
The last time when me and Ludwig did this for the bro versus bro, it was 40 minutes and it felt like
it was okay. It was all right, but I would have liked a little bit more time, but not that much
more. 75 split the difference. We'll see. But it's somewhere, somewhere between 60 and 90 minutes
is what it will be. Yeah. Everyone's going to start with the same house and everyone starts at
the same time. It's going to be like a chopped on food network scenario where it's like, hands up,
everybody stop. Okay. I got to read this. Hold on. 75 is good. I think we start with 60 and then we
can add time if we want to. We can do like a, let's veto everything and add 15 minutes, depending.
Who knows? It could get to a point where we get to 55 minutes or like 45 minutes and everybody's
just done. Like, oh, okay. Cause I want it to be pressure. They're going to be graded on creativity,
complexity, cleanliness, structural integrity, philosophy. I've got a whole five point system
and they have to take me through a tour of the house one by one. Philosophy. Yeah. Oh, by the
way, and chats grade on, and there's going to be a weighted scale. I put a lot of thought into this.
I tell you, I've got, I got a whole document with all my things in it. Yeah. Chat will get a grade.
When are you going to do a twerking competition? All right. Yeah. That's a, that's coming up on
Monday. Now it's possible that some things need to be changed. This is, you know, I'm going to,
I'm leaving it up in the air, but July 3rd is the date. Gotta make sure to get everybody at the same
time. A lot of people have different schedules, trying to get a bunch of people to do it at the
same time. So I'll give you more info this coming weekend. So just get the ingredients.
You got it. So I can eat as much sushi as I want. Yeah, sure. You have to pay though.
Let's check it out. Go sushi. His ass is not reading. Well, I'm reading some of it.
Okay, let's go. It's already finished. You, you're the fisherman Cobra was talking about.
Well, I'm more of a diver than a fisherman. All right. Anyway, it's nice to meet you. I'm
Bansho. So you like sushi? Sure do. Tuna belly, eel, sirloin, oh boy, just think about it makes
my mind water. Just as mediocre as I expected. Sushi is a food that combines the soul of sea
and land. It symbolizes mother nature herself. Most people, however, have only tasted more
accessible fish, just like you. How empty a life is one that ends without ever tasting the beauty
mother nature can offer. My calling is to bring the taste of mother nature to every...
What's wrong with those choices? What's wrong with tuna? An earthquake. The interior is really quite
a mess. Looks like we're gonna have to delay the opening. You know what? Spend all my money
getting this restaurant ready. I'll have to recover the repair costs though doing business.
In this state? Well, ha ha ha ha. In the end, the importance of a restaurant is the taste.
First we need ingredients. Did you bring anything? Well, I have something I just caught.
Only three fish. This won't be nearly enough to serve the guests. Please go and catch seven
more fish. The restaurant's gonna be open only in the evening. Okay. What? It's the chef's duty
to prepare the best possible food with meticulous precision, just as a warrior sharpens his sword
on a whetstone. You need to get me the best quality ingredients during the day. I can do that.
People are so mad. Why? Because of my blah ha ha ha? I think every blah ha ha ha that I do,
I lose like 50 followers. I have to be careful. How many followers do I have? How many times can
I do blah ha ha and lose 50 people a day before I lose all these followers? I wonder how long
it would take. It's probably gonna take a while. I'll be all right. I've been seeing
Banshee so enthusiastic since the incident. Oops, maybe I shouldn't have brought that up.
Well, anyways, we need more ingredients. Go catch seven fish. Followers plummeting.
No, no, my followers, my followers. Okay. Make a hundred gold and catch fish. Let's do it.
You go deeper than your current equipment allows. Your oxygen will flash red and will
deplete quickly. Okay. Catch fish. Make money. I got it. Does it matter what fish I get?
This one pyramid butterfly fish. Do I, does the quality go down if I use the harpoon?
Kind of like a Red Dead Redemption situation. Like am I messing up the quality? No. Okay.
Nah. All right. Good. Oh, look at these ones. What's that? I can't pick it up. Really?
Do I need a better harpoon? Oh, you just have to tap it. Okay. You need to weaken them if
their HP is too high. Okay. So do I, do I have to go up or will it kind of be like,
Hey, your oxygen is low. It's time to end the day. Or do I have to physically go all the way up
physically with the character? What is that? Ooh. Okay. The O2 just is the timer. You do not have
to go up. Okay. So I get to increase time by seeing those on the ground. Got it. I'm gonna
just only go for these ones. Two times with the harpoon. What's in the pot? Potion? Soy sauce.
New. Do I have to make recipes or something? What about the giant eel? Can I die? Okay. I
think I can die. So that's a bad idea. That thing looks rare. Running out of air. Warning. Give me
this first. All right. Go. Do I have to go up? I thought you guys said I didn't have to go up.
You said I didn't have to go up. Did one guy do that? Do you still need oxygen? I definitely
made 100. Prepare sushi ingredients. Ooh. Okay. Biggest fish was that one. Two stars. Cooking
ingredients? Fish. Two fish tank. Do I have to wrap up your day and get things ready at the
sushi place? Okay. You can only dive once in the morning and once in the afternoon. Get the
ingredients ready before the dinner hours start. Isn't it like 10 o'clock at night? What time is
it? It's late. How about you let me play this game? We'll just go get it. It's on steam right now.
Okay. Bring ingredients back. Okay. You can check your fish, crops, sauces, and all the other
materials you have. For now, that's all you need to know. Come back later for more information.
I have to make a menu? New recipes need to be added to the menu before they can be sold to
customers. There's a sushi recipe for the fish you acquired earlier, so try registering that
to the menu. What do we got? Clown fish sushi. What's the most expensive one? Four? Ten? This
one's ten. Add three. E-clown sushi. Setting ingredients to auto-supply will make things a
bit more convenient. Let me repeat. Only food on the menu can be sold. If you run out of ingredients,
you'll have to replace items on the menu or refill the ingredients. You can enhance the flavor with
the soy sauce. Okay. Just put the most expensive ones on. This one's, this one's nine. I can put
12 on here. Okay. Spill the whole menu out. Six and then four. Prawns are high. All right. That's
good, right? Give me a cup of green tea. Have you poured green tea before? No, only soft drinks.
You only had soda? Is this like Diner Dash? Do I have to do a Diner Dash game? Pour the right amount.
It kept going. It's good it was the tutorial because that kept pouring. I'm not doing it.
Wait until the cooking is done. Is there a sprint? Come over to where I am. Take the food.
Take up the food. You can dash when serving food. Can I drop it? What the hell? The food can't be
reused with throw it out. It's such a waste. We never reuse food. We do not put food made for
guests on the table twice. And I just eat it? Don't forget to press Y after filling the menu
for business to begin. All right. Open the business. What can I get you? Green tea? We got it.
That's pretty good. All right. What do you want? Who ordered first? I don't remember. I'm already
out of stamina. Does somebody's leave unhappy? I can only go as fast as he can cook. Anybody need
tea? Does anybody need any tea? I have to clean. You ordered first, but whatever. This is what
I'm talking about. Yep. I have negative $52. Wait, what? Oh, right, right, right. Okay. I was going
to say, what did I do? My service so bad that I have to pay. Not quite there, but in its debt.
It's debt. All right. $77. So I got to get some better stuff. This game's cool. I like this game.
You're a bit clumsy, but not bad for a first day. Try a little harder next time. Okay. He likes it.
What are you doing? All right. This game keeps changing the game that I think it is
every 10 minutes. There are gigantic monsters. There's a lot to this game, to be honest. Yeah,
this looks cool. Are you the man who's been diving around here? I think so. I was expecting a more
professional looking guy. I can hear you. In any case, can you do something for me? Can you tell
me who you are first? I'm Ellie. I study biology at the local graduate school. I've come out to
investigate after reports of anomalies in the area. Satisfied? Okay. So what do you want?
I'd like to study the ecology of this blue hole. Get me some agar and red starfish. I don't think
it's a good idea to ask for just one of each, so get me two. Your tone makes me want to refuse.
Got a reward. If you don't want it, that's fine. Reward? This is a side quest I'm imagining, right?
Okay. Phone. Wait, he's on the boat. A waste of phone fees. Talk to me in person. Throw the
phone into the ocean. All right. That's, that's cool. Let's go. I get it now. Call them again.
You definitely don't get it. I, of course I do. Watch. I want to pick up ingredients. All right.
Only good fish. I don't want, like, look at this is, it's not gonna wow anybody at the restaurant.
Underwater scooter? Allows you to move quickly underwater. Can't be used once the battery runs
out. 10 second of battery use? Oh, so it's a, it's a boost. He thinks the big fish equal best fish.
Early on, I would say that's probably accurate. Sword? Ooh. Does this thing have durability?
Blue tang? Rainbow rice? Rassy? Ras? What was it? You're wasting oxygen. How do you think
Peter Griffin would feel about this game? Uh, I'm sorry. Peter Griffin wouldn't play this game.
Peter Griffin would do a callback reference to when he was the main character of this game.
You've got your family guy wrong. Oh, it hurts. I don't think sea urchin is gonna be picked up
with these gloves. Really? He's so mad. I, I'm not picking that up yet. I don't need it yet.
Ooh, look at these ones. I need those. These are gonna be so expensive. He is seething with rage.
What's that big one right there? Okay. That, that attacked me. If you exceed your weight limit,
you will slow down. If you exceed an even higher amount, you won't be able to carry anymore.
Organize? Overburdened? Uh, what's the shittiest thing I have? This thing's pretty awful,
but it's the one I just got. Take off. It's the, your oxygen mask. Uh, this thing's like,
eh, this is just seaweed. Okay. These are two stars. I'm almost there. I, should I go up now?
9.7, 9.1. Okay. Well, I have to go up. Nice math. I'm learning. I just, I just learned.
Skulls indicate poison. Let me go back up. I have a full inventory. You're playing it wrong.
It's the second dive. I got a, I got a trigger fish. Those things are worth millions of
decimal points. I did notice that the fish in the blue hole have an odd violent streak. Something
puts them on edge. Speaking of which, why don't you also take a gun in addition to the harpoon?
A gun. My friend who's knowledgeable about guns. Who's the goofy guy? I'm Dave. I thought divers
were athletic and muscular. You seem to defy my prior knowledge. People who live in glass houses.
Oh yeah, that's right. So what's this about? I'd like to get straight to the point. I've begun a
very interesting business. This guy laughs a lot. And now I'm in need of some weapons. Duff, I need
your help. Hmm. Season two of The Straw Stella just ended anyway. I'll give you a listen. I
discovered a fascinating giant blue hole. The terrain and ecology inside, it changes every
time you go inside. Any equipment found inside breaks down when brought out. I'd like you to
make us a weapon that can be used inside. Anything that's not made from materials found in the blue
hole will continue to break down. So it'd be especially true of guns, precision parts. So
we'll have to get the materials from overseas. I thought that just said from overseas. I was like,
what? Okay. I need one rope and one scrap iron. You heard him right, Dave. Enter the blue hole and
bring back rope and scrap iron. If you run out of oxygen midway, you'll only be able to make it
back with one item. So that's the penalty. Okay. Um, I have to, I have to get rid of stuff. Can I
store the fish that I have right now? Or should I just bring them over to the menu? Cause I can
die again. You already did. Oh, so I can go back now. You already did that. Your inventory is auto.
Okay. I'll go back down. I need rope, iron, sunflower update. We're getting some really good
pictures. They just started opening as of two or three days ago. The last three or four days,
I want to say. We have a Hydra. This thing was really healthy and was really, it was fed very
well apparently. This sunflower, the big one has like eight heads. It's going to be crazy looking.
All right. Can I pick this up? Starfish. All right. There's that. I need two of those.
Ow. What? I need a scrap of iron. This is wood. All right. Don't use too much oxygen. I don't know.
Why is this depth blinking? The depth thing is blinking. Why? I'm too deep. Am I? Am I actually
too deep? But there's rope down here and wood. All right. I need one more. Where's my, um,
quest log? I need one more. All right. Go up, go up, go up. I need oxygen. I gotta get out of here.
Hurry up and get out of here. Shit. I thought I was going to die much quicker than that.
You have the harpoon. I do have the harpoon. You're right. Basic underwater rifle. Download
Duff's weapon shop. Only 42 megabytes. What the hell is going on? There was a missed opportunity
there. I feel like this is the character that would say exquisite. This is exquisite, right?
So this replaces the harpoon, I'm going to imagine. I can open a weapon chest.
Blueprints. So if I make it with a blueprint, they won't break down underwater.
Nice. I hope that when you're 50, you look back at what you said and cringe.
Ball fondler. Why are there like three of you now? I just read another, I've read a ball fondler
comment 10, 20 minutes ago. It was a different, it was a different account. Why are there like five
of you? I'm so confused. It's not the same person. It's a different account. These are fake accounts.
We'll just ban them all. Do we just ban any type? If you, if your name has ball fondler in it,
like you're just gone. It's just like, just not allowed on this stream. That's funny.
Everyone but the OG gets banned. That's funny. Somebody said, stop giving attention to these
people. Yeah. You know what? That's also right. That's also a correct statement too. Okay.
You can craft weapons now. All right. Wrap up the day and let's go. Yeah. Let's go do it.
Ban the false fondlers. I did nothing good, sir. Yeah. Yeah. That's debatable. That's debatable,
but no. Okay. All right. Who with a high taste score will increase customer satisfaction. He's
innocent. All right. Let me check the menu. What can I do? Level one. I can enhance it. Hold on.
What's the most expensive thing I have Mediterranean parrot fish and I can make it better with what do
I have? How do I make it better? Do I have to pay? But I have to give fish to make it better. What
am I losing by doing this? I'm losing three fish VIP ball fondler. So you know who the real one is.
I don't want to VIP ball fondler. I feel like that would all of a sudden ball fondler would
have like a massive ego trip. I think. No, that's not happening. I think we would get ball fondler
being like, do you know who I am type of scenarios? We're not having that here. It says Mr. Ego.
This is my channel. This is my stream. It says Mr. Ego. That's so funny. Do you have any idea
who he is? Yeah. I know who he is. This one can be enhanced. All right. I only have one of these.
So let's do the expensive items first. I only have one. These are, these are all right. Wait,
is this going to kill somebody? You guys said this was poisonous. Whatever. You only have four
sushi for sale. Well, I'm just trying to get to a hundred bucks. I'll be all right. Green tea. I
got you right here. Almost perfect for. Oh yeah. Okay. Now I know that that's the fake one. That's
okay. Now I know that's the fake one. A ball fondler account just said, Hey, give me 20 bucks.
All right. That's now I know you're absolutely not the real one. Somebody said, I want 20 bucks too.
Oh man. Yeah. Please be careful. Me too. Me too. I wanted to don't get tricked by any fake ball
fondler accounts, please. Or even from the real one. Don't you know what I'm saying? Like just be
diligent. 55. He tricked you into a six month of one guy, but it was all right. You can't deny
that the original ball fondler arc was not really funny. You can't deny that. It was.
Nobody can deny that. Okay. So we did the repair. I'm Dr. Bacon. I'm an archaeologist who studies
the sea people civilization, the sea people. I'll explain it to you. Aren't you lucky to have an
expert like me tell you about it? Okay. They worshiped fish and had gills allowing them to
live underwater. They live in the depths, allowing them to flourish without any concern for invasions
by other civilizations. The sudden changes to the sea bottom brought about their abrupt downfall.
About all there is. Everyone thinks it's a myth and nothing more, of course. The proof that they
were real was found right in the vicinity of this place. An amazing find. A lot of people want me
to do a lot of different things here. Okay. My assistant closely analyzed an artifact found
nearby and found that it is from no known civilization. It's dated to around 1500 years
ago as well. There were no civilizations in these parts back then. That's interesting. What business
do you have with me? Well, you see, my assistant's cryptocurrency investments didn't pan out and he
won't be around for a good while. That's why I'd like you to help me. My assistant told me that
the artifact was found 70 meters or so below the surface. Please go take a look. We're busy with the
sushi bar. I don't think we can. Sorry to interrupt the conversation. I'm Cobra. I work with Dave.
Of course we should help you. We'll gladly do so. What? We don't have time for this.
Swim around. Look for artifacts. Think about it. If an underwater civilization is discovered,
countless people will flock here. Bancho sushi will be bursting at the seams. What was that?
You have a point. All right, I'll help. Isn't that lucky? Of course. I won't be asking you to work
for free. I'll upgrade the diving suit you're wearing for free. With an enhanced diving suit,
you'll be able to venture deeper. This is essential for exploration. These days,
even such things can be handled by an app. Technological advancements are amazing, eh?
Let's first install the iDiver app on the phone before we proceed.
Okay, so you can upgrade. I love upgrades. I have a question for the chat. I love upgrades.
If there's a game where the oxygen tank is level one and you can get it to level 20,
what is the best one that I have not played? That's not a question. You had needed to wait
for two or three sentences to come up. What is like an unbelievable upgrade game? People say in
Subnautica. Really? I feel like I played Subnautica. Is that like an upgrade game? I love upgrades,
just to start timing these people up permanently for one minute. Upgrades! Upgrades! You all love
upgrades. These games sell like crazy and it's because you like to see the number go a little
higher every few minutes. I still need that starfish. Stardew Valley. Yeah, Stardew Valley. I've
played it a lot though. What's this one? Uh, idle games? Yeah, I've played a lot of them.
Factorio. I feel like I'm not smart enough to play Factorio. Factorio to me just kind of seemed
this is a lot of information that I don't know. Graveyard Keeper has a lot. I'm dumb as bricks
and it's fun. Maybe I'll check it out. The game you are playing right now, dude. All right,
I'm into it. Hey guys, give me like a good game that has a bunch of upgrades and it's like really
fun. It's like tons of stuff to do and good things to collect. Yeah, I think I don't think
I'll play this game again. What I'm playing right now. Yeah, I'm maybe like I'll try it like later.
It's like it's this one. All right, wait, what did I just get? Basic rifle, triple axle. This is worse
than what I have on. Metroid. Oh, sorry. I've been sitting here silently. So how does it work? Oh,
it's a gun. So wait, do I just, how much are these worth? If I, yeah, yeah, yeah. It is like Red Dead,
isn't it? This is definitely like Red Dead. I can destroy the meat, right? 100%. I need one of those
tanks. What's this? Ammo box. Orange juice just went up my nose. Stop making me laugh. Wait, you
just, you just distracted me and got me. You know, hold on. I'm gonna die. Swimming fat. I can't get
the pot right now. Try Ilona. You actually brought them back. I guess I expected too little of you.
This should do for now. Here's a reward. $70. Five olive oils and five soy sauce.
Animal Crossing is that game. Yeah, I have a really shit take that all of you are going to be mad
about, but I just, I have a lot of trouble getting into Animal Crossing because every time I've ever
played Animal, I play it at like two o'clock in the morning every single time and it works on real time.
So when I'm lying in bed, it's like, oh yeah, let me check on Animal Crossing. It's like 2 a.m.
every day. It's just like, I can't really even do anything. And then it's like, well, just change
the clock on your Wii or on your Switch. And it's like, I don't want to, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to go into my settings and change the clock a day forward, go back out of the menu,
go back into the game, reset the game and no, that is the solution. But then I forget about that and
it'll be like December, not time traveling. I would love an Animal Crossing, like Animal Crossing,
I would love an Animal Crossing colon game. Do you know what I mean? Like Animal Crossing colon,
let's get to it. And it's just, there's no time stuff. It's just, it's not like a main
Animal Crossing game. You know what I'm saying? Animal Crossing colon, up and at them. And that,
they call it that. And it has the colon because it's a different game.
You guys don't know, you guys make fun of me for grammar. You guys don't, I'm a colon, semi-colon,
colon. Okay. You can decorate. That's cool. Animal Crossing colon, New Horizons.
They all have colons, don't they? Do they all have colons? Is it Animal Crossing colon?
What are they all? They have to be, right? Animal Crossing colon,
new leaf or something, right? Animal Crossing colon, New Horizons, Animal Crossing colon.
It's okay. That shows you how much I've played those games. When was the last time that they,
have they ever numbered Animal Crossing? No. Social media app? No, that would be silly.
I love the theory of Animal Crossing. It's a wonderful theory, but for me, I'm just so,
I play every game on my own time, not on stream after like 12 o'clock every day, midnight.
And then I'll look up stuff about, oh yeah, well, as long as you play
at 9 AM, this bug exists. And it's like, I, the first thing I do at 9 AM, I'm going to forget,
I'm not going to wake up and play Animal Crossing. I'm going to forget about that.
Ever since the Zoom beanies stream, I get mid-roll ads. Uh, you shouldn't be. I mean,
I'm not running them. Oh wait, hold on a second. Oh shit. I think you did probably get caught in the,
I did run an ad when I was like fucking with everybody. Um, apologize about that. Yeah.
It's possible that you joined right. And that right when I was doing that stupid, like,
please play ad joke thing. Cause I think that's when I did that. But if that's not the case,
then I don't know. I'm not running them here. Hey, more customers will visit new foods would
be unlocked. 65, 65. I'll keep the one I have. All right. Now I got to go into the app and post
about the restaurant. I got to give it a like. Oh, I can do this. Rank up followers. I need 10
followers. Should I just go through and like everything? Let's get the menu gone. I don't
know how to use social media. I just don't do it. I know how to use it, but I just don't.
I got three mid roll ads on the next best stream and one on this. I don't know what they're doing.
Yeah. I'm I'll look in my dashboard and make sure I, cause I'm unless that's like automatically
happening. It shouldn't be. All right. Menu 20 bucks, 20 bucks. I got two of these now open.
What is this ingredients? Oh, I can sell these just as they are. That's cool.
Oh, cause you open at night. Should I sell some of this? Might as well. Just the stuff I'm not
using. I'm not going to sell the condiments or anything though. Stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop. Don't sell. Don't sell. Don't sell. That actually a bad idea. Okay. Do you like the beach?
I do. I haven't been in a long time though, cause obviously where I live.
I'm going to try to go down deep. I'm not picking up any boxes or anything. It's all a beach where
you live. Well, I mean, beach implies water. There is no water. Dolphin. Follow it. I'm not going to
shoot the dolphin with the harpoon for relax. A pink dolphin is caught in the net. You guys have
money. That's the noise I was waiting for that. I was waiting for that. A gift. Pearl. All right.
I got to go down to 70 meters. Wait, this is a, this is better. Yeah. Cause they don't, it doesn't
mess up the meter or anything. All right. Let's try that. Let me see. Oh, that's a great job.
All right. Pick it up. How do I pick it up? There we go. Oh, this is a three star. I wonder,
is this fish expensive? Underwater scooter. That's actually good to have right now. All right. I'm
going to just try to go fast to the bottom. You need to get to 70. Uh, I have to go back up.
Escape pod, escape pod. Let me get these fish here. Really drowning. I have 25. I'm all right
for now. This is an escape pod. Wait, this is not an escape pod. Okay. All right. All right. Right.
Right. All right. I could have stayed down there a little longer. Okay. It's already evening. I feel
stiff. All right. I have a lot of materials. Play Assassin's Creed Black Flag. I made a video on
Assassin's Creed Black Flag like seven years ago. I don't know how good the video is, but I made it.
I don't really remember. It got an update. This is a food critic. This place is getting
popular on cook stuff. The name gave me pause, but to think it's really your place. New food
using ever-before-seen ingredients. Can't taste this anywhere else. Did they mention me too?
No, not really. Brings you all the way here. Want to check out the restaurant. Looks like
you're still the same. Okay. You refused to listen to me last time in a similar fashion,
and that's what got you booted from the hotel. Talking about that again. It's the customer's
fault for judging the food without even trying it. Who was the shit character from the Black Flag
video that ended up in the rumble? I, wait, you're pulling out a memory here. I don't know. Those of
that don't know, there was a tradition on this channel on YouTube and on Twitch up until pretty
recently where I would, over the course of a year, every character that was kind of meaningful
in any game or any kind of joke, they would all fight in a rumble at the end of the year.
And sometimes those characters, it'd be like 20, 30, 40 of them sometimes. And it was like,
I always wanted a lot. So it's like, wait, who can I even, who could I even have pull from? What
game did I play this last year? And sometimes you had to dig pretty deep. And that's how you get
like the random captain from Assassin's Creed Black Flag. It's like, oh, I guess that guy,
like somebody thought that guy was funny for a minute. So sometimes you have to really dig deep,
find characters for the rumble, but they're always fun. Every serpent. Yeah, that was the,
that was the filler arc for the rumble, I think was all seven serpents from,
when sorcery, when I first did sorcery, half of the entire roster of the rumble was sorcery
characters. So many, I think it was a half the rumble and then all the planets. Yeah,
I had to dig deep on that one. You're just not going to do them ever again.
No, I think what happened was the games got kind of like, like the 2K games,
it had like this crazy creation suite back in like the early 2010s into the mid 2010s.
And then it just kind of became less like goofy and more kind of simulation based. And it's just
like, okay. And then after a while, you kind of you've done it enough times, you kind of the same
joke, start repeating over and over again. It's like, all right, that was fun. It needs to be
fresh for me to want to do it again, I think. What about the live rumble? Yeah, that's, that's been
floating around for a long time. It has been floating around for years at this point, besides
the one that I did on YouTube. I'll find a way to make it fresh. And the, the wrestling,
wrestling empire was sort of just like fun to play and mess around in. Okay, please get me a
white tip reef shark head and olive oil. Shark? Okay, get a shark head and need a gun. I already
have one, don't I? Sometimes special customers with a backstory will hear of the sushi bar and
visit. Learn dishes that the customers want through research and serve them to the customers, okay.
You can now research new recipes. Use the artisan's flame. Artisan's flame research.
The head of a white reef shark that's been deep fried whole. I only have eight of these.
53. Geez, okay. What's the menu look like? Looks pretty good. What can I get here today? I don't
have a shark head. Didn't you just watch us talk about how I don't have that? I thought you were
a vegan furry. I'm leaving. Perfect four, watch this. Perfect four, watch this. Vegan furry.
What was that again? I misread what somebody wrote in the chat. I don't remember.
I'd like to come again. Nice. Somebody said very funny. Ah, that's what it was. Very funny. Yeah,
I got kind of like all twisted up about it. I was like, what are you talking about? Like,
what the fuck are you talking about? Why are you saying that to me? And they were just giving me
a compliment. How do I misread it so much? Chat moves really fast, okay. There's a new post?
Should I make a post? I don't know. Do I really? I don't want to be the guy that likes every single
post from everyone, right? Or do I? You know why I don't like to be that guy? Why I don't want to
be that guy? Because if you don't do it, if I didn't, like let's say Glenn came in and I didn't do
it to Glenn. Like I just didn't do it one day, but I did it for everyone else. That kind of makes me
look like a shithead, doesn't it? Like, oh, why didn't they like my post? I saw you liked Luna's
post and CCJY's post and Rose Pink post, but you didn't, you didn't like mine. That's overthinking
it. I don't think so. Overthinking social media. Social media is a fucked up place. What do you
mean overthinking social media? Wait, do these people? All right, let's just call Dr. Bacon.
Do you have the mini game app? Where's the mini game app? What? I don't have any games. Wait,
where is my? Oh, there it is. Okay. I definitely want this. Cargo box. I think that's what I want
first. Upgrades, upgrades. I'd love upgrades. Dr. Bacon is my goat. What would you do if the
internet disappeared? Find something else to fucking do. I need to go down to 70 meters. I
keep not doing this. Goofy hammer? Rubber toy hammer. It doesn't do much damage, but
sometimes I put him to sleep. Whoa. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Leave me the fuck alone. I need to pick this thing up. What's going on? You piece of shit.
I cannot believe what just happened. Leave me alone. What do you mean? No. What? I can't pick
it up. Gold or something. What is this? Dinosaur bones? All right. I'm almost at 70. There's
oxygen right here. Holy shit. I got lead. Should I be touching this? Okay. We're good. All right.
I got to go down to 70 and look for artifacts. This might be one right here. Text in my mother
and I'm done. All right. I'm ready to go. What was that just now? To go back to the boat. What?
Is that? He thinks he's a funny guy. Well, I need to get rid of it. Should I attack this? I have a
gun. There's some weird animals in the ocean. I got to get some ingredients. What's that? What's
that? All right. I got to go now. Get the big one. I can't. I need like a submarine or something.
You can just kill the big one. What's your Twitch? Twitch.tv slash. So what do I unlock for this?
Okay. I'll be in touch. Can you link your Twitch? I don't know how to do that though.
I think there's like a way to copy text and paste it. Magic. All right. I think I have enough.
New character. Hopity hop. You do know a lot about this giant blue hole. Okay.
Is the best place to collect? Marinka? Marinka. Trading cards. Marinka.
Uteristic trading cards that utilize an AI recognition system that automatically
corresponds to fish in real life. Never heard of it. You seem quite behind. Let me help you
install the app. Do this. Do this. Do this. Done. Done. All right. All right. You don't really need
to do anything special. Just catch a new fish and you'll get a card. Check the cards every now and
then on the app and you're done. Okay. You don't want to be saying the name. I understand. I'll
try it out. I'm Sato. All right. Cool. Marine cards. Fancy your cards for catching higher grade fish.
I got a lot of money. I'm going to upgrade the gun because look at how much more damage that is.
It's ridiculous. I used all my money but it was worth it. I love upgrades. I really do. So what's
an expensive fish of these? I guess I could just look. I should just get as many as I can really.
What about a seahorse? I don't want to kill the seahorse. Is that weird? Oh I can't even.
There we go. These are expensive. Iron. These red fish they have a lot of utilization. Damn it.
Damn it. I'm playing with a controller so that's my excuse. Oxygen capsule. That's helpful.
Lightning harpoon. Harpoon tip charged with high voltage. Chain damage. Does that not work? Whoa
what's happening? Whoa. This must be shocking things around. Oh hold on. I'm running out of uh
I gotta go up. Will I keep this oxygen capsule till later if I can make it all the way up? What
do I have to get rid of? I don't want rope. This thing is I mean it's all right. It weighs a lot.
Eh whatever. What if you sneeze underwater like this? Excuse me. Yes it was real. I should make
some good money. This dude just sneezed for attention. That's a wild sentence. That is an
insane sentence. Level three. Let's upgrade. Pretty much upgrade everything. Upgrade again.
Upgrade everything. What is omega lull? It means happy birthday. It's usually somebody's birthday.
They're saying happy birthday too. A lot of birthdays today. You really had to dig for that
one. It's a um it means uh it means uh happy birthday. See there would be a cut there. This
is live. We're live. It would be like what's omega lull? Well happy birthday. He just didn't get the
audio cut and that's all right. That tea is chunky. Yeah it is. Lean quick. How's the progress on the
video you're making? Steady. Steady. We got new food. Kitchen staff. Is this video 10 years in
the making? Not really. When it comes out you'll know but we'll do a premiere. I made a lot more
money today. Can you do an impression of German985? I could try. I don't know him that well but let me
see. Hey I mean what about the aliens? Just aliens? How do we even tell the aliens that we're people?
How can we possibly describe electricity to the aliens? He kind of talks like that doesn't he?
That's not bad. He's not really close. I don't fucking know the guy. You're acting like I know
this guy. One off the cuff message from chat and I'm just trying to... I don't know this person.
Oh I got a radar. Your voice wasn't nasally enough? Nasally? Do I have a nasally voice? No I don't do
I? My voice is not nasally. Nasally. You mean nasally like this? Like that? Like this? I don't
have a nasally voice. How do we tell him? Let's test the radar. His voice is way milkier than that.
I know. I agree. He doesn't have... he didn't do the velvety buttery voice that he had. Buttery. I don't
like when voices are described as buttery. He's like stop. He's got a smooth buttery voice. Butter?
I only want it on fucking toast. Stop. Everywhere else. Unless it's like for you know obviously
just don't make butter a description for talking is what I mean. Oh the dolphin again. Again? Pirates
must have captured it illegally. Somebody just shot me with a gun. Who just shot me? Some people
are shooting at me. They'll shoot back. What's up bro? Oh I can't. Fuck you. Fuck you. What did you
say? Morgan Freeman voice. I wish I could have it on repeat. It's always the same thing.
I could probably speak dolphin. If you put me with some dolphins and I was just like
I would get viciously fucking murdered and it would rip out my eyes and eat all my organs and shit.
Gold bar. That's pretty huge. I want to find something new. This is kind of new. Have I had
a pinkfish before? A sea goldie. Can you make a real dolphin noise? Blueprint. Nice. That's a big
deal. I need to get a shark. How deep do I have to go for a shark? Nice. All right find a shark.
That's not a shark is it? No. That's a salmon. These things have a lot of health. Hey salmon
mackerel. Don't bite me. I thought it was gonna bite me. Well now I want that. Give me this. Indeed
this is my award-winning restaurant. My accolades. All right I gotta go up. Not before I pick up this
though. Why is he doing the pac-man confused thing from the pac-man game? Look. Look. I can't drop
anything. I just gotta go. Dave is going to die. Dave is gonna be fine. You're in the ocean?
Pirates? Sharks usually are near the surface. I'll check it out after this. What is that pac-man
game called? That's right. Pac-man like the new adventures or something right? Super Nintendo is
a side scrolling game. It was bizarre. It's a game where you had to tell pac-man to go you had to
control him with voice commands from a narrator and he was just sort of this weird childlike wonder
where he would walk around just look at stuff and he would get really distracted. Be like pac-man go
right and he would just be like and he would just go look at a butterfly. It was a really bizarre
game. I made a video on it but maybe one day I would stream it because it's so strange. I feel
like everyone needs to see it. Okay looking for a shark. I have a gun. Check the right side is what
people were saying. I couldn't swim down to what the radar is pointing me to. Uh that's way better.
It was from your what the fuck series. Pretty good one. It's copper? Okay cool. These are heavy
though. I don't want it. All right where's this shark? Olive oil. How long can you hold your breath?
Um probably not as short as you think. Two seconds. I mean I don't really care to try.
What's the average? What's the average? Average you know adult male that whatever what's like the
average? 30 you know let's say 35 year old. One to two minutes. This thing looks kind of this
thing's glowing isn't it? 30 to 90 seconds. There's a difference to me of holding my breath underwater
versus holding my breath just sitting here. I feel like I can hold it for much longer in
water. Does that make sense? Is there any scientific reason for that? All right I went
all the way right. I don't see a shark. That's an actual thing. I'm gonna pick this up and then go
down. Although I do want these sell for a lot. The hell just happened? Underwater you're not absorbing
any oxygen through the skin. That's not correct. I don't think that's correct. Why did I think
that was real for one second? Shock shock shock. This is mine. All right I gotta get up. I guess I
could get some of these. Hold on. I'm just going right up here anyways. What about the jellyfish?
That's one star. I didn't use a gun. Plenty of factors like pressure movement and exertion
and energy. Free diving or other types of swimming. Also depending on the amount of
oxygen percentages you take in. Hey just got here. Can you please tell me to fuck off? Thanks in
advance. Get the fuck out of here. I like the sniper rifle. We got a good menu tonight. This
is gonna be good. I bet I could do 60 seconds. Salt grilled. Oh this is a good one. 48 coins.
Let's do them all. Those things are so easy to get to. Okay so what can I do now? What do we got?
This one. This one is going on the menu because that's what the food critic wants.
I'm not gonna upgrade it. Okay salt. Where did I get salt? From the ocean? I calculated based on
your height and body weight and other factors. It is impossible for you to hold your breath for
60 seconds. You're smart chatter. You are tapping into insecurities of mine. Prove without me doing
it. That I can't do that. So like I calculated based on your height and like your weight and
everything. Oh you must have calculated it. All right bro. I'll prove you wrong. I know it's a
very good attempt. A really good attempt because you think oh well fuck you. I'm gonna go on full
cam and hold my breath till I turn fucking purple. Like no I'm not gonna do that. Yeah I don't think
I would have very much fun holding my breath as long as I could. No I'm just like playing Dave
the Diver you know. I'm just kind of hanging out. I don't think I want to hold my breath.
There's a lot of people here. Disgusting as usual. Apparently not disgusting. Yeah don't hold your
breath. Breathe. Don't be an idiot. Don't be stupid. All right I'm gonna hold my breath as long. Don't
do that. Don't be stupid. She really likes it. It is lovely. The book of five rings states that one
should look at the essence of something instead of its appearance. Okay you pass. Just pretend
you're holding your breath. How would chat even know? We mean go on cam and take a big
and puff my cheeks out but I'm just breathing through my nose the whole time.
I have a counter going in the corner. I'm just being like
like trying to communicate every such dog shit. How long can I hold my breath? Take a phone call
and do the thing where it's like yeah sorry man. I really gotta go. I gotta go. I'm doing
a thing on stream. I gotta go. Then puff the cheeks out again. Just do it without a face cam.
All right you guys ready? Time me. How long can I hold my breath for? You ready?
Oh that had to be like a minute. How long was that?
Jeez. How long was that? 10 seconds. That's gotta be a record.
You just take a screenshot of your face with your cheeks puffed out and closing your nose
with a timer going like hey I'm doing it right now. How long can I hold my breath? I'm still
talking over the stream. That doesn't make any sense. I am going for and right going for world
record. Play in silence. Oh I really wish I had clothing on. I wish I had a shirt on right now
and I am fucking gross. I oh man I have to like I haven't I like feel kind of like shit too.
Like this is not the day. All right save this. I promise I will do this on the next stream. Wait
the next stream is going to be the house flipper invitational joke thing. Maybe I'll just do it on
there and just everyone will think I'm a weirdo. We already have a screenshot. Wait why do you
all I hate this picture though. Okay anyone else? It's this one could do it. This image does not
convey I'm holding my breath. This is I'm holding in laughter. Oh that thing was so funny but I
can't laugh because then I'll lose. No that's not holding my breath. That's you laugh you lose.
I like this one. This one's so stupid. How long can I hold my breath for? I can't. I can't. It's
not even close. I am wicked red and this one is fucked. Okay this is definitely the one.
This is absolutely the one. Okay so then no hold on. Okay I need it needs to be a timer. Hold on
hold on a second. Let me get a timer. Okay stopwatch. Well no no not it needs to be yeah like
this. This is okay I like it though. Okay hold on. Is this one? No not that one. There it is. We got
to prepare this. It's very important. Okay I'm just cropping it so you can see it better.
All right you ready? All right I'm going for it. See how long I can do it for.
What's up? Yeah I'm in the middle of streaming. Yeah I'll call you in like a couple hours. All
right dude. All right yeah I'm streaming. Bye bye. Time what's that? 241 come on. And a phone call
in the middle. Yeah that was funny. That's literally nothing. That's a lot if I were to actually
do it. Don't try that at home by the way. You can actually hurt yourself doing that. Don't fuck
around. It's a funny bit but don't fuck around. It's actually kind of dangerous to do that to
yourself. All right I need it. Whoa it's all right. Okay mom. I just want to make sure people
understand that. Okay if that makes me mom then that makes me mom. But I'm gonna say it. Okay
mom. Look at it and all this is all ruined now. No it's the most expensive thing on the menu.
Oh but it's right here. It's right here. No no I just it's like when somebody's like towing
your car and you like walk out you're just like I'm fucking right here. God damn it. Who even
ordered this? Who ordered this? Why did he make this? Oh my god. It's because we did a little
routine. I had it up the whole time. There was a little routine we did. All right you can't say
that that's oh he's so bad. He's so bad. I literally stopped in the middle of that to do a I'm going
for the breath world record joke. Can I guess where this is from? This is this is from WarioWare
isn't it? This is a I'm mad at WarioWare face. Is that wrong? Rhythm heaven. Yep okay same kind
of genre. Yeah same genre. You were holding your breath the whole Wario stream. Nah you really are
impossible. Blue shells and brown shells. I can't understand your underlying anatomy in this picture.
What is your neck doing? Um well like we can examine it if you want. So that's that's my chin.
It's not my neck. This is where my face kind of ends but there's more face. That is really strange
looking isn't it? This is my chin. That's the bottom of my chin. See I have created a second
face on top of my face. That's gotta be worth something right? That's gotta be worth something.
Like a turtle going back into its shell. I might just do air twice. Oh I need 400. I'll save the
rest or can be crafted. Should I make this? Jerma you're wilding in the morning. I see why you
stream later. I feel like I've been pretty chilled out and kind of low key this stream. What do you
mean? I think I've been like kind of relaxing this whole time. This is a this is a little more
toned uh like dialed down like toned down. Should I make this? I already have one don't I?
You ever gonna go back to Final Fantasy 16? I want to but I think I'm gonna um think I'm just gonna
stream it. I'm gonna play it on my own time. Stream it on my own time? I don't know. Should
I have crafted that? I will. I was looking forward to it. I haven't completely ruled it out. Just
not uh there's like just other things that for instance the next time I'm streaming is
Monday and that's the house flipper invitational stream. So it would have to be after that. Oh a
lot of people weren't here. I could talk about it again. Actually let me go over a few really
important things because I think a lot of people trickled in over the last hour or two. Um in like
30 minutes or so we are going to raid uh Sea Dog Connor's stream. Connor is doing a charity auction
stream today and I have two different bundles in the event. Two Grotto Beast themed items bundles.
One of them's a raffle. One of them's an auction. That is where you are going. It's all benefiting
the Immune Deficiency Foundation. It's a lot of items. I'm not the only one. There is I believe
dozens and dozens and dozens of items from different streamers and youtubers that are going
up for auction and raffle. And I think the raffle my raffle my item I think is going to be pretty
early in the show. So make sure you go check that out. It's not the face mold. I told you no one's
getting that. In fact I I might just destroy it. It's really possible that I just destroy it because
it's like nobody can have this. It's just too just far too powerful of an object. I might just crush
it. You know what I mean? Like I know but that can't exist. But that's what's happening today.
Go support that stream regardless if there's items of mine that are in it. If you got some time
please support it. Also on Monday July 3rd we're doing a house flipper invitational
joke. It is not like actually officially endorsed by anything. Um just me and I got rewards for this.
Uh yeah so I'm gonna I'm trying to get like somewhere between five and ten streamers. I've
already reached out to a bunch of people already. We're gonna do a house flipper flip off where
everybody gets about 60 to 90 minutes. Everyone starts at the same time and everyone starts at
the same house. And then it's pencils down give me a tour now of your house. And I'm going to be
grading them on creativity, complexity, philosophy, theming, structural integrity, cleanliness. I have
an entire system and there is the object I need right there. Explain philosophy. Your design
philosophy. This is my grading system okay. You make your own grading system. Yeah there's a few
more people I'm going to reach out to this weekend. Tonight and tomorrow. I think it's going to be a
really fun time. I think it's going to be just jokey fun. Not going to be too serious. Just to
have some fun. What are you going to stream on your end? Dave the Diva. Now I'll probably
hang out in house flipper and sort of make my own maybe. Or just kind of be chilling out painting
walls. Yeah I am those of you that know me and those that have been you know invited or will
be invited. Why can I not catch this? There's a specific criteria that you should probably be
following. I'm not going to tell you how to make your house or anything but I cannot catch this
long time. I'm still contemplating if I want theming right. I give like a couple of words.
Let's just say I'm not going to use these because I don't want to you know this is not a leak.
Well let's just say that it was like okay and you're here at your house and your words are
sunshine dog food and pickles. What does that mean? You tell me. You tell me what that means.
That's a leak. No it's not. I'm not going to use those. I need one more blue shell and we're good
but I don't think I can get it. What brand of dog food did you have for breakfast today?
I actually had a coffee and that was it as of right now. I want to go deeper. No more this you
know like 50 meters candy. I want to go down to like 150. That's not breakfast dude eat something.
I usually do. I usually do. I usually do. I'll be all right don't worry. It's been like two hours
three hours. I usually will have some kefir. If you're a long time viewer of this channel you know
that kefir is a drink that I very much enjoy. He's always loved kefir. Of course I have. A very
great thing to consume. Good for you. Doesn't have any really like bullshit in it for your digestive
track. I need that now. You ever have peach flavored? I like blueberry kefir myself. Too
much kefir will cause kidney stones. Uh you're not you're not gonna be one of those people that's
like hey you know that if you eat too many apples it gives you you know fucking diarrhea. I'm not
gonna eat 10 apples. You said you love apples. I do like apples. Well but you you you must eat
three every day. I don't. Well why'd you say that then? You don't love apples then. I do.
Well then you must eat 10 a day. I don't. Do you think I can take them? That hurt a lot. God damn
it. Oh he's gonna cut me with it. Oh shit. What? Oh my god I have to get out of here right now.
Just eat this. Eat it. Eat it quick. We're good. You're back here. The wuss running away and that's
I got a shark meat but I love kefir. Oh you do? Improve it then. Drink a whole kefir right now.
It's really good. I promise. Does it actually give you kidney stones? Is that person full shit?
Bullshit. It has to be. It's yogurt. It's yogurt adjacent. It's a yogurt cousin. It's not.
It's yogurt. Research level gained. Eco watcher. Mission based app made to protect the environment.
You get points for completing missions on the app and get rewards for reaching certain levels.
This was for points on the app not for a paper. Oh dear. Dude kefir is a treatment for kidney stones.
There's a lot of just misinformation in this chat right now. I need a verified source. It can't just
be like fucking like Greg. Kefir kidney stones. I need to see what's going on here. It's good.
It's good for you. Don't listen to anybody. It literally helps with that. It helps with that.
WebMD Wilson. I don't know. Do you trust like bill from the subway or WebMD? I don't know. Which one
of those do you choose? Kefir is good for you and will help alleviate some gut bacteria issues
and is good for you and can help break up potential kidney stones. Hey that shit gives you kidney
stones. Don't listen to that fucking idiot. That's a liar. I would trust a real doctor and not a
website but you can't make an appointment to the doctor. Call the doctor. You can't call the doctor
and say hey doctor hi I'd like to have an appointment. Okay what are you coming in for?
Well you see um I just want to ask you a question. What do you okay you you're having any symptoms?
No I don't have any symptoms. What are you doing here? Well you see um do kefir cause kidney stones?
No. Okay you feel okay? I feel great. Okay bye. That's not how you don't you can't make it a
you don't go to like urgent care to ask that question. That's what your primary care doctor
is for. Yeah when you have like a an appointment like a physical yeah go ahead ask it but to make
an appointment specifically to ask the doctor if like eating watermelon will give you gas.
It's like I this this that's I don't think that's like a symptom. Getting a little scared of your
kefir consumption levels hmm. The whom on the end of that is my favorite. Okay we need another
staff member. Kitchen or dining area probably dining area. Training to consider. This is a
lot deeper than I thought this was a game where you swim around and collect fish. This is much
deeper than I thought it was going to be. I like it 150 to train. Yeah let's do it. Not too much
and not too little. Yeah do you guys honestly think the guy who has said Ben Franklin's name
probably more than every twitch streamer on this website combined ever you think is gonna
argue for like over consuming something. Oh I got 10 of these. He's in hell that's fine he's in hell
whatever whatever I what do you want to say. This dude takes advice from hell dwellers. A hell
dweller that's an interesting term. Hell dweller. All right this thing is look at the money I'm
gonna get from this. I gotta stop picking these up they're not worth anything anymore. I like the
way your earlobes stick out. Have a great stream. Hey thanks. First time chatter first thing you
ever said. Actually thank you. That's a good that's a compliment. Usually the first time chatters
say hey are you that guy that did X. Are you are you that guy that did this. I'm not even playing
the fucking game anymore. Like you see what's going on. Are you the sus guy. Are you the guy
that did X. You guys did Y. Right like are you that guy. I hate that guy. Somebody where's the
I should have put the person in the kitchen because I I don't know there's not enough food
to go around. There's not enough food to go around. He can't cook it fast enough. By the way don't I
have a staff member. What is going on. Where are they. Thank you. Thank you. Actually nice job.
Staff is asking for a raise. I have to return to that game one one day. It's been long enough I
think. I'm afraid to play Casino Inc because I feel like that's it's like the peak of my entire
Twitch career was how much fun I had in that game and I'm scared that I'll go back and taint it.
It almost lives as this perfect memory in my brain that I kind of don't want to mess with it.
Management app which works on your smartphone. Sounds handy.
Management app. All these apps. I think we're doing pretty good. Can never be replicated again. The
fire happening after waiting for it was the best build up and payoff that can never be replicated.
Yeah yeah at some point you know when you're doing a sequel you're just kind of grasping for that how
much fun you had and the sequel is just kind of like it was okay. We kind of remembered some of
the funny things. It's kind of funny because that's like my worst enemy is not wanting to do things
more than once. A lot of the shows and like events and stuff that you've seen I was just like no I
don't want to do this again like I want to do something else and it's kind of a detriment
because it's like well would you ever want to do like six or ten episodes of that and I'm just like
no not really and it's kind of a detriment sometimes. Can I get this now? That was sad.
That was really sad. I just shot this fish in the fucking head. That was like sad. That was kind of
sad. Am I poisoned? All right I'm going down deeper. I get bored incredibly easily
so and plus I don't know I feel like there's other ideas I like and I want to do. I feel like each
thing that I do is fun to have it live sort of in a little bubble on its own. It's typically how I
feel and this thing is aggressive. Do not please don't. Barracuda. I want a squid. I don't think
I've even found one of these yet. Yeah is Connor's stream live right now or is it starting soon?
10 minutes? Yeah. Again if you don't know what's going on in 10 minutes I'm going to dump you all
over on SeaDog on Connor's channel. There's a whole big charity auction stream going on today.
I have a couple of items that are included. One bundle is for the auction. One bundle is for a
raffle. So I believe they're doing my raffle bundle pretty early I think on the uh in the show. All
right last one and I'm gonna go. I feel like this game is for Marvel nerds? Marvel nerds? What do
you mean why are you truing that? Marvel nerds? I think it's just a fun game about diving in the
ocean and collecting fish and stuff. Where are you getting that from? Activate? These are mines.
All right I actually I gotta go up. I might be in trouble. Is this the ceiling? Hurry hurry hurry.
It's kind of rude. Like what? It just exploded. That's like I'm fine. I mean dude what are you
doing? What are you doing? I'm fine. I have a escape pod right there. Before you raid Connor
can you just get a DMCA strike? What is stop? All right I think they're about to start. Is the
countdown still there? Let me check. 10 minutes? 5 minutes? Is there enough to do one um one uh
restaurant evening? Six minutes? Oh let's let's yeah let's get you over there. I don't want to
be late. You need to do one stream that deserves a sequel is a kill the meme stream. I talked about
that six months ago. All right guys go say hello to Connor. A couple of grotto beast related items
bundles are available for raffle and for auction. Please go support it. We'll see you again. Let me
just get this set up. Yeah everything supports the immune deficiency foundation so go hang out. I'm
very curious how some of these items do especially the auction ones. Yeah I'll see you guys on Monday
house flipper competition with a bunch of streamers. Should be a good time. I'll be in offline chat
probably on Sunday night giving some more details or just show up on Monday 4 o'clock pacific.
Sounds good. All right see you later. Take care. Have a great night. Ta ta for now. We can do this
for now. Thanks for hanging out. Thanks for watching. Let's go. I'm very curious what happens
to these items. See you Monday. This music is fine for the outro. In the event that everything gets
cut off. Call your mother. Call your father too. This is nice isn't it? Yeah that was nice. See you
later bro. Drink some water. That goes for you too. Yeah sorry I've been a little messed up the last
week but it's okay. I'll be goodbye Monday. And don't trust me I'm fine. It's just some minor
annoyances. I'm good. See you later. Goodbye. Yeah it's stomach related if you're curious. I'm good.
Intestinal. I'm good. See you later.