Hey, what is going on everybody?
Jerma here with a live gameplay commentary.
Playing as the engineer with the new Eureka effect, soldier.
And you're probably saying to yourself,
damn it, to explain what you're talking about here, engineer.
Well, I will. The old Eureka effect was not really that good and it still ain't
really that good right now. The 50% slower repair rate and upgrade rate
takes 17 goddamn times before you get your central to zero to 200
or any of your other buildings, of course. But that's okay because now you can
teleport to spawn or you can teleport to an exit
whenever you happen to feel like it. So we're gonna let Jerma take over here.
He's gonna do a live commentary about the Eureka effect and I'm gonna go
and fill my diaper with shit. Oh, a sandwich.
That was delicious. That was delicious. That was delicious.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Not gonna waste any time here.
I'm gonna try to actually get the tele- I want to
show you the teleporter thing. I'm gonna try to- whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Oh god, I hate when this happens. You get like the uber for two seconds and
you think, oh my, it must be a panic uber and you run out and then it ends on you
and you turn around running backwards and you just get absolutely annihilated.
We really can't get out of here. I'm gonna go for
Indiana Jones. Indiana Jones engineer. You guys ready?
This is what we call Indiana Jones. See, I helped.
I helped with that. Come on, give me the kill.
I'm just gonna put this here for just because to give a
distraction so I can come up here and kill this guy.
No, the soldier already get down. Okay, good job.
That was exactly what I was going to do. What the fuck?
Oh, was he standing right there? Did I just completely miss that guy?
Well, whatever. Now I have some time. I've got some time to build
up my entrances and stuff. Hopefully we don't just steam roll right now
because that would not be good because I do want to try this eureka effect thing.
I want to go teleport to the exit. I want to find myself in a
teleportation device. Okay, we're just gonna forget.
You know what? Let's try. No, that's a bad idea. I was...
Oh my god, I'm gonna stop burping. Let's build this just so I can carry it.
This is the worst part though. This takes so long.
Let's get that exit built right here. So now...
Shoot him! What the hell was that? Did you guys see that?
No, no, no, no, no, no. This ain't gonna happen.
I knew you needed like a two percent shot left.
But once this exit is built, I can do wacky
stuff like this. Let's see if I can do it. Here we go. And let's go back to base.
Let's fill up on our ammo. And then let's immediately go back to
the teleporter exit. Okay, here we are. So that's kind of cool. That's cool.
Is it good enough? I don't know, because look, it really does
take such an absurdly long time to build up your centuries and to
repair and everything. So I don't know, I guess if you like to
fly around and teleport around stuff, it's kind of cool.
But at the same time, at what cost? At what cost? This is a really bad idea
because I don't have the Wrangler, but you know,
he probably does. I wonder if he does. Well, this is a terrible idea.
This is like a, yeah, this is the worst idea I've ever had.
Yeah, hey, hey, get him. Spray him. What? Oh, well that sucks. That really
sucks. What is this guy doing? This guy's like
inside of the door. Oh, I need some ammo to be the refill.
Let's get a dispenser up right here. Are we moving? Kind of. We're kind of
moving. Yeah, sort of. Let's build this up here.
That's probably a better idea. Better idea?
Maybe. I just, I don't have the Wrangler on, which is
not going to help me that much. Yeah, this is bad. It's all right though.
A little bit of distraction. It'll get probably one or two kills. It'll get this
guy too. No, maybe not. Well, if yeah, actually if
this guy peeks out, yeah, he's dead. This guy's dead because here comes a demo.
Fighting him. I'll just, you don't screw it. I'll go down there and get him. Wait
a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. Wait just one minute. Yes. I was going to say,
it's, that guy's not real. Oh, I need, I need my stuff. I gotta go back up
there and grab the sentry. Dispenser's gonna have to die,
unfortunately, because like I don't really care to repair it or bring it
because we're moving too fast. Come here. And we're about to get this
next spawn. So, life of an offensive engineer. You're
just constantly moving. But it's fun though. It's a fun time.
Where's that guy go? That's a spy. Oh, shit. No, don't go up there.
Get, please tell me you're gonna kill that Pyro because I really don't want to
deal with him. Come on, build, build, build, build.
You're, yeah, you're still alive. Still alive. I'm gonna have to do spy callout.
Spy creeping around here. Where is he? Which one? He's probably gonna appear
right next to me. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Well, I'll just have to kill you. Well, no, I won't kill you. Somebody else will.
Get out of here. Damn, dude. You're making my life hard.
Can somebody just get rid of that little mini sentry so I can build this?
Oh, damn. Kill him before he gets the sentry.
Holy shit, what the fuck is going on up there? I'm dead.
I'm gonna burn. Bye. But, please, there's like five people.
There's an entire crew in that room. Oh, my god. This sentry is doing so much
work right now. Why do I not have an exit built? I could
just teleport right to it right now. This thing. They have a teleporter in
here? Is that what this has to be, right? Yeah, they do. All right. Well, let's just
get rid of this stuff. I'm so sorry that you're dead. I'm so
sorry that you died right there. Nothing I could have done.
Nothing that could be done. We actually might win this right now.
I have, like, not shown the Eureka effects, like, cool abilities,
like, really yet. I've shown it, like, one time. We're just playing, like, engineer.
All right, now we're gonna show up, because I'm gonna have an opportunity
here to build an exit right here. Exit's gonna, by the time this is built,
so here's the strategy. Here's the, here's the strat right here. We're gonna try to
get this thing built. I'm gonna teleport back to spawn. So,
here we go. Teleporting back to spawn. Let's go, fill up, and then immediately
come back. Very good. And there you go. We are back.
I can build. Actually, I should destroy that so I can build one down here.
And, you know, we're gonna do it again. We're gonna do it again. We're gonna go
right back to spawn and come right back immediately.
Fill up, come right back. Hello. Yes, that is very cool. Who was it? What?
Oh, it's this guy. Well, don't. What is this guy doing?
What was that guy doing? Let's get this to level three,
and then we're gonna build an entrance so people can actually use this thing.
That would be ideal, right?
Oh, should I move this? I feel like this is not
really doing, yeah, it's not really doing that much right now.
We're moving too fast. Hey, spy. Block him. Block him. He's right here
somewhere. Where? I don't know. He's down here.
Get this. Come on, come on, come on. Hurry up. Get to level three already.
Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it, damn it.
It's okay. Here's the deer. Here's the deer. We are going to go back to spawn. I'm
going to build the entrance right out here. So,
entrants go up, bring you right to the action, and you know, while that's
building, let's just go ahead and teleport to the exit.
Hello. All right. Sentry going up, but this one I want like...
No, no, no, no, no, no. I don't think so. I just don't think so. Not today.
Not today. And what do we say to the god of death?
Not today. It's built. Is this? No, it's not level three. This is going to take
Ugh. What a snooze. What a total snooze. I would have been already done by now.
Well, it's level two now. At least it's level two. We'll just get it to level
three. Why not? I mean, what else am I doing
right now? I'm just sitting here being a fucking
dingus. I don't want to get backstabbed. That would not be cool.
Level three. Oh my god, somebody's calling me.
On the... Get... Move. Leave me alone. I don't want to be called right now. There
we go. Let's move. Let's get some action in here.
That was a good like three full minutes of me hitting things with a wrench.
So we got that. Got that covered. And there's a pyro dead. There's another
pyro that's gonna die. That's two dead pyros. Let's get on it.
Move, move, move, move, move, move, move. Now I'll get off of it because there's
somebody trying to come destroy my stuff. He's dead. There's another guy over here
just on fire. All right. We are going... No, we're not going to destroy that yet.
Oh, I wish this thing was the rescue ranger. Where am I going?
I'm not sure what I'm doing here, guys, but I did it.
Well, let's get on. Let's push it. We don't gotta go far.
Exit. Exit strategy. This thing still shooting? It is.
I may leave this back here just for the denial, the area denial, if anyone wants
to come back here and screw with us. But then again, it might not be a terrible
idea to bring it to the front lines. And let's...
He's a dead ringer. Can I come back in time? Yes, I can.
But we are right here anyways. Yeah, this... I can destroy my
exit. There's no reason to have it right now. Can't really build... Unless I could
do this, I'm gonna try for something really, really...
I wonder if I can do it. If I can do it, it'll be really cool.
Let's get rid of the entrance and let's try to build an exit. Just an exit down
here where nobody cares to look. Oh, but no, I'm being chased.
Shit. I didn't realize like three people were still chasing me.
All right, we gotta end this. I gotta go power class. We needed power.
Engineer was just not doing it at the moment. And what is happening and how is
this guy still killing everybody? Let me get that medic.
Let me get that medic. Let's do it. Me and you, baby.
Me and you. We're gonna take on the whole world.
All right, I'll just turn the corner and just get exploded by a
rocket. This is the one. This is the one. We only have two minutes and 28 seconds.
This has to happen now. I got a telephrag. All right.
I'll take a telephrag. Here we go. Here we go. This is the push.
We got it. Here we go. This is the one. This is the push.
Come on now. Geez, man. They got so much stuff and so many people. This is not the
push. I don't think this is the push at all.
That didn't hit him. You've gotta be kidding me.
That hit somebody. Any more medics? Where'd you go, man? Where'd you go?
Where'd you go? I need some heals. I need some heals.
Man, oh man. Come on now. Here we go. Come on.
Everybody get on it. We got some advantage here. We got an advantage.
We got the slight advantage. Come on, drop down.
Oh, I got fucking backstabbed. No. God damn it. I was gonna detonate that.
We got it. We got it. We got it. Come on. Everybody get on there.
All human beings get on there. Come on. I gotta get out there. I gotta get out there.
It's so close. We have one minute. One minute.
One minute. They're all going over there. It didn't hit anybody.
Come on. I don't think we're gonna do it. No, don't be bad attitude. That was a bad
attitude. Let's go. Get it. I died. Shit.
Oh, unless we get up there right now. 46 seconds.
Come on now. Let's just do this thing. Spoke too soon. That's
a spy. Shit, if I just couldn't aim my weapon.
That guy would have died a long time ago. Go this way. I'm going this way.
No, I'm not. Too many scouts. Don't care. I'm wrapping around.
Wrap all the way around. I got full ammo. Full loaded.
There we go. Scout doesn't know. Neither does the spy.
Now he does. All right. We just gotta get this heavy. Gotta get this heavy up here.
Get on it. Just get on it. Stop bottling. Come on.
Get on it. Come on, everybody. I'm getting off. I'm getting off. You gotta get off
right now because you gotta help out the team. You gotta get the
people that are going in. That's a critscreek.
This is too intense for my brain. Come on, push it.
I don't care about the gloves. No. No.
We were close. That's gonna wrap it up though. Thank you, everybody, so much for
watching. This has been Rage Demo and EurekaSnooze Best Engineer. Thank
you for watching.