Hey guys, how you doing? How are you? How are you? Hey now, get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here.
That's an old one from like last year. Our classic humor from six months ago or so.
Welcome, we're gonna be doing some interesting stuff today. And uh, did you hear me clear my throat?
Hope not. We're gonna be watching some more infomercials. I have a bunch queued up here.
We're not just gonna do food this time. First one seems very, very interesting and I'm very curious
how it plays out. Stream's not gonna be more than probably a few hours today. I think that after
like two or three hours of doing this, it's probably it. I need to take a break from the
overstimulation of infomercials. Plus, I need to make sure I get something ready for tomorrow.
Not for stream, but you know for Jeremy. So I got some stuff going on tomorrow that I have to prepare
for. So it will be live for like a few hours. We'll see. Have I seen Morbius? No, and I'm never
gonna see Morbius. I'll probably have a dream about the movie Morbius and that will count as me
watching it. I think that, is that fair? I think that's fair. What did you, what did you rate it?
I don't know. What does everybody else say? What does it have on Metacritic right now?
The exact score on Metacritic right now. The exact score. Yeah, 35%. I'd probably give it like a
30. I'd probably give it like somewhere in the 30s. Morbius is better than your streams, okay?
But I have a multi-million dollar, like a hundred million dollar Marvel Studios project
that had 5,000 people work on. It's better than me watching infomercials. Are you,
but here's the thing. Are you sure? Are you sure? I don't know. We'll see. Okay, then the YouTube
title has to be Watching Infomercials is Confirmed Better Than the Morbius Movie, right?
That's only if it's confirmed today. All right, I'm pretty much ready. Yes, it is confirmed. All
right, let's get started. We're only here for a few hours, so let me clear my throat one more time
because I'm fucking throat-andy. Hope you had a good sleep, those of you that slept. What does
that mean? Okay, hold on. All right, this one's called Amazing Discoveries Infomercial The Human
Calculator. Human Calculator. Apparently, it's for a product that teaches you how to do math
really fast or something, and I thought, okay, I'm very curious. I need to know. Let's find out.
You guys ready? Did you just wake up? No. Here we go.
Special program, Amazing Discoveries is a paid advertising...
Amazing Discoveries. ...by Media Arts International.
Coming up next on Amazing Discoveries, we'll show you how to turn on the human calculator in you.
All right, so I need to know this. Holy shit. That sweater is fucking insane. I love it.
...who is fondly referred to as the human calculator. You'll see why. Scott Flansburg.
Oh, he's here. 497 times 35. What is that? 17,395.
Whoa! They put him on the spot. Hold on. They put him on the spot for that. We're not gonna
watch all 28 minutes. Don't worry. Is this a game show? No, this is not a game show.
This is... In 30 seconds, they introduced the show, showed the guy, and gave him a gotcha question,
and he got it immediately right. You guys ready? 4,379 divided by 7. What is that? 625.57142.
What? All right. What the fuck are you talking about? What? Let's be honest with ourselves.
Is there a screen? How many people in today's studio audience have been frustrated or intimidated
by math? How many people here? Me? I don't know shit about math. But you know, the important thing
is that if you don't pick up math young as a child, it can actually slow down or stop how far you can
go in life. It can limit how much money you can make. What the fuck? Aren't we tired of hearing
how America's educational system is falling apart? How other countries like Japan are producing
smarter kids? Huh? Well, today's amazing discovery is going to turn all that around because our...
When was this? When did this come out? When did this come out? 1980 something? Like 80, like 384?
That statement. I remember. If you don't know math, you're gonna be fucked for the rest of your life.
If you don't understand how to become a human calculator, you're gonna be eating out of a dumpster
tomorrow. John? Our special guest says that by the end of today's show, everyone in our audience
and you at home are going to be able to do complex mathematical calculations, not on paper and not
with an old-fashioned calculator, but in your head. Okay. How is this possible? Mike, just keep an
open mind because today I'm going to show you and everyone watching... Well, can we do this? How we
have deep down inside us and we just don't know how to turn it on. That would be great. But before
you... If this works, let's do it. ...famous amazing discoveries challenges just for you. Are you ready?
I'm ready, Mike. Okay. Oh, this is to prove it. This is to prove it. ...on Gary Collin's home show.
And by the end of the show, 22,000 people phoned in and admitted that they were poor in math.
And we've invited four of them to join us here on today's amazing discoveries. Wait, what?
And they're from across the nation. Hold on a minute. He was on a show and they said,
hey, if you suck at math, call in. And 22,000 people called in and said, hey, I can't do it.
And they brought, they picked four of those 22,000 people. Okay. So I just, I wonder if
you're understanding how this played out here. Who cares? That's not a, that's not a big deal.
And they're from Florida, from California, and even all the way from Alabama. Welcome everyone.
Yeah, but I mean, this is not fair. This is like, this is a kid.
End of the show, 22,000 people phoned in and admitted that they were poor in math. And we've
invited four of them to join us here on today's amazing discoveries. And they're from across the
nation. They're from Florida, from California, and even all the way from Alabama. Welcome everyone.
Okay. But you don't, how would you know all that math if you're like a kid?
By the end of today's show, he's going to have you all doing complex math calculations.
Okay. I'm here too. I would be number five. Go for it. Oh, no, Mike, I'm not going to do it. I've
got to do this show with you. So what I did was I brought a friend with me that's going to take
him backstage during the show and teach him how to do everything. Okay. Bring out Scott.
What? Kevin, come on out. Kevin's a child. Mike, that's just it. This program is so easy.
Anybody can learn it. It doesn't matter how young or old you are. Are you sure you can do this?
Okay. That's a lot of pressure. It's a lot of pressure, son. I see some more demonstrations
from Scott. Yeah, let's see it. I want to see how this, I'm very curious.
We've enlisted the help of Ray Gayden. Now Ray Gayden is a certified public accountant
from a nationwide accounting. They're like a tax attorney? And he's here to check Scott's
accuracy. He's going to follow along with Scott using his adding machine here and Scott.
This is an expense they didn't have to have. In this image right now, this man is holding a
calculator. This guy and this, this guy doesn't need to be here. He has an adding machine. What
is this? What the fuck is this thing? Is that a fudge brownie? What is he, what are you talking
about? Why does this guy have to be here? For every correct answer, you're going to hear this
sound. But Scott, should you give us a wrong answer? Ray is going to give you one of these.
Okay. Thanks Ray. And to give you some really tough problems, we have an entire Girl Scott
troupe here in our audience. And they're going to give you some really tough problems. Scott,
are you ready? I'm ready, Mike. But afterwards, I want to show everybody how easy it is and that
anybody can learn how to do this. Okay. Let's give Scott a big long row of three digit numbers to
add up. Give him four or three digit numbers and Scott's going to add them in his head. Go ahead.
333 plus 454. That's 701. Six 99. Plus 13. It's 14. And I gotta give you one too. It's 2984.
I don't know. This is stupid. 3469. This is a calculator with paper. That was a calculator
with paper in it. Cassie, let's give him a hard division problem. How about a four digit number
divided by a single digit number? 5973 divided by seven. 853.28. He's using the force. Hold on
a minute. But wait. 800. Right here. This like, the like... I can hear the music.
Yeah, right. That's fucking impossible.
I don't want someone to get like power bombed through that table. This table,
this is the set table that is breakable. Let me just give you some insight here.
This is made out of like plywood, like one, like small thin sheets of plywood and no supports.
This is made for someone to go through this table. But I imagine somebody's going to get
annoyed with this guy and they're going to go at it and he's going to get like fucking chokeslam
through this table. Yeah. It's like an Eric Andre table. Yeah. This is the, this is the,
I'm going to go through this eventually table. Okay, so how do you do it? Patricia, when we
normally add a comma numbers up, don't we start on the right hand side and then go to the left
and carry and all that stuff? It's pretty difficult, but I want to show you a real easy
way to get the answer. Okay. Now, instead of starting over here, let's start on the left hand
side. And this one right here, it doesn't just stand for 100. And what does this two stand for?
200. Okay. So now let's keep a running total in our heads. Okay. What's 100 plus 200 plus another
hundred. It's 400. Right. Plus 200 more. 600. Okay. Now let's go to the top of the next column,
which is the tens, right? So this two tens stands for 20. So add it to 600. And what do you get?
620 plus 20 more. 640 plus 20 more. 660 plus 10 more. 670. Okay. Now let's go to the top of
the ones. What's 670 plus three. This is like a lot to do in your head. Six hundred seventy
nine plus one. Six hundred eighty and four more. Six hundred eighty four. Six eighty four. And
that's the right answer. What? No fucking way. So Mike, bring me the other girl down that gave me
the real hard division problem. I want to show the division problem. Now this one is horse shit.
I'm curious about this horse shit. You're pretty good at multiplication. Yeah. All right. I want
to show you a shortcut for real big numbers. Like let's say we wanted to multiply 95 times 95. Okay.
Now here's how you do it. How far is 95 from 100? Five. Okay. So what you do is you put minus five
underneath and what do you get? What's 95 minus five? Ninety. Ninety. You had it. You had it.
All right. And now take this number here and square. What's five times five? Twenty five.
Right down here. And that's the answer to 95 times 95. Nine thousand. All right. Hold on.
But this is not. Ninety six. That's not the problem he did though. That's not the problem
that she said. Wasn't it? Wasn't it like a huge amount of fucking decimal points? Where? That
means 96 times 96. Now how do you do it? Okay. Ninety six from 100 is four. Keep watching it.
What do you get? Ninety two. Okay. Write that down. Now what do I do? Score the four,
which is 16 and put it after 92. Great. And what's the answer to 96 times 96? 9,216.
That was terrific. So what? But that's not the question. God, these girls. Congratulations,
girls. How do you do that? Mike, I see thousands of kids, parents, and teachers every week.
And I get the same results time and time again. Well, we want to see those results for ourselves.
We want to see those results for ourselves. Okay.
Wait, he's a teacher there?
All right, Nicole, we have your math book and notice how I have to use a calculator for this.
You ready? What's 462 plus 385 plus 517. What is that? 1,364. That's correct. That's really good.
That was easy. What do you mean easy? All right, Kyle, what's 24 times 97?
Um, 2,328. That's right. It takes me longer to put in the calculator.
All right, Carly, your problem is 93 squared. 8,649. I'm not through pushing. You're right.
This guy's great. I want these like shirts. What is the cube root? And I didn't even know
what a cube root was, let alone do the stuff in your head. Did they get this guy in a time machine?
This is, this is, this is this person. Now, let's see if it works on me from fucking 40 years ago.
It's the same person. 5,112. What's that, Zach? 58. The same voice. Very good.
Well, those kids. It's the same person talking. So we visited a woman who's devoted her life to
math to discover why Scott's methods are so successful. Dr. Mary Hatfield, you're an
assistant professor here at Arizona State University and you've been a director of
the National Council of Teachers of Mathematics representing literally thousands of math teachers.
Okay, the camera's going to pan and he's talking to the lady over here. Teaching teachers what to
teach and how to teach. Now, I understand that Scott's methods are really very different than
the traditional way of teaching mathematics, right? Yes, they are. The traditional way is boring.
It's wrong. It's true. Math sucks. I hate it. It's so stupid. Doing something just the way the teacher
tells you to do it. And Scott's way is to take those numbers and say, hey. This is good. If it
works, it works. Try this. Double this. Square that. And all of those things. All right, let's go.
Diana here to our studios in Los Angeles and we're going to give Carla another tough problem. You're
ready? You ready, Carla? Okay, but just to show everyone that you have no calculators there,
show them your hands. This is not a magician. How is this a magician? She's not a magician.
I'm going to give you 73 squared. Now, 73 squared is 73 times. You don't have anything up your sleeves?
Like a fucking deck of cards?
All right, where does this end up? Wait, we got, hold on. We have an expert. I hated math. I hated
it through high school. I hated it in college and I was so thankful. So I fucking sued it. I sued it.
Lost 40 million dollars. And I use math every single day. Okay, how does this end?
By doing even the most difficult math problems in your head, often faster than a calculator.
1858. This has been a series of people saying large numbers. What would happen when the teacher
came over and slapped down a sheet of problems that Bobby finished these problems? Well,
if it was this hard, I would lay it down and I would go to sleep. You'd go to sleep? You must
have really hated math. Yes, I hated it, Mike. And Scott, I understand, showed you a new way to think
about math, right? Yeah. What happened? He taught us that it was easier for us to do it in our head
than it was to do it on paper or the way they taught us. Really? Oh wait, but hold on a minute.
If you need to show your work, how do you do it? You can't do that, right? You'd have to like put
it on. Now you can do calculations in your head, which is a three. We're finally across. When is,
when is, I want something to go through that table. That was the side of you. Five Pacific
drill and kill type activities with sharp math skills. Ready? Yeah. Oh, what? What happened?
What happened? 125 sharp math skills. This power, you can do anything you want.
All right. Human calculator. That was a pretty good one. That was a pretty good one.
Let's keep going. I got a lot, by the way. This one is also not food related. This one is the
Martinetti's bring home a computer. The following is a paid advertisement by Apple Computer Inc.
This is a dramatization. All characters are, why would you say that? As far as I can tell,
families have two kinds of people. The ones who want everything to stay the same and the ones who
want to spice things up. I guess you can count me in the second group. Why are you standing like
that? She's my sister. I feel like I stand like that in pictures. He's always up for something
crazy. And mom, she's a classic. Gramps loves opera, so you can count him in. I did all this
off my computer. And Schubert, he's just cool. Schubert? I guess in our family, it was only Pop
who was really set in his ways. Wait. Of course. Who? We all thought that he was really, I guess
in Schubert, he's just cool. Oh, is it? I guess in our family, it was only Pop. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait. Oh, it's the dog. I was like, is this guy's name Schubert? That's interesting.
Why are you calling dad by his first name? That would be weird, right? Of course, my dad,
but I call him by his first name. And Schubert, he's just cool. I guess in our family, it was only Pop
who was really set in his ways. Okay, dad doesn't like computers. We all thought that that would
change once we got our new computer. I'm TJ, and this is a story about when my family,
the Martinettis, brought home a computer. Okay, so who, grandpa is- Getting a computer in our
family was a real adventure. We're all so different. I never thought we could agree on one.
Mom, you see, she runs a home business. That is when she's not running the home. Did she say,
get off, like get off the computer? Is that what she says? She runs a home business.
That is when she's not running the home. Oh, she's kiddo. Frank, he's the brains around here,
studying to be an engineer or something like that.
Zoey and Gramps, they're the Martinetti, Fielder, Monica, and Jug band. Allegro, honey, more
Allegro. Oh, that's a kindly old man. As for Pop, he's got his own ideas about things.
Where's the sports? But he's a great guy. Hey, Pop, check this.
That's pretty clever, TJ. Yeah, Pop's understanding, supportive. But no points.
Delete that, delete that. You don't, you fucking put that on Facebook either,
making our family look fucking stupid, making me look like an idiot. Don't put that on Facebook.
How many likes does it have? 40? All right, if it gets to 50, it won't be upset.
And sometimes as stubborn as a mule. No points. What do you mean no points?
It's a work of art here. A work of art. Yeah, that's what everybody thought. Oh, I like it.
No points. Except Pop. No, why is he saying no points? And I gotta tell you how we weren't
gonna keep the computer until we earned enough points to convince Pop we should.
The world got along fine for thousands of years without computers.
The world got along terrible. And that's because there was no Tetris.
You hear that? Exactly. See what I mean? I better go back to the beginning though.
Okay, but. Because it's a wild story. And you really gotta know our fans.
Oh, this game's awesome. This game's amazing. I guess it all started the night I came home
late from school. Sorry I'm late, you guys. I was finishing up my report at the computer lab
school. Oh, well, since when's our typewriter not good enough for reports? Our typewriter.
He can do all kinds of stuff on the computer he can't do here. Like?
I use the electronic encyclopedia, the internet. I put pictures and words together. The thing is,
Pop had a computer. He's not even paying attention to his son. All he ever did was put numbers into
it. I don't blame him for not wanting one of those. He's daydreaming?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. He's the electronic encyclopedia,
the internet. I put pictures and words together. The thing is, Pop had a computer at work.
He's just not even listening. And about all he ever did was put numbers into it.
I don't blame him for not wanting one of those. But he didn't know there was a whole other world
out there. Hard disk drive. It's really cool. I hear you can even get music on the computer.
Opera? Sure, Gramps. And pictures, too.
What, you can do that on a computer?
Nothing has changed, by the way. Nothing. Zero. This was like 20 or 30 years ago. The exact same
conversation happens. That like, wait, what do you mean a computer? What's a computer? I mean,
30 years have gone by. Is this always going to be like this? Like, when I get to be like 80,
am I going to look at grandkids and stuff and be like, wait a minute, what is a computer?
You could do that on a computer? What's a computer do? Like, is the old people always just don't know,
don't understand? I feel like is that what's going to happen? Like, even though I've been
using computers, like my adult life, right? Am I just not going to know?
Use a computer, Lou. Maybe even you and me. I don't know, Mary. What if we get one and we
don't use it? We could just look. I want one. Me, too. No promises.
So that's how the great computer quest began. Grandpa's demanding. Of course, Pop said that
before we did anything, we had to talk to an expert. Who do we know that knows a lot about
this kind of stuff? Fletcher. Oh, is it going to be like a hacker? The next day we went to see
Fletcher. Fletcher was what Pop would call a piece of work. He was Frank's friend. A real genius.
Look at this store. Oh, the whole Martinetti family. Wow. Look at these monitors thinking
about buying a computer. Tell Pop it's a good idea. Oh, it's a good idea. Now I could sell
you something expensive, Mr. M, but I won't. Thanks, Fletcher. Now what do you got? Expensive.
Well, let's see. It's EB games. In a computer the whole family could use, right? Right. Yeah.
Something with multimedia. Yeah. Well, we have a lot of PC clones in stock. PC clones. PC.
Windows. CD-ROM drive. What the fuck? No, get that out of here. Sound card. Need that.
Memory management and adapter. Oh, what the fuck? Memorize some commands. You need some
instructional books for that. Yeah, you need all this shit. Fletcher was... You need all this. You
need a lot of graphics cards and you need a sound card. You need a monitor and everything. And look
at how much that is. And let's come over to the Apple computer, which is twice as expensive as
what I just showed you. It's making a point. Oh, and also you have to configure this one to run
multimedia. Mr. M, now all of this is yours for a mere... Uh-oh. Pop was not impressed.
Whew. But then... Not in the 90s. You could buy a Macintosh Performa.
Yeah. Fletcher showed us the Performa. It was like the Macintoshes we had at school,
except it came with a whole bunch of extras. It had CD-ROMs that Zoe and I could use for learning.
There are programs Mom could use for home business. Whoa, look at all these financial charts.
To get information online. Plus, there were games!
This was a lot easier than a PC with Windows. Is Grandpa the Gamer?
Mine. Plus... Grandpa's the Gamer.
There were games! This was a lot easier than a PC with Windows. And Fletcher showed us why.
On the Windows PC, he had to know pathways and commands to manage files.
No, you didn't. How long? Wait. You just clicked on a file and there you were.
This is the DOS kind of hating? On the Windows PC, running a CD-ROM was a real hassle.
I guess this was with... Yeah, DOS. The Performa. You just put in the disk and BAM!
It made everything you want to do simple. Show me your book, Birds of Prey. We all thought for sure
Pop was going to buy the Performa. I'll pay him the price.
All right, everybody thinks... This is going to buy the Performa.
All right, some of you guys might think that like, oh, that's kind of a random thing.
I have sat there on YouTube and just kind of had my chin down like this with like my iPad here.
And I probably have typed in to just like, what was Harry Truman's life like?
Show me an eagle in a nest. I feel like I do that all the time.
I just look up random shit. We all thought for sure Pop was
going to buy the Performa. I'll pay him the price.
It was a done deal. I'll think about it, all right?
Think about it? No way. How much was it?
What's to think about? We saw that one work. We saw this one work. This is better.
Now, here's where the fun began. Because Gramps and Pop, they always see things different.
Oh, no, they're arguing in the store. Pop went one way, Gramps the other.
I'll buy it. All right?
I'll also pay for the printer. And the printer?
If the family proves that they really need it, then you got to pay me back.
So that's how it started. A little friendly wager.
What do you say? Gramps was going to buy it and bet
Pop that we could change his mind about computers.
And that's when Pop thought of points. Okay, kids, everybody, we get 100 points
in one month and I'll pay for the computer. How do we get points?
I'll figure it out. You.
All I knew was that we were fined for bringing a computer home.
And the next month was going to be very interesting.
And they go to the back and into the computers.
If you're thinking about a home computer, it's important to make the right choice.
That means a computer that's ready for tomorrow with exciting technologies like multimedia.
The Macintosh Performa is way ahead of other computers
because its multimedia really works easily.
Want video? Yes.
It's as simple as plugging in a VCR or camcorder.
Wow, that's actually a pretty big deal.
And edit your own video production.
That's a pretty big deal.
Right on your computer. And with an Apple Color printer,
you can even put your video pictures into family newsletters or greeting cards.
All right, here, I know you guys have to understand, though,
we are so spoiled by how the world is right now with information technology, right?
But the act of printing a picture, like a color picture, was like insanity.
It'd never been able to happen before.
So, I mean, it might seem stupid now to be like, and by the way, the color printer.
It's like, what? Oh my goodness.
How? Like an inkjet?
No way.
That was like going from black and white to color.
It's a performer.
You see, many computers with windows have to be reconfigured or restarted
over and over again to run many CD-ROMs.
But with a Macintosh, a simple click is all it takes.
This performer also includes a fantastic new technology
that fills your screen with full size, full motion TV quality images.
Images that set a whole new standard for visual quality.
If you want true multimedia, get the computer that does it best and makes it easy.
A power PC driven Macintosh performer.
Quality.
Apple has a full line of performer computers.
And to find the one that's right for you, just call this number now.
Apple will send you a free information kit that includes all you need to know.
Okay, I just thought, okay, I thought something just popped up on my screen.
I was like, why?
The perfect choice.
You'll discover the performer 5215.
2300, eight, look at these specs.
Eight megabytes of RAM.
One gigabyte hard drive.
That's actually kind of, that's a lot.
75 megahertz power PC 603 times four CD-ROM drive.
Speakerphone and answering machine comes with it too.
A popular all-in-one computer that's great for families.
For modular design, a gigabyte hard drive.
That's a lot back then.
As your needs grow, it will too.
There are other performer models to choose as well.
And each comes with over 1300 dollars worth.
1995, grow your multimedia encyclopedia.
Encyclopedia CDs are huge back there.
Software at no extra charge.
This is a tremendous offer.
You can't afford to miss, but the time to act is right now.
Call this number now for your free product.
All right, so how did the, how did the family turn out?
Did we get to see the end of that or is that a cliffhanger?
Is there a part three?
I have part two here.
Where's part three?
Oh, there we go.
We got, there's a part three.
There's a part, there's so many parts.
There's so many parts.
Great work.
All right, let's.
Who did you hire to put this together?
I did it in house.
It's six parts.
All right, we're just going to skip to the, to the family.
Here we go.
They got it.
They got it was a pretty big deal in our family and we couldn't wait to set it up.
There it is read all the instructions, but we kids knew it was simple keyboard mouse.
Yep printer.
It's only three plugs.
That's it.
Take a rocket scientist, but pop took no chances.
According to this, the procedure about the cable management.
You want the honors now came the moment of truth.
The cable management's fucking dog shit here.
Even the dog likes it.
What do I do now?
Imagine being presented.
Being presented with this for the first time.
Okay.
Back in like the like 1800s, if you were to film like a train coming towards the camera,
the people in the audience would run out of the theater thinking the train was going to hit them.
This is a very, very, this is a very collected response to this kind of, you know, technology.
This is the first time you've seen this.
All right.
What do I do now?
Like that's very collected.
I would be freaking out.
Click here, mom.
Right from the start, everybody could.
Clarice works.
Ah.
Best of all, the computer came with all kinds of programs ready to use.
There are programs for writing and drawing.
Programs for men with a 3D atlas.
Wait, is that like diagnosing?
Wait, hold on.
It had a full encyclopedia with pictures and sound.
The family doctor.
And it came with.
Huh?
Wait, the family doctor third edition.
Is this like WebMD?
So you could go and type.
That was so cool.
You could believe you're anywhere on the planet.
This is so interesting.
It really didn't take long to get the hang of things.
And mom proved it.
She put together the first ever Martinetti family newsletter.
She took pictures we had from extra made those part of it, too.
And when she printed it out, I could almost sense a new career in the making.
Media.
Somebody didn't say the Martinetti cinematic universe.
All right.
Now, remember our deal.
Earn 100 points and I pay for the computer.
Dad, the thing's fucking phenomenal.
It's a remarkable new ridiculous piece of technology.
You lost.
I mean, come on, just pay grandpa.
Really?
Otherwise, how do we get points?
Well, here's what I've worked out.
You do your homework on the computer.
You get a point.
You raise your grade.
You get two points.
No, no, no, no.
Come on.
That's worth at least 10.
Yeah.
Grandpa, come on.
All right.
I have to hand it to pop.
Five points.
He never makes a decision lightly.
I use it for business.
If you told him this computer could take him to the moon,
he'd want to go three times.
Well, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You know, the reason why grandpa's not into this is because
this kid's got like fucking D's and he is now has to rely on this kid
to make it so he doesn't have to pay like $2,500 for a computer.
So it's like, oh, God, now, let's not tie it to grades.
How about let's tie it to times that they do the dishes.
Is that better?
That sounds better.
That's a good idea.
If you told him this computer could take him to the moon,
he'd want to go three times to make sure.
It's just an important purchase, Mary.
I want to make sure everybody uses it.
What did I tell you?
The funny thing was the computer fit into our family just like it belonged.
2,590 bucks.
That's all in different ways.
What is that now?
Mom found she could do her whole greeting card.
10 grand.
She could design new cards and make changes just like that.
Like five, five K, six K.
And to send a copy to her publisher,
she just faxed it right from the performer.
We played this game.
We actually played that exact game.
That's dinosaur adventure.
The whole other universe to explore.
She loved learning with multimedia and couldn't get enough.
Arthur's teacher trouble.
Stories that came to life.
That week, everyone in Arthur's class studied harder than ever.
And that taught her things about the world.
Bro, what the fuck happened?
We went from this to like Elsa beats Spider-Man up with a baseball bat.
What the fuck happened?
What the hell happened?
There were thousands of CD-ROMs out there.
I believed it.
And Zoe would have had them all if she could.
For me, I like that our computer's a Mac.
Algorithm.
Because that's what our school has.
And the Macs at school have tons of stuff I use.
Only now, instead of staying late, I could bring my work home.
Boppy disk.
I could use our computer.
All right, those are so cool.
I like the sound those made.
I can make reports with pictures and sound that were just fantastic.
When you punch that in the machine, it did this like
It was awesome.
I think it was Gramps, though, who did the most amazing things.
He figured out all kinds of stuff to do with the computer.
Great sub sound, Grandpa.
He discovered E-World, the online service from Apple.
E-World?
Gramps had never seen an online service.
But before you knew it, he was meeting people from all over.
Well, Grandpa's meeting people?
I think it did him a lot of good.
More good than he ever dreamed.
You know, Frank, there's other people out there just like me.
No.
Really?
People like the same things.
There's other towns.
There's other cities.
So who's Rose?
There's other...
Whatever you mind.
Wait, what?
As the weeks went by, we kept earning points.
Grandpa's on Reddit.
Okay, now, including homework, mom's work, grandpa's stuff.
There's 72 points here.
They're so close.
Not bad.
Of course, Zoe thought she deserved points for beating Pop in games.
No points for games.
And Gramps agreed.
Hey, why not?
You learn things from games.
Exactly.
Frank and I thought so.
But Pop didn't exactly see it our way.
Somebody's not learning enough.
TJ, we'll get points if you bring your math grade up.
I know, I'm working on it.
You got a D.
The proof's in the pudding.
That's my grandpa was sold.
Didn't want to do that.
The proof...
I hate it.
...is eating the pudding.
Okay, everybody.
Family picture.
Perfect.
Oh, this is where the...
The thing was, we were having the time of our lives...
Full circle, here we are.
And there was no turning back.
We just had to convince Pop to keep it.
We were desperate.
And desperate people try anything, even math programs.
Was he eating out of the dog bowl?
People try anything, even math programs.
What is that?
Two of rows.
I've heard several of her performances and think she's simply the best.
Tomorrow, I'll send you a list of some of her best performances.
Regards.
Carmine.
What's this?
Never mind.
I'll be up here in a minute so you can do your math.
Grandpa, what are all those tabs?
This machine can make so much difference.
No, those are nothing.
Those are absolutely nothing.
Nothing.
Just for a family.
And you know what?
I still didn't know the half of it.
Like, who's Rose?
Who's Rose?
One of the best gifts you can give to any child is a love of learning.
And there's no better way to do that than with a Macintosh computer
and a world of learning programs.
Hi, folks.
I'm evil uncle Greg Martinelli.
I'm going to come in and fuck the whole thing up later in the show.
Skip.
Stop skipping.
We've seen this already.
This is our house.
This is my room.
This is our kitchen.
This is my hallmark.
This is due tomorrow.
This is where I plug in my guitar.
This is where you plug in the printer.
This is the lawnmower I'm fixing.
I thought he was plugging the lawnmower into the computer.
Like, dude, that's not, you got that, you got wrong info, man.
Fixing.
Ties.
Checks.
Paints.
Faxes.
This is my encyclopedia.
Our taxes.
Astronauts.
Dinosaurs.
Socks.
It's always dinosaurs.
This is our Mac.
It's easy.
You guys notice that all old multimedia, all old software apparently has to be dinosaur related.
It has to be related to a dinosaur.
In the days that followed, we all worked on the new computer.
Mom did business.
Zoe learned all about animals and music.
This my equation.
And nobody played with the dog.
He made friends all over cyberspace.
Frank went back to college with email from the Mac in his dorm.
Using the computer just became second nature in our house.
Pop send money.
What?
So this is really helping?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, you can do your business better now?
Absolutely.
Come here, I'll show you what I'm working on.
Do you like this one?
Very nice.
Good.
I'm faxing a draft to the publisher.
How?
The computer had programs that could help mom do everything.
She could keep track of work schedules, addresses-
It's a cyber scam?
All right here.
Zoe, now there's another story.
What she did on the computer was awesome.
She had a video that we shot at the zoo.
And she took scenes from it to make her own picture book.
That's cool.
We went to the zoo, TJ and me.
You wouldn't believe all the animals we see.
Do you like it, Pop?
Dad's going to get addicted to the league.
I think it's going to be a best seller.
Oh, here comes Tamino.
He's a hero.
He's the guy that gets the magic flute.
Now, Gramps, he loves to talk opera.
With the CD-ROMs he had, he could talk it with us.
And we could learn.
Tamino being chased by a serpent.
What happens after that?
Gramps took to the computer like an old hand.
Is this a choose-your-own-adventure book?
I had a feeling there's something different about him now.
Like he had a secret he wasn't ready to share.
Every time you see the serpent, you hear that same music.
As for me, I worked on my favorite subject.
Well, math wasn't so bad.
If you could go at your own pace.
Yeah, what was the anti-feminism thing?
What?
Was that what that said?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's happening?
And with the computer, I could.
I think you've got it.
It was about this time that Pop got it too.
I mean, liking the computer.
I remember one night.
I was awake late.
Oh, he's going to catch Dad.
It was Pop.
I couldn't believe it.
He was calling up eWorld to get quotes on stocks.
And he found news articles he wanted too.
That's what he told me.
Why would Dad lie to me?
Budgets and investments.
Yeah, investments.
He even uses DOS files from the office right on the Mac.
And MS-DOS.
It's DOS.
I know you're there, TJ.
Have you ever used this thing before?
The last few nights.
It was milk and cookies.
It's Dad's Santa?
Wait, I don't.
And then came the day of reckoning.
Email from Frank.
He's coming home this weekend.
I got a new order today.
A Happy Mother's Day card.
Yay!
That's a point for us.
Yes.
Oh, it's another point.
I believe this.
Guess what?
I got a B+.
TJ, a B+.
He did it.
That's terrific.
We're just a couple of more points to go.
You didn't add mine, Dad.
Why, you got points?
What for?
Oh, I use the computer to balance the budget, analyze our finances.
I made some big decisions on it.
Put me down for five.
What?
Even Dad is there doing it.
Now Dad added points and the computer now is, he has to pay for it.
We did it.
We're keeping the computers.
I love this frame though.
We're never going to let the computer go.
But are we realizing right now that Grandpa's the only one that can hear the music?
We're keeping the computers.
Can they all hear it?
We're never going to let the computer go.
I just wanted to make sure everybody would use it.
Can they all hear it?
You know, I guess I better write that check, huh?
Who is it?
It's Grandma.
Oh, no, it's, oh, it's Rose.
You must be Rose.
And you must be Carmine.
Am I late?
Oh, no, no, you're right on time, right on time.
Hey, everybody.
This is Rose.
Where'd you two meet?
Right over here on the Opera Lovers Forum.
Oh, the Opera Lovers Forum.
So that's what Gramps had been doing all this time.
So this is your performer.
Yep, that's it.
Oh, it's a real, it's a real piece of shit, Carmine.
I knew you were a power user.
You know what?
I read all the magazines.
I do, too.
Oh, but can it run Crysis?
Mine can.
There's more.
I'd like to propose a toast.
To our honored guest, Rose.
You are always welcome in our home.
Salute.
Salute, Dad.
That's our story.
One month in the life of the Martinettis.
I wouldn't say that everything that happened was on account of our computer.
But I wouldn't say it wasn't, either.
I mean, we didn't only get a computer, it got us.
Power user.
Sometimes I think it even knows what it got itself into.
Well, after all, it is a Macintosh.
Here comes the guy, here he is.
What do you think about that?
How'd that make you feel?
You ought to write down your thoughts on that last commercial.
What would you write?
Alright, that was fun.
Any more?
This is a tremendous offering.
Family room?
The marketing department.
This is the conference room.
These are not the Martinettis.
We almost missed the fucking dog post-credits scene.
Is he pissing on the computer?
Okay.
That's it.
That was a blog?
Okay, that was the Martinettis take home a computer.
I've got some more food ones, but should I do some more food ones?
Yeah, absolutely.
How about the grill disc?
That's what I'm, yeah, grill disc.
Not anymore.
Joe Fowler and this is the non-stick grill disc that turns virtually any pan into an indoor grill.
What?
Eat and eat.
You'll hear the sear and see the grill marks locking in that delicious outdoor flavor.
So, okay, let me just be, let me ask a question.
Very, everybody here.
This doesn't do anything, right?
This is just a way to make an aesthetically pleasing image on your food.
This doesn't do anything different.
You're still cooking.
It's not anything different, right?
No, am I wrong?
Does it actually do anything different?
And the taste?
Isn't it just like, so good.
But if you just cook it.
The grill disc is made from high heat steel.
That creates a cooking surface of a real grill inside your pan.
And unlike flame flare-ups that can ruin your food, grill disc distributes the heat evenly
to the entire disc.
Does it do anything?
So the food is always perfectly cooked.
Grill disc makes the world's best hamburgers.
Cook juicy pork chops to grill perfection.
It kind of just slide around.
They'll come running for.
And now when it rains or snows, you've got the grill that will never close.
And I want you to see this.
Because the disc is raised, it creates a flavor channel for your favorite marinade.
Just add the lid and seal the flavors right in.
That's cool.
The grill disc is super nonstick so you can grill up that delicate fish without the worry.
We've all seen foods that fall through the grill.
But with grill disc, they never will.
Make delicious shrimp on a barbie.
Tasty sausage and peppers.
Or grill veggies and fruit to perfection.
Wow.
And here's a family favorite.
What's up with that hot pan?
Too close.
That's a hot pan, man.
Don't just bring it over to the table.
Grill disc makes the best grilled cheese sandwiches.
Grill a pound cake for a delicious dessert.
Plus, clean up some breeze.
You can call or go online now.
All right.
I mean, all right.
The grill disc.
All right.
Whatever.
Fine.
The grill disc is dot whatever.
That's fine.
What about the flavor stone?
Pound cake?
Yeah.
What?
That's weird.
A pound cake on the grill?
I was just not even paying attention.
I honestly just I blanked on that one.
Yeah.
That was a grilling a pound cake.
That's kind of fucking weird.
All right.
Okay.
We're going to do.
I got a lot of tabs up here.
How about a culinary rocket chef?
The program you are watching is a paid advertisement for Rocket Chef.
Presented by culinary.
Don't touch that remote during the next few minutes.
We'll tell you about a 40 million dollar giveaway promotion.
You can get a fabulous rocket chef for a friend.
What the fuck?
During the next few minutes.
No way.
There's no fucking way.
Oh, stay tuned.
We've got buy one, get one free.
Oh, stay tuned on a fantastic deal for the Rocket Chef.
Stay tuned for the 40 million dollar giveaway.
Don't go anywhere.
You can be rich soon.
Oh, what?
We'll tell you about a 40 million dollar giveaway promotion.
You can get a fabulous rocket chef for a friend absolutely free.
And for yourself, you'll get the amazing fat free gourmet.
We can't go anywhere.
A $100 value also free.
We're not going anywhere.
I need to know about the 40 million dollar giveaway.
With fewer calories, less cholesterol, but lots of flavor.
Watch how you can get it free as we introduce Rocket Chef.
A modern marvel.
This company, I don't think even had 40 million dollars in like liquid capital.
What are they?
I need to know what they're talking about.
I have to fucking know.
We need to know.
Replaces all these bulky machines.
Wouldn't be great if one appliance could cut better than a knife.
Slice faster than a slicer.
Chop better than a food processor.
Blend better than a blender.
Yeah.
Do it all in a fraction of the time.
Of course.
Rocket Chef can and it goes from the freezer to the microwave to the table.
Plus it does your food preparation so easily.
Yes, that one appliance is here.
Stay tuned to learn how during this one-of-a-kind 40 million dollar giveaway promotion.
You can get an extra one of these amazing appliances absolutely free.
And 40 million dollars.
Stay tuned to find out how you can get not one but two Rocket Chefs and 40 million dollars for free.
Holy shit.
Plus a calorie-saving, fat-free gourmet.
I'm shocked.
As an additional 20 billion dollars, you'll also get the fantastic Magic Can.
Absolutely free.
It's the only can opener which opens from the side of the can so it stays smooth and safe.
And it's yours free.
Ladies and gentlemen, Nancy Nelson.
Hi, welcome to our kitchen.
I am Nancy Nelson.
And today together we're going to discover a whole new way to make life easier, simpler,
and a lot more fun in the kitchen.
This is why it's called the Rocket Chef.
I'm sure it's a good product.
I have to admit I'm not the expert on Rocket Chef.
The guy who is is someone who's very familiar to you.
The famous man with the red bow tie.
A friend of yours, certainly of mine, John Marcus.
Billionaire, John Marcus.
You're looking at this gorgeous food.
This is not just gorgeous food.
This was made by the Rocket Chef.
It's fresh, nutritious, healthy meals, rocket fuel, rocket fast for your family, Nancy.
Why did it just get quiet?
Oh, sorry.
We had to cut off the part where they're giving away the 40 million dollars.
I can't even hear it.
Is it?
All right.
I think there's got to be another version of this, right?
24 minutes?
25 minutes?
Is this the same one?
This is the same one.
I think this is, yeah.
No, I think this is the same one.
22 minutes?
Shit!
It's all fucked up.
There's no, it doesn't exist.
I can't turn it up.
It's as loud as it goes.
Sorry.
Two blades.
Get that away from her face.
She's going to take a whole step this way.
So it's a food processor.
When you needed it.
Nancy, you want to try some?
That took you a few seconds to do.
A few seconds.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, you guys.
Is this like a salsa?
This is so good.
You know what, Nancy?
Nancy?
Let's say you didn't want to make salsa.
Okay.
Why this?
That was four salsas.
All you do is you chop up your ingredients,
add some molasses and some chili powder.
Why don't you do that, Nancy?
I'm going to do something different.
Wait.
Into the salsa?
Put the chili powder in here.
All right.
Turn the handle.
You ready?
You put it into the salsa.
I don't have to take the top off.
I can pour this.
What?
See, that saves time too.
All right.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
And you know what, Nancy?
The few years, you know, you know what went in.
So you know what comes out.
I mean, you go buy these things from the store, you know,
who knows, you know, what's inside these things.
But Nancy, take a look at mine.
And look at that.
Don't read the ingredient label.
It's lies.
Barbecue sauce.
I'm lost.
Wait a minute.
Everybody hold on.
You are.
You're putting them in.
I want to do something like salsa.
Put some herbs in.
We'll take some onions.
He's made a salsa.
And then he just put molasses in it.
And it's a barbecue sauce.
That's what happened.
Nancy, take a look at mine.
Because you know what I made?
Fresh, delicious gazpacho.
Done in seconds.
But you know what, Nancy?
I got to tell you.
What's the one job we all hate?
With those things back there, clean up is complicated.
The clean up, you rinse and run.
That's it?
What about baked on cheese?
And you know why we need it?
Because now we're in John's Deli.
Here we've got three ladies from the studio audience
who are going to put the rocket chef against the rocket clock.
Now then, on the count of three ladies.
Making a sandwich, a Deli sandwich?
And they're going to prepare, you know, family favorites.
There's not like Deli chicken, Deli cheese, and mayonnaise in there, right?
Joyce, you have three teenagers at home.
You made gorgeous.
Oh, this is great because they can prepare themselves.
They can clean it up themselves, which of course gives me more time.
Good plan, mom.
What did you make?
I'm just looking, Excel.
Do you have a little three-year-old who likes to help mommy?
Yes, loves to chop things.
The blade's on the inside.
It's safe. It's easy.
She can even spin it and help clean up.
What a good idea.
All right, they move over to this lady and she's just like, she didn't do anything.
It's just all the ingredients are still in there and she's just like,
I didn't understand the instruction.
So they just like move on.
Okay, yeah, sure, whatever.
You're single, so often.
What is that?
Right, I always make too much.
But this, I can use just the right portion.
Oh, but you know what?
If you make a small batch or a large batch, it makes no difference.
There's no waste because with the seal and save lid.
What was in there?
Oh, thank you.
Get the door, raise the problem and just pop it in and your leftovers are taken care of.
Don't forget rocket meals, rocket fast with the rocket chef.
Now, what about the all-American favorite meatloaf?
You simply pop all the ingredients into one bowl.
Yeah, it's making meatloaf.
Okay, so it can make sludge, right?
Like if you're, if it's a sludge based food, then it'll be fine.
It doesn't, it doesn't.
Is it mayo based?
Is it a sauce?
All right.
Don't open those.
That could cost you hundreds and hundreds of dollars, Nancy.
Potentially even 40 million dollars, John.
You'd love to have one, wouldn't you?
Using the microwave in its dishwasher safe, you also get all the blades and attachments,
which mean you can virtually replace a whole kitchen full of appliances.
Now you get the rocket dough with the patented gravity speed feeder.
The rocket dough?
So you can work in the power of eight blades.
Nancy, you know, we also give you the seal and store lid so you can put it on the top.
Refrigerator and the microwave and all that time, but you know what?
Nancy, we're also going to give you some great low fat healthy recipes with the recipe guide.
Nancy, you know, you could spend hundreds and hundreds of dollars to try and buy
appliances that can do what this guy's doing.
This guy's doing TikTok shit.
Imagine this guy, but framed with just like this and it's a TikTok video.
Nancy, we're also going to give you some great low fat healthy
recipes with the recipe guide.
Nancy, you know, you could spend hundreds and hundreds of dollars to try and buy
appliances that can do what the rocket chef does.
He's like doing the animated thing.
That's TikTok right there.
Especially right here.
Right here.
This guy was killing it.
Wow.
Okay.
No, fuck that.
You put edit, edit her in there, hold up a phone like this, holding the phone up,
facing him.
And I'm telling you right now, this is a TikToker.
She's going like this right there.
To replace a whole kitchen full of appliances.
Now you get the rocket dome with the patented gravity speed feeder.
And of course, the two gear ratio so you can work in the power of eight blades.
Nancy, you know, we also give you the seal and store lid so you can put it on the top.
Refrigerator and the microwave and all that time, but you know what?
We're also going to give you some great, low fat, healthy recipes with the recipe guide.
Nancy, you know, you could spend hundreds and hundreds of dollars to try and buy
appliances that can do what the rocket chef does.
But I got to tell you, we're not going to charge you.
Payments of $19.95.
Oh, that's great value.
Don't you think that's wonderful?
Isn't it wonderful?
Now it's time to take the peak.
Lift the lids.
We get to see what's in here.
You want to see you guys?
All right.
What do you think, Nancy?
Oh, is it just now?
Remember what I said?
You could replace virtually a kitchen full of appliances and no kitchen would be complete.
I only did that for like the 10 of you that thought that was funny.
And I know and we you and I get it.
We get it.
You know what I mean?
Like this, like this, this tens of thousands of people.
And they're all like, this guy's fucking bad joke was terrible.
But for like the 50 of you, you know what I mean?
Like you and I, you would get it.
You know, we get it.
We get it.
A screen maker.
I mean, that one over there cost almost twice the price of the rocket chef system.
And it isn't going to do everything that this can do.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you going to tell us that the rocket chef is going to make ice cream and sherbet?
Your kids are going to love this.
Your family, the 10 of us don't use tick tock, which is going to show you how to make sorbets
and sherbets and healthy ice cream.
We're also going to give you a rocket chef blade, which will allow you to make all of these.
Is this a special blade for special blade?
We've also got a fabulous rocket chef scoop.
I hated that.
Did you hate that because you don't like the song or did you hate that because you didn't
like the routine that just happened?
You know, I thought about it.
I was sitting there going like, should I do the like, should I do like the oh no thing?
Like I could.
I couldn't.
I'm going to lose 5,000 people.
But I had to do it.
I had to.
There's nothing that was going to stop me.
Nothing was going to stop me.
Ever quit hold the bowl.
Has this ever happened to you?
You've been at home.
You're in a hurry.
Lots of hassles.
You're trying to make salad.
Jesus, man.
Stop.
Watch out for the knife.
Be careful to us all.
Well, look at this because this is the rocket chef chopping board.
It's not nice, but watch Nancy.
When you take hold of the handle, it folds.
So from now on, every single time you're going to hit the spot.
All right, that's cool.
All right.
Nancy, this on its own is a $20 value.
All right, that was cool.
On this occasion, we're going to include it at no extra cost.
That's the complete rocket chef system for two easy payments of $19.95.
That's great, isn't it?
That's $40.
What?
That's, you know, $40.
Professional chefs.
Okay.
Cool.
Yep, yep, yep.
I live in a very small apartment.
So number one is spending a lot of money with this product.
By changing the attachment.
Where's the $40 million?
I did exactly what I needed it to do.
I live in a very small apartment.
So number one is space saving.
Clean up the stench.
What if they just don't go anywhere with that?
What if that was just made up?
Since the beginning of time,
I've been searching for ways to make life easier in the kitchen.
Onion?
From the Stone Age to the Machine Age,
our kitchens have become cluttered with expensive kitchen machines that just take up space.
What is going on?
Why are they all so fucked up?
Why are they so like disheveled?
From the Stone Age to the Machine Age,
our kitchens have become cluttered with expensive kitchen machines that just take up space.
What is going on here?
Are they clearing out their cabinets?
Why is everything so dusty?
And why are they all so beat up looking?
It's a meth lab.
Take up space and collect.
It's an illegal meth drug den.
Dust.
Well, now the art of cooking blasts off into the space age with Rocket Chef.
That's so stupid.
Rocket Chef is like having a kitchen full of appliances combined into one.
And it's so easy to use.
Just insert the kitchen machine.
Imagine using the Rocket Chef.
And you're ready.
Watch as we make tasty homemade salsa rocket fast.
Want a slice?
Just snap in the thick or thin cassette blade and it becomes a supersonic speed slicer.
In a caveman?
And in Rocket Chef's speed feeder, this cucumber is sliced to precise perfection every time.
All right, 40 million dollars.
I'm sorry.
Where is that?
Not even the most expensive food processor does that.
And you can cut up whore tears because it's greater.
Okay.
Or insert the space age whipping blade and it's as powerful as a professional mixer.
No, it's not.
Rocket Chef is even stronger.
No, it is not.
No, it's not.
Spinning a blade like this is not as powerful.
No, it is not.
Lie.
Come on, man.
Things cool and it probably works, but more than a professional whipping machine.
Watch as we put blood in the Rocket Chef.
And we separate the plasma and the white blood cells from the red blood cells as a centrifuge.
Chicken or egg salad in just seconds.
Making lunch just became a lot easier.
That's an application I would use this for.
I just would.
That's a pain in the ass.
Making tuna.
It's kind of messy.
It smells right.
Like that's a pain in the ass.
That's the one reason why I'd use this.
Rocket Chef system includes the microwave safe base.
The two speed rocket dome with speed feeder.
The patented cassette system with thick and thin slicing blade.
What did he say?
Wait, what did you say?
Peter?
Rocket Chef system includes the microwave safe base.
The two speed rocket dome with speed feeder.
The patented cassette system with thick and thin slicing blade.
I'm sorry, that's all I heard.
That's the only thing I heard.
The handy snap seal and save lid.
And the Rocket Chef fast and easy recipe guide.
Rocket Chef replaces well over $500 of bulky and complicated kitchen machines.
Where's the $40 million?
Call now and the complete Rocket Chef system is yours for just two low payments of $19.95.
And it's backed by culinary lifetime, that's right, lifetime warranty.
And when you call right now, ask the operator how you can get the Rocket Chef ice cream maker free.
To make healthy homemade ice creams, sherbets, and frozen desserts in minutes.
An extra $15 value, but it doesn't stop there.
Call right now and you'll also receive Culinary's ingenious cutting board
that folds to make kitchen mess.
Where's the $40 million?
Isn't that clever?
And the Culinary 2-in-1 Chef's Choice Miracle Knife.
That's the best mixer and peeler you've ever tried.
All right, these bonuses add up to an extra $35 value.
But when you call right now, they are yours at no extra charge.
Try Rocket Chef in your own home for the next 30 days.
We're almost halfway through this.
And there's no more mention of the free $40 million giveaway.
But you can keep the cutting board and discover what space age cooking is all about.
Here's how to get your own Rocket Chef right now.
To order Rocket Chef or just two low payments of $19.95,
have your credit card ready and call this toll-free number.
Or check your money order for $39.90 plus $7.95 shipping and handling to the address on your screen.
Remember, Rocket Chef comes with a lifetime warranty
and replaces hundreds of dollars of bulky kitchen appliances.
Where's the $40 million?
It was the other video?
The program.
Oh, this is so exciting now.
What are you doing?
Stop. Listen, we'll get to that in a second, okay?
Let's not forget what time you're going to hit.
And Kind has been searching for ways to make life easier in seconds
and heat them up in the microwave.
Right, lifetime warranty.
Right.
And when you call right now, ask the opera clever for $35 stage cooking.
Yeah.
For trying Rocket Chef.
Low payments of $19.95, $9.90 plus $7.95.
Cover what space age cooking is all about.
Right into the space age and boy has it ever.
Well, thank you, Nancy.
But don't forget, it'll not just save you.
God damn it.
Stop. Oh my fucking God.
I am so sorry.
I did not mean to do that.
It's just the whole thing is the audio is so fucked up.
Absolutely free.
And for yourself, you'll get the amazing fat-free gourmet.
A $30 value also free.
This cooking breakthrough lets you cook food
in its own rich flavors in a row.
Don't touch that remote during the next few minutes.
We'll tell you about a $40 million giveaway promotion.
What?
Would be complete without mashed potato.
Extra cold.
Don't forget, best of all, healthy home.
Okay. All right.
Oh, Nancy, look at this.
Oh, doesn't that smell delicious?
Does that look delicious?
Nancy, look at that.
Oh, gorgeous.
Oh, wow.
Sauce.
They always do this.
And this is my problem.
Ready?
Here's my problem with infomercials.
And this is a big problem.
So they make it.
Oh, look, it's so easy.
Nancy, I've got the sauce.
I've got the cheese.
I've even got the chicken salad.
It's all here in front.
You have, you need five of these.
You have to grate the cheese, clean the fucking machine,
make the sauce in there, clean the machine.
They have six of them.
There's usually like six to 10 of these lined up.
Of course, it's going to take you 30 seconds to make a pasta dinner.
You've got 10 things on the counter.
They should do one where they clean it and then they do it again.
Oh, well, over here we got, this thing's dirty.
Yeah, because you have five of them.
You know what?
We actually wondered how the rocket chef would do in a head-to-head competition
between people who are trying it for the very first time and some professional chefs.
So why don't we join Discovery Channel's own Maria Kalea?
She is standing by.
Okay, this has to go on screen right now.
It's very important.
It's fucking terrifying.
I hate it.
I hate this, but it has to go on screen right now.
I'm so fucking sorry.
That was so loud.
The audio is all screwed up because of the, you know what I mean?
I'm so sorry.
I'm just fucking killing you today.
Killing me too.
Uh, okay.
Wow.
Jesus.
All right, so here comes the pro chefs.
Okay.
Does this, anybody else kind of feel like this makes like the craft and like the amount of time
and like care and passion that this guy probably like puts into his food and like,
oh, look, look, some fucking lady can do it in a machine.
It takes her 10 seconds.
You're, yeah.
Then that kind of, I feel like that kind of diminishes what this guy does every day,
doesn't it?
Oh, look, this lady came over and she, she does.
She's not like a professional chef.
He's making coleslaw.
What?
Hold on a minute.
They're making these chefs do stuff that only can be made in the rocket chef.
Oh, professional chef, like doing a crazy, like he's spinning a knife around.
Uh, you're going to be, you're going to be chopping up like cabbage and making coleslaw.
Oh, you, you're like a, you're like an executive chef at this, uh, at this restaurant behind us.
Um, just make like guacamole real quick.
You make coleslaw.
And it's a lot of chopping.
Yeah.
Well, this isn't that long, John and Nancy.
You two on the count of three, start chopping.
We'll see how it goes.
Beat, go.
Don't forget everything in the same bowl at the same time.
You'll save time.
Rocket meals, rocket fast.
That's right.
You can throw everything in at once.
Look at this, Cathy.
Did you throw everything in?
The guacamole, check this outside.
And who's, who's is better?
Oh, you're not even close.
No, you know what?
No, no, you, you, you get the, get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, get out of here, loser.
Coleslaw.
No, please.
Okay.
I'm going to be, let's be really, I gotta be real.
If I took cabbage in my hands and I just fucking crushed it like this
and squished it with my fucking hands and a bowl was underneath and I put mayo in it,
just like, and then I stirred it up.
I don't think anybody would be able to tell the difference.
That's like this, not much goes into that really at all.
I don't know why they're making it seem like this, this master chef.
Oh, it's just one of those days.
You know, it's just, look at how much better the rocket ship does it.
I could do it with my bare hands.
It's like carrots.
I could literally just break up like carrots in my hands and cabbage.
I mean, it'd be a little chunky, but three out of three ain't too bad.
But it's not what it's about.
Now, I mean, with your kids, for example, you want them to be winners too, don't you?
And what a better way to start, you know, let me give them fresh cooked vegetables.
I mean, you can do them so quick.
Wait, oh, I thought they were talking about,
I thought they were talking about giving it to like, oh, your kids, not like a baby.
Okay, okay, okay.
It has a few specific uses, but it's a food processor, right?
It's a food processor that's easy to clean, whatever.
I think this is the last opportunity we're going to get to the 40 million.
There's only one opportunity left, right?
It can't be this easy, but it was.
I had mascara on.
Not a tear came out when I did this onion.
It really was brilliant.
I was thinking this is going to be hard and hard to clean,
and it was just so easy cleaning this opposite.
Whatever it is you're trying to make, just put all the ingredients in a few turns
and it's done.
Ever since the beginning of time, mankind has been.
I don't think it's going to be there.
Life easier in the kitchen from the stone age to the machine age.
Our kitchens have become cluttered with expensive.
Again, take up space and collect dust.
Well, now the art of cooking blasts off into the space age with rocket chef
snap seal and save lid and the mess is a thing of the past
to order rocket chef for just two low payments of 1995.
Have your credit card ready and call this toll free number.
Discover what space age cooking is.
Back.
We're in the culinary kitchen.
This is so much fun with the rocket chef.
John, I don't want to lose any time.
You promised ice cream.
Let's have it.
Nancy, you can make ice cream with the rocket chef rocket fast.
Ice cream, can you really?
Eggs and cream.
You simply blend them together into a custard.
And then, of course, you add the flavor of your choice.
You know, vanilla, for example.
Sure.
What about a few chocolate chips?
Oh, what about any flavor we want?
Any you want.
Doesn't that look good?
OK.
And then all you've got to do, Nancy, is take it to the freezer.
All right.
Yes.
Just give it a turn a few times before it freezes.
And look at this, Nancy.
Ice cream.
You want to try some?
Oh, let's see.
OK, Nancy.
Try it.
Tell me what you think.
Oh, oh, you guys said it's so much better than good.
There's nothing like homemade ice cream.
You know what?
Nancy, Nancy, don't limit yourself to vanilla ice cream.
What about all the family favorites?
I mean, the kids are going to love strawberry ice cream.
Chocolate ice cream.
Yeah, that probably works.
Remember, you promised us $40 million.
I didn't do anything.
I watched the same commercial you did.
I mean, Nancy, just look at the place.
But what?
Remember, you're going to get perfect professional sizes
time and time again.
And Nancy, you tell me, what's the worst job in the kitchen?
Onions.
Why is that, Nancy?
Because they bring tears.
Not anymore.
You've got onions without tears because the owners are locked inside.
How about blended drinks?
I mean, fruit smoothies, chocolate milkshakes, power drinks, diet drinks.
And you know what, Nancy?
You can do turkey salad, chicken salad, tuna salad, crab salad, shrimp salad.
Did we just watch this whole infomercial and get $19.93 click-baited?
Onion ice cream?
No, that was an onion ice cream.
But wait, was it even part of the same commercial?
The program you are watching is a paid advertisement
for Rocket Chef presented by Culinaire.
Don't touch that remote.
During the next few minutes, we'll tell you about a $40 million giveaway promotion.
You can get the fabulous Rocket Chef for a friend absolutely free.
And for yourself, you'll get the amazing fat-free gourmet, a $30 value also free.
This cooking breakthrough lets you cook food in its own rich flavors and aromas
with fewer calories.
Laser chop better.
Yes, that's what appliance is here.
State saving fat free.
It's the only cattle.
Her kitchen.
I am Nancy.
What happened?
That's okay.
All right, we got another amazing discoveries.
Alpha netics with the red devil grill.
This looks really crunchy.
I'm going to put this one on.
What a spread.
Terrible day to be kitchen.
Didn't even go in the kitchen.
How did you make all this incredible looking food?
It's so much food.
Everybody here today.
I want to show you something Mimi and I have found that is so revolutionary.
It is literally change the way we think about cooking.
Every single dish.
That's like 50 pounds of food.
So you get perfectly cooked food every time.
And just because it's portable doesn't mean that it's small.
Rob, I think you've got 15 burgers.
There's so much food that's never ever going to leave.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
freeze, freeze, freeze, freeze, freeze, freeze, freeze.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12.
There are there are like 13 people here.
There's like 40 people's worth of food already here.
They start putting burgers on a grill.
There's like 15 patties here already.
And this motherfucker over here.
Somebody you guys need to communicate with each other.
You guys need to communicate.
You don't cook food over here.
Like I got this already going, man.
There's like three or four people making three or four different parties amounts of food.
And on my big $400 grill, it's never ever going to leave the backyard.
And we've got 15 burgers and five dogs on the Red Devil and I can take it anywhere.
What?
250 square inches of cooking surface means that there's enough room to cook food for
all your friends and family.
But remember, the Red Devil isn't a grill.
It's a portable outdoor kitchen.
Looks like a grill to me.
They're your friends.
I know.
If all the Red Devil was was a barbecue that I could take with me fishing or tailgating.
Getting called out.
But believe me, the best is yet to come.
This is the Red Devil Super Skillet.
This is what really makes a Red Devil a complete outdoor kitchen.
It's a but it's a it's a grilling rack and the radiant heat plate.
Got the super skillet over the high output burner.
And now I can get a man size skillet kitchen stove outdoors without any pots or pans.
Let me show you what I mean.
No, stop making food.
Mimi, the next time we go tailgating with you folks,
I'll have in some of my famous three bean.
Right now, like Jack over there is like the meat starts to brown.
It's just like cooking it in your kitchen.
Look how easy that is.
All you do now is you add your beans.
OK, then we add our other beans.
Right.
Did I turn this off?
I turn the grill off with the sauce and just take a look at this.
Now we just mix it all together.
And in about five minutes, it will all be done.
Just take a look at this.
Wouldn't it be a nice addition to your family's tailgating on a cold Wednesday
instead of boring burgers and boring dogs?
Boring.
I love burgers and dogs on the grill.
Would you prefer salmon?
Oh, not on this.
OK, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, guys.
You bring this to a tailgating party, the record is going to scratch.
And people are going to be like, you're going to go tailgating
and make salmon and potatoes in a white wine sauce?
That's not going to.
I don't think people are going to care.
Oh, these people are here.
These people don't fucking want to be in a commercial.
It's just like they just started to do an advertisement now.
Look at the reactions.
They're kind of just like, what the fuck are you guys doing?
Look at what's going on over there.
This guy's reading a book.
And the red devil turns into a cordless deep fryer.
What do you do with the oil?
The very best picnic food.
Crispy, hot, cooked up, fresh.
What do you do with the oil?
Look at that.
Beautiful.
Just pour it out?
Pour it into the ground?
It makes the perfect portable wok.
I'm going to fry up my shrimp in my wok at the tailgating party.
If you want to use chicken, if you want to use beef, then that's fine.
You can use whatever suits you.
Because the only thing that limits you with the red devil is your imagination.
Just take a look at that.
Now, I served it to my family and friends.
And every time I serve it, it goes down the tree.
Just take a look at that.
It goes down the tree.
Wait, it goes down the tree?
It really is the perfect wok.
But there's a much more important reason for this curved design.
That's right.
You see, what happens is...
Somebody said he's just describing what cooking is.
He's still over there.
I don't know.
You tell him, Amy.
Oh, my God.
This guy, this poor guy, this poor guy.
Somebody tell him.
Somebody tell him to stop doing that.
It's really very simple.
Once you place the super skill over the high-output burner,
this parabolic shape directs the flame up and out over the curved surface,
creating three distinct heating zones.
The center is for medium heat.
Three heating zones?
The way around that is the hot zone.
And around the edges is for warming.
It's just like having a multi-burner stove
that folds up and fits right in the trunk of your car.
Exactly.
You can cook complete multi-course meals for the entire family.
Dude, look at all this.
With no more time and trouble than it takes to cook those same old burgers and dogs.
In fact, let me show you.
Here's a meal you'd never dream of cooking on an outdoor grill.
Breakfast.
Now, our bacon and sausage need to be cooked on our high heat.
...takes to cook those same old burgers and dogs.
Look at his reaction.
Here's a meal you'd never dream of cooking on an outdoor grill.
He can't believe it.
Breakfast.
Now, our bacon and sausage need to be cooked on our high heat.
But we're gonna put them on the middle ring, remember?
That's the hot zone.
Now, when you find your cooking meat on the super skill...
Still, he goes back to cooking?
Still?
...it doesn't take longer to cook.
And you know what?
With the Red Devil, you can please everyone.
This guy is freaking me out.
Which might be something that someone might want instead of what's an egg.
I think he's freezing.
Is he moving?
I'm just gonna put that in the hot zone.
Guys, he's not moving.
...eggs.
I'm gonna take my eggs and I'm gonna put them in the center.
Remember, that's the medium zone and just take a look at that.
And you know the best bit?
Thanks to the three distinct heating homes, all the food finishes together.
For instance, your bacon doesn't go cold while you're waiting for your eggs to cook.
Look at that.
Exactly.
And you know what?
I have some sweet rolls here that we need to warm up.
Well, let's pop them around the outside then because remember...
I love that so much.
...the warming zone.
Whoa, what are you doing with all these sweet rolls?
Now, look at that.
We are cooking an entire breakfast all at once, all in one pan.
That's right.
Complete meals for the whole family.
Less time and less trouble than it takes for burgers and dogs.
No, I wouldn't...
Right, so the kids can have frankfurters and beans.
Exactly.
What?
Perhaps gonna love this one.
Oh my god, that's right.
Philly cheesesteaks.
Authentic Philly cheesesteaks.
You can do...
Who made this?
Look at this.
The vegetables are sizzling...
They didn't cook this.
...on the medium heat.
That looks beautiful.
The meat's warming in the hot zone and the buns, right?
This got recalled.
Look at that.
Isn't that beautiful?
Delicious.
But I gotta tell you, Mimi...
What the fuck?
...here's my favorite...
What's that?
...for heaters.
Oh.
Now, first I grill my chicken and my beef...
Right.
...round the hot zone.
Just add my peppers, add my onions, and then just mix it all together.
And in less time and trouble than it takes grilling a piece of chicken,
I can be enjoying beautiful fajitas.
Fajitas.
Look at that.
On the deck of my friend's boat.
Now we've had the fire tortillas.
What?
Put them around the warming zone of chicken.
I can be enjoying beautiful fajitas.
Look at that.
On the deck of my friend's boat.
On the deck of your friend's boat?
Don't you guys love how...
You've started to see through the bullshit a little bit here.
Tailgating.
Bring it to a tailgating party.
Hot dogs.
Ah, yeah.
Hot dogs and hamburgers.
Tailgating.
Cooked salmon in a white wine sauce on the deck of my friend's boat.
Yeah.
Okay.
So.
Interesting.
Oh, it's all about the tailgating though.
Now we've had the fire tortillas.
Put them around the warming zone.
And now, once again, we've got complete meals for the whole family.
Just look at that.
That's great.
But watch this.
Here's where it gets really handy.
Simply connect the stay cool handles.
Dude, they're just walking away from all this shit.
Carry the super skillet to the table.
Set it on the Red Devil's serving cradle.
And dig in.
Look at that.
From cookware to heated serving ware in seconds.
And one left hand to clean.
And that's the way heaters are served.
All these things.
On a sizzling hot plate.
They're gonna come back one time.
And one of these is gonna be on fire.
And he's gonna be like putting it out with a fucking bed sheet or something.
Like this guy is still here.
The food stays warm.
And it's a fun way to eat.
But we're still not done.
While you're eating, plot to grow back over the burner.
And put the kettle on for some after dinner coffee.
Now you can cook directly over the high output burner.
Ta-da!
It's a camping stove.
So you can boil rice or pasta.
Cook soups or stews.
Steam corn.
Even cook a lobster.
No one is going to do this.
At the campsite, the beach, almost anywhere.
And if you think you might want to keep the leftovers warm.
Simply pick up the super skillet for the stay cool.
No.
It's burgers.
Bro.
Hot dogs.
Hamburgers.
Maybe like a piece of like chicken wings.
Chicken thigh.
Like grilled fish is fine, right?
But like they're just trying to make up all these reasons to use it.
No one's going to do that.
It's like burgers and dogs and fish and foil.
And like just be...
No, but do like be realistic about it.
And maybe I would think about it.
No pound cake.
Yeah.
I want this guy to be in the pool eventually.
Just swimming around.
It's on the ground.
He's rushing it on the ground.
Yeah, my friend's boat.
Yeah, we're at my friend's house.
Just wiping fucking charred bits on his ground.
And back to the fun.
Guys, I think my burgers are done.
I bet you haven't.
Like a burger, Rob.
Man, I can't believe it.
The Red Devil cooked those burgers as fast as my big backyard grill.
That's right, Rob.
But remember, in the same time you cook burgers and dogs on your grill,
we made on the Red Devil, Texas chili, sauteed fish and wine and dill.
Fish and chips, fried chicken, shrimp stir fry.
Also complete meals, beans and franks, Philly cheese steaks, even a complete breakfast.
Even chicken fajitas and lobster.
And we're only halfway done.
That's the instant where more than 250 square inches of cooking surface means that
there's enough room to cook food for all your friends and family.
But remember, the Red Devil isn't a grill.
It's a portable outdoor kitchen.
Each and every time.
And just because it's portable doesn't mean that it's small.
Hey, Rob, I say you've got 15 burgers and five dogs cooking on my big $400 grill.
It's never ever going to leave the backyard.
And we've got.
Well, so he know he knew why was he acting like he didn't even know they were in his backyard,
right?
Like it's like, oh, hey, hey, Rob, we're cooking over here.
You're not going to be able to beat us.
And the guy turns around.
It's like he's a fucking ghost.
Can't believe it.
You're done.
And watch this.
Guys, I think my burgers are done.
I bet you have it like a burger.
Man, I can't believe it.
The Red Devil cooked those burgers as fast as my big backyard grill.
That's right, Rob.
And we made lobster.
Oh, my God.
This is so ridiculous.
Wine and dill.
Fish and chips, fried chicken, shrimp stir fry.
Also complete meals.
Beans and Franks, Philly cheese steaks, even a complete breakfast.
Even chicken fajitas and lobster.
And we're only halfway done.
Yeah, you had five grills.
And when we come back, we'll show you how the Superdome package.
Oh, we got it.
We got to continue this one.
A smoker, a old turkey, a poacher, even an outdoor oven that lets you bake
breads, cakes, and what I've got cooking right now.
Mixed favorite food and something I'm sure you've never seen cooked outdoors before.
No.
You'll see.
So keep enjoying your food and we'll be right back.
Okay, where's part two?
I want it right now.
Did I do part two?
I think I queued it up already.
Yep, this part.
Thank God.
Part two.
Get your hands off that.
That's dessert.
I want to show them the rest of this first.
Okay, but that better be good.
Don't worry.
Dessert.
Okay, say you're watching your favorite football team and it's their most important game of the season.
So you're out in the stadium parking lot tailgating.
And guess what?
Back to the tailgating.
Right, so burgers and dogs just aren't going to cut it.
I mean, in this country, Thanksgiving means one thing.
Turkey with all the trimmings.
Wait, it got recalled?
It was people being burned and set on fire?
What?
Holy shit.
The intake tube can warm up to as high as 750 degrees.
What the fuck?
It would get so hot that sometimes it would collapse.
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
And for that, you're going to need an oven.
Are you serious?
For that, you're going to need the Red Devil Superdome.
It's specially designed to work in conjunction with the super skillet
to turn your Red Devil into a portable oven.
So now you can have family feasts anywhere, including the big game on Thanksgiving.
Exactly.
Simply put your turkey, chicken, or even a prime rib.
No, no turkey.
No turkeys, man.
No, don't put a turkey in here.
Holy shit.
On the specially designed roasting rack.
Don't put a turkey in here.
Put your vegetables around the outside and the special shape of the Superdome circulates the heat so efficiently
that in less time than it takes to roast in your kitchen oven.
You can have a delicious Thanksgiving dinner absolutely anywhere.
So how does this end?
Bill, we've got something you're going to love under this one.
Now, you don't believe in barbecue sauce, right?
Right.
You believe that true barbecue should be smoked, right?
Look at this.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Why is this guy the authority on barbecue?
Absolutely anywhere.
Hold on.
Did you see that?
Bill, we've got something you're going to love under this one.
Now, you don't believe in barbecue sauce, right?
Right.
What do you mean?
I don't believe in barbecue sauce?
And you can tell that Phil is fucking annoying, by the way, at these parties.
Like, every time he sort of brings up barbecue, you know that he's going to spend like 20 minutes
talking about it.
So they've got to convince Phil.
You believe that true barbecue should be smoked, right?
Look at this.
And that's like, they call him out like that.
Like, he's this barbecue authority at the party.
Just add moist wood chips underneath the grilling rack.
Oh my goodness gracious.
And you can cook meats like delicious smoked turkey, even real old-fashioned barbecue ribs.
You think they can convince Phil?
That's the way ribs should be cooked.
Smoking gives the meat that delicious barbecue flavor all the way through.
Mimi, try this.
You ready?
Oh beef brisket.
Now, let's just check the meats here and see if it's done.
Wait, what is this thing?
Press the button.
Yes, it is.
Oh, you ready?
Just try this.
That's delicious.
But Rick, what is that?
That's the optional perfect chef grilling fork with a built-in meat thermometer.
It's a meat thermometer?
It takes the guesswork out of cooking whether you're indoors and out.
Simply press the button and the light will tell you exactly how your meat is cooked every time.
That's a great idea.
It's the perfect companion to your portable smoke and a roaster machine.
All right, we're almost done with this one, but I'm, this is so, this is bizarre.
Why don't you head off back down to the beach for some delicious clam bake?
Ooh, look at that.
Clam bake?
What are you talking about?
What about Phil?
Steaming fresh vegetables or add a little bit of fish stock or a little bit of wine.
I want to know.
I got to see the end of Phil's art.
The very best thing is the special design of the Superdome system.
The heat radiates so evenly that I can literally cook anything I can cook in my oven
outdoors, any loaf and cornbread.
All-American meatloaf and cornbread.
Look at that and that's bacon outdoors.
Ready for dessert?
What?
I baked a cake.
You baked a cake outdoors?
Not just any cake, your favorite.
Pineapple upside down cake.
But you don't have to do this.
But you don't have to do that.
Just make a grill, man.
Like make a grill and like, look, make a good grill.
That's like outdoors and whatever, like a good grill.
Doesn't have to bake a cake.
So you really can cook anything anywhere with the Red Devil portable engine.
I mean, give me some of that, will you?
You can cook anything anywhere with the revolutionary Red Devil.
The portable outdoor kitchen from Quantum Homewares.
Compact and portable.
The Red Devil goes anywhere you go.
Okay.
All right.
It's even a portable.
Okay.
With no more time in trouble than good burgers and dogs.
Let's see what they thought.
Let's see what they think.
Hey, Jack.
Hey, Pete.
Hi.
What have you got cooking there?
Pasta Primavera.
Wait a second.
Yeah, we're big campers.
We only get to eat.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on, guys.
What the fuck is happening in this video?
What is happening in this video?
They're cooking pasta on the grill?
Wow.
That looks great.
Yeah, we're big campers.
You know, usually we only get to eat mac and cheese.
It's not only it.
How long did it take you?
What we do is we use the grill, the grill on top to boil water for the pasta.
And after that, we saute the vegetables.
We put the pasta in, mix it all together.
And then we grill the garlic bread right on top of the skillet.
Why?
Looks fantastic.
Explain why you did that and not in a pot.
Why did you do this?
Why?
Explain to me why.
No, explain why.
Why do it here?
Like, seriously, that's what I would do.
We can have two or three things, a whole meal at once.
Thanks, Jack.
Thanks, Pete.
Hi, Angela.
Hi, Shane.
Hi.
How you doing?
Look at this.
This looks great.
What have you got there?
Both got chicken nuggets and we have grilled cheese sandwiches.
Our grilled cheese sandwiches.
That's my favorite.
Now, tell me, Angela, what...
Now, tell me why you have a toaster oven that's inside of your RV right now.
It's perfectly fine.
Why did you do this on the grill?
Explain to me why.
Your favorite thing about the Red Devil when you're out.
Well, when we go picnicking with the kids, it can be a little finicky.
So with this, we can put a wide variety of foods and cook them at the same time.
And everybody can help with their legs.
Oh, that's great.
So what's your favorite thing about this, Shane?
Well, I even cook some pizza, too.
I love pizza.
Hi, Ida.
Don't tell people to make pizza on a grill like that, right?
Like hamburgers, hot dogs.
Hi, how you doing?
Got to tell you, that looks great.
What the fuck is that?
We put the chicken in first and let it go for about a half an hour.
And then you have the vegetables, whatever you want in it.
You can put onions.
You can put just about anything in the world.
It's just great.
Doesn't that make a change from burgers and dogs?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
In fact, we used to use the microwave all the time in the RV.
Do you go RVing, Ida?
Yes, we do.
I want you to think about this for taking.
Grilled pizza is good.
That was a bad take.
Very nicely.
Plus, usually we use microwave food a lot.
And this is much take dearer.
Thanks, Ida.
Thanks, Gary.
I think they proved it.
You really can cook anything.
But what about Phil?
Anywhere with the Red Devil Portable Outdoor Kitchen.
What do you guys got on here?
Somebody said human meat.
Oh, they've got...
You got...
What are the weird shit do you guys have underneath there?
You got cooking pasta on the grill.
You're cooking...
What do you got?
Chicken nuggets?
What's it dear?
Well, let's say it's a human leg.
And all we cook are human legs and human arms sometimes.
Are we an Ida?
Yes, we do.
I want you to think about this for taking.
No, it's compacted noodles.
Oh, that's not as weird as the pasta.
But still fucked up, by the way.
Still incredibly fucked up.
Fit into the RV very nicely.
Plus, usually we use microwave food a lot.
And take dear.
Where's Phil?
Thanks, Gary.
I think they proved it.
You really can cook anything.
Anywhere with the Red Devil Portable Outdoor Kitchen.
But best of all, you can try it risk free.
That's right.
Take it to your next picnic.
Take it to a tailgate party.
Try it out in your own backyard before you decide to keep it.
And if you can't cook all of your favorite foods, absolutely anywhere.
Quantum Homewords will refund your purchase price.
This is crazy.
No questions asked.
Even better if you call right on the next nice day.
Devil Portable Outdoor.
Okay, cool.
Hey, save some for me.
What?
Hungry, I'm gonna eat.
Hey.
Kitchen.
No, I'm getting hungry, I'm gonna eat.
Hey, save some for me.
Now you can cook any.
Be concerned.
I went to a backyard barbecue and there was a full
like 30 pound turkey on the table.
And it was like, I cooked this on the grill.
I'd go, I'm not eating that.
I am not gonna cut into that one.
That's something I'm gonna avoid.
I'm not gonna eat this, right?
It's gonna be like, oh, that's cool.
I guess what you just told me is sort of interesting.
Like you cooked something like that on the grill like this.
I'm not gonna eat it.
That's crazy.
Wild, wild world of infomercial products.
Now that we saw that grill, how about the micro grill?
How about the Bissell Big Green?
I don't even, I don't know what this one is, but we're gonna watch it.
We're gonna turn that way fucking down.
Tracking.
Oh my God, the crusty tracking.
Like I was trying to adjust the volume and was hitting tracking.
Yup.
Are you sucking shit out of the sink?
Yeah, we're gonna, we're, I'm interested completely in this one.
What are you sucking out of the sink?
Okay.
That's a great name already.
Cool.
I love her.
I love her already.
I don't have problems.
Big ones and little ones like this.
How do you get the last drop of ketchup out of a bottle?
Well, the way I do it is usually the old.
If she sucks it out of a vacuum cleaner, I'm going to fucking shit my pants.
Grab the bottom of the bottle like this and then swing it.
See, it's right off the top of the shelf.
Do me a favor.
Make sure the cap is on tightly when you're swinging it.
Wait, that was just a helpful hint.
Stains galore.
Messes are what we came to talk about today, right?
You better, and messes can be cleaned up with this.
Wait, that was her opener was like, hey, here's a hint.
Whip your ketchup around.
How?
Yeah, new technology.
A fucking vacuum cleaner.
Show you how fast.
What are we going to put this right in here?
All right, absolutely.
I'm just going right down.
You see, and then it goes, you see, we added a funny burp for the kids.
The greatest deep cleaning extraction machine that you could use to clean your carpet,
your upholstery, your floors, your car, your boat, your RVs,
things that are big and things that are very expensive.
All right, now those are pretty big claims you're making here.
So let's make you prove them.
All right, we've collected the dirty dozen of stain makers.
Come on over to my favorite.
And this is really a collection of the things
that make the worst stains in your home.
What is it?
What makes them?
OK, that fucking click sound is going to kill me.
Ah, coffee, coffee stains.
Chocolate milk.
Oh, yeah.
We understand what you mean by that.
We don't have to add anything.
OK, all right.
It's like a jar of dog piss.
Yeah, OK, we start up.
I mean, that's it.
That was not that much wine.
That was barely anyone usually on my carpet.
That's right.
That's your choice.
You've got a low pile, a Berber and a high pile.
And what are we going to do?
He takes it back.
She's like, we don't have any dog urine we can use.
And he's like, hold on just a second.
He goes off stage and he's like, this is a dude for a second
and goes back in.
OK, I would say the Berber because it's the most expensive
and it's the lightest color.
This will be the hardest for you to get out, I think.
OK, so let's spill it like we do at home.
Pour it on.
OK, here it goes.
Oh, what the?
Oh, no.
Oh, ruined.
I step in it.
So let's grind it in here for you.
Make it tough for you.
What do you do next?
Well, then I grab anything absorbent.
Somebody's skirt, a shirt, a paper towel.
And I get down on my hands and knees.
And you say a little prayer that will come out.
Please come out.
All right.
And then I like smoosh it all around.
And then I clean it up.
And then take some soap and put it on there.
You're doing absolutely the wrong thing.
First of all, you're just moving that stain
and you're making it bigger and bigger.
It's going down into the padding of the carpet.
And guess what?
The soap just attracts more dirt.
Soap attracts dirt?
It does, unless you get it all up.
So you've got to blot and blot and blot.
And that's almost impossible.
Hasn't it happened to you?
You've gone to bed at night and the stain's gone.
You wake up in the morning and it's back.
It's back again.
That's true.
Oh, it actually does happen.
But here's the solution.
Oh, it is actually.
It's stupid.
I hate it.
And it is the big green clean machine.
OK, now, Mary Ellen, how does this work?
It works easily.
You can set the whole thing up in less than one minute
and it eliminates a big mess because it's got two tanks.
One for the clean water and then one for the dirty water.
So it's got dual tube technology.
We can put an outer tank here for the clean, dirty inside
so it separates the dirt from the clean.
You wouldn't want to clean with dirty water, I guess.
Absolutely.
And the cleaning solution is marvelous.
You just put it in the clean water.
So that's a special proprietary cleaning solution.
The vacuum switch and then the pump switch.
The pump will spray on.
I just want one of them just turn it on and be like,
gee, gee, and everybody laughs.
OK, Joe, turn on that machine and let's go get that stain.
That's very dangerous, too.
Don't do that.
Listen to this audience.
Listen to this fucking audience.
It's like they're like they're like kind of heckling a little.
They can't believe this shit.
Getting a stain out of a carpet that's not that hard.
You just have to be persistent and have right cleaning tools.
It is the big green clean machine.
Listen to this.
I'm just imagining like a fucking large soda
gets thrown down here and hits the back wall.
Like no fucking way the tank and you dump it in the toilet.
And that's the thing.
OK, how about ketchup?
We're going to clean the sofa.
You know, people are scared to death to clean their upholstered furniture,
fearing that it's going to become waterlogged.
Yeah, it's full of stuff.
You don't want to get a wet.
No more.
Just pick up the big green clean machine.
OK, right.
All right.
So we need to catch up.
That wasn't bad at all.
You can just take it from room to room and follow spots wherever they happen.
Absolutely.
Now let's lay that ketchup stain down.
You take the top off.
Here we go.
Little dollop right there.
OK, I'm going to mix it in right there.
How's that?
OK, no, no.
While we're waiting for the people acting like he shit on the couch.
He didn't get on the couch and like shit on it.
In the past, I used to tell people to fill a spray bottle with water,
then spritz down their furniture and then take a brush and brush off all that.
No more.
The big green clean machine.
Just use one of those rollers.
Because of this special attachment that's made for upholstery.
OK?
All right.
Same formula and everything.
It's useful.
And that's all there's to it.
And the pet hair is gone like magic.
All right, another great and helpful hint here.
You would literally buy anything if there was a wholesome,
sweet, middle-aged woman telling you to do it.
Look at that.
That's not true.
OK, now I'm going to pull.
Mistake.
Would have been very easy to do, by the way.
I just pull the trigger, put the water and cleaning solution down,
and it pulled it right up.
And it's not very wet at all.
It'll be dry by morning.
Now I'll tell you what.
This shit does work, though.
It's like a carpet cleaner.
Guys, the carpet cleaner is the same technology.
He's the big green clean machine.
Like a doctor?
Who is this?
I'm very, very impressed.
And congratulations.
This is just the beginning.
This machine is three machines in one.
It's a dry vacuum cleaner.
It's a wet shop vacuum.
And it's a deep cleaning machine.
$500 worth of machines.
And this machine is as powerful as all those machines.
They've been using this same exact technology for like 50 years.
It works.
A very powerful motor.
In fact, I will show you later they can unclog a drain.
All right, we'll hold them to that, won't we?
I want to see that demonstration.
Right now, I'm going to show you just how powerful it is as a dry vacuum.
Mary Ellen, if you turn that on, it can handle dirt.
That's not impressive.
Why are they cheering?
Thanks, Joe.
If you'd hand me the bowling ball and attachment down under that counter.
You're not going to try and suck up the bowling ball through here.
Oh, no.
There's no way that's going to work.
All right.
You'll put that attachment on there.
You'll see it's clear.
No strings or wires in there.
Nothing up the sleeve.
Now, John, what I'm going to do is I'm going to lie down on the table
and I'm going to lie facing up on the table.
What I want you to do is hold the bowling ball over my face.
And I trust the suction.
I created this goddamn product.
Ooh, be careful.
All right.
Show the people that it's no glue on there.
Okay, just now, Mary Ellen, if you'll turn that powerful motor on.
That's how much I trusted.
You were going to do a demonstration like that.
And when we heard that, we decided to devise a little test of our own here.
Right now, I'd like to introduce you to someone who's very near and dear
to Mary Ellen's heart.
This is her husband, Tom, who's standing by outside our studio.
What?
Hi, honey.
Mary Ellen, I think you've gone a little bit too far this time.
What has he rigged up to?
Just pull the camera back just a little bit.
You'll see that Tom is in the hot seat or maybe the cool seat
because underneath him, can you see that?
Excuse me.
Are they going to put it on his head?
That's cold water.
Now, as you can see, we've got a big green clean machine set up out there.
And that's what we're going to do.
What?
Machine on.
OK, we've got a situation set up just like Eric's test.
We're going to put a bowling ball.
Oh, hi.
And any time that motor fails or burns out under the stress.
Hi.
And Tom, you know what's going to happen.
Don't kill a friend.
You owe me for this.
I thought they were going to put it on his head and turn it on and suck his head
and then drop the lever as if he was going to fall into the water.
And I thought I was going to keep him up by holding his head.
I didn't.
OK.
He has anything to worry about.
But there's something about the big green clean machine
that's better than anything else you've seen so far.
OK, just hold on.
I got to get this ready.
This is important.
Just bear with me for one second, please.
I'm going to go away for a second.
We've got a situation set up just like Eric's test.
We're going to put a bowling ball in his shell.
That motor fails or burns out under the stress.
So it's going to fall off to a switch.
And Tom, you know what's going to happen.
Don't kill a friend.
You owe me for this.
I don't think he has anything to worry about.
But there's something about the big green machine that's better than anything else
you've seen so far.
Because we have been cleaning our homes the wrong way.
Joe, if your hair was dirty, what would you do?
Quick question.
I'd wash it.
If your shirt was dirty, what would you do?
What the fuck is this?
What if you vacuumed your hair and your shirt?
What would you call them?
I call them dirty and me stupid.
I guess that doesn't work.
Exactly.
Vacuum cleaning only gets the dirt on top.
The big green clean machine deep cleans.
It injects a warm solution that grabs the deep down dirt.
Is he all right?
And then somebody went in to get him.
Somebody went in to get him.
He leaves behind.
In fact, we have an independent lab run a study for us.
And this is what they did.
They took an ordinary vacuum cleaner, went into a nine by nine.
Save them.
They vacuumed out as much dirt as they could get.
And this is what they got.
13 grams of dirt.
Turn off face cam.
Exactly.
Then they went in with the big green clean machine,
cleaned the same carpet that the vacuum had first crack at,
dried down the water.
Now I'm back in there.
23 more grams of dirt.
I missed everything.
Was still in the carpet.
All this was left behind after vacuuming.
Look at all that dirt.
Now, girls, what these guys are trying to say
with other machines is that all the vacuuming,
all the scrubbing, even a team of Marymaids
is not going to get your home as clean as a big clean machine.
Now let's go from the big green clean machine to clean floors
is to use the special floor attachment.
You want to grab that one over there?
OK, this is it.
It snaps on very simply.
Also use the floor care formula that is absolutely marvelous
for tile, vinyl, marble, lots of things.
Everything but wood because everybody knows water
cannot be used on wood floors.
Look at this dumb ass shit.
Everybody but Joe, that is.
I just keep thinking of the guy in the water tank.
OK, now, it's very easy to move around.
Panisters do not scuff the floor and it's not top heavy,
so it's not going to tip over.
Little casters on the bottom here,
keep it spinning smoothly.
Let's get the plaster on.
OK.
All right, here we go.
Take a swipe right through.
Holy shit.
That was great.
Clean plants.
Well, usually I pour the water over the floor.
And it makes me understand why I sold 2 million books.
And watering day is a umbrella.
You're an oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What happens, we've been talking about stains here now,
but what happens when a stain really gets set in?
What do you do then?
Now, that's a toughie.
But come on over here and I'm going to show you
what a great job the big green clean machine does.
OK, now on this step, we have grape juice.
And that is tough.
All you have to do is turn on the pump.
Just the pump.
And pre-treat the stain by just laying down
the cleaning solution.
OK, just spray on the cleaning solution like this.
Now, go have a cup of coffee or maybe do a helpful hint
while that does the job.
I like that one.
OK?
Oh, another helpful hint.
I actually want to hear this.
No way.
Just switch it on and rub it out.
That's all there's to it.
And then you can remove the WD-40 whip,
your big green clean machine.
You want to take that up.
It's a very helpful hint.
Stain, has this been pre-treated long enough?
OK, that should do it.
Now you turn on the pump and the vacuum.
Excellent.
Why can't I skip this ad?
Is it blood?
That wasn't blood.
You don't ever run into a professional carpet cleaner.
Yeah, some motherfucker is sitting
right next to the camera's microphone in the audience.
And their clapping is what you're hearing.
That's what's going on.
That's what you're hearing.
Somebody's like, somebody's too close to the mic in the audience.
Because many times they end up looking like this.
Dirtier than the carpets you're going to clean.
Anything that irks me, they sell you all these a la carte bottles.
Foamers, anti-spiders.
Look at this one.
Classic lane cleaner.
Isn't that cute?
And on and on it goes.
It drives me crazy how this one bottle will do to prevent future stains.
You can, it's OK.
You can tell just how unenthusiastic most people in the audience are.
Because listen to the, we got somebody mic'd up.
We have an audience member mic'd the fuck up.
We can tell every time they clap their hands.
Every single time.
And what they're doing is they're like kind of trying to blend in.
Like they're not really, they don't really care.
They're not participating.
They don't really give a shit.
And we can hear it in real time.
We know how they feel in real time.
This carpet care formula to do, let's say, a 10 by 10 room.
With this formula in the big green clean machine, about $1.50.
A dollar and a half for a 10 by 10 room.
One, two, three, four.
Thanks, Eric.
Now let's switch gears here for a second.
The other day, we wanted to find out how this machine compared in price to what the pros charge.
Now we've all seen deals advertised for $9.95 a room or $25 for five rooms.
It seemed just too good to be true.
What's this?
All right, now here's the situation as we've set it up.
We've contacted a number of different carpet cleaning companies,
the ones that usually send you these flyers in the mail.
And normally they advertise low, low prices per room.
And we've asked them to give us an estimate based on two rooms,
two hallways, and three pieces of living room furniture.
Why is this a prank?
Now these estimates are going to be based on the same exact job that the big green clean machine can do.
Now they have no idea they're going to be on camera because we've hidden cameras all through the house.
There's what they call a lipstick camera.
Oh, is that really?
That's literally right there.
This is fucking weird.
450 for the furniture and the carpet.
450.
Somebody said it's a ghost camp.
To catch a cleaner?
Now say that again.
Say that again, but into this microphone that I have in front of me.
Can you say that into the pot of flowers?
Just real quick.
That was fucked up.
To act fast.
All right.
Now let me see if I can summarize what we've seen here.
The big green clean machine is a powerful vacuum cleaner that uses a reusable bag.
It's also a powerful wet vac.
It picked up that Kool-Aid in one gulp.
It also deep cleaned some carpets, got out that really deep down dirt,
and also gobbled up some of the worst things I've ever seen and replaced about $5 worth.
Are we going to check in with the with the husband?
Will you help me out, Eric?
I sure will.
Okay, Eric, what do we have here?
We have the dry vacuum accessories, including the washable filter bag.
We need to check in with the husband, right?
We have the wet vac attachment to unclog the drain.
We have the caddy organizer for your closet to keep everything handy.
We have an instruction manual, and this is nice,
an instructional videotape to get the best results from your machine.
And to get you started, a bottle of the carpet care formula and the baroflora formula.
That's a lot with this machine.
That's a lot.
And as my special gift to you, my new book, Mary Ellen's Wow,
helpful hints that really work, Joe.
Wonderful, thanks, Mary Ellen.
I kind of feel like it's going to be able to feel like that book
is actually kind of probably kind of interesting.
The Mary, the Mary Ellen random hints.
I'm like, look, spend the ketchup bottle around.
I feel like that's a great bathroom book.
I really I honestly feel like that would be it's probably like a just a bullet points
of like thousands of little bullet points of like two or three sentences
where you just kind of go, oh, that's kind of funny.
Even if it's like doesn't work.
I feel like that's a great toilet book.
I really do.
I feel like that's like a cool.
Oh, that's fun.
It's a lot.
It's just life hacks.
Yeah, I don't know.
If you're a 1993 grandmother, maybe.
Would you buy a Mary Ellen joke book?
You guys remember those?
I would like, oh, funny little Mary.
Mary Ellen's funny jokes.
Do you remember those?
It was like 500 pages long.
And it was just these two sentence little jokey little clips.
Do you remember those?
I used to read them.
Oh, there he is.
Oh, yuck.
Aren't you disgusted?
You got to buy this now.
Total cleaning system.
We got to see this green clean machine.
It's three powerful cleaning machines in one in the dry mode.
It's a state of the art dual filtration vacuum cleaner.
Dual filtration technology.
It's a wet bath, gobbles up, spills in seconds.
And it's a self-contained deep cleaning extraction machine
for carpets of post re-employed.
I like that.
It looked like ice coffee.
That looks like an ice coffee advertisement
with like the like the pillowing cream and the coffee.
I like that.
That's a big green plane.
Wait, the guy's name is John Bissell.
Because it was this actually the guy's name is just John.
It's John Bissell.
This is the man himself for carpets of post re-employed.
Really?
If even holy shit drains and it's quality built right here on the USA.
I believe that the big green plane machine is the finest unit.
Holy shit.
Actually, John Bissell.
We vacuum this carpet with an ordinary vacuum cleaner.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I use a Bissell.
Thing works fucking great thing actually works great.
And we are the big green clean machine on the sand carpet
and look at all the dirt ordinary vacuuming left behind.
Now you can attack.
I got a Bissell.
The worst day nightmares when they happen.
Just fill the big green clean machine with water
then add the special carpet care.
Prove it.
The big green clean machine will pre-spot.
Right back.
Back.
Not quite.
I am going to refill my drink.
I'll be right back.
Here it is.
Bissell.
Check it out.
See?
Not a liar.
Bissell.
Hey, look.
Works great.
It's got technology in it.
This is a Bissell.
Suck up a bowling ball with it.
Yeah, look.
Look.
Bissell.
Model number I use.
I didn't just go to the store.
Stop.
I don't want you to say the model number.
I told you I have a-
I told you.
It's a Bissell.
They work good.
They're good.
You got same day delivery.
Oh, please.
Oh, yeah?
Same day delivery, huh?
Stick it out of the box.
Does that look like same-
No, that's disgusting.
That's gross.
I was about to say same day delivery, huh?
And show you what's in here.
Same day delivery, huh?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
How do I get this back on?
How do I put it back in?
Oh, no, I know.
I know.
Look at how easy this is.
Look at how easy this is to do.
Check this out.
Look at how easy this is.
Done.
Now you're ready to go.
Do a bowling ball.
I can't do a bowling ball.
It's not that type of a vacuum.
It's all over me.
I can't do a bowling ball.
That's not that kind of vacuum.
It doesn't have that attachment.
I don't-
Why? This music is still playing.
Okay, we're good.
I don't-
I don't have that attachment.
It's just-
It's a stick vacuum.
You can't do that.
Clean, defoam, deodorize, brighten,
and lay down a layer of protection all at once,
saving you time and money.
You get professional results without being-
Dump your drink on the ground and clean it up.
I love the big green cleaning-
It's not a wet vacuum.
My kids love to make a mess in the kitchen.
That's why I'm glad I've got the big green clean machine.
Replacing all these old-fashioned appliances,
you'd expect the big green clean machine
to cost well over $500.
But now, the entire system can be yours for only $299,
or better yet, just 10 interest-
That's not how much I paid for mine!
$290 a month!
Get Bissell's big green clean machine,
the dry vacuum attachments,
the washable-
That's not how much I paid for mine!
The construction tools,
and the storage caddy,
the carpet and upholstery,
and floor care formulas,
the instruction guide,
plus the step-by-step how-to video,
and as a free bonus,
Mary Ellen Pickum-
Anybody from Evolved is watching.
Any vacuum cleaning shit I could do?
Wow, helpful hints that really work.
Bissell's big green clean machine
is not available in any store.
Put it to your ultimate test for 30 days.
If your carpet to upholstery and floors
aren't cleaner than they've ever been,
return the big green clean machine
for your money back.
I didn't borrow it.
Ice coffee.
And order the big green clean machine right now.
To order for just 10 low monthly payments of $29.90,
call one-
Pet owners.
1-800-69-
I'll go along with the-
All right, here we go.
Dump all that dirty water in there.
Commercial, we dumped all the dirty water
from these machines,
and even with the few stains
we picked up here in the studio,
look at how dirty this water is,
and that probably would have been
left behind in your home-
And, hey, hey, hey, Frank,
get her husband back over here.
I think so, and you know something else-
We can see how long he can put his head
under there for without puking.
And the big green clean machine
is a must for pet owners.
You can have all the dogs you want now.
Invite the neighbor's dogs over, sure.
And another thing,
when our children are younger,
we are sterilizing their baby bottles
hours and hours and hours,
and they're running around the house
with a contaminated stuffed animal
in their mouth, right?
Defeats the purpose, yeah.
Sometimes you can't launder these things, so-
I know, I've seen a lot of people
say a few things about
you should do an infomercial thing,
acting like I haven't made that call yet.
You're acting like I haven't made that call?
Another great use for the big green clean machine.
I have.
Clean them up.
For the stuffed animal.
And another use-
I'm not saying a fucking single other thing
about this.
Decorate a pillow.
All right, you can do this one.
Stop!
My head.
Uh, that's a fucking $300 cashmere shirt
you just ruined with your-
Don't touch my shirt.
I thought that was the same guy for a second.
I just had to take a double take.
I thought that was the same person.
I was like, it's him, again.
Okay, Joe, now remember.
Always use your big green clean machine first
to unclog the drain.
Never after you've tried chemical drain cleaners.
Hit that powerful vacuum motor switch
and let's see what happens.
Okay, now, I just put it right over here.
Put it right in there, Joe.
Okay, here we go.
What the fuck?
It came right out.
You bet, Joe.
And come here, I'm going to show you
what's worse than dust.
It lives right here in your mouth
and you know there's 18,000 dust-
Ah!
Disgusting.
That is really disgusting.
But with the big green clean machine-
Oh, come on.
You had such an opportunity to go.
No!
No, help me!
How- I- Really?
Unbelievable.
They missed an opportunity.
All right, I'm going to finish this mattress.
When's the last time you cleaned your mattress?
It's easy to do with the big green clean machine
and it's a must if you've got a bed wetter.
Believe me.
Joe, are you out there yet?
What?
You know, a lot of care of the outside-
Who is she talking about?
Well, with the big green clean machine
you can deep clean that upholstery.
Even the headliner.
Look, it came out great
and it smells good in here too.
All right, let me turn off the machine.
Let's go over and check with Tom
to see how he's doing in the dunk tank.
And let's open it up.
As you see, we have a full 14-pound turkey
inside of here cooking from all the vortex power.
All right, well don't go away.
Introducing America-
All right, I think we're good to go on this one.
You'd expect the big green
structure to both reinforce-
I think we got everything out of this one.
Recall 1-800-
Sucked it up so easy.
Let's have a look at the off-screen machine.
Here's what's happening.
How are the results?
Oh, this sheet of linoleum was covered in mud, dirt, and grime
and it sucked it up so easily.
Look at this.
Holds the dirt right up there.
Beautiful.
All right, I'm going to turn off that machine.
We'll share here.
Guy, you're doing just great.
I didn't know you could do your own light color upholstery.
I always thought you had to have a professional.
All right, not in this case.
Beautiful. I'm going to turn off your machine.
It'd be so loud in this room.
It'd be so loud in here.
Well, to tell you, this is one example of what happens
when the results speak for themselves.
Congratulations.
Don't congratulate me.
Thank the guys that this will take a bow, Eric.
Thanks, Eric.
All right, we're concerned the big green clean machine
dunk tank test has been a success.
Tom, thanks very much for your high drive.
Yeah, let's see the trickery.
Wires holding that ball up.
No, don't!
Oh, no.
I don't know if he made it.
Why is everybody acting?
Like he got like crushed by like a cinder block.
With the new helpful hint for the big green clean machine,
I'm going to be extracting water out of it today.
Green clean machine is going to keep all those valuables
in your home valuable.
It was a full of missile cleaner.
Bye, clean machine.
I can't, I can't.
I got a fucking goddamn infomercialism.
I swear to God, why would you keep,
why would you freeze on this?
Why would you freeze on this?
It's so like, it's so weird.
Why?
Okay, we're going to go to this one.
The following is a paid advertisement
for the Ready, Set, Go!
Brought to you by GT Direct, Lewisville, Colorado.
We don't have busy lives to wait for food.
So we fall into the fast food rut or buy carb filled snacks.
It's Kathy Mitchell.
Millions have discovered the secret that fast food can be quick and
My heart is fucking smoking right now.
No, it's Kathy Mitchell.
Oh my God, it's Kathy Mitchell.
I just want to, I need to pause this because I want everyone to know
you have heard me say things on this stream
over the last probably four or five years.
That came from this commercial.
I've seen this probably a thousand times.
I have made weird references to this and never explained it.
I just kind of copied her talking.
And people might have just been like, what is he talking about?
It's from this.
This 24 minutes has given me like four hours worth of stream content.
In under 10 minutes.
You can, thanks to the all new Express Ready, Set, Go!
I'm not kidding.
No, that's not a joke.
Pork tenderloin with sweet potato in eight minutes.
Grilled paninis in just five minutes.
This is geek.
Kathy Mitchell, by the way.
This is the infinity war of Kathy Mitchell infomercials.
I've said this before.
If I saw Kathy Mitchell somewhere, like at like a fan meetup or convention or something,
I would actually be like, oh my fucking God.
I don't give a shit about like, oh, what have you met?
Like Brad Pitt.
What have you met?
Like, um, I can't even think of the celebrity.
Um, who's another fucking celebrity?
Is there any celebrity I can think of?
Brad Pitt.
Give me anybody else.
Any other name.
Harrison Ford.
Yeah.
No, it doesn't matter.
I would be like, oh, hey, what's up, Harrison Ford.
Nice to meet you.
Don't care.
Kathy Mitchell comes up and is like, hey, Kathy Mitchell here.
I'd be like, hands are fucking sweating.
I'm not kidding.
She's incredible.
She's so good in front of the camera.
She's so good at like taking a show, running a show and being like the quarterback of the set.
I'm not kidding.
Seriously.
You're not kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Here she comes.
Ready.
Set.
Go.
Just like millions of you, the Express 101 is always there for me.
And I can't imagine improving on what's already my most used kitchen helper.
But I've heard improvement is exactly what's happened.
And there's only one person in the world who's qualified to let us in on the news.
So let's join my friend, Kathy Mitchell, and discover what's happening to the easiest
cooking appliance in my home.
Kathy, how are you?
Good to see you.
Great to see you too.
I love my Express 101.
I think you're going to love it even more now because look what we can do.
Big, thick, man-sized sandwiches.
Beautiful frittata.
She said it.
Full-size.
And look at these guys.
She actually said it.
Even cherry.
You couldn't do that before.
You've improved.
Man-sized.
We've made it even more perfect.
Come on, Joe.
This is the Express.
Ready.
Set.
Go.
Well, Kathy, this is beautiful.
And it is ready.
Look what we've done.
We took out that center divider.
So now you have 25% more cooking area.
So you can cook a lot of different things in here.
Exactly right.
Like how about pizza?
It makes the best pizza I've ever had.
Now this is my almost instant pizza dough.
And the recipe comes with it.
All you have to do is pop it in there and then put whatever toppings you like.
It's a personal pizza.
So you don't have to wait for the delivery man.
Pay extra for all the toppings.
No tip for the driver here either.
Why get delivery?
You can make it in the Express.
Ready.
Set.
Go.
You'll never tell the difference except it's not so greasy.
So we ain't helping you.
Saving a lot of calories.
Little light mozzarella.
Do you like peppers?
Sure.
Greasy.
Throw it out.
Oh more toppings.
Okay.
That pizza is going to take seven minutes and we've got a built-in timer.
So I just said only seven minutes and it'll call me when the pizza is done.
And the go part is see the green light.
That green light comes on.
You know your machine is preheated and ready to start cooking.
Ready.
Set.
Go.
Wow.
A lot of improvements here, Kathy.
Seven minutes possibilities.
Now you don't always have to use pizza dough.
Like look here.
These are corn tortillas.
I'm going to make kind of a Mexican stacked pizza.
What I did was I just spread some beans on this corn tortilla.
I'm going to just drop it right in there.
That easy.
I'm going to stack another one on top of that.
And now we're just going to put on some meat.
This is a great way to get rid of leftover.
So yeah like practical.
And this one's only going to take about five minutes.
So I can spend time for five minutes and now I don't lose track of what's cooking.
Have you ever had a Hawaiian pizza?
I know they exist.
Okay.
This is pita bread and it tastes almost exactly like pizza crust.
So you got a pita pizza.
Pita pizza.
That's right.
I mean I don't know about that.
All you have to do is add your toppings.
I don't know about that.
Okay.
Just smush it around there.
Exactly.
In this case I'm going to use Canadian bacon.
Okay.
But like using leftovers and like kind of making new foods from like leftovers.
Sure just scoop on a couple of chunks on there.
Okay.
You can have exactly what you want on it.
Matt's going to take again about only five minutes because the crust is basically already
cooked.
This is all great but I think all of us are really going to miss cooking those side by
side meals you used to.
I know like in the express 101.
Let me show you something.
Is this what you thought you were going to miss?
This is the new insertable divider pan and it goes in just like that.
Wow.
So they've got two machines.
And it's still the world's best no-bold omelet maker.
Love those omelets.
I do too.
This is just two beaten eggs and I'm going to divide it between.
Look at that.
We've seen so many of this shit.
We've seen egg steamers, omelet in the microwave.
Take a look at that.
And on the other side how about a veggie omelet?
This is mushrooms and peppers and onions.
It's an omelet.
I'm going to just put a little cheese on top and close that lid.
And neatness doesn't count.
I remember you said that.
Now that's going to rise up.
It's going to rise up and in seven minutes we're going to have a perfect omelet.
Cooking from top to bottom.
Now a weekend breakfast.
How about some stuffed french toast?
Oh, stuffed french toast.
I've never heard of that one.
Oh, it's delicious.
I bought this extra thick bread.
I've spread it with a little cream cheese and some strawberry jam.
And all I'm going to do is I'm going to go ahead.
Man-sized french toast.
Just roll that sandwich in that egg batter.
And in this case now I'm using the entire cooking area of the machine.
That's going to take about five minutes.
So I just set the timer for five minutes.
And how about some lunch?
I'm ready.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to make you a grilled sandwich.
So I've just got a nice piece of french bread here.
I'm going to put a little ham.
Ham looks good.
Some cheese and some tomatoes.
Yep.
And the top.
Oh, now I like to brush it with just a little bit of olive oil.
Oh, not anymore.
Which is very healthy for you.
And we'll pop that right in there.
Hey, this is like a panini.
And that'll look in just about.
What'd you say?
And we'll pop that.
What did Cathy Mitchell say?
And some tomatoes and the top.
Now I like to brush it with just a little bit of olive oil.
Which is very healthy for you.
By the way, I trust Cathy Mitchell more than like members of Congress.
So, I mean, let's fucking go.
Are you serious?
And we'll pop that right in there.
Hey, this is like a panini.
And that'll cook in just about five minutes.
So we'll set that timer.
And over here, I'm going to make two sandwiches at once.
So that's not a high bar.
Now you like wraps.
Yeah.
This is pastrami.
So I'm going to put a little bit of mustard on it first.
You can use the different tortillas, the red and the green tortillas.
And we'll just lay that on there.
Oh, yeah.
That's good lean meat too.
And some.
I hope she's doing all right.
You know what I mean?
I hope she's like living a great life.
Pickles, right?
All you do is fold in the sides and roll it up.
Now, don't try to miniature.
She's actually doing this too, by the way.
And you got a nice deep cheese.
She changes.
She ain't just putting like, oh, yeah.
Like, here's the thing that's already done.
Like I look, I pretended like I was going to make it, but I didn't.
Here it's already done.
Look, I pretended I made that.
Look at this.
Pastrami and Swiss.
She's actually making this sandwich.
All you do is fold in the sides and roll it up.
Now, don't try to miniaturize the food.
This has got plenty of room.
And you got a nice deep well top and bottom.
And it's got the hinge lid.
So it'll raise up.
Exactly.
Now, how about a corn dog?
I love corn dogs.
It reminds me of being at the fair.
You're just a big kid.
I know that.
Now, just like if I was cooking this in the oven, I'd spray.
Mustard disappeared.
I'm going to spray my big kid.
What are you talking about?
You know what she's talking about.
She's got plenty on me without pickles.
You don't know what she's talking about.
All you do is fold in the sides.
Where?
And roll it up.
It's right there.
Now, don't try to.
Are you?
What are you trying to?
Hold on.
We're trying to like smear in a way that's not going to work.
Kathy Mitchell's fucking infomercial.
It's not going to work.
I just hate to tell you that's not going to happen.
Because this has got plenty of room.
It's not going to happen.
And you got a nice deep well top and bottom.
And it's got the hinge lid.
So it'll raise up.
Exactly.
Now, how about a corn dog?
I love corn dogs.
Reminds me of being at the fair.
You're just a big kid.
I know that.
Now, just like if I was cooking this in the oven, I'd spray the pan.
I'm going to spray.
It's what do you mean the mustard disappeared?
Ever.
Now, mustard doesn't disappear.
Now, personally, I put the whole hot dog in.
But a friend of mine says they like it cut up because that way they get dog in every bite.
Look at how cool that is.
So you got the whole pack in there.
It all works just like that.
This wasn't like a recalled, right?
Please don't ruin it for me.
We've seen like four or five girls at this point.
Like three of them got recalled.
This one's all right, right?
Express like 101.
Express, ready, set, go.
Come on.
It's a good product, I hope, right?
There's no really awful article about something horrible happening, right?
I think so.
This one awards.
This thing won awards?
All right.
Okay.
No recalls on this one.
Nice.
What do you fucking like?
No, get out of here with this bullshit.
It's got four stars on Amazon right now.
Still on Amazon, it's got four stars.
Yeah, get out of here.
And close that lid.
About seven minutes.
All right, ready, set, go.
Ready, set, go.
It's one streamer of the year.
Come on.
Okay.
Kathy, it smells like a pizzeria in here.
Oh, I know, but it doesn't cost like a pizzeria in here.
Listen to that crunch.
Because these pizzas cost about one dollar each.
Look at this, a perfect personal pizza with exactly what we want on it.
It looks pretty good, I'll be honest.
I would eat that.
That's our Hawaiian with the Canadian bacon and a pineapple.
All right, now how about our stacked pizza?
Look at that.
Stacked pizza.
Now that's our tortillas with the...
Oh, I would eat that.
Oh, can you smell that?
That's awesome.
It smells great.
I'm going to add on a little bit of lettuce and tomato.
Get this.
It was...
No, it wasn't.
You guys are just fucking haters, I think.
You guys are trying to find anything you can on this.
This looks fucking cool.
This looks good.
You just hate us.
Are you just looking for anything?
I think.
Come on.
And my daughter made this up.
These are crushed nacho chips and it just gives it a little zing.
Fiesta.
Fiesta, exactly.
Now, up right on time.
Right on time.
Here's our pepperoni pizza.
Now, this is your traditional...
All right, get the olives off there.
And that dough smells so good.
It's so fresh smelling.
Wait till you taste.
Now, this is just...
Oh, and can you hear how crisp it is?
I heard the crunch.
Listen to that crunch.
Classic, Kathy, that's the one.
I am, but it's going to be really hot.
I'm going to jump in and eat it.
It goes...
So fresh, so crisp, and so gooey on the top.
And believe it or not, that's under 200 calories and only about a dollar.
That's under 200 calories?
A slice?
You mean the little thing he has in his hand?
About a dollar.
I need it.
This thing is fucking 200 calories.
That whole pizza is like 1500 calories.
It's going to be really hot.
I feel for this guy.
This guy's great too, by the way.
But he has to eat this.
He has to do that.
You can't just not eat it.
And if he takes even one second where he's not biting this and not enjoying it,
it looks bad.
Product doesn't look good.
This is probably molten lava in his mouth.
And he fucking...
That's a champ, right?
That is a champ.
Are you kidding me?
Without even flinching?
Jump in and eat it.
And you can tell.
You can tell how fucking burning hot this is right there.
It's like this is unbearable.
But it's like the show's about to get so much...
The show got to go on.
Are you finally going to feed me?
I am, but it's going to be really hot.
I'm going to jump in and eat it.
So fresh, so crisp, and so gooey on the top.
And look, he's right back in.
That's under 200 calories and only about a dollar.
That's an actual showman right there.
You know, people love omelets, but a lot of people are afraid to make them.
But look how easy they come out in here.
Isn't that beautiful?
Beautiful.
No folding.
And another thing you're going to love about the insertable divider pan
is that it makes it a lot easier to serve.
Two great showmen.
Two great...
That's our meat lover's omelet.
We got Kathy Mitchell.
Vegetarian omelet.
And look how they just come right out.
Look how clean up.
That would just wipe out with a damp cloth.
You know, it'll go in the dishwasher.
It's wonderful.
More versatility for you there.
Absolutely.
Look, here's our French toast.
Exactly.
And remember, I can utilize the whole base
and the other side of the spatula that lifts the large...
That looks perfect.
And look at this.
Now, wait till I cut into this.
Remember, this has the stuffing of the cream cheese and the strawberries.
And it's hot.
He's going to eat it.
He's going to go...
Does that look delicious?
He heard that and went...
Oh, fuck.
Not again.
Now, you remember this was our grilled sandwich.
Oh, look at that.
Our panini.
Right.
Now, I'm going to use the large side of the spatula
and just lift that onto the gutting board.
This is real.
It is just chock full of stuff.
Kathy Mitchell would not fuck with us.
So crisp and so delicious.
All right.
Now, look over here because here's our corn dog.
There it is.
Look at all those little guys in there.
They popped right out.
You can have it fast and easy just like that.
And Mike is like a little bit of mustard to dip it in as they eat it.
And now this is our pastrami wrap.
Oh, the pastrami.
See what we got.
Oh, look how full that looks delicious.
I want to buy that right now.
It does.
Oh, I love a good wrap.
Now, are you ready for some dinner?
I'm always ready for food.
Come on down here.
Wait a minute.
Now, you're going to put.
Oh, no.
Kathy, no.
Kathy, wait.
Go steak up against the finest restaurant and win.
Kathy, those sandwiches were so good.
And the.
All right.
Now, I'm just brushing with.
Now, are you ready for some dinner?
What is she saying?
All right.
Come on down here.
Wait a minute.
Now, you're going to put a steak in this?
I would put my ready set go steak up against the finest restaurant and win.
All right.
Now, I'm just brushing.
I hope that would be real sauce and we're just going to put it right in the machine.
The divider is out.
So you have the full cooking area.
And now you.
OK, you like onions and mushrooms.
I hear that sizzle.
Let's cut up this mushroom and onion.
OK, now let me turn this over.
I want to show you how much sear we've got already on that steak.
Look at that.
So this does heat up quickly.
Oh, it does.
Now, I'm just going to go ahead and put in those mushrooms and onions.
And that's going to cook to medium in about seven to eight minutes.
Seven minutes.
How about some unfried fried chicken?
Fried chicken is so delicious and so much fat.
We've got a skinless breast and some legs.
And I'm going to just roll them in some crushed up cereal crumbs.
You can use any kind of cereal you want.
Just crush it up real fine.
Now, the only oil I'm going to use for this chicken is a little nonstick spray.
No deep fat fryer.
No warming the oven up.
This probably works in this.
And you know, without that divider, you've got 25 percent more room.
Three pieces of chicken in there.
There's three pieces of chicken in that thing.
All these recipes are in the cookbook with times.
That chicken is going to take about 10 to 12 minutes,
depending on how big the pieces are.
Okay.
But you guys don't say anything yet.
I've got a full course meal.
And there's our divider.
Guys, do you not trust Kathy Mitchell?
I'm starting to see some, like, consent here.
Excuse me.
You're not going to give her at least a minute to explain what's going on here?
You don't trust her?
You should trust her.
Like, I actually can't believe this.
If you had a ramen cookbook, I can't trust her.
Are you serious?
It's probably fantastic.
Kathy Mitchell would never lead us astray, ever.
Pork tenderloin medallions that I've marinated in a little teriyaki.
Listen to that sizzle.
Listen to that.
Now, for a side dish for pork, I love sweet potatoes.
So I've got some sweet potatoes and apple pieces mixed up together
with a little bit of brown sugar.
And that is going to cook in about eight minutes.
All right.
It's not like cooking in the microwave where the food comes out rubbery.
It's juicy.
It's warm.
And in fact, being able to cook with a little bit of oil
is a good, healthy habit for me and my kids.
Come on.
Has been watching our weight, trying to get healthy.
For the working person, very fast.
Just frees you up from everything.
Look at that omelet.
Dishes thrown in the dishwasher, and you're done.
It's got a timer on it.
It tells you when to put things in.
It's quick.
And when you finish, you don't have to clean it up.
It's great.
This is the mini food pattern.
It's probably my favorite because it'll just cook everything.
This is copium.
Cinnamon rolls.
I love to make cinnamon rolls in the morning for the kids.
But who wants to heat up that big old oven?
Oh, no, but I get the oven.
Get it away.
Get it out of my house.
So in here, I just spray it with a little nonstick.
I cut each cinnamon rolls into three pieces.
So now we're going to make cinnaminis.
And these only take four minutes.
Remember, it's ready, set, four minutes to go.
OK.
Now over here, I've got some little smoky sizzling.
Ready, set, go.
Ready, set, four minutes to go.
My grandkids love these.
And while I do this, if you could go back to the refrigerator,
bring me a pan.
You'll find in there.
OK.
I've just got some pancake mix.
And I'm going to pour it right over those little smoky links.
I would eat these.
These are going to make great finger food.
I find that little kids really would rather eat with their fingers.
OK.
We're going to have to be a grown man, too.
At night, before I go to bed, I take a frozen tater tot,
drop it into each well, and then pour some egg over it
and put it in the refrigerator.
Then all I have to do is get up, pop it into the ready, set, go.
And I'll have egg stirs, or potatoes and eggs, in four minutes.
Ready, set, go.
OK.
Now, how about some meatballs?
I know you like meatballs.
Grandma Farago's favorite.
Farago.
These are made special, low-cal meatballs.
These are ground turkey.
Less than three ingredients.
My kind of recipe.
Wow.
I'm healthy for you.
Form the meatballs, absolutely, and pop them right in there.
Now, these are going to cook without watching,
without rolling, without turning, in just about eight minutes.
You don't have to deep fry.
The way you taste them, you won't even hardly tell the difference.
Look like you have a tiny arm.
I feel like you're a middle-party animal.
Yeah, as long as it's before 8 o'clock.
Well, you know, or during the party.
I love the banter.
What I've got here are some crab-stuffed mushrooms.
All I do is mix up the stuffing, and then
top each one with a mushroom.
So they're kind of upside down right now.
Stuffed mushroom?
But when they're done, we'll flip them over,
and we'll have hors d'oeuvres in about four minutes.
It is so much fun.
Four minute hors d'oeuvres.
That's right.
All right.
Ready, set, go.
Oh, I think that steak is ready.
You ready for that challenge?
Yep.
All right.
And let's take a look.
Oh, look at that.
Can you smell that?
Oh, man.
Wow.
He said you'd put this steak up against any other steak.
Put it any other way.
The mushrooms have caramelized with the onions.
Can't just take her word for it.
I'm going to cut it right down the middle,
because I want you to see.
Look at that.
That's perfect medium steak.
Now, if you like it a little more well done,
you could leave it in a little bit longer.
I'm just going to catch a little.
Now, it's going to be hot.
OK.
Oh, no.
Yeah, but it's worth it.
It's as good as a restaurant steak, is it not?
Kathy, you met the challenge.
Kathy.
Excellent.
Excellent steak.
All right, now how about some chicken?
There's the chicken.
And would you look at that?
Fantastic.
That was medium, as it was.
Unfried fried chicken.
That's cut the fat way down.
That's a good size.
Guys, Kathy Mitchell.
Kathy Mitchell got famous and popular.
She became a huge streamer from this.
She got really popular.
Well, she played a lot of Among Us.
But besides that, she was in the Minecraft stuff for a while.
But she is known for doing kind of like out of the box recipes.
So she would like, I know, people are like, what the?
Ew, gross, like cereal.
No, it's like she's like imitating recipes.
She did like recipe imitations, like leftover recipes.
She's not making fried chicken.
She's doing, it's like her thing, right?
Why is everybody minus twoing me?
I'm telling you what's going on here.
The Among Us joke?
OK.
Beautiful.
Now over here, this is the pork.
And again, I love the fact that I.
Oh, right, I said the words Among Us.
I forgot.
That's an automatic minus two from everybody.
Can take this out, because it makes it so much easier to serve.
I'm just going to put out that pork.
And let's get those potatoes out.
Those are sweet potatoes.
Oh, they look delicious, don't they?
Want a little taste?
Isn't that delicious?
This is the most delicious program I've ever worked at.
All right.
I want to show you a couple of ideas.
That's kind of weird.
This is an idea you're going to love.
This is my leftover box.
Leftovers.
What's in there?
I'm going to make you a white pizza.
For a white pizza, I'm just going to use a little ranch dressing.
See, she's like the left, just leftover stuff.
Let's see what needs to get used up.
Here's some broccoli.
This may be the only way you need broccoli in your kids.
Broccoli, ranch.
I've got some, oh, some shredded chicken here.
Let's add that.
OK.
And a little bit of mozzarella cheese.
What?
Get rid of these leftovers.
Think of the money I'm saving.
You guys are so above this somehow.
Why?
It's from pizza.
All right.
Oh, sounds like our minis are ready.
That's probably going to be fine.
All right.
Now this was city minis.
Why is everybody so above that?
That's very good.
Aren't these cute?
That's your grade.
Perfect.
Now these are our little pigs in a blanket.
And I want you to see, because that's the pancake mix.
We use seasoning.
It's just a little smokey at the bottom of each one.
Look at that.
Hey, that chain was probably already seasoned.
It's leftover chicken.
That was leftover chicken, leftover broccoli.
It's probably already ready to go.
You just have to heat it up.
I mean, seasoned.
It's been seasoned already.
It's leftovers.
The kids just dip them right in the syrup
and eat them with their fingers.
It's just a great breakfast for kids.
These are the eggsters.
Right, the ones I brought from the fridge.
We can just dump these right out onto the plate.
OK.
Those are just little taters with the omelet around them.
Kids love them.
And this, because it comes out, will go right in the dishwasher.
No cleanup at all.
I love the ding.
All right.
This is not your grandmother's meatballs.
This I've got to try.
All right.
Now, I'm going to give you a tiny little bite of one of them.
That's kind of cheating.
And I'm going to put some on my spaghetti.
So hot.
This guy, I feel so bad about this guy.
Is that good?
And remember, that's turkey.
So it's almost a health food.
So you make those meatballs up ahead of time.
When you get home from this part of the machine.
Here, it's going to be burning hot.
Here, take this.
It's hot.
Now, over here, this is the party stuff.
He eats his pizza.
It's burning.
Right.
I feel bad for this guy.
These are mushroom-stuffed mushrooms.
And again, because I can remove that insert,
I can just put my plate right on there and flip it over.
And look at that.
Wow.
That goes back in there.
Because if you're having a party,
there's nothing worse than cold, hot hors d'oeuvres.
Seriously.
You know, Kathy, this is absolutely remarkable.
But have you been holding something back from me,
like dessert?
Well, I have some very special desserts.
Come on over here, and I'll show you.
This first one I've got, it's kind of a giant cookie pizza.
I call it a cookie pizza.
This is your favorite cookie dough.
This happens to be oatmeal chocolate chip.
Any time you need a quick dessert,
pop it right in, just like this.
Look at that.
A cookie pizza right in the well.
Right in the well in four minutes.
Now, I know you love chocolate.
I heard this is your dad's favorite.
Dad loves this one, and he's got those little candy bars
around the house that he uses.
Candy bar filled cakes.
There is a recipe that tells you how to take a box cake mix
and split it into thirds.
So you just fill the wells.
And now, on this side, I'm just going
to put a little candy bar treat.
Now, this is really going to be a mystery dessert,
because I have no idea what flavor this is.
Into that same chocolate cake, I've got coconut macaroons
right down the middle.
So that's that.
Close the lid.
You don't know what it's in there?
Sit the timer for seven minutes.
Two different kinds of desserts.
Fantastic.
Now, come on over here, because I got something really
special to show you.
There's lots of different insert pans that will go in here.
This happens to be the full round insertable.
And I like this because I use it for my world famous upside
down cake.
So in the bottom, I've got some butter and some brown sugar.
These gross.
And I'm just going to put three pineapple rings.
People keep making them in commercials, and I never had it.
This will serve three to six people,
depending on who those people are.
The pineapple rings and a little cherry
in the middle of each one.
I feel like I would like this.
Am I weird enough to like this?
So you just fill it, pop it in there,
and that's going to bake for seven minutes.
They're pretty good.
And you didn't have to heat up the whole oven.
And that's going to save you a lot of money on energy.
I love pineapple.
It was always seen as the jokey meme cake from the 90s.
It was such a meme that I didn't want to try it.
We made this with leftovers, things you normally
would have just thrown out.
So it's really good for the budget.
And wait until you taste it.
All you guys were talking shit about this.
If this was here right now in front of me,
I would eat this right now, and I would probably love it.
Everyone was talking all this shit.
I would eat this.
It's just chicken broccoli with like a nice,
like, crispy crust with the cheese and ranch.
Like, that's fine.
I think it would be good.
What's wrong with that?
What do you mean raw?
Can you hear how crunchy that is?
I know you want to taste this.
Yeah, I am kind of a pizza fan.
Give that a try.
Is that good?
You know, this does not taste like leftovers.
It tastes like a freshly cooked meal.
So you're loving the Express Ready, Set, Go now
as much as I do?
I am, and I'm going to have another bite of pizza.
The Express Ready, Set, Go.
I want it so bad.
This unique cook rolled in files and minutes,
glitches, and wait, we'll do it.
All right, we'll see you again.
It's good tasting food.
Dude, 20 minutes just blazed by so fast.
I just love it.
I love Kathy Mitchell's so much.
That just, that time just disintegrated.
Save time, money, and calories.
Pizzeria quality pizza right here in just minutes.
It's a pizza maker, it's a panini maker,
a perfect omelet maker, and it's even a dessert maker,
which I can't wait to try.
And don't forget the new accessories,
the insertable divider pan.
Watch the ramen commercial, I will.
And the fantastic mini food ban,
which certainly puts the fun back in cooking.
I am impressed with the controlled cooking chamber
that cooks foods from the bottom and the top,
and it lets me fry and bake and grill
all with one appliance while saving me time,
saving me money, and saving energy.
Hogan versus Kathy Mitchell.
Almost 70% savings in energy.
Hogan versus Kathy Mitchell grill.
I'm laughing.
I'm laughing about what you said.
Energy costs.
And you know the cookbook gives you simple
step-by-step instructions,
and most are made in under 10 minutes.
Finally, dessert.
All right, we're good to see it.
Are you ready for the family cookie?
I am so ready.
The cookie-tza.
All right, now this is one big cookie.
There's the cookie-tza.
But if you have a favorite cookie recipe,
you can use it.
Now, do you like yours a la mode?
Of course.
Oh, yeah.
Nice big pile of ice cream in the middle.
All right, now here's your dad's favorite cake.
That looks familiar.
All right, let's get that guy out here.
Your dad's favorite cake.
Now, this was the joyous almond cake, remember?
Oh, yeah, with the macaroons in the center.
That really is beautiful the way it came up.
Now, let's see.
We're gonna solve the mystery of what's in the mystery cake.
Oh, I think that was some caramel.
Yep, great.
And finally, the pizzerias of stones.
Yes, the pineapple upside down cake.
All right, let's see it.
All right, so we're just gonna turn that upside down
and flip it over.
Presto flippo.
You know, I usually leave one piece of pineapple behind.
Oh, look, they all came out.
Oh, candy, look at that.
That is a piece of artwork.
Fast food can be a fantastic food
thanks to the express.
Ready, set.
Bro, this looks like gas station food.
So?
So what?
What's wrong with gas station?
Some gas stations do pretty good shit.
What are you talking about?
Ban that guy.
All right, give me the link to the ramen thing.
Let me take a, we got another Kathy Mitchell here.
Where is it?
Hold on, let me, this one here?
Is this the right one?
Okay, this is called Ramen Joy.
This is the right one, right?
Eyes on these homemade dishes and chocolatey desserts,
all made with ramen noodles.
Really?
Ramen noodles?
Yes, ramen.
Hi, Kathy Mitchell here with my new Ramen Joy cookbook,
filled with unbelievable recipes everyone will love.
This entire basket costs under $10
and wait till you see what you can make with it.
I trust her.
Ramen shrimp, ramen tacos, even ramen sliders.
Watch this.
Brown some beef or any other meat
with a ramen seasoning pack.
Dump in a package of ramen,
a good size squirt of ketchup,
and a can of cola.
Yes, cola.
For a fantastic barbecue beef pasta
better than what they serve at the rib joint
at a fraction of the cost.
What more?
Some cooked ramen and egg into a fast pizza crust.
Then add your favorite toppings.
Trust her.
For a mouth-watering pizza in minutes.
I trust her.
It's right here on page 84.
And here's my favorite.
Just dump some ramen on top of some leftover chicken
and veggies.
Add a can of soup.
I trust her.
Stir and bake.
A delicious feast for the whole family,
all for less than three dollars.
I'm gonna sit here and go like this.
What the best salad.
Thanks, Kathy.
I trust you.
It's good.
You're the best.
Why don't you take another bite?
Yeah.
Of course I will.
That one was so easy to get done.
It's delicious.
Start with lettuce, onions, and mandarin oranges.
Top with crushed ramen and pecans.
And use your seasoning pack to make an awesome dressing.
It's probably fine.
The rest of the best seller.
You can easily make it home.
Oh, love that crunch.
How about these apples?
Or grandma's ramen apple pie?
Ramen apple pie?
I love these recipes.
I made the king's berry crumble.
I trust her.
It was fast, easy, and so delicious.
I don't care.
I would eat all this.
So amazing everyone with my new ramen joy cookbook.
I would eat all this just to make sure
that she was happy.
You know what I mean?
I would eat this and be like,
yeah, no, it was all right.
It was pretty good.
Just because I know that might make her happy.
That might make her like,
yes, she'd be like, oh, cool.
We liked it.
What?
Get ramen nibbles with my favorite party recipe.
You would be a great poison tester.
Like these cheesy jalapeno poppers
or this fresh ramen hummus.
And don't forget dessert,
chocolate mousse filled ramen cups.
Yummy.
You can get both books
with nearly 100 delicious ramen recipes for 10 dollars.
It could be a joke.
Here's out of order.
Call 1-800-383-766-P to get ramen joy
on the special TV offer.
It's just for fun.
It's probably fucking just for fun.
www.byramenjoy.com.
So call.
It's just like a fun thing to do with like ramen, whatever.
It's probably fine.
It probably tastes good.
I am telling you right now,
I trust Kathy Mitchell, so I don't care.
No, I don't care.
If Kathy Mitchell is doing it,
I support it.
Sorry.
All right, what else we got?
I got a little bit more time.
Let's do some of the quick ones.
How about the handy peel?
I got it already here.
Are you tired of peel, peel, peel?
This is from, this is from,
this is Stirr's,
this is Stirr's sub sound, isn't it?
Are you tired of peel, peel, peeling potatoes?
Stop introducing handy peel,
the quick and easy way to prepare a meal.
Pick a raw potato, hold under the water.
Wasn't this his sub sound?
Peel and scrub all at the same time.
It is, or was for a while.
It's that easy.
The secret is the handy peels molded rubbing nubs
that grip and cleanly peel the skin.
Old fashioned peeling is hard and wasteful.
That actually might be all right.
You just rub, peel, and scrub.
Just look at the difference.
Now you can prepare a pile of potatoes in no time
for mouths of mouth-watering, creamy mashed
or fabulous homemade french fries.
You don't think it'll work?
Cooked to perfection.
Sweet potatoes are really hard to peel with a knife.
Ouch, that hurts.
Not with handy peel.
Simply rub, rinse, and peel all at the same time.
It's like plumbing gloves.
They don't work.
With handy peel, you can prepare
tasty homemade chips in no time.
All right, so it don't work, it don't work.
And it's not just for all types of potatoes.
Handy peel is perfect for carrots.
Aroma trim?
Well, we took both Krave Ender and suppressed
to the third street promenade in Santa Monica, California.
Where there's over 45 great restaurants
in a three block area.
First, we tested Krave Ender.
Boy, are these folks in for a surprise.
Watch this.
What is this?
Now you have chocolates.
I want another piece and I'll put it down
knowing I shouldn't have anymore.
But I'll go get more.
It's a good brownie, yeah?
Okay, wait, hang on, hang on.
What?
Do you think there's a product that could help you
not eat that brownie anymore?
Would that be amazing?
That would be more than amazing.
That would be a lifesaver.
It's a good brownie though, what's wrong?
It's changing the taste.
What?
Do you wanna finish the brownie?
No, I really, I really don't want it.
Are you serious?
What does it smell like?
I really don't want it because it's changing the taste.
It is definitely changing the taste.
So you could tell, you're gonna tell me
you don't want that brownie anymore?
I really don't want it.
I don't believe this.
This is chocolate.
I have no taste for another piece.
Eat it, that's kind of sad.
This lady loves brownies.
This lady loved brownies and we just ruined it for her.
She like hates them now.
She's treating the brownie like cigarettes.
That's kind of fucked up.
And how do you feel then?
I feel, I'm shaking because I'm excited.
I feel fabulous.
I do not desire another piece of chocolate.
This is wonderful.
Oh world, listen to this.
This is fabulous.
Take a little bite.
What?
It's good.
Delicious cookie.
Eat that entire cookie, couldn't you?
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, not a problem.
What does it do?
What is it?
Three or four of them.
Smell this thing, now you don't like things you like.
All you have to do is just smell it
and you won't want that cookie.
Not really.
Keep chewing.
Keep enjoying that cookie that you love so much.
You can eat three or four of those.
It's all right.
I couldn't even possibly eat this anymore.
Somebody said there's a little piece of dog shit
in the container.
That's fucked up.
Are you serious?
I'm really serious.
You just told me three or four cookies.
Smell this dog shit.
Do you want to eat anymore?
No, actually, I don't want to eat anything.
I just smelled dog shit.
I think I would.
Hey, when was the last time
I know you stepped in dog shit?
When was the last time?
You know, I've been talking to like the joke is like,
oh man, don't step in dog shit.
When was the last time you ever stepped in dog shit?
I don't think it's ever happened.
Like, have you ever stepped in fucking dog shit?
And people talk about that, it happens.
I don't think it ever happens to anybody.
It happened to me a few days ago.
I feel like it's been like 10 years
since I've stepped in a pile of dog shit.
I never am able to stick with the diet.
This I could stick with, definitely.
I like this, though, it's good.
Because this is making it taste differently.
Wow.
It's like an herbal smell.
Definitely took away my desire for the sweet.
Is that amazing?
Amazing.
Yes, amazing.
You could eat this whole thing.
Yeah.
If I gave it to you, you could consume the entire thing.
Fuck that whole thing.
That whole thing?
That whole thing.
All right.
Take a fresh one.
But listen, who is...
Okay, if I order a thing of french fries,
I go to the counter and I order french fries.
Okay, please, thanks for the french fries.
I bought that, I'm going to eat it.
I'm not going to buy french fries,
take a bite of the french fries and smell this thing
and then throw the french fries away.
That's weird, right?
If you already buy the thing, if you bought the brownie,
you're going to have inside of your head a fight here
where it's like, I just bought this brownie,
I want to eat the brownie.
Why did I buy the brownie?
No, I'm going to eat the brownie.
It's not going to be like, oh, bought the brownie, thank you.
Here's like the two dollars and 50 cents,
thank you, three dollars, whatever, for the brownie.
Mm, throw it away.
What?
People are going to eat it.
French fries.
You don't want any more?
No.
Are you sure?
No, I don't want any more.
Well, if I had this in my face with,
I don't think I'd want any french fries
and I know that would kill half of my diet there.
I want this guy to like, enjoy those french fries, don't you?
That's like, I don't know, that's like kind of sad.
I wonder how long it lasts, yeah.
Instant alarm?
Every day you live with the risk
of someone breaking into your home
or a child getting into harmful chemicals
or even falling down a stairway.
Hi, Anthony Sullivan here for the new instant alarm system.
It'll make your home safer for you and your family.
It installs in seconds with no tools and no wires.
As soon as the door is opened, the alarm goes off.
Use the wireless instant alarm on every window in the house.
As soon as it's opened, you'll be alerted.
It can help safeguard young children by alerting you
when they get into places that they don't belong.
Use it on sliding doors.
As soon as the magnetic seal is broken, the alarm goes off.
If you have a soon to call the wireless instant alarm,
it's great.
It lets you know where your children are going
and they add extra security
for people who live alone and the elderly.
It's practical, that's practical.
This is actually a, this has a good use.
That's practical, like an alarm, like a window alarm.
Like this, what, come on.
This is practical uses for this.
There's even a chime feature that's great
for users of doorbell for a home or a business.
Just peel off the back end, stick them on,
and it's an easy way to add security and get peace of mind.
I mean, I wouldn't want that to be my doorbell, but.
As soon as the instant alarm works,
when the magnetic field between each unit is broken,
the alarm goes off.
So even if somebody breaks a window
with the wireless instant alarm,
the 90 decibel alarm will go off.
And for all an intruder knows, the police are on the way.
The wireless instant alarm lets you worry less
and provides more security for your entire family.
How do you remove it?
It really gives me peace of mind
to know the instant alarm.
I don't know, maybe it's like a little hack or something.
Looks like Velcro or a tack.
Call now and you'll get four instant alarms
complete with batteries for just $10.
So that's not all.
I'm sure it has an off option, yeah.
We'll give you a second set of four free.
Just pay separate shipping and handling.
That's right, you'll get a total of eight
deluxe wireless instant alarms
complete with batteries for just $10.
Why is he in a bathroom?
He's like recorded.
Why is he like in a weird echo?
That's right, you'll get a total of eight
deluxe wireless instant alarms
complete with batteries for just $10.
So call the number on the bottom of your screen
right now.
Here's how to order.
He's in like a big house, okay.
He's in a big house.
Perfect patty.
Smart spin.
It's a celebration.
Over eight million people have made smart spin
America's best-selling TV advertised storage system.
And to say thank you, we're giving away
$1,000,000 worth.
It's just storage, it's just storage.
Detailed tips ahead.
The Easy Smoker?
No smoking here, no smoking there.
These days, you can't smoke anywhere until now.
Introducing Easy Smoker electronic cigarette.
Wait.
An all-new easy alternative to smoking cigarettes.
What?
You can smoke virtually anywhere
without the flame, ash, tar, or carbon monoxide
found in traditional cigarettes.
Because there's no tobacco and no smoke.
Why would you want it to look like that?
Here's how it works.
Why would you want it?
People are gonna come up to you.
You're going to get confronted.
This is like a prank.
Wouldn't you want it to not?
You are pretending to smoke a real cigarette
in a restaurant.
You're trying to call attention
to the fact that you are doing this.
It's like, that guy's smoking a cigarette over there.
I'm looking at it.
We gotta go up and talk to that person.
I mean.
Easy Smoker consists of two parts.
Why would you want it to look like that?
The lithium ion battery and the cartridge.
As you inhale, air flow is detected by a sensor.
Oh, this is the technology.
Do you hear the fucking cigarette technology?
You inhale and the cartridge.
As you inhale, air flow is detected by a sensor
which activates a heating element
and vaporizes the solution inside the cartridge.
It produces a smoke-like odorless vapor
that's not really smoke.
And without any of the over 4,000 toxins
found in traditional tobaccos for 4,000.
Why did they key this guy in here?
This guy's keyed into this like office, I guess.
Why can't you just do this in a room?
It's not really smoke.
And without any of the over 4,000 toxins
found in traditional tobacco cigarettes,
the tip even glows for a more realistic smoking experience
and automatically shuts itself off when not in use.
Oh my fucking God.
You can smoke it virtual.
Automatically shuts itself off when not in use.
The bad part is you can smoke it virtually anywhere
in your home, at the office, even at a restaurant or bar.
No more having to stand outside
every time you want to smoke
and no more dangerous smoke.
That's such a bad habit to like, come on.
You know, it's so great.
I can even smoke in the office now
and my hair and clothes don't smell anymore.
I don't have to go outside to smoke
and it saves me money.
Easy Smoker has sold for over $150.
I'm like falling asleep.
It's so...
This motherfucker's on an airplane.
Again, he's not sitting on an airplane.
He is keyed into an airplane picture.
It's going to make a difference in your life
that we'll send it to you absolutely free.
Just pay shipping and processing.
Your free Easy Smoker comes with a membership
in our Easy Smoker club.
Oh no.
So you can get refill cartridges
at a special discounted price.
Easy Smoker is available in regular and menthol.
So if you're going to smoke, smoke easy.
Here's how to get yours.
Oh my God.
That's wild.
That's fucking wild.
How much was it? $150?
It's 150 bucks.
How much is a jewel?
10 second Kathy Mitchell smoothie maker.
Yep.
Stay tuned as Kathy Mitchell
introduces her amazing twist and flip
10 second smoothie maker.
Hi, I'm Kathy Mitchell with my amazing smoothie maker.
Just fill the cup with whatever you like.
Strawberries, bananas, even low fat yogurt.
Then just twist on, flip it and watch.
In seconds, the reverse turbo action
turns your favorite fruits or veggies into a smoothie.
What?
Reverse turbo action?
Flip it and watch.
In seconds, the reverse turbo action.
What is it?
That doesn't do anything.
Like turning it upside down doesn't,
it just turns the blender on.
That doesn't do anything.
Who cares?
What's the, I feel like half of this machine
doesn't have to exist.
Mm, and delicious.
Plus it virtually cleans itself with this cleaning cup
and just water.
Ready for the next smoothie.
The ball?
Look, the blade is clean.
Sitting on the countertop?
Now everyone gets exactly what they want.
Is the product.
Like cookies and cream for my grandkids.
And it takes up such less counter space.
Why do you have this thing?
The unique emulsifying disc blade designs
reverse action technology creates a turbo funnel
that sends your presentation to this blade design.
Holy shit.
That was a mouthful.
That was a true technology mouthful.
What was that again?
Everybody's happy.
The unique emulsifying disc blade designs
reverse action technology.
Holy shit.
Hold on.
I gotta write this down.
The unique.
The what?
What was it?
The unique?
I gotta get this written down.
Unique.
Gotta be like red.
That was a lot.
That was an insane amount of info.
Okay, unique.
Unique emulsifying.
Disc blade design.
Reverse action technology.
That's a lot.
Unique emulsifying disc blade design
reverse action technology.
Jesus.
Make that the stream title.
That sends everything into the vortex.
Creating a perfect smoothie every time.
Every smoothie maker comes with my recipe guide.
Including this recipe for Orange Genius.
A little milk and ice,
one orange and a spoonful of the secret powder
that's probably already in your kitchen.
What's the secret powder?
Just like at the fair.
Stop with the lots of bucks frozen coffee orders.
Now you can make the most delicious
cold coffee combos for pennies.
And with a sip lid.
They got a little lid.
It's ready to go.
Just secret powder.
What is it?
For safety, this blade will absolutely not turn on
until the cup is locked into position.
What?
Safety, they're thinking about safety.
Super strawberry slush.
Veggie feel great with eight.
No, you're not gonna do more than three.
No, no, no, more than four.
No, more than five.
Not only are they scrumptious,
but you're getting 100% of the vitamins and dietary fiber.
Including the pulp.
Not just a glass of juice, a smoothie
that no one can resist, especially me.
That's delicious.
I trust her.
Draw the number on your screen now
to order Kathy Mitchell's smoothie maker in white water.
All right, we'll do a couple more.
Just like one or two more.
I don't know, there's so many.
There's so many.
Grab a bite.
Kitty litty.
The ruggies.
The dog dicer.
Toilet tunes.
Is this TOS?
This is, I'm not gonna be people like pissing, right?
I'll be right back.
Is this TOS?
Ooh, dry skin.
Are you okay in there?
Fine.
That's not what happened.
I was testing to make sure it was friendly for Twitch.
It was.
Okay, fuck this one.
I'm out of here.
How about the Easy Yolk?
The Easy Yolk sounds good.
You know egg whites have only 15 calories,
are high in protein and are virtually fat
and cholesterol free,
but separating the egg yolk from the white
is a real pain until now.
Introducing Easy Yolk,
the world's most easy egg yolk separator.
Easy Yolk separates the yolk in seconds
indirectly from the frying pan.
What do you do with it?
Without leaving behind a big mess.
We all know egg whites are healthier,
but are they worth the hassle?
No, fuck this propaganda.
Fuck this propaganda.
I'm taking a stand right now.
Egg yolks are good for you.
This is where all the vitamins, all the fucking fats.
Oh, but Jeremy, there's cholesterol.
Oh my fucking God.
That's where everything is.
Yolks are where all the good shit is.
Oh no, cholesterol.
Oh no.
Shut up.
Eggs are good.
Eat eggs, they're good.
Just don't eat a fucking hundred of them.
Don't eat a hundred eggs a week.
This whole, this don't eat the egg shit.
Don't eat the yolks, only eat the egg whites.
No, man, that's where all the good stuff is in the yolk.
Pancakes and waffles, omelets and souffls,
French toast and homemade muffins.
Even breakfast burritos can all be made with egg whites.
And if you like to bake.
And look, I understand.
Egg whites are great.
If you want to do like an egg white omelet,
somebody said egg white omelets are good.
Yeah, they are.
If you want to have an egg white omelet,
people that like, oh no,
take the yolk and fucking throw it away.
No, no, why get rid of it?
If you want to specifically have like, oh, you know,
today I feel like I want to feel like a little lighter.
I'm going to do an egg white omelet.
All right, cool.
I'm sure it's delicious.
It is.
The super frog sound effects in here.
You'll love easy yolk.
It's easy to master meringues or heavenly angel food cake.
You'll wonder how you ever live without the easy yolk.
Watch us separate the yolks with easy yolk
while only one yolk is removed the old fashioned way.
That is super frog.
The easy yolk's patent pending design
pulls egg yolks quickly and easily.
With one squeeze, the egg yolk is sucked up
the perfectly sized sleeve and deposited into the bowl.
Okay, listen.
I know that there are a lot of people
that have dietary restrictions.
Maybe you do have really high cholesterol
and you need to take it down.
I get it.
But if you just have a regular diet
and that you're like a healthy individual
and you're not trying to like go on a diet or anything,
the yolk is fine.
This did not get stopped.
One more, one more, and then I gotta go.
Can we end it on dump cakes?
You love delicious homemade desserts,
but recipes can be complicated and take so long to make.
Hi, Kathy Mitchell here with my new Dump Cake Cookbook.
Forget measuring.
Now you can easily make homemade desserts in minutes.
It's a simple as dump and bake.
For delicious desserts every time, guaranteed.
I don't even care.
Watch this.
Start with fruit, dump on your favorite cake mix,
and finish with a can of soda.
Or you can use diet for a guilt-free dessert.
Then just bake it in the oven
for a delicious razz and peach dump cake.
Oh, so scrumptious.
What's wrong with this?
Look, your kids will devour this s'mores chocolate cake
and salad at ease. I want that right now, Kathy.
Here's the cake mix. Kathy.
Just dump on the good stuff.
Chocolate chips, marshmallows. Kathy, are you gonna feed me,
Kathy? Even chocolate cookies.
Bake and voila.
That looks good. Best dessert ever.
Now here's one of my favorites.
Just dump syrup, sugar, cinnamon, and nuts in a pan,
and then just layer in some biscuits.
For fresh, warm, sticky buns.
Just like grandma used to make.
It really is mistake-proof.
You just dump and bake.
I never knew homemade desserts could be this easy.
You don't need to spend hours to make homemade cakes.
Get my dump cake cookbook today.
Wait, did she, did that kid just hit,
the kid just punched mom.
All the carbs, all the calories
make you wince when you pinch an inch.
Now lose the carbs and help twist the calories away
with the skinny gourmet.
The new food prep miracle that twists fresh vegetables
into healthy pasta dishes.
Watch how easy.
Just insert a zucchini and twist, presto.
In seconds, you'll have
I already saw that one.
Some low-carb noodles.
Now add marinara sauce.
One more, this is it, last one.
This is KNN, the Kids News Network.
Good morning, I'm Chuckie Stewart.
Today's top story, is this the end of the sandwich?
As we know it.
Most of us expect a sandwich to be plain, square,
possibly with a crust cut off.
But Susie Brady reports that this is changing.
Thanks, Chuckie.
I'm here outside Swatts Elementary
where a new trend is invading lunchboxes.
They're called Samut Shapers.
Is this a school project?
Let moms and kids cut the usual sandwiches
into some very unusual shapes.
Like this spiral, this fish,
or even this rabbit in a hat.
Brian is so finicky.
Wait a minute.
But when I started using Samut Shapers,
well, you can see how he gobbles it right up.
Brian's mom was the first to try Samut Shapers,
but it wasn't long before every kid at Swatts
was begging for these new lunchtime treats.
Oh look, I got the butterfly, pretty.
I got the donut, awesome.
But not everyone's thrilled with the change.
It's hard on the kids who can't get these Samut Shapers.
If you'll excuse me, I have to get back to my lunch.
A bear, cool.
What do I feel like that's gonna be fucking me in 30 years?
Back to you, Chuckie.
Excuse me, I have to get the Samut Shapers.
It's hard.
But not everyone's thrilled with the change.
It's hard on the kids who can't get these Samut Shapers.
If you'll excuse me, I have to get back to my lunch.
A bear, cool.
Back to you, Chuckie.
Hope that guy's doing good.
Thanks, Susie.
And we'll have more after this commercial break.
Samut Shapers have a cool new way
to turn ordinary sandwiches
into extraordinary lunchtime treats.
Pull a rabbit out of a hat, then eat them both.
Let your butterfly fly free.
I mean, that's kind of cool.
Or just have fun with a PB&J.
You get to eat the donut and the whole.
Hate the crust?
No problem.
With Samut Shapers, mom-
I mean, I would say,
I mean, if you're only gonna eat this one,
like, big part of the sandwich,
that's kind of, it's just a tiny sandwich.
Get easy.
And with our special sandwich boards,
they slide straight-
I think, like, okay, you eat this whole thing
and there's a cool imprint, right?
Into the bag.
No touching.
No mess.
There are nine Samut Shapers to choose from.
When you buy these three for 10.99,
you get three more-
I mean, if you're only gonna eat
the bunny rabbit part, that's-
I mean, at what point is it like,
I'm going to make a sandwich
and throw half of it away,
so I can have the bunny shape.
Anything you'd wanna, like,
slowly introduce to the kids,
like, hey, we're gonna start to eat
out of, like, a sandwich.
And then we're just gonna eat the bunny ears
and not, like, throw, like, half the sandwich away?
It's a bonus.
Just pay separate processing.
I mean, that's a waste, all right?
It's $11.
All right, one more, one more.
What have we got?
Okay, what have we got?
We're gonna let the algorithm take it.
Let the algorithm take it.
Whatever it is.
Perfect pie cutter.
Tired of serving your pie like this?
You bake the perfect pie,
but it crumbles apart when you serve it.
You carefully cut your pie,
but the slices end up uneven.
You cover your pie to keep it fresh,
but the topping comes off.
Now there's a solution.
Introducing the perfect pie cutter.
The same pie cutter used by hundreds of top res.
What is this?
What?
Hey, Germans, since you've been watching infomercials,
I thought I could recommend one
that's pretty entertaining.
When I was about 10 years old,
I got cast as Chuckie Stewart
in an infomercial advertising a product
called Sammich Shapers.
It cuts the crust off your sandwich
and also turns it like an animal or a fun shape.
I got the audition for it through a talent agency.
I later found out the commercial had gone national
and nobody told me.
Are you shitting me, dude?
You were Chuckie Stewart?
I did not see that over here in Mod Chat.
I promise.
I just played that.
I didn't even know that was here.
Really?
A viewer here was that kid.
I don't know, that's fake.
I think that's real.
Turns across the country.
Mods, is this real or is this a bit?
No, it's real.
That's apparently real.
Simply push down on the perfect pie cutter
international star.
Into perfect slices.
No more crumbling slices.
No more uneven cuts.
That's fucking insane.
With the perfect pie cutter,
you get perfect slices every time.
Ban them.
Hold on a minute.
Guys, I want to make sure that we make this
get all the facts here.
The mods are telling me that was posted yesterday
in the Discord.
That was posted yesterday.
I did not see that.
So this is for real.
This person's not jumping on the sandwich shaper
bandwagon here just because it was on camera.
That was in the Discord yesterday.
Wow.
Actually real.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is posted yesterday in the Discord.
You can have the same secret
used in restaurants in your own home.
What the fuck?
Now I can have that look at home.
My friends and family.
And I'm just like,
how do you make everything look so fancy?
That's Chuckie Stewart.
And it's the perfect pie cutter.
I love this shit so much.
The leftover pie running and drying up?
Well, not anymore.
Leave the perfect pie cutter in your pie.
Actually ban him though.
I'm not gonna ban.
I'm not gonna ban the kid.
I know, I'm just saying, I know.
I'm not gonna ban the, he's not a kid anymore.
Chuckie Stewart is like 40 right now.
I don't know why I was just imagining,
like, oh, ban him.
It'd be funny.
I'm like, I'm not gonna ban a 10-year-old.
Chuckie Stewart is like 30,
he's 30 or 40 years old.
Actually, I would probably ban a 10.
Yeah, I would ban a 10-year-old.
You're not fucking allowed to be here.
Covering your pie only to have the topping come off
when you remove the covering?
Well, never again.
Just place the plastic wrap over the perfect pie cutter
and it won't touch your topping and ruin your pie.
Tired of your spatula being the wrong size?
That's so cool though.
The perfect pie cutter comes with a specially designed
spatula that fits perfectly between the blades
so you can serve perfect slices every time.
The perfect pie cutter is durable and dishwasher safe.
Get ready for the holidays or any special.
All right, I'm done.
I've had enough.
I'll see you guys later.
That's gonna conclude the stream.
It was a quick one today.
Yeah, I know.
He actually could be closer to 60.
No, he would absolutely not.
That commercial was like 1998,
like 2000 or something, 2001, 2002.
Yeah, that's it.
When's the next stream?
Let's see.
Today's Tuesday.
We could do...
Maybe we'll...
Maybe this weekend, Saturday, Sunday?
Well, I'm thinking Saturday, Sunday on the weekend.
I think that works.
This was 2013.
So, okay, so that would be...
All right, so, yeah.
So if Chuckie Stewart was,
it'd be like 20, 23, 24?
Early 20s?
That's so funny.
That's such an insane happenstance.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
Thanks for watching.
Those infomercials.
Whoops.
Take care of yourselves.
See you this weekend, Saturday and Sunday.
I actually don't have a plan.
By the way, that's not the last time
you're gonna see infomercials.
I think we have way too much fun with these.
That, I mean, there are literally thousands
and thousands of infomercials.
But there's plenty.
We should probably take a little bit of a break.
Maybe not for a few streams, you won't see it.
Just because I don't wanna, you know,
I want it to be fun, fun and special.
I don't wanna just have it, just do it every day.
Take care, yeah, take care.
All right, let's take a look real quick.
Let's do a raid.
I want to raid.
Stir is live, and Vinny's live.
There's a bunch of people live right now.
I never catch Stir live.
Stir, I mean, his thing.
Dump, opening up the dump cake and pour.
Be good, be nice if you're gonna hang out with Stir's chat.
He's gonna be very furious with me.
Stir's gonna be upset with me that I did this.
So, be nice.
Let's say hi to Stir.
Playing Rogue Legacy 2.
If you don't know who Stir is,
there's a lot of new viewers here, let me just explain.
You didn't remember if you don't catch it
or if you can't, oh, who's that?
Stir was in the replacement stream.
Obviously, he's one of the judges.
Very funny guy, I've known him a long time.
Just went offline.
Wait, because I was talking about it?
No, he didn't.
If he did that, that's really funny.
Okay, I'm gonna cancel that.
Okay, so.
Oh, all right.
So, there's a few other people we could raid.
You know what, let's, you know, I haven't raided it.
You know what, I want to, let's go say hi to Boxbox.
Boxbox is awesome.
What's Boxbox doing?
What are you up to?
Training in Valorant.
Valorant training?
Yeah, Boxbox is awesome.
I got to spend a little time at the streamer roards
with Boxbox.
Really, really, really swell, swell person.
Valorant?
He didn't end because of you,
he was on an eight and a half hour stream, oh, okay.
All right, good night guys, see you later.
Take care of yourselves.
Goodbye, good night.
See you Saturday.