Well, have you guys been just sitting there spelling? I saw T-E. T-E. T-E. T-E. And I realized, oh, it's because half of you were saying T-E, half of you were saying L-A. Right. I see.
Well, too many of you guys were doing T-E because that's all I saw. Yes. How are you? I'm not supposed to be here. I'll be right back.
Two minutes have to go by before I say a word. Be right back. Two minutes? It's been 12. Yeah, I know.
Okay, listen, you guys ever do a thing where you're in the shower and you get you say to yourself,
I'm going to give myself 10 minutes, eight minutes to take a shower. Okay, take like just get in there.
I'm just going to wash my hair. I'm going to wash my body. I'm going to whistle for 30 seconds,
you know, and just sit there in the hot water. You get to the part where you shampoo your hair
and then every time limit you gave yourself never existed. After the shampoo goes in,
it's almost like you can't count anymore. It's like, all right, shampoo is going in. I got like
60 seconds. I can do this in 60. And then everything, it goes blank and you just sit,
it's like 15 minutes goes by. And then you realize that you like glitch out as a human. You're like,
wait, no, I was supposed to get out of here. I was supposed to get the fuck out of here.
Once I get the lather into the hair and I run my head underneath the hot water, it's like a reset
button. I don't know if the hot water gets involved in your brain or something. I don't
understand. But I've run my head under the hot water and all of a sudden it's like, oh yeah,
that's what I like. And now I, now I don't even know what, what was I doing? What was the plan
today? So I, I stayed in there for an extra few minutes. Hot water melts his brain. I don't know.
It's like, I don't know. Maybe it's like a little, I don't understand. Should I bring that up to the
doctor? Yeah. Hey, every time I get like hot water running over my head, I forget, I forget where I
am. That doesn't happen. I'm kidding. You promised us eating on stream. Did you, did you, you must
have not have watched the stream from three days ago, four days ago. Jeremy, you promised us eating
on stream. I did. I did it. I ate the Whopper. I ate the chicken sandwich and I ate the salad,
which is the French fries. That counts as a salad, it's potato, it's vegetables.
Hold on. I don't like where this mic is. Give me a second. Okay. That's better.
Yeah. I didn't like the placement of the mic. It was, it was making me very angry.
All right. So what we're going to do today, we're going to go back to Jedi Academy,
going to finish it. I have one more chapter left and then we have to discuss how the next
three or four weeks are going to play out. Those of you that have been on this channel for the last
year or longer know that 2020 was supposed to have about two or three very major streams in it.
I ran into some medical problems in 2020 and obviously the coronavirus fucked up everything,
right? So a ton of those streams that were supposed to happen in 2020 have been moved
into 2021. So the theory is over these, the baseball stream comes to mind. That's the number
one, big one. The theory is that in the first quarter here, we will do a couple of really big
streams. The theory here. So over the next few weeks, cause we're already into January and it's
like, oh shit, it's already January. It's already almost middle of January. So I need to take some
time to make sure that these big streams are going to be ready to go. We've got, I didn't
forget. People think I forget the 30 webcam stream. That's going to happen soon. The 30
webcam stream is not going to happen in like six months. That's going to happen like probably in
the next like 45 days. So we're working on that. That's like the next one. That's the first one
you'll probably see. Baseball stream is going to be after that. So we're going to really try to get
that to happen, but it requires a little bit of time. So streams are going to be kind of sporadic
here over the next three or four weeks. While a bunch of work is done on these various streams,
your 1080 is going to fry. That's another thing. I'm glad. Hey, thank you. Not a plant for bringing
this up. I have, I'm doing the new computer is happening like over these next three to five
weeks. So I'm getting a new computer. I'm going to upgrade this computer. There's a lot of, I,
I'm stupid and I can't do anything. So I need help. Good luck getting a GPU.
Don't worry. I'll get one. We've been, you've been saying that we've been saying that shit for like
the last four and a half months. I have to get one. So I'm going to be building a new streaming PC.
I'm doing that. This is just kind of, I've got some friends that I want to hang out with.
No, I've got, I've got to go. I've got to go visit italics. It's been like six months since
I've last seen that guy. No, this is a lot going on and streams are going to be a little
sporadic here over the next three or four weeks. So we will go from there. I'll give you a good idea.
He's your friend? Yes, he is. Pour milk into the GPU. All right. We, all right. Thanks for the tip.
I appreciate it. I don't have, it's not here yet. So you're like, you're like three and a half weeks
early with that one. The bird watching stream. That's another one. The plan is for me and my
manager, some of you know, the producer of a lot of these events that have happened,
we're going to just block out a shitload of stuff to do in the first two quarters of 2021.
Some of them are already done and they just need to be streamed. But now is the time for that stuff
to happen. So all this long winded thing is for me to tell you, break Andy's taking another break.
No, I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm not taking another break. I'm kidding.
But you'll probably see maybe like a couple of streams a week for the next three or four weeks.
I'm not taking another, I'm kidding. I thought I looked at the, uh, like the calendar of streams
that I've done and I'm like, Oh, how many streams have I done over the last like month or two?
And it's like, Oh, right. I took like all the holidays off because that was like 10 days off.
And then like, Oh, the time to go break, break Andy again, like another 10, like doing 15, 20 days
off. Oh, I mean, that's like, like, I mean, I, I can't do that. So no, I'm not going to do that.
You'll see a couple of streams a week until we get a solid sort of foundation on everything.
But I am insanely excited for 2021. The baseball stream is ready to go. We just need a date and
we need the venue to be ready. That's it. We've ever, it's ready to go. We were ready to go
back in August, but we had to stop it two weeks before the event was going to happen.
We had to pull the plug on it because there was a huge spike in COVID and we just couldn't,
we just were like, this is not something we can do right now. It was back in that period where
it was just a major, major spike in like every major city in America. So over these next three
to five months, we'll see. We're hoping that we can get it done. How about right now? It's worse
now. Well, we're not doing it now. Oh, you can hear Star Wars. You're not supposed to hear Star
Wars yet. We're not doing it like tomorrow, but to do a, to do a major stream like this in like
April, we need to make sure that it's ready in January, in February. You know, it's got to,
we have to, you can't just like, you can't just like in April, like be like, Hey, it's time to go,
go, let's do the stream. These things take time later today. When's the hacker stream? Well,
just, I've, there's, that was going to happen. It was, I think it was a little back and forth.
I had to do with, with Twitch to make sure that like, I could do that. There was a little back
and forth. We're still kind of, I'm going to figure that out. God damn it. Stop like pulling
a truck into my driveway. There we go. When is the, no, no. When's the bathtub stream?
Illegal streams are the best streams. Illegal streams are also what they're called illegal
because then I get in trouble. And then what do you want me to do? I need to do an illegal.
Stop playing trumpets in my fucking garage. Stop doing that. Stop playing. Just leave me alone.
And the cat boy stream. That's another one. We look, there's going to be a shitload of streams
in 2021. A ton of them had to get pushed from 2020. Like I said, so it's just like we got,
we got double time to do. That's what I got to say. Long story short, after today's stream,
I'll see you in like four days. Four day break Andy. All right, let's go. That was such a long
winded way for me to say, I'll see you guys on, that was an insanely long winded way for me to say,
I'll see you on Thursday or Friday. And oh my God, that's another one. We have,
there's a huge Minecraft server that's being worked on and it's awesome. It's fucking awesome.
You have no idea how awesome this is. You have no idea how, how fun this is going to be.
Not FTK. It's just a Minecraft server. It's just Germacraft. You guys are going to love it. I've
seen so much of it already. No mazes. I promise. There's a look. We, we, we, I don't hurt my hand.
We got a lot going on in 2021. Let's fucking go. Anyways, you guys, you can play the trumpets
again if you want. We're going to continue our Sith training. We, oh wait, wait, let's give some
context here. Uh, the context is, uh, we're, we're like about to fight a, we're about to fight a
monster. It's way too loud. Those of you that missed the last stream from two days ago,
we were in the middle of fighting the, uh, the, the rancid monster. I haven't even used this new,
I made this new lightsaber. All right. Well, hold on. I need his help. What was the goal of this?
Holy shit. That jump. Don't eat him. Don't eat him. Don't eat him. Don't eat him. Please don't eat
him. Like what? Holy shit. What? Wait, was he giving me like a chance? It's so loud. Hold on.
All right. Is it loud for you? It's really loud for me. I mean an intruder.
I forgot I had that move. Right. I forgot. I forgot I was unbeatable.
Then what do I have to do? Just lure him away. Oh shit. Oh, you also got force lightning, don't
you? Oh, I see. Somebody else also has a fucking lightning tool in Premiere Pro. Oh, fuck you.
It's on easy. No, it's not. Wait, maybe it is. No, it isn't. Oh, hold on. He's spitting acid at us.
Wait, why is he just puking? What do I do? What should I do? I'm gonna go this way.
Press this button. Press this button. What the fuck? Wait, hey. There's a button I can press
here, but I can't activate it. Why? Oh, here we go. Oh, wait. It's a crane. It's picking up. Is
it gonna drop it on his head? All right. I'm gonna drop this on his head. We're gonna anvil this guy
like Looney Tunes. All right. Now it's I guess that gives me an opportunity. Should I go that way?
What the fuck are you doing here? All right. So now if I walk him over here,
do these things matter? What do these things do? They are. I'm gonna. All right. You're gonna
turn into a fucking pinball. There goes his fucking head. There goes his head. There goes. Oh,
my God. I cut his whole. Wait, why is this? Holy shit. I'm fucking out of here. All right.
So just remember what works now. Cool. What is it? This one. Did I? Oh, I just instantly
killed that guy. There's a lot of reverse Jedi here. If you wait, I have a question for you guys.
Star Wars lore heads. If you have a red lightsaber, does that automatically mean you are a Sith?
Can you have red lightsabers just because you like the color red? Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. But what if
you just like put like red Sith? What if you just have like Sith food coloring or something?
Does that could you do that? If you had an orange lightsaber and you like just kind of died the
like just added a red light into it or something. He's still bad. What if you just like the color
red? I did not kill him in the air. Come on. That's bullshit that you are fucked up. Okay.
What? So you're fucked up if you like the color red. What happened to me? I like the color red.
Therefore, I'm evil. No, but hold on. We've got an all capitals lore master here. This is all
capitals. They were very upset about this. No, but depending on which lore context it is,
there is a certain process required to make your lightsaber crystal red,
which only a Sith would do. So you probably wouldn't have a red lightsaber in that context.
Otherwise, if it's just a normal crystal, then yeah, it's basically team colors. But red is
only for the Sith team where the Jedi get like six. Okay. So, okay. What if I had the the kyber
crystal that was in front that was orange and then I had like a red led that I got from Home
Depot on top like in front of it to make it like a red tint. Does this does that make me an evil
person? Am I a bad guy? Why? What's with Jedi's in the color red? Then get ready to be sliced up by
a Jedi for having a Sith lightsaber. I can't stop it. All right. Where do I go from here? Over here.
That was I just gonna do it was like hey, that's not so you fall damage. Yeah, I'm gonna say.
All right, let's go this way. How about we just power this guy? Yep, get powered. All right.
No. All right, slice them. No more dismemberment, by the way. It happened for like one second.
We got to cut one guy's head off. All right, watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
I just goomba stomped it. All right, go, go, go, go. Here he comes. Oh my god. Here comes the rancor.
Hey, look. There's a guy coming behind. Look at the guy with the two sabers. It's like oh my god.
This is my chance. This is my chance. Can I get him? Can I slice his leg off? He's laughing at us.
Do something. Attack. Nice keyboard turn, rancor. Now we know who paid for their account.
Oh, he's dead. Okay. All right, don't get killed. I think I have like realistic lightsabers on too,
right? Is that why I'm getting killed in one hit? I can't stop it. Basically, yeah, okay.
But why even fight anything if the rancor is just going to kill everybody?
We could just have like, look, their AI range is only that far and then they just get...
Thank you. Yeah, nice try. Look, their AI range only goes so far and then eventually the rancor
is just going to kill them. So why am I even wasting my time? I don't. He can't fit through
this door. Can he? He just sneaks his head under here. All right, no, dismemberment's still on.
I think he just ate somebody. What? I'm trying to lead him in here. What am I doing? Oh, you idiot.
All right, get in here. I don't know why. I figured if I led them in there he would just
kill them instantly, but he killed me instantly. What an idiot. I don't even fight them. Just go.
Let's press left and right click at the same time. Is that this guy's internal monologue?
What? Why did we just get a narrator? All right. Oh, how did he get in here? What? Um, I would love
it if I could click this button. Oh my god, he doesn't stop during the cutscene. Come on.
It's on easy. It's not on easy. You can't change difficulty unless you reload a whole new video
game. What should I do? Checkpoint. Oh, all right. Wait, does he just have to press a button here?
Am I safe in here? I don't think he can do anything. No, there's a huge window right here
he can come through, but can he come through it? Yes, apparently. I guess he can. Sure. Touch it.
Touch it. Now what does that do? Maybe I can trap it between those containers and the door.
Uh, okay. I don't trap it between the containers and the door. Like, he wants me to trap him right
there? Just squish his head on it? But how do I? He needs to be standing there. All right, hold on.
Okay, come on over to this side. Over here. Get over here. Stop. He's stuck in the door.
Well, I think that guy's dead. He's stuck in the wall. I think if I turn him around, I think this.
All right, come on. Oh, you idiot. You eat me. I'm gonna be so fucking mad. All right, come on.
Get over here. It's so many slashes on him. There we go. All right, I cut his arm. Here we go. Now,
ready? Here we go. Give me the indicator. Give me the indicator. Give me the fucking. I just
stabbed myself with my own blade. Oh my god. Isn't this the thing that comes down right here?
Super speed. Another console right here. Oh, he's in slow motion. All right. Um,
how's this a secret area? What? All right, then lead him back here and then press it when he
gets right there. All right, press it. What the fuck? Wrong computer. What do you mean?
There's a button on here inside the room. Yeah, I dig to get. I can't get the indicator never
shows up. All right. Where you here? Ramp. What the fuck is this place? Oh my god. He just instantly
killed me. Yeah, it's going to go. Maybe I can look and stop his head between those containers
and the door. Yeah, maybe I can fucking trap him. Wouldn't this be horrible to fight in a hallway
like this? You had a double sided lightsaber. Can you only fight in an open area? He's fucking
head off. Come on. Oh my god. Oh my god. This guy's unbeatable. I got also used to it doesn't
matter. Okay, he's gone. Save it. Why would I just spin it around in a circle in front of you?
Like a baton. Just spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin, spin and walk forward. Okay, here we go.
I got him. I get him. I feel like I cut my own head off. That's when you start when you're really
trying to struggle to learn to do yo-yo tricks. And you sort of lose control when you do like
around the world and you kind of you cringe your face up and you go and you mouth purses and you
just wait for the yo-yo to hit you in the head. Yeah, that's what happened. All right, let's get
him. Oh no. What? He's waiting for his cue? Why didn't he jump over it? He's like, oh shit,
I'm not in place. I gotta get into my theater manager's gonna be so mad at me. I wasn't where
I was supposed to be. He missed it. He missed his cue. It's okay. It was still a great
scene. I've been tracing Tavian's movements over the past few months. It looks like she acquired
the scepter from a collector on Kama, then she killed him. All right. Okay, cult sighting,
force theft, dismantle, or weapon destruction. Which one? What do you think? You have force powers
other than lightning, but do they matter? Do the cult? We've received word from the chandrillians
that some cultists have broken into an ancient tomb that is supposedly the burial site of a Jedi
knight. Hurry there and stop them from siphoning that force power. He's lowering the volume a
little. Sorry, I just cut off Luke. And what are you guys talking about? I have more powers? Look,
I'm already decked out. Gonna collect his force power. Yeah, wait, what is this one? Jedi mind
trick. Get rage, please. Force rage. Jedi is protected against 50% of all damage, has stronger
attacks, and cannot die. Oh, why didn't I get this first? However, the Jedi loses health rapidly,
must wait for 10 seconds after the rage before it could be used again. The Jedi must have at least
25 health to use this. Okay, I like the rocket launcher and I like the sniper rifle. I don't
even know if those are the two things I picked. It's been two days, I forget. Okay, let me key
bind these. Okay, heal, rip, lightning, drain, rage. Okay, rage is going to be R, rage. Drain
is going to be, um, I don't know, zero? No, what should it be? G? T? Okay, T. I'm never going to
use it. So that's the rage power. All right, cool. How do I turn it off? I turn it off.
I have one HP? What the fuck? All right, how do I get out of here? I don't even- what was that? Who
was that guy? Who was that guy? All right, well, I don't- sorry.
Off his head goes. Off his head goes. That's not what it is. It's off with his head.
He's not quite gone. There he goes. It's me, the Jedi. I'm here to save the day.
Hold on just a second. Oh, that's- I thought you guys were just two regular, like, henchmen.
Oh, you are. Okay, that guy's dead. Oh shit, you blocked. Oh, see you later. They go all of his
body parts too. You have to just watch your body fall. You have to watch your legs fall from your
torso. Man, that's a horrible way to go. Darth Maul. Well, I mean, Darth Maul has this, but it's
red. I'm not allowed to have red, apparently. Even if I like the color red, I can't just add a
little bit of red LED. That makes me a bad person. These are ball breaking. Holy shit. I want to
ricochet this back at him. Do you think he'd keep shooting? I don't know if I would. You know what?
I would probably pick up a rock. It would be probably harder for me to hit a rock back at him.
He had a family. Yeah, he also had an opportunity to stop shooting. I wouldn't have killed this guy.
If he just put his gun down, I was like, all right. I just thought his head came off.
If he put his gun down, I was like, all right, I'm going to leave. I'd be like, all right,
go ahead and leave. Go ahead, get up. Point blank. This has got to feel real bad right now.
Come on. Point blank. No, stop bouncing that high. I'm sorry. I can't? Are you sure?
I thought I could go down. Is this going to hurt? Well, he had just missed it by a few feet.
Too bad. It was a good attempt though. I just heard another one. What was that one for? What
did that one do? I don't know. I don't know. I guess we'll never know. All right, here we go.
Save it. I haven't saved it once. Saber color one. Wait, Jeremy, you can change your saber color
with the console commands. You moron, you absolute buffoon. You missed the reference.
It was a reference to how Darth Maul died and you missed it. Embarrassing reference. I just saw the
word Darth Maul because I have to. All right, wait. Saber color in console to change the color.
Really? That doesn't work. I guarantee you that's a lie. This is a lie. It has to be, right? Yeah,
it's a lie. What is that? Okay. You guys, come on. I hate when they do that. It's not fair.
All right, let's do left click, right click. Wait, I have a better idea. Just come over here.
No, it's not. You don't do a cartwheel to avoid my attacks up here, man. That's a bad idea.
That was me pretending to know what I was doing. What was that? Hold on. Oh, it's the thing that
he does in the movie. It's the guaranteed way to die in real life if you ever did this with a weapon.
The little flourish. Now, your head is off. Imagine that back in the medieval times when
people actually using weapons like this. They allowed each other to dance around
for five seconds. No. No, it was brutal and horrible. If there was an opportunity,
that sword's going right through your stomach. It would be brutal. Holy shit. Hold on. Wait a
second. Let me do this first. I'm trying to kill him with it. All right. Finally, we got a raid.
We did. Oh shit, we did. This is from Daleks. Thanks to the raid, Daleks. Hope we had a good
stream. Whatever it was. Hey, you may have been playing Jedi Force Academy. If you were playing
Jedi Force Academy, then good for you. Welcome, guys. Is that a kyber crystal over there? Is
this like a kyber crystal dungeon? Can I make that jump? Of course I can. I'm a Jedi. No raid song.
There it is. It's a raid song. This place is confusing. Step them from dissecting the tomb.
Okay. Where should I go? The flourish. He just gets lost. So he started dancing around.
Wait, hold on. Dance up. I literally... No, I did the Super Mario thing where you jump
and you're terrified and you're panicked about missing a jump. You land the jump, but then go
and jump again when you're right on the edge of the first jump that you actually made.
So I'm sorry. This is the wrong way. There we go. That's what I wanted to do. I'm going back.
You killed... Where you killed those guys? Isn't it... Yeah, it was back here, right?
Yeah. I'm not on like a two or three second delay, am I again? What do I go from here? Check. Check.
All right. Ready? I'm going to clap and you tell me when you hear the clap. Wow, that's actually
kind of long. Why is that long? It should be like three seconds. Why is it like seven or eight?
Well, I'm going to do it again. I don't think you guys are ready for it. Why is that long today?
All right. Well, I got to go up there. Up there. There's something I can do up there. There's like
an orange thing up there. You're ignoring us. Oh, what are you talking about? I'm not ignoring
you guys. What are you talking about? What are you guys talking about? Here we go. Okay. Shit. Check
the doors in the chamber. Is this going to fall damage kill me? Holy shit, it almost did if I
didn't heal. I cannot read entire coffee pasta. The chat's going too fast, dude. How am I supposed
to do that? Oh, I see it. What? What happened? There's no enemies in this room. There's no bombs
or traps are in this room. That doesn't make any sense at all. What actually happened though?
The screen started shaking. Was the rancor back? Okay. Now let's force push. Electric lightning
attack. Swing. Pull. Oh, I opened it. All right. Cool. Does my screen look all weird? Yellow saber
is underpowered. They don't have, it's, it's who, it's who's wielding it, not who's fucking, what
power level it is. It's just a bright beam of hot light. That's all that is. Oh my god, dude.
Well, apparently I'm not telling yourself that. Yeah, it doesn't matter. Look, I can go to single
too. I'm going to try that. I'd rather, I'm going to, I'm going single for now. Let's see.
Get high rage mode coming in. He choked me to death. Get over here. Yes. Let the rage
flow through you young master padawan. Let the rage fuel you. Holy shit. Where did you come from?
Time to add a second blade. Okay. No more fucking around. Get over here. It's in slow motion.
Why was it in fast? Why was that in fast motion? All right. Now it's my turn. Fuck off. Get out
of here. Somebody just gave a shitload of money. That's 69 community subs from zap. That's 69
community subs. The funny, the funny number. That's a huge amount of substitute. Thank you.
That's insane. Insane. Oh, come on. You got to be fucking kidding me. I just want to kick a guy off
the edge. Okay. Well that worked. Wait a minute. Hmm. That's how you get that shit done. What about
you? Can I take you out with a blaster rifle? No, no, no, no, no. Did he just launch those back at
me? Holy shit. How are you doing that? Where'd he go? All right. Okay. Oh my God. I just fucking
annihilated this guy. Oh, I didn't have full health. Right. Nice flourish. What am I supposed to do? I
don't know. Fucking kill him. Watch out. Watch this guy strong. Back it up. Let go of me. Let go.
Got him. Okay. I did it. Use force push. It's so weak. It doesn't work on people. I can't. Can I
force choke from all the way back here? How do I get over there? Okay. I'm gonna. I can just jump.
Can't I? I pressed it. I got it. Let's kill this guy first. When they're two. What the fuck are you
doing? I know what that's like though. I know what that's like dude. It's fucking hard to keep you
footing. You could have just stepped down. Okay. Let's go. There was. I've been there before. Plenty
of times. Okay. So from here, we're going to go this way. Dave, Jeremiah. I got it. Both of us
clearly have no idea what the fuck we're doing. Like it's very clear. Hey, he died twice. Okay.
We're going to go over. Easy. Where do I go from here? I go up this way down. I mean, I feel like
I have to go down there, but I have to go that way. Okay. Hold on. F8 for the fart and burp mechanic.
It's real. Oh, cool. Let me press it. Can you imagine if they actually added that?
This place is amazing. It seems like it goes on forever.
Don't be so stupid. F8. F8. F8. That's the fucking stupidest thing ever.
Why would they add that? That's like, it doesn't make any sense. The Jedi's even like.
How am I going to get down there without breaking my neck?
How am I going to get down there without breaking my neck? Get to full health and jump and hope it
doesn't kill you. Don't land on your neck, Omega Lul. Okay. Yeah. We can do rage. Oh,
oh my God. I have no health. Oh, no, don't do it. I'm okay. Got it. Okay. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy.
Easy. Easy. I had no force power left. That was bad. Let's just snipe this guy. What did he hit
his head? What? How did he do that? That was weird. Did I do this wrong? Oh shit. This is bad. No,
hold on. I think I might be in trouble. I jumped all the way down here and I don't think I was
supposed to do that. Can I make it up on the bridge? I see. Not soft locked. Two at the same time.
A Jedi's worst nightmare. Oh, just barely have your footing. That was a smart move but it didn't
work out for you. New objective. Why is my game slowing down? Are they letting me in? Okay.
Fuck you guys. I'm just going in the chamber. Get out of my fucking way.
There's one guy sitting in the middle. I feel like he's strongest. He is. He's got the double.
Okay. What's in the... Should I go in here? Oh, wait. They're desecrating. All right. Stop
desecrating. This is the same guy. Oh, my God. All right. All of you get in here. I was going to do
that to you. Stop. I want to do something to you guys. Stop. I just cut that guy's lightsaber in
half. Wait. I'm deflecting their lightsabers back at them? Jump. Oh, shit. They're all working
together. That guy got impatient. Let's see. I want to test their patience. These are the
Sith Ritz brothers. Holy shit. He made it. No, he didn't. He was just showing me he could.
Okay. But wait. If they deflect it, won't it? They just instantly fucking deflect.
Instantly. It doesn't matter. Look. I shot it in the fucking air. It doesn't even matter. Watch
this. Give me... Okay. Yeah. Sure. Yeah. Oh, you weren't even there. You weren't even there.
You weren't even in the right spot. Unbelievable. All right. I'm done. I'm done. This is where you
die. You're all going to die. Let go. That's so unfair. Let fucking go of me. Force push. Force
push doesn't work on people. It's not strong enough. All right. I'm going to fight you guys on my terms.
Let's go. Yes, it does. Watch. Ready? Force push. Wow. That was very useful. That's not even a cool
power. That's not lightning. That's not choke. That's not resurrect the dead. Oh, no. You can't
speak of that power, Jeremy. All right. I'm going to do rage. They can't kill me. All right. I'm
done with these three. I'm done with these guys. I really am. Fucking kill them. All right. I can't
fight three. Watch out. Watch out. Watch. Block, block, block. Okay. Got one. Back it up. Back
it up. Back it up. Heal. Does that guy have no head? Okay. Hold on. Got it. That was a nice
little maneuver. Side stepped him. Just one more. One more. Now, he's going to get aggressive. Good.
I can do that too. Let's go, motherfucker. Let's do it. I love that Darth Maul move. Okay, I did it.
Defeat the Jedi and find a way to protect the Jedi. What? Defeat the Jedi and find a way to
protect the jedi's coffin what do you mean jedi he's a jedi who i see force pull what is this big
button for okay so pull it the big button push the button i can't push it do you pull buttons
no but apparently you can't push buttons either in this universe push i already did what am i
supposed to go in the car get open what am i supposed to do push the other button i thought
i did that already i tried to press i did force push this whole building is collapsing all right
it's just it's just a show it doesn't actually do anything it's gonna blow it's gonna blow
i think i did it we have to stop taveon give a quick little shake on that heel nk thomas yeah
whatever all right how about this what's which one's better it was disgusting it was just liquid
shaking in a container that's disgusting do you when you like take a bath are you disgusted by
the sound the water makes when you move around if you take your hand and go into the water do
you go oh oh oh my god what this is liquid now we're going to dismantle device a resident jedi
scholar kyon recently learned of the planet yelara from our jedi holocron the planet was once home
to a peaceful yet primitive species that was not ready to be integrated into galactic society
for this reason the jedi master broden kelverdox harnessed the power of the planet to create a
cloaking device hiding the entire planet from discovery but to the disarray of the entire planet
because everything disappeared buildings roads ground people created a major major problem running
into people on the sidewalk accidentally but now someone else has discovered yelora go to yelora
and find out if anyone has been there if the cloaking device is in danger of being stolen
it'd be better to destroy it rather than have it fall into the wrong hands sidewalk is still there
whatever device is too powerful all right destroy the planet you got it i got you luke all right
force rage uh is 75 percent force drain is no let's do this um i like this one who's a sniper
rifle no that thing sucks why do i even want it i like that i like these two let's go force push
then force choke it do be simple all right i'll try it all right i don't like the orange anymore
looks like no one's home guess i should get up to the top and disable that cloaking device
so i have a question for you star wars lore masters uh if at any point in my 40 plus year tenure as a
jedi if i get sick of the color orange can i just change the color can i be like hey um i've been
using orange for 15 years i kind of want green is that okay stop asking about the sabers
why i can't ask oh we can't ask a question about lightsaber lore and stuff what i'm
is he shooting at me okay where you gonna go where you gonna go i'm blocking the door
where you gonna go come on where you gonna go i'm like a big brother the little brother's like
trying to get to dinner you can't go you're not trying to get upstairs you little squirt
i'm trying to get sick mom lucky enough there by the way i'm gonna eat your oreos no you're not
you say i'm gonna eat all your oreos dude all right fine you can get through
fine good mom we're coming down i'm gonna eat i'm gonna eat your oreos
you're gonna eat my oreos i'm gonna eat all your oreos okay that part of the joke is over
we're now in the game again
you know it didn't imperials oh wait these are the imperials sorry
hold on a second a few of the customers got lost i have to pick them up with the pinch tool
and put them back on the path you guys need to ride my new roller coaster get over here
what are you doing i just saved you all right all right all right i'm gonna let you go
i'm gonna let you go you are free to go or i am gonna watch you leave because i feel like
there's a chance i knew it okay i didn't push him i didn't push him i didn't push him you know
what fuck this whole room that was a big voice crack worst voice crack of the year nomination
number one that's probably a new category that's a new category for next year i didn't even do
anything i just knew he was gonna walk i didn't force push him i just walked i got out of here
stormtrooper stormtrooper scum just like burning this guy
holy shit why is this guy not still alive why is he still alive this is horrible he needs to be
dead now oh my god i got his head up wait where did that guy come from press this button and press
this button all right let's go let's go let's go go go go how do i go through here sing another
raid song oh what's up tyler thanks for the raid thanks for the raid tyler
didn't i say i was never gonna do that again i promised i was never going to do that sound
again i said there'd never be a raid song again and i did it twice today but thanks for the raid
welcome guys we're playing jedi force jedi training oh it's pretty fun it's something like that
did i go up holy shit that's gonna kill me what am i missing here
and then mods on there are no mods on right now i've never played the game i'm just doing
through the vanilla storyline i feel like i'm missing something am i missing something you
already did the thing oh all right let's go up there are no mods there are all right so then i
jump through there because that's the fan i stopped let me save it i i did that really sloppily but i
feel like i did that correctly somehow okay more people just wait i have people to throw into the
the disintegration ray no i don't the jedis i can't he cut my head off but there was a head there
that was weird whoops got him double head the galactic war has begun who will win in this
galactic world it's like a youtuber thing i am a youtuber what am i talking about are they
working together right there right now youtuber andy don't shoot at me stop get out of here all
right i gave you a chance and now you're not getting any other chances don't miss this okay
we're sick recharge my orange and take a look at this over here cool i think this is just to look
into the stream voice no just because i bring my tone down to here to kind of like a normal
speaking range does not mean the stream is going to end in five minutes like this is my i'm bringing
it down to my normal kind of tone this is my real voice alert got him i disintegrated him no it
doesn't it doesn't look this is my just mine this is my normal speaking range right if i'm just like
talking on the phone with somebody if somebody called me right now i didn't see the phone what's
up what's going on yeah i just uh just i just ended stream i'm cool what's going on with you
yeah yeah it's not end of the stream voice normal voice andy we go up again
you can tell they're friends now you just watched them die what oh shit what's happening what's
firing at me who's firing oh you what this does not look sturdy at all this is a little
wooden plank bridge no that won't fall that's not gonna fall here in a minute force pull or stab
wait save it okay i'm ready hold on let me heal first let me get to 100 it will both be at 100
and then it's okay it's okay i win i win the duel yeah you're the guild mates to come on in
tried to make it look like that was intentional and just one guy left that doesn't have a lightsaber
fucking wow streamer no i'm a wow x wow player not a current wow streamer
i said jedi jedi i was gonna say that you really just stepped over on my toes there
sorry oh i see you got some force rage you are very good at the game i thought jedi were powerful
hey hey did i squish somebody i think i crushed somebody like a pancake what's happening
save it save it right here quick what's happening oh come on whatever you guys are annoying oh my
fucking god yet i don't want to wait for this one two whoo okay what's that do oh i gotta plant
some bombs a true gamer spams force lightning you're right you're actually right what where i
pulled i pulled that guy through the wall wait that guy wasn't even here okay somebody's dying
so oh okay i think i did it arth vader's in the game he lied about x-men origins wolverine
any new days they've decided to go i did yeah i was supposed to play that a long time ago
all right we got uh three more missions left force theft investigation or weapon destruction
which one i'm gonna say force theft since rosh never completed his mission at biz we still need
to determine if tavian managed to siphon force energy from the remains of the planet the emperor
spent a lot of time there so it would i'm trying not to burp so it would be a huge source of power
that has been taken we'll have an idea of just how powerful tavian is
so take this all right force rage level three is jedis protected against 90 of all damage
is 50 faster and has stronger attacks and cannot die yeah i wasn't making that i was making a dumb
reference leave me alone red saber this time i don't sense the dark side here kyle me neat
that's not good tavy i must have been here already an imperial dreadnought i'm gonna get us out of
here where oh that's us no it's not it's them got a tractor beam on us i can't break free
okay how did you not see him pulling up i served on one of these ships back in my imperial days
you disable the tractor beam and i'll trigger the ship's self-destruct ready we were very ill
prepared for this how did we we just kind of got in here i can i can help we do it together it'll
go faster sorry let's concentrate it in the same spot man well i guess i gotta disable a tractor
beam or something you get to do the fun thing i could do the boring thing but the amount of
times you see somebody's head come off yeah run run run away from this guy run away from me
run away there's an absolutely unhinged psycho god if they knew i was doing this at the academy
this would be all of my report card i'd have to get a signature from my parents if they knew
i was doing this all right i got a security key key card why are they just crumbling are these
even people holy shit these guys are popping they're just popping around holy shit i didn't
save it no god damn it where am i what what what just happened what the fuck are you doing
what happened why did that happen what the fuck just happened is this the right one i need to
load checkpoint right i loaded the quick save oh man i just got a literal call like a actual
game actually hard crushed okay yeah the where the save state really fucks everything up when
you haven't done it in a while and you're just using regular saves and you press save state
just load state and you are four hours ago that's happened a million times before all right load
checkpoint here we go i don't sense the dark side here kyle yeah i was trying to die on his
lightsaber let's go i was i could interact with that but i just saw i saw red sorry everyone oh
that's unforgivable people are gonna be so mad at me for that one i was gonna i was trying to interact
but i didn't oh people are gonna be really upset that's everyone's like favorite character people
love that thing people love that little guy oh no oh my god i'm so sorry i really am so sorry
people are gonna be so upset about that pop it twist it it really is the same one
once you come in i'm surrounded are you sure are you sure it's not you two stuck in a room
got the security key i don't care they're in a shooting gallery yeah they kind of work
are you sure you're not the bad guy i mean i probably am you're asking me for id now is
not the time to ask me for id what the fuck are why is there a space marine here why the
space marines behind me wait what i'm not fucking with these guys oh shit okay go go go run run run
they involved me in here what did that do like i disabled the tractor beam oh fuck
incoming tie fighters i'll be right there anakin oh wait they they cut me off these guys they cut
they actually cut me off be serious i know what to do i really wait i get turned around
oh my god damn it where's the safe all right let me heal do all the way the tractor beam you're
right tractor beam disabled i need more time i can't man i can't oh what the fuck are you guys
doing over here that didn't kill him that didn't kill him that didn't kill him help me toaster i
need 25 health to do here we go rage damn it you fucking stupid thing all right just stop here
activate rage die oh my god i'm just gonna sit here and get to full health and then full
no god damn it this sucks combine rage with four speed hold on run run run run away run run run
get away all right they did i win good that was hard that's fucking hard tractor beam disabled
i just need a little more time the wrong way we've got save save i got it it's the wrong way
wait no i oh shit huge guys again oh these guys are these guys are huge save i just did all right
i'm ready i'm gonna do force run or slash force jump or spin force dance in that order one two
three go worked fucking attack him what's going on um okay what you have the you have an air gun
what do you have for a weapon what does this guy have for a weapon get the fuck out of here all
right i said i could do a better power than that one that's better i feel better about that one
security guards this is on story only mode no this is on normal i'm just very powerful
i've leveled up this okay uh right it's ridiculous okay hold on use the rockets
hold on a minute hold on a minute what's this room excuse me let's clear this out real quick
oh wait that's a that's not a person all right well you kind of were in there you good are you
good all right i want you to recite the rebel alliance uh motto we will always fight for you
you didn't get it stop freaking me this guy's right thank you oh please hurry hurry hurry hurry
hurry hurry i don't have a time come on what am i doing put this lightsaber off
he's doing the right thing though i'll give him yeah i informed the commander oh no he did it he
actually did it i can't believe it not this time i'm sorry that's not gonna happen what's going on
was it all sounds literally died to a stormtrooper yeah d cards nope right everyone yells me when i
don't get this and it's gone now easy that was right in the head nice if they put a stormtrooper
in the rumble now i guess you're right specifically that store not that stormtrooper that
stormtrooper whatever all right i'm not going to kill the trash compactor i'm going to pet the
trash compactor i think that's what you can do it's getting too close though i have to do this
okay pet trash compactor pet trash compactor right what am i doing i just got scared
he just went i'm not going to do it why would i do it there's no reason for that trash compactor
to get destroyed here we go die die die die die die die die activate look i'm no i'm not hans solo
okay this is not what i'm doing i do here jedi doesn't mean i can use a giant military anti-air
gun where did the jedi go check the main weapons on the side of the ship good shit is it raven claw
oh that's my house oh come on give me a break give me back at the raven claw
hufflepuff streamer so there's gonna be a problem with that where's this go we already went over
this if you say you're a slytherin you're really a hufflepuff if you say you're a hufflepuff you're
actually a slytherin griffin doors are raven claws and raven claws don't exist there's like
two in the story i i am a raven claw i'm house raven claw but who's a raven claw in harry potter
didn't spend any time on that house we needed some more raven claws in that story
griffin door griffin door griffin door griffin door slithering slithering slithering slithering
slithering look at the snake slithering where are the claws i go down here i i'm not gonna
give you the satisfaction of seeing that because i knew it was gonna fall house white claw
oh can you imagine the shit face dude sitting there at the halloween party right and he's drinking
white claw and he's got like the harry potter costume on hey house white claw yeah all right
like dave we heard it already hey did you know that i'm in house white claw yes we did and
this glasses are broken he's got like there's no lenses in him they're like tilted hey do you know
have you seen my wand idea that was expensive i got that thing made at disney world it was like
200 bucks i love that thing house white claw hey we don't know what your fucking wand is why would
you bring an expensive wand to a halloween party you should have just got the one from the bag
that's made out of plastic there's the same thing on game of thrones night
yeah he brings the wine this dude doesn't even like wine he just you know what i gotta let me
tell you something let me go off i'm gonna go off game of thrones made a bunch of pretend wine
drinkers can i tell you how annoying that is as somebody that's a very of wine enthusiast
oh yeah i drink wine i drink and i know things oh i love red wine now no you don't you don't you
like to drink red wine and like sit there and pretend like you're in the fucking game of thrones
universe oh hey what kind of wine is that you say i don't know it's red what kind of red i don't
know um it's kind of like maroon looking what kind of red wine is it i don't know how dare you drink
that in front of me just gatekeeping wine wine snob i'm just kidding obviously i drink wine out
of a box you guys think i'm really serious realizing to assist the disciples for one more mission
no but really like people people started drinking wine oh i did and nobody by the way let's go let's
go over this nobody started drinking white wine after game of thrones did they nope the sales
of white wine didn't go anywhere it was red they didn't drink white wine in game of thrones it was
just the big goblet with the red swirling around and oh yes let's talk about medieval politics
what game of thrones i mean like the last season that show was terrible
i didn't drink enough wine and talk that's the best part about that whole show i didn't give a
shit about the battles everyone's like oh man i can't wait the next season when they're gonna
do like another huge fucking like helms deep battle i don't care i want like just varus and
terrian to drink wine and talk that's what i wanted i wanted i wanted the uh the queen of
thorns to just be in a conversation with like little finger wow they just had big red wines
comically sized like joke sized and that's the whole show then we had to get the big
big like battlefront two battles anyways i'm a ravenclaw i'm proud of it information to serve
us about a large stockpile of old weapons hidden in the waste of old mantle destroy the stockpile
so they don't fall into the wrong hands records from the time of the rebellion indicate there
should be seven caches hidden around this is gonna be horrible i can't wait to not i don't want to
do this we're all hufflepuff okay you understand like we're all of us are hufflepuff what should i
do destroy all right what should i do i have everything maxed out almost force push
oh mine trick it's too late it's too late for mine trick we gotta go drain don't be evil
right there no well it must be good to be evil sometimes i didn't even say the first part
without evil there could be no good so it must be good to be evil sometimes there all right i am
so mad that i'm getting this many question marks that you did not see the south park movie
that's from south park the movie that's satan i really come on
oh my heart is hurting oh look i can't do that my heart attack is off both of that
holy shit dude all i got a gun battle with boba fett oh shit i didn't win
oh that's so funny
i feel like he he pressed too much on the exhaust and he smashed into a wall
you can't trust forever you know what just no all right how do i how do i power up
new info new information kill boba fat pretty sick cameo he's yeah where'd he go
destroy the weapon caches oh he's just gonna be he's just gonna be mr x i get it oh there you are
wait what oh fuck it i'm just gonna go do the thing destroy the weapon caches there's three on
this side three on the other side fine these weapon caches no those are minecraft blocks
fucking he said it again i hate that joke fucking idiot i fucking hate it here we go he's still
just following me i'm gonna all right i'm gonna shut this door on your head weapon caches looking
for weapon caches are these weapon caches no where are they they're not showing up on the force sense
didn't they be showing up on force sense is that one no where are they use the force map oh there
it is use your force eyes shut up stab it oh no boba fat saw me and he collapsed in here
oh he's doing the fire so really come on you just can't kill him just run away
i can use the force kin sure wait what did i say no what the heck oh my god he got he got me
force what oh my god guys guys what the heck stop
he's a health bar wait why do they have a health bar uh can i kill him oh that's gonna kill me
i don't think i can do anything uh he's not i don't think he can die he can't die
wait if i can fly up there and cut his head off force throw wait hold on he broke it what he broke
he broke my lightsaber no wait give me it i can't do anything freedom okay well you know oh no no
no he's dead okay he is dead he's dead he just has his rocket still on i get okay that's what
happened oh boy it was a t-pose into the skybox okay i'm gonna go that way come on force hurry
up oh come on come on oh i'm so annoyed he's back oh you fucking asshole what are you doing
he's gone i'm gonna go this way and then over here is there an entrance over here oh this place
sucks i have to go that way but there's no way to it didn't look like a way i could go um are you
fucking kidding me actually that helped me i'm glad you did that there's no door down here i can go
through i'm gonna go this way this way or this way this way oh i got it cool now there are there's
one more over we'll go this way horse pasta he doesn't know i can see him that was so dumb
that was dumb it's so stupid it instantly instantly killed yeah okay i'm holding something in my hand
that's hotter than that fire oh now where the hell is he i did what is this thing for that though
that's a death star that star right those are the plans for the death star okay now that's three we
got a few more where are we going from here oh fuck here he comes that's factually incorrect
well they keep they keep making them so who cares all right now fuck off he's gonna drop a bomb on
me i have to take him out i'll get out of here i'll get out of here i don't see any more over
this way we're gonna go all the way on the other side other side right mods thanks for controlling
the copy pasta spam can we get a just a little bit of a clap in the chat room please for the
mods today mods thank you nice work all right this guy's actually annoying really shitty placed a
quick save but i don't know whatever what do i care fire's still going get over get over here
yeah run run run run keep running he's avoiding everything i'm gonna now you're locked in and now
you're locked in and now you're fucking screwed i'm gonna turn you into a skeleton oh shit i
can't do anything about it he's got midichlorian armor on whatever it is all right i think it's
this way gooey gooey armor almost okay i need to i need to leave me all right hold on let him do
that move he runs i would objective complete building unit ready building unit ready building
construction complete oh oh i only have three two three more to do
oba fat versus i don't even know my character's name i have no idea i don't know why i want to
say is it brandon jaden okay right yeah what are you doing that was the wrong way to run
his name's melvin i wish i wish his name was melvin so bad garth melvin all right straight
garth melvin okay there's only one more that remains and it is down there oh a mandalorian is
here what though i'm getting minus two for that that's just that's the man it's a mandalorian
that's the that's a mandalorian i can't say that the mandalorian is here i don't understand why is
that i'm not i'm just saying the mandalorian is here well i don't get it you knew what you were
doing you know i'm saying like a boba fat like here the mandalorian is here he's not mandalorian
i don't know what wait what oba is not a mandalorian what are you talking about
i don't know melvin is a mandalorian stop all right now what do i do return to the ship
yes he is we talking about what are you doing what is this nonsense melville melville oren
oh please where's that ship right in the middle somewhere where's my ship just leave me alone i
don't want to fight you anymore mandalorian leave me alone no that's bullshit that's absolutely
horseshit because i played star wars bounty hunter and the guy's like hey hey mando right doesn't he
say like hey mandalorian no he says hey jango not mandalorian not mando oh it's outdated though
it's supposed to be jango is it jango no it's not no it isn't it's boba oh i got him he's under
arrest i'm sorry i couldn't hear you over the sound of my lightsaber vacuum cleaner what did
you say one is an enemy but not an enemy though he chooses his own path and thanks soda cat for
the 10 subs kyle and i have sensed great anger in you jaden you must learn to control it or it
could lead you to the dark side i mean very clearly all of my answers have been dark side
when they give you the jedi personality test i mean if i get just s i t h in meyers briggs
i'm pretty sure you should know by now okay whatever an end to the disciples of ragnos
i believe that taveon is storing force power in the scepter for one purpose to resurrect marco
ragnos is that possible the force holds a great many secrets it may be possible that if a high
enough concentration of force energy is infused into a body the cells might regenerate why is
everybody calling me shit lord what what is shit lord so we're going to the core of the vacation
spot or shit lord it's the burial place of a whole diagnosis resurrected there's no telling
what you might be able to shit lord melvin no that can't be this guy ash could still belong to the
dark side it could be a trap i don't know why that's making me laugh so much but it is it's not that
funny i i know it's like it is though like i don't know why it's doing it all right here we go gain
entrance into the cult facility on task for three to search for rosh pennon here we are the enemy
base to pee yeah i'm going pee have a wreck see you guys in like two three minutes mine chat i
guess you are my little drew crewers come here at least i like this a lot oh no versus auto
oh no all right let's go auto wins fatality all right so here we go
in access to the imperial power facility by jumping twisting and spinning oh my god this
is heavily guarded but it's not a not a big deal it's a good link this time it's been we haven't
seen one link at all the whole day let's see what this is all right i'll take a second this is the
first link but that it has to be red doesn't it didn't this be red oh wait that's again okay hold
on a minute wrong image no but it needs to die it needs to be red this one also please all right
hold on i'm gonna look no that one's stupid i'm not i don't know change the color you can't it's
not allowed what are you guys doing i'm not one of these links what the hell are you linking me
all right i'll go i'm playing let's go yes you can i all right i swear to god if this is fake
you know brb for a sec if this is fake i'm gonna be pissed give me a second i want i don't want you
to see it i want to reveal that it's fake what's the command shit this is a fucking stormtrooper
trying to kill me okay color red red it doesn't do anything it's a lie it's a lie it's a complete
lie you tell me what i did wrong no parentheses did you enable sb cheats i did no quotes saber
color one red oh saber color what two red oh shit what about how i put it i what happened
i it broke it broke it broke in half i thought you guys were just lying to me people was i
kept seeing the debate face they were three red saber color three red oh i just made them bigger
and lighter wait gonna be any color no i can't have like the dark saber
okay i want one red and one black i'm a sith lord and i have the dark saber it's a really weird way
to wait what did i just that just turned my shit green it's like a spray paint house why did it
just turn green oh what oh my fucking god i didn't say it once valid colors i'm gonna see red orange
yellow green blue purple you can't even okay saber color three red saber color three red one or two
saber color one red saber color one red red there is no three all right well i got it
there every christmas sith every christmas lord melvin do sith lord celebrate like holidays
i feel like they probably still do but you can't celebrate christmas just because you're evil
kill this kind of hurts my eyes i'm going back to double red any other weird cheats saber color
two red saber color one red i quit saber color one red red saber color one red red no you fucking
idiot don't put a space no space between red like that it's turned blue beat saber
okay between saber and color there's no brown connect them i i can't connect them i can just
hold it like this i almost fucking died all right what's the what's the mission here gain access to
the facility okay let's go what are you supposed to do about that by the way kill kill kill kill
kill kill kill kill kill kill half off you're dead if you do this next mission without dying
or do the macarena if you fail it no absolutely not 100 no that's this is such a good link all
right we'll just wait a minute one guy community chest one guy in your favor remove 500 million
from the debt wait i got a community chest nice i just picked this out and i just picked it out
one guy in your favor remove 500 million from the debt nice that's a good pull i'll take it
all right we're gonna go all the way up no no more deals not yet i'm trying to be a sith lord
okay here we are force choke this guy and then force pull him and snap his neck
and then electrocute all of them at the same time shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot electrocution
where's that bridge a billion off the dead if you ban links you're not gonna get everybody
on board on that one that's not happening you really think you're gonna get people on board on
that one nope there it is um i mean i had to do that it's just hands up why was he
hands up yeah i'm not even a sith lord i'm just adding these to my collection everybody agrees
with that maybe i'll think about that then maybe i'll think about that but hey uh lose the attitude
i love that saying yeah yeah no that's not that's a really good idea i really appreciate that that's
good uh lose the attitude please oh wait wait i had what fuck you what are you talking about what
saber dual one what is it saber dual one saber dual underscore one is that it
wait one okay red red right saber color red red right the color one red red that's correct right
yes and go oh somebody start playing it
i'm holding it like this i'm holding it in one hand only a master of evil dog this is halloween
this is everybody scream everybody scream in our town of halloween i am the beast hiding under your
bed i am the moon and the inside your hair cheese in my teeth then spiders in my hair
this is halloween this is halloween i can end this open open the fucking door okay i can't
get in that door you pissed me off can you help me whoo why can't that open maybe i can open it
later use the force i oh right use the force luke use the force luke i don't even have the
sabers anymore oh no it's okay i didn't even fucking do that and i'm really hold on i'm okay
i'm fine i'm all right i can get up i can get back up there stop all right underscore saber
dual of hates dual what is it saber dual underscore one that's pretty cool but saber
color one red red thank you up the hule of fates oh i laughed too hard and i like blew up my
fucking throat all right let's go i did i saved the game already this doesn't open you pissed me off
it has to be something out here i didn't mean to do that oh i see i see there it is you pissed me
off stop shooting at me you've got to be fucking kidding me the guy killed me with a default blaster
how is it even possible that that's not even possible i was very angry so i had to kill the
guy the little robot that didn't do anything okay so i can go up here can i push these oh my fuck
do player model mutant rancor please not yet not yet i'm not going to transform
into the monster until i've gotten this far i'm almost at the end of the game look i need a key
card for this obviously do it do it can i be player model darth vader he's alive now let him
fool you don't let him fool you you literally can i can what is it i don't want to be doctor
i want to be doctor player model darth vader hear me you sound like you're in your mid-20s today
um in maturity or in tone of voice i don't know what you mean what does that mean both what in
tone what are you talking about i don't know what that means hear me you sound like you're in your
mid-20s today what lose the attitude yeah hey all right drop the attitude we'll see
all right what is it player model darth vader that didn't work it's darth vader close enough
yeah we just just they don't see me as an enemy do they no can i even kill them oh no i think
i broke the game i cannot injure anybody on the other team great okay i can't move
my head was stuffed in the ceiling and i was suffocating hold on i hope can we get the
final cutscene as the rancor i can't move i can't move is the rancor you can't move
it's because you're near a wall i have to do further away from the wall like how about right
here no i can't move what is the green thing stuck inside me switch to melee i can use a gun
i can't move though i turn on noclip no i get this it's over the stream has been completely
derailed can i use the lightsaber yes this i can't use them oh wait wait melee no it's not working
get out of noclip and then you can use it i get out of noclip and then i can use melee
okay no clips off what's enough i need flv i need to pull the flv what if oh shit look
at this i can move okay how do i pull the flv back i can't get in here i just got a checkpoint
as the rancor that's not good okay um player model gonk sith gonk i can't use the lightsaber
i can use the gun hi can they i not kill them just like a trash can you know whatever i'm just
going in uh gonk can't jump sorry guys i wish i could be the emperor get back to playing the game
it's not a bad idea play a model jawa hold on i need somebody that has animations for swinging
a lightsaber jawa is to have a lightsaber swing animation i take your word for it i'm gonna save
it right here let's find out oops they do okay i mean this just looks like a this is just a sith
lord padawan okay well let me press f8 do they have it too oh they do too holy shit that's so
funny nobody suspects the jawa sith lord jawa do i stare like this in cutscenes too i'm afraid to
save uh i did it it's over where the heck i can come from let's go jawa sith i can always revert
the player model that's true here we go basically the head off oh no i'm i'm light now am i a sith
lord still i'm just chrome gandalf hold on there we go i fixed it this way this way this way stop
firing at me like that you make no red lightning use melee you can grab people uh the jawa doesn't
have a melee i know kung fu i know kung fu where's my but i don't have a lightsaber anymore oh yeah
i do okay i really am just the mini emperor
power before me i will show you unlimited power i will show you
oh i saved it what the fuck what else we got do both mouse buttons all right hold on
huh i can't kill him moves rolling stab cartwheel attack enemy medium attack
flip attack slash back oh my god it's the fucking emperor the emperor's in here how are we doing
today coming to check and see if you have any skill in the name of the force have we found the
jedi scum that has been walking around aimlessly uh commander no uh we have not found the jedi yet
jedi has not been found we are doing our best to find him i think you can do more than that than
simply looking have you have you tried looking inside of yourself commander green you will find
those jedi and you will bring them to me i want them alive what happened wait oh fuck you game
oh my god i gotta exit i need the quick save is this a quick save download a mod just play the
game i we're at the end of the game man relax okay here we go okay spawn wait wait what about
motorcycle can i get a player model what player model r2d2 player model mouse no you can't i
crashed the game you can't it crashed not gonna happen unfortunately do player model jedi master
okay that i didn't get a chance player model jar jar he's not in the game jar just not in the game
player model chui oh yep okay sith lord all right i want to stay chui i don't think chui
chui can't use powers if i just okay i need a second hold on
go away for a second hold on i need to fix the player model all right i can't do force moves
chui i can't heal i need to just get out of this area for a second
chui sucks chui sucks chui's terrible he's terrible i'm not even doing any damage
okay hold on i can't even force heal does this prove that chui is not force sensitive
oh my god fuck i can't go in here okay chui's done the chui can't do anything
chui's terrible he's awful he can't even do any force power i can't even stop why is he doing
he can't do force powers he can't do anything just hide i need to change my player model
boba fet so i can't hold on boba fet player model boba fet i did i got it i'm gonna lose
my fucking mind i have to kill these guys as chui there's no way i can do i can't do this
all right easy easy easy i'm all right okay all right all right let's go player model boba fet
oh jesus christ okay hold on oh my god does he have force powers he doesn't oh my god he
has that though i can't heal though i he doesn't have any heal i'm gonna save over this one okay
how long this is last it's like boba you could have just walked you really could have all right
who else who's next player team player luke jar jar no space ice what is it sith sword we want
wampa okay now back to chui oh fucking my god i have to do this i have to hold on just wait a
minute did i win fuck you no just get in there chui and just spam and kill them oh my god i'm
gonna freak out just kill them chui thank you okay now i'm player model luke okay i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna save it as luke just because his lightsaber is massive he's 200 force power holy
shit okay now fly x-wing what is it fly underscore x-wing oh ice what the hell are you writing ice
wallow what is that nope not reading that one all right i'm not reading the rest of it not reading
the rest of that one i don't know what it was almost npc spawn vehicle npc spawn vehicle
then is a code what code need to spawn large vehicles this has a list of all the npcs and
cheats all right yeah i'm just gonna click this i can put it under the monitor what we got all
right god mode uh dead mode refill health okay hold on turn invisible spawn npc spawn vehicle
vehicle name okay npc spawn vehicle space vehicle name let's see what they got for vehicles
okay atst x-wing the swoop bike okay here we go it's gonna explode get off get off get off
get off grab his lightsaber why am i just beating up the droid what are you doing luke
i'm gonna make this jump on vehicle swoop i want to go i didn't make it wait i'm still i'm good i'm
good i'm good i'm good okay what about player model wampa and then spawn vehicle i can't get on
i'm fucking use this holy shit i can wait a minute i can't get in damn it i got it i got it i got it
he can't do anything use your fists fucking god damn it i did like god vote on
he dies instantly he literally dies instantly i can't do anything i'm clearing this room first
goodbye okay there you go you're not gonna fuck with luke looks like the best swordsman in the
galaxy literally best swordsman in the entire galaxy no one can beat luke nobody nobody could
ever he's the best to ever live right okay i am now ready we're gonna save it here and we're
going to go wampa here we are get an atst this this area is not big enough
he takes so much damage we can't do wampa is npc vehicle spawn npc spawn vehicle uh npc spawn
vehicle atst npc spawn vehicle atst really what am i doing wrong oh it's atst underscore vehicle
pc spawn vehicle atst underscore vehicle uh oh there it is i can't even shoot the blaster
why is it walking like this i can't it's stuck the player model two rocks yeah this thing i
can't move this thing's too awkward it's gotta go atst peepo hold on i'm gonna play as luke i love
games you get to play as luke he's the most powerful he's so good no force lightning but
i mean like that's kind of dumb fix the texture uh well i'm not gonna be playing as luke the whole
time get him change stance high stance yeah you want to do a luke you want to go one-on-one and
just in clash sabers with luke bad idea please play as yeah funny low stance love whoa
no where did i you're kidding me why is this even down here i can just i can smell the omega
lows that are happening in the chat right now i can smell them let's go oh
no luke you jedi trainer okay who is this the hell am i um it's a worm it's a sand worm
wait i can move what it was rocks you jedi trainer then jedi master why player model jedi
trainer player model jedi master why play model yoda he's not in this game
i don't know i took it from a copypasta oh well what the fuck player model um
i think we did it all altist saber strong oh it's just one of these guys it's just one of the i'm
just one of these guys now do yoda not yoda play model test no i don't know someone's firing a
fucking missile launcher at me okay what a player model rocks oh shit uh can i jump do i
force powers as a rock it's the jawa voice darth rocks oh i just ruined everything no am i gonna
get to see like one of the final cutscenes as rocks well we made it across you can't kill me
i am i'm floating above you unkillable rock you can't have too powerful oh shit no he's gone
the rocks talking you can't stop me i can't let you do that he's back we believe you can't stop me
following is going to be encouragement for me not for you because i'm unstoppable can i use the
lightsaber oh sith rock this is so stupid this is the dumbest thing ever beat the game like this
i mean i'm i don't i'm gonna save it before the fight oh my god that guy got carved up like a
turkey oh all right i feel like i'm am i progressing is this game progress i have no idea what's
happening ready to go up again where do i go am i going the right way i feel like this is a this is
like a boss this looks like a boss fight who's this oh that guy i feel like this is an important
character oh shit i'm alive i'm alive rocks can't die i forgot rocks can't die i'm unkillable
it was up here right other way i i'm so turned around i have no idea what's going on
i have absolutely no idea what's happening this is just cheating all right all right all right
going back to jawa and that's how we're gonna do it go back to the rocks for the ending
player model dark saber i even go in the right way i have no fucking clue over there
i think it's over there oh well but just kill these guys that's it's this way all right here
we go oh shit is this the no we're not the java it doesn't work in cutscenes you so fun's over
i has come to rescue his friend that's so sweet where's rush what makes you think he wants to be
rescued tavian turned him to the dark side just like that bitty bitty someone's getting awfully
angry aren't they forgetting your jedi training look alora why serve tavian it's not too late
to join us and fight her i'm taking rosh out of here make it easy on yourself and tell me where
he is oh he's around i think i'll go look for him oh no oh no she's got me locked with her jedi
powers her jedi cement body ah you fiend villain i'll get out of this soon don't you what i'm good
i thought that was an x-wing i was like that's not an x-wing uh i it spawned somewhere where
that is how do you get out oh no it's okay it's all right we're gonna get this back
okay i think i've hacked the game i can by the way i can no longer walk but i can jump
this is not good uh player model drone oh shit i think it's actually completely
fucked up no no no no we gotta go back and change back was it uh default who is it what's
this guy's name jayden i only can't find jayden he's the main character okay there we go that's
change let's get this right what's that one for dual saber what is it again saber dual one okay
button oh that's quick load fuck you jeremy come on why am i small wait um hold on this is not
right this is inaccurate this is not accurate something's wrong
save player model player give me back my player
saber dual one okay saber color one red red but why am i tiny he still is small in the cut scene
what you so the itty bitty jedi i don't care all right let's go objective update find rosh
i don't have any powers my lightning is gone i don't know why i have 200 force power itty
bitty ooey gooey i just reload the game you use for set force all set force all four there we go
thank you they didn't see me uh touch the computer why am i locked in here oh shit boss room boss
room save it yeah i'm gonna go against tavian where watch it watch it watch it watch it come on
get him sith versus sit i think i've actually grown like i i'm back to normal oh my god what
have i done thank god you can't save the game while dead how up how up get away from me all
right we're good ultimate power okay now we're gonna go just pick a door about this one saving
the game quick i'm weak what do you think about that use electricity in the water for extra
damage that makes sense doesn't it no it doesn't turn the fucking lightsaber on why'd you turn it
off why do i keep turning the blade off it's saving power no it's just it's it's not smart
it's very stupid you still have melee the lightsaber would boil the water i don't know
how lightsaber is supposed to work it's just heat right it's so hot that it burns through flesh and
bone instantly that's kind of how it works right they don't it's a saber of light yeah that'd be
hot who's that both dead yes they are save it time for the final confrontation between who tavian
was rosh the entire time no i mean tavian rosh was tavian the entire time wait that's the same
thing i just said it again different way tavian is it there's a big big bad right that they're
working for rosh is the big bad nice no i'm not a jedi look at my saber we both have the same one
and by the way those who don't know to get a red lightsaber it's all it's about punishing and making
the crystals submit to you right remember that i'm reading the lore somewhere he was lying he knew
all along of course i fucking knew i'm a huge fan of star wars nice try but i dodged it oh fuck
let go let go let go let go get me out where the fuck did these stormtroopers come from
let go of me that's so stupid so unfair unfair unfair get me out not very much fanfare for
that guy's death took his blade too sick oh shit i was scared for no reason all right force
push while choking somebody i'll try it i didn't i didn't do anything force push force push is
terrible force push when being choked while you are choked okay uh what am i doing here
oh my god why i even have the bottom part what's the point there's no point to have the bottom part
why is it in here dev oh come on i mean i'm gonna i gotta activate it when it does this
we go already three two one fucking horrible i made it okay so i gotta go down sure wait till
we get to made it down where are you what does her all right now i can turn this goddamn machine
off i guess not can't touch this okay can't touch that either that's the goal here only people
could subscribe to germa 985 and touch that oh fuck i'm that sub only door keep going whoa
kyber crystal the way to get a good kyber crystals you gotta make sure you
you have to mine it yourself right don't you have the crystal has to what just happened what just
happened what's going on yeah you have to mine the crystal yourself i think all right it's the
whatever crystal calls to you or something i know i know what i know how the thing works
it's electrified i feel like i'm dying in this game more than i'm dying in dark souls i didn't
touch anything it's fucking electrocuting me what the fuck when do i get to go so there's
electricity there it smashes and then you can go in smash all right i fucking did it now what
oh fuck okay hold on what go go go hurry up hurry up come on open open open open them
too fast for you okay save it keep moving i'm almost at the final encounter in jedi master
maybe i will serve tavian's gonna be darth vader or emperor or something i wasn't paying any
attention at all when does this game take place you're in between what saga luke looks pretty
young so i'm gonna assume i mean luke doesn't look old or anything after episode six ten years
after return to the jedi okay yeah because he doesn't look old or anything so this is between
the sequel series cool all right okay i get it none of this is canon anymore it's not none of it
jayden oh i found you look like much of a captive rosh did you dream this up
or was it tavian's idea no jaden wait i was wrong please take me back to the academy
i need help okay jayden stay back please don't hurt me you tried to kill me and now you've lured me
into a trap jayden i was scared you have to believe me we're we're friends remember
let's get out of here before alora comes back good that hurt that apparently hurt real bad
oh fuck i am the bad guy look at me betray me again you're always trying to beat me how do i
know this isn't just another trick jay don't do it what finish him jedi wait listen to what you're
saying you're angry don't give into it leads to the dark side right you see the saber i'm holding
dude afraid of dying saber strike him down give into your anger i need a new apprentice
angel and demon on the shoulders who do i listen to deactivate your lightsaber
remain on the path i don't even know what it said why should i yourself said how powerful the dark
side was i was wrong no you were weak don't do it oh my god he's gonna do it
yeah no no excuse me excuse me i i'm on my own person we will defeat the jedi
and rule the galaxy no you get down you're next why should i trade one master for another
the scepter of ragnos is too powerful to be left in the hands of someone as weak as tavian
if anything it should belong to me of course it should i think so you on the other hand are
useless i should have killed you on hoth you won't get a second chance tavian has taught me
much since then oh has he oh fuck no no no i don't want to do that either let's go wait what that
was it i just fucking slaughtered her she's two pieces she can't even do her ending dialogue
she just does she have dialogue at the end oh my god i'm so powerful jayden has turned both your
students no i'm not supposed to be a big boss battle jedi no he didn't no he didn't he didn't
pass the jedi bar exam but i'm still he was a para jedi game just like blew up okay well i guess
we're gonna open it again big point is it right okay here i am jayden what happened out of my way
the scepter will be mine i sense the dark side in you jayden i can't let you pass
i will pass whether you want me to or not oh i'm a bad guy now that's right i've got
forced lightning the path of the sith oh fuck off he turns he's like no the scepter will be mine
and this guy over here the mask on stabs him through the chest it's my scepter this is lazy
right like can we have another reason why a villain would become a villain
it's like a big greedy artifact item the only thing that we can do to make people like evil
oh that powerful art of these different these people wait what i sense the dark side in you
jayden i can't let you pass i will pass is a different person want me to or not
it's a different npc don't just instantly kill me he killed her no that artifact is gonna be mine
i will kill anybody that's in my way to get that artifact no it's my artifact oh wait somebody
else looking for an artifact well i'm sorry it's mine oh fuck you did i save it where did i save
it jayden what did i save it did i save it here okay let's go save it right here enough of this
bullshit and by the way what do you even do with that item what the double bladed lightsaber is
not enough for you what the fuck is this it's mine the scepter will be mine dude i heard that
scepter was unguarded right now right now did you say money power fashion what are you doing here
same really sorry wait same reason you're here is that a stupid question
all right if i was gonna say we could split it i don't know maybe i go like this put my
fingers up by temples and go um i don't know it's like a weird puzzle or something
line up the diamonds our diamonds are lined up what happened nice job
it's a war sent versus jedi versus me oh okay we got two jedi gone cool saber combo though i
like it one big orange i like that too what do you say opportunist yeah fuck you get out of here
do a mine trick and that's not even bound force powers mine trick um i don't know
t no let's drain uh whatever i don't care t this made my screen brighter what is healing okay
okay t wait so stupid all right mine trick how far does this go how long can i control this person
i'm trying to burn them did i kill him i see the music just played oh shit okay it's pretty funny
where am i supposed to go wait what happened down i have no idea what i'm doing jedi mind float
okay here and then into this room over here new objective find a way to open the door to the
valley uh it's got a big triangle on it oh okay look at this because the end of the game puzzle
i'm gonna assume it's the one that's the triangle my god is that it that's good that's triangle
triangle and this one hey one triangle and did it oh shit all right here we go
here comes the jedi mind trick holy shit what was that jedi mind trick i want to get oh i got a
jedi mind trick somebody wait what wait oh he died instantly got you okay whatever there's too many
people there's too many people holy shit this is like six jedi versus me this is uh killing each
other i can't get in come on you can do it get on in here fucking please
he clearly just ran and spun it into her head that wasn't even trying it would be that easy
it would seriously be that simple it would just be like just wave this thing and it's just like
like a hot knife through butter it's that's ridiculous who's this so that's me don't kill
that person don't kill that person that's me i see it okay
she's just standing there just looking at him like yeah are you and i are friends
head gone like just it was one not even one false second head is just gone oh yeah yeah okay wait
go this way dear psycho i'm sorry i just fell off how do i get out of here force pull i pull out
these like pillars pull out yeah that's what i'm trying to do i'm trying to pull these things out
okay it's these ones force pull out make sure oh you're gonna be force
i can't even say it man force pull out force i can't say it i'm not gonna say it it's too much
i'm done okay i'm done i'm done it was that fun this is a fun game this is very fun i'm not i'm
not gonna push that forward anymore it's too stupid i can't even say it force protection or
force pregnant ah get me the fuck up here i gotta get out of this game
why did you do that why did you do that what he kicked me
she she had enough of that shit man wait come here come here no shit what happened
okay are you not you are not a jedi why would you say that um it's me oh i lost it okay continue
it's me a jedi that's right i think we're going down oh uh nice job dude wait we're almost in the
we're almost at the temple we're almost at the temple this guy sucks nice move but it doesn't
matter i will give you an honorable death two on one let's see if this guy can do it no no that's
unfair that's well it's he's still alive he's still alive holy shit he did he's doing so good
nice work thanks for clearing everything out for me like i fell out from the ceiling i think
whatever whoa who's attacking me who's got who's shooting me this game is bitrate something's
going on with the fov in the game something's messed up here force bitrate what did this drop
bad nice good job behind you behind you behind you behind you tried to warn him how many people
are down here there are way too many people here there's so many people here this is just
a dumb amount of people all right falling down into lava in three two one unfortunate
falling into lava in three two one come on falling into the lava in three
two one get over here okay well it still happened not the way that i wanted it still did
here jump jump jump okay now kill him how do i get out how do i get out of this guy get out
okay i'm just gonna just die lava no hold on i'll just force pull him out lots of jedi
you move around so quickly stop it's burning this guy's a loose kid i gotta get rid of this guy
i had to get rid of that guy that guy was just i could not be around for many longer
this game is something else i'll tell you this is something else so where's tavian
tavian's gonna end up being kyle or something right it's gonna be something stupid like that
is the reason why you guys are saying that tavia that this game is not canon is because is it luke
is luke at the end be like that's right i'm tavian and this is not canon wait you have to
go all the way back oh fucking my god i hate that at least give me a second after i die before i
have because i'm clicking to swing the sword force push okay all right all right force push
all right i gotta run come on i'm about to turn on godbone just run to the end of the game
you know what just all of you come back here to the lava you're all so stupid you're just gonna
walk in it anyways why even have a jedi fight when you're just gonna walk in the lava and die
there's no point in having this fight where are they
oh no get out get out get out who's that punching why was my character punching
quick quick get in there quick come here fucking die he's in the lava are you kidding me
what okay wait wait wait i don't just run what's wrong with me all right we're good all the way
back to the beginning wait wrong way can i go the other way fuck that's i don't know why that
scared me so much hey but away from him hey away from him don't touch him okay so can i get there
from here is there where to go i go up from here oh shit all right cool shit i can't exit oh no
i hope i don't get killed i hope nobody kills me go go go go go go get in get in get in oh thank
god all right i'm fine here we go the guy that was guarding the door i'm here am i gonna beat the
game right now new objective fucking fall down a cliff fall down a cliff already fall down a cliff
already oh my god die already how do i get out she's dead what okay no i'm gonna do it to myself
okay i'm fine around have to go around the whole building where the hell did you
where did you come from are you alive how are you alive after that yeah no just kill them just
fight this guy oh god damn it jump to pull out yeah i was oh that's it that's a huge fall i can i
do i need to go over here oh he struck at least he got to do that he died with dignity
i'm not supposed to go that way force fall resident sleeper mind trick jump but it's so
effective and so easy okay just get up here i'm gonna fucking freak out just don't even go that
way it's not even worth going that way just go up here oh fucking come on oh you have to remove the
force skin yeah this is i can't make that that's so frustrating i can't just step on that i
definitely can my god jeremy fucking stop this madness and just go the right way go over here
spawn luke and push him off his the screen dude wait how do you spawn luke spawn what is it
just beat the game end the stream no hold on i want to spawn luke i didn't do anything spawn
npc luke luke is not a spawn function npc spawn luke uh i do not see anything wait
holy wait what i'm sorry what a disaster okay i need to just what's the right way to go
it's a fucking disaster guys i tried to jump i promise
okay from here i gotta go this way holy shit
spawn no i can't i can't can i
i can't i can't mind trick him can't stop okay i'm gonna stop i'm gonna stop this is stupid
this is stupid i have to stop this is dumb this is dumb i'm not doing it i'm only gonna do one
more time where is he no don't fall in i'm waiting for him to fall in behind me i spawned him in the
worst place okay that's it it's i'm done it's time to play the game can i go around is the wrong way
i'm just trying to hop the other way all right let me just leave let me look i have to go this
way but how do i even get over there i guess i could you walk i mean i can i get up here no
there's another big pit here the way i was going the first time yeah but there's a huge pit here
isn't this is wrong isn't it can jump like i did before okay i jumped it yeah i know but i'm
supposed to be over there it didn't look like i could open that door can i make it i make this
jump here i definitely have to go this way so all right okay can't open that can i get on top of
this or no can i knock this down oh you gotta be fucking kidding me are you kidding me are you
absolutely kidding me sonic adventure 2 yeah all right let's go let's do the same thing pull it
right no i don't oh i don't die if i go down here that didn't work there's a door down here
what what the fuck is this why is this here all right i'm in the center of the mountain here
this has got to be close roger that roger that convincing fall joke it just took a little longer
than usual it just took a little bit longer but we got it oh here we go one on one on one on one
one on one on one on one oh no it's three v one i had it wrong free for all hey green versus red
good versus evil i don't know what happened evil evil loses you know what fucking i am holding it
together here i'm just going in the temple who cares i got in his head that guy didn't stand a
chance all right i'm just going i'm going in the temple i don't care get me in open the door open
the temple door open the door no you motherfucker well i don't need to go in there that's it who's
stop tavian from resurrecting marca ragnos i will and i'm gonna take the crown oh hi guys
um all right well bye checkpoint there he is the scepter of orange light oh this is tavian right
i forgot from the very beginning of the game i did not i forgot this person existed am i hiding
behind the door no i'm here to kill you something that my old master couldn't do but why with
ragnos reborn the jedi will be wiped out and we can serve him as he rules the galaxy
i want to no longer serve i want to rule the galaxy i will the scepter and its power for myself
now give it to me i will enjoy slaying you
she keeps wiggling off of it did i win
oh come here get over here i'm gonna do this dumb shit i don't care gotta get it in the exact
right spot that looks good i can't do that man we're gonna be fire andy i can't believe that
fucking work finish it kill me i want to like spawn the x-wing in there we fight ragnos jayden
don't get in my way but it's not too late to renounce the dark side
tavian and her cow it's way too late we can end this here oh no this is just the beginning
jayden the lure of the dark side is strong but it will ultimately destroy it already did fight it
rosh resisted it you can too you walked into the end of the movie dude he was to afraspe the dark
side can't let you do this jayden stop me master no oh i didn't kill him what's wrong what's his
head pulsating his head's getting bigger what's happening to his character what's happening to
he's mutating oh my god he didn't even say anything we didn't get to talk what am i doing
don't just point at random shit oh now you show up luke jayden has turned to the dark side
and he's taken the scepter and rosh dead jayden killed him he felt betrayed are you alive isn't
that most powerful item in the universe i misjudged him maybe i shouldn't be teaching at the academy
it's not like i've been the perfect jet his head would be like a crushed watermelon yoda and ben
were great teachers yet we lost a lot more than students luke we've since good and he's killing
everyone and he has the most powerful scepter on earth you may be right it's gonna have to be
you luke well at least taveon and irkman stopped the scepter is too powerful we must find jayden
and destroy it i'll take care of it as my student jayden is my responsibility i'm taking a leave of
absence from the academy for a while if i find jayden i'll let you know be careful if there's
anything i can do to help i will yeah the force be with you show up 45 minutes ago luke before he
killed 400 people and took everything and almost killed me you just walked in didn't get my texts
now you have read receipts on i saw you saw it at fucking exactly 355 pm said help for the love
of god he's killing everyone and here you are at 450 interesting why is there a guy lying down on
the ground that's it wait didn't they just say luke was gonna come find me is it dlc or a second
game or something is there a sequel it was just there is is jedi is there a jedi academy 2 or is
it just jedi night there's a ton of these games in there jedi night 2 jedi outcast hmm okay are
they as fun as this one was or did you guys want me to play this one because this is the fun one
this is the good one right this is like the fun interesting one right okay outcast is good outcast
is the better one hmm is there any after credits things true baka is himself what this is not a
marvel movie whatever all right i think that's a that's a good place to stop you chose this
ending you could get the good ending well actually you know i want to spawn the rancor in this room
is there nothing else after this i do want to spawn the rancor inside the boss room
like kotor i feel like kotor is probably a little too slow for me it's a lot of dialogue isn't it a
lot of dialogue choices i think it's a little too slow i know it's an incredible game but i don't
know if i want to stream it it might be a little too slow for me on stream kotor is like 30 hours
yeah i don't know okay spawn uh rancor okay i need to hide for a second wait i can just do this right
okay where is it where's the rancor move jaden okay i have to hide her whoa no no fight each other
there we go you grab her please eat her eat her please wait he's still in the cut scene
he's still in the cut scene not as i didn't kill who is he attacking it's wait he's blocking
this is just
i need a second
oh my god there's nobody here he's gone they're both gone he ate them both
okay what happens if i hit enter oh the game's about to crash hard yeah the game's crashed
the first reaction is not why is there a rancor in this room no he just gets fucking swiped
he's just fucking screaming okay i'll that's it i'll see you guys on friday
get to the third cut scene so he eats luke i can't that's not gonna happen he's gonna kill
everybody in the room that's not gonna i don't think i'll try i'll try my chest i'll try it i
promise i'll try once okay so can i spawn in the cut scene spawn during the kyle fight
okay i get you i get you okay that's a good idea that's a really good idea that was so easy
okay here we go here comes the kyle fight okay here we go let's spawn them this motherfucker
eats luke i'm gonna shit my pants i get it oh fuck you oh my god you just put me into the menu
press up arrow oh shit okay here we go okay here we go it's let's see if he eats luke
i gotta get a good spot why is it so easy yeah this is just really fucking easy
get out get out of the menu where is he don't kill me fuck okay stay away from me
wait why is he doing that what wait what the hell was that what he doesn't do that
i gotta restart the game he's he's doing the force choke turn on god mode okay all right all right
okay i might actually be able to get this i'm gonna right here okay and let's get him spawned
in three two oh fuck okay what's god mode okay here we go actually i i don't want god mode i
want to be able to die in the cut scene npc spawn mutant rancor okay we've got it it's time for me
to lose control of this and i'm gonna run i'm gonna leave so how do i pull out of this
i know i have to move force okay here we go how you got him okay you got him you got him he's
gonna eat him this is it we're finally getting to see it okay here we go come on we need luke we
need luke right now come on in luke luke where's the rancor what i don't think he's here anymore
oh he is and he's taking the scepter and rosh dead jaden come on he felt the anger was too
strong for him to be in a better spot i know all right hold on wait wait wait we're gonna try again
oh my fucking head's gonna hurt i he's gonna if he get that side big wide shot man that big wide
angle if he gets swiped out of that fucking cutscene spawn him right in the middle okay
hold on let me get a good spot we need to spawn him right in the center right here like right here
spawn more than one dude i'm gonna fucking die okay right here is where i want him to spawn
right there i have to run immediately forward Jesus oh my god why are they all red
why they've read oh hold on okay come on no no no don't kill me jump jump jump jump what am i
doing did they get him they got him somebody got him kill him kill him kill him kill him
kill him somebody kill that motherfucker please there's no way this doesn't happen now it's
impossible for it to not happen bring on luke skywalker come on quickly please please get out
jayden yes i got out okay i got out it's gonna happen did somebody get him he's still under the
rock wait i want to see one more time i have to see it just one final time one more time okay
and i'm done just one i want to have to see luke get grabbed from that wide angle it's the only
thing i care about i don't care about anything else on earth i spawned a bunch of luke's now
no don't get me let me go let me go let me go leave me alone get him got it okay make sure he's
right in the middle this is perfect okay bring it on i'm good here we go he's stepping on me
no shit i missed it does luke still come does luke still walk into frame
he's gonna say that there's nobody under the rocks what happened here kyle
wait wait wait come on give us the wide angle give us the wide angle please rosh please give
us the wide angle no yes he's so close yoda and ben were both great teachers he needs to
be like a hair forward what was that okay i'm done i have to stop i'm done it's streams over
wait is the red course still in the z in the ship what wait the red course in the ship
it's that's not possible right impossible oh jesus okay well that's enough of that
i'll see you guys on friday that's the end of the stream i'm gonna do a bunch of stuff oh man
that was a very fun game i'm glad i played it yeah i will see you guys very soon on friday
thanks for watching everybody we'll see you soon we're gonna do the uh little credits here
yeah academy was awesome i might play the other ones too not kotor though oh my goodness my whole
body hurts oh i got a workout today that's good pause that thank you again everybody
here come all the subs that were today we had a shitload of community subs thanks a lot guys
oh man oh man what about the force unleashed i never played either one of them the first one's
better than the second one though right i'm gonna take like a shower after this one play fallen
order i'm gonna give a look at of all the star wars games we're gonna give a look make sure i
take a good close microscopic view who you should play jedi outcast too it's such a good game
i missed all these i didn't play any of them we will check out at least one or two more i promise
a battlefront maybe i'll we'll do like another star wars week or something
when are you gonna do the awards encore that's a good question probably the end of january late
january is probably going to do the little encore awards because i want to do a new poll and do a
new voting and everything so because they were not on the poll and it probably won't take that
long we can just kind of add it to the end of a stream or the beginning of a stream too but have
a wonderful week guys i will see you on friday uh probably around three o'clock pacific on friday
take care of yourselves have a great night and i will i'll be back with some with some things
to talk about see you real soon have a great week good night guys