Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jirma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Demoman with the stuff that's on the screen right now.
I believe it's the strange lock and load, the charge and torch, and the islander, strange islander.
And of course, you got the hats and crap, the miscellaneous whatever, battery canteen, who cares?
So today I want to talk about something, not really to do about the gameplay, but to do with Team Fortress 2.
Specifically, how to get better at landing your pipes, or really anything in this game that has travel time.
This is not really gonna talk about hitscan, although this will probably help you out with your skits- skitscan.
What the hell was I gonna just say? With your hitscan as well.
But it's mainly gonna focus on the travel time things, like the Demoman pipes, all the rocket launchers,
and even the syringe gun, this could probably help you out with the syringe gun as well.
And what it is, it's TR Walkway. I didn't know anything about this map for the longest time.
And just very recently, like in the last two months or so, I've been going onto TR Walkway,
it's just a map you can play pretty much by yourself, and just been shooting bots.
And it might seem like the most mundane, boring thing in the world, but it actually is pretty addicting.
They just keep coming out, and you're on the red team, they're on the blue team,
and it's just they walk in a straight line, straight at you, and you can kind of make some adjustments,
you can make them do jumps, you can make them move in a different direction, and it's pretty fun.
You'll find yourself just sitting there for what seems like hours shooting at these bots.
And it's so important that you do this for a while, and you practice inside a TR Walkway,
because eventually your muscle memory will get down to a point where you know exactly where to put your crosshair in an actual game.
You'll go, oh, this guy's moving in the direction that I'm used to, I know where I'm supposed to place this,
because I know exactly how it's going to move, I know how the trajectory is going to go,
and it's going to hit the guy, and he's going to die, and I'm going to get more points,
and I'm going to do better in Team Fortress 2.
And I mentioned why it's so important to be in something like TR Walkway,
because everybody always says that to get better at the game, you got to play, you got to practice,
to get better, you just play, and you get better.
But it can be pretty damn hard sometimes, because when you get into a server,
and there's a bunch of people that are way better than you,
you're not going to get to practice your rocket launcher shots,
because they're going to just kill you in less than a second, and you're going to start to feel bad.
So what the bots don't attack back is the main thing.
They just move, and you can practice, and it's a way better environment,
and a way better place to get comfortable with the way that these weapons actually work.
And you don't have to feel so pressured by going up against these guys that have been playing forever,
that know everything about every class, that you can take your time with it,
and just sit sort of in a corner, and just get used to the way the item works.
I've seen such a huge increase, guys, in my amount of pipes landed, especially with Demoman.
Like, I mean, Soldier is one thing, but my pipes landed with Demoman has gone up significantly
just by hanging out in a Skype call with friends and just messing around in TR Walkway.
And then there are many more places besides TR Walkway, don't get me wrong,
TR Walkway is not, like, the only map in Team Fortress 2 where you can practice your shots,
but it's the one that I use, it's the one that I've fallen in love with, I guess.
And I will leave a link in the description to tf2maps.net,
where you can go download TR Walkway if you do not have it.
And please, in the comments section, if any of you guys have any other options
for people that are just as good as TR Walkway or even better,
some better options or other places you can go,
then please, by all means, leave some comments for some of the people that could use the help.
So that about wraps up that part of this video.
And the second part of this video, which is only about a minute or so long before this ends,
is I got this question asked in my livestream the other day,
and it was, when is my sister's due date?
Because somebody said that that was probably coming up pretty soon.
And yes, I'm going to be an uncle fairly soon here, in the next three or four weeks.
I believe my sister's due date is July 31st, and I'll be going down to North Carolina,
be taking all kinds of pictures with the baby.
I'm sure I'll tweet them out, so if you're not following me on Twitter
and you want to see these type of things, then that's probably where you're going to be able to see them.
But it'll be interesting. My parents are all freaking out.
Everybody's like going nuts right now, trying to figure out flight plans,
when we're going to meet down there, who is going, who is not going.
So it should be pretty interesting.
I'm sure I'll be in overdrive mode in the next three or four weeks.
But we will cross that bridge when we have to.
And also, before this video ends, I'm sure you're noticing right now,
we're losing by a pretty huge margin.
I'm not exactly sure why, because, I mean, we were doing pretty well.
I think people just weren't going on the point.
I'm watching it right now, and I seriously can't believe that with overtime,
we only have like, what, 15, 20 seconds capped right now.
And I mean, I was killing a lot of people.
I was doing pretty well in this gameplay.
And it was probably because I was just moving around too much.
I was going, I was dodging around the point rather than jumping on the point.
I didn't really have stickies either, which was pretty much a disadvantage
when you use this setup.
You can't really defend points as well as you could with stickies.
But regardless of that, that's going to wrap up this video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.