Hello. So, uh, we are exactly on time for the time that I told Ster. Which was 3.30.
Oops. Uh, I thought it was 3. Uh, accidentally I said 3.30, and oops-a-daisy, here we are, 3.30 exactly on time.
Okay, sorry about that. But hey, you know, I usually start at 6. We're about two and a half hours before earlier than that.
Yeah, here we are. How you doing? I'm gonna wait one or two minutes because I have something I want to, very important to talk about.
Very, very important grotto beast information that you need to know. I want to make sure it's very clear and I'm gonna make sure you know what's going on.
So let's wait a minute. Body sound like a teacher. Get out of here. I played it with my friend and it was fun. That's awesome to hear.
We hope you like it. Like we've said many times.
Okay, I'm gonna be playing Orcs Must Die 3 with Ster, who is in the call right now, but we are muted. He's using his teacher voice. Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, that's how you know something is actually, this is actually really important though, for real.
It is an update on the shipping issue that some of the early orders have been seeing. And I want to make sure people know that what's going on.
This guy hates Orcs. So just to give you a little bit of context, the Grotto Beasts project, uh, we had a presale and a lot of people that ordered in that first week, they got an estimated ship date.
And I want to, just anybody listening right now, if you have an estimated ship date in March, if you're one of the people with an estimated March ship date and you have not heard anything yet, Represent is going to reach out.
Represent is the fulfillment company, by the way. So at some point tomorrow morning, Represent is going to come out with a statement to everybody explaining kind of what happened.
And it's unfortunate that we have to do this, but those early orders are going to have to wait a little bit longer.
And we're doing, on our end here, every single thing possible to make it so those early orders get fulfilled, but Represent is going to come out with a statement.
They're going to explain what happened on their end, and that's pretty much all that we can do from here.
But the early orders that still have estimated March shipping dates, they now, they have complete priority.
So this is not a case of, oh, shit, I'm going to have to wait till the May estimated shipping date. No.
It's a manageable amount of orders that we think working with Represent here on correcting some of these issues that they can actually fulfill these in not that much time.
I'm really sorry that it came out like this. This is not, obviously, a lot of orders have already gone out, but Represent is aware of the problem on their end and they're going to figure it out.
And they're going to be sending out, you shouldn't have to do anything. There's probably nothing you have to do.
They're going to reach out as of tomorrow. So that's the thing to talk about.
That's the thing I wanted to point to. If you have an estimated March shipping date, keep an eye on your email.
They're going to reach out in the next day and they will tell you exactly the issues that they're having.
And that's pretty much all I can say. We're really happy with people that have gotten it.
Everyone seems to be excited about it. We're excited about it.
It's people that seem to be having fun. People are getting their orders.
But that doesn't I want to make sure that people that fucking ordered in the first few days get treated better.
And that's exactly what's happening right now. And we're doing it literally the last two weeks.
We've been desperately trying to make this problem solved and Represent wants to as well.
So they're going to handle this. If you have a March estimated ship date, please spread this around too.
If you know of people that have a March estimated ship date that didn't get any information yet,
tell them to keep an eye on their email as of tomorrow. I can't tell if what you're saying is real.
This is very real. This is very real. This is not like a routine.
I want to be very upfront and clear about this. But like I said,
it's a manageable amount of orders that we can completely expedite it.
Everybody that's an early order now has complete priority and it's it's not going to be.
Oh, now you have to wait all the way through May like the May estimated ship dates.
That is not happening. I can assure you of that.
But anyways, let's go talk to stir. You have to be corporate Andy.
I mean, I have to. I mean, people that people are spending money on this shit
and I want to make sure that we can assure everybody that they're going to get what they ordered.
And that's exactly what I'm fucking doing.
You know what I mean? Like people spent money on this shit.
I got to be upfront. So we're taking care of it.
Shouldn't be that much longer. There'll be a really comprehensive update tomorrow.
Check your emails. If you have a March estimated ship date, stir isn't laughing at you.
Hey, it's three thirties. Oh, it's three thirty eight.
Oops. How the stream needs to progress.
Yeah, I did. I did. I gave stir a schedule.
I did. So I assume your apology took a little longer than expected.
Is everyone everyone very angry? No.
No, it was it was very clear.
Oh, you can still hear this. There you go.
Yeah. But can you hear this? You fart.
No, that's usually when that's usually when you put a fart in.
Just want to make sure you understand.
Making sure everything was working.
All right. So we're playing orcs must die three.
Yes. A new orcs must die.
You're you're the party leader.
You are the operational manager.
Oh, wait, I am.
Oh, boy. Oh, I'm not leaking like a room code or something, right?
I I have no idea.
I didn't even like look at that.
I don't think so. I think we're good.
I think I have to ready.
I'm ready. I just want to make sure it wasn't like this and like a friend code.
All right. So this is why you want to explain why we're playing orcs must die three.
You said that you were into it. You wanted to check it out.
We're playing orcs must die three because you contacted me and said,
hey, do you want to play a game?
And then I came up with a bunch of ideas.
Five nights at Freddy's ideas weren't very good.
Five nights at Freddy's watch along.
Excuse me. Also my idea now was yours on like a whole other stream.
Excuse me. Credit.
Excuse me. You want the five nights at Freddy's watch along.
I don't know. I thought that was your face for a second.
I don't know why I just saw a face on my screen.
I thought it was you.
Wait, you want to skip this?
No. Oh, what's the lore?
I don't know.
Don't don't you want to know the lore capabilities?
Yeah. A real ogre would have eaten you by now.
You will miss that face for a while.
I think he said we've come back.
Wow, it's like you're allergic to saying smarts.
For an ogre?
What the fuck?
Right? Time is over.
I just want to kill some orcs, man.
I want to get in there in game, man.
All right. Do we have to choose between who you want to be?
Wait, do they have different weapons?
Do you want the magic longbow or do you want the blunderbuss gun or bow?
I want the bow.
I think the bow is the person who has to run around and do things more.
Sounds good to me.
At least that's how it was in the second one.
It's like a YouTube video thumbnail.
Enemies through the rift reduces rift points, right?
So don't let them get through.
This is your loadout.
And then yeah, blazing trap spends money.
Do we share money?
I don't know.
This is this is world's first.
No one's ever played this game before.
All right. Enemies through the rift.
I think I'm playing at like 720p by the way.
I'm back at the menu.
You are?
Yeah, like I'm back at like ready up again.
Oh, okay.
Failed to connect.
Trap placement is critical.
It's like the trap you want to place and look at the surface.
Are we playing on a split screen?
Oh, no.
No, no, I failed to connect.
We're not playing together at all.
Waiting for player to connect.
This is waiting for you.
Invite me again or?
Maybe we should just redo it.
Maybe.
Let's redo it.
Or maybe we have to do like the tutorial by ourselves.
This is waiting for player to connect.
Now, let's try out these traps.
Maybe we'll just skip the cutscene this time.
So you're at the menu.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's try this.
Your stream is there.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's I didn't mean to do it.
All right.
It says waiting for player.
Can you invite me again?
I guess I'm a pal.
See this steam is down.
Is it is it?
Wait steam is down.
Oh, come on, man.
What where we started?
What day is it today?
It's Wednesday.
I thought it was Tuesday.
That's so funny.
Well, I guess we could do the tutorial.
Wait, let me make sure my game is.
That's so funny that that happened right when we connected into a game.
That makes me very upset.
Somebody was just sitting there waiting to press the button.
All right.
Am I what what frame what graphics quality?
I think it's good.
Good.
So you guys just need to play Roblox instead.
I don't think I could convince her to play Roblox.
That would take an unbelievable amount of convincing.
But we already did.
Yeah, but a second time.
Didn't we do everything there was to do?
Didn't we play literally every game mode?
Hmm.
Yeah.
People saying Five Nights at Freddy's watch along.
But the plan was I was going to raid stir and stay in the call so I could get it in real time.
So we're not we're not quite ready for that.
I would just I would have just turned my stream on to make a grotto be shipping update
and then raid you.
So that's is that the stream?
Welcome to the corporate stream.
Is that what we're doing today?
No, we're playing orcs must die.
Maintenance only takes like 30 seconds, right?
Sometimes it takes like 30 minutes.
And you're the one who wanted to start this early.
What?
No, that's not true.
You you're the early Andy.
I started 6 p.m.
Pacific.
Let's do a podcast.
All right.
I mean, let's meet.
Let's do a little.
I mean, I have a long questionnaire for you.
I've been waiting for your judgment on a very particular situation.
Okay.
But what do you want from me?
You're going to have to stay with me the whole time because I feel like as I'm starting to explain this,
you're going to cut me off.
But I really want you to be the judge and and and like arbitrate the situation.
Okay.
Are you down?
No, but I think you're going to ask it anyways.
Okay.
You are you're like a judge in a court.
It is it is your decision to like figure out if I'm guilty or not.
I as an individual, I knew that there was a police sting operation going on,
you know, where they like be like the guy walks in the room and like buys prostitution.
Okay.
And the cops jump in the moment you like hand over the money and there's an exchange.
They run there.
You're arrested and they take you away.
Okay.
So I come in there knowing that it's a sting operation because I'm trying to I'm trying to get one over on the police.
I do the whole thing.
I hand over the money.
But as it's revealed later, I have no genitals.
So I end up in court.
Am I guilty of a crime?
If I'm like, oh, hey, babe, why don't you knock on my wood?
And then I don't even have any genitals.
I'm completely smooth.
You're the judge.
What do you say what what because the crime is is purchasing prostitution,
but I can't I can't but I'm giving her money for something that I don't have.
Well, hold on there though.
You you are the exchange.
The exchange has happened and you're you're exchanging for I'm being I would ask her for something very specifically requiring the having genitals part.
I'm just being nice and not going into explicit detail because I know there's a lot of like six-year-olds here.
But all right, but but okay, but your intent was not oh come over and like play cards.
Your intent was in a sexual nature.
Is that incorrect?
Yeah.
But I can't.
I'm a smoothie.
Okay.
Well, I'm not I'm not a judge.
So I don't think I can give you an answer here.
But I wonder if intent would be a case here.
I have no idea.
I'm not a fucking lawyer.
I thought you went to law school.
Disturbered.
I've been wondering about that for a while.
I don't know.
I don't know what the answer to that question is.
Well, if the answer is no, then could you countersue?
Who is countersuing you?
No, I'm countersuing because you get brought to court and like you get arrested for like something like a crime.
You didn't commit.
What's your diet like the last few months?
My diet?
Yeah, are you getting enough like B vitamins?
I started I started doing fasting again.
I'm on attempt number two, two meal a day.
You're getting like all your B vitamins, right?
And like vitamin like C and E.
No, no, I'm I'm eating like nothing.
Okay.
Like literally I haven't eaten anything in like two weeks.
You should probably consume some food.
I would recommend a nice balanced salad with maybe some lean protein.
Maybe a turkey.
Maybe some fish on it or something.
Well, not on the salad, but you know in general, do you eat breakfast?
No.
Start doing that.
Is that what you think this is?
How much?
You're the judge.
I come into court and you're like eating breakfast kid.
How much breakfast are you eating?
Are you getting like a bunch of whole grains because they're necessary?
No.
What about sunshine?
Are you out of the house?
At least you are.
I got a blood test and my doctor was like you need to take vitamin D.
And then I did and then she's like, okay, take less vitamin D.
Yeah, I would say going outside even for five minutes just to let the sun hit you in the face for five minutes is something everybody should be doing.
I do I go outside.
Okay.
So yeah, I've ruled go outside and eat guess it will be vitamins.
That's what I'm okay.
So I don't go to prison.
I didn't say that touch grass.
All right.
Is or is it back up the steam back up?
It's not it's not unfortunately shit.
We're gonna we're gonna have to talk to each other.
Oh, no, you're gonna have to like talk unfiltered for more than 10 minutes.
I'll be unfiltered.
Also, you know, what are you doing?
What are you doing for fun nowadays?
You know, and the nice day out.
Oh, no, I got a topic for you.
Listen to this.
Okay.
So you're in the kind of the art world.
You're an artist.
Yeah, do you know what I started doing recently?
Art I guess based on that.
You started art recently.
Oh, what kind pottery close like?
Like clay.
Yeah, like like clay shaping.
I have been molding clay and just kind of messing around making like little creatures
and objects and stuff.
That's so you what that's very you creatures.
How are the creatures you have any creatures you can show off like on cam you got a creature
you can grab I could I could get a creature right now.
Could you yeah, you want me to get a creature.
I'll be right back.
So for a lot of like give me one sec.
A lot of troubled young children around Jerma's age.
They all by the way Roger Rabbit.
I just want to make sure that it's very clear to that you are no longer coming through my
stream.
So however, you want to do that.
I just want to make sure that's because every time I walk away, you're walking away for
that long.
No for like maybe 30 seconds.
Okay.
Well, you've been explaining this for like 30 seconds.
So yeah, but it just you know, you're not going to come through my stream.
Okay, he's not coming through.
Nobody can hear him.
All right, I'll be right back.
Okay, I'm back.
I'm back.
Oh shit.
I just like broke it.
What did you look what you did?
Look what you just did.
Look at you just did this.
I did this I walked in here and I sat down and I heard I was rushing because I thought
you would make being weird.
They wait.
I wasn't I mute it.
Yeah, but I don't know you're I don't want you to be weird on your stream either.
Oh, yeah, and like like do another jump scare on your stream somehow.
All right.
Here we go.
You ready?
Are you ready to see one of the creatures?
I'm ready.
I broke him.
He's not supposed to look like this.
Hold on it.
I have 160 he had wings and I accidentally ripped him off.
He's like a I don't know.
What the hell is that?
It's not a creature.
It's not painted yet and it's not even fully sculpted.
They didn't even see the texture.
You didn't even see the texture.
This is just a prototype.
It's a prototype.
It looks like Jar Jar Binks.
What doesn't you look very happy in the picture.
I took to show my stream.
I've never seen you smile this much or have this much joy.
So I'm glad you found a hobby that really works for you.
What's his name?
I didn't well, I can't name him until I put the wings back on.
I accidentally ripped his legs off too.
Oh wait, there's another let me get another one.
This one.
This was just a prototype.
Hold on.
There's more.
Oh, hey guys.
Did he leave me unmuted when he walked away?
I'm going to tell you about my giblets.
Okay, he did.
I am over.
I just dream with anyone else where he's like I need to be like
I need to show caution when he plays with like Vinny.
Is it like oh dude like I am I'm going to get up.
I can't I can't let him like talk to my chat.
What is he saying?
What's he doing?
Stop stop it.
Stop it.
What ready?
Let me show some more.
I'm ready.
This was the all right.
Let me show this.
This is like a kind of like a ghost or something.
Do you like it?
So what is a ghost that one doesn't look like anything is it is
like they see that it's a mouth you see it look there's a side
profile.
He's going I I like the other one.
I can't I I can't understand this one.
You can't see this.
Oh, I I kind of see it now.
Okay.
What about making beehives?
I might make some bees the golf ball, dude.
Shut up.
I'm a golf ball.
This is the start of a kind of a half rhinoceros half-elephant
creature started his head.
Why am I taking he's going like this is a.
The start of a kind of like a bird like a weird like duck or
something.
This is his mouth.
I'm going to put big eyes on top and he's going like, okay,
that one that one also doesn't it's like very nice shapes
and contours, but doesn't look like a bird.
It's not done looking anything.
This is the head.
This is literally the face.
I made the face like the head.
Do you have like a kiln in your house?
No, this is this this stuff is this air dry.
Some of this is air dry or what some of it's not you didn't
say how can you can't see the ghost?
Yeah, you can.
It's just not close enough.
I just like burp with the mic.
What were those things that growing up as kids where you
like threw them on the ground and they were all they were
all like monsters like that.
There's a whole game for it.
It's kind of like pogs, but there was like little creature
figures or something.
This could be a pineapple.
I don't know.
I don't remember this could be a pineapple and sometimes hey
those of you artists out there sometimes you start with an
idea crazy and it can turn it can turn into something else
do a creature sculpting stream.
Only if sir does it with me a crew.
I'll do it with you a hundred percent.
I just I actually don't want to do with you.
Okay, probably do that.
I mean, I'm kind of artistic and I could I could probably
meet you halfway on that.
Would you actually want to like you want to do like a
creature craft off?
Yeah, I mean I got a little bit of experience on you, man.
I mean, I'll make something that looks like something you
either do.
Okay.
Hold on crazy crazy bone crafting session.
Hold on a second.
You think you're going to do better than the rhinoceros
elephant?
I mean artists objective and beauty is in the eye of the
beholder, but I think I think I can beat that.
Okay, he's cute.
That one.
I like that one a lot more than the ghost say you didn't
even give it a chance and it's not even done.
Can you see the texturing that I did?
Have you painted any of them?
Hard to see the texture.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I sat there and individually put little like little
bubbles on all over him.
There's this more too, but kind of just hard types.
This sounds this is great.
This sounds like this is being on the toilet for you, but
like without being in the bathroom like it's relaxing.
You can just take your time with your craft.
You don't have to like you don't have to be on the
toilet.
But why do I have to what would you but why does what
does that matter?
Wait, say everything you just said one more time.
We're playing Elden Ring.
You were saying that like your most relaxed time is
when you're on there's nothing else to do.
You're in the bathroom 45.
None of those Ember your 45 minutes on the toilet 985.
Oh, no, for sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, this is like this is like pooping but it has like
a better outcome.
I'm going to do so much crazy stuff to I'm going to like
I don't know.
I'm just saying it.
You know, I'm one of those people that makes like 15
different heads of various shapes and then you're going
to go any bigger.
I want to get a little original.
I want a German original signed.
I'm going to put it in a vault.
I want to make like a big building and have like a
bunch of these like weird creatures is hanging out in
front of it.
But if you want it you want to put it in the vault you
can.
Hold on this comment.
So I'm saying I'm ignoring ignoring I ignored you
someone in your chat said stir remembers what Jerma
says and it's awkward bringing it up because you
don't know.
Like what is he talking about the bathroom?
I just I sometimes like audio comes in this way and
then just like goes out that way and it's just it's
just gone and I it depends or sometimes I'll just
talk and let me okay.
Let me ask you a question mister.
Let me get this on you.
So you asked me a question in court.
I'm asking you a question in court now.
How many words do you think you have said recorded
what why is this being brought before a judge
because the reason why I get system the reason why
I have so much time remembering things is because
I feel like I I say so many things every day and
I'm recording so much like like 90% of it is you
can just throw it out.
No, it's just like it's like millions and millions
of sentences over like 15 years to 12 years,
whatever it's been on like YouTube and Twitch and
stuff.
No, no, I mean like on a grand scale.
I agree that I forget most of the things I say on
stream even when people bring it up like two days
late and that's the judgment right there.
Thank you very much.
You can go home now but like things that like
someone says to me or that I say to someone like
conversations with like a real human.
I'll remember that because you know, like I respect
you and well, I remember about major things that
I talked but like just random just stuff that we
just bring up on a regular kind of daily basis
sometimes just gone and I feel like shitting for
45 minutes a major part of your life.
Well, I know I knew that what I'm talking about
but you but you but I knew that I did that I know
that I use the bathroom for a long period but you
were equating it to like crafting creatures and
I was sitting there for a second going it's not
I had to connect that first.
Well, like wasn't this recently to that like you
had like your family was in town or something you
went out for like a big fancy dinner like everyone
got all dressed up and you got up to go to the
bathroom and you were gone just like the whole
night.
No, yeah, like before you went to the bathroom you
like dug in your backpack that you brought like
you're in a you're like a suit in a nice restaurant
you dug in your backpack and had all your toys
and stuff to like keep you entertained you picked
out an iPad and you were just gone for two hours
in the bathroom.
No, this this is this is not a real I don't know
there was a squeaky toy in it to it like everything
you could possibly need for a moment really like
I'm going to get bored at dinner.
You told me that you were not going to bring up
the squeaky toys that I like to have you I'm going
to talk to you off stream about this because I
my backpack of squeaky toys is something that you
said we weren't going to be discussing ever.
But now we're going to it seemed like appropriate
to bring up considering you were pretending to not
remember you're looking kind of big by the way.
What do you mean?
No fuck off.
Are you serious?
Well, have you been making your webcam bigger?
I mean it's bigger than yours.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm making sure no, it's not going to be like that.
Is it webcam bigger?
Well, like I'm trying to like react to what you're
doing and you're like I should be the prominent
focus of the fucking what's going on.
I don't think so.
I just trying to make sure that I have my webcam is
bigger than yours.
I thought you were doing a small webcam.
That's I just want to make sure I was bigger than
it.
Steam up steam is up.
Imagine sitting on the imagine you go into the bathroom
and somebody's playing with dog toys.
Well, you wouldn't see him.
You just hear like squeaking coming from like one
of the stalls like childlike laughter.
All right, let's go for it.
Hey, that was kind of fun.
That was cool.
Yeah.
Well, I started a new hobby recently.
Let's play let's play work.
Most I did you wait.
What are you?
Is this a mine's not mine's not like cool.
Who cares?
It's probably cool.
New hobbies are always interesting.
What are you talking about?
I started I bought some roller blades.
How is that not cool?
Is that is that cool or not?
Cool.
I feel like roller blades are the most not cool thing
you can wear.
No, I don't think so.
It's like a fun outdoor activity where you're going
to take like a little bit of a skill.
Yes, I've been outside.
I think a lot of your ass.
No, that's cool.
I do not ever doubt something that you're doing.
And if it's like cool or not, do you want to do it?
Yeah, then it's then it's cool.
You understand?
Yeah.
Okay, I think we can play.
I'm ready.
Oh, there's no audio home.
Do we have audio?
Yes.
Yeah.
All right.
We do we need to see this these children born with the
ability.
We saw this already.
Rift magic.
We saw skip skip how powerful he was.
All right.
So orcs must die three.
They say this is the third in the series, but it's actually
the fourth or the fifth or maybe even the sixth.
We turn this up.
That rift is different.
Quickly get trapped placed and stay on the move.
Okay, so we have you want help with the basics.
How do we hear her?
Is what it's asking me to ask you that?
Yeah, I think it's just give me like a quick rundown.
Let's try out these traps for real.
Okay, roll over enemies or gear to learn more.
Okay.
I think it just works like all the other ones, right?
Yeah.
I wonder if we share currency though.
Okay, back to back to basics.
Okay, so I've got the spike wall and the spike ground.
On my loadout right now.
I think that's all we can use.
All right.
Oh, I can use the bow too.
We got like a whole inventory to buy stuff.
There's someone talking to me.
All right.
Do you have 1400 or do we share?
I have 2000.
Okay, so we don't share.
I'm going to put two here on the mini map.
I can see where you are and then I'm going to go one right
down the middle here and then one right down the middle there
and I'm out of money.
Good luck.
It's up.
It's up to you.
Okay, I'm doing spike walls.
The hordes coming when you press G.
Oh, so we okay.
I went out on like a time limit.
Is there a reload?
No.
All right.
Let's just do it.
There's like a slow moving projectile and a fast moving
projectile.
Enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
They've broken through a gate.
Good.
Oh, it's mouse scroll to it's easy to switch that way.
Now it's too loud.
I'll fix it in like an hour.
I wonder if you can pull aggro and make them walk over it
too.
Why are you not talking?
My game FPS is really low.
I'm sorry.
I know that like in the play-by-play the minute-by-minute
I was supposed to make a joke right now.
I'm sorry.
More enemies all the way.
Do you forgive me?
Yeah, I do.
Okay, I'm going to fill this up.
So what up?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, it's the tutorial, you know, it'll be fine.
We just said roller skating is not cool.
I was watching a whole video about how not cool
roller skating is on the break.
Nice job.
I'm curious actually because a lot of the like roller skating
isn't cool is like very much like a 90s thing.
We're like where all the extreme sports were popular.
So like if someone missed out on the 90s because they were
just like in a black void before being born, but I think
it's roller skating on roller skating would be given they
didn't get the whole like smear campaign that skateboarding
put on roller skates.
Well, there's a roller blading and roller skating, right?
I mean, they're basically the same, but are you talking
about the four kind of the two and then two two in the
front and two in the back or you mean like the blade like
roller blade in line skates there in in line.
Okay, so like yeah, so we're talking about in line skating
and yeah, that's I think that is pretty synonymous with
being cool.
I think you're fine.
I gotta be cool and even if it was roller skates.
I think I think they're making a comeback roller skates.
There's a whole bunch of like weird roller derby things
that are like guys.
Let's go fucking let's derby it up.
Is that something you're are you into the idea of kind of
doing like a roller derby thing?
No, no, I'm not.
Okay, but I know I know that it's like I've seen more
and more of it and certainly Austin has a lot of weird
stuff like that.
Vegas probably has a lot of it.
I don't know.
There's a lot of like weird hobbies.
Yeah, I would imagine I bet there is I think you need
to unleash the horde and doing it a good thing.
We're on like baby mode.
We're on the I don't think we can even select a higher
difficulty.
I just did the regular one.
But imagine how badass you'd look pulling up to Jerma's
house and skidding to a stop and roller blades seriously
badass.
I'm imagining you doing that and then you go like whoa.
All right, dude, let's go get something to eat and I'm
like hold up and I have to take my skates off for 40
minutes.
I'm imagining you doing the big like going super fast
and doing the thing where you go inside and I kind of
do the kind of spin out thing.
Yeah, but you were going a little too fast and you have
to do like the run in place kind of thing while you're
falling and you fall fall fall fall running running
running and then you go right to the grass.
Okay, but what if I like didn't fall and then I just
closed the door?
You're sending some mixed messages.
Is it cool?
Or is it not cool?
That is like super mixed message.
No, it is cool.
Wait upgrades upgrades, dude.
Yeah, I think you get to like buy new things.
Oh and like, yeah my your weapon might have a way to
unlock the next year.
I have to get 50 headshots with my bow.
Oh, we should probably figure this out then because we
don't want to upgrade the same stuff.
I'm upgrading my bow or just upgrades complete milestones
to unlock a unique upgrade.
Okay, blade staff.
I kind of like this kind of confused reduce mana cost.
I just I went all in on this.
I don't know if that's stupid idea.
It seems like everything has its own amount upgrade
points.
I used everything on my bow and I still had more for
the other traps.
I went all in on the weapon.
Okay.
I mean, yeah, I skipped the tutorial was that's the
worst weapon.
That's all right.
What's your favorite kind of meat?
Harami skirt steak.
I like brisket.
Brisket is good.
On that note, I have a good question.
If you could have the animalistic trait from one
animal, what would it be?
That's interesting.
I mean, the easiest thing is say lion because you'd
be super strong and fast, but I don't know I maybe
like chimpanzee.
I got a good one.
I was thinking about this long and hard and I have
a really good one.
The male anglerfish explain specifically they attached
to a female anglerfish and they just sort of become
part of their body.
They sort of like meld into the female and they're
almost like a parasite because at a certain point
they just sort of like absorb into their body.
Well, I'd be a chimpanzee because they can like jump
around fast and they're like very noble.
They're very noble.
No chimpanzees like known for ripping people's
faces off.
Very noble.
What's the most noble animal do you think?
We didn't even put traps down.
It took two seconds.
The most noble animal noble as in like born to a
noble family or like, I don't know.
Elephant.
Okay.
Oh, he just went.
I screwed that up.
Oh, there's another door.
Oh, no one was coming out of it yet.
It's just you want me to focus on this one.
Yeah, I'm so bad at this.
Hey be nice to yourself, you know, that's true.
That's right.
You're a lot better at this than you are at sculpting.
We do it.
Okay over there enjoy your roller skating.
I mean as long as you enjoy it, but you made a
competitive.
That was you when you said that I wouldn't be able
to out sculpt your Rhino.
I was kidding though.
I was a little jab.
That wasn't real.
Oh, mine was a jab too.
Okay, we're cool.
We're good.
They're not coming from here anymore.
Okay, mine are getting through.
They actually
a little bit.
Sword is the worst weapon in the game.
What are you talking about?
But there's a sword.
That's what I told you.
I was upgrading it.
I want a swordy look.
Yeah, it's a I got three upgrades in it.
I like it.
Remember this is a spear.
It's kind of both isn't it?
Maybe it is a spear.
You're right.
It's a glaive.
Yeah.
Did you press G?
I did.
I wasn't I was adjusting my settings.
Webcam better not be bigger than mine.
Okay, I can't I'll tap and make that joke anymore.
Wow, that is a lot of drop.
This is pretty fun.
I can see how this is just the beginning.
This is just baby mode.
So you explore I was very very confused and you tried to explain this to me before we started but
so they did orcs must die one and two
and then they made like
a shitload of other games that were not orcs must die one.
I we played one of them together once.
I can't remember what it was actually called.
Yeah, it was like
orcs must die like forever
and it was a mobile game
and it was meant to be a live service forever
and it was not good
and then I think they tried something like that again.
But orcs must die to is a great game.
So we were excited first one the first couple were good.
Yeah, right.
Remember looks like you need some help over here.
Oh sick.
Is that the blade of unrelenting?
Wow game was strongest weapon in the game.
The game was a stadia exclusive for a while.
Oh that too.
That too.
Yes.
Stadia
this is it's so wild.
Oh just how fast that came out and how fast it went away.
Yeah, did you own a stadia?
I mean stadia came out.
It's called Xbox game pass and it's awesome.
Like that's like the actual stadia
in my opinion.
Play it.
You can play shit on the cloud.
It's just to me that was that's where it where it evolved into
or can you tell me more?
I know it's like a meme that I talk about Xbox game.
Every time we have played a game together like the last four
times you've brought it up.
I know I know and people like not this shit again.
Shut the fuck up.
I know I know I know that's why I'm not going to say anything.
But if I were to say anything it would like this fortnight
dance five star or five skull.
Sorry.
All right.
What about some of these other there's the tar trap.
There is the gravity pillar.
There is I didn't see it.
You could just unlock you can just like user skulls to unlock
stuff.
Seems like a lot of things.
There are a lot of things you're using the broadsword sprays
aloe acid fountain damaging enemies and applying acid.
Maybe I'm going to think I'm going to get the acid plate.
I'm going to try the wizard staff.
Wait, were you using the wizard staff?
I am using the blade staff.
Okay, there's a broadsword broadsword looks pretty cool.
Mom.
He got the cool one.
I did.
Wait, can I not?
Oh, it's six.
That's not fair.
I think I'm already he doesn't realize they have this on Roblox.
That's why we should we just go play Roblox.
That's not what we're playing today.
Only the oldest living warmage can open riffs.
Wouldn't that mean?
Yes, Kelsey.
The oldest is master Cygnus if he is still alive.
Why would master decide on my upgrades?
I didn't take anything.
We didn't pick any upgrades.
No riffs provide magic.
This magic is not a positive force.
All right.
So how big is the acid trap?
I must travel elsewhere for answers.
So they can only she takes a vacation.
It's cool.
Can they come from the other side over there on the top middle?
No, so they only can come from here.
Yeah, the mini map shows the one exclamation point at the moment.
I'm doing I only have enough to do acid and then I'll maybe slow them down.
You can do whatever you want.
I did it.
I'm ready.
Now's the time.
We want roblox.
Enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
You hold two weapons.
You have like the staff and the gun.
Yeah, it is treated as if it is just an item flux.
So you can probably have up to as many as you want.
You're just slaying.
You're getting some kills too.
I wonder if we can turn up the difficulty because we are kind of destroying this.
Yeah.
Yeah, those are cobalt.
We say that now, but we'll see.
I was kind of born for this.
It is Wednesday after all.
Yep.
I was sparkle on.
You're letting a few through.
I was getting another acid spewer.
Let me see you.
Did you?
Oh, no, you didn't do anything.
You didn't buy anything, right?
I didn't I didn't buy anything.
You like the strategy here?
They're coming from the other door now.
Exclusively the other door.
Oh, it would be nice for you to say that.
Like I mean more than a minute ago.
They haven't come yet.
More enemies on the way elsewhere.
You're just like you're taking all the kills.
I'm not going to get any experience.
I can't buy anything.
Well, I put like I almost fully upgraded this thing.
I just you're on your unstoppable.
Well, let's turn it up to hard mode.
How do they stop you?
You're getting kills.
Oh, you're how are you not doing the getting mom?
I think they're going to come from both probably.
Yeah, both.
You want me to stay over here?
Do you want to?
I don't know.
We'll adapt you are stir.
Look at that.
Like the parkour you just did.
He just press jump once.
I'm shooting him from here, dude.
Nice.
We're really doing it.
Oh my God.
All right.
This right click on this weapon is very good.
It's incredible.
Yeah.
Well, you got mana.
Okay.
I think they're just coming from over here now.
Oh, I missed my grenades launching over there correctly.
Yeah.
These orcs should go another way.
That sounded like an angry bird.
Oops.
Oh, sir.
Shoot over here.
I was kind of tunnel visioned.
What?
Maybe maybe we got to stay on easy.
I thought yeah, you told me they were only coming from the other side.
I lied.
Yeah.
That's not very fucking nice.
So, oh my God, you can spam that.
How'd you enjoy talking to me about playing POE for a whole week
and then not playing?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on a minute.
Excuse me.
I hit you up two different times.
Yeah.
And you were not available.
You're not ready.
Yes, it is.
I believe I believe I believe your exact phrasing was
sorry.
I haven't slept in three days.
You said I'll play tomorrow and I was like, yeah, I'm going to bed.
I'll see you then.
Well, I but I asked you if you want to play over the weekend
and you didn't say anything and then you said sorry.
I was asleep for three days or I haven't slept in three days.
You ghosted me for like like a week.
But say that again.
That's simply not true.
Sting interesting.
And then I asked I was like, oh man, but like I want to it's
a complicated game.
I kind of need some help figuring it out.
And you said what was it?
I believe it was.
Oh, no, I'm not going to give you that much info.
Like it's you'll just like you'll figure it out.
What you said you were going to play with Holly.
Yeah, we wanted to a guide.
Okay, well there.
Drama.
But honestly though, I do I'm like interested in playing it.
I I opened it and I looked at I looked at like what it was
and I got to I got to the point where you have like skill
gems and then I saw the gigantic I got to the gigantic spider
web though.
I just looked at like the spider web of points to put in.
I was like it was so you got you got to level two.
Yep.
I was waiting looking for my guide my guide.
I didn't sleep for like a week and I've been playing.
I was there.
I've been playing.
I don't know how this I don't know how this is on me.
This is all you I asked you for help and you said you would
didn't want to give it to me.
I say I like acid the acid.
Yes, it's pretty good.
Okay.
Are we are we going are we done?
Yeah, let's keep going.
I don't think we can even do the higher difficulty.
I don't think it's like unlocked or anything.
I think we have to beat like the game on the regular difficulty.
So do you think the sources will be back soon?
We're doing pretty well.
We allowed to select difficulty before we started.
Yeah, but I think there's three difficulties though.
One two, three three was great out to know all the answers.
Then tell me why glue does it stick to the inside run to we
are on two.
Okay, there are passive things as well.
This is a passive trinket.
Somebody said I hope steam goes down again and the person up
for five minutes.
Okay, so we got I am going to get this side situated.
Okay, but do you see you see the top mini map now?
There's like no one coming from the side yet.
Yes, but I feel like I want to prepare eventually.
Okay, you can save your money.
I'm going to just go like you're a grouchy old man.
I'm fine.
Okay, you didn't have to go there.
But okay, I'm going to have a cool.
No, I think I'm kind of cool young hip guy with my rollerblades.
Somebody was saying that about me not you.
I was responding.
We kind of said it out loud to me.
You're going to you're going to have to watch your your tone.
I'm fragile.
I don't I think you're pretty like strong.
Wait, so does Holly talk in my chat because you won't see it.
That's kind of sad.
All these one of your mugs.
Yeah, you must and you're not going to even mod me.
Yeah, I unmodded literally everybody great packed.
Yeah, I know, but you've okay.
You know what?
You know, how many don't unmod me on yours.
I've been I was grandfathered in.
Yeah, I wouldn't I wouldn't unmod you.
I trust you like if I walk away from my computer.
Hey, but wait, I won't have to mute you.
Who has a longer sub to the other person?
Fuck, I think it is.
I remember this being a thing.
Who has a longer sub to well, well to counter that.
I am the longest sub to my own channel.
I have the first subscriber badge to my own channel.
Everybody has that.
No, they don't type in your chat.
You don't have it.
What's this guys waiting?
Nope doesn't have it.
I mean don't have it.
Mine has a founder a founder like, you know, when like someone
is the like it keeps track of the first 50 subs to a channel
are yeah, I'm I'm the fifth subscriber to my channel.
How is that possible?
Because isn't every streamer just automatically has the sub
badge of their own channel.
Exactly.
So how does that make any sense?
What you can't even subscribe to yourself.
Yeah.
So what happened?
I'm I paid for my own subscription to my own channel for like
three years.
What so I've been subscribed to me longer than you've been
subscribed to me.
So I'm my number one best enemy.
That's true.
I know Twitch like you used to not be able to use your own
emotes unless you were subscribed to your own channel
like a long long long time ago way.
Wait.
Yeah, right.
When they when they switched over so I just so I paid Twitch
to let me use my emotes and now it's funny because they
added the like you're you're your own first subscriber bad.
Oh the misery don't trust anyone not even yourself honestly.
Yeah, and you know how many times I've like left reminders
for myself and I just fucking forgot about them.
Every time I said, oh I need to like oh, yeah, I really
should like put away that fucking spaghetti and I don't
do it and I say I'm going to do it.
I'm going to trust you.
All right, they're coming from both.
What a what a what a difficult life that must be what
I don't even trust myself.
What to put spaghetti away.
Well, I got to put the spaghetti where I'm like, oh you
piece of shit.
You're not going to do it.
Are you you ain't food that sat out for like a week.
You have no say in this one day and also it was my wife
that left it out.
So not me.
Oh, it's so you so now we're you're deflecting now.
It's not.
What do you mean?
All right, so now now now every ounce of the anguish in
my life is her more enemies all the way Jesus.
I think you can handle that.
I'll stay over here.
Honestly, it's not going well.
Really?
Okay.
These little runners don't have a giant cleave sword.
I watched the right side though, because they're actually
going to probably start going that way in a minute when
they do.
Yes, I did.
Have I Pete?
Yeah, I know someone's gonna say I do have to look down
at my keyboard to press five.
All right, stop.
Somebody was thinking it.
That's sad.
So good on the left.
Yep, man.
It'd be pretty sad to be classified as a light work.
What like you just like smaller?
Yeah, like oh shit.
Oh shit.
I thought you were reacting to what would happen if you
were classified as a light or I'm reacting to the light
works getting past us.
All right.
Next wave coming next wave get it get your head in the
game.
My hands in the game has the game.
I think we just stay in the middle.
Just stay we should just be staying here.
That makes a lot of sense.
I mean, I know this looks like shit, but it's it's
practicality not for looks.
I don't think they walk through here.
They don't walk through the middle where you're putting
the trap.
Left side is clear.
I believe it truly epic.
All right.
So let me sell all this then because if they're not
going to come through here that maybe they will eventually
or no, I just know you can see the path they're taking
on.
Oh my goodness.
You can.
All right.
Hold on.
Yeah, you're trying it.
You're Copia miming.
I am three of those there.
Yeah.
But anyway, Holly was saying that she is extremely sad
that you didn't play Pue really looking forward to
I was too and it's kind of messed up.
Maybe don't maybe don't ghost me if you don't ghost me
for like five days.
Okay, so it's like it's totally okay for you to do a
roblox birthday party when we only had a we had prior
plans again.
Totally okay again.
I just want to make this really clear you.
I'm sorry, but somebody's birthday party is going to
take priority.
That's a little selfish thing.
Who whose birthday was it?
Are you asking?
They was it.
Yes.
Oh local e-clown.
It was their birthday.
Oh, just push that right back at you.
Didn't I which mod just like told you that?
Nope.
There was not enough time because you know, you know
about stream delay.
It wasn't enough time.
Aren't you on like quantum?
You're not in quantum yet.
I switched to quantum my mods responding to things that
I haven't even done yet.
They're like dude.
No, no, no, don't say that.
That's too much.
Well, I think they caught me a couple of times already
the stream were like I was gonna I'm sorry.
Did that thing happen to where I've just I'm not hearing
anything.
I'm sorry.
It happens a lot but like you.
No problem.
What's the best class in POE?
That's for what?
I don't know room clear.
I don't know.
I don't know man.
What do you what do you play in POE?
Can you even answer that?
There's like 5,000 classes in POE isn't there?
There are actually there's nine ascendancies.
Yeah, or nine classes.
Or there's a lot.
They're all good at different stuff.
I think which is probably still the most played is POE 2.
When is it coming out?
Exile con which is going to announce POE 2 stuff is the
end of July.
Is it worth waiting for that or is it better just to play
like I mean, I kind of want to play it my take would have
been wait, but like if you're really interested it's I think
POE 2 is going to be different enough that you'll be able to
like you'll get like two different play experiences of
playing now and playing later.
You're not really going to like miss.
Yeah, or I don't know.
I don't know how to phrase it.
They're different enough is set up to it's it's not an
Overwatch 2 situation where it's not going to be any
different at all.
If there's there's slated a lot of change and it's a whole
completely different campaign.
So like you played through this campaign.
It would be very different if you played POE 2 later.
Yes, I'll play it then I'll still play it.
Oh my God.
He remembered.
Yeah, I did.
I remembered your birthday.
When's my birthday?
August.
Yeah, okay.
So there we are.
Then you can't say that you cannot fight me on this one.
I'm not like googling.
My hands are up cops.
You got me.
I'm going to I'm just going to throw a guess out.
But I'm going to think for a second because you would have
done like a like drama drama stream of birthday a fun
and I'm just thinking if there was one.
I'm going to say May 4th.
Not even in the right fucking season.
Okay.
Oh man, you were.
Oh no, because you were coming at me.
That's Star Wars.
What?
That's not you.
May the 4th be with you.
That's Star Wars day.
Yeah, all I'm saying is but if you're going to come at me
with that kind of a
Hey, when's my birthday?
Then you better know my birthday.
You know what I mean?
You better know mine.
September.
I wonder if you were reading a chat room.
No, I'm remembering.
I'm remembering our long lasting friendship and all of
the birthdays that we shared together.
May 4th.
May the 4th be with you.
That's so funny.
All right.
What do you upgrade?
I don't know alchemist satchel.
I thought I upgraded.
I didn't I didn't have it.
With me.
So you got like a quick weapon differently.
Yeah, you just put on your loadout.
Where do you modify the loadout in the in the game?
Like when we're actually in the game?
It's B.
Okay.
Well, I'm ready.
I think yeah, you can do your loadout when before we get
the first wave.
Okay.
What's this title?
It's pretty bad.
We are not facing something new, but something very old.
Oh, how we've just been killing orcs and stuff.
No big deal.
Okay.
So what's the deal with these strange?
Oh, we can change their route with that new thing.
We got I'm going to leave that up to you because I that's
there's like math involved with that and game mechanics
and game awareness.
I'm going to leave that up to you.
Yeah, there's like math.
I'll be the blocker.
All right.
So what how do you want to handle this?
Do you want to block everybody from like this way so they
have to go up this did this staircase?
I feel like that's a good idea.
Thank you.
We can just block the stairs and then yeah, then they go
to the other stairs.
Okay, so they can't like walk around here.
Yeah, so I'm going to just focus on one stair.
Yeah, so then we just focus on the stairs and I'm going
to go like this.
I'm going to save my money and then we got out.
We got a teleporter.
There is a tip.
Where does it go?
It goes all the way to where we're defending the top of
the stairs.
It was a big staircase.
It's pretty big, but I think if we can keep people funneled
this way, we should be fine.
What did you do for your last birthday?
Okay, if you don't even remember how am I supposed to
remember when your birthday is I feel like I was a really
busy during that period like I was there's like just a
lot going on.
Yeah, it sounds like I get a pass and you know, I didn't
get a message from anybody on it though.
What I remember it's okay.
Sometimes we forget each other's you know, that's all right.
Let's just play.
Yeah, that's fine.
Let's go.
Open enemies are preparing to breach.
Whoa, that over seems bigger out here in the wild.
Oh, this guy remember if he hits you, he will stun you.
Done.
Okay.
I'm throwing these green potions.
Don't drink any.
Oh, I've been stunned.
I've been I've been stunned most dead yet.
They don't even have to like swing if they just walk on
you you get stunned.
I don't like that charge.
I'm gonna die.
Can I remind you?
I don't know.
I just auto revived here.
This is all your fault.
What is what is this difficulty curve?
Hey, why'd you do this?
They taught us how to play and now they're giving us the
real deal.
Okay, the leash is off as they say, okay, so they obviously
are going a little too fast.
So I mean, I'm gonna yeah, we should do some slow down
followed by more poison followed by I think that's all
right.
We just need to we need to stay in one spot.
We need to make sure they're like bullied at the door.
Okay, we're ready.
Right.
You know what here might as well.
All right, let's do it.
Okay, I think it's gonna be a lot of big ready and cleaner
killing them.
I'm killing them.
Wait, what are they getting in?
These little runners just got by me hair.
Nobody got by me.
How do you regenerate man?
It's just over time.
I think it does.
Oh shit.
There's many potions that kind of lie around and healing
potions.
I wonder how they do they spawn randomly or wonder I don't
know.
I think when probably random when you kill things.
All right.
Okay.
Look, I love streaming.
Do I have to wait a minute?
Do you have to have this the artifact out for it to heal
you or is it just I think it has a passive effect and you
can use it and it will heal.
Really?
Okay.
Oh, that's good to know.
Ooh, that's a good idea.
I'm gonna put this one here.
But then I don't have to walk that way.
I I would sell that.
Yeah, I'm here.
I got you.
Okay.
What?
Why don't we want them to be coming down like a really
narrow?
Which or is walking into this corner?
When they when enough of them come up here the ghost do
you see the ghost walking by?
Yeah, but when but when there's enough of them walking
they're gonna hit collision.
They're gonna have to spread out.
And we want them in a narrow narrow place.
That's it.
That's as narrow as it's going to be.
I'm saying is it if like a dozen orcs walk this way then
you owe me a thousand dollars.
Okay.
Well, I'm just saying that the barricade is like the most
expensive thing we can build right now.
And you put it you put it in the corner.
Runner.
You got to kill these little gobbos.
Yeah.
Watch out big guy.
No, you owe me a thousand dollars.
Wait one guy by me.
Wait, why do I I'm space?
I did a you and I didn't listen to anything that you said
you owe me.
You owe me a thousand dollars.
Why somebody went like they were walking like off the
traps like the right.
Okay.
Was that like was that a problem like such a problem that
we lost?
Tell me dude.
It's been like an hour and a half into the stream and you
haven't we haven't brought up like a food topic.
What's going on here?
A food a food.
Do you want to I know what's like you talk a lot about
sauces.
What's it?
What's a good sauce?
What's your favorite sauce right now?
Bingo blue cheese sauce.
Yeah, I would classify it as sauce not as a cheese.
Well like blue cheese sauce like it's blue cheese, but
it's also part of like that base for it.
What's what's the base?
I actually don't really know what is like in the blue
cheese sauce because blue cheese is obviously like blue
cheese crumbles.
But what is it?
What is it?
What's the basement?
Is it ranch?
I don't know if it's if it's ranch every time this milk
Oh, so you're allowed to talk about milk.
Okay, kind of weird.
You know what?
I'll tell you and I people are going to they might be
doubters in the chat and then that's all right.
You might be one yourself after I say this but a thin
crust pepperoni pizza with Tabasco sauce just like a
pool of it like a little pool of it on the side and a
pool of blue cheese on the side and you just smear that
shit all over it and take a bite.
It's going to change your entire life.
And I know people like it.
I'm just I know that that's you haven't seen the light
yet and don't want the light.
It was in blue cheese with Tabasco sauce.
It has to be specifically.
It's a specific that hold on we're going to lose.
Where's the where's our limit of how many people can
like go in before we lose at the top and then it starts
at 20.
All right.
We I got a lot of money.
So let's make sure we get this right.
Let's slow them down.
I agree.
I want them to be slugs coming in here.
I hear here come up here eat Buffalo wings known and
I thought you have money left.
I do if we did like a tarp.
It's all the way around this whole corner.
That's all I have.
Okay, that's all I got.
So so yeah, you were talking about dipping a sauce in
a sauce.
No, no, no.
What it sounded like for a slice of pepperoni pizza
and you get a little bit of Tabasco on it and then you
dunk that into the blue cheese like sauce.
There are not go on pizza.
Yes, of course.
I know question.
I know question mark question mark, but one day you're
going to do it just because like oh that fucking weirdo
on that like he clown like moron that I watched last
night and then your eyes are going to go through it and
you're going to go what happened?
How did I not know about this and then you will be
Officially a pepperoni pizza blue cheese Tabasco to
site.
Now that I understand like the whole combo all those
words just don't go together.
What German's been having like chat GBT make his food.
This was a good idea.
I'm just telling you one day someone's going to try it
and they're going to just like the tune efficient
pretzels and everyone's like, oh my god, dude.
What what wait what I haven't heard of this.
Is this all is this the thing I'm unaware of some of
you guys just really need to see the light and you
just won't and that's fine more for me.
Oh, if you jump while you're in the air, you do a
thing.
Maybe that's just a bow thing that I didn't know.
You can like float.
Yeah, you do like a ground pound.
We're just going.
I think we are just I guess so I wasn't ready.
Let's get that same concept over here.
There's some enzyme.
I don't know what it is.
It's something to do with the enzymes of the food
but like a pretzel stick into a fresh thing of
good tuna like solid albacore tuna.
It's just something about it the same thing with
the blue cheese Tabasco and pizza.
You know, there's some sort of enzyme that validates
your your bad taste.
No, how you have I'm going to make I'm going to
like make this I saw you licking your lips to the
dog food the other day.
That was a joke though.
We're talking about a piece of comedic work.
Not a real thought of mine.
So like laughing at the cars was awful a bit.
I don't actually think cars are funny.
No, I do.
Okay.
Making sure we're not like I think that heals you
too, by the way.
Yeah.
Oh, I got a stun.
That's good to know.
Yeah, but you can't give me shit for the car thing
when back in the old days of YouTube you were like
the king of the car go fast into like a wall joke.
I think I think cars are funny.
Okay.
Oh, so you weren't I just I was just bringing up
because you felt like really self-conscious about
Oh, no, they weren't on the same page.
Then I have some complex feelings that I think cars
are both funny and also I hate all cars and
I wish I could destroy them all.
Okay.
I'm getting this giant flip trap.
Ooh, mega boom barrel launcher.
Like Sanical.
I can't upgrade them.
Did I fully upgrade the acid duration?
What's the difference here?
Increased duration or increased melting duration?
What does that mean?
I don't know what the difference is.
I feel like this is the actual damage and this isn't
how long it sprays for.
Okay, I'm good.
I'm just going to keep shooting my bow.
There's also I think there's a refund all your upgrades.
It looks like it's some dumb choices.
I'm doing it.
What are you doing?
Oh, no, we skip.
Okay.
Nevermind.
I was going to refund all my upgrades.
And we go.
Oh, hey, hold on.
Lore, Lore.
Boss.
Known to all.
Oh, Master Cygnus taught my hero Maximilian.
Yes, he tried to teach your hero.
He was my teacher as well.
Didn't you turn evil for me?
Sorry sorceress.
What is not known is the story of his best friend.
The elf Vorwik.
Human and elf fought side-by-side the most talented
warm ages of the order before infighting forced the horde
into small factions.
They used massive traps and defeated the largest.
Yeah, I was taking it in.
Ages of their generation.
But when their final test came only one of them would pass.
We're getting new characters.
Maybe I know you're going to want to be the elf man, right?
I want I like elves in like in the same way that I like cars
that I think they're funny and stupid.
They shouldn't exist pain lightning staff or short swords.
I don't think we're probably not going to have a choice
and just to give us either one.
Oh, we're in the television.
Oh, I was going to say that.
Armies ever assembled.
I welcome it.
Friends sickness and thousand curious about what drives the orcs.
You must we need to think about this.
They're giving us 10,000.
Oh, well, we got the you can equip the legendary stuff now.
Definitely stubborn.
Oh, perhaps right.
It's not letting me drag them on nonetheless.
You probably need to.
Yeah, you have to like match for my strength.
Oh, they require two slots of magic.
Is that what is that large amounts of enemies?
Maybe it is two slots.
It says war scenarios only, which this is.
Oh, they're like ultimate shift one and shift two.
You always have them.
Oh, okay.
I guess.
Well, let's what where they come from.
They come from here.
We should probably do a block scenario.
What's the most efficient way to block this?
Just kind of go from here Ross or from like here to like here
or just wait till they get up to the stairs and just fight.
Yeah, fight on the bridge.
I guess we could just fight on the bridge.
Do you want to follow them through just one little zone on the bridge
like walk a couple of zones here?
I don't know, man.
It seems like a smart idea.
I'll do it.
So they have to walk through here here.
Okay, so then I'm going to give them with the getting with the poison.
Boom right here is where they will level.
I fucked it up is whatever.
Oh, I see.
Okay, so they're going to have to cross through there
and then they have to cross through here.
Go like this.
No better spot than this.
Okay, this is an Omega launcher, right?
Yeah, just send them into the lava.
Should I put one of these down too on the other side?
Do you move this back a little?
And I'll put one going the other direction.
Are you how can you move things?
Do you sell stuff at full value?
Why do I got to move mine?
Because I we should put another one right here, right?
Because they'll go like this is just I think this is in the way.
I think this is the only place we're going to be able to put one of these
like lobbers because I don't I don't know like I well,
I wonder if we need to put I'm selling your things.
Why are you selling my stuff?
I'm snaking them.
Oh, you're doing like the tower defense strat.
Okay, we should just do that again.
Just pull this thing back.
Let's just make them do another snake.
Then we'll go like this right here.
That's all I can afford right now.
Okay. Yeah, I'm out of money.
All right, let's go for it.
Am I okay?
That was weird.
I just did a full front flip and landed right on my back
and knocked the wind out of myself.
Waiting for a player.
I think it's a heel.
I fell.
What do you mean?
How?
What did you do?
Oh, you're good.
I'm coming.
But you fell too.
You jumped in.
Well, I just you couldn't resist because something like someone fell
and you had to fall in.
But mine was cooler than yours because I did a front flip.
Dude, this is like hell of a speed.
Oh, right.
What does the right click on this even do?
They can actually shoot at us.
I'm dying.
We'll pull back.
We can look at all this time we got.
Oh, Santa.
I got you.
Okay, we both did that again.
All right, question.
Watch out, big thumper coming through.
I want to see him go off.
I want to see him go after it happens.
Laugh like really hard.
Why did it not launch it?
It launched one of them like a little guy.
It did.
Yeah, I didn't see that.
Okay.
Well, we got some orcs to kill you.
Oh, what can you react?
I didn't see anything.
It's not happening on my screen there.
They've they have reached.
Where are you?
They're in the back here.
They're getting through.
Did you see it that time?
This one got lost.
Am I the only one being a tuber?
I'm trying to not lose.
I've been they're getting through do something about it.
Oh, heavy orcs.
It's kind of reminds me playing Dynasty Warriors.
One time I was playing Dynasty Warriors and just running around
just going like this.
I think I'm pretty sure I fell asleep doing it and I was still
pressing the button.
Target demographic right there.
And I woke up and it wasn't that long.
Probably was like maybe five seconds 10 seconds pops.
All these are traps up here.
You can pour them.
I loved that game.
That game was so fun, especially the first few.
I've never actually played one really.
Yeah, they're rich.
The first two or three were awesome.
I especially like the other first like five.
Which one was the best one?
They were always the best one.
Yeah, it was one of the early ones.
Are we keeping the same strategy gone?
We got more money.
Have you even seen this catapult shoot?
Do we need to do it?
I haven't seen it.
I think we might need to like tell it to fire.
I'm selling your stuff because they're why did you not make
it flush?
What I sold your two things.
You didn't make it flush.
I didn't flush it was not was an efficient use.
Oh, okay.
I built them in a panic because I can hop.
In this and use this thing.
I must feel like we should sell the launcher and just make
a longer s.
Yeah, honestly, I feel like that thing is not helping us
that much.
Have you used this thing one that I'm in this big like
cannon thing?
No, don't sell my can.
I want it.
Oh you that's what I mean.
You can sit in it.
Okay, you have to actually used it once launcher is strong.
How can we why we not doing it right?
I don't know.
I think it's like a you problem.
He's being such an affliction warlock right now.
Me or who I don't know.
I just read it.
What does that mean?
Can you catapult them from there?
I can take a look watch this.
Oh, dude, this is just like Helm's deep.
What a view you got.
All right.
These things are actually amazing.
That's gonna mentally scar me for years definitely should
make more of these because we could just we could sit
back and do this.
All right big guy coming in.
I hope this doesn't hurt our stuff.
Let's find out.
Is that like hurting my hurting like the doesn't look like
it did because this is this is a crazy amount of damage.
Honestly, we just put two of these side by side and hang
out.
Okay.
Would you got the money for one?
Not yet.
We will soon.
Yeah, you're cheating starting to get through.
Is that a ultimate or something you're doing?
That was the right click of the staff calls down a bunch
of beam.
It does use some mana.
Are those things cost 3000?
I'm on it.
I'm getting through.
I'm on it boss.
I have enough money to make another one.
I'm going to get out and I'm going to make you one.
Okay.
All right.
You good.
I'm dealing with these ogres.
I'm good.
Focus on yourself for one.
Is it too close?
I think it's a good spot.
Well, I still have let me do this too close.
Should I put it back like here?
But he can't he won't be able to see there's there's a
whole other platform back on the other side where we can
like kill all the guys in the beginning.
You know, I wish they put the big launcher then.
But over but over but over but over here but over here
but over here because we should just be double like
double teaming with these.
Yeah, I'll double team with you anytime.
Let's fucking go put it here.
Wait, it's I can't I gotta make sure it's the right way.
But it but it has to be like here because they won't
hear can't aim in the right direction.
Do you want this one?
Do you want the one on the bridge?
I want this one.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
What's your highest score in Papa's freeze area and
Papa's freeze area?
What more coin did I not speak clearly what pay attention
we have to get the book.
I'm paying attention.
How many people can play this at the same time?
I think 64.
It's not fair.
You can actually hit them from there.
All right.
It's almost time to put your attention on to the bridge.
Wait, one of them got knocked all the way up here to me.
It's time to focus on the bridge.
We got five big guys about to come through.
Okay, how are they getting up here?
I don't know.
I think we're getting launched here by the other launcher
little little.
Oh, I got him.
Oh, you're good.
Yeah, they are getting launched.
Dude, that thing I think is launching them the thing behind
us.
Yeah, it's it's launching them the whole way.
I'm going to go sell it.
I can't sell it.
Whoever built that's a moron.
They're overwhelming us.
Nice.
I got him.
That's that's the guys getting launched over.
Where's the fan art?
Oh, it's the title.
Where's the thunder?
You know what I'm talking about?
Hey guys, I need you to focus up.
We got five big guys coming in.
Focus up.
Coming.
I'm coming to help.
How?
Stop.
Dude, I'm gaming.
I have never reached this level.
What's your favorite game?
Dude, we've had this conversation and we just agree every time.
Isn't that boring?
It's like Diablo 2 Bloodborne, but actually it's Path of Exile.
Name me your top 10 games.
Do you think you are your favorites?
That's too hard.
I'm going to be thinking for like hours before I say some stupid shit
that I'm going to regret that everyone's going to quote me for years
because I said this one time on the stream stream that I said like
at my little pony ponies are forever is like my favorite.
Can you slowly tell me about what you had for breakfast this morning?
Slowly like very slow like do you have a little
Left over Jersey Mike's sandwich with some milk.
All right.
Wait, you drank you just you had a sub with milk.
You shut the fuck up.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What about my eating habits?
Oh dude, blue cheese is gross, man.
Fuck you.
Milk with a sub was muscle milk.
So I think that gives it a pass.
Yeah, I guess so.
Why don't I just do that?
All right.
Do what we need to figure out.
They're going to breach this.
So do we want them going around here like through here?
No, don't do that.
Look, you can you can pour these.
Okay.
Well, then we want it.
We want it over here.
No, because there's one on each side.
Okay.
Well, then we don't need it and then we need to figure out what to do
after they get through that my god, then maybe we should put some
tar down there.
Maybe we should go like this so we can start the snake again.
Is that are you okay with that?
So then they have to sign with that.
All right.
Go ready.
Get in your launcher.
When we're hitting these guys are getting like a hellwork
pack word logo.
Like what is this?
I honestly don't even know what words you just said.
Hey, what logo they make like printers and Hewlett Packard.
Something like that.
Yeah, Hewlett Packard.
What did you say?
I don't know.
Hell wart.
What did you say?
Hell, hell work Packard.
Hell, I don't even know.
I don't even know what I'm you.
Are you shooting your bombs?
I am.
I'm focusing on the bridge.
That didn't even hurt anybody.
What?
Okay.
Well, there's a lot of guys on the bridge.
Oh goodness.
Oh my goodness under control.
One little guy getting through nothing to do about it.
How do I do this?
How do I do this here in my mouth?
Dude, do we get do we get like an end of the game scorecard?
We get to compare each other and see who is more valuable.
Possible general electric logo.
Is that what it is?
That looks more like.
Oh, don't worry.
I've got you.
I'm clicking left click now.
Oh, you've launched one off.
Nice.
All right, this is the last wave.
All the orcs sound like bugleberry.
This is too big.
You can't put anything down.
So I guess we're just going to do.
I think I'm going to upgrade the slow trap thing.
I feel like it's really useful and with any points in it.
It'd be way down.
I'm liking the slow.
I'm just I'm just ready.
I don't I don't think these things are even a threat.
He's things innovating our castle.
Oh shit.
It's crack.
Crag has shown up to fight.
We should remove him quick.
Sable the traps.
Should we just go right and kill that thing right now?
Yeah, maybe we're kind of just going to let him walk all the way up here.
I'm aiming at him and I'm aiming my bombs.
I don't even know.
He's right there.
I missed.
I'm missing.
I got a direct hit.
Oh, he's he destroyed our thing.
Okay, I'm going to go fight Craig.
I will handle the enemies that come up through here and try to get through
the bridge.
You handle crack.
Crag is incoming.
Can we start bombing Crag?
I am hard to get in here with all these boogers.
I am currently bombing Crag.
People getting through no one important point enough for our perfect rating.
Four.
Yes.
Nice.
Okay, we got a we got a whole situation here pal.
That was actually kind of fun.
You got the heal thing.
I do.
You've got to be trolling mate.
They're gonna get through the gate.
I think I think if you just deal with those guys, I keep bombing.
I will try.
I think I upgraded this thing.
Upgrade it.
All right.
They are all done.
All the ones that got by are killed.
I can now make my way in front of you.
Clean up this walking off the edge and dying.
Why is there pathing making them go walk up?
No, I think that's there's the thing that's boosting them down there.
Have you noticed this is kind of just like home deep?
I think that's kind of the idea.
Inspiration.
What I think that's kind of the idea.
It seems like inspired by big, you know, one of the rings type stuff.
Okay, there's no ladders or anything.
That's a five-star.
Perfect.
All castles must be Helm's deep.
Yeah, I'm a five-star man.
All right, the tar trap.
This is good increases slow.
Absolutely more more.
I just put all my points into this.
So this thing's gonna be amazing.
I remember the ice amulet being cool.
I think we can probably swap for heroes now.
How many orcs does it take to break into this fucking base?
Why do they keep doing the same strategy?
Yeah, it's true.
You think that after like a thousand years orcs wouldn't just walk out of building anymore.
You think that they would develop some new type of way to attack a base or something?
Yeah, the walk at structure.
I don't think that's fair.
Every orc only gets to try once.
How are they gonna learn?
Well, that's what I'm saying that all the orcs collectively have not learned
that walking with a big sword or a big club is the way to do it.
Yeah, what is all this new stuff?
Orcs.
Hello, are we not going to talk about how this warwick guy is clearly in love with the
long-range multi shot ice attack?
No, that's me.
You can't copy me.
I'm playing ice shot.
Okay, this was Earthling weak against arcane and ice wrong against physical damage.
I like this loadout.
I can't shoot that fast.
It's not fair.
Yeah.
Well, maybe you need to get the upgrades.
Why did we I didn't we didn't put why did we both press the button?
I press the button.
I'm not scared.
I think this is we just if we just defended Helms deep.
I wonder how much the slowest now.
Wow, it even freezes them.
I think it freezes him now.
That was me using.
Oh shit.
Oh, yeah.
Oh wow.
You're right.
Oh dang it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh wait.
Are you freezing them?
No, that's you doing.
Oh, you're absolutely doing that.
That was a pretty good impression.
I think I could do a pretty good bugleberry.
Oh, yes.
Better than how many cards you have.
I think that's pretty close.
You want to be in charge of building the block?
Yeah, I'll just I'm just building barricades.
Actually, let me complete it.
All right, probably a good idea.
I'm out of money.
All right, I got some cash.
Do you think you could drink this slime?
Might kill you.
The Earth Lord.
Watch out.
It's an Earth Lord.
Oh, no.
But you you knew you were doing this because you were shooting at people.
Yeah.
Oh, you were messing around with me.
That thing's actually kind of fun.
It's got like, you know, like a ice floor Nova, too.
Yeah.
I remember from the older games being like one of the best things you could get.
Yeah, that's why I'm free some work.
Yeah.
I'm usually like the ice guy.
So like how are you doing that?
You can do like fire or something.
You're like a you're just like the fire guy.
I mean like I are okay.
We're gonna have to I'm gonna have to refund all my upgrades.
I mean, you know, I'm like usually like ice like I like like ice chill
and water and I usually I'm gonna be ice.
I think I don't think I don't think that's actually true.
But you do if you if you need to pick an elemental wizard, honest honest,
you're you're joking about being an ice person.
What is your elemental wizard casting bowling balls?
Also, you're an earth vendor.
Oh, I'm a bowling ball vendor and bowling balls are made of earth.
Bowling balls are made out of a synthetic material.
You know, you know, listen to this, you know, do you know that bowling balls?
I'm gonna fucking blow everybody's mind that has not seen that one YouTube video.
Okay, do you know when you think of a bowling ball?
What what is a bowling ball?
Like what is it?
It's just like a big ball, right?
Yeah.
No, there is shit.
Let me fucking talk.
There is there's shit in the middle of a bowling ball.
There's a core.
There is a bowling ball core that is different for every bowling ball.
It's like this weird metal core that's weirdly shaped depending on what kind of ball you want.
It's crazy.
I did not know that.
I thought it was just a big ball of like like plastic or whatever.
They are next.
Next thing you're going to tell me is that there isn't like an under dark to the earth
and that there's also an earth core literally incorrect.
I work at a bowling ball manufacturer.
You must not be paying attention then.
That's what's inside a bowling ball has a like a core in the middle.
Do we want to make it so they have to go through here really stuff them in here?
That's only for the pro ones.
Yeah, but you're not you're not good enough to use those when we said apologize to stir.
What why I don't know why but you probably owe me one.
Oh, it's because I said like what I say like shut up.
I'm talking or something.
Shut up.
You're going to want to hear about the bowling ball.
Bowling ball facts.
I'm so much smarter than everybody.
I thought what was in the center of a bowling ball was your fingers.
Now that's drilled in.
Well, yeah, because you like if you got like really long fingers and your fingers
are going to the core and then you're probably going to have to off balance
the holes that are on one side only the pro bowling balls.
Yeah.
Well, it's in bowling balls, but it's all that's not even true.
I feel like we're the bad guys.
I felt cool killing the orcs because they're like made in a vat
and they don't even really have true sentines.
But as soon as like earth elementals were against this is like,
okay, the earth is is not okay with what we're doing.
That's true.
We it was the actual orcs.
Yeah, it's not works must die.
And also the soul of the earth.
That's true.
Also, the soul of the earth is a problem.
Wrong side.
Another mind blowing fact, the Earth's core has mountains in it.
What?
Oh, the Earth's core has huge lumpy mountains apparently inside of it.
What are they planning in there?
If we if we keep talking about weird facts, none of us really know anything about
this is going to be a Joe Rogan podcast.
Wait, wait, you're telling me what?
There's what in the earth?
Nobody said mountains are a liberal lie.
Changes everything.
I knew about the earth.
What the hell is it?
What the hell is even in the core of the earth?
Isn't it like?
Would you be surprised if there was a fucking Duncan in them?
All right.
Hold on.
I got to help Duncan.
You think earth splatter or are you into the fruit roll-up model?
Root roll-up.
Yeah, it's like the earth is flat.
What is actually rolled up on top of it felt like a fruit roll-up.
I think the bigger question to ask.
It's like, I don't know.
Don't you think it's kind of ridiculous?
It's ridiculous like how plants function like how we put these things
in the ground to become these gigantic fucking monstrous things.
That's ridiculous.
Isn't it?
Isn't that like kind of crazy?
I wholeheartedly and completely agree.
Plants are fucked up and anyone who's doubting it is like these things.
Okay, so you're telling me they're alive.
They live for hundreds of years like thousands of years like the
great redwood oaks and shit that are like true drive a car through
these fucking things and they're just they're just living through.
Yeah, it's so it's so growing sunflowers kind of really changed
my view of everything.
It's kind of funny.
It's some serious.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me let me let me call it wasn't laughing at sunflowers changing
your perspective of reality.
You put like something funny happened in the game.
You put one seed in the ground and this thing grows to be 10 feet
tall and then hundreds of other seeds appear inside of this thing's
head, which then you can individually put in the ground that turn
into this thing, which also produce hundreds of things to put in the
ground.
Isn't that the kind of the same thing with like people though?
You just put one seed in and you could end up with hundreds of people.
Yeah, but oh, no, no, no.
I mean in a kind of in a way but no because we're talking about like
thousands and thousands of seeds.
One person doesn't have thousands and thousands of babies.
I mean back in the old days speak for yourself.
What does he mean?
One person doesn't get thousands of seeds.
What is he saying?
I mean, there's no real point of what I'm saying.
I'm saying it's kind of remarkable that that look like a corn corn.
That's wild.
It's wild.
I agree.
You I'm dead.
I you know what you know what about nature gets me if we're going to
take a step back from corn for one second how you get all of these
like in like a rain forest in this really tiny ecosystem.
You'll get like one bug for a plant.
Well, let's we'll stay on plants a plant that evolves its flowers to
look like a very specific kind of butterfly you attract that like
how does the plant wake up in the morning go that fucking I know that
that like Monarch.
I'm going to be that Monarch.
Yes or or let's talk nature.
You want to hear nature.
What's that bird that can literally imitate the sound of a chainsaw
like it's a recording?
I heard I know I know you're talking about they can play back sound
effects exactly the way that they sounded it is a recording.
What was that guy's name from police Academy?
He got so much credit and fucking birds were doing it already.
All we need now stir is we need that YouTube shorts fucking music
thing to play in the background while we talk about this the one
that goes I know that there's one that plays I didn't know that
it went like a like a Christmas Halloween, which okay.
I'm we're having some trouble.
We're having some trouble.
But at the at the rift, what do you do?
There's some guys here.
You dead.
It's Michael Winslow.
Yeah, the sound effects guy Michael Winslow is so talented.
It's unbelievable Michael Winslow Michael Winslow can do the X
files.
I was thinking the other one whenever someone's like like speaking
like the truth.
It's got this like low rumbly edgy sort of how to put it.
Are you planning on doing anything with fire?
And I know I made this stupid joke that I want to be the ice
guy.
But one of the unique upgrades on this is enemies that are in
the tar trap take more fire damage.
Go for it.
But I'm the ice guy.
Looks like are you guys going to be the fire guy?
There's not even a fire weapon yet.
I don't even know why I picked that.
I don't know.
I don't really know.
I want anything to cane.
What about Dwarven Warhammer?
Stone staff physical attack wind belt flame bracers.
Okay.
I'm almost ready for it.
Anything else I can do we use in the barricades a lot.
I want to reduce their cost here.
I'm I'm refunding all my upgrades.
Don't start.
I have nothing already did don't start don't I you have pressed
it already.
So quick was just as powerful as master sickness.
We have a new thing.
Yes, I don't that's just sickness.
Look at how cool this looks.
We go back.
Can we refund it every upgrade right before we started?
I guess we could just go back.
Or do you want to do you think you can handle them apart?
I think I can handle it.
You're supposed to be a gamer actually.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to be responsible for fucking up this whole thing.
So seriously, I mean, do you not trust me?
No, I just don't I'm the only one that can place stuff on the
ground and I will I can play stuff.
Oh you can yeah, I'm just like don't have none of my stuff
is upgraded.
What's this new archer thing we got?
Oh, we got a lady was it we just make ladies already an archer
medium-range unit going into defending order riffs deals.
Okay.
Thank you.
What do you do to say to someone who doesn't like cheese to
convince them that they are wrong?
You take a step back and understand that people have preferences
that are not yours and you relax.
Okay.
What do you say to someone who thinks corn is like normal you
get fucking furious?
Wait, no, no, no, you see you said normal.
No, that's fine.
Well, we're just talking about how weird corn is.
I should I'm just going to block one of these and they cross
the lake.
Probably not, right?
Okay, I guess we're ready.
Good.
Watch out here.
They come the funny way you do.
Yeah stones.
Oh stones there stir.
That'll be a thousand dollars.
Enemies are preparing to I didn't what I didn't ask.
I just but I want you to pay.
Here they come.
No, okay.
You know what last time last like four times you did this
joke.
I paid you.
I'm not doing it this time.
You're gonna kill the troll.
Trolls Trolls.
Yeah, but I mean I appreciate that ice is actually very
good for those guys.
Yeah, me and the elves got this covered.
So did you play any of you play in any World of Warcraft
lately?
No, why is that?
Because I don't have time to dedicate to World of Warcraft
right now.
But don't you just like get your gear score up to like a
certain amount then there's no content to do anyway.
So like like how much time do you really need to dedicate
to that?
I don't really want to play an animal.
Okay, just wondering but why though?
I don't know wondering.
I know they had like dragon play and like usually do you
really talk about like wow, I haven't played any of you
put all those archers up there.
That's actually a really good idea.
I did.
I got the goons really smart.
Also, they're all loyal to me.
Okay, here.
So now we got to figure out this part here.
Now we got to watch.
Will they walk?
There's more coming.
I think we need to block one of these.
Should I come over here?
Start pressing buttons on your go XLR.
That stopped being funny for five years ago.
Don't come to this side.
Come to this way.
You want to block all of them on one side then so they
only come to one side like if we can like barricade this
whole spot.
If you got got money got money right there money got money.
I do do it.
That's tar.
I messed it up.
I didn't mean to.
Did you see tar?
I have it on my bar.
Okay, that's too disturbed minus two to clown boy.
I don't think that's fair.
So what about this other side then where they're going this
way.
So is the idea that they're going to only come up this
staircase there?
Yeah, that seems to be how it's going and then they're all
going to walk past my my archers.
Well, I guess let's do it.
I mean what else is there to do but do it so be prepared.
Another doors being attacked.
I should focus on this door first dessert.
They got the shortest path.
I'm gonna stay up here.
Would you say you're a nerd a dork or a geek nerd?
I think I'm a dork.
I agree.
I agree with that.
I thought that was you.
I thought like you exploded into blood.
Yes.
So they're figuring out they can't go that way and they're
turning around.
Yeah, this is a corners looking a little little rough.
All right.
I don't know my in my brain.
You said corner is looking a little rough and in my head
it was we were talking about corn and like everybody calls
themselves like the thing that we're currently oh like drew
crew like Drewers and stuff.
I thought you were talking about people that enjoy corn
in the chapter because of like you were talking we were
talking shit about corn earlier.
Like all the corners are looking like they're really rough
right now.
I was like, what is he?
Why are you saying that?
Well, I wasn't saying that is the secret.
Yeah.
I know that now corn crew.
Yeah, corn through corners.
Corners the corn the corn guys or whatever these archers.
I'm with all my upgrade points that I don't have and was
unable to use.
I think I'm gonna upgrade these archers.
They seem really actually really good.
They can't even get through.
You've got this completely on lockdown.
Shout out to you don't actually I had corn yesterday.
How is that?
How funny is that?
It is not necessarily that surprising corn is like a base
of tons of different meals.
Yeah, but like raw corn.
How funny is that?
Wait, that's funny.
That's funny.
Yeah, I thought so.
Do you want me to block this?
So they have to go like the optimal here.
I don't think you're needed.
I don't think so either.
I think we're gonna lose our jobs to these archers.
Oh, they are coming this way.
You don't fuck.
Don't don't worry about it.
My gal will handle it.
They're already doing this well with three points.
I feel like they're going to be disgusting.
We're three points.
What if you upgrade them?
Yes.
You get it.
This guy fucking gets it.
Yes corn on the cob or corn from the can corn from the can.
What what you gave me the option of like natural from the earth
and canned corn.
Yeah, but corn from the earth can be kind of messy.
It's I don't I love corn on the cob.
It's it's like a it's an S tier.
That's what it can get kind of messy and you get that thing
where there's those weird fibers that go into every single
gap in every single one of your teeth.
I'm going to say that we're living in like we're lucky to be
living in the like very brief part of human history right
before we all start to like live in spaceships and like in
vats and we're like grown.
Right and we're going to be like one of the last generations
that can appreciate like really like grown foods.
So I'm every time I'm going to choose something that's not
out of a can that's just one of many privileges of living in
this era.
Why are you assuming that the corn that they pull off the
cobs and put into the cans is somehow not real?
I mean, it's every every, you know, a couple years.
It's getting less and less real.
Is the problem can understand that it's going to be all
virtual.
I mean, if if Facebook alien guy live this fucking way in
the metaverse, we have a meal.
Hey, sir.
We have bombs to drop.
You see these barrels.
Yeah, we have.
Have we done it once?
No, have we needed it?
No, but it's kind of fun to do.
I assumed that they were like a limited so I didn't want to
like waste them, but I'll shoot one.
I'll do it.
This is way too lean.
Corn could be ground hydroponically with patients, right?
You wrote ground instead of grown.
Like I'm not going to trust a single thing out of your mouth.
It's not happening that way.
Well, this means cornflower.
You got a corn tortilla before once they start growing
in on the spaceships.
It's going to be all like a barricade is under attack like
grown with like super hormones and shit.
You know what I mean?
Like a strawberry today isn't what a strawberry was in the
old days.
They're going to get in.
I don't do anything.
What we just almost lost in one second.
What happened?
I'm dead.
I don't know.
They broke it.
What?
Okay.
I don't know.
I don't know how or why this is fine.
I rebuilt it.
I was destroyed.
Okay.
Should I put some stuff here to hurt them?
I'm gonna and let's do this too.
I mean we should I'm going to get some shit here that they
can just slow down.
Do you okay?
Here's here's a you know, continuing down that line of
thinking because my brain went a little bit on it a little
bit too long.
And this is when we get like the truly transcendent takes
so they're learning how to make their growing meat in labs.
What are you?
What do you say?
Are you kidding me?
What?
No, they aren't.
Where did you hear this from?
Are you fucking kidding me?
I just saw it on the internet.
I read it on the internet.
You had your fun.
Do you want to have a conversation with me?
Do you want me to shut up?
Oh, I was going to say that's it.
Whatever you said.
They're getting in the back.
It's over dude.
It's over.
Do this.
My god, it's over.
Dude, it's over.
We don't stand a chance.
We're fine.
Holy shit.
We're in trouble.
Five.
Yeah, five.
The lady archers are up here too.
They're helping.
Thank goodness.
Well, that was almost a disaster.
That was scary.
We had five stars to you gotta be kidding me.
Okay.
I've never I've never run.
I have to do all of my upgrades.
I'm not I'm not getting distracted on this right now.
There are more important things in life.
Yes, I will bank bank of archers.
What is a bank of archers?
I don't know.
It's like a whole squad of them.
So it looks like the only upgrade for the Guardian archer is health.
By you fire damage.
I have something that increases fire damage.
Okay.
I took the fire damage.
I heard that is the slow the tar traps do more fire damage.
There's a bunch of other stuff.
I want to look at confusion flower is 10 seconds.
Song is actually fire.
That's kind of cool.
So they imagine that they they attack each other giant killer
beehive tree Dwarven hammer is Pog.
You have to get it.
What about the floor scorcher the shock zapper?
These all sound like one punch man characters snow cannon shock
zapper ripsaw saw blade launcher tornado in a box friend kisser.
Okay.
Where's my thing that I mean, just say you can like try it.
I'm going to get the flame thing.
Okay.
I've re-bought all new stuff.
I'm good.
What I was going to say is in the future even the growing meat
in labs.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So at what point will it be considered like you're no longer
a vegetarian if you eat grown vegetables like oh this corn grew
out of the ground and like that's no we only eat lab-grown stuff
like if you're eating like earth-grown stuff, you're actually
a bad person and you aren't a real vegetarian because you're
not eating lab-grown meat.
That's the only like truly moral way to go because plants have
feelings too.
I mean, I think that there's a very big question to have about
how to have a more ethical meat industry.
I think that that's a good question to ask.
I'd really do.
But I mean that's that's a that's like a six-hour conversation.
And you're not ready for that.
I don't think you're ready for that one.
Why am I not ready?
Nice politician answer.
What are?
Well, you know, I think there is a question to be had about
ethical meat and how we address that and how we going forward
we come up with these complex solutions that eventually will
put our humanity obviously forward and first throughout our
galaxy and throw up to the cosmos.
But the complex questions and answers that we've been asking
about this exact topic is absolutely something that we can
address and we can move forward when that time comes to that
topic and that topic is incredibly important by the way.
I want to make sure you understand that the topic at hand
we're discussing is this concept that I think a lot of people
really they relate to and I think that it's a very good question
and I yield the rest of my time.
I'm glad you didn't you're I'm glad you're taking it seriously.
Oh Doug Doug right.
What's going on?
Thanks the raid.
Welcome Raiders.
Welcome Doug Doug viewers.
Thanks Doug Doug.
Planes of Orks must die with stir.
It's real.
Oh you came in at a really weird spot when I was that's kind
of funny.
Yeah, welcome.
Thanks.
I saw I saw Doug Doug doing a funny thing trying to get his
chat to to beat Mario maker levels.
He had one one life to do it.
That was pretty fun.
I'm dead.
Yeah, welcome.
You've got to be trolling me.
I do have a question for Doug Doug viewers.
Did you actually do it?
Would you beat those levels in a row?
You actually did it.
Okay.
No, I'm seeing a lot of nose.
How are we handling this?
This is like a scary one.
I put a barricade on the left side so they're all going to
go on the right and then we have our super abilities this
time.
So I don't know anything you want to do man.
We have new super abilities though is important.
Yeah, I put a whole bunch of ladies up here.
What should we block?
I blocked the left side.
But I mean what sorry rephrase that.
What should I block as I have ability?
Okay here.
Let me let me like grab you by the hand.
Well, I'm just trying to see what I don't I don't know.
I really I don't know what you should make at the end of
here.
You should play as one of those giant mortars.
Okay, and then we could like snake them down this whole
way.
So I'm going to put it right here.
I could put another one.
Do you want to put one up with you?
No, I think you should make some snakes.
Okay on this bridge you're talking at the beginning go
like
yeah, do do like a little bit.
Okay, I can make like I think that sounds good.
Is this enough space for them to move through?
Yes, it is.
How thin does it have to be for the like can I put it
here?
Will this work?
Or is that not enough?
No, see like ogres are going to smash the ogre.
They need two by twos.
Okay, one of these that is all I can do.
I'm going to get into the launcher.
Do you follow a build guide when you cook?
A recipe.
Yeah.
I guess it depends on what if it's something complicated.
I mean, yeah, I already know what I'm doing.
Can you have fun cooking something you've never cooked
before without a build guide?
I think it can be.
Yeah.
I think if you just kind of experiment like hey, why do
you need your handheld for PoE?
Because there's not 12,000 ingredients in a fucking steak
and cheese sandwich.
There's there's literally any ingredient in the whole world.
You could put in it at any time you could choose you could
randomly even choose to put like Tabasco sauce and blue
cheese and dip your pizza in it.
Yeah, but the difference is you are shit.
That's it.
You got me.
Fuck you.
Hold on.
Give me a minute.
I'll come up with something.
Yeah, there's like every ingredient is available.
Look, laugh at that guy.
Every ingredient is available.
So therefore like I am polish it because why?
Yeah.
Okay, hold on.
If I go to the grocery store and I know what I want to
make, for instance, I want to make a like a fire mage, right?
Do you want to go to the grocery store and you want to
cook a fire mage?
No, you don't get it.
You don't get it.
I'm trying to make like if I want to go to the grocery store
and make like a salmon like a pan seared salmon, I know
exactly what I need to buy to do that.
I'm going to buy salmon.
I'm going to get on, you know, like oil for the pan.
I'm going to get like some dill.
I know what that is.
It's only like four things to make that.
If I want to make a pan seared salmon and path of exile,
I need to look at every fucking food that's ever existed.
What we lost if you just hold the L hold the L on them getting
the end.
Yeah, but here's what I'm saying.
Like if you want to make a pizza, then you start with pizza
dough.
But if you know you want to make an archer, then you start
with a bow.
It's the same thing.
Yeah, but it's but it's not but here's the thing if you
come to me and say, hey dude, think about pizza tonight.
Oh, yeah, that sounds good.
What kind of pizza are we going to have tonight and then
you back a truck up in my driveway and every single pizza
ingredient every topping ever is put out into a fucking
driveway and it's like, oh, yeah, there's like 700 different
things that could go on pizza.
What do you want?
I don't know.
How do I just have like a pepperoni pizza and then you
have to go on a second and you like dig through all the
ingredients.
We're like, oh, no, that's grapefruit.
What is this one?
That's pineapple.
Hold on.
I can find it.
Oh, let me let me let me let me find that.
Let me find pepperoni.
It'll take me a minute.
I need the guidance.
You're not winning this as long as as long as my
constituents care, right?
Then I win.
I don't know if my archers were shooting anything where
they're not shooting.
I know they're up like on this hill.
I don't think anything's walking close enough.
I wait that means you guys wait you guys you guys are
against me though shit.
I'm going to lose the election to stir.
I think we both won.
Oh, you got that flower.
Is it any good?
That's the first time I've used it.
Yeah, I saw I saw these guys were like stunned every
time I looked over here.
And what is what is this shift for?
What is this giant tower?
What oh by the way all the pizzas is another scenario.
You've cooked every pizza you you you back up with a
truck and every topping every combination is in that
truck and you they're all open.
Everyone's like opening up like oh look hot and fresh
and ready.
Which one do you want?
And I'm just like I don't that one has olives on it.
I don't know.
Do I want all of today?
I don't think I do where's the who's who has just the
pepperoni who has pepperoni and there's somebody in
the back just like screaming I got it.
I got it, but I have to like this guy's got fucking
pineapple on it.
I don't know what I don't know which one I want.
You're trying to min-max your pizza is your problem.
You're worried about picking the wrong ingredient for
your pizza election lost.
Is it just like Helm's Deep?
It is and hey, let me tell you something.
I am fully prepared to enjoy any pizza.
I just need to know I need to I need a little bit of
help with what it is.
Okay.
I'm so ready to open Path of Exile and become obsessed
with it.
I will be obsessed with it.
I just need to know where to start.
Are you speaking like you're the president?
I'm the president of this channel.
Aren't I?
I could see that I could definitely see that I can see
how you are.
Who's the people saying?
No, who's the president of this channel then?
Hey, we got a lot of guys coming through here.
We are Josh.
I can't be the VP.
Would you would you run for office with me as your VP?
Am I just like the publicist of my own channel?
Are we talking about?
Am I like the am I like a PR agent for my me?
Oh, it's me.
I own this shit.
Hold on one day.
I'm doing like too much goofy stuff.
I feel like we're gonna lose.
We might all my money on like towers.
I think we'll be all right.
I don't think we're doing anything.
If we did, it would be fine.
I don't know if you sell things for full value.
You're the mascot.
Yeah, that's fine.
I am the mascot.
I get out there in the in the fursuit and I like to like
dances my hands up and then it's like did did did did did
did did did did did I'm like super like getting the crowd
pumped up and then I take the fucking helmet off and I'm
like, let's talk about the issues now and then everyone
listens.
Why can't I be both?
You lost me at fursuit.
I just got distracted.
I got a hill for you.
Started thinking about Legoshi first.
I don't know for them like mascot costume.
All these archers are dying and I don't know what to all
the way on the top of the tower.
We're gonna do a recall on you.
I am out of money.
LOL poor.
If they was they was PvP you'd be in trouble when I go
sell these giant towers.
We don't okay.
We definitely need stuff in here.
If I'm going to be barricade.
I'm going to be the barricader.
You need to you need to put some stuff in the middle here
as it kind of just waltzing right through.
I'm having some trouble.
Oh, he died.
I just need a minute.
Take your time.
Good time.
Mods ban me perma.
I am bored as a raider from Doug Doug said that.
I'm gonna sell on you.
No.
Okay.
I'm turn it up.
So what does the big the big block thing here?
What does it even do?
The big block thing this huge like the tower you can build
things on the top of the tree house and the portal takes
you to the top of it.
I was putting archers on the top but they were still dying.
So I gave up.
I'm ready waiting for player.
Is that you are you player?
Yeah, once more into the breach.
Are you in the cannon?
No, it's a very expensive thing.
That's just sitting there as a giant.
You're not you you're not using it.
I can come use it.
I gotta get it.
I gotta get you.
Oh my god, you have so there are so many archers up there.
It looks like a joke.
It looks like you spawned him in like gmod.
Way too many up there.
Can they even shoot?
I don't know.
Yeah, they're like shooting like big volleys starting to
get through a little have gotten that think we're all right
as long as we just focus on the bridge.
Keep your eyes on the prize which is winning.
We should play plate up again.
Did we beat the game?
I mean, there's a lot more to it.
Oh this other we did win a run.
I forgot.
It's like a kind of like Binding of Isaac.
You just do it again.
Nice shot.
Thanks pal.
I really mean it.
You killed like 10 things or more.
I'm unleashing my fury unleashing my rage.
We got him.
So that's that's a fusion flower.
Yeah, I don't know what it's doing to him.
Honestly, I think it's like it's confusing him.
It looks like it's eating them or something hard to tell.
I think it's like eating them and then spitting them out.
I mean, I think they're just dying.
It says that it would confuse them for a while.
Oh, no, no, no.
Okay.
It's not like I thought it was closing around them.
I think it's just when it opens it puts out like a nice.
All right.
Cool.
Do you think do we need more damage down this kind of these
rows or do we need them to be slower?
I think we're set which one you know what you choose.
You know, I can't I can't make this pizza for you.
I'm going damage.
Oh, that's going to be scream.
That's a lot of archer player.
I would just say I'm just making sure we're good.
This is oh, man.
This is a lot like home is deep.
Well, now it is that should hit a lot.
What?
Wait, what?
Wait, what you hit me really guys reference reference reference
reference.
He made a reference reference reference reference reference.
Wait attack me.
What?
All right.
I gotta get up.
The archers really do rain just absolute hell down.
Yeah.
I think I'm just going to keep buying archers totally under
control.
We actually do have it completely under control.
You're right.
I'm I'm curious.
It feels like these stages they don't intend for you to like
it's a big stage for them to just walk to the left and go
like now let's all go down this one long road.
But how would how would they not expect that?
To be what happened?
Well, I think what this big skeleton.
I think a lot of it's probably won't they start attacking
it eventually or they were before what made him attack it
before.
I have no idea.
I think the game just wants you to be efficient and says hey
pick a way to be efficient.
It doesn't matter how and like will that's fine.
That's the way that they're going to run every map has
special challenges.
Exploding hole Bob's do not reroute so they'll just blow up
a barricade.
That's good to know.
And perhaps that's what happened.
Does it show like what enemies are in the next wave?
It does on the screen before we start it shows a list of
everything that's in it.
Should I start making archers too for fun?
How much money do you have 4300?
Yeah, I think you can put some up here.
You know, I'll do it.
I'm already here.
I'm ready.
You can play the hard mode now by the way.
We should try it.
Oh shit.
It's Corvash.
Corvash Corvash Corvash Corvash Corvash Corvash Corvash Corvash
shameless stolen nemesis system.
I'm looking forward to the Wonder Woman game made by the
same company.
I didn't even I haven't seen anything of it.
I don't know if it's been very much shown but made by Monolith.
So I have pretty good.
We were just talking shit about this barricade and
I got a long way to go.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Hold on.
You got any money?
Enough to do that.
Oh shit.
Okay, we can lose one to the other ones are starting to
get through on the other side.
I think we're gonna have to pull back into the room.
Yeah, but it's just like almost deep.
Oh, there's so many ways they can come in here.
Oh, Gorbache is coming.
That's why Gorbache destroyed.
Oh, Gorbache did it.
I think we lose.
No, we're fine.
Just stop crying.
Don't let them in.
Oh, he's just going around and breaking all of your barricades.
He doesn't care about anything else.
Okay, any stragglers are gonna get caught.
He's kind of just no standing over there.
Do we got to go Gorbache him?
I think I know he's going all the way back to destroy the
other barricade.
He's not even part of the fight.
He's slowly going to destroy the other barricade.
Is he dead?
Your archers killed him.
Nice.
What an idiot.
They could have won this.
They had it right there.
They had it in the bag.
They couldn't win it because I was here.
True.
I wasn't going to make the archers.
You don't provide these quicker.
Hold on.
Stay alive.
I can go like this.
Yo, are you the lightning guy?
I have lightning on my staff.
Are you going to be the frostfire lightning wizard?
You could just use stick.
I do literally force for so easy.
We could make nights nights.
You could probably do a whole you could do like a whole
chessboard.
It's like the power sword.
I want the flame thing.
Well, I'm going to upgrade the scorcher.
I'm going to save my points giant killer beehive tree.
I didn't okay.
You need to like let me know when you're going to skip.
I keep I have I have no control over it and you just like
don't like me.
I keep forgetting period.
I keep forgetting.
That's not already up.
You think it's already up afraid of what he might do.
So what was the point of that story again?
The gigantic orc army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of Master Cygnus and
Borwick and now they're back.
Kelsey has it right.
This is a bigger spike wall.
I think that one swivels out like spins out to create armies
and hits things and push them back.
We've got this sorceress.
How does this work?
This is like supposed to be a fire.
Is it what direction is this the right direction?
I don't know.
I don't know friend.
All right, so I don't know pal.
We got to figure out what we want to do here.
And what are we going to do?
I'm going to build ladies.
Yes, but I'm making barricades and I didn't know where they
should go.
Looks like I mean down here where the stairs go.
Oh, there's a whole second floor man, and it's complicated.
It's like a it's like a hitman level.
There's two paths like a hitman level man.
What do you say that for a change of pace?
Sure, we defend here and then like defend outward rather
than like make a barricade.
So you mean we could just barricade like one path barricade
a path and then go for it from there.
No, no, I was talking about the opposite like let's make
this the kill room of death.
Okay, this is the kill room.
Yeah, I feel like that's kind of scary considering
how close we are to the thing.
I'm not afraid.
Are you afraid?
Maybe a little I want you to be a little bit of wait.
Can't we put on hard mode?
They were saying you think we're ready for that right now.
I think we're ready for that right now.
All right.
How about this?
Do you want to take like a BRB go pee get like some water
and come out and put it in hard mode?
Okay, you can do it in level select.
Oh, okay.
Well, okay, let's do that.
And then I can even upgrade my stuff for a change.
Okay, so I just five minutes.
Okay piss master in five minutes.
Okay.
Hello.
Hey there.
So I just want to make sure of ladies and gentlemen,
if you could please hold your attention for one moment
at the end of this broadcast, we will be watching stir play
five.
Wait, what?
Okay, so we will be we're going to watch stir play five
nights at Freddy's when we're done.
When I mean, I'm still having fun doing this.
But I just want to make sure you understand the what's
on the plan for today.
Stir will be going through five nights at Freddy's and five
nights at Freddy's to stir will be playing his choice of
five nights at Freddy's one or five nights at Freddy's two.
This will be determined by a poll in stirs chat.
Is this a lie?
No, no, this is real.
All right.
Let me re-invite you.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean?
Don't we have to go back though to put the difficulty?
Yeah, we have to remake the game because we have the
wrong difficulty.
Do you actually want to play this on hard?
Okay.
Well, then let me let me re-invite you.
Oh, they can't hear you.
I keep doing that.
Oh, you should really just trust me.
You should like not feel like you need to like, I don't
know.
So like I'm not a child.
We're on War Mage right now.
Yeah, we are moving to Rift Lord, which is enemies are
stronger.
There's left less time between waves.
They carry shields and we have half as many rift points.
So instead of 20, we'll have 10.
Okay.
All right.
Now let me get you invited.
I think I'm still with you.
You are.
Okay.
And yeah, we can see that the bomber guys are on this
stage.
Oh, okay.
Well, let's get our ass kicked.
No, we're gonna do great.
We're gonna rise to the occasion and we're gonna kill
guys with your guns.
So actually which one should stir play first one or the
second one?
I would say two, right?
I may have them both.
So I don't know.
There were rumors that master sickness banished him from
the order afraid of what he might do.
So what was the point of that story again?
The gigantic orc army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of master sickness
in Borwick and now they're back.
What?
These new rift rifts are what smaller or why are you
yelling?
Just scratching my chest since Borwick's time.
We've got this sorceress.
Let's turn it up.
I'm same strat.
We're not going to do a snake.
Okay, I just wanted to they were talking so same strat.
So we're just gonna I'm building up here on one side.
You build on the other side the other door this door and
we're just to go in you handle that corner.
I'll handle my corner and this is just whoever is doing
better wins.
I don't know what directions needs to face.
Do you face grill out or grill grill in or grill out?
I don't think you should call them that it's real.
Oh, it's this way the grill shoots the fire out.
Okay.
I wonder how what the range is.
We'll find out.
I don't know.
It's hard to say.
I'll figure it out.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Okay ready.
This is what this game is.
I had no idea.
This looks fun.
Yeah, it is fun.
This is more like the first second game.
Although I don't remember I could be just making that
enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
They've broken through a gate not about the same.
Oh, they do have shields.
They do exist only hurting me.
Oh, see we didn't even need traps this level.
I mean big guy getting through.
There is what we lost one.
I think a runner got by.
Oh, we don't get to say I'm ready.
We just have to do it.
Oh, are you serious?
There's a werewolf.
They're breaking through you thought I was going to do it.
There's a there's a lot of big ones coming.
That's a scary.
Okay, not as scary as I you got a little.
Okay, this is a little spooky.
I got this on the control.
Don't worry.
The barricade is under a barricade is down.
Do you?
Oh, they destroyed that barricade.
I think you're letting a few through friend.
I was doing something very important.
I think this may be like a reset scenario.
No, no, no, we're fine.
Everything is fine through for the bit.
Yeah, it's a regular Wednesday.
Okay.
Enemies in our ripped room.
No, what's remaining?
That really okay.
Okay, not another guy's getting through.
Am I right?
You're right.
I think three more.
I think this is a reset.
I think we learned me if we did we learned we learned let him
in let him in we learned to let him in.
I don't think this even attacked anyone.
Nobody even came through here.
I thought we were doing I thought we were dancing.
We can't oh, it's on you.
I guess all right new strategy.
Mm-hmm.
I think we got to actually block a path not long.
I think so too.
So are we looking at there were rumors that master sickness
just walk this side here afraid of what he might do.
So what was the point of that story again?
The gigantic orc army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of master sickness
and warwick and now we deal with this should I funnel them
with more blocks new red or no
because eventually there are going to be able to destroy
those so we can't completely rely on that.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's trap it.
Okay.
Yeah.
And eventually we should sell all that.
Hold on sell all of this.
We need to block further down.
Don't slow somewhere.
And then attacking that's true.
Then for now, let's focus on defending this stair.
Okay, so we should probably get a little bit of a block here.
This is that's that's cut in the corner there.
So let's go right here.
Okay.
First wave wasn't very hard either.
I think we're good ready to go.
I think I might have missed something.
So you want to fight up here, right?
Yeah, just double-checking.
Enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
This is sponsor stream.
What about two bros can't have fun in the game together?
They instantly broke it.
They did.
It's probably one of the Cobalt.
Yeah.
Do you have like an instant retry thing we can do or do we
have to beat us?
I can just go like this.
In that case original plan.
Let's defend the final room and then as we get more money,
we build out.
We need just damage damage damage.
What's the highest damage thing you're up?
Poison.
I'm kind of afraid to use poison because it won't last long
enough, right?
All right, that's all I can do on this side.
So we have to put shit here.
And then they're going to eventually they're going to
come through here.
Rotate the jump pads.
The these are fire flame pads.
So they shoot fire up.
It's backwards.
You get what are these fire things do?
They when people get close enough that lifts up and breathes
fire in their face and the slow trap increases fire damage
taken and I don't know if I have the right way or not,
but people are saying the grill out.
I imagine the way the arrows pointing.
That's what I thought too.
But if I spin it the other way, the grill is facing the
other direction.
That looks right.
The way that looks right.
I believe we'll find out.
Okay, we'll find out just know that we can't like sell in
between rounds anymore because there's no in between rounds.
So it better be right.
It better be freaking right.
Let's go.
Yo, let's get it.
Enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
So the game is hard.
The game is challenging.
We get it.
They're going to dig on the other way.
We're going to go back up.
No, that's correct.
All right.
I want to make sure it's right.
Okay, I think they're getting up the other way.
They are.
There are.
There are enemies in our rift room.
Don't do it.
I got it.
I will be rift room protector for now.
Okay, I will be out in the world.
Trying to thin the herd as possible as much if you're not you're
having trouble.
Let me know.
I'm okay for now, but I imagine in about five seconds that will
change.
There's also like teleport back to the room trinkets that you
can buy that I just never bought because it was easy before
this.
We're okay so far.
Okay.
I'm imagining we need some of this shit right here.
Enemies are breaking through elsewhere.
Look out.
Our defenses have been breached again.
Wait spray fire.
Why?
What are you doing?
Oh, it's the wrong way.
Oh my god.
I got so in my own head.
Oh shoot.
Uh-oh.
Oh, we're good.
We're okay.
This map is it is hard to tell like where everything is because
it all goes over top of each other.
I wonder if I can spin that around in the next like 3 2 1
room.
There's a lot of people in here.
If you're not busy.
I think I got it.
Big guy coming.
Oh that hurt.
Meth Lord.
There we go.
Okay.
At least one of them is right.
Sure gamer face.
What's going on with this thing?
This guy needs to shut up about them being in our room.
He is not matching the vibe.
It's a long cooldown.
God damn it.
I had a chance.
I that was two seconds.
Oh, it gives you like two seconds to sell.
Yeah, that was not very much time at all.
What is what is the yellow on the mini-map?
Oh, it's all these things.
All right, so the yellow on the mini-map that's good.
Oh boy.
Amazing.
They're a little spooky.
We're anything.
Could be way worse.
Yeah, your tar trap.
That's actually set up the right way is doing a lot over here.
Oh, you need help.
There's a lot of big guys coming over here too.
Man.
Yeah, this isn't a bad strap, but it's scary.
No one got in.
I really see him.
Oh shit.
She it was a cheater though.
So I don't worry about it.
He was just cheating.
He really is saying that every three seconds.
I can tell you this much.
There's enemies in our riff room.
Okay, she didn't know.
I got it.
Thank goodness.
I'm gonna.
It was going the right way.
It'd be good.
All right.
This room should be pretty protected guys.
I think there's enemies in the rift room.
I feel like there are going to keep that like I really feel like
I could just keep building archers in this room.
Just keep freezing stuff.
Oh fast.
Maybe I don't know what just happened.
I wonder if we should build a barricade like in the corner as
like they go after the archers like no matter what.
Okay, there is a lot of guys coming.
Yeah.
This this is pretty well-defended over her.
I think we are right.
I need the sword.
I wonder if the broadswords any good.
This thing's great.
Sounded good.
I'm just a raid from from the city earlier.
You're still here from six straight.
Thanks everybody.
I don't know if you're still here or not, but missed it.
Oh shit.
Oh, that's bad.
It's all right.
There's still only halfway.
Well, we are halfway through the level.
So just.
Yes, these barricades got blown up and I got to spend all
that money remaking.
I got it.
This back.
We're going to go like this.
Where I don't know.
This guy is freaking me out.
Where are they?
Are they going up this way?
You're going up this left side.
I don't think I have any of my traps upgraded.
The slow full upgrade is very useful.
Now this is fun.
I like this.
I like want to play more.
Yeah, I like sense you being like, oh, let's play five
minutes of parties.
Now.
No, no, I'm good.
This is fun.
You can play five minutes of parties in Roblox.
You can play you can do anything in Roblox.
I don't know what I would be doing without the frame.
Just this hallway.
That's it.
Nothing else.
I'll show the Bomber coming in yellow.
I still don't know what this plan actually does.
It's not a confusion.
Whatever it looks like he was making them walk backwards
there.
I don't know if they were chasing me or confused.
Oh, no, they're next wave.
Shit.
I'm gonna go the other way.
Yeah, you fucked it up.
I'm all right.
Hey, all matters is that they die.
It doesn't matter how cleanly it is.
There are.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, there are.
Whoa.
You good?
Basically.
There's a lot of people over here.
Not good.
All good.
Oh, not good.
If you got in we got to rebuild this barricade.
We got another barricade to rebuild.
There's so many enemies here.
Oh my goodness.
I got you.
And if I was an orc, I really hope I'm a heavy orc.
God watchers are smelly.
Why would you say that?
No, no.
What happened?
The fucking elementals just walk by everything.
The little tiny elementals kept getting by.
Shit.
That was hard.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
We going again.
Yeah.
Oh, let me buy.
Okay.
I got I got what I needed.
I feel like I want to refund points.
He wants to refund the game.
I thought you just said you liked it.
I think you know, I think I want to refund.
You know, that makes sense because we've we've just been
buying like experimental stuff.
It doesn't refund the stuff that you bought just the upgrades
for him.
It's all right.
We're coming up close on the two hour mark.
If we could refund real quick.
It's been way longer than two hours.
Like four.
The gigantic Orc army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of Master Cygnus and
Borewit.
What are we missing?
They're back.
Kelsey has it right.
These new red wreaths.
What do we need?
I am you have Tar.
Let's I'm gonna not buy shit you already have.
Let's trap it up.
Tar and I got these brimstone tiles.
I'm gonna put at the beginning because it's damage over time.
So by the time they get to us, hopefully they're less
strong tar poison and I got the story.
Oh, you got the sword.
Okay.
I feel like you're gonna like it.
It writ canteen.
I'm ready.
But are we ready?
We're we're we what's are we changing strategy?
We keeping the same thing going.
We going back to the rift.
Oh, we got enemies in the room.
I don't know.
I'm putting fire down at the front.
We could just run door and just kill them as they come
but but then once the side doors open, we got to change
strategy.
Yeah.
Yeah, delete those.
Why?
Because I want to put the slow traps first because then now
they take more fire damage.
Okay.
And then logic and then after they go to the fire, let's
hit him with the poison.
Let's say they'll turn this way and let's fuck them up.
Do you do we know if the the bombers only destroy barricades
if they're blocking their path or if like I think they
probably just run right through a barricade because it almost
seems here like with these pouring things that you would
want them to walk around this so you can actually make
use out of it.
But if you put a barricade here, they're going to instantly
just blow it up.
I wonder if maybe we just have to be really diligent about
when they spawn.
Okay.
Yeah, I like this better already.
The sword is really good.
Crossover.
Yeah.
What is its ability?
I put down the lightning sword.
Hold up.
Stop hitting them.
Nice.
Yeah, but I all I had was the bow so I didn't have like when
they all grouped up.
I didn't have anything to shoot them.
All right.
Look at that.
We're good.
I'm going to do poison.
They're entering the rift.
But I don't think we did it.
We lost who we two got in shit and they're coming through
this way.
We have no defense over here.
Well,
that hurts.
I don't like the noises my guy makes when he gets hurt.
Oh, also the trinkets to like teleport back to the end.
I think there's something we need someone needs to have that.
Yeah.
Somebody is getting in there.
Yeah, I don't know.
It looks like the maybe the strategy is to fall back a
little bit to the room.
That's the first we got without any problems.
I think we're still good.
I just wanted to put the fire at the beginning so that they
like take a lot of damage by the time they get here.
Yeah.
Okay, we need to come back to the room.
I'm dead.
Yeah.
I don't know where you were.
Yeah, it's over.
We only have half our remaining just restart.
In the game.
Shat you guys failed.
No, I don't.
I thought that was one of our characters though.
That was my character.
Let us do Gambo.
I think those are doubters that want to Gambo
an easy way to make all my points back.
Not long after it disappeared.
There were rumors that Master sickness banished him from
the order afraid of easiest win.
Yeah.
So what was the point of that story again?
The gigantic Orc army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of Masters.
I'm just I just thought about I just got it like a flash
in my brain of you with like a face cam and like and you
being like what the fuck I can't wait.
I can't gonna be so funny.
Let's trap it up.
What are you talking about?
Oh for five nights is for okay.
He does want to quit.
No, no, no.
I just like I just got like a huge.
I don't know.
I got like a YouTube video image of my brain of you sitting
there and the camera zooming in really close after the
after you get scared and being like what the hell where
did it even come from Reno like a zoom in quick?
Okay, this is going to be one of the most viewed videos
on your YouTube.
Is it is it really?
Yeah.
Okay.
You do you cut up like you have streams cut up right you
cut strings and put them up.
Yeah.
Yep.
Can I can I make my own little bit here your own back stir
place five nights at Freddy's 2 will have at least 10
to 20% more views than every video on that channel is
going to be my crowning achievement.
I think so at least 10% and if I win the bet you ready
up but I'm scared we haven't made any I haven't put
anything down.
I don't know what the strategy we're doing.
I think it wants us to do this so bad.
So I'm going to keep this is what we had before enemies
are preparing to breach one of our gates the door.
You're like I'm playing 40k same gameplay loop power
stored.
Nothing else mine launches them though.
So I have CC.
All right.
Now are we falling back?
We'll fight these guys.
He's the only guys on the map at the moment.
Okay.
Now there's more guys.
Okay, they're all coming this way.
We're good here.
Yeah, keep the communication good.
We're good.
They are old.
They are better one little barricade.
I put there.
I'm dead.
It's fine because you respond in the rift room, which is
actually helpful.
We need you.
I'm going to die too.
How they do deal a lot of damage now.
They do.
Oh, I may have put this on wrong and it's going to shoot
them.
Yeah, I did the same thing downstairs.
No, I wonder if upgrading the heels a good idea.
I wonder what it does because it's healing us like full
health.
What would an upgraded heal do?
If it's like a buff, maybe make you even more healed shorter
cooldown.
I can't believe only one got in there.
I wish I could spin this.
All right, that we got we got the bomb.
Hope all things those will go straight for barricades.
So they're fast and they have bombs on their backs.
Dude, I've been counting.
You've done three.
You've done 300 lip lights.
Jump up.
They they're getting in.
I think I think Defender Rift Room was the strat.
I think it is.
Enemies at the Rift too much going on on this map.
Hey, we could be cowards and turn it back down.
Are you a little baby?
Are you like a little child?
Well, it's technically not over yet.
Oh, what's remaining?
Oh, this guy's getting in.
No, they're not.
It's always just one small elemental just goes right by
reset, reset, reset, reset.
We got it this time.
Defend the Rift Room easy.
But we're we almost got it.
No, we no trust.
We got this next one believers.
Believers all in believers.
Oh, are you sure about that?
I'm positive.
I know what needs to be done.
Okay.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
All right, positive.
I'm gonna take like the barricade off my bar.
No barricades just damage and we're only being Rift Room Andes.
I think barricades only at the end so we can defend them.
Rift Room Andes.
So do you want to just pick a side and I'll fortify one you fortify the other and then we'll eventually come into the middle.
There's three sides.
Yeah, but this they don't start coming.
They don't start coming down here till later.
It's the left and right rooms first.
Together to create armies not seen you taking the left side.
Okay, I will fortify this right side.
This time.
I'm not going to mess this up.
I'm ready.
I'm doubting this time.
Oh shit.
Okay, there's a lot of doubters.
I'm going to what's the ratio here?
Actually, no, it's pretty even.
Never mind.
Fine is believers.
They want people believing in your chat.
Yeah, honest to goodness.
Let's game one of our games.
The door is I just hear you're dead.
Do you lose money if you die?
I don't know.
I kind of did die on.
Oh, no, the believers.
I want it.
I wanted to come back quick.
This map has me paranoid paranoid.
So is there only one level in this game or what streamer?
I mean, I've only seen I've been watching for a while and I've
only seen this one level.
Oh, right.
What there are.
Okay, they're coming down the middle down.
I turn around to deal with your fucking problem.
I don't need to defend the middle.
Walks down the middle.
I don't know what you said, but it was you scared me.
It was a rap.
Bro.
What?
I don't know what to do.
Come up the middle.
All right.
Now we focus a little bit of building in the mid.
I think there's some element of like dealing the correct damage
types to certain enemies were missing.
Yes, that is a good point.
I think if you're on hard, you need to do that 100%.
All right, still the middle.
They're coming from your way.
I'll handle this in here.
There's a lot and I'm getting hurt.
This big guy over here.
There's a lot in the room.
I'm having some trouble.
He got me.
He outplayed me.
Okay, not another one's getting through.
You sure?
I'm sure.
All right.
We have a second here after this.
We have one second enemies in my rift room more likely than
the same three PC check.
What why would I just got so distracted by that?
Yeah, you'd let one in.
I said no more and you went in that the mods post something
funny.
Okay, I see how it is.
We just we just let them into our rift now.
Okay, watch out for these bombers.
Oh this they walk over this fire trap.
They just blow up really.
Okay, don't let them blow up on you.
But yeah, they insta died on the fire.
Maybe we just put those out in front of all every door that
makes them.
Watch out enemies.
I'm so tired and old from saying this.
Kind of sounds like the principal from Beavis and Butthead.
It does.
Oh, Beavis and Butthead.
You're both expelled.
Every episode expelled.
They get expelled like every year every episode.
I love the old the old man voice is such a classic.
Everybody's got one.
And it varies right?
What is your old man voice?
That's Deckard Kane.
Yep.
There is I'm an old man like I do that one sometimes.
It's also the one with a little more a little more in the
side of his road area.
Are you going to talk like that when you're an old man?
I honestly probably I feel like I talk like that now sometimes
honestly.
They're almost in the rift room.
It is like this.
It's more air.
There's air lots of air in this one.
Yes, you can combine them even if you want to.
The one that's more in the throat can also be used with
the one that's more airy.
Oh my God.
I am focused on this.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about the bit the bit.
Enemies at the rift.
I'm not focused on the bit.
We're going to lose.
I know.
I know doubters salivating right now.
We were going to win.
We were not going to and then there was a there was a bit.
I didn't know there was going to be a bit.
There was no bit.
We were dead from the last five minutes.
We were done.
I leaned in and went.
Oh, well, well, well, well this trinket equipping increases
rift points makes enemy was worth zero rift points for a
short time if used you can just stand next to the rift when
you see those guys like oh, there's a whole bunch.
Just just cast your your empty rift.
What that's insane.
We're missing a whole thing here and then there's the ring
of storms which defends the rift.
I'm refunding all my upgrades.
I am purchasing the ring of storms and I'm going to use it.
I don't know how you feel about that.
I think now what are some of those those one very important
question.
Is there a kind of list of enemies we can look at like a
it's like a tome or something we can open that shows enemies
and how what their damage types are and everything because
we need to find out what is hurting the elementals where
they are the earth ones the most I don't see it anywhere get
jar of ghosts a hundred percent.
Yeah, we need this.
We got a got to be any strategy here cause the enemies that
hit the player to run away enemies turn and run away.
So it's like a here arcane and lightning is what you want.
So maybe I'll get the arcane staff.
Yeah, we had nothing that was arcane long-range.
I have brimstone floor deals arcane damage.
I didn't even know there was an arcane.
I'll I'll get the arcane staff staff real good.
So I need to hurt things with this.
So I got that upgraded.
I will use that as a weapon and then what about the grinder?
I just got the grinder.
Okay, and you can hit me off on grinder if you want.
All right, but priestess the priestess is arcane.
Okay.
Okay, you want us to be arcane just do a ton of arcane damage
with these priestesses.
On priestess it says war scenario only.
Oh shit.
Okay, there's a few of those.
I wanted to get those before tornado in a box war scenario
only maybe we should can you toggle something to make
so you don't get to see them?
I think push trap.
We need some we need some pushing.
Oh snow cannon short-range cannon that freezes and damages
enemies.
This looks like it's on the ceiling.
Is there ceiling?
I hope this is ceiling in in the rift room.
No, but like there's only ceilings downstairs.
All right, I'm gonna I'm gonna get it.
I'm curious.
I'm gonna try it wind belt short-ranged AOE crowd control
that pushes enemies secondary commute.
So this is a I think this is rooting.
Is this like a weapon get jar of ghosts get jar of ghosts,
please.
All right.
I'll get jar of those everyone saying to get it increase
passive fear duration.
Okay, and then I got enough to do like one more or two
more things window of butterflies.
Stracting enemy deep freeze.
I'm ready kind of want this but it's not on the ground when
I need something on the ground ceiling lasers.
No, I am so like what do you have to make sure I can I've
got grinders.
I've got archer ladies.
I think I'm going to upgrade the spike wall the big one
that like pushes him back.
Yeah.
Yeah, that makes sense.
We need some push backs.
I upgraded my the floor fire all the way.
That seemed good against the Bombers.
Yep.
And then maybe I'll do tar.
Yeah, yeah, I got Targon.
Enemies remain slowed for a brief time or they take more
fire damage.
So there's a after they walk on it.
They're still slow or enemies take increased fire damage
on tar just keep the slow.
Maybe I don't know.
I don't know man.
I don't know dude.
All right.
Well, I got we got we got some shit here.
Let's give it a try.
I'm about to just like, you know what I mean?
We need to not long after that battle.
We need to redo this whole thing.
There were rumors that master sickness banished him from
the order afraid of what he might.
So so what was the point of that story again?
The gigantic orc army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of master sickness
and boric and now they're back.
Putting the fire traps on these corners.
So when the runner boys come out, they'll probably just
die.
All my shit is expensive.
You've got this sorceress.
Let's trap it up.
Yeah, she did.
All right.
Let me take a look how this all works.
Okay.
So that's like of AOE.
Let me see.
So this has to go on a ceiling.
Oh push traps are really cheap.
Are we doing rift room?
Yeah.
Okay.
I wonder how much range these have because I could probably
aim them into the room.
Okay, so they're gonna and they're gonna come this way.
All right.
I got this is gonna be disgusting.
Okay.
Yeah, and I have this turns the rift into like a lightning
storm for one like shit's all getting close to it.
We're we're we're winning this one.
We like bought things.
You know what I mean?
I think we're good.
Let's give it a try.
I got snow.
I got free expensive snow cannons right here aiming right
and then probably gonna be like there.
There they are.
Yeah, I think that's a good spot.
I want so that I can activate this but it's a passive but
I can also activate it.
And I think it's just a big fear.
I wonder.
Okay.
Oh fun.
Oh enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
They've broken through a gate.
This is like very bright.
Yeah, I just have like more damage on the sword and
everything.
All right, pull back someone the other way.
I have no cannons over there.
Hey, I'm back at the roof room to make sure.
Okay, so are you really like the corner archer?
No snow cannons.
No snow cannons fucked him up by the way only like three
people here.
I'm going to load even more.
I'm going to make this like this is just only snow cannons
over here.
Good luck getting through that.
Oh, that's a fast.
Reached again.
Okay, watch out.
Okay, we got to get back.
They're almost there.
They're in the room.
Dude, what the fuck?
You want to fire guys little firemen?
Okay.
That was I guess if they want to do that, that's cute.
They can do that.
Everybody gets one.
What's that right there?
Yeah, you got it.
People in people in I died.
Okay, I turned on the lightning rift.
I don't I barely saw it do anything.
We're okay.
Little sketchy so far could have been way worse.
You're I can do that eat shit.
No one fucking getting through here.
I think I'm through the middle.
We have multiple elementals.
Oh left side.
Oh fuck by little fires little fires little fires.
We need some barricades up here.
Anything so they don't just like walking.
All right, let's let's regroup a little.
Oh, I see what's happening.
I need to sell that shit.
Why does it feel like the worst we've done?
It definitely isn't but it's it's up there.
We still have seven.
All right, this waves almost done.
We got to we got to rethink the strategy here in a sec.
Oh, I got to sell this thing is when does the wave in like
when they're all dead you get a moment to sell when they're
all dead.
Yeah.
What are you guys?
Who's who's spamming this?
Okay.
I wish I had one second.
Yeah, I really I'm if I could sell one thing it would help
so much.
Are yeah, I know I know once we get one second here.
We'll be all right at this the opportunity.
Okay.
I'm going to put some tar in the middle.
Yeah, all the bombers are just blowing up.
Yeah, they all died.
I even have to look at them so we can actually set up
barricades in here.
Do you have barricades?
I don't on my bar, but I do.
I'm going to focus on that then.
Okay, which way to go that way.
I think they're coming up the other side.
I'll take it this side.
You go to the other side.
Okay.
I got to get a snow can up here.
That would be nice.
There's not a lot of feelings up here.
There's a lot of people coming in behind us too.
Yeah, we're done.
Nope.
Good freeze.
And I have whatever I still am not a hundred percent sure.
I activate like super long cooldown for the rift.
It's only these two sides right now.
I think we're okay.
All right.
I got a snow cannon going up in a second.
We can do it.
This is actually the best we've done.
We're actually doing all right.
Yeah, I think that we're not worried about these barricades
getting destroyed.
It's only going to get a little easier.
Okay, I got a bunch of snow over there.
All right, they're coming all the I think yeah, this is okay.
I got remember the snow cannons down here.
Doing work.
So much damage.
Holy shit.
This word is good.
Finally.
Why are they not shooting?
Oh, okay.
I was gonna say what's going on?
Still only this way.
So we're good.
Could we was betting allowed here because I think we're this
is this looks like it.
This is the one.
Yeah, I'm freezing them too.
That's the only way five of eight still.
I need more mana.
That's fear actually.
Thank God.
Oh, I'm dying.
I just died too.
All right.
I don't know who here destroyed my barricade.
Something blew up and let's write everything.
All right.
Where we going?
There's plenty over here, but let me go like this.
All right, we're looking where we're looking.
We're looking where we're looking.
Middle where middle and I'm going to go middle.
You say I'm on the side where we were.
I'm good over here.
I think I know this troll.
I got you good.
All right.
They're coming on the right side.
No, you're in here.
Tom's comp.
I'm coming.
Watch out for little fireman.
Fireman.
We guys look at damn morning.
I did.
They got the barricade over here.
I don't know.
What's causing that barricade to constantly blow up?
I think they just run it up here.
Oh, there's so many.
No, we were doing so good.
So many.
It's just an overwhelming amount of enemies.
There's way too many.
There's so many.
There's like a thousand people.
Oh my God.
Explosive archers.
Oh my goodness.
That was this we just got overwhelmed.
I lost.
I lost in the game and IRL.
We were doing good too.
Yeah.
I think we can do it.
I think this is our Placidusix and we could do it.
This is tough.
I understand what was going wrong.
I had archers behind the barricade.
So things were shooting at the archers at the barricade and
blowing up the barricade.
And if that barricade didn't keep going down, it would have
been a lot easier.
I feel like I'm going to reduce the amount of these.
We, the middle room here, I think it's overwhelmed to very
these rooms we get to so.
We get overwhelmed.
I think honest.
You want some honesty?
Sure.
I think now that the bombers are just running into my fire traps,
we could we could wall off that whole middle part.
You want to wall off that because I got I'm putting stuff up.
Not not immediately.
But like as soon as like we get pushed back to the rift room
and we have some extra money would be like three barricades
for the middle and I can protect them with fire and then
they'll only do left and right.
We won't have to worry about them.
Like just walking in that room.
Okay, honest to goodness.
So do we just wall it off and then just fight?
Do we just keep putting barricades up?
Just only just put barricades up every time they get destroyed.
Just put them up there in the middle.
Yeah, I'll I'll spend the money on it.
I have them on the bar.
You don't have all right.
So I can put it up there if I need to.
So in that case, I'm going to put some snow shooters in.
It's too high though.
I think that's too high or anything.
That's all right.
They should be shooting down.
Okay.
Well, they're they're ready.
Will they complete level?
Yeah, we could work.
This is it.
We learned every close big learning curve.
We learned like I'm I'm a high school
dropout.
Okay, so it takes me a second.
Stay in school.
Okay, we're good.
Yeah, let's do it.
They're destroying the barricade.
I think I just goofed up the barricade.
Enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
The door is down.
Here they come.
It's me grandpa.
They need to sell the voice packs.
I'd buy the grandpa MLG grandpa voice pack.
A couple ends up going the other way.
Double kill.
Triple kill.
Quadra kill.
Panther kill.
They're like a mana potion you can buy too.
I don't know.
Maybe I think I'm going to go in on that.
Get feared.
That a fake enemies at the rift or are they actually?
No, they came there.
There is a few in here.
And yeah, you're you're slow.
Your turrets are shooting right as they turn that corner.
It looks really good.
Actually.
That's very good.
There are enemies in our rift room.
Okay, I'm going to do the same thing in the other room.
I'm going to put two or three over here.
More enemies on the way.
Yeah, once I once I'm able to have enough money to seal that up,
I think it's going to get significantly easier.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that was good.
And I also think your turrets being up here instead of like downstairs.
Yeah, I didn't want to say nothing last time.
Well, I'm really happy about it.
I did put a few down there because that's the only other way they're
coming in just to slow them down.
Okay, good.
We still got 15.
We got 15 lives.
Did you get that Trinket thing?
What Trinket thing?
We have 15 lives now.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Oh fuckers.
What what happened?
Well, we're still ahead of where we would normally be.
I blocked off this that area.
So I shouldn't be coming from the middle anymore.
All right, good.
Good.
How about over here?
How's over here?
Look this hallway.
I haven't built anything in it yet.
I've spent all my money on making so they can't come that one way.
Oh, there are two turrets.
They trying to go down the middle.
No, okay.
Other side in the herd.
Yeah, there's there's guy in here.
He needs to come back.
Cover.
Barricade down.
You piece of shit.
He got in.
I use the cooldown so they wouldn't count, but a little late.
All right.
Watch this side.
We need to start building stuff in our hallway.
I have a little bit of money.
I've been up to do one of those big spike wall things.
I wonder if I should put one over there.
I can't believe it.
We're doing it.
So far, we're really doing it.
Honey is the only side that has anything.
I'm gonna I'm gonna run to the other side and put some stuff down.
Yeah, like we need something to attack somebody here.
Well, they're all coming this way.
Sorry.
I have I fucked up.
Why would it be facing this way by default?
I gotta be ready to go sell that right now.
Thank God.
Do it.
More enemies.
Oh my goodness.
The mix.
Okay, I this this thing this damage shit in here now.
Where are they?
Where are they going?
I'm going to say I like that.
I like that.
Is that thing even attacking?
Okay.
Yeah, they are there.
I was making sure that these things are attacking.
How's it going up there?
Really good.
There's a lot of guys on the mini map.
I'm gonna come here.
You got one big guy on the other side.
What are these orcs must die symbols on the ground that you can
pick up?
I think it's money for like the upgrade.
Oh, yeah, I think the skulls.
Whoa, big guy.
Oh, I summon the storm above me.
I think we're just pretty weird.
Oh, they grouped up.
That's good.
Okay.
Well, what do we what do we need?
What are we missing?
What's what's what's the problem here?
Yeah, I need to just sell that car so I can build better
barricades.
What do you need me to sell?
This tar over here so I could do a second barricade here.
I think this one right here.
Okay, next time I'll do it.
All right, they're coming in the left side.
Bombers are coming.
This is the only way they're coming up right now, right?
Maybe to make sure they die.
Whatever the yellows are on the map.
These are these the crossbow guys apparently blow them up
to flaming crossbow guys.
Okay, where are they getting kind of stuck up?
Okay, so we there the fear is so good.
I'm so glad I was bullied into using it.
It's gonna keep freezing them.
I'm just I feel like I've been doing good with the staff.
We got some bombers coming there down the bottom of the
stairs.
Why why does it default to I tried to spin it?
God, why does it default to facing the towards you?
I wish I could answer that logically speaking.
It it feels like it's a good idea to die when they're at the
rift.
You could just spam magic.
Yeah, and you just when you respond there.
Oh, they got one.
Okay, please.
Oh my god, I'm gonna put some more up some frost after like
didn't down over there where they would you know anything?
Yeah, I think I know what you're saying.
Okay, they are going around here.
We got a lot of bombers coming.
Hard to read map.
Barricades down over here.
You can't because you're dead.
We got a lot of people coming up in a minute.
Her dude, I got a lot of trolls on my side that are going to
be hard to deal with.
What?
What it was shooting through him.
Okay, we got we got an issue.
Yeah, I have no shit.
Enemies in the radio.
Can you see what happened here?
There's just there's too many so many you can't how do I kill
that many trolls?
There's still two more waves.
Oh, they just like pile in just a two dozen omega enemies.
Shit.
We were doing we were doing all right.
Damn it.
Still they're still beating me up.
I thought we had it too.
I thought we had a good thing going there.
Is this possible?
I think part of it is that it expects you to have more of
the upgrades from playing the game on the easier difficulty
first.
I'm going to cope with that and say yeah, yeah, that's pretty
good.
Cope.
I mean, I'm I'm an addict.
I would just keep playing on hard.
Yeah, man.
I'm at that.
Okay.
Wave wave 6 was hard, right?
That's when all the trolls start coming and we had a hard
time.
What if on wave 6 after we destroy the bomb guys, we just
build more barricades on one side so that they have to go
the other way and then we double team one side.
You confident?
I'm confident.
That's like that sounds like an actionable plan.
I'm just going to follow you around and just kill things
with you.
When are you going to do a puppet show?
Um, I don't know.
During I already did that.
Remember the puppet show spring.
No, what's the point of that story again?
The gigantic orc army's genius.
I actually might need more damage.
The freeze is great, but I don't think it hurts very much.
Kelsey has it right.
These new red rifts are bringing smaller orc factions together.
I just think you don't need to build that many of them.
They were doing some pretty good work at the end, but once
they got through they got through and that was it.
Ceiling lasers people say in ceiling lasers my ceiling
lasers.
Yeah ceiling lasers.
I'm going back and let's do another full like refund
everything and try again a full.
Okay.
I mean, I'm ready, but you know, I'm going to optimize.
Okay, so let's do this.
So on Rift Lord.
Here we go, right?
Oh shit.
Can I upgrade my barricades because I don't think I've done
that.
I've never even looked.
Oh, wait, wait up.
But what do we read?
What do we read on?
Before this?
Yeah, but I quit out to here.
Is it even before this?
Click the book at the bottom, right?
Oh, it's the book.
Okay.
All right.
I got to get a new strategy.
People saying ceiling lasers are amazing.
So I want to I'm going to get ceiling laser barricades block
two spaces increase costs.
That's that's kind of probably good increase health and yeah,
what am I what?
Okay games over games over dude.
Yeah, we win gives over.
Yeah, it was fucking it's it's all over.
Okay, the jar of ghosts is now a lot better.
So I got ceiling lasers.
So what about what should I get?
What should I use for a weapon?
I feel like the that arcane stuff is doing pretty good.
But I think it looked good.
I think also just focus on as few things as you can fully
upgrade it.
Yeah, and then like with your extra by trinkets, okay,
because I should be able to upgrade it all now, at least
let's see.
Where is it?
Free secondary radius or mana cost probably not.
All right.
So I have ceiling lasers leveled up all the way.
I have my arcane staff maxed out all the way.
I've got the jar of ghosts all the way.
I can do one more thing tar all the way I can.
Yeah, you do tar and I'm going to do the floor the fire
floors.
I cannot I don't have enough points to do the fire damage
increase.
I just have enough to do the make it even slower.
Okay, and I'm not ready.
Only he wins.
I'm going to go play Bioshock which one did you get the
laser ceilings?
I did.
I'm just going to put tar traps down and laser ceilings
above in those little corner rooms and hope it works.
Okay, I'm ready.
All right, let's go.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Oh now I'm ready.
Yeah, I didn't all of the barricade upgrades are reduced
cost.
So depending how cheap they are long after that.
Yeah, they're usually 800 they cost 600 that's a lot afraid
of what he might do.
So what was the point of that story again?
The gigantic ork army's genius.
They haven't been seen since the days of Master Cygnus
and Borwick my loadout.
They're back.
I'm okay with these new red wrists are bringing smaller
orc factions.
How big is all this thing is huge not seen since the laser
ceiling thing is across the entire ceiling trap it up.
Well, let's ready up and look at that.
So does it aim at them through it?
You should put it by the stairs right here where I am.
You can rotate it long ways.
I do more than one.
I think you should do one on both stairs.
Yeah, I want to tar it up over here.
That that looks okay.
I don't have enough to do should I prioritize the tar or
should I prioritize putting another one over there another
one over there because they should also kill the the bombers
Okay, and you talk about like over here and I can save money
on focusing on barricades like right here.
You mean this spot right here, right?
Yeah.
Okay, then I'm gonna put all my money into barricade.
I can put another one.
Is there another spot that we need it's gonna be all my money
but I don't think so because upstairs doesn't know then I'll
start putting tar down.
But one on the other side too.
Well, I guess I'm ready.
I'm a believer.
We just just remind me when it's like wave six.
Okay, we need to close another doorway.
I'm the healer.
Yeah, I like to play support.
I don't spend any of my money.
I just feel what's with this going for me.
We got runners going up.
Their headshots probably not there are there are it might
depend on the weapon.
But yeah, you do a lot more damage with that shot.
I think the staff was doing them.
You have to like aim oddly up into the right.
We should probably work to hit things.
Yeah, we got a lot of money now, too.
Okay, I'm gonna put another ceiling shooter.
It does concern me that you just now realize there's headshots
though.
I had no idea.
Oh boy.
I yeah, okay, you can hurt people with the headshot.
Sir.
Yes.
Yes, you can.
It hurts a lot.
It's you basically can't hurt like the elementals without
headshotting them.
Speaking of which there's some getting into the rift room.
I need help.
I feel like I have actually been instinctively shooting at
the head.
So I don't think it's problem.
I hope Charlie.
Such a liar.
Hey good middle.
Me is at the Rift.
I'm trying to save my money so I can block the middle room
and defend it.
We got guys in the room.
There are enemies in our rift room.
Okay, I'm blocking this.
More enemies all the way.
Why do it too?
No, don't.
But nothing walks here when I block it.
If I buy at the end.
Okay.
Well, it's not the end yet.
We have a wave six.
That's I'm preparing for wave six.
I'm preparing for wave six.
They keep coming up there in wave six.
Make sure you make sure your head shot him.
I will be good.
I might need a little help.
Like a lot of money, you know, you got money.
No, I'm saying it just seemed like a lot of money to build
those there.
Okay, we got guys in here again.
Yeah, there's a lot of people on this side though.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, there are enemies in our room.
We need to go find the shaman who's summoning these.
No, no jokes are allowed until we win.
Okay.
Hey guys.
Yeah, in the game.
All right.
What do we need?
What what what do we need?
We need a we need like to defend this path more and the
other path has nothing in it where we need to kill the
bombers before anything.
Okay.
We'll go straight for barricades.
I believe so.
They will absolutely smash any females that comes across
their path.
Sure are.
Okay, let's look.
All right.
He's focused on his new toy.
He doesn't care about strategy.
He just wants to see how many lasers he can buy it.
There's truth to that, but not as much as you think there
is truth to that.
But look at this.
Check this out.
Watch that left.
Watch out.
Watch that left side.
I'm going over coming.
I'm going to need help.
Yep.
You okay?
Oh, they can't walk in.
I used my thingy.
But I think one did get in.
The barricade is down.
Enemies at the Rift.
There's enemies in our Rift room, dude.
What?
There are enemies in our Rift room.
I'm going to put some more lasers up there.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
All right, we're about to get good to me.
There's one enemy left.
We got a second here.
What what do we need?
I think you need.
Why'd you kill it?
I don't I don't know.
Like I don't know what we need.
We just need more.
I killed him because I'm in gamer mode.
No, I freaking freaked out.
I got to fix that.
Watch out.
Enemies are broken through again.
I pressed it.
I just you know what I mean?
You know, sometimes it goes like I need tar on this side.
Yep, like right right here.
Yep.
Is that jar that makes them run just like always active?
I don't know.
Does that null hit you and just walked away?
All right, hard down.
Same side, right?
Yeah.
That staff is really good.
No, it's great.
That's awesome.
Spend so much money fixing those.
These these archers, dude.
Yeah, they're awful.
Hey stir.
We are about to be on wave 6.
Do not kill that guy.
Let him roll.
Oh, he's gonna die from the lasers.
So what?
How are we?
We are I'm gonna block this whole path.
So sell this tar immediately.
Once this is so all this right here.
So everything here besides very good.
What even the stuff downstairs?
No, no, just like this thing on the wall.
Okay, so I got it.
I can sell your stuff and I'm gonna barricade here and then
we're gonna presume that they're gonna go only the other
way.
All right.
So now I'm I got money.
Where should I should I stack middle?
Or this this side needs some help over there.
They're only yeah, they're only coming that side now.
Okay.
I'm aware.
I am right now, right?
Yeah.
Eat shit.
We're ready this time.
Evil villains.
You're right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, they're all only coming this way.
I have this so many lasers over there too.
It's ridiculous.
If you if you turn the corner, you're gonna laugh.
It's a joke.
How much did you have?
Okay, I have to go look.
Yeah.
All right.
Watch that other side.
Bombers are coming the other way.
Yep.
Can't let the Bombers get through.
Okay, we're good.
We're going over this side.
Okay, which we can ping the map.
I like what we're looking at.
Any game that doesn't have that now feels like it should have
it.
All right, you had that hit at that left side.
No, they're not going up.
Oh, they're not going up.
That's right.
Okay around.
Yep.
They're not going up.
Okay, good.
We just need to if there's ever any yellow on the mini map.
It's a problem.
You don't have those feeling no cannons anymore.
Do you?
I do not.
Bombers are coming.
I'm going to check the other wall.
Yep.
Hopefully they don't break it.
I can't really look at them right now.
I'm okay over here.
You need to go over there.
Okay, there's like two layers of wall.
So I'm saving my money.
All right.
This is clear.
Okay.
Yeah, they walked around bombers are coming the other way though,
but it shouldn't matter.
Yep.
Got him.
I guess there's two bombers coming in this way.
I'll take care of it.
Shit.
I didn't heal you in time.
Sorry.
No, I'm fine.
I get to come back in the convenient place looking good.
It's pretty messy over here, but it's okay.
There's one guy left.
I can clean this up.
Okay, this though.
I haven't spent my money yet.
He's on it.
He's gonna die in a second.
He's literally walking through the lasers like right now.
Okay.
Hold some of your car up here.
All right.
Whoa, that's a lot of those things.
Thankfully they all came this way.
Okay.
We're we're all right.
That was a lot of guys.
All right.
I think that place that's safe over there for a little while.
Where are we prioritizing the guys on?
They should only be coming on the bridge.
Keeping an eye on the map in case something weird happens.
Like the others.
There's more guys.
There's more bombers.
They're not the lasers will kill him instantly when they walk
through her.
All right.
We've got every angle is being problems, but they should only
be coming this way.
Hope so.
Just keeping an eye on it.
If anything slips through I have the they can't go in the
rip button.
Good.
There's so many big enemies.
It's ridiculous.
It is uncomfortable that this is still like a how are we ever
with this before and I don't know one way what is hitting us
something to shoot us or something like an archer all the
way that shooting over bombers.
Okay.
Yeah, they're hitting the lasers and dying attacking the
barricade where we're good.
We're good.
It's right where you were the barricade that's right here.
God damn it.
When you put something on the ground and click this sometimes
it not happen.
Me problem.
I think using these wall grinders have helped a lot too.
Yeah, they do a lot of damage looking good should be one more
wave as soon as this wave ends be aware of any Bomber.
Yep.
And then if we can handle that we're probably okay.
I'm just going to fill the rest of this room with lasers like
it's going to be the whole hallway.
I think you should put them in this room where all the grinders
are walking around the barricades.
I don't think they go down that far.
They don't fit on the ceiling.
Oh, yeah, they can't go up there.
All right.
Only if you love are we having then you should put tar all
along that path.
Yeah, I'm going to just go to that.
I mean in the where the barricades are where you are
right now.
Yeah, so just like tar tar tar tar tar all over here.
You got it.
All right.
Here they come.
Where are they going?
They got me.
I think they're all going to run down this hall.
So I think we're all right.
Yep.
All right.
How we doing?
Good.
They're going to have to come down this hall, right?
There's no other way to place it.
No.
Yep.
Here they are.
There's so many enemies.
Heart is ridiculous.
This is brutal.
This is fucking brutal.
These orcs gotta die.
What are the green dogs on the map?
Yeah, I think those are things that are killing us that are
shooting us from far away.
Yeah, I put these push walls in here.
It feels like they're just stuck now.
Oh, I heard doubters are shitting and screaming.
The only way to shit.
Oh, the green things I think are mana potions.
Oh, okay.
Somebody said hallway.
I'm ruined.
Money money always believe in the banana bros.
That's right.
We're going to do it eventually.
I mean, we're lapping toad right now.
Like they can't even come in this room.
Second lap.
Yeah, we've second lap toad.
I know.
Unfortunately, chat is toad or the doubters.
It's kind of hard to hit in the head.
I'll take a three stars.
Yeah, let's go.
Hey, most McDonald's are three.
I'm okay with that.
Most McDonald's are three stars.
Most McDonald's sit between like 2.5 and like three.
I think that's good.
I think we're fine.
I think I got like 14 upgrade skulls from that though.
Additional lasers.
I kind of like that.
Just a quick question for you.
Yeah, just to make sure that we understand the you know,
the remainder of the stream time.
Are you are we playing this for a while or are you playing
Five Nights at Freddy's or you just what's the deal here?
What do you want?
I mean, I'm up to you.
I'm enjoying this.
I'm I'm an enjoyer.
Okay.
I think like we just look we just like got it.
You know what I mean?
Like it like we just got it.
Well chat seems disagree.
Chats like Five Nights at Freddy's.
Let's go.
Okay.
I mean we did just play this one level for like four hours.
That's true.
Well, I mean we even we've been gaming.
Are you are you like in a funny Five Nights at Freddy's mode
or do you just want to chill and play?
Good.
No, don't pressure stir in doing this.
It's what if whatever stir wants to do is Five Nights at
Freddy's ha ha funny.
I mean, it's yeah, I want to do the next stage and then we'll
see.
Okay, because I feel like we just we just comprehended the
game.
I feel like we could beat the next stage first try.
Okay, let's do it.
Well, yeah, I knew I'd like Orcs Must Die a lot but I'm as
the difficulty ran.
I'm remembering why I like it a lot, you know porn with
innate magical ability like Warwick.
Oh, this is this is fun.
This is great childhood curing.
Your mother's fever.
This is um the family cat down from a tree.
I remember and yeah stuff when I was around just good time
and luck, right?
This one seems it's not equally as complicated.
For you.
It just happens.
There's two doors.
Oh, I got I got a laser section right here.
Okay, we got teleporters as well.
Okay, maybe we don't beat it first try just because it's
confusing.
Oh shit, they're not long enough.
Okay, right about I effectively put him at an angle.
I guess I could go like this and then like that I could
stagger it up.
I think ultimately they all are going to have to come down
this main bridge.
Yeah.
Even if they come from other ways, let's start at the
bridge.
They think I should put some of my stuff right here right
like in front of is this the only this is the only way
they can come up is that there's no other way they can
get up here.
It there's there's two ways up.
What are they going to have to cross that bridge those
stairs go up to like a high ground for us.
Okay, I'm going to laser it up right here.
Okay, I just clicked like four times and it didn't place
that was weird.
I don't know why it's doing that seems like okay, I'm
just going to collaborate with the laser village was
this new thing charge wall the new thing we just
unlocked.
Oh, I don't know.
It said adult lightning damage.
That's all I know about that do this thing.
I'm going to put the next one back here in a moment.
What's your what's your strategy?
I have a strategy.
Where does this go?
I am walling this off right here in the front and then
they're going to have to walk around this narrow side.
I'm going to put a push wall on that because it goes into
the death pit.
Not let's do this.
My barricades are also metal.
Now.
Look at that.
Enemies are preparing to breach one of our gates.
They've broken through a gate.
So now the obits are covered in armor all that armor
should make them pretty.
Yeah, they were last time dumb dumb.
Here he goes.
That is a great strategy that works great.
Yeah, they go into the meat grinder.
It also appears like I'm just they're trying to attack me
and then I keep hopping back on the thing.
Oh, they broke it.
I think I know what happened.
Didn't work out as well as we wanted to.
I think I messed it up on purpose or not on purpose.
Easy money.
They're not counting.
They didn't count.
I used my scroll.
Oh, that's right.
These are not counting.
Damn it.
Okay, that one counted though.
Tried to fear but it was too late.
Okay, I would be down for a quick reset with reset.
Yeah, cuz I think I made them blow up all my shit.
But we don't have to okay.
We did last one then it's like five nights at Freddy's
maybe kind of baby.
Five nights at Freddy's.
What about my money?
Just refund.
Just refund the money.
Everyone's worried about their money.
Capitalism.
Grinders, lasers and then walk the middle.
Oh, I think I know what's happening.
Here do the lasers here.
I think if we're standing on the other side of the barricade
things are going to try and shoot at us
and it might be why the barricade blew up.
Okay, lasers here.
And then we'll like defend this narrow and then I'm doing
slow here.
I'll just do a line of slow.
I will I'll prioritize slow this whole line.
Okay, let's go for it.
I can't wait to stop these orcs.
I just clicked three times and it didn't actually wasn't registering
this something around my mouth should make them pretty weak
to lightning attacks.
I'm missing input.
They do.
They're like, hey, they're weak to lightning and then you lightning
them for one damage.
Yeah, that kind of really isn't hurt.
Maybe these are a little weaker.
I'm sticking with Flynn.
Oh man, there's so many just floating in here.
Do a zigzag with the barricade.
It works.
Okay, give me money.
Give me money.
Look at this.
There are way too many people in here now.
Let them in.
They're in.
Let them in the bridge.
Never never activated the thing so we could just let them.
Oh, I hear my PT lay down how long it lasts.
Oh, nobody got in.
Nobody got in.
You want to keep slugging it up the barricade again.
I want to keep slugging it up.
We're not lazy.
He breached another door.
Don't don't don't build anything.
I think they're they're coming from the other way.
So none of that's going to even matter.
Oh shit cannot put lasers here.
Unfortunately, so I can't really do very much in this.
There's you can put them the underpass.
That's oh, yeah.
Who got by?
Huh?
Oh, a bunch of the little runners got by.
Oh, this is fucked up.
It feels like you need a lot of lightning damage.
That's probably why they gave you the lightning trap right before this.
What is it around my sword?
It doesn't feel like it doesn't know.
I wonder if the blue highlight mean like a shield or a barrier or something.
Who has on what some of the enemies are highlighted blue.
Some of them highlighted green.
I wonder what that means.
I haven't seen it got bombers coming.
I shoot them.
Yeah, they'll they'll die from this.
I was just jumped into that because there's a bunch of orcs.
Here's there's a bunch of orcs.
Oh, I thought we were going to fight.
Ragged.
Now there's a bunch of fucking orcs.
That looks like a lot.
Brothers, there's so many orcs.
We got more enemies in the rift.
Okay, this is really hard.
Damn, this game is hard.
I didn't think it would be that big of a difficulty from like normal to hard
when normal was like we could win every round.
No effort.
I mean, that's that's a good thing though.
That means it's you know, it's you don't just blow through the whole thing.
Yeah, I think you are right though.
I think you play through a bunch on normal upgrading a bunch of stuff
and then we need we need like your options of it.
Like we don't have we would have to respect every single time
like by the wall charger upgrade the wall charger.
Yeah, the lightning thing like six times or whatever.
Well, sorry believers, but I do have to give you a little bit of a
we didn't know the level and we didn't know what we were dealing with.
I know that you should always believe but we didn't know what we were doing.
What it gave me the middle finger.
What is this special upgrade as well that items have I was able to do it
on the jar of ghosts and I don't know why it was just there.
I could press it.
I'm not sure why I could because yeah, I imagine that I don't even know
any of them are just special upgrade for the special enemies.
It literally tells you why.
No, it doesn't.
They're lying.
I'm talking about a different thing.
Is it do you have to complete this thing first like fear
a hundred enemies for instance, like the thing in the middle.
That's for the unique upgrades.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Then the special upgrade is just an X.
It doesn't have like an explanation.
Yeah, I don't know what I did but I unlocked it for the jar of ghosts.
I don't know why I think you just unlock it.
Maybe.
All right.
So how are you doing?
Are you how you feel feel?
All right.
You feel like you want to is FNAF is FNAF watch along a different night.
We can do that if you think you have the energy to play it.
How long is five nights at Friday's because I'm picturing it as
like like a 20 minute thing.
I mean, it's it's as long or short as you really want to make it.
It's probably like do you want to beat it?
Do you want to be stir the gamer and beat five nights at Freddy's
is it'll probably take like an hour or two, but if stir the gamer
does not want to game it could take like two to three hours.
Let's do it another another night.
Let's do it.
Like at the start of the stream another night and this way I also
like I'm forcing you to play something with me again.
Okay, he hates otherwise if we do right now, it is going to be
like a 10 minute like haha or the ghost.
Yeah, we want to start to be to be really locked in focused not
after five and a half hours of heavy gaming and then this way
you also get an additional Jerma stream and this way otherwise
he would not show up.
He's going to be making his clannations.
I'll be making my clay and molding all that.
Yeah.
All right.
So what are you on?
I'm I'm taking I'm taking some time off.
Be gone for like four or five days.
You want to you want to square up and kind of do this on are you
when you're ready?
I don't really have anything on my schedule except for Fridays
and Sundays.
I do some stuff.
Otherwise, I'm totally free.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll ping you on discord with them with a game plan.
Okay, but can we play again on the other difficulty you on the
way you like you want to play on the normal difficulty right
now?
Yeah.
Yeah, we do other one more.
I want to earn some skulls.
I don't know.
I'm really enjoying this.
Yeah, we will play it.
We do.
Yeah, that sounds good.
There was never going to play for now.
I was dude.
It's you know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
No, I know what you said.
I mean the energy level.
No, I really do the energy level of the stream.
Right.
I want it to be yeah, it's like it's it's a game where you
need a lot of like there's not much going on.
I want us to be like in our prime 20 year old.
I want to get in a time machine go back to 2008 when this
shit came out.
Sure.
I was building up now that it's going to be like the greatest
content I've ever produced.
No, you're good.
It's kind of a big deal.
It's kind of like, you know, well, it would be when you're
at peak energy levels, then it'll be it'll be more fun.
That's what matters.
Okay, so what we're on the same level is on the regular
difficulty.
Do we want to rethink a strategy here or just kind of
go?
I think on regular difficulty we can just we should be
fine.
You can just go.
Yeah, we were doing what we're doing.
I think would be okay.
All right, I'll do I'm going to take the there's also you
got to do like these special challenges and stuff thing.
You said like I want to want to try the wind belt and
push them off.
You don't remember your childhood during your mother's
fever teleporting the family cat down from are you sure
you sound upset?
Remember, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
you sound like I just I just ruined your night to use
magic.
Hey, thank you.
Sorry.
Thanks for ruining my night.
We were all waiting for now you have work to do.
I completely understand and plus we're having fun playing
this so we are what's the difference usually what to
see?
That's the thing usually when I suggest the game to you
you hate it and we only play for like 20 minutes but I
like you're enjoying this a lot hmm yeah i mean not everything i don't i don't think there's been
a game that i genuinely didn't like i could pick one you could do one oh i thought you meant like
oh yeah i know when you didn't oh oh i don't know you're a good sport you just brought me under the
bus what is it you're a good sport all right so i'm just gonna put lasers in random places here
okay i did the same thing i'm ready we're doing the same strategy i'm gonna go like this okay
but now the enemies will like die oh keep in mind if you're betting this is on normal so i mean we
could screw this whole thing up that's true there are eight waves preparing to breach one of our gates
there's armored men all that armor should make them pretty weak to lightning attacks
dude enemies are dying when i shoot them yeah you probably shouldn't have bet against us if you did
i mean i'm that's probably that's probably not a great idea let's see what what a lot of people
probably did is they knew that everyone was going to be betting like of course they're on normal
they're going to win and they put in like every dollar they they have in their pocket on you know
on red at the relay table they're just like all i could i've not read sorry on my channel on zero
that it's like whenever there's like oh 80 percent yes this is going to happen 90 percent like oh i
want to bet on the opposite for the odds we realize the odds are that way because you're going to like
you're going to lose your money even if you only put a little bit because the odds you're still
losing your money well we this is not going that smoothly so far so i'd say that it is
i'd say that there is no way we're gonna lose okay yeah i just i went i just got three times
to get that out there i'm gonna complain about this all the whole night oh yeah we get to pause we
get like our take our sweet time now they're coming from the other way if you want to set up the lasers
time to throw no i'm prioritizing the tar i feel like that's the best thing to do
why would you put a barricade right in the middle
into the easy better oh shit i'm so sorry and then you can set up lasers like after that when
they're all in the ground and stuff you want to put a laser just like right above that just like
wham and wham yeah you got it because they're they're gonna get all jammed up on that
enemies are attacking on another front they've breached another door the barricade is under
attack the barricade let's go put archers like in the final room oh they they really
see they they knew it was they knew it was a threat they are wait people are getting
by some who got by yeah the the little tiny rats i'm gonna i'm gonna go put archers back there so
that they catch the stragglers are they coming from both sides now yes more enemies all the way
fear is really great with the lasers because the big some just walk through them like four times
pretty funny if we lost you want to lose as a joke charlotte it would be um unfortunate to
all the people that believe in us yeah but like how many people really is that two three million i
think put it down come on what the hell good freeze good freeze right right in the zapper
what is that purple that keeps going on that you're doing is that the fear or something else
uh the purple i'm putting down is an aoe and then the green is the fear all right i think i'm gonna
goop i'm gonna do some goop start a goop spot right here probably right so they can slowly go
into your things oh yeah i'm ready i think okay boop i will stay down here all right i'm gonna i'm
gonna do the other one because i have the wind thing to push them off from the high ground is
he sleepy um no we're just he is how did i point behind me like you were here and i'm behind you
yeah ah he is yeah that guy over there oh they're all coming from up here we got nobody
head come on here they go i'm like perma stunned oh you're dead oh yeah which might have been for
the best to hold them there longer i miss that guy so many times it's embarrassing good uh i'm
gonna continue uh the goop it's one of my favorite things about you uh i want yeah i'm gonna go down
here put it down excuse me game i clicked a hundred times sorry it's like kind of late
to be going i'm screaming wait come up you're only supposed to click once i know but when i
click once and it doesn't go twice it doesn't go and then and then it finally goes i wonder
what why is that happening that wasn't happening earlier the computer's overheating oh good look
at that breeze big big huge get that skull you wanted to collect skulls look i'm getting it
hey i want to share it no talk to me when you've earned one one day i will
one day i might even surpass you okay you can't keep up can't keep up i'm too fast
looks pretty even so i guess just stay there wave six out of eight that went quick
i need a bigger tower oh shit you're right yeah no i'm good try to try the game we got we got
some problems too many orcs too many orcs oh there really are too many orcs
uh i'm gonna do we lose money if we let them get in and i do the protection thing
i don't think so i think you just get money for killing stuff
yeah so don't we technically lose okay well he got it i know you want those skulls but
be harder all right we don't have any time really here i'm gonna start gooping here
okay i like i like freezing them in the zap zone it's very good stop
pooping here comes the collapse why can we get a little bit more goop i i'm out of um
hey can we get some more goop i'm out of money here comes the collapse why don't let them win
don't let don't prove that person wrong there totally was a mana potion right i want to get
that and upgrade that and just be guy who uses mana a lot i feel like that's very useful like
the wind thing you can just keep spamming it so once they get over here i just keep clicking it
but it takes mana this is it this one's for all the marbles i believe you you're welcome
what has healed you oh thank you you know guys he has not even noticed that i've been healing his
ass i i think maybe it's assumed that you heal over time or something no it's been me
in me the whole time me barry got some uh work getting in the end the this is clear for now
i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming all works dude man about to become twitch's
number one orcs must die streamer you already are
that's a new high score two star oh that's not very good hey let's be good
uh so i guess streams up to you if there's if uh you know you're gonna cancel five nights at
freddy's then uh i'll keep playing till i cancel it i we we had a joint decision
it's weird that you cancelled it but are you still streaming uh yeah i'll do one more
okay but i want to upgrade something i agree with that i think it's just that some items don't have a
special upgrade is is what's going on i want to try something different i'm doing a refund here
wait how come i have 98 skulls i had 100 but what's going on what you have what 98 skulls
oh do you refund it yeah yeah the things that you buy do not get refunded what do you mean
it's like if you buy yeah it's it's refunding the upgrades not the purchases of specific things
yep everyone wants to see the hammer i'm gonna do it try the hammer oh there is a mana potion
but we can't i can't use it complete mage power to unlock i want it man i'm gonna do the poison
grenade so poison explosion potions saw blade launcher what about window of i'm doing window
of butterflies it distracts enemies apparently i actually think i can still do ceiling lasers
oh yeah yep i can still do ceiling laser i don't know why so many of these are are the war scenario
only all the cool looking ones it's like oh that sounds oh i'm not gonna buy something that is
only for some missions i think they're just i mean it's a one of them's a gigantic catapult that i
feel like it's kind of overpowered anywhere else uh you good he asks am i good i mean do you want me
you want to yeah do you want to first continue yeah got a new loadout don't check it out we'll
watch you no matter what because if you're not having fun we aren't having fun stream for now
oh look at this place wow we're at the world's edge oh shit it's one of these levels history here
are we here we're apprentices we just deal with the smoke attacks we got like a stoke top in the
middle here you must face a slightly bigger problem but you will have it's in the middle
yeah this is normal we're playing on normal again not on her okay we got this only slightly bigger
where the heck's the red could it be lois maybe hammer poison oh i didn't i don't have this anymore
okay you go in the middle and it's a giant castle with a hundred stairs and i think it's all the
way at the top lasers was a great choice here yeah it's all the way at the top you can take
the lasers on babe and then there's a teleport all the way up to the top i guess it is a spot for it
in here yeah jesus this is elaborate you know there's other entrances too that by like i feel
like you should just build in the middle not care about yeah although if they can come from two
different it looks like a multiple different directions this might get overwhelming really
quickly yeah maybe so where is they come up through these areas here no where do they actually come
up to the rift oh wait no there are only two risks i was i'm wrong hmm i was looking at the
green doors there's only the two rifts so it's just two sides you take one side i take one side
probably all right so i guess i'll just be at the top we're gonna have to play some of this stuff
what is this new thing this big like range this gas range the grill uh they just walk over the
grill i guess well let me read it snow blower triggers snow blast that damages and freezes
enemies hmm i kind of like that i'm putting that out putting that yeah you you you take
care of your side i'll take care of mine i'm taking care of my side
okay i'm ready ready to go if you fail your side
i'm gonna be mad um this could work very well or this might be very bad i don't know
i gotta put my my i gotta put the butterflies down i will i have a strategy those of you that
are question marking i do have a strategy sorceress i'm worried i have not seen before
is heading towards us those are fire fields kelsey and they are oh it's only one side right now
totally immune to fire damage uh too much stuff that i picked up takes mana that was a mistake
now they're on the other side man that's not cool but my computer crashed mine too
fuck no i i'm still in the game what happened no i it was era i i got i got annihilated
i mean my side's going awful mine's going probably worse i would i wasn't even here
to defend it at the beginning quick get distracted by this
oh and my computer crashed again that's unfortunate uh here they come uh we're gonna
we're about to lose are we are we uh i used my scroll oh you did roll and i saved the day
okay i need to go back enemies at the rift what where where am i where's all my stuff all right
i don't this level's weird i i kind of just want to build up here okay so when we beat this wave
i'm gonna get all my money back because this did not work out i agree all right so let's do a new
strategy here this hammer is kind of a i'm not a huge fan let's put it that way takes mana how is
that butterfly thing working out i haven't really had a chance to try it so you think we should
build in the middle honestly yeah well let's go for it you still made it to the next wave
i mean the stairs this stairs is not a bad idea either but there's a lot of stairs gonna build
a whole bunch of archer people out here they got a long way to go up these stairs i feel like
they get this choke point in here and that's like the first time where it's easy to do anything
about to them because yeah there's this it's really it's the stairs so i mean i'm just gonna
pick a spot downstairs on my side and just hope it works you know what i'm saying i know what
you're saying we could block the top somebody's saying and then they'll just have to go around the
entire other side just put barricades up so they have to literally come all the way up here and
walk all the way around up to the other side that makes a lot of sense and i blocked my door it's
just this area here all right in that case i'm gonna i'm gonna do some butterflies let's try it
i got lasers you know what load that shit up butterflies the optimal spot just keep them here
keep them sitting right here okay i'm ready this will surprise them put it down no ready up
i am ready let's do it how would you fight a pack of orcs in real life i would seduce them okay
i would yeah oh i would fight them with what you'd get destroyed by like a real orc you need some
sort of like cunning guiler charisma you need to riz them up there's no way you're beating an orc
in a 1v1 i don't even want to hear it they're like oh weird that you would like i that's the
only thing i can try i'm gonna kill me i would run thanks for just speaking for me the whole time
okay i would run a barricade is under attack that's weird that's kind of cowardly at least 25
all right are you how you doing over there are you good uh i goof oh like they're getting in but
like who cares oh they're in on your side too okay yeah i thought we were doing a choke point
on the stairs because we blocked off one of the stairways no i fucked up i didn't block one of
the stairs oh we'll be fine i blocked the doorway yeah they're going away is there a okay i hope i
hope we're good here i'll be fine where are you just making shit happen over here they're coming
yeah um there i need help same i'm okay on my side actually you know we're gonna lose like
one wave it's fine i need you can look at the map yeah i don't have any control over this
oh i'm clean over here by the way is that your side i don't know i mean i don't know
yeah i might i need help on my side bad okay probably need some distracting butterflies
where are you oh no other stairs oh that hurts emergency riz needed to try try again so do something
quick um my side's still okay but i need to i have to go defend their cup yeah i believe in you
it's it's going pretty well over here i got a room full of distracting butterflies and a bunch of
lasers they're not getting through this all right come back i need more mana like what's wrong with
that game look dude what the fuck's happening my game why what's happening your game you didn't
look how am i gonna look at your game i i was flying above you that's cute victory uh where do
you want the choke point to be like here because i'll give you some lasers i i'm i'll be fine i
just i spent all my money on nothing and i blocked the door the wrong way well you can have that no
here's here's i just need to block my stairs so they go up your stairs
okay yeah that's that's what i'm doing so i am i safe to get rid of all the things i put here
yeah all right okay and now i need to go find where my useless rows of archers are you have orange
cream mini twizzlers why does that sound amazing orange cream mini twizzlers that sounds great
are they not even on my side brother this is okay this is gonna hurt my eyes
yeah i built all of my archers on your side that that's what we want to do though right
because theoretically they all should be coming up this way don't even worry about it don't even
like just say less hey i've already readied up i'm spending i have 10 000 to spend oh my god
just give me a second just please obama's in the chat hey what's up obama what do you
what do you got cooking up here i'm calling them in because i i can hear how impatient you are
no no i just said i was curious what your plan was i'm i'm we're a team you need to tell me
your plan we're i'm teaming up with you i'm teaming up you want me to put down the you want to put
down the riz here is what you're saying down here we're gonna rhythm up here did i say it right
i think so stop that stop stop it right now i don't okay grandpa the old man thinks he's
hip with the kids but when hold on when stir says it that's okay but you guys don't understand is
stir is also in his 30s why a lot older than me yeah by not by very much i'm 23 i'm young and
hip and i it's totally normal for me to go rollerblading doesn't matter how old you are
you can go rolling that's what i'm saying but i also just happen to be 23 bring him into the
electricity chamber the gondola of pain this actually does like hurt to look at it i i can't
tell if the butterflies are good because i i think you're okay i think they're doing something
decent they open up and they go over there and look at it and they just stare at it for a few
seconds uh i mean yeah i mean i guess they're in the death zone i really can't look at this
i know it kind of hurts cast a spell someone for god's sake cast a fucking spell or something
help yeah i like this where they all come up one tiny simple path and then we win the game
i don't know if this is killing them no it's just making this take longer
but i have to do it for the achievement i wonder if it's up that high if it'll still work i think
so all right boop is down nice i think i'm stalling this wave i apologize uh no this is
better than losing no i i mean i i keep pushing them off and they don't die and they have to walk
back up the stairs again yeah but i mean they'll be a trail of them coming up eventually but then
i push them off again it doesn't loosen uh pull back i gotta heal in 10 seconds oh i couldn't
heal you what a shame unleash the horde we're ready we go put the snow things down uh if i'm
gonna push them i should do it here so i didn't level it up you good oh i wanted to sell these i
guess i can't yeah i'm good i have a strat i need 800 i have to like i'm just gonna look this way
and just hope they are well i'm winning honestly the blunderbuss or the shotgun or whatever it is
with points and it is probably unbelievable i haven't touched anything like besides the bow
and sword and ice it's a shotgun and then it's got a grenade launcher and the grenade launcher it
just does so much damage it's got a huge blast radius still but no no points and i don't have
it's not up yet kill me five seconds you're alive i guess i'll heal myself it wasn't up yet
feel greedy end the stream please scream when i want to end the stream
i need to go to bed and you scream it's past otto's bedtime true so what was it what was
the deal with the hammer it kind of stinks maybe with the other upgrades in it is better
so it's a whirlwind but the whirlwind doesn't really do a whole lot of damage and it takes
mana to do it it's kind of like other things have such a better secondary it hurt it hits
for a lot but it's kind of slow too it's okay hope otto's doing good um yeah he's doing great
i gotta heal for you in three seconds yeah you better i guess you can't get stunned while you
are in the whirlwind so that's kind of a big deal so the big guys the big deal was that it said it
knocked things away it probably does that too have i shit myself yet like once an hour ago
but only a little bit yeah i mean you okay though what's a little shit between friends
i didn't say anything there's a sprint button all right is that is that as bad as me not knowing
that you could headshot people have you been sprinting no so you didn't you didn't know that
either yeah but you had at least you had something too oh that's at least you had something too
what we never pressed shift wait so fast hold on we've just been we've been we've been like
diablo 2 walking yeah wow i can't believe we didn't press the button i was really like this
level takes so long to walk around is it is it does it use manna or stint no you can just
sprint forever man you really can technology these days six almost six and a half hours and
we we pressed ship for the first time in six and a half hours that's incredible you even
remember what button it was yeah it told us that in the very beginning that's so weird that both
of us didn't do it once why self-imposed that's crazy i can't believe we did that
well hey well we made it this far apparently you don't need it one time six hours of rp walking i
know what are we doing the older games had a sprint i know for sure and i've done it we have
to be the only sorry motherfuckers in this whole world that have honestly a developer probably can
like oh let's take a look at the game analytics and see these two clowns have not hit the sprint
button for the entire time they've and i'm not even talking once go through this whole vod i
have not sprinted once ever not one time i got to go kill this special guy no i mean like to
realize i could do it a second ago i pressed it once like shift by accident and my character
moved weird i was like what was that you and i just created a game development study on hold on why
was that why did they do that a customer did that why fast for some reason why where where
is this guy who's destroying everything um this is there i think they're going up i think they
broke what no they didn't know everything's good everything's good my like stomach just might um
this is also why like in game development you make things like excessively easy and you you get the
zelda games where you have the characters hand holding you that everyone hates well like we
we're the reason we were contributing to that we are actually the reason why the game freezes
and says hey press the sprint button right now or you cannot go to the next screen
it's pretty incredible we beat that hard hard level we beat that hard ass level without sprinting
once we that's an achievement that's unbelievable i can't i actually cannot fucking believe that
we're wondering why it was so hard man this game is so hard we would like running around
this level because of how big it was it feels so big and empty and there's no way to get around
quickly i didn't like it i was like this is kind of awkward it's a good thing we can we can lock
up that one door you guys are going to walk so much we're the reason why the resident evil
barrels are bright yellow no that's because of how the contrast is different in no it's real no
there's a real reason for that i don't did you play reasoning before i did not did you ever play
any of the resident evil games i played resident evil one those are great i feel like you would
i've i've watched them be played and i enjoy watching them but i just i don't if the moment
a puzzle shows up i'm gonna quit i'd rather just watch it like the moment i have to match like
a green gem red gem and a blue gem what ordered like i'm out i'm just you know what it's fair
well when you get there just hand it to me and i'll i'll do it for you i'm pretty good at this
that's a good two-star mission we got the thing that i want it scramble unlocked what is scramble
i don't know i want to say site it what is find out reduce damage while spinning first
move speed while spinning i'm not a big fan of the hammer i really don't like it
all right dude i'm gonna get going really yeah i'm getting tired really
okay are you still swimming uh i would feel weird playing orcs must die without you now
i'm gonna go to bed it's late for me you know i'm i'm an early i'm an early sleeper you got me out
here at midnight oh it is it midnight yeah i always forget that being on the west coast
you're always just time travel behind everybody in the united states all right well no i know i
think you're on on the west coast oh i see okay i see yourself yeah like i'm yeah also if you
were saying that's like oh i'll host you like oh i'm done like if you hosted me and i didn't
play five nights at freddy's yeah that's disgusting they'd be an uproar there would
you'd look over a chat and be like when is he playing five nights at freddy's five nights at
freddy's question mark question mark question mark yeah yeah well it's game over well we'll
figure out when to do it but that was a lot of fun that i actually had a really good time
yeah same that's a great game maybe we'd play it again maybe hey maybe we maybe we'd play this
before five nights at freddy's again and just play this for six or seven hours again and not
play five nights at freddy's for a second time in a row it's two dlcs to the game as well i
heard one of them was bad but one of them's good so a lot of content anyway bye i'm gonna let you go
let me know uh anything yeah if you're gonna yeah yeah everybody's closing statement
good night that's a pretty good closing statement see you later sir all right yeah that was fun
that was a good time thanks for watching because that is going to be it how many levels are there
in this game in the base game 18 and then this dlc we got pretty far then we're almost near the
end if that's the case yeah i will see you guys later i'm gonna take a break for a while uh
probably like four or five days actually the next time you see me it might just be five nights
at freddy's mister imagining that might happen oh not brb what am i doing i want to reiterate one
more time get back out of here i want to say this one more time because i don't know how
many people trickled in during the stream but at the very beginning i want to say the thing that
i said before uh if you have if you were part of the presale and you bought a grotto beast
and you had a march estimated ship date represent is going to be in contact they're going to be
sending out an email tomorrow there was a shipping problem that they had it was an error or whatever
it was um i mean obviously no but there's going to be an explanation and we're going to be as
soon as humanly possible putting a shitload of resource into it um expediting as fast as we can
the march estimated orders uh we're all very aware of what's going on over there
and if you were part of the march estimated ship date you're going to get an email tomorrow um
explaining sort of the next steps if there were two estimated ship dates i'm sure you probably know
there was a may somewhere mid to late may was an estimated ship date if you are one of these people
that was affected by this you are not going to have to wait until may you're not going to have
to wait until the end of may these people these early orders that had some kind of problem with
the shipping with the the error whatever happened with represent they're going to tell you and
we're going to go from there we're going to expedite those orders first that's what's going
to happen you're going to get your order it's not a may estimated ship date i've seen that question
pop up a lot obviously it's been pretty frustrating it's been pretty stressful um that's something i
did not want to have happen but it did it did and represent is going to is going to figure it out
and fix it so that's all we know that's what we're going on who is he talking to come on dude and
again thankfully the amount of these early orders that have not been fulfilled yet it is a manageable
amount of orders so we can expedite this process and make sure that you get product so it'll all
be explained in an email that you'll get from represent tomorrow it's frustrating and i'm
obviously pretty upset about it but it is what it is we're doing everything we can to make sure that
whoever is part of this group in march for the march estimated orders they get it as soon as
fucking humanly possible as soon as possible so just keep an eye on your email and we'll go from
there i'm so confused all you need to know the march estimated orders there was an error on
represents front where they were fulfilling orders in the wrong order is essentially how it played
out and they're going to explain that to you and we're going to go from there we're going to try
to make everybody happy trust me when i say this has been the thing that me holly jake and we've
been we've been on this all day every day for two weeks trying to get this situated but the problem
everybody's aware of this problem now and it's we're just gonna fix it there you go is your mic
cutting out wait really shouldn't be oh you're good okay but yeah also if you want to keep up
to date on a lot of this stuff we uh the whole team has been talking in the grotto beast chat
that's in the discord we're giving updates there pretty much every few hours as we get them so
let's uh let's just go from here i'm very confident that we'll get this situated very quickly
and obviously this is not the way i wanted it to play out but it is manageable enough that we can
fix it in a relatively short period of time because a lot of people have gotten it already
and a lot of people have shared wonderful wonderful things all their unboxings and all
their cards they're getting and it's it's awesome and we're super fucking excited to see people
um having a good time with it but there are people that were early orders that got sort of
left out and that does that makes me unhappy so i'm doing everything in my power to make sure
that that is fixed as soon as fucking humanly possible have a great night uh i'm gonna take a
little bit of a break not long maybe like four days five days but this whole last two weeks
i feel like i've been running um essentially in a full sprint uh obviously part of the reason why
you didn't see me for a while before was getting some other grotto be stuff situated the commercial
stuff and i think i want to take a little bit of time at least a few days probably three four days
at least keep an eye on the sus take care of yourselves call your mother thank you for watching
and again if you know somebody that has a march estimated ship date that is like what where's
where's my order uh let them know to keep an eye on their email as of tomorrow thanks guys see you
soon see you in at least three or four days have a great evening have a great night and yeah let's
fucking go five nights at freddy's coming up soon with sir i'm gonna laugh so hard if we do this again
and we just play orcs must die it's five nights at freddy watch along with stir going to be the new
thing that just never happens we just do other stuff every single time it might be all right
take care of yourselves see you later call your mother better not ready but i'll say it again
have a good night