Hello everybody. Okay, give me a moment while I set this up. I should be able to do this.
I spy or we're all gonna leave. No, I have to write a children's book.
Doesn't mean we can't play I spy again. All right, let me uh, let's go. So if I do this,
I should be able to get this open. Close that. I remember when this was an I spy stream.
But, but yes, I spy goes away. But you do get like a on camera guy stream right now. I mean,
we've got a guy on camera writing children's book. I don't know. I don't know. So I need paint.
I need notepad. I got to block this out. I'm not going to do this like stupid. I'm not going to
be like, oh, no, no, no, no, no, I'm not going to make noises. I don't make noises. Okay.
Don't be naked on this camera. Please don't be naked on the camera for one frame. In fact,
I'm going to like open it here to make sure it's not right. I think we're okay. Can you see me?
No, not yet. Good. Good. I don't want you to see me yet. I'm not ready for my like close up.
All right, let's go down here. Let's grab a window. Let's get the paint window,
which there it is. Let's get it nice and clean looking. Those of you think that I'm messing
around, I'm actually going to do this. This is not me fucking around. Sometimes we make jokes and
sometimes we write whole children's books on stream. So I got this. I need like a notepad
to like to write the story. No, this is just to block it out. This is not blocking the scenes out.
Let's go with like a gray background though, because this is gonna, it's gonna like hurt
people's eyes. That's better. Steal my book and publish it. No, you can't do that because
right now you're ready for this. Everything in this stream from here on out going forward,
now I gotta be on camera. Okay. You ready? Was that, that was not like a naked frame, right?
Okay. So everything on stream here for the remainder of the stream here, I am copyright
trademarking the next three hours of the stream. All characters, all original characters and all
text written and created by me, Germa985 on the channel Germa985 will henceforth be under my
property. So here's what we're going to do. Because I don't want to get myself in any trouble. That's
not how it works. Yes it does. I have documented proof. I have a fucking email I sent myself at
fucking six o'clock in the afternoon. Why did I just look into the camera like that? That was weird.
Okay. So I sent an email to myself. This is now copyrighted to mine and I did it first.
So let's go over some characters here because this is important. I'm going to throw out a
few phrases and you guys tell me if they've been made into children's books. I'm going to change
the title too. That's a good, that's a good point. I'm going to change the title to writing a
children's book. This is people are going to come in. Writing a children's book. Is it children?
How do you spell children's? Like children apostrophe S like a children's book or is it
children's book? Yeah. Okay. But IRL, what would it, what is this even categorized as?
What is it? What is this? Just chatting? It kind of, I don't know, creative,
science and technology, special event, education, creator verse. No, that's like a fucking,
that's like a now defunct Minecraft clone, isn't it? I'm just going to put it under,
I can't put this into art. I can't. People are going to come and be fucking angry at this stream.
They're going to be like, who's, who's like, oh, like, oh, a nice art stream. You're drawing
like fucking children's stick figures. Dick. It is art. All right. Fine. It's going to art.
And that is a misleading title. Whatever. It's dumb. All right. We are now in a different
category of writing a children's book. So here, this is very important. Incredibly important.
Number one, I'm going to throw out some characters names. I'm going to throw some characters like
animals and other worldly special effect type creatures. And you tell me if they've been made
into a book before, like a creature book. Okay. Ready? Scenario one. Scary monster that's in the
closet. That's it. That's hiding under the bed or in the closet, right? A person is scared,
but the book is about how the monster just wants a snack late at night from the fridge.
Like Munchy the monster just wants a snack. Has it been done? Been done. Been done. Okay. Like
monster wants to like, go get a snack and it's late at night and he's hungry. I was sure about
this because that's a good idea. Okay. So you've done it before. So you've done it before. All
right. Small animal needs help doing basic human activities. That's a big one for a lot of these,
right? So you've got like mouse needs help tying shoes. It's been done before. Small
rat learns how to ride a bike. Been done? That may have been done. Give a mouse a cookie. That's
right. Okay. We can't do that one. Ratatouille. Yeah. But does Ratatouille learn how to ride a
bike? No. So Ratatouille in the movie does not learn how to ride a bike. Okay. Okay. So that's
a D. He does ride a bike. I can't throw that one in the trash. Okay. So what about, um,
there's another, another view. That's the route we can go down. Well, we'll vote on it.
So we'll put it up on the screen here. So we got small animal doing basic human children's task.
Okay. I'm going to call that option two. So let me write that out. So we've got small animal. It's
great. Doing basic children's tasks. Put it in bold. Cause I like that. All right. Can we,
can I make that bigger? I don't know. How the fuck do I even do that? Okay. So this is that,
that is that option. So now we've got, I really liked the idea of something that is scary. Like
is another thing, right? Something that is scary, but is shown over the course of like the 15 pages
to not be scary. We're talking dentist. We're talking doctor. We're talking, uh, haircut,
go to the haircut. Has it been a haircut book? Scary haircut, but it's not, it's had these been
done. All right. But things, things that are, would you fucking let me write this things that
are scary to a child, but actually not. Right. Well, actually the dentist is fucking scary. I
haven't been in like three years. So that's, I don't know if I agree with that one. I take the
dent, take, take dentists off the list because that's scary. Okay. Uh, we got things that are
scary to a child, but actually not small animal doing basic children's tasks. Uh, we've got
learning, right? So like counting, uh, alphabet. I mean, this has been done a lot. They're like
a for alligator B for bear, like that, read that kind of thing. Learning, learning material,
not super fond of that, but we can, we keep it there. Okay. So there's learning material,
things that are scary to it, but they're not small animal doing basic children's tasks. Or
I think we don't want to get too fussy here though. Do the dentist book so I can convince
myself that the dentist is not scary. That's really funny, but not today. All right. Learning
material, small animal doing basic. Okay. How about growing up, right? There's things you need
to know, like how to fucking write a check. The child learns, right? Think growing up,
writing a check, doing laundry, um, bathroom, like going to the bathroom. There's a shit load
of those books growing, like go into the bathroom. So we got growing up things that are scary to a
child, but are not small animal doing basic children's tasks, learning material, growing up.
Um, what else? What else? What else? What else? What else? What else? What else?
You guys got me how to do taxes. That's not for, that's not a children's book.
Uh, dealing like with, with consequences, like, like the wizard of Oz, that was a,
that was a hilarious children's book, right? Go into like the wizard of Oz. That would have,
what a hysterical trip that was when they met the lion and the dog.
Got to keep it simple. Things kids should not do, but I think that goes into, yeah, like, but that
growing up kind of fits that category too. How to deal cards. Kids aren't going to dealers.
How to play Fortnite. Don't make me write that. I think these are good. I think this is good.
I think we got to the basic four here. Or, you know, there also is just like for fun,
like the cat in the hat, the cat in the hat didn't have a fucking message. A cat shows up
and breaks a bunch of shit in their house and like does a bunch of drugs. The cat in the hat
has no act, does the cat in the hat have an actual meaning? The cat in the hat had a meaning. I don't
remember that. It's about responsibility. Okay. Um, James and the giant peach. A giant peach
rolls into New York and like fucking catamari meatballs in front of James and he gets on it.
And then like, they go on a funny adventure. That was it. He meets like a bunch of bugs.
That's the, what was that one? It was about friendship. Got it. Uh, friendship or love.
Okay. Friendship or love. I'm going to block this out too. I'm getting, I'm getting a flow chart.
We're going to have like 17 different scenarios. We're going to like just be ready to write the
book and then I'm going to go to bed. Okay. I'm going to look at all this material that we got.
All right. See you tomorrow. Is he doing the bit yet? This is not a bit. What bit? I told you one
guy said that I've got, you can't write it. You never got to write a children's book. You're not
talented. And I said, what the fuck? All right. I think we're good. So things that are scary to
a child, but not small animal doing basic children's tasks, learning material, growing up
friendship or love, or like a learning, like teaching or learning a lesson. Right. But I guess
that could be growing, growing, growing up or no, cause that like going to the bathroom is not like
learning how to do something. No, learning a lesson could be anything. Right. So I'm going
to move these around. How do you even, how do you select something? Oops. How do I do this?
How do I grab this? All right. Yeah. You just don't. Okay. So just make sure you click in the
right spot. So we got, we're almost ready to start here. What do you guys think? Let me get out of
the way. And by the way, this does not dictate exactly what we're doing. This is just like a,
what do you guys think? Write a book about the bear? No, it's got to be, it has to be very simple.
Where, where's my click thing? All right. What do you think? Hold on. You can't see them. Okay.
It looks like a lot of people gravitating towards small animal doing basic children's tasks.
Once we pick one, we have to be damn sure that it doesn't exist already.
We're going to write out like every basic children's tasks that I can think of
small animal going to the dentist, like biting the guy's hand. No, we can't put that in.
All right. I would probably gravitate. What do you want to do? Edit colors?
I'm not going to paint with 3d. So someone said mix them all together. So we've got a
learning material, a math book about a small animal doing a basic task,
something that's scary, but it's not learning a lesson at the end and growing a little
and finding a friend along the way. I'll be a millionaire in a few years.
It's a small animal doing basically, let's, let's, let's get this shit out of my face.
All of it. I don't want to leave and look at it. Oh, that doesn't look right. It looks even worse.
How do I, how do I do that? How do you delete text? I got shit to do. Okay. Okay. So we,
I don't, I don't use paint to draw like in like the black marker and that's it.
All right. So we got easy. I'm going to eat. What was it? The task. So we've got tasks
that are a basic human tasks that an animal is going to do. I got one for you right now.
Lawn care. Okay. Forget about the animal because we got to pick one that hasn't happened yet.
Lawn care, basic human task, laundry, cleaning, cleaning the house like a duck that cleans the
house. That's pretty good. Or a very large animal that's cleaning the house. And you think that it's
funny because they bump into stuff and break stuff and then they have to clean that up too.
That's pretty funny. Oh, that's pretty funny. Like a, like a bowl has to clean like a bear,
turtle. Okay. What? No, no, no. Okay. Shopping. Like whether that's, uh, I'll make it clear.
Rocherie or otherwise. Okay. What else? Capitalism versus communism. We're talking
about like laundry here. No, doing homework. That's a basic task, right? Homework. Um,
reading, like learning to read, but that's kind of learning, but it's that's all a basic human thing.
Teaching like a fucking alien to read. It could be that doesn't have to be, it could be an alien.
This could be the first alien, uh, children's book. Cooking. We've got lawn care, laundry,
cleaning, shopping, homework, reading, cooking, uh, eating healthy. Pretty, yeah, that's pretty
basic stuff. Hiding a body. You want this thing to sell or do you want me to like get in trouble?
Computer, computers. Ooh, we got a whole new generation of kids that are going to be on
computers and iPads, computers and tablets. Like a rat with a computer, like a mouse will get the
fuck out of here. A mouse on the mouse. Has it, no one's done it. Has somebody done like a computer
kids learning, like fun, like kids computer mouse with a mouse? No, they haven't. No, they haven't.
We'll get the mouse a headset too and it'll be like talking because that's people are going to be
talking on headsets. These kids are growing up with the fucking technology. ABC mouse is already
a thing and that's what they do. Is that real? ABC mouse isn't a book. It's yeah, it's an online
fucking web media portal. Yes, it is. Game. Okay. Keep that in mind. Keep like, okay, I'm going to
just make sure I don't forget this. Possible gaming mouse. No, no, no, not gaming mouse. Fucking
computer mouse. Computer mouse. You know what I mean here. Okay. So we've got computers and tablets,
possible computer mouse. Farms. Out on the farm. Right. I know there's a few that already exist,
but it's okay. We can have our own different one. Basic human task. No, skateboarding is not
basic. It's hard. Self-defense class. That's not dancing, but that's, yeah, you know, dance. Okay.
Dancing. Let me fix that. Dancing is possible. Crypto investing. Construction. No, I don't know
anything about construction. General like housework. No, that's like kind of cleaning.
Gardening. I would put that under lawn care. Hygiene. Yeah. Hygiene is a good one. Hygiene.
I don't know if I spelled that right. Who gives a shit. How to steal things from work. Manners.
Basic. Very basic human thing. Yeah. They always have like, oh, it's a fucking monster that doesn't
know manners. A monster that doesn't understand manners and needs to be taught manners by the
family. Has it happened? Why does everything, including a monster, had to have happened in
Monster's Ink already? Teaching a monster manners. Teaching a monster hygiene. Like a monster doesn't
brush its teeth. A monster does not brush its teeth. And there'd be a really cute panel of them both.
You know, like it could be like a little girl, like just barely being able to see above the sink,
like brushing the teeth. There's a huge monster like brushing and there's like soap all over his
mouth. And he brushes his teeth with the soap because he didn't know. That literally happens
in Monster's Ink. That's been done thousands of times. I don't believe you. Hold on. Monster's
Ink brushing teeth. God damn it. He does brush. He brushes his fucking teeth in the mirror.
All right. Forget that one. No monsters and hygiene. It's been done. Monsters and cooking.
They don't know how to cook. So monsters. What? No, no. We're going too far. Stop it. We're going
too far. Forget about the main character. Get the composition of the story first. Okay? Dancing
monsters. Haven't done that yet. So okay, we're getting to the point where we can pick.
I think this is good. So now over here, we are going to put people or things, right? Animals or
maybe not animals. We got rats. We got mouse. We've got alligator. We've got, we got monsters. We have
aliens. We have a chipmunk. We've got duck, crabs, lobsters, mollusks. No, that's way too weird.
Kid doesn't know what a fucking mollusk is. Armadillo. Lobster modillo? That's not right.
How do I fix this? Lobster, armadillo, aardvark. Aardvark is pretty good. Frog. Frog
and toad are the same thing, by the way. A seagull. A germ. Oh, actually, you know what?
That's kind of funny. Like a germ that needs to learn how to eat healthy. A germ that needs to
learn how to cook. A germ that needs to learn hygiene. What? You know what I mean? Like what
the fuck? That's so weird. Not good enough. It's not good enough. Okay. Germ. A stove.
I thought about, okay. A bear. A turtle. I'm not writing gnome. It's not an animal. Cats. Yeah.
Cats. Dogs. All right. All right. Hold on. Slow down. Slow down. We don't want to get too crazy
here. Snake. All right. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. Rat, mouse, alligator, monster, alien,
chipmunk, dog, crab, lobster, armadillo, aardvark, frog, seagull, germ, bear, turtle, cat, dog, snake,
a cinder block. An animate object might be kind of interesting. We could pull a like a beauty
and the beast and then lose everything because Disney will DMCA claim my life. An elephant
learning how to fucking brush its teeth. That's pretty cute. Elephant. Spider. Whoa. Whoa. What?
I'm losing something here. What did we lose? All right. All right. That's enough. That's enough.
That's enough. That's enough. Enough. I got it. No more. That's good. What was under elephant? I
don't even. Spider. All right. Spider is down here. Just remember that. So then in the middle here,
we are going to put a theme. Okay. A theme right here. The theme is going to go down here.
Oh, what the fuck? So if you can, if you've got a rat doing laundry, what happens? You know what I
mean? We've got aliens doing homework, but what's the theme? Where are like, we need like a setting.
That's important. Setting. Just throw them out here. I'll take, I'll take a few of them.
Like setting. Okay. You, the, no, but the United States is way too vague. Like the kitchen or
like a home, right? A house. Okay. College. Like in college. The playground, right? Like we're outside
in the garden at space in the, on the moon, on the moon, on the sun in space,
in VR, in olive garden, in a restaurant, in a restaurant. I don't, who cares? On a cinderblock
and a castle. That's a good one. Nice. Excellent work in the school, right? Like in the school,
we're like learning how to like read in school. We're learning how to clean in school. Okay.
In underwater. Okay. School and underwater school. I'm liking it. Not in the casino,
not in prison, in the sky, on a cloud, on a cloud, like on Mount Olympus or something, right?
In the, in the dirt. No, in the grass. Well, we've got, we got garden, right? In the garden.
I think we got some good ones. In the wild west. That's not a bad setting. It's like, you know,
like the cactuses, the cacti, the sun. It could work. Set the book in hell. I don't think that's
going to work. At the beach. Nobody said the beach yet. Come on. The beach. What's perfect
for half of these? At the amusement park. Yep. Like the theme park. No. Yeah. Theme park. Like
an amusement park. At the, but the fair could be the theme park. On a mountain. Okay. In a graveyard.
I don't know. Graveyard might be a little too scary. I think graveyard would be too scary,
I think. But like maybe it'd be possible. Like at the graveyard. Maybe you could like make it
like a Halloween theme. You can make like a Halloween theme children's book. It's like,
ooh, like we're at the graveyard and okay. Now like the mall. Okay. I think this is good
because I'm going to show you what we're going to do now because this is important. The zoo. Oh,
you've got it right at the end there. The zoo. The zoo. The zoo. The farm. I can't forget the farm.
So here's what we're going to do. We're going to play a game called each one of these is getting
a number and they're going to be thrown into a random number generator and we're going to pull
them up. So for instance, category one will be numbered category two, category three,
and we're going to just pull them fucking out randomly. That's the plan. So let's go ahead
and do that. I think, I think this is good. Let me, I think that's it. Right now. Like anybody,
anybody else see one at the hospital? That could work. Okay. Two for it. What the fuck?
I got to move this though. Okay. So we have, let's see what we've got for numbers here. I'm
just going to do this very, very easily. I need to open up like random number generator.
So we need to generate numbers. So we need to number these. This is one,
two for it. Who's that? What kid is going to know what the fuck two for it is? So we've got one,
two. Let's just number them just to do it. Uh, with the, where's like a crayon? Just give me a crayon.
So we've got, who cares? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's not, that's the same category. Delete that. 11, 12, 13, 14.
I'm just realizing it's very possible we're going to get like a seagull at the zoo out on the farm
or like a crab on a cloud eating healthy. Oh, this is going to get fucking weird. I love it.
Set the book here. What is this? Oh God. Me brushing my teeth. That's so cute.
A seagull in the hospital in the wild west. Some of these are going to be hard to do,
but I'm going to do them. Okay. So we got one, two, three, 14 things. Fucking God damn it. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight, 11, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 18. That settings are themes.
There's so many of these. One, two, three, six, seven, eight, nine. It's hard to do this.
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20. And spider is 21. 21 is spider. Okay.
You mislabeled the activities. Aliens at school. Otherwise. It's too late. I can't fucking fix it.
I don't care. Are you ready? So here we go. Kat, let's get a number generator over here.
Let me get it. Hold on. I got random.org. This is truly just random. Let's get a good image of
that on screen. Where is this? Oops. No, I should be able to get a nice box here. One second. Bear
with me here. Otherwise. I'm a fucking idiot. I'm doing like, I'm doing like fucking skexy neck. I
got to like straighten up. You know, they're remaking the dark crystal. Why is Kobayashi
versus giant bear still here? Okay. Random.org. There it is. Well, you can't see it, but there
it is. Where the fuck? No, that's, that's just not right. Is it? There we go. Okay. Let's make it so
it's nice and prominent. So, you know, I'm not fucking faking any of these because I could fake
them. We're not faking it. All right. Here we go. You can still see everything, right? I'll get the
fuck out of the way a little bit too. Here we go. So we got, this is for category one. Category one
there's a 14 different responses, right? So no, no, no, we need to do category, no, no,
category three first. So that's 21. We need to find out what we're working with. So we're
working with one of the 21. Here we go. Bingo. 19. We've got a snake, a snake on a cloud,
snake on a cloud. Otherwise. We're going to stick on a cloud. Otherwise. How do you make that a book?
Uh, so let's write it down. We got snake on a cloud. We're going to do this like 10 times.
We picked the best one. Snake on a cloud. Otherwise is the first one. This is an ugly fucking
text here. Here we go. Let's do it again. We got, uh, we're going to go same category one,
one out of 21. County, the next possible option, uh, a seagull, a seagull at the beach,
seagull at the beach. Oh, seagull at the beach learning manners. Cause holy fuck man. Seagulls
perfect. Seagulls are assholes. They're eating people's like french fries and they're like
flying over, shitting on people at the beach. Oh my God. Somebody gave a lot of money. That's
perfect. A seagull at the beach learning manners because they're fucking, they're like flying rats
and they're, they're, they, they like eat people. They're like vultures. Oh, I like that one. But
somebody gave a lot of money. Uh, La Cranda just gave 50 bucks. Thank you so much for the $50
La Cranda. Snakes on a cloud sounds like a good sequel to snakes on a train. Snakes on a plane.
So, all right. Thank you so fucking much for the $50. It's a huge amount of money.
My God. Snakes on a plane clouds snakes on a cloud. Otherwise. I like this one a lot. This is
great. Seagulls at the beach learning manners. Perfect. Let's move it over here. We're going to
do this like another six, six or seven times. We didn't spend like 35 minutes making this.
We only do it once. You get the fucking idea. All right. Let's do it again. Next category.
I know you can't see it. Don't worry. I'll move it. No. Oh yeah. Well, I'll move out of the way
in a second. There's a lot of possible outcomes here. We have to see a lot of them because I'm
going to vote on which one's the one. Here we go. Animal or thing. 21. We got nine. Lobsters.
Lobsters. Pretty good start. Lobsters in a restaurant. It's writing itself.
Doing homework. Lobsters in a restaurant doing homework. And at the end of the book,
they get like dropped into the boiling water. Uh, no, that's I don't know. I don't want to write
that one. Uh, lobsters in the restaurant doing homework. The seagull book already exists. No,
it doesn't. If that fucking book exists, I'm going to have a meltdown. Greedy, naughty seagull at the
beach. James is a little bear who happens to save a seagull that has some behavioral problems. One
day James goes fishing with the seagull. James is disappointed with the bird's display of greed
when she eats nearly all the catches. James replaces the fish by spending his pocket money
to buy fish for the at the beach seagull being greedy at the beach, not knowing manners.
Delete it. Uh, snake on a cloud. Otherwise lobster, lobster at the restaurant. But you
understand how this one can't be done that the lobster is at the restaurant. They're like the
food at the restaurant. So it's going to be dark. This one can't be done. Lobster at the restaurant
doing homework. And then they get like eaten. Like they're at, what are they doing at the restaurant?
Okay. Well, I got it written down. Let's do it again. One, two, 21, 16. We've got turtles
or a turtle. A turtle at the zoo. Turtle at the zoo doing laundry. Turtle at the zoo doing laundry.
That's very, very easy. Turtle at the zoo doing laundry. Okay. We'll do it again. We got, we got
four and one of them I can't do. Three of them I can't do. Uh, we've got a bear. So that's bear
at the zoo. You fucking better not be doing laundry. Learning manners. Bear at the zoo
learning manners. That's a, that one's a resident sleeper. Okay. Only like a few more and then we'll
move on from here. This is, we've got monsters. Monsters. Monsters in a castle. Does it know
that I'm trying to do this? Monsters in a castle dancing. That's not bad. Monsters in a castle
dancing. Okay. What else we got? I want 10. That's one, two, three, four, five, six. That's called
Shrek. Now, but Shrek was one monster. This is multiple monsters. All like a ball or something.
All right. 120. Let's go. 13. Seagull again. A seagull underwater eating healthy. An underwater
seagull eating healthy. He might have scuba gear on, right? That's possible. It'd be funny
if he had to hold his breath and go underwater. Don't they have to do that anyways? To like eat
fish? This is going to get messy. I got to shrink these. Seagull underwater eating healthy. I got
the font has to be smaller. This is too big. Okay. Three more. Let's get a good animal here.
We've got two seagulls. Alligator. An alligator at the beach. What are you doing at the beach?
Reading. Learning how to read. That one sucks. How do you make a coherent story with an alligator
learning how to read on the beach or just reading on the beach? That one sucks. All right. Two more.
An aardvark at school. Aardvark at school. Thank God. Doing homework. This is a copywritten
character already. We have to trash this one. That's an aardvark at school doing homework.
There was a PBS show that ran for like 40 years about that exact topic.
That one's vetoed. I'm not even going to write it down. Cats. We got a cat or multiple cats
at the zoo. Cats at the zoo. Otherwise. Great. Fucking hell. All right. Vetoed Arthur,
so I got to do another one. 20. That's an elephant. Elephant in the wild west.
This could be good. Reading. An elephant in the wild west learning how to read.
Fucking reading. I'll write it down. I wish we got shopping. They're all over the place,
but don't worry. I got a system. All right. Three more and we're done. Aliens. No matter what they
are, I'm going to keep them. Even if they're copywritten, even if it's Mickey Mouse learns
to read, I'm going to keep it. So we get aliens in a restaurant. Aliens in a restaurant. What are
they doing there? Cleaning. They're teaching aliens cleaning a restaurant. They don't know
anything about like humans and they can like learn. Watching them eat. Humans. Humans.
Eating humans. It's Twilight Zone level. Snakes. I didn't know. I put my head down and snorted.
God damn it. What's the next one? Okay. We've got aliens. Why? Oh, I don't like this. What are they
doing? They're on a mountain observing humans. Aliens on a mountain cleaning.
Okay. Aliens on. Where did that go? What are they cleaning? I don't know. That's just predator.
Okay. Elephants. Elephants in space. Elephants in space. This is great so far. Elephants in space.
What are they doing though? Something cool. Come on. Give us a good one. Oh that means they're dead.
That means they're dead. Elephants in space. Out on the farm as they say. All right. I gotta go.
I gotta get out of here. I gotta get out of here. Only like one more of these fucking things.
We have so many categories already. All right. We got an armadillo. No. Fuck it. Ready? Lightning
round. Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang. What are you gonna get? What are we gonna get?
Something, something, something, something. Nine lobsters. Lobsters. I wonder where they're
gonna be. Lobsters on a mountain. Lobsters on a mountain. There they go. Where are they? What's
the plan here? They're shopping. I can work with all this. I can work with it. Last one and we're
moving on. We have to block something out here. We've got a turtle. Turtle in a restaurant. There's
so many in a restaurant. Shopping in a restaurant. For what? One more and then we have to do
elimination. This is the final one. Absolutely no questions asked. Last one. A seagull on a cloud.
Seagull on a cloud doing lawn care or gardening. Okay. That's one more. Last one. Last. This is
actually the last one. No questions asked. Final one. That's a duck. No, no, no, no, no, no. That
was a duck. I got duck on the farm learning computers and tablets and that's it. That's
fucking it. I gotta get these together. I gotta get out of here. Okay, here we go. We can close
out of this. All right, so this is a mess. I gotta clean these up. Okay, clean them up. Doesn't
matter how they look. We just gotta get them in the right spot. We gotta start eliminating them.
Right here. Alligator reading on the beach. Duck on a farm learning computers.
Seagull on a cloud learning lawn care. Aliens in a restaurant observing humans and cleaning while
they observe humans and stuff like that from outer space. Yep. Elephant learning how to read in the
wild west. Aliens on a mountain cleaning. Elephants in space on the farm. Lobsters shopping on a
mountain. Snake on a cloud otherwise. Seagulls at the beach learning manners. Lobster at the
restaurant doing homework. Turtle at the zoo doing laundry. Bear at the zoo learning manners.
Monsters in a castle dancing and seagull underwater eating healthy. This is very messy.
I gotta get a notepad open. Nobody can read this. This hurts. This looks like a glitch in a computer
game. This looks like you just grabbed the N64 cartridge and fucking pulled it out halfway through
your game. All right, let me get a like actual notepad because this shit ain't gonna work.
Notepad. A rich rich text document is also good. Let me get that off the screen before somebody
fucking throws up. Where am I? No, I don't know. I'm all squished. Go back to normal. There we go.
All right. Uh, it was very thin. So that's that. Get the notepad open. Okay, I gotta get this
fucking clean. You know what I'm saying? So we've got turtle in a restaurant shopping.
That one sucks. We've got cats at the zoo otherwise. Alligator. Alligator of reading on the
beach. No, what do I do? Just put it in a straw poll. What the fuck am I doing? You know what I'm
saying? Like just put it in a straw poll. Why am I writing it over here? Uh, by the way, top five
answers move on and then I'm gonna fucking decide which one. Uh, let's get one over here.
Okay, uh, so let me get, I'm gonna just condense these so they're easier because there's a bunch
of them. We get cat shopping at the farm, right? What was it? Okay, we got turtle in a restaurant
shopping. Let's clean them up, right? Let's just get it clean. Cats at the zoo otherwise. Top five
move on, by the way. I know I just said that, but I'm gonna reiterate it. Alligator reading
on the beach. Duck on the farm learning computers. Uh, seagull on a cloud doing lawn care.
Aliens in a restaurant observing humans and cleaning. Aliens, turtle doing laundry.
Did I miss one? Chat, what am I looking at here? A mess, but it's gonna be cleaned up right now.
Okay, uh, we've got elephant learning to read in the Wild West. Almost getting on,
almost halfway there. Aliens on a mountain cleaning. Elephants in, oh fucking god damn it.
I pressed enter. Fuck. Can I add to this? Damn it. I gotta do it again. Fuck me. I pressed enter and
it like stopped it halfway through. Fuck. All right, well, hold on. Ah! All right, I gotta do
it again. I'm just gonna copy and paste. Yeah, I gotta put it like a fucking video for you guys
to watch. Hold on. This won't take long. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Turtle in a restaurant
shopping. Cats at the zoo otherwise. Alligator at the beach. Duck on the farm learning computers.
Seagull on a cloud doing lawn care. Aliens in a restaurant observing humans and cleaning.
Elephant learning to read in the Wild West. Aliens on a mountain cleaning. Okay, uh, lawn care.
All right, now I got just a few more. What was the last one? Aliens from, aliens from outer space on
a mountain cleaning. Right up there. Elephants in space out on the farm. Uh, alien, uh, elephants
in space on the farm. Uh, undo lobster shopping on a mountain. Oh, that's a lot of work. Damn. Snake
on a cloud otherwise. Seagulls at the beach learning manners. Lobster at the restaurant
doing homework. Fucking morbid. Almost done. Turtle at the zoo doing laundry. Bear at the zoo
learning manners. Monsters in a castle dancing. And seagulls, seagull underwater eating healthy.
We're ready. That's it, right? I didn't miss any. We have a straw poll already. Well, I made the
official one. It's already done. Great poll. Somebody made it 10 minutes ago. Uh, just use
the official one. Top five, move on. And then whatever the top five are, I'm going to determine
which one I'm going to write a book about. Since we're voting on this, we get writing credit. How
many people are here? 5,068 people. It's going to be like a, it's going to be like a Kickstarter.
All right. The book is going to be like 200 pages long because it's going to be like
12 pages for the book and then 195 pages for the Kickstarter credits. All right. Let's see
what we got here. Uh, we got the aliens from outer space observing humans in restaurant and cleaning
snake on cloud. Otherwise duck on the farm learning computers. Seagull on a cloud doing
lawn care. Seagull underwater eating healthy. This fucking snake one. Okay. Link the poll.
There you go. Let's see what's at the bottom. Let's see what nobody wanted. Turtle at the zoo
doing laundry has 19 votes out of 1400 people that clicked it. Holy shit. Nobody wants to see that
one. Uh, it's what's with the turtles. What's with the hatred versus the turtle? Turtle in a
restaurant shopping and turtle at the zoo doing laundry. Fucking nobody clicked on them.
Although they, they, they do suck. So not turtles, but like the restaurant shopping and like the
category didn't come out that well. Also lobsters in space, odd on the farm. I'm surprised it's this
low. That's just elephants are dead. We've got the aliens from outer space at a restaurant observing
humans and cleaning snake on cloud. Otherwise duck on the farm. See, all right. You got like 30
seconds. Okay. This is artwork. That's really good. Look at that. It's already fucking there for you.
That's already made for you. It's already here. That's already cover art. How do you make it so
fast? All right. 10 seconds and the poll closes. And then I monsters in a castle dancing is down
there in the middle. So we've got the top five. Thank you for voting. Uh, I'm going to write just
to make sure they have them. We've got aliens from outer space in a restaurant observing humans
and cleaning snake on a cloud. Otherwise duck on the farm, learning computers, seagull on a cloud,
doing lawn care, seagull underwater, eating healthy. I think I could work with some of those
seagull underwater. Okay. Here we go. I am going to put these new poll, new poll. Let's get a new
poll going. This is the final five. Just make it a short story. Yeah. It's going to be like
10 pages long. Write them all and then do a crossover like the Avengers. No. Okay. Snake
on the cloud. The snake one. No, that's another thing. We have to make sure that of these top
five, they don't exist already. Is there a duck on a farm learning computers? Because if there is,
it can't be done. We tried our best to make original content. All right. We've narrowed
it down and then I get to have my vote, which is worth 600 votes. So just be aware. All right.
Here's the final poll. I'm going to take a piss while you guys vote on this last one.
There it is. And then it's time to start writing the book, doing lawn care. I'll be right back.
I'm going to pee. Good luck. And then I'm going to start blocking the book out and they're doing
panels. Are we reaching a consensus? No. Yes. No. Okay. Duck friends, computer chase. What is this?
Give me the middle finger. All right. It looks like at the moment here, we got snake on a cloud
otherwise is currently the winner. Snake on a cloud. Otherwise. Jesus Christ. How the fuck am
I going to write a book about this? Duck on the farm learning computers. It could have been
seagull on a cloud doing lawn care. What the fuck does that mean? Snake on a cloud. Otherwise.
This one keeps turning me upside down. Okay. But how did you get up there? All right. It's time.
I think it's time to figure it out. So here we go. Let's block it out. This is it. Snake on a cloud.
Otherwise. It's going to be like an indifferent snake that doesn't care. Got up on a cloud somehow.
How's he going to get down? How did he get up there? What? Brilliant. What did I just say?
What did I say? Clip that. Somebody clip it. Clip it. Clip it. Clip it. Clip it. Right now.
Clip that. Right now. Give it to me. Give it to me. What I just said. I don't remember, but it was
good. That was good. Let's block it out. This is it. Snake on a cloud. I rhymed it. Otherwise.
It's going to be like an indifferent snake that doesn't care. Doesn't care. Got up on a cloud
somehow. How's he going to get down? How did he get up there? Fucking brilliant. That's the opening
line. How's he going to get? That doesn't care. Snake. This is a story about a snake that doesn't
care. That doesn't care. Got up on a cloud. Got up on a cloud. How did he get there?
Write that down. So make sure everybody writes that down. But no, me. Oh, me write that down
because it's my book. What did I say again? I repeat that again. What was it? It's going to
be like an indifferent snake that doesn't care. There once was a snake that didn't care. Got up
on a cloud somehow. How did he get up there? What did I just say? What did I say? Clip that.
Somebody clip it. Clip it. Clip it. Clip it. Right now. Clip that. Right now. Give it to me.
But sometimes I just like just pure genius. All right. That's the opening line.
When you get an opening line, that's how you get started. I don't care about the other categories.
This one wins. So we're going to do we're going to start with the it's flowing now. It's flowing.
Get back to where I was right here. Okay. Get all this out of here. I don't want to look at this.
Okay. Let's block it out. So the first panel, first page, this is going to be this can be page
one. Okay. Page one is there once was a snake that didn't care. Got up on a cloud somehow.
How'd he get up there? That's a little too wordy. I think. Hold on. Page one. There once was a snake
that didn't care. That's page one. The cover comes later. Okay. This is page one. Easy words for
children. There once was a snake that did not care. This is not the layout. I just got to get
it on the front first page. Huge fucking fun. And we'll block that out later. I got to get the
the basis of the first page. So here's what I'm thinking. So you've got I just Kramered. I'm sorry.
There once was a snake that did not care. We've got establish the perimeter here. We got
we got to look it up here like this. You know what I mean? I've seen the cloud and it's just
an establishing of the cloud. Like they're like fucking children right here. Take a look at this.
All right. I need the paint tool now. There's remember we need like 12 pages. Okay. So we
got the kids down here. They're like outside. Remember I'm going to I'm going to fucking
commission an artist. So we got I'm not an artist. Let's go with like okay. So up here we got like
cloud right because they're looking up. You can have a couple other clouds like over here
in this section. Maybe a couple like over here in this section. This is the one the snakes are.
Don't fucking forget it. It's important. So maybe there's like a ball. There's a two. There's a ball
bouncing between. I got to just I got to get the action of the ball because I'll forget it.
There's a ball. No, no, no, no lower ball. Like like I just kicked it. You know what I mean?
That's the ball. Then you've got let's have the we're going to stick figure because I can't draw
anything. So you've got like one kid here. You know this like it's a kid. Right. This is I need
the kick of the ball. Right. Easy. Okay. Easy. It's fucking easy. And then another kid is like here.
Easy. Maybe like catching a bit like oh I'm about to catch it. Like here it comes.
Oh maybe like yeah. So the kid is about to catch the ball. They're very happy. Right. Like that's
a good. This person looks like they're getting a ball kicked to their face. They don't look very
happy. Well he doesn't. But look I fixed it. So this is the playing of the ball. There once
was a snake that did not care. And then the reader that has no idea. Right. Reader has no clue what
the fuck you're talking about. What do you mean that once was a snake that did not care.
This I see kids playing. There's a house over here too. So we've got the house and there once
I don't see a snake here sir. Right. That's not a factory. That is a house. It's that's a chimney.
What are you linking me here. This that's pretty good. But I didn't get that far yet.
But that was exactly I didn't get that far. But you got you getting the right idea.
No this is a chimney. It's cold. Look they're wearing jackets. All right. That's the ball
playing ball. There once was a snake that did not care. But we make sure we had the clouds are very
prominent in this shot. They are like wow it's pretty pretty. God fuck. It's all right.
They're huge. So this is the first page. And then maybe like a couple of birds.
And then maybe for the people with the keen eyes. What color is a snake. This is very important.
Green. Blue. Pink. Red. Blue. Like you could like a little like right there. Like a little
face. Little snake face with tongue coming out. Just like oh I see him. Right. Kids love that shit.
Kids love to be like there once was a snake. Where's this. I found him. Right. The sky is blue.
Then the snake can be. But is there but is there any copywritten green snakes.
Is that make sure there's no copywritten green snakes. Are there. None. There are a lot. It's
a green snake. Snakes are green. Yeah but I don't know what there's like a copywritten fucking snake.
All right. Well we need to maybe like a green. There once was a snake that didn't care.
There's a little face popping just barely over that cloud. So they could point it out and be
like wait is what is that. And then we're gonna medium zoom. Next page. Save this one. There once
was a snake that did not care. All right. I'm gonna save this. Let's just open up another one.
Open. How do I quickly just open a new paint. The next page is just this image.
Yeah you guys are getting it. You are. The gray makes this very depressing.
Now the grays do not hurt your eyes. What's the what's the fucking. Do I need to open like
another one of these. Can I just do new. Well let's delete this one. It's control n right.
Can I do tabs. Save as png. I'm gonna title this page one. Okay. And then just control n.
Control n. That works. Look I told you it's gonna hurt your eyes. That's why I want to block this
shit out. Because look. Nope. Right there. Like I just blew everybody's eyes out. So then we got
the the next one is there once was a snake that did not care. Got up on a cloud. How'd he get there.
Got up on a cloud. How'd he get there. 50 dollars just came in. From some guy. Thanks for 50 bucks.
Okay so I've got the greatest idea. Let's say the snake got up on the cloud because he didn't care.
Right. That's how he got there. But he got removed far from his friends. He's lonely. He wants to get
back down and through a process of learning how to care again he gets back off the pedestal he
created for himself. That's too deep for kids. I was gonna have him like fucking ride up on a
rainbow because like he don't underestimate kids. Well he could still get up there because he wanted
to get away. He didn't care and he he got removed from his friends and maybe there's a bunch of
snakes. This is gonna be groundbreaking book. But how did you get up there? Rainbow is the serpent.
Rainbow snake already exists. Well it doesn't matter. Okay well that's a great fucking idea.
I'm gonna hold on to that for a second while we make panel two. So this is panel two. We gotta
get first two panels. Uh the once was snake that did not care. Got up on a cloud. How. Remember
it's gonna be simple english. Like how did he get there. But we only got you look all these kids
books are not even one sentence per page. How are we gonna get like a struggle in here. The cloud is
from the it's not a factory. It's not a factory. Okay so again here we go page two. We are we are
now up here. Put some more back here for for distance and depth and that way there and then
here he is looking down. You know he's like staring down like that. I don't know how to
do that in uh pretend painting. Like he's looking down like that. So he's like looking down.
He's on the cloud here. Okay that like you gotta get it right you know.
Okay okay okay okay okay okay. Now we gotta get his mouth. All snakes have the fun tongue right.
But this is down. He's looking down and he could even have the factory over here. You know what
I mean. Like we need perspective down. Like maybe you could have like some other shit that's over
here. Maybe like some other like buildings or something. Like he he is looking the perspective
is that way. No like this. Like I'm looking at you right now. Like all right so let's get uh I mean
I can't really. You understand what I'm going for here. Okay got up on a cloud. How did he get
there? That's page two. Just say bird's eye view. It was a snake. So it wouldn't be it would be a
snake's eye view. Wouldn't be a bird's eye. Okay page two is done. I don't want to blow your eyes
out when I do this. So I'm gonna go like this. Save this one. Page two. Okay let's come back.
There we go. So page three. Here we go. Once was a snake that didn't care. Got up on a cloud somehow.
How'd he get there? Where we're used to the rain. Droplets of water. Don't fall up there. Watch the
teeter totter. Um should a storm come in and like fucking lightning and stuff. And that's what he
like maybe he falls off and goes like down the chimney. How'd it get up there? No that was a
fun book. Um see you later. No uh the chimney he climbed one day. To his friends. Wait goodbye.
I'll see you another day. The why could I turn to seagulls doing math? There once was a snake that
didn't care. Got up on a cloud somehow. How'd he get there? His friends and family he did say goodbye.
Friends and family he did say goodbye. Reaching higher he wanted to try. It's about reaching too
high. It's about trying too hard and not setting correct goals for yourself that you get in over
your head and you get to a point where you can't come down. What did I just say clip that? I don't
even know what I just said clip it. It was genius though. Whatever it was. It's about reaching too
high. It's about reaching too high. It's about trying too hard and not setting correct goals
for yourself that you get in over your head and you get to a point where you can't come down.
Okay what what what what was the shitty rhyme that I did?
No that's no but you don't know. It's about reaching too high. No but what was the actual
line? It was he's okay but how did he get there? To his friends and family he did say goodbye.
It's about setting realistic goals and this could be like a flashback of him like with a
fucking hat on right like getting on a train like waving and like getting on a train yep.
This is going to be an elaborate one here okay so we've got the train to his friends family he
did say this is like if there's a flashback there's going to be look right watch this
so in this panel there's going to be like there'll be some like mist around the edges so like
children can understand that this is like this happened before right so there's like mist here
how it's cloudy kind of mist and make it cloudy you know what I'm saying let's just get the train
out so this i'm thinking i'm thinking like this way right i'm thinking like dye like this
like this is the train and here's like the like the bottom part of the train i gotta get like
look it's hard to do this there's like the tracks it's it's a fucking dream sequence all right lay
off you get the idea though like yeah like that is the snake his snake friends are here here they
are and he's gonna be like out of hanging out of a window with a fucking hat on like it like it
happened with the 30s just blocking it out this is just like the fucking bitcoin chart so hanging
out the window he's traveling he's away he's leaving he's traveling he's going to he's going
to do something he's going to where's he going and it could be like other people like walking
with other snakes like walking briefcases right with other like fucking hats on it's like a
fucking briefcase uh and you know like walking in the subway there's like there's like fucking
40 of these snakes like walking around with like briefcases and shit and imagine that's like just
kind of everywhere and this is like it's like a living fucking city back here there's a there's
a factory you know uh there's a couple of the buildings in the back this is like other shit
over here well i want like you know i want um what do i want over here i want a guy
uh like okay just imagine these are like other snakes like going to and from places
okay let me get the hat it's just like a hat uh let's go with like this okay you need a hat
too you're a business you're a businessman you need a hat on you know like children's worlds
and books that this is need that needs to be believable you know and make it really really
obvious that he you know he's got he's got like fucking laundry in here or something he's got
like a backpack or a suitcase or something over here you're wearing like a backpack right i mean
this looks like somebody's sitting that is like there's a person sitting on the train next to him
this is just a person just sitting that you know there's people here there's people but you get it
okay there's like something going on in here there's like a there's like a there's like a
fucking elephant or an animal like a lion or something there's like a tiger right here
waving because kids all kids want to like point out the shit it doesn't matter if it makes no sense
kids want to like point and bow lion that's right lion oh this is zootopia no it's not
this is snakes or otherwise okay two friends oh shit that's fucked up isn't it oh god damn it
you know what i was fucking saying to his friends and family he did say goodbye
we're out that's page that's page three remember this missed it got a bit missed here
well what was the next part it's a it's a it's about he wanted to try what did he want to try
on to his friends and family he did say goodbye reach for the sky he wanted to try
this book fucking sucks i haven't even gotten done with it yet we've got like four more pages
just okay so wait i gotta how did he get here flashback to his friends and family he did say
goodbye he desperately he wanted to try he had some idea that he wanted to try he thought he
would sky high is what he wanted to try the friends really did say goodbye his final no
to his friends and family he did say goodbye on a whim he wanted to try there done got it this is
page three so shield your eyes i was just pressed print reprint this fucking page oh god damn it
maybe he's like a fucking like reporter or something who knows it doesn't matter okay so
this is a new page on page four so to his friends apparently he did say goodbye on a whim he wanted
to try let's get a new page here no no no no no no don't do that okay so bright on a whim he
wanted to try get like him in like in an office or something on in an office no in a on a whim he
wanted to try on a whim he wanted to try what a guy no on a whim he wanted to try for the sky
all right no more try sky by on a whim he wanted to try for the sky where is he now where's the
train he's off the train this is another flashback right we gotta get like the mist he wanted to try
maybe okay maybe this could be like three or four things going on here right so we could have like
like small bubble small bubble small bubble small bubble we get to get like four page we're gonna
get four pages done right now yeah i'm thinking like flashback photo here flashback photo here
flashback photo here showing flashback photo doesn't matter how the fuck he got there
flashback inside of flashback no but this whole thing is a flashback so we got him it doesn't
matter what it was he got he went away trying to do something you know he's like excited and in this
one uh maybe there's like fucking money in his hand no no kids don't understand money this one
he's here uh maybe like a calendar a calendar here with a bunch of like x's on it like he's
been doing a bunch of shit not very sweat marks you know what i mean like there's like oh x like
he has like all the things that like okay that's a calendar we get some like fucking sweat marks
maybe he's like he puts his hand up like you know wipes it away like sweat kind of like a hand he
wipes it away with his hand you know like he like whip whips the sweat i'm just blocking it out just
seeing it maybe like it's him uh if this is like like it just it could be anything back in like a
couple of buildings this could be just buildings back here behind him like he's in like is it like
a window seat he's got like a big window behind him you know maybe a factory back here like this
is he this is a window that he's sitting like in front of okay you know wow that was hard
and then now it's like no not okay now he's remembering this like friends and family you
know so we gotta have like a flat like a second like a third like flashback of him remembering
his family you know like oh wow i'd like where's my you know here they are and there's like a whole
other scene in here of like the like everyone's like waving and saying hello you know he's like
remembering like oh i remember buddy oh my god like i mean like he moved away or something okay
he's like a piece of working too hard you know what i'm saying and then maybe he looks out over
all the factories he owns no that's like all right what does he own the fact i don't know
now that's stupid he wanted to try for this guy he's like fat no he's not fat in the first
panel i think no sense i have this guy i don't know maybe the company like tanks his sports car
no kids won't understand that okay like oh like what the hell and notice the symbolism here
with the way that these are the way that they look they could be factories but it's like so
muddled in his brain this could be factories they're like shaped like factories could be
pollution i don't know writing fucking books is hard okay especially when you write them in like
40 minutes all right wait wait is this a flashback yes this is a flashback so he's
up on this cloud now and when he wanted to try for the sky what's the last fucking thing he does
here maybe just maybe just like another front facing camera he's got a nose in this one okay
he's like irritated he's working and there's a bunch of money behind him no kids don't know
what money is no he's not going to die either in the story this book sucks uh you couldn't
pay me to read this well it's a snake on a cloud otherwise that's what we had to work with we got
to work with it okay hold on i'm gonna try for the sky that's fine this is fine done page done
there's money behind him this is gold doesn't matter what it is it could be anything something
okay done that's that's it he sends up the rainbow no he goes up like the gold he goes up like the
fucking gold and he's on the cloud right he like goes up on the fucking gold and he's on the cloud
now like yeah i made my millions on the fucking gold it sounded so easy at first all right so
he's got all the money behind him so let's save this one here i'm gonna let this one's done
still on this joke i say we're gonna write a book it doesn't matter if it's five or six pages long
it's still gonna happen all right let's save it it'd be better if i could have any artistic
ability at all all right page four he's gonna ride up the fucking gold all right i got the
rest of it already done okay so we're riding the gold i get this done in fucking five seconds
okay here we go i can write the line after so that's like this is like the the yellow brick gold
there's like a fucking window here it's not a factory this is not a factory it's like his
office somewhere let's get the clouds over here okay i fucked up a little bit over here but it's
fine there he is he's like going up like whoa he's really fast he's like his face is like head is
like whipping around like holy shit this is i'm going too fast that's his mouth is up here
whatever his mouth is supposed to be that way but it's fine like his head he's back this way
okay i'm just blocking the story out okay i'm just blocking out for the when i give the artist
direction all right so read back to me it's going too fast i better hold off now or it won't last
no this is somebody just said easiest money what is this have we talked about how like writing a
children's book would be the fucking most easy money you could ever make those you guys like
wondering oh what the like i have like some artistic talent like what what should i do
make a fucking children's book your whole story can be like 14 words yeah and just draw like
cute fun pictures if you're like artistically talented like just write a children's book make
up a story doesn't matter what the story is it doesn't thread i'll prove it to you guys i will
something you guys have to remember here i mean this is i've been live for four hours
and we've been doing this for like two so if people spend a decade of their life writing a book
people spend years of time writing a book if this is the bullshit that i can come up with in fucking
45 minutes to an hour that's some pretty good like time versus investment you know what i mean
that like really some people write a book for fucking four years and i'll prove it to you
but it's not good though but that's this is art you can't say that
that's why we're in the art category all right here we go you just you you're fucking up with my
mojo here so it's too fast it won't last now soaring and seek soaring and seeking
how high can he go soaring and no soaring and slithering because he's a snake yeah
kids love that shit done this page is done this one's done now we're now cranking them out see
i'm gonna roll here this is page five and yes i am well aware that this is gonna end up being
the quality of something that you would get if you went to a diner and it's the shit that the
kids drawn with their crayons to like protect the table i'm aware of that that doesn't mean it won't
sell all right soaring and slithering how high can he go to the moon no that no i'm not doing
a cryptocurrency bullshit thing here soaring is living how high can he go yeah i saved it i
saved it i have a good comeback there's only like three more pages and then we're done soaring and
slithering how high can he go it's the furthest a snake the snakes ever known where it's soaring
soaring slithering how high can he go shut up guys writing books is fucking hard
uh all right how can he go this looks nice comfy and this looks nice comfy and oh comfy and
this looks nice he's getting off on the cloud and he's like really up there this looks nice
comfy and this looks nice comfy and nice no this looks nice comfy and soft no it's gotta be this
looks nice comfy this spot is cool comfy and nice this part is this this spot is wow this
shit is fucking dank this looks nice comfy this looks nice full of mice no but we don't have to
eat anything this looks nice comfy and covered in lice no this looks nice this will suffice
you fucking saved this project whoever the fuck you are bingo and the fucking gold road is going
up and down and around and he's it's right he lands on the cloud only two more pages after this
guys and i'm done and i win the bet what somebody got me the five grand that i wasn't gonna do it
pay up you could have gone you could have gone even like higher you know what i mean
like this keeps going right yeah they got this like okay yeah yeah yeah and if you guys are
wondering here what's going on with this it's shaped like a snake interesting because this
is his own greed that got him here and it's his own we're talking metaphors inside of
the metaphor when he lands like a factory smog is gonna go right into his fucking face
and he's gonna like cough like like a huge hack no no okay i gotta get rid of the fucking
how am i gonna wrap this up in a single page he look in the next page he realizes that he
misses everybody and like he well why do i i miss like everybody and i want to like
come down and see everybody and then he's gonna slide down um a slide i've made it to something
and then he lands in the family everyone's happy no he's not gonna jump off so he's like looking
down there's the cloud you get the idea this looks nice this was suffice he sees the cloud
he's gonna get off no no what do you mean no conflict book sucks so this is all shit this is
all flashback isn't it yeah this whole thing is a flashback so i had like the mist on the edge of
that the whole book has been a flashback it's okay we've got two more pages page six here it is
and then page seven incoming this looks nice this was suffice now we're back in the regular time
like now you understand so bright okay here we go there's no point to the book there's no point to
any children's book it's about like how to clean your room this one is about uh a random number
generator and uh not being not going don't like make sure you like don't lose your friends and
family and friendship and like the james and the giant peach the fucking giant tomato rose through
town is the same exact story he has to go back and like and enjoy his friends and shit james
and the large tomato i never read the book i i haven't read the book in like 30 years
reset we lost him no let's finish the book right now here we go it's gonna be two panels back to
back right here just imagine this is a line in the middle here this is the okay this is the fucking
book okay you like this there's that one there's that one i'm not gonna make another page why i
just shouldn't have done this in the very beginning okay here he is looking down at like again this is
real time there he is looking down again tear drops from his eye no why would it be sad
not yet no the smog no the tear drops then it starts raining and the cloud bingo bingo
bingo bingo okay so he's up there it's he drops a tear starts raining okay because he's remembering
his like friends and like oh i miss my friends and everything so then the cloud has the rain in it
cloud disappears and he fall he slowly falls because yeah i don't know something like that
if he like lands in something like that but that's a good that's a good start so he cries a tear
one tear oh like i you know i miss my i miss everybody like i wish i could just let's go back
i want to go back home and visit everybody and it's like you can you just you can and then like you
know it rains and then bingo right here clouds start dissipating a little bit and like yeah then
the sun comes up over here you know i'm saying the sun is over here we're going but we're in the end
game here so clouds dissipating and then like the bit that maybe the gold bridge back here can like
you know okay whatever it's like gone it's like starting to fall apart starting to like wither away
and uh and this whole time remember he's like maybe he'll like think about like that we already
know what he's thinking about and something like something like his friends like he's like his
friends help him here how like his friends are in this panel somehow as flashbacks around him and
they slowly let him fall but we just didn't kids don't understand the sun
he sees his friends as forest ghosts maybe people look up because they think it's raining
and then they i don't know this is close this is just a draw my life it's not even a book
this is just my draw my life guys the kid from the beginning catches him
okay all right whatever who cares they may be like the okay the flashback bubbles we we saw
them earlier in the story flashback bubbles of all like the people having fun they're like at the
beach right hanging out having a good time like everyone's hanging out who cares they they like
doesn't matter there's like people and like they're like oh i'm having a great time remember when you
hear yeah me too i remember i sure do yeah okay and he's falling right oh i'm funny but these are
slowly catching him as he goes down fucking books are hard okay he's the this the other like the
memories and like all the things he likes are there other thing could happen here no he doesn't
jump he's crying because he remembers like how much fun thing he remembers is like he wants to
like go back and hang out with his friends and stuff and like now he's realizing it
and like he doesn't he doesn't really care about all this stuff he cares about his like friends
or something this is not a children's book anymore and then he there it is page seven and eight
he slowly falls down and then like he's able he's caught by all of his friends there's no
words here that doesn't need to be there doesn't need to be words here this is a panel with no
words was this okay this is six this is page seven and eight final panel what was the last
thing that is that what was the last thing happened because now he's currently okay take
a look at this so this last panel is there he's like everyone's like oh it's raining and he's
he's caught by everybody down here you know like there's another big scene with okay you
could have some like grass or give it to me you could have some grass remember the people playing
outside and everyone's just like like everyone catches him while he falls down and everyone's
like happy like hey like you're back okay there you go i've done i've did it i'm done you know
like everyone's here there's like you know people and shit like all like he's floating down on his
like fun nice memories and then everyone's like happy this guy's getting his hips let's get this
could be a person this is a snake he's just slowly falling down on these like nice memories
these are all his friends these are all his friends and it turns out you have friends
and family and you don't you don't need anything else you know you can you can you can you if you
want to you can there done it turns out you had it all along you can do all that if you want
the end this is the ending to bloodborne there's memories remember memories and then we're going
to get some more like snakes but what's the sinister thing going on here like he's slowly
floating down this is a placeholder text for something else there you go this is this whole
it is a book done i told you i could do it and then it is i get what was the last thing that i
what was the last thing the moral of the story is somebody said like the moral of the story is
don't do any of that just to hang out with your family and smoke crack in your basement
what the fuck was that all right let's put it all up on the screen but i need to i need a better
line um how many people left fucking like a thousand i think a thousand people left the
stream over the course of the last hour that's fucking like so funny to me this is fucking stupid
oh otherwise turns out you had it all no no otherwise turns out you had it all along
if you want but you can do all that if you want otherwise i hate this but i love it otherwise
just fly to the skies that's an amendment it's okay this i mean i amended that
if i go to crack don't do crack anybody no doesn't no no it turns out you had it all along
otherwise just fly to the skies no what does this go keep the green text because it symbolizes the
snakes that's good all right i'm done that was fun that was fun there's page nine so let's get
them all on screen people are just coming like they don't understand the story we've got to like
this there's a story here let's read the book okay hold on hold on hold on i gotta get them all
i gotta get them all loaded up here we're gonna go over this shit one page by page two three
the fuck are these panels don't look at that look i i had a certain amount of material to work with
and i think i came up with a pretty decent story that half half of chat came up with it as well
all right page five page six we're gonna we're gonna do this proper i'm gonna put music in the
background i'm gonna get the fuck off screen okay i need a title page i need a title page title
easy don't ever tell me i can't fucking do something you know i'm saying you can't write a
children you can't write a book in fucking 30 minutes yeah i can what was it called something
or otherwise what was it actually called something snake snake on a cloud in the clouds
snake in the clouds just snake in the clouds a snake in the clouds there let me get that saved
out this is the cover hold on not done yet not done yet just give me another minute you'll
appreciate this one let me get that there okay hold on you guys will appreciate this okay i need
an image right here quick quick quick quick quick image image image come on give it to me i don't
even care what it is i just need an image of me where is it i'm just gonna go to fucking google
images i don't care uh this is fine okay this is so huge hold on fuck no come on i have to have
this page here all right hold on i can do it i can do it i can do it come on windows get that
there we go all right are you guys ready because i'm not okay save it get it out go go go go go go go
get the cover in there get the last page in there oh this setup for a book that sucks okay
where's the cover it is all right let's go wait i don't know which one it is let's get the music
cued up ladies and gentlemen here's the book a snake in the clouds written by jeremy elbertson
there once was a snake that did not care got up on a cloud how did he get there to his friends
and family he did say goodbye on a whim he wanted to try for the sky soaring and slithering how high
can he go this is the point where the streamer gave up turns out but you can do it if you want
to otherwise just fly to the sky that's it can i just say that uh slimer from ghostbusters i did
it i wrote a children's book on stream and i'm gonna not sell it because it's awful that was
worth 22 dollars for the hardcover version all right now let's try it with different music
a snake in the clouds written by jeremy elbertson yeah can you fucking feel it can you feel it i know
you can there once was a snake that didn't care got up on a clown how the fuck did he get there
to his friends and family he did say goodbye on a whim he wanted to try for the sky soaring and
slithering how high can he go this nothing here turns out you had it all along you fucking idiot
when you can do that too just fly this guy sucks what did i just say clip that how did we get here
i have no idea oh somebody said something about a children's book and i said they were very easy to
read easy to make
wake up ah it's all right somebody somebody's fucking somebody's idea
well that was fun i actually did have fun doing that i'll read that to my children 15 years
back to i spy well were they easy to i gotta get this off screen that's like an embarrassing photo
what is this photo what is this oh you gotta check the creative tab the snake emo that's amazing
now people just like i just wanted to look at these some of these are just beautiful
absolutely wonderful i just wanted to fly so high the art is so good in the discord
just have we have people made page by page every panel here because i'll do it again and show the
real one let me go look because that's hilarious oh my god this is fucking hilarious okay hold on
there's the cover someone made a cover and it looks great
i want to get this one on stream this is that's a snake in a balloon look at this one look at that
see this is a million dollar idea there's another one we'll get the gist of the whole book here
please look at how good these are i'm just saving them all one of my favorite things
let's be i'm gonna be really really real uh is it's really really incredible to me that like
people are able to do this and watch a dumb little stream where we have fucking fun time and make up
fucking dumb children's books and just sit along and play along i love it it's fucking amazing
it's hilarious i love it let's take a look at some of these uh there's a lot here so i'm just
gonna kind of throw them up as they come oh my god somebody did like the first panel
and it's perfect all right i get it let's get these on here there's too many great ones hey
drama fuck this book i'm just i know i'm downloading i'm downloading i'm downloading i had to download
because i want to get them like in all their glory all right here you go so look at this cover
it almost looks like soap it's too cute it's great albertson it's all right it's great and
then here is this is the first panel take a look at this first panel like really that's exactly
what i was looking for there he is see the ball the ah this is great i think it has the factory
yeah that's so good i can already see the money rolling in now it's a community effort now
take a look at this one it's just so it's so good this one for pretty much every page you got
another yeah there is like another one i need to get like a system where i can show this shit in
all its glory you know what i mean this is great the talented fucking people that watch these
streams it's fantastic really uh is there already an approved art channel there is in the discord
it's the creative channel you can post anything creative as long as it's safe for work it is there
show fan art yeah i think i'd want to do it maybe like once in a while once a week maybe
and like have proper crediting and no lewd channel no no there's a few more somebody put
gnome oh great i almost just downloaded that yeah this i don't have like a rhyme a reason to this
at the moment i'm just i just caught the ones that i caught in the discord here's another great one
they're all great but this one's cute too it's raining
beautiful work he says okay look but this is what i was talking about i see i don't have any
artistic like drawing and like cartoon kind of skills right but if you did and you made a little
cute snake comic kind of cartoon you can make a book you can do it i know you can here's another
one i thought this one was really good i'm not sure who this one's not credited but just still
equally as good i think i like i like the line work on this one it's just it's nice looks pretty
good uh then there is this one and also by the way those of you that may have come to the stream
later uh i this one's so cute this one is adorable i have a vive i bought a vive i bought a bunch of
stuff so the next stream that you see is potentially going to be vive it depends on if it gets here or
not when i say i have a vive i mean i like it's in transit so there's a shit load of things that i've
wanted to do for vive that i'm really looking forward to the vive i finally bought it i finally
own it space channel is coming back space channel part one there's a play this is i can't wait to
play this game i'm gonna tell you about it it's called um it's called africa it's a photography
game where you go take pictures of animals that's the whole game i can't wait to play it it's gonna
be a fucking blast that's a rare game that's a rare game uh i have a couple more look at this one
this is the quintessential moment during the story where he rises too high i bought i got c man too
so i got c man and the microphone is this time is coming let me just check and see if there's any
other i know there's a bunch more uh in the creative channel if you are into art and you like
artwork and you think uh that's interesting to you i very very much i imply and i advise
that you go check out the creative in the discord oh here's a good one this one's good i'm gonna put
this one on here see the person that put this in here thought i was gonna just scroll by this one
and be like okay whatever nope it's going on it's going on stream durama is short pogchamp you
thought i was gonna scroll by that one i'm not gonna keep it on there for long but there's so
many great doodles in here this is amazing oh i want to put this one on here this one's interesting
too did i get it i got it here it is they're just pouring in it's so great you guys are
fucking awesome did i show this one already i don't think i did it's hyper realistic
why would i put this on stream and i'm going to because why would i do this though there's
nothing to do with anything i know everyone everyone you guys know me too well that's it
yeah i i just i just like blew up the creative discord by the way i'm sorry for the mods
there are very listen listen there are very strict rules in the creative channel
please follow them follow the rules in the discord follow the rules now do not put the snake in my
mouth i will not show that on camera but um i think that is good that's gonna wrap it up guys
i want just to hang out and have like a little chill stream play eye spy and then rant about
a children's book we'll be up to five hours we'll go for about five or six hours okay that's all
right i'm okay with that so here's the plan uh there are a few things that i want to do
the vibe is incoming shout out to the one guy that said you couldn't do it and i mean we there
was probably like 5400 people 5300 people there i dropped a thousand viewers writing and doing
that stupid stream it's okay uh look it don't matter you were number one trending on twitch
no it doesn't matter look as long as i'm having a good time and you guys are having a good time
it's fine it's that don't matter i had a lot of fun this is a fucking fun stream
i spy was fun children's book was fun you guys are fucking awesome you guys are you guys are so
talented and amazing all the artwork thanks for uh putting up with the bullshit here at the uh at
the when i gave up on the book but it's okay i've given up on a book before way before getting to
the end and we are gonna get to the bits but i'll see you guys uh probably tuesday i'm probably
here's what's gonna happen i'm gonna do a shitload of five because i am way backlogged with vibe so
nothing tomorrow and we're probably gonna go tuesday wednesday thursday with vibe just straight up
vibe i want to do mine show i want to do some of the vibe exclusive vr things that i missed a lot
of people thought were fun late to the party pretty much a five week coming up here but the
reason why i'm gonna do three days in a row with five is because those streams are not going to be
very long those of you that know that you saw me play other games with the psvr i could get this
image off the fucking screen too by the way i can really only go in that thing for like four hours
so we'll just do three days in a row right with like three to five hour streams can i even get
this off the screen it's like kind of stuck here forever keep it for the stream over but yeah we'll
do a few days in a row five shorten the streams up a little bit but go more days so thanks for
coming thanks for watching a little bit shorter today but uh i did the things that i thought i
would that would be fun to do that's the thumbnail for the stream oh god yeah and also i was talking
to uh i was talking to kiwo and she was talking about maybe doing vr chat because i don't know
anything about it and she knows that whole world so we may do a stream where we just do vr chat and
fuck around you know we talked about it don't do that heavy supervision don't worry i'm gonna be
i'm gonna be on lockdown it's the meme game boomer explores the virtual world it's our virtual world
can be explored it'll be good but see you guys really soon thanks for coming up and we're gonna
go back to uh earlier in the stream about five hours ago here thank you creation of the cyborg
for the one dollar hey i'm sorry about last night you know the scene but i know you enjoyed seeing
nick get nick cage get vaporized it was wild uh thank you wire tm for the one dollar what do you
call an annual gathering of un uh dead nerds the what i don't get it and then the i don't get it
can i read this am i getting in trouble reading this i don't know what it is i'm trying to figure
out what the joke is but i know it's a con like a convention annual gathering of undead nerds the
necronomicon i don't get it i don't get it i mean i do but i get it i get it thank you thank you to
creation the cyber again for the one dollar i just got banned from your discord all right well maybe
just like just just settle down okay if you're getting banned from the discord more than a few
times i uh you might need to figure out maybe some things you might be saying or doing
that is getting you banned more than once or twice from the discord i'm not really sure what to tell
you uh there are rules we have specific things that you have to adhere to in especially in
specific channels in that discord but uh maybe just maybe like if you think about the things
you might be saying or doing just be careful you don't want to get yourself in any trouble
but thank you for the one dollar hopefully uh you don't get banned hey c bentley thanks for the five
dollars uh hey jerma can't really afford too many bits as i'm from new zealand but want to show
support for my favorite streamer and content creator since forever ago thanks for everything
thank you for everything thanks for the five dollars thanks for continuing to support the stream
as long as you have thank you thank you c bentley for the five dollars thank you zero giblets for
the one dollar jerma my art degree is already enough of a joke i don't say that thank you for
the one dollar you get you absorbed knowledge though you got knowledge knowledge you can use it
whatever you studied you absorbed it knowledge but thank you for the one dollar thank you flippy
for the one dollar hey man nice to catch you live thanks for stopping by and thank you for your two
dollars here flippy thanks for hanging out i am now mostly moist and thanks for the one dollar
i spy a streamer and auto a scary spider a bee in the ceiling a green screen fighter
comcast is a terrible service provider lastly i see you shito insider oh fuck what happened
no thank you timmy tim tam for the one dollar uh his daily english lesson let's take a listen
and see what it is your present in a toy thank you timmy tim tam thank you divas for the two
dollars you can advise me yes ma'am a toy from my niece yes thank you divas for two bucks she'll be
seven years old on sunday skateboards are still very popular seven-year-old on a skateboard
what about a barbie doll set i don't think so she has many barbie dolls have you got anything
educational you see she's a very intelligent girl i've got the perfect thing a do-it-yourself kit
where you can build your own barbie doll who rides a skateboard i would fucking throw that in the
trash thank you divas though for the two dollars thank you nile aureon for three bucks the ending
of home alone is that the kid goes on a no i am not going to read that thanks for three dollars
thank you for three bucks thank you creation the cyborg for the one dollar how are you going to
explain the t part to kim t part what happened t part i'm not sure what what do you mean by that
uh thank you tar all a crin for the one dollar do you remember earlier this week when i donated
money to ask when you were going to play shen mu and you said you would start on thursday i remember
rich streamer lies to his fans no no no no what happened was here's what happened i got addicted
i got addicted to crazy taxi and space channel to a point where i bought space channel part one
and i'm gonna play that so i got addicted to other dreamcast games before opening shin mu
so what's gonna happen which i own one and two shin mu is gonna have to turn into one of those
streams where it's just i'm just gonna relax and i'm gonna play it because it doesn't it didn't
fit in with like the dreamcast streams because it's a long game that requires a lot of attention
and a lot of time so i couldn't really just open up shin mu for 40 minutes all right that was funny
hello well no you gotta get that game attention in time so that's why they haven't seen shin mu
yet that's why and also ace attorney a lot of people have been talking about ace attorney
and i know i said i was gonna play ace attorney but then i was told that there's a better version
that's gonna come out that's being remastered in hd and the ipad version sucks and it's buggy and
broken and terrible and then i'm like ah i was gonna play it on the ipad and then get a ds but
i'm emulating a ds is i'd rather just own it and do it legally change oh i gotta change category
you're right because that is true we're just kind of sitting here change the category i'm no longer
streaming art you are correct on that for sure uh just irl uh chatting right okay there we go
yeah i don't want to just be in a category i'm not supposed to be in well other people are
actually doing art and stuff on stream so you can play ace attorney on apple yeah but that's what
i'm saying uh the ipad version i've been told by many people is not the version that i want to play
it's apparently not very good it's not as clean as the ds version kind of sloppy from what i've
heard it is something i'm going to do eventually when the pc version comes out the pc version has
a random release date of 2019 yeah it is just going to come out one day but i'll be ready uh
flug boy flug boy gave 22 dollars earlier thank you flug boy for your 22 bucks hope you're doing
well germa after the space channel 5 stream it got me really into the series and i do love it
uh i just got fucking gnomed by an ambulance did you guys hear that run that back and play it
that's i swear to god that was really weird um anywho really got me into the series and i love
it dearly oh i why did they never do more of it is beyond me also i don't know if you mentioned if
you were doing your one year anime or if you were just waiting for the new uh mha season anyways
love you uh i have i watched one punch man the whole thing that was great that's my one year
one anime per year let me listen to this because i swear to god that was really weird
yeah did you hear that i just got fucking uh it's rolled by and did that for half a second
but uh for your first uh comment that you said space channel 5 is amazing and i got news for you
i don't know how intricate it's going to be but there is a space channel 5 vr game that is coming
out this year somehow randomly i don't know what it's going to be like i don't know if it's a port
or remake of one of the other games but they're doing a vr game and you better believe not that
i got a vibe i'm gonna play the absolute hell out of that so looking forward to that one but
thank you flug boy for the 22 bucks and the uh two comments here uh lazy luke thanks for two bucks
thank you lazy luke wizard ribbit thanks for one doll thanks for the door of the explorer stream
jerma you're very welcome flank tank thanks for three bucks oh man the nostalgia on this stream
is real i used to play these games these i spy games in my elementary typing class in the fourth
and fifth grade the teacher let anyone over 75 words per minute goof off and i had the highest
in my class at 95 yeah at some point the teacher is probably just you know what you're doing at
that point you probably had to pass with like 30 or 40 words per minute that's a lot for being
that young though you could go on to be like a court stenographer going that fast but yeah i
never played the i spy games i did not play it it was cute it was cute it was endearing
i could see what people have such fond memories of it i can a stenographer needs 200 plus words
per minute how do you not run into sentences on each other if you can do 200 words a minute
at some point you the words that are coming before the words you just typed are already
happening in your brain and on the screen it's just too that's too fast i don't know how that's
possible uh hey rtm thanks for the three bucks i remember when i was a little lad i would read
the look alike books which were kind of like i spy but instead of having things to look for
they would just present an image of day-to-day life recreated with common items like for a movie
theater scene the ticket booth would be made out of film canisters and the bright stage lights
would be popcorn i haven't thought about those since school so thanks for unearthing a pleasant
childhood memory absolutely i never played them but they sound interesting 3d movie maker was my
childhood game that i played on the computer that was like 1994 1995 so i was like how old was i
uh like 13 12 something like that yeah thank you rtm for the three bucks thank you creation
the cyborg for the one dollar i've ever heard about the atari vcs no atari is one of those
systems that i i love reminiscing on how it's like the stepping stone for all video games
but i also don't think i'd ever want to go back and play atari because it's actually like two
tetris blocks on the screen moving back and forth in a ball going somewhere between them
it's not they're not like oh yeah i can't wait to go back and play tanks not really but i do
respect the fact that it was the stepping stone for pretty much everything so you have to respect
that the pitfall is at least is interesting enough but a lot of the atari library is very very
simple stuff the 2600 can be fun no i know it can be but i'm not sure that's something i would
want to go back and go get and oh i'm gonna spend like a grand on atari 2600 stuff not necessarily
i'll watch a documentary about it and say that was awesome thank you damona cucumber for the
one dollar he takes so long with the camera because talax needs to set up the facial tracking to make
himself look like germa it's me it's me i'm here i'm real thank you for the one dollar germa did
this entire stream just so he could do that copyright joke germa disgust i don't remember
what you're talking about uh demonic cucumber thanks for the one dollar again gloom and adventures
children's book that's exactly what an imposter would say uh thank you amphoteric for the one
dollar choose mom or dad in court what i don't know what that means thank you keith ward for
the one dollar at the time of my donation your stream is the highest viewed art stream beating
out bob ross repeats by several thousand viewers most art streams have around 100 viewers and your
monstrosity is sitting at the top with nearly 5000 keep up the good work yeah and i that's
why i'm fucking that's amazing that like 5500 people 5300 people were here to just fucking
around and have fun but there are a lot of great art streamers and i don't even want to make like
a joke out of the category so that's why it's kind of hard to put myself in a category on when we do
these things because it's like it was only 3k relax wait what no it was like it was like 50 i
looked over it was like 5500 and we transitioned out of the uh it was like at least 40 48 to yeah
it was 5k it was relax it was 2k egomaniac well anyways anyways what i was saying is it's sometimes
it's hard oh what what okay i'm gonna pretend to write a fucking children's book all right uh art
and then it's like oh but there's like people actually really like painting and shit i don't
even want to make like a joke into that category like just chatting i guess or creative you had
200 viewers get over yourself he's lying about views to appeal to advertisers they look like
six grand here but thank you appreciate it keith word yeah thanks everybody for hanging out anybody
that hung up tonight hope you had a good time i did dk oh 723 thanks for 10 bucks uh i wanted
to write you a little something but it's kind of long uh and sad so i want to put it on reddit you
can read it later uh the tldr is uh thank you and love you thanks for the laughs yeah i will
absolutely read this after the stream thank you so much for whatever this letter is uh hopefully
you know that i appreciate every single fucking money thank you i will read it after the stream
in before it's a gnome ascii art it's no that's not what it's gonna be but for real thank you
thank you dr stein for the five dollars striking back against the bourgeoisie hey lux thanks for
the two bucks hey germa my first stream and first donation to you love your videos uh welcome thank
you for the two dollars and happy that you were able to catch a stream hey pigeon thank you pigeon
for the four dollars here hey germa just wanted to tell you that i'm writing my paper on a discourse
community a community which people share a common goal and communicate among other things
on your community and i'm gonna have some trouble explaining the way that people here use language
to communicate messages but i look forward to it also i get to interview two people likely a mod
and a newer person to use as sources in my paper just want to let you know that you mean so much
to me and everyone and the first thing that popped in my head about uh when asked about a
community they belong to is yours not only activities i've involved in in real life but
yours watching your streams truly is an experience among a community and i can't
emphasize how important that is oh well what about me i got a source for you
they're gonna interview me now i'll give you a quote you want a quote i'll give you a quote
i'm not a trustworthy source though yeah that's true he's an egomaniac i could give you a quote
but no uh in all seriousness though that's when i first started doing this years ago i never
thought that somebody would be making like a discourse community paper on me and my online
community that's it's crazy to me like i can't believe it i'm so happy that this stream means
so much to so much of you guys so like from the bottom of my heart thank you so much everybody
seriously i'm your thesis project now you guys are fucking awesome so thank you uh good luck on that
by the way if you need a quote then like maybe hit up one of the mods i'll give you a quote
friday weapon thanks for the three bucks this reminds me of the time that i made a children's
book i never did get paid for that i think i've been had did you how did you probably look into
that uh hey benji thanks for the three bucks and 50 cents germa it's okay to admit you're just
brainstorming ideas for rat movie four probably four what about three i don't want to just cause
myself and come up with four and everybody forgot that three existed so they was just
caused just cause two just cause four people don't remember three even came out i'm not going to do
that to myself but thank you thank you sticks renegade for the two bucks all these choices would
be more interesting if the animals were anthropomorphic there were a bunch there were
a bunch of anthropomorphic characters in that book it was standing on two snake legs and holding
briefcases and all that that's pretty anthropomorphic if you ask me um me people thanks to the one dollar
i accused the duck in the library with the candlestick uh jess you got it thanks for the
three dollars i spy with my little eye a little nevada streamer guy he'll try to make a children's
book but plagiarize even the dumb snake in a cloud otherwise there's a book called serpents in the
clouds no no no no no no no this is that this serpents this is a this is like a harry potter
ripoff no it's not no it's just about a no that was wrong and then a lie that was incorrect
this book about snakes like an actual book about large snakes so i ripped no i ripped off harry
potter yeah thank you jesse you got it thank you uh winterly parsley for the 10 bucks twist ending
he's not actually on a cloud he hey climbed a tree and then fell on his friend's sheep and is happy
to see his friend yeah go edit that and put that in that's a better ending that's a much better
ending than him crying but i like the crying and the rain is the you know the cloud and the tears
and he slowly drifts down on the clouds of his memories getting him back to why am i explaining
a 40 minute children's writing exercise more like three hours not 40 you know what i'm saying
thank you bonjour for the one dollar his name was germa he wanted to die no that's not what
happened did you even read the book jay paul thanks for the one dollar germy can you publish
this on amazon so i can read it to my kid on my kindle thanks no it's free free book that's right
free book just go back to the stream to the vod where i read it on stream page by page i was
turning the pages in real life uh bonjour thanks for the one dollar hey germy the last bits were
meant to be part of a line in the story it didn't really work out though anyways very good stream
so far i literally have more money in bits right now than real money till my next paycheck so
instead of food today i'm having germa for dinner thanks for a good meal i would implore you take
care of yourself first save you need to make sure you have good savings you don't have to
don't feel obligated to pay me anything please you don't have to like you know i was gonna eat
today but i'm gonna give you fucking 10 bucks don't do that eat the book show them the doom
music version of the book but thank you bonjour just watch it for free forehead i i mean you're
not wrong like i can't say hey oh yeah bastard little bastard don't you say that
eat book or pre-recorded hey flying sombrero thanks in three bucks for some reason that weird
sun video you played last night gave me a nightmare where i died from unavoidable burning thanks great
snake story by the way when is the anime adaptation coming out um well the anime
adaptation is going to come out in the middle of my story and then the anime is going to need to
catch up to my story but i'm not done writing it yet so they're going to make their own version
where the he lands on the sheep and then i'm going to finish it and they'll do another anime to do
that one too sorry for spoiling but thank you flying sombrero thank you one mystical for the
10 bucks germ i just want you to know that this is one of the best live streams i've seen in a
while even during the children's book arc the stuff that happened during the rng maybe laughed
so hard it woke my dog up and that was a lot of fun there's a lot of fun my favorite part was
getting really amped up and doing four pages or five pages and been starting to get like a
coherent story and then clearly even seeing that the characters are not even colored in
at page six seven eight and nine it was just like it was like not only was it getting to a point
where like the i was like phoning in page nine and the phone was across the room and i was
screaming on speaker from somebody like to somebody else's line page nine that was my
favorite part it was a great stream i had a lot of fun hope you did too thank you uh bunt tally
bunta bunt i'm gonna call you bunt thank you bunt for the two bucks thanks for the great laughs
this has been one of the funniest dreams you've done and always makes me feel a little better
when i'm feeling depressed germa hart absolutely thank you so much for hanging out and absolutely
if you can feel a little better while hanging out i'm very very happy to hear that thank you so much
bunt uh lacronda did i miss you given 50 i did another 50 bucks from lacronda the huge amount
of money that i missed earlier somehow i must have been in the middle of a meltdown
but this will sell at the book sale perfectly i want a hundred copies thank you lacronda for
50 bucks on top of everything else you've given you rock thank you hey tingy thanks for the one
dollar hey germa since you now have that store page and said you can sell more than just shirts
i was wondering if you could make caps like this but with germa jex on it oh and you might want
to have audio on audio why do i want audio on oh okay i don't get it what cap are you wearing
oh you i don't wow tingy thanks for the dollar and how did you not expect that
well because i have a teespring store and well above yeah and oh you might want to have audio
but i here's the thing i muted my desktop audio and when i saw that this it was it was immortal hd
right and i was oh did he say something i mean so i wanted because i've talked i've like hung out
with immortal hd a few times at like conventions and we just kind of been passing like oh hey hey
how are you what's up man we just kind of sometimes we just see each other so i'm just like
make all right whoa i wonder what maybe he said something he's bragging about it you know i you
know i you know i was more like do you want that ow but that's why i was curious i was like well
hold on a second this can't be a gnome maybe they said something about like my shirts i don't know
no i got a who that was that the first gnome of 2019 i don't think so i think it's happened
like in the last few weeks isn't it stream sucks why why what happened you knew i was
gonna look over there you knew okay some of you guys are so good at this you know what i'm gonna
they you've timed it you know what i'm gonna look over and you get me you know what i'm gonna look
over at the chat it's some people that have like magic powers to like get i turn my head there it
is i just got here he's paranoid they're all around me they're fucking surrounding me what
did that person say what did you say hey germa what i was gonna say good stream man thanks germa hey
hey the food's ready okay all right cool anyways thank you to uh novi 333 for the 333
i demand to purchase a copy of that masterpiece no it's always free it will never be charged i
will never charge money for that book it doesn't mean i'm not gonna put it on a t-shirt and sell
it though hey the freak for the one dollar thanks reek hey germa here's my pre-order deposit for
your new children's book can't wait to read it to my future kids what if what if i put all nine
pages on different shirts and you could get a group of people of nine people they might have
done something like that have a whole children's book on a series of shirts that's the ultimate
sellout each shirt is 20 dollars and you need to buy 15 of them to have it even make a any coherent
statement at all so you have to get like 15 of your friends to buy the same line of shirts
that's genius how come no one's done that yet one for every day of the week twice make them all
available only by grab bag so you have to keep playing the watery that is just that is just
disgusting that is just disgusting behavior can you imagine if i was like hey guys i'm coming out
with a t-shirt yeah it's gonna be pretty good it's good yeah it's uh the night sky yeah but it's in
this box that uh it's like a like a five percent chance that you'll get the night sky in the box
and the other 60 percent of the time you're gonna get like a couple of dumb stickers
and then like 20 percent of the time you get like the glue man shirt but that was already
available before imagine if i boxed that up and did like a box bullshit hey chat did germa ever
get the Pikachu so i lost in the mail i never found him i went searching out of binoculars and
i was up fucking looking up looking at stuff couldn't find him uh thank you spaghetti spanky
for the nine dollars nine bucks hey it's my birthday today a solid 31 years ancient
would it be all right if you could sing me happy birthday yeah sure
happy birthday term i can't sing yes i can i'll prove it happy happy birthday turn this off it's
fucking me up happy birthday uh thank you spaghetti spanky for the nine bucks
happy birthday 30 years old it's a milestone it's good i feel good uh it's vex thanks for
10 bucks you don't need to read this one okay uh could i use clips of you in resident evil for
just a video yeah i mean i don't what am i gonna do i'm gonna like come after you hey hey don't
look as long as if you take a clip of me and you do something terrible with it and you make
it out of context when you say something fucking horrible or you put me in something that i
shouldn't you know if your grandmother's if your grand if your grandmother's daughter's child would
watch it right and think it was interesting and funny then okay you know what i'm saying then that
would be okay with me but as long and just be reasonable with me okay but no i'm not gonna like
no i get asked that question frequently but oh can i use this like image of your face
i'm what am i gonna say no there is an official highlight channel that has all the you know it's
it's like where to go to see a highlight but if you want to like look i put myself in front of a
green screen what am i gonna hey hey hey hold on a second there's six hours of green screen footage
of me but i don't want to i don't want you to use me in your fucking video the the book's out on
that one just be reasonable you know it's all i ask anyways uh thank you so much it's vex for the
10 bucks maybe you hopefully got what i was saying there uh tuskor thanks for the one dollar tuskor
since the story is similar to icarus name the snake may name the snake icarus what do you mean
kid icarus the game boy game you were at a screaming compilation you know god
no the no not the not the game boy game the god you know i've never heard of the
icarus story this is a lot of stories you know how many greek gods and shit there's like 40 of
those guys there's the god of butter the god of wine the god of cheese i don't know who the fuck
all these people are this one guy like wrote a book and then frisbee'd the book into the space
and then zeus grabbed it and read it and he liked it so he named him
reticus i don't know anything i only know that there's one that runs fast
and delivered the mail to everybody hercules hermes thank you tuskor for the one dollar thank you
uh thank you have gun for the two dollars yo germa i enjoyed your mountain blade rampage across
calradia the base game is kind of hard and you seem to have adjusted adjusted quite quickly to
the game the mod just so much i can't even speak the mods are so much better i recommend star wars
conquest as it has nearly everything including wookies blasters speeder bikes and cool force
powers if you don't go back to warband could you at least give conquest a play on stream
i think it would be much more enjoyable yeah i i had like a meltdown last night you all were there
that wasn't even i wouldn't classify that as a meltdown i got agitated i got agitated i needed
to take a break and come back strong the next day and play eye spy and make a children's book
but uh i did say that i was never gonna play it ever again in a very aggravated stern speaking
voice and that not necessarily will is not true i did not know that there was like a 200 person
multiplayer servers i did not really know that you were very mad i did click on exit as fast as i
could oh i remember that i called you a fucking idiot and you say i can look back on it now and
laugh but but like past me future me is like i was like kind of funny past me is like on fire
that's all good it's all good for goodness i'm only human you know i'm not a god and i'm not one of
these powerful zeus gods that we all know the stories of i'm just i'm just a guy i'm one guy
you know i'm i'm no icarus he's one god but anyways uh have gone thank you for the two bucks
and that's warband multiplayer would be fun with mods i'm sure it would be great thank you flair
pancake for the 10 bucks hey jerry my favorite children's book as a kid was uh chocolate hip
chocolate chippo hippo which was just about a hippo that loved cookies and how his whole
life revolved around them it had no moral or anything but i still loved it as a kid
so we went in too deep remember i told you guys at the very beginning that it didn't have to have
a story and no you got to make a story and i'm like yeah i guess i know i gotta make a story
it's gotta have something there he could have just been on the cloud and liked being on the cloud
and watching the birds that could have been the whole book we did a story about a capitalist
snake going through midlife crisis yeah we didn't need to just hung out on the cloud who cares why
he's up there eating bugs and like blown snot rockets down but thank you flair pancake for the
10 bucks uh thank you ray gun for the one dollar uh thank you rag arnoi for the two bucks hey germa
funny thing i passed out three hours ago when you were doing a point and click thing turns out i
could hear germa in my sleep so i dreamed about germa being a shit teacher and not being able to
teach italics to build a bird house so do you have an anecdote that proves that you're not a shit
teacher i can't prove that how am i supposed to prove anything like that but thank you uh thank
you clink for the five dollars hey germa it's me twitch chat uh you might not remember me because
he left me in the i spy spooky mansion looking for ingredients for shrinking soup anyway you
should come back and get me out of here i think the skeleton is going to turn me into the next
ingredient hey spooky spitfire thanks to the one dollar i basically missed this in last stream but
i want to tell you my work just shafted my shifts so i only have two shifts per week i will still
talk to you through cheers so that's unnecessary it's okay uh sorry you got kind of screwed over
with shifts i'll still talk to you though it's all right man don't worry about it hopefully you get
some more shifts next week or the week after what if you can do we're gonna get pictures of germa's
feet yeah what do you what would you what would you like me to tell you no what are you talking
about why people like this why did i read it out loud because i had to i had to read that dude i'm
gonna fucking one of these streams i'm gonna put on like hobbit shoes i'm gonna put on like the big
hairy fucking hobbit feet you guys you guys have cut that shit real quick people would want that
more no i'm not doing any of that i'm only going fucking rib cage up for the rest of my life on
twitch uh but thank you germa is the best for one dollar hey i missed the stream where you talked
about one punch man so if you'd give me a summary of what you thought about it it was great i liked
i loved the concept i loved the humor i thought it was very well paced and i'm looking forward
to 2020 when i watched season two thought it was great don't link the clip with me slapping myself
what is this uh something i wrote it thanks to the one dollar i've been falling in and out of a
fever dream and it is a snake why does he have what's what's with the why does he have a gun
taped to him what uh dr clay thanks to the one dollar i played that eye spy game as a kid i
got the game at one of my school's book fairs i remember toying around in 3d movie maker but
it was a demo and it had only three backgrounds and two characters and you could not save
interesting how today there are more programs to create content and one of them is releasing
hopefully very soon here dreams i've been waiting for that game for years i think there's a lot of
fun there i'm willing to give it as much of a try as i can but thank you dr clay thank you creation
one dollar oh uh i said that atari is making the atari vcs atari is like getting back into the
console game they're like redesigning it or something if you like fun you should check out
minecraft minecraft what's that is that a game um that sounds cool sounds fun uh thank you dr clay
for the one dollar a real talk you're my favorite streamer your community's awesome take care you
as well thank you uh thank you peanut gangster for the two dollars and 50 cents germa i love
your streams man i've been watching your stuff for a while my only question is do you think
you will do another live rumble uh love from boston yes yes the the plan is to eventually
do a live rumble on stream a lot of moving parts but i'm willing to make it happen uh
cardamom thanks for the one dollar hey germa just watched aquaman yesterday and i was surprised when
i saw you as volko in the movie and guess what william defoe was up for an academy award did he
win it did william defoe win the academy award when did that happen when was that show was it
today when is the academy awards over did william defoe win for uh his van goh performance because
he's nominated for an academy award and he has never ever received one he was nominated once
like 20 years ago no not for aquaman for he was van goh the name of the movie is like the beauty
of everything what's it called that every uh something about the the gate what's it called
the beauty of the at eternities gate there it is yeah he's he's normally for the academy award
best actor hanging out with bill gates no that movie sucked what it was called snakes on a cloud
or something the movie sucks i haven't seen it it tanked oh thank you meme machine for the two
bucks love you boomer hey thank you thank you meme machine for the two bucks hey thank you pigeon
for the one dollar what do you have to say about all the overwhelming amount of furry germa fans
uh why do you think there's such a large presence of them who are attracted to your channel
specifically it's something that you or your community offers that others don't something
that would explain the abundance of them thinking i don't know well are these is this the are these
the questions is this the interview is this this is the this is the interview here no i don't give
shit i don't care who you are you know i don't care who you are who you are where you're from
which background is what you like what you don't like it that doesn't matter to me
what matters to me is you you know uh it doesn't matter you know what i'm saying don't dodge the
question i just said it it's okay what do you have to say about the overwhelming amount of furries
i don't even think about that i see them as you talk about the overwhelming amount of germ
to take take furry out of that sentence overwhelming amount of germa fans i don't
got nothing wrong with that what's wrong with that i'm not a fan well every fan is a furry
i don't think that's true did you just call it no i'm saying it doesn't matter i like that
doesn't matter to me it should oh my god jesus christ well there's your quote um do i think
this community offer i don't know i have no idea that's classified i don't know next question
uh thank you raisin for the four dollars thanks for all your hard work thank you for the four
dollars raisin thanks for hanging out here uh yen wen thank you yen wen len for the one dollar
okay so it's almost 4 a.m i'm pretty much beat but i tried my best to get it done in time i'm
dead also we should hang out sometime oh god oh my god you did it all oh you gotta be kidding me
here you go let me let me like let me get this saved we'll go over it let's see the whole
thing it's one giant book uh where the hell is it oh fuck it's over here well i don't think i can't
i can't even put this on the stream i don't think i have to like open it hold on i think i have to
open this in a different window okay there we go can i save this as something else because it's a
pdf how do i change that it's bedtime for me read the book yeah i know you're right open the pdf in
your bra okay i guess i can here okay here we go i said i can get it on the my browser here
all right give me one sec there's so many fucking tabs open how many goddamn tabs do i have why is
this not showing up what the hell i'm gonna have to like capture the screen there's no way i have
it in a new window but it's it won't um i gotta close this shit out hold on sorry guys for some
reason it won't pull the i can't like capture it let's try this again capture this whole window
no i can't get it to capture this i can't save it either it's pdf and i can't get it to show up
on any of these things for some reason now what if i do this this will probably work i'm just
gonna pull the whole monitor hey look at this i'm gonna pull the whole damn monitor all right here
we go got it pull the whole display now and that is it ready ready ready ready ready three two one
action okay so here's the first panel having fun kicking the ball around let me scroll down up in
the sky the whole thing is here like the cloud work and then see you later i'm on the train and
you put the smoke here you put the you got the mist working get the tie that's a good nice touch
february 2019 i miss everybody climbing the stairs of gold all the way up to the cloud
sad in the clown raining it's the current month down to all your friends and there you are at the
end there everyone's happy and that's me that's fucking awesome he just made that an eight out
of ten but the book was a very good book just needed a little work but thank you yen wen that's
one of those stories that over a couple months you're gonna look back and be like that's a all
right i liked that i know i will but thank you so much for that it was very well done
nice touch in removing the dialogue it improved it so much
thank you tingy for the one dollar that gnome was too good to not hit you with it but in all
seriousness a snapback with jackson it would be nice to have yeah let me give me like a month or
two before i think about other merchandise because there are two things that i just
launched so i want to give some time for people to decide if they want to buy something and if
they do and they don't that's fine and then put something else up there later on the year
meme machine thank you for the one dollar kek but seriously love you germa at almost my birthday
happy almost birthday meme machine thank you d soyd for the five dollars today is my birthday
i turned 26 i spent it at home watching you and playing video games i just moved to canada and
don't have any friends to hang out with thanks for being here on my special day happy 26 birthday
d soyd feels birthday happy birthday hope you had a relaxing one uh moving's hard it always is no
matter what thank you for the five dollars i wish you the best and a meme machine for one dollar my
birthday is on the 20th i'm turning 21 can you sing for me yeah i got you got the first part
uh snooze and coffee thanks for the one dollar still thinking about making those trading cards
now that you have the store i remembered it don't think you i forget it uh i've talked about the
trading cards a couple times the thing about the trading cards thing that i want to do here's if
you're not curious the thing like an idea that i have that i thought would be fun is to make
collectible cards and physical packs uh not a card not a game but just kind of a collectible
physical tangible thing to hold on to for fun and have different you know oh like i open you open
up like a pack and there's art on the pack and it's nice and they're made well and they're you
know distributed and there's like a bunch of different commons and like really like an epic
card in each one it wouldn't be very expensive would just be for fun just to have for the
community and what i ran into with i know a guy that knows like that industry about like selling
and wholesaling and uh did a lot of research for me and how much things are going to cost
and the whole thing was going to cost like tens of thousands of dollars it's going to be like
probably thirty to fifty thousand dollars for the whole thing so i was like uh i'm probably
gonna have to hold off on that because it was gonna cost a lot of money just even the card
packaging and card packs themselves is it like a lot of production cost just to get them made so
not now but i always told myself so for instance if it was let's say i could like kind of if i could
like swim by because obviously it's the production cost which was a lot of money just to get it in
the first place and we're talking remember we're talking if you sell a card pack and there is think
about this how just just physical how many of these things would have to be made because if
they were like five to ten cards in each like card pack i would need to produce potentially
thousands of cards right even if they were only like 50 to 100 pieces of artwork they would need
to be hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of cards made it's a lot of cards so my theory was if i
ever get like to a position where i had a lot of extra kind of income or a lot of money that i had
that i was ready to go it would be sort of a decision i'd have to make because as long as i
could like break even that i was it was something i wanted to do and maybe the production cost
paying i was gonna have a bunch of artists potentially but as of right now it's not like
on the table not now so that's kind of the long and short of the whole thing so uh and i what
i've told myself recently is coming up with ideas and things that i'd like to do are great
but i really need to focus on things that i can do now not things that i want to do later things
i can do now and that's something that i can't do now hope you understand green screen green
screen card is just a green card yeah it's gonna be like a bunch of characters a bunch of original
like rumble characters and no like copy written characters but there's plenty of original stuff
to make into like a little card thing at least i think but we'll have to wait maybe but thank you
snoozing copter uh thank you though for the one two dollars you oh i accidentally press enter now
see what you made me do i messed up and i forgot what i was saying oh yeah apparently you didn't
promise my me my lawyer just told me but whatever if you still want to do it you know where you can
find me yeah and that's i've wanted to make like a game to all these things of stuff that's gonna
have because it's got to be by the fucking book because i'm not gonna do like a kickstarter or
do like oh i'm gonna throw up like fucking 30 grand unless like it is certain that it's
going to be completely by the book people are going to get paid like this amount and this is
what's going to happen this is who's going to be involved it's a it's very messy and i don't want
to cause like a mess in this community so i'm going to have to be very very careful with stuff
like that because then you kind of get into the weeds of are there too many people that are on
the project are there do you have enough money to pay everybody make sure that first before it's
like oh yeah you you you you you you you and you it's got to be done right and i obviously
want to have a significant amount of money to pay people because people are going to be making
potentially at least a handful of pieces each so it's got to be done right i can't just do it
just there let's go tomorrow i guess i'm gonna write like some stuff down no it's gonna be done
correct but i do appreciate the enthusiasm because it shows that there are there's a lot
of interest so but thank you thank you to base grandpa as well for 15 dollars thank you base
grandpa hey germa i think you'd appreciate this old flash game called gateway 2 without saying
too much to spoil it it's a fairly short puzzle game about 45 minutes worth a lot of interesting
cool ideas uh check it out when you have the chance gateway 2 i did want to do another just
flash game online kind of game stream eventually here this next week maybe so hold on to this one
because there are at least a handful of remember i said in the recommended channel throw me some
ideas i'm willing to play it for sure actually good game well hell yeah i will put it on the
list of games to play during the flash game stream uh getting close to the end here thank
you spooky spitfire for the one dollar hey germa i am in a game of smite and i think we should add
the god of coffee the god of cheetos and the god of chicken to smite they would call him germa
pantheon uh i am monk thanks for the one dollar we have another uh piece of snake artwork this
would bet three what a cute little is this is this snake cannon now is this is this snake in
universe yeah i think so well done very cute very very very nice uh thank you clue the sniper
for the one dollar whoa that's a lot that's a lot right now i'll get to you in one second
because that's 50 fucking dollars but clue the sniper thanks for one dollar hi germa fun stream
tonight it was cool seeing people create different pieces of art based on your scribbles uh community
art show could be a lot of fun uh anyways here's my attempt yeah we got this one earlier
i think we saw this one earlier it's fucking beautiful it's good shit i like the background
a lot it's got a great background got a great it's a there's a lot of great symmetry here
but yeah no it's great i love that stuff it's always great to see it thank you so much clue
the sniper and thanks for the artwork bloody doctor gave 50 dollars bloody doctor thank you
so much bloody doctor don't think we forget you killed santa hope justice finds you i didn't do
anything i merely had a fucking fun statue and i did not know anything i did a funny lol laugh
out loud stream joke and all of a sudden the how i'm the bad okay i'm gonna slow down here because
i've been told i have 72 lawyers 74 actually because i wanted 64 of them for the fucking
nintendo 64 but that wasn't enough so i need to get 10 more ignorance isn't an excuse
thank you so much bloody doctor justice appreciate it though thank you 50 fucking
bucks thank you tar alecran for the one dollar you really don't have to pay that much respect
to atari they were first but due to their awful decisions on every level they're nearly destroyed
the entire video game medium it was like two years where no new video games are created
and everyone thought it was just a fad that had passed until nintendo resurrected the industry
with their nes console this is partly true yes thank you spartan cat for the one dollar that
was a damn good stream my dude needed a good laugh it did give me an excuse to draw so here
are two drawings of the snake one the second page and the final page
jesus fuck where did this snake come from catch me uh like that's all just in his head
that's great thank you so much spartan cat it's great uh flank tank thanks for the one dollar
before you go one last thing can you give me a good bia berry can you combine both voices i
tried it's very hard easy uh thank you though flank tank uh thank you at the end here for
dr clay snake snake and then snake with a really lot a bunch of a's thank you thank you for the
art everybody thanks for everything uh thank you creation of cyborg at the end here uh will you
try any of those dreamcast games that were uh like half-life and cancelled games probably not no
i'm probably going to do space channel five and see man and then put a cover on the dreamcast
for a probably an indeterminate amount of time but let's roll the credits this is a lot of fun
stream is a little bit shorter but sometimes you just have a short fun stream you know what i mean
i will see you guys in a couple of days and hopefully the vibe is here and i have it all
set up if there is a change somehow we will still do something if the vibe is not here which it
should be but if it's not then there's a couple other things we can do on tuesday
and then whenever the five gets here we're going five week so hope you guys are ready should i get
beat saber oh fuck yeah let's throw the credits uh there's so many images here here we go thank
you everybody all the new subs all the old ones and then we just had another uh dr stein came in
with five dollars they say release the book release the book i mean i i i already i yelled
it to the world put it like in a pdf and put it up there tomorrow something maybe
but thank you dr stein it's no snake but i drew a hot dog bear i'm telling you that
you guys are fucking too much a hot dog bear that's really cute so what if you guys could draw
so well if you need the title page let me know i think that's just fun to have you know we could
have like four or five different versions of the book you know in the discord maybe people can
just throw them together and make them out of community pieces and just have them that's that's
for you guys you know that's sick that's six feet of bubblegum for you not them you didn't see my
sub gifts wait wait wait wait wait did i miss you oh you did absolute coro thank you absolute
coro for five community subs i missed him earlier i had to scroll down a little bit sorry about that
but thank you so much thank you and then we had a couple more bits come in from superintendent
chalmers when is the inevitable grandpa stream grandpa's a demon didn't you see the movie
thanks though and thank you creation the cyborg for the one dollar am i going to get the new atari
probably not and then creation the cyborg again for a dollar can you do one you can do me a favor
on my birthday can you watch the burn scene again no happy birthday on the 17th but i'm not going
to watch the nicolas cage burn scene again thank you though hey the tiz cha tizcha boy thanks for
the one dollar check out the message on germa985.com i think it's a great idea this person sees you have
good intentions is it a placeholder yeah i don't i don't know on a website i don't really have a
need for it i don't really have a need for it you know what i mean but thank you to all the new subs
on all the old ones that sounds like a fire i'm afraid to click on that is that like a virus
website i'm afraid to touch it but yeah i mean i do i do like look if somebody grabbed like a
germa985.com and they just kind of have it and they're just like keeping it kind of under a
lock and key and if they you know if i ever asked him for it and they would give it to me i mean
that's that's all right i'm not like oh how dare they because i didn't do it and i didn't think
about it but i don't think i really need um i don't think i really need a website because that's more
from me to think about and do remember it took me a long time to come around to the idea of having a
discord and even that is like another thing and then i'm gonna run a website i'm gonna have a
discord and i'm gonna i'm gonna get a vibe two years late you know what i'm saying he wants
to give it to you for free oh well i mean that's okay if if if there comes a time where that needs
to happen that i maybe i would look into it just make it link to the store yeah i would need to
think what i would want to do with it i would really need to think about that like what i
actually would want to do with like a .com i don't really know what i would do just take the damn
website you're my amino ill will and i'll be content you inspired me since i started watching
it went literally zero publicity from this but that's why i didn't say anything on this you know
what i mean i'm only paying yeah yeah i know like i'll i'll i'll look into that i will but that's a
nice kind message from that person are they in like chat are they in like the discord or something
are they in is it how do you how would i get in contact with that person you know what i mean pay
somebody to make a cool website yeah i guess but at some point like a germa985.com is like a branding
i'm an influencer website catch him on twitch tv he's been over here too branding options like i
don't it's like a tuber website maybe i could do something fun but we had a couple more come in
uh we had jess you got it for one dollar i'm officially third done with the painting he he
i can't wait and then creation of the cyborg thanks for the two bucks make your own controllers
for the playstation 1 and playstation 2 uh i need like a 3d printer to do that but thanks for
watching guys i'll see you on tuesday i had a lot of fun take care of yourselves much love to you
see you soon ta ta for now dr stein five dollars playing mine show it's a really good game that's
one of the first things i'm gonna do with the vibe that's kind of why i'm buying it
is to do a mind show a little tidbit for this week take care good night and goodbye thank you
for the five dollars dr stein