So, I bought this shit. I know this game sucks, but when am I going to do this? There is no
opportunity for me to put this in. Zero. I don't have any other chance to play this right now.
It's the only time it's going to happen. Otherwise it's just going to sit there,
and I know it's going to be terrible. It's not even going to be funny. It's going to be such a
shit game. It's the bachelor video game for the Wii. I've been trying to find a place to put this
on stream, and I can't. It's so bad. When it's three hours, I'm thinking like probably like
another couple hours on this. I don't know. I have to play this. I bought it. What do you say?
Well, I have no other opportunity. This is it. This is the opportunity. I've got my opportunity
right here. Let's change it up. That's your fault. Yeah, but okay. Let me level with it here. I'm
not going to start a stream with the bachelor for Wii. You know what I mean? This is like a
put this in for 10 minutes, and have everybody tell me this game is horrible. Please do something
else. To a point where the spam is uncontrollable, and I'm forced to change games, right? 10 hours.
All right, here we go. Let me make sure this is actually accurate, because the GameCube actually
pulls the screen differently. I already hate this. I already don't want to do this. Okay,
I probably don't need the nunchuck, but... And guess what we're doing? We're going on camera for this,
because I have to hold the Wii mode in my hand, and I probably have to go,
catch the fucking flies with your fucking net, right? So I have to do it like this. So we're
going to be on camera. All right, by the way, remember, the Wii processes the data through
the capture card differently, so it might be a little different. Let's check this out. Ready?
We all right? Let's see if I have to change it. I have to move the resolution a little bit, because
see how bad it looks. Actually, it's not that bad. You can pull it out a little bit.
That's hard. I'm trying just to see. It's hard to see. I could have changed this game title.
Is somebody naked? Oh, this is the product of the Wii being the most popular console
ever, and your grandparents potentially owning it. I can't believe this is even a game that's
on here. The Bachelor. I can't even click it. I have typed in the Bachelo. The Bachelor
I can't even click the fucking game. Does it say the Bachelor? This was on the DS. How? All right,
select a contestant. Well, I've, I've, I've, that's, I've, I don't, I mean, that's me already done,
and I'm a movie producer. I can't change that. Love test. I kind of want to do the love test.
Personality quiz. Let's do the personality quiz. It's complete season one. Okay, the dating style
quiz. Okay, how do you make a first impression? I like to dress in style. Nope, I went jogging
pants and like cut off t-shirts everywhere. A warm smile and hello works for me. Nope, that's not,
also not true because I smile like this. So no, that's inaccurate. Be respectful and show up on
time. I'm late to everything. I've never showed up on time to do a single thing in my whole life.
Arrive with flowers and chocolates in hand. I'm never prepared for anything.
So I would, that's, none of these are accurate. What happens if I don't do any of these?
Whatever. Season one. It's Jerma and Diana Pappas. How do you play this game?
It's going to be, it's the party games. It has to be. It's on the Wii. It's going to be party games.
Are you guys at a funeral? No, you're the bachelor with your host, Chris Harrison.
Okay, why am I so sad?
This character just turned and just fucking just blasted the other guy.
Welcome back, Diana Pappas. Holy shit, they say the name. Oh my God. I thought it was going to be
like, please welcome back our contestant. Before we begin, I can provide a for the game.
Yes, let's, how does this work? You participate in a series of dates. Let's go on dates. Each one
has an exciting challenge to be met and will be your chance to impress the bachelor.
Kissing under a restaurant table. You know that this is, this is, oh, you could, it's okay to do
that at dinner up top. This is not that Disney dog movie that this is okay where you're humans.
Okay, depending on the type of date card you receive, you'll either go on a group date
or a one-on-one date. What do you mean go on a group date? Group dates involve everyone
while one-on-one dates. Why would you go on a group date? The instructions on how to play are
explained on each date card. You can also warm up by selecting practice. Oh, this is like dealing
with somebody that has to plan everything, like obsessive compulsively. Oh, did you get your date
card? Did you get your date card that explains everything about what's going to happen on our
date? Like, um, I have to go, my entire family has got hit by a car. It's like, oh, okay, sorry,
I gotta get out of here. You'll earn heart points based on your performance. The better you do,
the more hearts you'll collect. Sometimes the bachelorette will even send out small
floating hearts. And I gotta catch it. Catching any of these will improve your odds with her.
I knew it. I told you we were gonna get like a net to have to catch things. However, not everyone
will make it. During the rose ceremony, the contestant with the least number of hearts
will be eliminated. No, I will not marry you. It's not happening. Along with his dream of
marrying the bachelorette. Isn't this some statistic somewhere that, so, what a great,
uh, little slide here. Along with the dream of marrying the bachelorette. The boy with, oh,
I choose you. We're dating now. Where we love each other. Isn't this some statistic that
none of them ever work out? You get to the very end and they stop dating within like three days.
That happens almost every single time. Why do people still watch this show?
Are we all ready for the first date? I wish you all the best. Let the journey begin. Let's go.
All right, first date card. What's it gonna say? Group date in the hot air balloon. The skies are
all clear for lift off. Let's get these air balloons up in the air. Don't get left on the ground.
We have to take an individual balloon? Who could inflate their air balloon the fastest? Pressing
a hold. Do we have to do it? Wait, don't we hire a company to do this? Press and hold the A button
on the Wii remote to keep the needle inside the green margin to inflate your balloon.
I don't even know which one I am. Top left? This is it. Get that heart. Got it. Oh, that's hard.
I got an extra heart. I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm tied first. What is it? What does this guy
below me have? Six? Seven. I gotta get, I gotta get there first. I don't know why this makes me want
to scream. Okay, I'm good. I did it. I don't know why it makes me want to fucking scream when I was
doing that. I was just like, I want to like get energy out of me. I hate that. I hated that. Okay,
I win. Jerma, Nate, Simon and Keith all going for the same love. It actually is just, is Mario
Party. Now I have to drive a car. Automatic plus one letter grid. It's time for some off-road racing.
Yeah, if we have that rule, we have to use it whenever it's available.
Um, I don't make those rules. Who will finish first in the off-road race? Point at your vehicle
with the Wii mode and hold down the A button while moving left and right to navigate the race
course. What do I mean? Hold, point at your vehicle. Why would I not do this like every other Wii game?
Are you kidding me? This is a game. This is a game already. This exists. It's like an old one.
You know, where have I, I'm seeing, you know what I'm saying? Well, you know, this is a game that
does this already and it's an old one. It's a physical thing you do this with. It's hurting
my head to think about this. I need to know what that is. I had one of these. Yeah, I did too.
None of these guys get in the extra hearts. Um, this is awful. This is awful, awful, awful, awful.
I'm still going to beat it and I'm still going to get first place on that date.
You bet your ass. I'm going to get that one-on-one date.
Ice skates. Does she, does she come with us? Or is she just standing, like, just stand up here?
Who can collect hexagons the fastest? Press and hold the A button anywhere on the ice to mark
hexagons. The longer you hold, the more hexagons you mark. Release the A button to collect
your hexagons. Why is nobody doing anything? Oh, I get it. That motherfucker got so lucky.
Oh, come on. Do it. I'm going to get this whole corner right now. The whole thing. Get the fuck
out of my way. Got it. It's not going to hit me. I'm going to be able to get this whole thing.
Two, three. Got it. It's going to go underneath. Oh, am I in the lead? Take this whole corner.
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. Why do I care? This is the worst minigame.
Spare us from this hell. No, I'm interested. It takes five minutes for me to realize if it was
worth doing. It's worth doing. I'm interested. I'm going to get that one-on-one date and then
we're taking the, we're taking all the, I'm beating the whole game. No, why did I say that?
I'm not doing that. I'll be probably like a tenth of the game.
Why was this on the, why was this on the coke? What is this? What is that?
It's not a tooth. It's not a tooth. That fucking tooth just comes up. It just like falls out.
All right. Let's get, let's take some shots. For each mystery photo, be the first to answer
the question. All right. So we have to find out what the mystery photo is.
Ready? How many chairs are in this picture? You guys are so slow. Bachelor is holding her
by the shoulders, torso by the arms. The contestant at the far right is holding
cheese, a spatula. It's going to be, oh, he got it wrong. Fuck. How do you guys know this?
In this picture, Brad is drinking wine. Drinking wine. Fuck. Pouring wine. In this picture,
the people are not, it's definitely not playing baseball. They're writing, eating,
making a toast. Eating. What is in this photo? Floating restaurant. Yeah. In this picture,
we can see a pair of sandals and a plastic beetroot. A plastic beetroot is in a bottle of
sunscreen. A bottle of sunscreen and a pair of sandals in a bottle of sunscreen. This one.
That's it. How many wine glasses are on the table? Two, three, four, or eight. Where was this picture
taken? In a bathroom. In the desert. On the beach. I'm winning, motherfuckers. I'm getting that one
on one date. In this picture, the female contestant is wearing a brown dress, blue, red, and yellow
dress. Oh. Oh, you got me. How many female contestants are wearing sunglasses? There was
no way to discern what was going on in that photo. Not possible. What's in the foreground?
The beach. In the background, we can see the sea. A road. Snowfall. A wall. A wall. It's a
snow. A wall. The sea. It's just a Truman Show? That's not what the sea looks like in the background.
That's a fucking Truman Show wall. The female contestants' eyes are looking at. Her eyes are
closed. His mouth. I think they're looking at his eye. His mouth. His mouth. Yeah, I thought they
were kissing. Her eyes are closed. The couple is looking at the sunset. Roasting marshmallows.
Kissing. Swimming. Gonna be looking at the sunset. They are not kissing in that photo. Zoom the fuck
in. They were at least three or four inches away from each other's faces. From the left, the yellow
surfboard is fourth. Alright, gotta get one more. One more. In this picture, the man is playing golf.
Cutting grass. Playing baseball. Cutting grass. Cutting grass. Playing golf. How did I come in?
How? I got five questions first. Whatever, I got more hearts anyways. You didn't catch enough. I win.
One-on-one date. A one-on-one date invitation has arrived. Who is it for? It's for me.
Jerma, you're going on a one-on-one date. Jerma, you're in Smash Brothers. The Bachelorette chose
you and she would like to keep the intimacy going. She's waiting for you here with a finest.
Okay, here we go. Oh, it's a fucking ugly couch. Why do they look like YouTube Kids animated
characters? I feel like suddenly we're going to start singing about like eating your carrots
and peas and shit over and over again. Point at each falling feather with the Wii mode. Press
A on them before they reach the bottom. Wait, is this? Why are there other people here? Get the
fuck out of here. This is my date. Oh, they're the ones dropping them. Okay, it's hard to aim
when you're scrunched up like I am. I win. I win. Does that mean that I win the game?
Another one-on-one date? I get two one-on-one dates in a row?
If you don't get a rose. I know I'm getting a rose.
Bonus hearts. Yeah, I win. It's impossible. Will you accept this rose?
You did it. Of course I did. Why are you sad about that? That means you get to keep going.
Why would you be sad about getting a rose? Why would you be? Eight hearts.
This guy was on his phone half of these mini games. He wouldn't even try it.
That was Binding of Isaac music. Everything is Binding of Isaac. Everything, apparently.
Everything. Next round of dates? Wait, that was an entire season. Congratulations,
you unlocked Close to You. The Caring and Kindness Quiz. I can't wait to take all these quizzes.
Oh no, that was just episode one. Okay. Oh man, we gotta do more of these. I'm gonna stomach this,
I think. I want to do these quizzes. It's the same- oh yeah, it's the same person.
Who can solve each puzzle the fastest? Bullfrog. Bullfrog. This is imitating a bullfrog.
Grasp each puzzle piece with the A button on the Wii mode and release them on the puzzle
outline to complete the picture. To complete the puzzle. Um, are we doing it together?
It's one of these. You gotta be fucking kidding me. Hey, hey, hey, move, move, move. Get out of my way.
Oh, I won. I'm first place. Uh, fuck. Some of these are baits. Some of these are baits.
I just fucking had that one. Oh, he saw me do that. He saw me pick that one up and he was like,
oh I'm gonna get that one too. Oh. Oh, we don't even finish it. Has he seen that picture?
I have not. Yes, I have. I have seen that picture. We've seen- this picture props back up like every
three or four months. I have seen it. I've seen it. Turn your light up. It's scary.
That better? All right, made it to the party. For each weight comparison, determine which drink is
the heaviest. Okay, I have to- what? Oh, it's- oh. Oh, okay. I get it. What? Got it. Speed. Oh,
sorry. They're so far behind. You idiot. Easy. Pretty close. That's fucking cursed. Are we at a casino?
Blackjack? Who can collect casino chips the fastest? Point at each falling chip with the
Wii mode. This is not- you can't even code in like a simple Blackjack game. This is- this is moronic.
This makes me want to scream. I don't know why. Like, the way I have to move and the way that
it's looking, I think I have to scream. Anybody ever get like that? I don't know why. Just like,
something about this whole package is like, like I want to just fucking move and scream.
I don't know what it is. The webcam's not showing the Wii mode. I'm playing on the Wii.
Like, yeah, you need to be able to see this information. You know what I mean? Like,
what am I, a bad fucking screamer? Okay, you can see now, right? Okay. Who can bake a souffle the
fastest? All right, so hold the A button on the Wii mode to keep the needle inside the goal. It's
just the same game that we've done three times. This is the quickest way to fuck up any food in
your oven. Oh hey, um, honey, could you preheat the oven to 200 degrees and then turn it up to 500?
And then after two minutes put it down to 100? And then put it to 700? And then put it at 300?
Sure, what are you trying to make? Um, diarrhea tomorrow morning. Oh, okay, sure, I'll get right
on that. One-on-one. Rapidly changing temperature. One-on-one date. He's arrived. Who's it for?
Oh, it's gonna be this guy. Why not take a short rest here before continuing with the date?
Short rest? It's a beautiful sunny day after all. Is this the way the game's waiting to be telling
me to not play anymore? Nintendo Wii always did this. It really did not. It was so concerned about
you getting up and leaving. It's been 30 minutes. Get up. Stop moving. You should sit down and
read a book for a while and then come back. 20 minutes. Why not get the outline of each
image with the weave mode and just press A to start tracing? You're gonna trace every
nature image on the left side of the screen as fast as you can. I'm gonna have like shaky hands.
What? Why is it zapping me? I thought I could cheat. I thought I could cheat. I can't cheat.
I have to scream. I can't breathe. Can somebody with like ADHD do this? This is like suffocating
them. No, don't show them kissing. I win again. Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
too big. Too big and too bright. Too big and too bright. Too big and too bright. Too big and too
bright. Too big and too bright. I looked at that. I saw that in the rear view mirror thing and then
nope. Whatever. That's the- no it's not- I know it's gonna be one of the- it's gonna be one of those
things where I see that image on the top. The first thing when you type in German on 85 it's
that face where I'm going like and ohhh. I'm not going back. Yeah there's no going back.
No going back. No going back. There's no going back. There's no going back. I- I- I- I- yeah
yeah I'm just not going back. I just look like a fucking idiot. Look at fucking Bob's Burgers
character. Hey I got the rose. It's all that matters. I know it wasn't easy but I'd like
to congratulate you on making it through. All right what personality- what personality quiz
that I unlocked now? Right you got the money matters quiz. This is the real reason for this
game being streamed. You know that right? I could give a fuck less about everything happening here.
When we do this I care about this. I don't care about anything. I have this. I care about that.
For me you could be streaming Doki Doki. I could also not be streaming Doki Doki which
is what I'm currently doing. Oh they're models. Who will be the first to get dressed? Memorize
the position of each fashion item. You receive a random color. Oh it's just okay it's only two.
You receive a random color. Point at any draw with the wii remote and press the A button to reveal
items matching your color. Memorize the position of each fashion item. Oh no the hat is- no!
Holy shit how did he do so bad? How did he do so bad? I can't believe he lost.
You waved what? You sat like you're in a casket.
What does that even mean?
I know I know exactly what you're talking about.
Like the puzzle thing. Oh this sucks. Okay here we go. Give me that. Too slow. Too slow. Idiot.
This guy's getting so badly destroyed. It's embarrassing.
I just need one more. Let's let him get one. No don't let him get one. Fuck him.
Notice that I drink. I notice that I drink shit weird when I'm on camera.
It's like I'm pretending to drink it a way that I don't typically drink it.
Let's- let's get- let's pull like the cover off this and I'm gonna drink that the way that I
normally would if I was just sitting here normally. I don't know what- here we go. Ready?
Okay that was normal. What I've been doing is stuff like this. I don't know why. Like you know
that when you're like con- self-conscious about the way you're drinking out of a can of soda.
It's time to take a bath. Oh can we pick up some coins?
Mystery photos. I love this one. Where was this picture taken? Highway, hotel entrance, concert.
Concert. Hotel entrance. We both got it wrong. This makes no sense. Where was this picture taken?
Casino. I immediately know. Definitely. What color is the contestants dress?
White. Yep. What is this person holding? Playing cards. Pretty good hand. The spectators are waiting
for a ticket, holding lighters in the air, watching a movie, holding their hands in the air.
Holding their hands in the air. One more. How many female contestants are at this table?
How would you- how would you even know- how- there's no way to- a couple in this picture is
sitting on a couch in a plane in a movie theater on a park bench on a couch. Nice one. Couldn't
even just- this is five blobs at that table. The computer's good at one thing. I thought that was
a dog. Zero. Holy shit. Not good. I did it again. All right that's just- that's just like a Photoshop
where you just like push my mouth up and like spread my nose up top. That's funny. It's funny.
It is. Who can- oh! Who can trace every beach image the fastest? I have to do it like this.
I'm not kidding. I swear to god. I fucking hate those. You have to breathe.
Move the sensor further away. No, not that I do the sensor. I have to do it like-
I've already clicked this image. I've already- I've seen- I've seen it.
Okay I haven't seen that one. I have not- okay this one's a little different. This one's-
I feel like I can make this face. That's fucking terrifying. This is what I feel like people that
are trying to kill me and my dreams look like. That's the image that you see. It's like not a
human but it is a human and they're like walking with it like erratically with their fucking
shoulders and shit and they like have something like a like a trophy in their hand. That was the
wrong thing. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait.
Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Hold on. Wait. Where am I? Okay. Zero hearts. Fucking loser.
A 1-0. Who is it for? The guy with zero or the guy with 48? Let's try Simon.
I just looked over and saw the guy with the fucking like golf trophy about to kill me.
If I ever need to settle you guys down, I just have to press that button.
All right. We're in the hottest restaurant in town. Drinking some red wine.
Did you find that in your food? Did we complain? Wow. Holy shit. You just- that's like- that was
like her grandparents' locket. This is a hexagon minigame. Bang right there. Don't get greedy.
Wait. And go. It's not gonna hit it. Check this out. It's gonna bounce.
Too late. Got it. Oh. I'm winning by a lot. Hopefully we find the locket that's on the ground.
That's it. Game over. I win. All that to climb under here. Did somebody pay for it? I don't know
why but for some reason didn't- didn't- did anybody else want them like just to go up there and to go
like blow into each other's mouths? Am I the only one that like thought- saw that happening?
No? Are you sure? I won the whole thing. Where's the road?
There's no one that contested. They're all gone. Is it the guy that got zero points and that didn't
just blow into the girl's mouth? We're getting married. From a fucking game show. From a fucking
game show. Oh we didn't get one extra one. We didn't get an extra one. There's no extra one.
I'm Chris Harrison from everyone here at the Bachelorette. Good night. And that's a wrap.
All right get the fuck away from me. Oh you- you've smelled so bad this entire fucking game show.
Yeah whatever. The rose you had. Fucking- wasn't even real rose. Plastic? We're giving plastic roses?
So wait I- so I get- I got married. Okay love test. All right it's time. It's time to do- to do these.
Let's do it. Personality quiz. Let's act- I'm gonna answer this as truthfully as I can.
How do you make a first impression on a date? If I- okay if it was me and it was real.
And it's- it would never be A. Ever. It would be B. Like hey how are you? Hello. Just saying hello.
Well that's terrible. Does love at first sight really exist? Of course I have that effect on
other people. It's romantic but hard to take that seriously. No it's a cliche that only happens in
movies. Yes I believe it exists. It's romantic but you- I don't take that very seriously.
Your date shows up at the door. What's the first thing you look at? Their body, their eyes,
their shoes, their smile. Just like hey good good to see you. Oh yeah uh hey hey Carol.
It's it's it's like it's it's like one of these. It's like there. How do you feel about blind dates?
How do I feel about blind dates? Why? I don't even need to answer this. Hey I know somebody
that you might like. Oh cool. What do they like? Fuck you. Just go on a date loser. Oh and you did
this to the other person. So two people have been told hey I know somebody that's single. You should
you should you should go on a date with them tomorrow. Go and like go to like a nice place
so you're like you get nervous when you eat the food. We've already gone over this shit.
All right I can arrange my own dates thank you very much. A. They're fine as long as other people
as the other person is my type. But I like to know the person before going out with them. Okay
I think they're sweet. That's how my parents met. It's it's a it's a it's a I like um I'm
I feel like I'm like just getting set up on like a blind date. You don't even know who the fuck you
are or who you are or who you're talking to. It's almost like you get like dropped off at school by
mom. Like your first day of school. Okay have a fun time. Okay mom. Is it you? Jen? Jen? Jeremy?
Oh you? No not right person. Oh neck. What's wrong with my neck? How do you feel about blind
dates? I can arrange my own dates thank you very much. Where would you prefer to spend your date?
Would you rather be at a fancy restaurant? I like a bit of class. Coffee shop but like a good
conversation. At the movies I like the familiarity. At the park I like holding hands.
It would probably it's coffee's easy. Coffee's the best. But movies actually is the correct answer
here. You go to the movie. There is a long archived conversation about what you do on a date
from personal advice from germa985.
Conversation should you avoid most on the first date? What topic should you avoid the most? Your
ex? That's terrible. Politics? That's also terrible. First date? I need to know first of all before we
go in before we even see the appetizer menu. Are you a democrat or a republican?
Oh oh that was not the response I was looking for. Okay we don't have to talk about the politics.
Okay settle down. Do you want me to go? Okay I'll go. I'll go. How much you hate your job
dating a car? There's a car in the restaurant where they sit at the table and you're across from the
car. All right don't talk about politics. Religion it's not terrible because you can just be like
man like how did we really get here and people fucking talk like that all the time. Don't talk
about politics. You're coming to the end of a great first date and there's definitely some chemistry.
Do you move in for the kiss? Okay you're coming to the end of a great first date and there's
definitely some chemistry. Do you move in for the kiss? I can't. I never make the first move. I'd
want to but the other person has to feel it too. Not on the first date. It wouldn't be appropriate.
Both of us make the first move at the same time. How does that work? Is it like...
Okay no wait wait wait hold on. I need to I gotta get this. I think I broke it. I think I'm breaking
my stream. Holy shit this is so delayed. This is fucked up. I yeah I broke it. Oh it's because I
don't have two cameras right. Hold on. Yes I do. No I don't. Yes I do. Hold on. This is worth it.
Trust me. Go to the bathroom for a minute. It's because you can't do it with the same camera. I
gotta get my reference cam. It becomes a five minute joke. Maybe I can do it. Hold on. I think
I can do it. Let's see. Shit. The other camera's not here. Damn it. It's not here and it's not
possible to get. Fuck. You know what I was going to do. Shit. There's no other way I can do this.
Is there no other way? There's no other way. Oh I'm sad. Damn it. Print out a picture.
Oh yeah I gotta have two cameras here. Oh it's disappointing when you can't capitalize on a
fucking potential plus two point of the stream. All right what. Oh none of the first date.
Both of us. We make them over the same time. Your date is 20 minutes late and there's still
no sign of them in the restaurant. You call but there's no answer. What do you do?
I'm gonna go home. I'll wait around for five more minutes but that's it. Call again. Maybe this time
it'll get through. I'm staying here. Something must have happened. I'm going home. You're out on a
first date but the two of you just don't click. It's getting late and you'd rather leave. You end
the date. That's really easy to make up a lie and leave. Tell them honestly thank them. Have a friend
call them and bail me out. I just go through with the rest of the date. Yeah you know you just say
uh it's uh hello hello what is this oh no way oh you're in town you're in town for just the next
two hours oh yo shit oh i'm so that's crazy i'll have to catch you i'll have to catch you
okay see you soon bye by the way that's what i was doing not with a real phone going like this
and then i get up and leave first date and it's going well your day turns to you it says
pretend you didn't hear that that's nice but we're skipping a few steps are you out of your freaking
mind uh i yeah that's we're skipping a few steps here i think the dating style you are the free
spirit happy and carefree you enjoy meeting new people and take everything in stride
you might be a bit cautious when it comes to love and you definitely believe in its power
wow we got more of these to do you're walking along the beach when you come across a dog with
a broken hind leg struggling in the sand what do you do do you leave it there it's probably
infected these are all fucked up i'd approach slowly to see if the thing is okay that's okay
call the animal shelter oh my gosh so cute can i take him home
uh you you make a phone call you make a phone call you say there's a herd animal here
honest communication between lovers is better on a cell phone incredibly important in strengthening
a relationship a two-way street one one must listen while the other talks uh it's a two-way
street this is seat you've got to have good communication what's the best way to cheer them
buy them a gift that'll make them happy have a quiet talk and just hold the other person
ask them what's wrong and help us solve the problem cookies everybody loves cookies
how could you not like it it's got cookie teenage son borrows the car without permission
i wish i if i should have clicked that one crashes it into a pole your first reaction
your teenage son borrows the car without permission crashes into a pole what's your reaction
when i get my hands on him he is dead oh my god is he okay i guess my insurance is going up
it's okay as long as he learned his lesson um it would be like holy shit is my son okay
attention does a typical house plant require i don't know i never had a house plant some water
and sunshine once a week a lot the leaves need to be a healthy green i'm not really an expert on
plants you see a homeless person begging for money on the street what's your first reaction first
reaction tell them to get away from me say i have no money walk by and make no eye contact
give them some spare change well here's the thing there's there's a couple
there have been there have been plenty of scenarios where someone's sitting on like
the sidewalk and you're just like oh i feel terrible that that's too bad you know and they're
just like you know hey i'm just looking for food like you know whatever and it's like here have
some take something take something you know what i mean right there's also scenarios where
this person may or may not be actually scaring the shit out of you it's c or d or it be dependent
this is this is true sometimes we're in a credit card world there's been a lot of times when it's
like oh i don't have i literally don't have anything i actually don't have it i have like
my credit cards i don't have anything i don't like carry cash sometimes i do
this is i this i don't know this is not give them the credit card here you can have
you're gonna have this oh you look at like your credit card statement and you see like stuff
that's not typical like wait a minute oh yeah i gave that credit card to uh to that guy on the
street there's a lot of like lift rides on here and a bunch of movie tickets and a store called
creighton barrel this guy saw like fucking 15 movies in the last like three days it would be
one of these three so i i don't and i don't know which one of these because a different
scenario every time so we're gonna go like this after the office party is about to drive home
but he seems a bit tipsy what do you do let him go he's probably fine ask him if he's okay take
away his keys you call cap get a cap or like if you figure out who's there then you say hey like
i i haven't had anything to drink i'll drive your car you do you drive you know get get a cap get a
lift it'll be a cap you can come back to you can come back and your car is not going to get
you're not going to you're not going to trouble get a cap get a lift one day when your parents
become too old to take care of themselves you will ask my other relatives to deal with it
have them move in with me put them in a retirement home visit them every day this is this is
unrealistic uh i don't i don't like any of these visit them every day that's i'm not i can't i'm
not gonna do that i don't want to do that but i mean what if they want to do that i got other i
got siblings that are way smarter than me in every single facet of life every single one
do you find yourself filled with a sense of joy and happiness during the holiday season
not really am i supposed to yeah i think so must be all the gift-giving well lately it's become
more hectic and busy absolutely my favorite time i think so i think i feel all right during the
holidays those who fight constantly have forgotten how to express affection do you agree those who
fight constantly have forgotten how to express affection that's obvious who likes fighting i
would agree that being caring and affectionate takes practice not fighting doesn't necessarily
mean you don't have problems i don't completely agree but fighting certainly doesn't help
i mean it's probably i would say probably d for me i mean these all could be accurate c but not
fighting doesn't necessarily mean you don't have problems i don't know it's what are we talking
about like fighting like what does that mean that's obvious who likes fighting i mean it doesn't i
fist fight it's not what that that's incorrect not combat it's not combat now fighting doesn't
help but i don't know it's i don't know i don't know what they mean you're the teddy bear you are
a walking hug always putting others before yourself your actions are genuine and ever selfish watch
out for those who might take advantage of your sweet side i wanted i thought i wanted to get
like the bull you know what i mean the teddy bear that's not accurate money matters after a dinner
pays the bill
oh look honey i'm worth it imagine saying that had like a first date or a second date imagine
how much of a fucking psycho you would have to be oh here comes the bill oh okay so uh look i'm
worth it that would be like a instantly leaving the restaurant uh i initiated the date i'll pay
it is the money and the relationship somebody's got to do it but it won't be me times have changed
people need to be aware of their money situation the person who is more financially competent in
such matters if you're rich i don't see a problem why is everybody automatically saying this is d
for me this is me people have to be aware of their money situation you got to be aware
are you okay with you if your partner makes more money than you okay with that more than okay that's
how i support my lifestyle uh it wouldn't feel that i was doing my equal share depends on how
much it depends by how much and if i was able to earn more if it doesn't affect my relationship
then i'm fine with it now if it doesn't affect the relationship though i don't care what do i care
if money can't buy me love what can it buy uh education security freedom uh it's one of these
two education is fucking expensive yeah educate what is it what is it how how much does it cost
to go to school now like 489 000 but having a bunch of money to go to like to like not worry
about school um gives you security it's security it's been said a person's wealth is not always
a reflection of what they have what does that mean it means don't be fooled by someone who
looks rich it means that happiness is not always linked to money it means you can make a lot of
money but still owe a lot it means they're not spending enough it means that happiness is not
always linked to money that's what the saying means after checking your bank account you
discovered your spouse has been making a lot of expensive purchases lately how do you feel
no big deal people should live a little angry we need to talk about this are these purchases
made out of necessity that's the idea you're sharing a life together i mean this is probably
the like it would be like what it would be like what what did you buy like what is this
are we talking about like you bought there's a lot of different kinds of expensive purchases
did you buy a expensive bracelet or a jumpy house because one of those things is a little
bit different than the other i mean i don't know i'd be like that way i'd be like why'd you buy a
jumpy house i'd be fucking really happy about it so that uh not a big deal you've met someone new
and everything is going well until you find out they're actually in heavy debt does this affect
your relationship definitely how can i expect them to take care of me i'd continue seeing the
person but this is a warning sign difficult to see myself with such an irresponsible partner
everybody has debts nobody's perfect i have a heavy debt i mean it's it's either b or d
but what does that happen like it's okay you met it you met someone new and everything is going
well until it's almost like they're scratching out until it's like until the rest of this is
scratched out they ask for you to pay for all their credit card bills and all the loans they have
it's like that what doesn't all of this i mean it's it's probably like d or like b
but if it's student debt everybody has fucking debt whatever how would you feel if your spouse
couldn't complete their own income taxes and is incapable of filing a report you lose your job
while your family relies on you as the primary source of income how do you feel i i pay some i
i got a cpa that does that for me i got no idea what the fuck i'm doing i got a cpa that goes
over the whole books i don't i don't you lose your job while your family relies on you as a primary
source of income how do you feel uh i'll get another job so what i feel like i let them down
i'm not worried that's why we have savings um it probably bothered me a little bit that probably
i'd probably get i'd be like uh oh shit i mean if i would hopefully have some savings
i mean if you if i lose my job if i lost my job i would i feel like shit like that's like it's
like fuck that sucks no you just that you would always be like regardless of the scenario and
remain close to your loved one or live in luxury but be too busy to make time for one another
live in luxury but be too busy to make time for anybody or live modestly and remain close to your
loved ones luxury i don't like living poor modestly a life without intimacy isn't worth it
luxury everyone wants to provide for their loved ones it doesn't matter as long as we're still
together we have a chat full of psychos a is based what b i don't care like i did that doesn't bother
me the money you're the piggy bank you refuse to let money interfere with your love life bills and
romance just don't mix although this may be ideal having a bit of financial awareness would do
you some good hey i'll have you know game i'll have you know that i lost a shitload of money
uh trying to short beyond me and i don't yeah all right i it wasn't that i wasn't a shitload
of money i always i did that i did that for the comedic effect of being on a live stream
hundred fucking thousand dollars did you out of your mind add a zero wait yeah what is this
select update match to compare yourself with diana papas oh i did okay i did the quiz now
it's gonna see if we're compatible the piggy bank in the money bag here the irresponsible object
versus the fast spending person with soul mates i don't even have to play that anymore the game
you have what everyone is searching for loves eternal bliss as the saying goes you were made
for each other and tend to grow old together for that we salute you what's the purpose of this game
uh to make people that watched this tv show uh play own a more i don't know there's no reason
why would i even do anything else i want to do how do i get another quiz i want to do the quiz
oh we have to so why am i doing this again is my soulmate is right here somewhere why am i back
in the game season two season two with second wife to the bachelorette post chris harrison
first you've all gotten to know each other a bit better gentlemen i get a new wife every year
every season and and germa wins every season this would get really really boring don't you think
well who's gonna get the rose season nine it's germa wow we're gonna be together forever see you
next season when you do this again she was our very first bachelorette ever physical therapist
from indiana makes her return please welcome the original bachelorette first date i wish you all
the best these are all real people please play something outside beg you one more quiz one more
personality oh man this is so bad this five games programmed on this this is mario party
it was free in captain crunch i i need to like blink hard so i hold on it's like i don't like
this oh i have to do the trace game again i have i'm gonna have to stand up for that one no i'm
already thinking about it i'm already thinking about the trace game five games program and only
one royalty-free song is the bachelor is the bachelor theme song whatever even on here
not tracing no tracing it what is this one this is oh this is i know this one this is click the
thing that falls from the top of the screen all these were free on pop cap 10 15 years ago
it's one more personality quiz i don't give a shit about anything else and i'm a woman after
this excellent why did you turn me into every single character that gives advice on game of
thrones no tracing this beautiful river is where you'll be white water rafting grab your oh this
stupid thing all right what do i need i just only look at the ones that i need to look at
it hopefully it's pink pink or purple i know where they all are pink or purple
pink fuck it's the only one i don't know if only they were impressed by gaming skills
server you have goblin eyebrows actually i need to like work on the middle here it's been a little
while i gotta like get some uh some luggage going on here it's been it's been a little while i gotta
do some uh we're rolling out the red carpet tonight rafting whatever started hollywood movie
premiere and you get nothing but a-list treatment excellent yeah that's it that is right there
please what are you talking about this game is broken oh you know they were right oh shit
everybody's going for it oh excellent fuck out of here bachelor game joke has been going on for way
too long i don't think so who said this was a joke i want to do another personality quiz
we're going to get it restaurant is to your liking the bachelorette invites you for a romantic
night view on the terrace would you care to join her what would you have a locket oh yeah my my
old wife had a locket too just like no you want to meet you want to meet like under the bed whatever
the thing is you want to meet under the the table excellent doesn't help frog get the frog get the
whole frog i'm gonna turn it off i think incredible you have no idea this is the i you have no idea
very good i need to like jump on a trampoline after this it's
i need to like jump as high as possible and just like i can't do that out because of this shit
don't i did that for me not for you okay new personality test time for our rose ceremony
the person who does not receive a rose i'm afraid the dream is for you avatar is so ugly
that was amazing okay personality test i'm gonna do what everybody else did when the bachelor aired
for the first time watch season one say this is dumb watch the first episode of season two
and then go i'll never watch this show again i know that wasn't easy but i'd like to congratulate
here we go personality quiz incoming you unlocked the leisure quiz let's go
which idea of relaxation what's the most relaxing thing on the beach with a pina colada and a massage
hiking in the woods nope catching up on my reading no spending time with my pets that one
it's been said the couple that plays together stays together would you agree
um not really no one should do something they don't want uh somewhat different interests can
complement one another absolutely doing things together encourages teamwork and synergy you
should just be happy spending time with the other person i mean it's b or c it's it's b it's probably
b or c i'm gonna go with b can someone's style of relaxation tell you more about their personality
um what you do is an extension of yourself perhaps some aspects but not all
i guess but don't we all enjoy relaxing for something to rent at the local movie rental
store which criteria helps you the most hmm okay well i'd go in there i'd go in there for
donkey kong country and it wouldn't be behind any of the blockbuster boxes
it would be there'd be a three rows of donkey kong country all of them would be would have no
blockbuster golden ticket behind it so what you would do is you'd go in for that and then you
you would have to i mean i i guess i'm gonna rent the unicycle game for a fourth time
new york i can go sightseeing and shopping australia i can go travel the alpaca scuba dive
oh paris i can visit the art gallery and practice my french
why i can lie on a beach and dance the i what i don't know um probably australia
new york is just no new york is just a city you can't scuba dive in new york
which of the following hobbies or pastimes would you rather not do with someone else
surfing the internet that's boring yeah that's easy watching the game on tv i'd rather get
some exercise playing poker losing money isn't my idea of fun playing chess it looks complicated
i would never want to play chess with any other human ever ever um you see your partner stressed
out you're most likely to prepare hot bath turn on lights play soft music cook them their favorite
meal i don't i can't do that it's gonna be a always pick bath as you get older do you find
there's still time to relax there isn't i make the time not as much as before a lot less my life
is busy about the same if there isn't i make the time and make your definition of a workaholic
somebody's addicted to work somebody who does a lot of overtime somebody who is dedicated to their
job somebody who misses out on the fun a workaholic would be somebody who's uh is a lot as addicted
to work or somebody there's a lot of overtime it's somebody that's out there's a lot of work
i have to do this one where do you see yourself during retirement this is a great question
nope definitely not traveling around the world uh not going to learn how to play the piano i
uh i i have a really shitty uh pinker so i can't my my pinker doesn't work when i i would never
be able to learn how to play the piano or play the guitar um start my own small business nah
smell roses and listen to the birds chirp now that's my kind of retirement
you got the yoga pose for you time is short and it's important to make every free moment count
you're more concerned with spiritual peace and personal fulfillment rather than instant
gratification this is not even true this couldn't be more inaccurate this whole the first sentence
is maybe accurate the whole second part is just not even true i need instant gratification for
a lot of things instant i can't just give these to me i want another quiz and one more quiz
one more quiz another quiz enough no no one more quiz i'll have to trace again i don't want to do
that all right fine fine fine all right fine how long did i stream this for an hour and a half
i got my money's worth this thing was like 12 cents i'm gonna be i'll be right back and i'm
gonna put it on the mystery gaming