If I can get to it, that would be great. That was my time at Porsche. And it was pretty fun.
It was actually really fun. This game is a chill game. We're not gonna play for too long,
but it's supposed to be a chill game. We'll find out, right? Our game uses Unity analytics through
this certain personal data is collected for detailed information on the type of data collected,
its purpose, and transfer, as well as your rights. Please refer to the privacy policy on our website.
In addition, Unity also uses this data for other purposes of its own. Information about
Unity is used to be found here. I can just decline it? What? Okay, I didn't think that was
good. I thought I was going to close the game. All right, click and drag left mouse button to
move the camera. W A S D. All right. Drag the right mouse button to rotate the camera.
Okay, or Q and E. Okay, makes sense. While hovering over the background with your mouse,
scroll the wheel to zoom. Oh, do this zoom. Endorph romantic. You build landscapes out of
the hexagonal tiles. Click on one of the empty tiles around you with the left mouse button to
place your tile. Oh, so I can I get it. You can form groups of elements like forests or villages,
place tiles next to each other and connect their colored edges to form a forest spinning at least
five tiles. Oh, there it is. All right, cool. The tile count on the bottom right shows you the
amount of tiles in your stack. Once it reaches zero, the session ends, place three tiles to
continue. You gain tiles by fulfilling quests. This place looks like a fucking awful indicated
by the speech bubbles to complete this quest at least six additional houses to the colored edges.
Connect exactly two fields to the quest tile. The symbol in the corner of the speech bubble
hints to a follow up task. Connect exactly two fields. What's a field look like?
What do you have a field? I don't know what it means by field. Like an open space? Connect two
fields to the quest tile. Okay. How do I do that? What does it mean by fields? Oh, okay. I thought
I okay. All right. All right. I thought that field was a different tile type. I didn't know that
field was this yellow shit. I'm thinking of like a green field. All right, so let's go.
How is that wrong? I don't get it. There can only be two fields on it.
I have no idea what the fuck just happened. Exactly two. All right.
Okay, I'll get it. Just wait. Okay, a flag just spawned, which indicates its group can be closed
to gain extra points and tiles. This field group is closed when it cannot be expanded anymore.
Hover over a flag to hide the remaining open edges and place the tiles there.
So close the edges here. So just go around it and close it. Does it matter what I use?
Do I just have to close this out? I do? What's happening? Oh, I made way. Oh, I made way too
many. Okay, I get it. I made way too many. Okay, man. I'm just made way too many. I didn't. Okay,
listen. I did not know that a field was that. What the fuck is that? I didn't know that that's
what they want when meant by field. Okay, that looks to me like, like a haystack. Okay, I thought
it was like a haystack. Train tracks and river tiles have placement restrictions. Their ends
cannot lead into different types of tiles. Okay, so we'll put some train tracks on.
I feel like, I feel like somebody hit me in the head with a hammer before I started this.
I just got dinged in the back of the head with a frying pan before I turned this on.
Okay, all right. I just need to start over. Collect 100 points. You got it. Oh, fuck off. Okay.
If all six edges of a tile match its neighbors, it counts as a perfect placement. Ooh.
Let's go. Be honest. You don't like this? No, I actually really do like this. Quiet.
All right, let's go. This is where we start. Everybody relax. I've had my two donuts.
Let's do it. I want to have the village be this way. And this can the fields can be over here.
Yeah, a nice big village town here. I don't like that. Maybe one over here.
I don't like that. Sorry. That's not terrible. That's kind of near the trees. Pog. All right,
we got a river here. Oh, yes. River's gonna go right through town. This can work here.
Kind of not really though. I'll make a little small town over here. Shit. That's all right.
That's okay. That's fine. Hey, wake up. Wake up. Wake up. Water tile coming in. Windmill. All right.
Not bad. Not bad. All right. I'm gonna put that one in here. What? Oh, perfect. Look at this
placement here. Check that out. This is cute. This is cute. Good placement there. Little lake.
Little lake that goes over here. Cute. Ignore them. Oh, I'm ignoring them. They're being hard
ignored. Oh, wait. Okay, we need to finish this up. Can I connect them all? I can. That connects
everybody, right? This is beautiful. This game is really cool. Perfect placement there. That's it.
Right for the flag. What's missing? Right there. Quest fulfilled. How much further do I have to go?
Uh-uh. It doesn't like that. I don't know if I'm gonna be doing- I can't do much with the train
track shit here. Oh, yeah, I can. Look at that. Um, I'm in trouble here, but it's fine. Can I put this
anywhere? Shit. I think I screwed it up. It's okay. It can be right here. It's not gonna be pretty,
but it'd be fine. It's good enough. Yeah, this single house over here. I gotta connect it.
This one person surrounded by water? It's all right. Another windmill. I wish I could put it
right there. I can put it here. That works. Wish I put this one. That's not fast enough. I could
give it like a cabin over here. I'm still going. This is still just rolling. It looks kind of like
shit over here, though. Um, that's gonna go up this way, I think. Yep. I did it. I'm just- I'm
rolling here. Zoom out. I'm okay. I gotta stay zoomed in. I think I'm screwing it up, though,
over here. This is fucking strange. There's a goal? Oh, well, let's head that way. I did it. Wait,
was I not supposed to? Oh, I was just trying to get to the tile. Oops. I fucked it up for the
goal in the top right. Form a body- body of water with at least 15 water segments. This is getting
there. Place down 100 tiles in total, okay? Finish five sessions with a score of at least 5,000.
I thought that was gonna be the end of the level or something. That's why I did all that.
I think it's salvageable. It's salvageable. It's fine. Where's this last segment?
Highlighted edges? Where? Right here? Shit. It'll end if you have ti- oh.
All right. We're good. I'm fine. Yeah, this is my first time playing. I get it, but I don't get it.
I'll get it eventually. Oh, fuck. Uh-oh. No, I'm all right. I have to close these edges.
Like, close it. I wish the highlight was a little more strong. I can't even see what I'm looking at.
Where is this highlighting? Is it- can you see anything? Oh, it's right there. It's hard to see
that. There we go. I fucked up. This is all fucked up. I- I think I understand it, though.
I'm probably gonna have to turn the stream off soon. I think I'm evolving.
I can't place this here. Oh, for those of you that have no idea what I'm talking about,
Holly has COVID, and I probably do, too. So, uh, I've been testing negative the last
two days or so. A little more than that. And I took a PCR yesterday, so I'm kind of, uh,
possibly about to be in it. But I feel- she's got a mild case. I feel fine. I'm fine. Don't worry.
Have a good- I almost have the water one done. Biome lavender? So, does this just keep going
till I place all the tiles? See, I- I screwed it all up. I was fine here, but then when I was like,
oh, that's the goal. I just have to get to the goal. I thought it was going to end the level.
That's my own fault. That's fine. I don't know where I can put this now.
Let's be over here. Okay, I got a boat from a train route with at least 10 tracks.
I have to close this. The level ends when I get 100 points. I need some- I need water. That
actually might do it right there. Shit. Damn it. Not quite. That doesn't close that out. I need
houses. Uh, whatever. I don't care. I need to end that anyways. Did I do the quest? What's the music?
Uh, yeah, it's whatever the same music is. I can come out that way. That's fine. All right,
38 more tiles. That's all right. That's okay. I don't know where the hell this is supposed to
be going. I'm just trying to get the achievement. I have to connect this or stop it or something.
Like, I just keep making it bigger. Ah, oh, come on. What happened here?
Train. Nothing says one million followers like a crisp Cuban cigar. I love that comment. That's
funny. Crisp Cuban cigar. Try to complete this over here if I can.
Screw that up. Wait, can I- I can close this now. Uh, this is like a little kid's train.
There's a little park here. There's a carousel. There's a little train that goes in a circle.
And then there's like a petting zoo and stuff. That's not a real train track. That's fine.
At exactly two houses. At at least 42 houses. Um, dude, how am I supposed to do that?
Does that not count? That's not- uh, it's three. Shit! There's two right here. No!
Yes! Perfect. Hell yeah. Oh, fuck it. I can't. This is a map of Disney World.
Did I lose? Oh, it's just a session. Okay. That's fun. That's actually pretty cool.
I'm only 251,000 in the world. All right, that's it. I should probably go. That was Dwarf Mantic.
I might actually play this off stream. Just hang out. That's actually really cool.
There are other modes. I probably- is this on iPad? Because I really kind of want it.
Yeah, I was only going to stream for like three hours, but here we are.
Now, very important. Incredibly important before I go.
Green screen submissions are due tonight. You've only got about three or four more hours
from right this very moment to get a submission in. Go to the Discord. Go check it out. Go read
the rules. Also, we are playing multiverses on Tuesday. It's going to be sponsored. It's
going to be lit. I'm going to have a ton of fun. I would be there if I were you to watch some fucking
skilled Bugs Bunny gameplay. You know I'm the- you know I'm the guy. I would be there. So,
that was cool. July- that's July 19th. Green screen movie night will be probably only a few days
after that. So, probably on Thursday or Friday, potentially, depending on how fast we- all right.
Okay. Okay. I will see you guys later. I'm not going to say very much anymore. Take care. See
you. Thanks for watching. I'll talk to you guys on Tuesday. I hope I'm not fucked up on Tuesday.
I hope I'm not fucked up on Tuesday. Okay. All right. I'll see you later. Good night. I'm going
to- I'm going to sleep all day tomorrow. I promise. Across a million- a million subs.
That would be crazy. Yeah, the last like half- 45 minutes or so, it really started to hit me.
What time on Tuesday? To be determined, but probably around the same time in the afternoon.
I'm good. No, thanks for a million followers, guys. Seriously, it's insane.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday. I'm crying. No, seriously. That means a lot. I- thank you.
I'm going to go. This is not going to be much of an outro. Good night. See you Tuesday.
Multi versus I'm excited. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. See you soon. Good night.