See you later, dude. You're right down there. Yeah, I you want to buy you a what do you want a car or bike? Good car. Let's go kill it. Cops are after you. I've been laying low man. Oh, hey, there you are. I get hurt by that. Go go kill German and start doing your sandwich to me. I'm helping. I'm blocking the door. I'm getting in. I'm getting in. This cop is after me. Right.
Now, by the way, hurry up. Hurry up. I thought you were ready. He just started shooting at me when I opened the door. What is going on? Is this like the finale of the fireworks? What the hell is going on here? Dude, seriously, this is like the Fourth of July. Oh, hey, wait, wait, wait. Get in the car. Get in the car. This is like the last 10 minutes of die hard. This prick just like ran me over. Hey, your car is on fire, by the way. I'm not getting
it. Well, it was a second ago. Oh, God. Just go up. Oh, okay. Steal that guy's car. No, this tire is on fire. I don't want it. I'm getting. Oh, my God. Get in. Get in. Get in. Okay. It's like DJ.
It's like Armageddon. It's like Armageddon. It's like Armageddon. Dude, seriously, you guys are dicks. Oh, the sign. Oh, my God. This is terrifying. I feel like this is a boss fight. Like, hey, where's like your help on the top of the screen? Hi, Zach.
Like, seriously, my view. Oh, my God. All right. It's like your health at the top of the screen. Boss fight like the commander of the military or something. This is like finding a visor.
Can't lose the beast. I'm coming back to you. The helicopter that is raining fire down on us all.
This is so hard to control. These guys are taking too many turns. I shot that guy. I shot that guy off the bike. It is so hard to turn on this. You guys are so far away. I don't know how the hell you ended up getting a rocket over here.
Fail. All right. So I'm going to stand right here. Stop. This cop just did a barrel roll. That cop just did like a nine foot barrel roll. Are you serious?
I am going to run your jeep over with my bike. Okay, stop. We have to do stunts. What stunts are we trying to do? Dude, we have to do this guy. What a psycho.
Why do we have to go this way? GPS, you always take the weird routes. And okay. This is not the highway. Why did that happen? Oh, God. I just saved you from Star. He was about to kill you. I changed my mind at the last minute. This is very difficult to get in position. Try and get in position. If I can land on you with the car, this might be ridiculous.
I'm going to go right here. I'm not going to go any further. I'm going to go straight off from right there. This is so difficult. Let me get on board. Are you going to get in? I need to get this spot on. I pressed down on the arrow.
I wasn't even paying attention until it happened. I just saw you launch off the blade. What happened to the helicopter? Oh man, that was so funny from my point of view. I had no idea it was there. I was trying to adjust the position.
Slowly breaking out the angles and then incoming. Nobody even knew that was going to happen. He just did it. I'm flying around. I'm at the airport. I see you. I don't see you. Oh hey. I'm not touching anything right now. Look at you. You look great.
I can't believe I smashed into you like that. I was spinning and then you chopped off and I fell to my death.
I'm going to the Empire State Building. When I say Empire State Building, I mean just coming for you guys. I'm just trying to shoot your faces up. This isn't Battlefield. I was trying to blade your car.