Hello, it's muted. Yeah, I was cleaning a few things up. Let's take a fair, fair few things.
How we doing? Welcome back to another stream. Tonight we're gonna do more Darkwood and hopefully
get somewhere close to the end. If we don't get close to the end then
gonna have to do it a different day. Gonna have to finish it at some point and when I come back
after the weekend here. But before we do any of that, before we talk about Darkwood
or even play Darkwood, we have something to talk about. What's wrong? I'm gonna wait till people
come in because I have a small announcement to make. Triplets! We're gonna have triplets!
Just kidding. So there is gonna be a Halloween stream this year and the Halloween stream is
going to be a fairly elaborate one. But hold on. I need to wait because there's a lot to this that
needs some explaining. Let me just wait till people trickle in. I'm excited. I'm excited
because this is gonna be a shitshow. Here comes the bugleberry takeover. Somebody actually
mentioned this yesterday and it was so hard to not say anything. Do you know how difficult it is? I
cannot get- don't ever tell me a secret, first of all. If you have a- hey man I gotta tell you-
I gotta tell you a secret. Oh, Jerry. Oh my god. He was like so annoying today. I'm gonna tell Jerry
immediately. Like within 10 minutes. We're gonna be like, bye! You're gonna be walking away and
Jerry's gonna walk by. Jerry! I got to tell you something, Jerry. Don't ever tell me a secret.
He's just a snitch. No, no, no. That's a really bad example. That's a terrible example. No,
if somebody told me like a secret, something in confidence, I would not tell anybody if they
didn't want me to. I'm just saying like I'm- it's hard for me to sit on information.
Jerry trusted you. No, it wasn't Jerry that trusted me. It was somebody else.
No, no, no. Let's put it- no, no, no. Hold on. Let me rephrase that.
If you told me, hey I want to- we're planning Jerry's surprise birthday party for next weekend.
Oh, this is gonna be three clowns. We're gonna have a tractor. There's gonna be like a fire engine's
gonna come and honk the horn. I'm gonna be like, holy shit, that's awesome. I'm gonna see Jerry the
next day and I'm gonna accidentally be like, what are we talking about anything? And I will slip up
and say, oh dude, like the- that's such a bright red. Oh, that's such a beautiful bright red. You're
right on that painting. Just like the fire truck that's gonna be there next weekend. That's what
it is. Yeah, I corrected it. It's better. So it's not- I'm not like a- I don't like- I'm not gonna
like somebody tell me something in confidence, but that would be in confidence too. But anyways,
so this stream is gonna be on maybe Halloween, maybe a day before,
maybe a couple days. It depends. We have to lock in the dates here, but we're going to do a secret
slime action stream. What is this? What are you guys- what are you guys linking me?
Robotic Sideshow. Jay Albertson's Robotic Sideshow? What? No. Is this in the game?
Wait, what? No, it's not. Holy shit. Okay, that's awesome. Really? Oh, that's awesome.
It's a new community map in the- oh wow. That's so cool. I am- I'm like flo- I don't even know
what to say. That's so cool. I thought there was like somebody just made a- like a Photoshop or
something, but that's- that's awesome. There's a Vinesauce- Vinesauce stuff in there too. That's
awesome. I'm gonna have to check that out. He's gonna cry. That's so cute. Yeah, I'll show it on
screen. That's really cool. But anyways, yeah, that's- I got all kinds of emotions going on
right now. There's like four different emotions. I'm excited, I'm happy, I'm like humbled, I'm
surprised. This is- I got all of it. The whole cast of Inside Out is in here right now,
and they're all talking at the same time. Except for the- no, the anger. I got- the anger is on
lunch, and fear is on lunch. So only like four- like three of them. I don't even know- I've never even
seen- I don't- I don't- I don't even know- I don't know what that plot of that movie is. I've never
seen it. I just know that there's like emotions that all hang out in somebody's body. I don't- I've
never seen it. But, uh, besides that, which is awesome, we are going to be doing on Halloween
a secret slime action stream. What does that mean? Well, it's taken about three or four days to
scramble to get this done, but I have to do it. Over the next few weeks, the next two weeks or so,
not now, but this weekend, probably- probably Sunday or into Monday, there's going to be a
couple new channels in the Discord. In those channels, what you are going to do is you are
going to come up with- one channel will be for discussion. So you can talk about it. What- what
should we do? What should we try to see? What he'll do? Discussing actions that I am going to be doing
on stream without my knowledge. Just like that, those old Nickelodeon shows. So, for instance,
I'll give you an example. Scratching your nose. That's going to be one of the actions, possibly.
And if I do the actions that you guys come up with during the course of probably 10 rounds,
I get slimed. With real slime. Sitting at a computer. Now, that's all fun and dandy,
but what about you? See, you also are going to have actions that you cannot say or do. And if
you do them, then you're gone during the course of that stream. So I get to come up with a two.
So each round, there will be maybe one or two actions that we both cannot do. There will be a
bot. There will be- it's time for slime, thanks to five community subs right on time. So your goal-
well, the goal here is, let's say, uh, I'm going to try to explain this piece by piece because it
takes a lot of explanation for it to understand even what the hell this is. I am going to start
with a certain amount of points and we're going to do it by rounds and each round is going to have
a timer on it. So after 15 minutes or so, that'll be the end of round one. And however many people
did the thing in chat that was the secret chat slime action, those people are out of the game.
I'm not going to make this easy for you. It's going to be very, very, very hard for you not to talk
about stuff. Just don't chat. That's fine. But we're going to have a program that is going to be
created to track who is participating in the games. You're not going to hit permaband. Why would you
permaband? This is going to be a lot of fun. And that's just part one. Uh, I think my computer
crashed. No, it's fine. Uh, there are going to be three separate activities that happen on this
stream. That's part one. There's a part two and a part three that I don't really want to talk to you
about because that would kind of spoil it, essentially. Not yet. BF Bugleberry, please.
I mean, that's the most hated character in the whole entire universe, this whole channel.
I don't, I don't, I don't think that Bugleberry will make an appearance. I mean, why would they?
But, uh, there's going to be more, I just want to really bring it up briefly because I don't want
to overwhelm everybody yet. Uh, but there's going to be a Halloween stream, secret slime actions.
You're going to be directly competing against me to not do the thing that you and I have come up
with over a series of 10 rounds. If I get slimed, I lose points. Each person in chat is worth one
point. So if you get eliminated, that's minus one point for the whole, all of you are working
together on this. There's no such thing as minus one. Well, there is now. You're going to lose.
I don't know. It depends. It depends on what you guys can come up with for actions and they
could be anything, but make them good. We'll talk more about this at the end of the stream.
I don't want to overwhelm you. Breathing. And no, it can't be anything like that.
Stuff that is required to survive is not a secret slime action. It's breathing.
Like air going in and out of your nose is not a thing that can slime me. Drinking water.
I mean, okay. What if like, if going to the bathroom is one of them and I get slimed in the
bathroom, that's so stupid. But we'll, we'll come up with some stuff. I want to give it to you now.
So you can start to preliminary think about it in your brain.
And those of you that have never seen any of the old Nickelodeon shows where they used to do weird
shit like this, I'm going to try to not do the things that you are. Cause remember, I don't know.
I'm not going to know what you guys are suggesting. The people running the show have all that
information. So I don't know. Oh, Hey, by the way, don't, uh, don't sneeze this round. I don't know
what is potentially picked, but it just comes from a pool of things that you guys have suggested.
Also, I want to talk about this too. This is a talk about stuff stream.
A week or two after that, I'm going back in front of the green screen.
We're going to do green screen DLC for free. This is going to be the name of that stream.
We're going to do a whole nother thing where we take in more of your suggestions for actions
over the course of a couple of weeks. And I'm going back in front and we're going to give you
guys more material because it makes me laugh every time. So I don't want to throw this all
at you at once, but that stuff is happening. He's stalling the stream. He hates dark wood.
Happy Halloween from this company to spider. All right. For a second, I thought that was coffee
and I was about to gag. It's lemon water. I don't know why I thought it was an ice coffee.
So we're in dark wood. We're going to continue. We're going to play dark wood. I'm going to try
to finish dark wood. I might. I don't know. Is it going to be tough to get to the end of this?
We'll see. We're on day 19. We will find out if I can do it or not. This might be a situation
where I play for like six hours and go, we'll finish it later. Or I might just Simpsons hit and
run sit here until it's done. But we left off. I'm so fucking excited for this stream. I can't
wait for the slot, the secret slime Halloween stream. You even examine seven hours. I have to
sleep. Well, I'll try to get it done in seven hours. So I'll get done in five. And there are
people that are going to be coming into the stream. That's why I didn't want to throw it all out at
the beginning and just, it is an overwhelming amount of information that I think is better
if just like read in a discord because I'm going to write up a whole thing for you guys to like
read in the pinned channel there. There'll be two channels. One of them would be for discussions
on things that you want me to, but not that you want me to do things that you think I will do
that I don't know. And one for obviously a single sentence of what that thing is.
We'll talk about it again at the end of the stream. So the last thing I remember is we
organized the workbench. Don't, don't put them in here. I don't want to see them. Are you trying
to win this competition or you want me to be prepared for when it happens? And some of these
rounds, by the way, once we get to like round five, six, seven, eight, there might be multiple
actions that if you do, you know, if there might be three or four things on the screen that I can't
do, we're going to make it hard. And you too don't get banned blinking. No, that's, that's a human
survival reaction that doesn't count. All right. So the last thing I was going to do was that the
wolf, the wolf told me, Hey, you got to go up here now. Cause here's the hideout up here.
And there's a, there's a spot here that I'm going to go up and I'm going to just get to
the hideout, new hideout incoming. Look, look, look, look, look. You guys are on like, all right.
Cool. I guess anyways, uh, what do I have? I have, I need some new armor. I got to kill a bug.
I also have, I need to take some stuff with me because this is the journey
to go to the next hideout. I need a couple of things. Gas. I'm going to bring some wood and
I'm going to bring a bunch of nails. What else do I want to bring with me to survive this place?
To, to have an, okay. The bandages. I need alcohol. All right. This goal is just to get to the
hideout, the new hideout. I think everything else is fine. What about batteries? Yeah. I'll take a
couple of batteries, a couple of things of gas, get this bottle out of here. Scrap metal. Let me
take that too. All right. I'm ready to get out of here and try to get to the next hideout.
Jerma's current score is minus 46. That doesn't count. People did minus one, like a hundred,
a hundred times. How, how do I already have minus 40? No, I'm serious. How do I already have minus
46? I haven't done anything. I haven't said anything. I talked about like, what is this? Reddit?
Gave us a little low. All right. Let's go. I'm going. Uh, so, uh, the fastest route is to go
all the way up left and up. I have bandages. Let me put those bandages on. I got pills too.
And I got lock picks. I'm ready. Let's put the, no, the pills. No bandages. Okay. Go for it.
Time to go to a new hideout and do the, uh, this third little zone up here,
cause that's where I need to go. You forgot the bell. Wow. I almost just ruined this whole place
for you. I almost just just forgot those things hurt you already up to a great start. All right.
Come on. Give me the bell. Who the hell's the bell? Is this just in like a wardrobe somewhere?
There it is. All right. All right. All right. All right. Let's go out. Out. Let's go new hideout.
I got plenty of time. Do I still use a Velcro wallet? What the fuck are you talking about?
No, I wish I still had Velcro shoes. Velcro shoes are awesome because they allow you
Velcro shoes are just so easy to put on. All right. I got two people. Let's go.
He's getting better. Take the rag, leave the bottle. Let's go. Not wasting time.
Velcro underwear. I, that doesn't make any sense. The bike man's not going to get stuff out of the
wardrobe. It's too late. I fucking, if today was a secret slime stream, just do step in poison
mushrooms. I would, it would happen immediately. He gets everything in the hideout. Well, why are
you yelling at me? That's what somebody in chat just, that's what people in chat were telling me.
Well, I, why is everybody yelling at me? I left it in there. Okay. I need to heal with no, not yet.
It's not, I'm not, it's having that one. Okay. I'm probably going to need to heal. Found a cottage.
I haven't seen this yet. Why? Get out of here. Oh my fucking God. Really? No, not really. You're
still, he's just tracking me. Dude, get the fuck out of here. I don't want to, now I have to heal.
Whatever. I, I need to see what's in here. No, I'm on a very specific mission. I can do it later.
The hunter becomes the hunted. So I'll go up from here. Moose Monka S. I know it's
scary. Old car. Ooh, broken truck. Let's take another thing of gas, scrap. Hello. What is it?
Keep going. Just get it. I got to get to the hideout. I got to focus. The wolf told me to go up here
and I need to get up there before it gets too dark so I can get a sanctuary ready. Nothing else.
Don't pick up anything. Don't do anything. Just get up there. Watch out for the poison.
Straight line. The best way to go. I have to be getting close. Give me a landmark. All right,
here we go. I'm right here. Is this it? Is this the entrance? Am I going the right way?
Scrap. Nice. Still over here. Found the bridge. Here we go. Uh, I'm gonna take the wood.
So now I gotta get, that's kind of far away. Am I gonna even get here in time?
I might have to. He's just zigzagging. Oh, that's so bad. Red meat. Okay, hold on. I need to make a.
This shit is important. Besides the tire. All right, get me out of here. I got such a long way
to. Is another one of these? Oh, for the love of God. Well, this sucks. He's still alive. Why is
he still alive? Damn it. This is going to suck. You're telling me that's what's up here? That's
what I have to be aware of now. That's what I have to deal with every time. It's no longer the guys
with the. I have a long way to go to that hideout. Whatever it is, I'll get it later. Creepy house.
Don't go to the creepy house. Just go to where I need to be. Is this like slender? Yeah, it's
essentially it's top down slender. Oh shit. This stuff that I know. Just go just get out. I can
come back here later. I can't climb this here. Almost there. Almost like halfway there. All right,
it's time to activate the runner. Go. No, no unnatural. No unnatural walling. No natural
walling. Please. Oh, that's a guy. Broken tree. Get in there. Almost there. Come on. Don't die.
I need that axe too. Bad. I'm getting lots of meat though. Yeah, I am. All right, come on. Where is
this? Here we are. Come on. This is it, right? Lots of wood over here. Keep this in mind. Somebody
remember this. Let's make a good hideout. Oh yes, it would. Turn on the stove. Nobody's in here,
right? There might be somebody hanging out in here though. Turn on the stove. This is actually sick.
This place is huge. I'm just gonna hide in the bathroom. Left 4 Dead 2 style.
Oven. There we go. Light the oven. Awesome. 240 extract. 240, 240, 240. That's a shitload. Nice.
All right. Very, very good. Where's the workbench? Here. How do I get over there?
Go like down and then around? The fucker. Here's the workbench. Sickle. Oh, is this better than a
shovel? All right, what else is over here? It's not better than a shovel, huh? Okay. All right,
let me get, let me fill up the gas because I'm running out of time here. I gotta start to really
think about how I'm gonna do this. I tried to pick it up. I tried to pick it up. Okay, hold on.
I gotta deposit some of this shit. Now keep that. Get the bell for the batteries away.
I put two of the gasoline tanks away with the wire and the nail. All right. Now I can actually do
this shit. It's so dark in here. This is so much darker than the other ones. I wonder if I'm like
stepping on like the bird shit on the ground. Okay, I'm ready to fill up the generator, which is
over here. Where the fuck is the generator? There's the cooking table. It's over here.
Okay, gas tank. Spill it up. I got some time. I'll call the guy tomorrow to bring my stuff.
All right, tank is empty. 16. I got, let me see. So this can't be repaired. So they can come in this
way. They can come in this way. So generator room is off limits. I can repair. This is all right,
but no, not really. It's tiny. They can also come through here and they can come through here.
Not ideal. Here's one of the lights. This room not ideal either. Maybe down here. All right, so
all right. Okay, I like this area. I can board this. Okay, this is two doors here. I board this one
and then there's no, this window barricade, this window. Let's just do it now.
So that's window barricaded, which leaves me with this from here. There's the workbench. There's a
way to get in this way. No windows, no other ways to get in here. There's that. Okay, so what about,
what if I just hang out in this hall? Window here. Shit. Window here, barricaded. The window,
there's only two windows in this. Okay, wooden door. There's a lot of open space here. The safest
place in this whole house is probably right here. Like right here. Down, like in this bottom hallway.
There's a lot of places they can get in. Or in here, but you get stuck in here. I don't know,
I'm running out of time though, so I have to do this now. I could go like this and put traps
everywhere. Hold on. Let me make a few traps. Let me go to the workbench. Fuck. There's too many
rooms for me to think about what I want to do. I only have like eight minutes to figure this out.
When I built my house in Minecraft, it took me like four hours. What about up here? Barricade
this. Okay. Barricade this door too. I think this is all right right here for the first night. Oh,
check this out. Watch this. Door right here is all right. They, this is, I'm gonna barricade
this door. So check this. I can be up here. They can come in through this door. I have barricaded
window, barricaded door. There's an entry here. There's also an, oh, all right. This might be a
pretty good spot to be here. I need the, I need the light. I need the lights. I need the lights
right now. It's fucking dark. Give me a break. I can't see shit. I'm just turning the fucking
generator on. I don't even know where anything is in this house. There's only one light. There's
only one lamp here. Oh, that's not good. Um, just get all the windows. This is coming to the hall
just for tonight. And then tomorrow when I have infinite time, I can figure this out. This is
coming over here. Make sure I have like a weapon. This is gonna be hell. Okay. So they can't,
there's no way to get in through here unless they break that wall. I can bring the wardrobe over to,
wait, I need items. I need items right now. Where's the workbench? I don't remember where
the workbench is. It's like down here. Okay. Um, battery. I still have a magazine. I still have
the shovel. Store this stuff. There's heels. Okay. All right. All right. All right. I have some heels.
Speaking of heels, I got like a second. Okay. No, no, no, no. Get me in.
All right. I can't barricade this door. I'm gonna have to go for it. Two points of entry.
Is there anything I can grab here? Like a chair or something right off the bat?
I need to stop moving. Stop, stop, stop, just stop, stop, stop, stop. Close the door. Oh,
fuck. What is it? But what is it though? What kind of enemy is it?
Will he savage? I have a place to run. Keep that in mind. I have a place to run below me.
And I'm still in the house and I can wrap around. Holy shitty left.
A dog. A dog just saved my life. A dog just saved my life. No, he didn't. He just got one hit KO.
Point blank right in the head. What is it? Is he gonna break the door?
It's just a dog. I'm gonna open the door and hit him. Oh, fuck. Did I break the door?
Where is it? Oh shit. It's down there. It doesn't know he can go around. I'm gonna aim here.
Cause there's something in the house. Where is it? Oh shit. Okay. I gotta be ready.
What is it? Dog. I'm in trouble now. Where is it? Oh my God. It's right there.
Take it. Ta. Why? I'm gonna move. It's three big dogs. So what happened? One of the dogs
ate the other dog. What am I drinking? That is water with a little bit of lemon in it.
Just gives it just enough a little bit of a kick.
Oh my God. It's a 1-8. Please. Was that two? Was that you guys? Was that somebody in chat?
Did I just get stream sniped? They both came in instantly and attacked me instant. What?
Where the fuck were they for the last like hour and 40 minutes? Yeah, it's water. God damn it.
It was like 730. That sucks. Pain in the ass. All right. So now that I have a minute to look.
Let me turn the generator off first. That's important. Died to lemon water. If I had my
hands on... I have to like talk with my fucking hands. Why can't I just sit here? What's going
on in this room? That... No, I didn't die to lemon water. I died to animated speaking. Well, you see
just a little bit of a kick of that lemon juice. The lemon... Oh, and there's... Oh, hold on. I'm
playing a game over here. All right. Generator's off. I have infinite time. Now let's go over a
strategy. This is not a terrible strategy, but it's not a lot of room to move. So I think I want to
be in here. There's enough places to move. I could potentially barricade this room as well with the
oven. And then if only I can... There's a door here. I can barricade this and need to worry about
these two spots. Trap. Let's check this out. Trap. Trap. Trap. This is where I'm going. This is the
one. There's three mushrooms in here. I'm going to step on them. If I step on one trap for the
remainder of this stream, I will do a spin in a circle. All right. So go back to the cooking
utensil thing. Here we go. Level up. We have a new tier. Careful step. Once a day, you won't trigger
a trap that you step on. If I step on enough trap for the rest of the day, I'll be able to restore
my health by eating wood. Once a day, I'll be able to scare off nearby enemies. Yes. I don't care
what the other ones do. I'll recover longer after exhausting myself. When my stamina gets low,
I will deal less damage in combat. These are both so awful. Just eat your way out of the forest.
Eat wood. Eat wood. Eat your desk. Bite your desk. That is good. But I feel like this is a...
If I had this, I probably would have survived the night last night. Yeah. And this one too. I
don't want it. This one seems horrible. When my stamina gets low, I'll deal less damage in combat.
They're both horrible. They're both just game ruiners. Which one is worse? I don't know.
Weaklings only happens when you put your stamina at zero. Yeah. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. It's done. Eat wood, Omega Lull. Oh, I get what you're doing. Okay. Now
let's go over here. The smell of grass and trees. The earth bends under my footsteps. The sky swirls
pleasantly. I think it's here. Bugs haven't even had two headphones in this whole time.
That's why I've been so bad. Oh, I wasn't expecting this. A completely ordinary dead
man with a smile on his face. Is that a... Is that a... Is that a monkey? I think. I don't know. I'm
not sure what to say in the chat. Can you hear it? This is actually kind of scary. Can you hear it?
Yes, it's you. It's me. Can you hear their song? Get out of here. Get out of here, you
fucking man-o-wraith. You pre-spell. They deleted you from the game because you sucked.
Now what's that? What's that? Oh, it's a live stream from German 985.
Gotta have one wow reference per stream. The game sucks. All right. What we got? What? Why
did that happen? Oh, I have one of these. 4,000. I'm already 20% of the way there. Not even. I'm 20...
I'm 22% of the way there. I'm 20% of the way there. Let's see. Where do I want to go?
German is sweating. Why am I sweating? It's been like 50 minutes. It's your overreactive glands.
It's been like 10 minutes. It's been an hour. That's how you know that this stream is
popping. I got like my YouTuber glands. All right. I'm so glad I have frozen time.
So I need to make traps. I need scrap metal. I got a little bit. I can make like two, three.
What the fuck do I want to do now? Turn off the webcam. Why would it turn? All right. One guy.
I'm back. So traps. Let's build them. Let's build them. Let's build them. Let's build them. Let's
build them. Need to be the workbench. I want bear traps because they're the best.
He's already... He's already forgotten where the workbench is because this whole game is gray
with some orange in it. And he's sometimes... His brain cannot decipher between orange and gray
because he didn't pay attention in school. Bear trap. Make three of them. These are going to help
me out immensely very soon. Speak up a little. Okay. Fine. Well, there goes the scrap. I needed
to make sure I could have a weapon, but it's okay. I'll find some. Now these are going to go over
here. Let's... I think this is the best spot for me. Might not be the best spot for you
because I can barricade this door. I can hang out in here. I can have a piece of furniture. Once
this guy gets out of the way, let's get this one down here first. Actually, I actually more
comfortable having this down here. So if I do this... Can the dogs jump over the table? I don't
think the dogs can jump over it. Maybe they can. That's a good question. Anyways, here we go.
I'm thinking of a scenario where we take these three. Let me go like this. Put something here
and then right here. Bang. They'll get caught in it if they turn. There's one. And then that'll
give me time. I'm gonna put a piece of furniture here and then one here. I'm gonna... Where am I
gonna stand though is the real question. Stand... I'll be standing here because against my back
against this wall, nobody can get in this way. This corner is pretty good. So if I stand up here,
that means that this would have to go here because they would be... Essentially, they break through
and they'd be running up this way. So right there. God, I hope this is right. Okay. The third one
is gonna go down here. Right here. Because they'll break open the door and they'll come up this way.
I am now ready. Oh, fuck. It's ready. The room is good. There's my entrance.
There's my other entrance. I hope I can get back in there. I... When I come back, when I come back
and I... When you see my character Avatar walk through these doors, please, for the love of God,
I want everybody collectively to type in all capitals. Bear traps. It's the only thing I
want to see over here because I'm gonna forget this exists in like 30 minutes when I come back
after scavenging out here. And I'll walk in one and it'll... I'll go like this. Oh, what the fuck?
And everyone will be like... I was ready. And then I'll be irritated. All right. I'll take a
mushroom. I have an axe head. What do I need to build the axe? That's very important to me.
I'm gonna scrap. How many nails do I have? I'm gonna buy them all. I have plenty of money.
This guy... This guy loves me. So like he's just gonna give all this shit to me.
Another magazine for the gun. Gas tank. All right. We'll take this one up. He nods. Okay.
I need Joe. All right. Fuck. I thought I stepped in the trap. I have to cook this. Jesus Christ.
What the fuck am I doing? I don't want to come back in this room till I have to.
They need to be placed though. They have to be there. All right. I'm ready. That's the
survive room. I'm gonna bring the light over there too before anybody starts to panic.
Get the rags and a battery. I got plenty of lock picks. I took the magazine. All right. Let's do
this thing. Disarm them now and then arm them at night. That's a very decent chance. That's
a very decent debate there. But if you dismantle them, you get two scrap and they take three to
make. Why would somebody have that as an emote? I just thought something was wrong with my channel.
All right. I want to make sure I don't forget anything that was in these boxes. I know there
was some shit around here. That room is good to go. Here we go. Wardrobe, pills, rags.
Forget anything. I'm gonna grab the lamp just to get it over there so I don't panic later.
Ah. Ring the bell. That's also a good idea. I will do that too. I think I can just run it in there
now or at least close enough. How am I gonna get this in the room with the bear traps? I'm gonna
carefully do that now because if when it's like 17 o'clock that is not gonna happen. I will panic
and I will activate like three of the traps. There are only three traps in there so you know what I
mean. Can you help? This one is just gonna it's not gonna catch this in the trap, right?
Easy. We're good. I can stick right there. I like this setup. That's going down and then I'll put
something else up here. Any of the big furniture around here? There's got to be like a big piece
of furniture I can drag, right? Workbench. There's a wardrobe. Welder. Gentleman magazine? Bear trap.
I know the bear traps are in there. I know the bear traps are in that room. I'm talking about
for like like 35 minutes from now when I leave and come back. It's fun to decorate your house.
So this one's gonna go up because that one's gonna block that doorway. Leave. Is that gonna
be enough to block? I don't think so. No it's it's enough it's enough to be annoying though
so I can know when someone's coming in. No it's all right. That's not terrible. That's enough to
be annoying. Stop being mean to the trader. Kidding. All right I'm I'm happy with that.
I wish I could repair my shovel because that's did I get I got more nails but did I get enough
to let's see. Oh I do okay I do I do I do just no I don't. Fuck. I okay I need to use the bell.
Something's happening. I'll give you an alcohol. Do I have alcohol in my inventory? Where is he?
Front door? Back door? Oh this is big. I can pick that up. I'll move that later. Where's this guy?
I know but where are you? Kill trader. Where's the guy on the bike? I just heard his bell like twice.
Oh you're all the way out here. Uh here's some alcohol. A good vintage. Your bottle a day keeps
the monsters away to your health. I can bring you junk from the other hideout. Which hideout
should I take the junk from boss? From the silent forest. Oh on it like a fox in a trash can.
See you later. First course of action is where what did the let me look at my journal. I remember
the face face of the man who saved me. Where's um wolf? Northwestern part of the dry meadow.
It's up here. Okay so that's not that far. Let's get out of the place.
I'm gonna go do that. I do need a couple pieces of wood though to repair my shovel. I don't feel
comfortable going up there. Did I look at everything? Make sure I did. No. Note. Who the hell are they
assigning to us? Macy's fucked off from the shack. The whole night he was rambling about some merrick.
I think his younger brother or son. I don't know if it was the boredom of the stress that got to
him but he was fucking unbearable. It was the third night in a row. We tried to silence him but
it's fucking Masiak. Better not risk it. I slipped inside my sleeping bag and zipped it shut. I
prefer to suffocate in my own stench than listen to that fuckhead go on and on about it. After a
while I realized Masiak is not there anymore. He left around morning. He took all his equipment,
three liters of water, a sleeping bag, radio, gun, gasoline, flamethrower and his lucky stone. He only
left the hazard suit. We're debating on whether to report this. No one's crazy about running around
the woods looking for psycho with a flamethrower. Well we'll know who that is if we come across them.
Checking one few more little things. Any objects that I missed. I can get wood right here. Thanks
to the person in chat that told me there was wood out here. The saw needs gas. Prepare the shovel.
This is the wrong place. Chicken lady's despair. The wolf didn't want to talk to me anymore. He
grunted that he had something urgent to take care of and rushed off. If this is wall brain,
thinks that he will get rid of me so easily, then he's mistaken. He mentioned he'll be staying in
the northeastern part of the old woods. So over here. I was going up here. So he's up there.
That's not bad. Good to know. Let's get some logs. And now let me repair my shit.
Good. I should be able to repair the shovel. And then we move. We move. That's just north.
No north. I flipped it around. Wait, hold on. I um northeast. I used to I used to live in the
northeast. Don't queue. I should know what that is because I have these headphones in.
If I had both these headphones out, I could feel my brain power coming back.
It's like breathing again. When they're in, I can fucking breathe again when they're out.
Somebody just say because I'm a vegan. What the fuck are you talking about?
What does that even mean? All right. Nothing else from you that I want. Let's do it.
Workbench. Prepare the shovel. Make sure I have healing items. Good. Upgrade item. Maybe I can.
No, I can't. Take the proper healing. And we're going northeast. Bandage. Looking good. These
flares. I'm gonna sell them. Make make two bandages. Why not two? Make, you know, make another one of
these. And then another one of these. Put the welder away. I might need it for something.
We don't need the wood. We do not need this scrap metal. We do not need the weapon parts.
We do not need the we need the battery. We need one battery. I think that's sufficient. We need
the two clips. We don't need the rags anymore. Actually I do. Maybe you can. No, I don't. I got
plenty healing. Flashlight. Two. Nails. Go away. Don't need these pills. Welder. Go away. Bottle.
Alcohol. Here we go. Get rid of that bandage. I got three. Get rid of the flares. Three healing.
One battery. Two clips. Any food? No. Let's go. I'm ready. Lockpicking. You're right. Take the five
stack. And that's it. Good to go. So we're going up here northeast. Nice bangs. I'm gonna get angry.
I mean it right here. Just let's go. You guys want some Pringles? Pringles are awesome.
Actually I take that back. Original Pringles are awful. But cheese Pringles are like B tier.
I fucking can not do it. Of course this is like a poison area. Why do you even live up here for?
Road. Wait. Road. That's not where I want to go. A natural walling here. It's gonna go all the way
up. Gotta go down. Take me home. I have to go back through this shit. Slow it down. Barn ruins. Is he up
here? Dogs. Oh there's a lot of dogs. There's a lot of dogs here. A lot of them.
Is this a dog? No. Could open it with a lockpick. What the hell is going on up here? Go down here.
Hey. Shit what's with all the dogs? And what's even up here?
I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. Why are you not on a hotbar?
I don't want to shoot this gun. Everybody will know where I am. This fucking reach sucks.
Oh shit a dog is in front of me. It's two down. I thought this was going to be just a breeze to
get back up here. Okay. I think this is already to go back up there though. Let's see. First of all,
get this on the hotbar. What are you dumb? Are you fucking kidding me?
Is there nothing over here? No, there's this. Nothing. There's nothing in here.
Where the fuck am I going? Is this a person? I found him. The greeting sounds like an angry
girl. The wolf makes a quick leap and bouncing against me with his swollen belly, he puts his
paws on my shoulders. He ostentatiously licks his face. What a gift you've given me. I notice
fresh blood stains on his fur and feel streaks of his saliva dripping onto my coat. He leans
towards me as if he wanted to say something to my ear. What? The wolf squeezes my arms and starts
licking my face, once from the left side, once from the right. Comrade, meet, his breath stinks
of rot. What would I ever do without you? You're not such a worthless piece of carcass as you look.
Next to you I feel fulfilled. I've got my girl, my sweet lady. Hard to believe the same blood
flows through the veins of- I just got a rifle. This bitch reeks of chicken. What? Suddenly the
wolf sends me back with a powerful push and reaches into his coat pocket, some object hits the floor.
Here, no need to thank me. Now, since that part of the deal is behind us, I'll help you recover
your stupid key. I will take you back to the doctor's house. I'm sure you'll find some clues
on how to reach his current hideout while there. You two will have a little chat. You will get back
what you've lost and then nothing will keep you from getting the fuck out of my part of the woods.
Do you get me, meet? You will pack your bags, dive into that stinking hole of yours and
dis a fucking pier. I appreciate the dis a fucking pier. Return to the doctor's house. And are we good?
So he gave me a rifle. Are we good? I mean, I don't think so. I think I want more.
You don't got like a coupon back there for me somehow? I wonder, is the rifle any good?
Oh, are we good? Did I get it? Are we going? Huh? I can't seem to see. I need my glasses, I think.
Let's go. Wait, do I have the rifle? I had the earphones in. I'm telling you,
I don't know. There's something wrong with me. Let's go. I'm so glad I stuck that out.
I saw at least two or three people in the chat that said, get out, get out, stupid, get out, just
bad. And then they fucking almost passed out. Stupid and bad. Wait, where am I? All right. Look,
I'll agree with you. I am pretty stupid and I am pretty bad. Don't remind me. That's rude.
All right. Where am I? Where are we? Time is frozen.
I don't know why I know exactly what you're talking about. I think it's time for a change.
No more, no more faces. I'm just going to be emotionless.
I just want to see it. Where's the rifle? Hunting rifle. What kind of bolts does that take?
Medium, medium caliber. Pretty sick. Oh, geez. Bear trap, bear trap. There it was. We told you,
we told you, we told you, we told you about it. What's the single best episode of television
you've ever seen in your whole life? Good choices there. I see a couple of good choices.
Plain countryside bed. The metal buckles of the leather straps fastened to the bottom of the bed
are twisted and broken. SpongeBob pizza episode. I can't do anything with this person. Move you
out of the way. I can't move him out of the way. Go in another part of the house then.
Can't go this way. All the way around. Um, is there a door here? I can't grab this. It's dark
in here. Give me a break. It's dark. The game is dark. By its very design, the game is designed
for you not to be able to see what you're doing. The doctor? Where is the doctor? Daddy went out
and left. Angry and hungry he was. I'm hungry too. Don't get up. Can't move. Head is exploding.
And if I move, I'll burst myself. Here. No, that's not meat. Here, have some of this. Go get it.
It's delicious. Didn't want it. I tried. Partially decomposed corpse. The left hand has been
bitten off together with the arm. That's disgusting. Oh, generator. The way to keep this
stuff in time is frozen. It usually means odd stone. All right, I'll take it. Strange. Why is
this bed different when I come over? There's a way down a couple of ways down. Safe. Oh shit.
Somebody's coming in here. Maybe not. Cage. Huge empty cages. Huge empty cages.
I saved the lock to the code. I don't know the code. 8-9-8-9-9-3. Was that a code?
No, those are shoes. Destroyed. Well, destroyed at 125p. What's the code for this? Do I have a code?
Didn't go this way. Easy. I know him. Wait, this is the, this is the prologue. This is the guy.
Oh shit. Did I already open this? Um, you guys told me there was only one person that ate people
in this game. Ice? Rotten mushroom. What do I do? How do I take this stuff? Okay. Battery. No. I have
to get back. This is worth a lot of money. This doesn't do anything. Thanks for wait, thanks for
not letting me waste time. I mean, I still want the ice though. Cooking ice. You can't cook it.
Cook the ice. I'll take one stack. I've never seen it before. I don't know what it does.
All right, that's fine. Outside. Uh, can I jump this? I cannot. Nothing else over here.
This is fucked up. This game is fucked up. I need a code. That's not shoe. Those are not shoes.
That's one five one five nine four one five four nine. I had the right idea with the shoes.
Just wrong place. One nine. What was it? Nine one nine one nine five four one nine. So that's not
a one. This is just a five five four nine. That's not 15. Okay. That's just the piece here. Five four
nine. One nine. What's the other number? One five four nine. Photo. It's over. It's somewhere else,
Mr. Stupid. Zero viewers. Everybody left. They couldn't handle me looking at this. Like they
couldn't take me trying to find the safe code and they all took off. All of them. Uh, this is a photo.
Eight five five four nine eight. Let's try that. Five four eight nine five eight four five nine.
There it is. Map code toy. Doctor's note with a code. The code to the cart door. 8909. 8909. Remember
that. Note with a code. Okay. The map shows the location of some train. Train wreck. And then a
toy. Okay. I got my heel ready. I gotta get the fuck out of here. Free wood. Trees blocked the way
ahead. So what the hell? Map? I can't use a map. Map. Map. I can't do that. Use a map. What? I can't
do that. I could probably just leave. Do I have to leave just all the way out? I think I did
everything I can. Wait. What about down here? I don't think I looked down here yet. There's
not much to see anyway. So. All right. I'm just gonna leave. Yep. Time to go. He's too strong
to dismantle. Come on. We are out of here. My, my house also burst in half. Everything here just
bursts. This person's freaking me out. I think they're gonna get up and chase me and shit.
I shouldn't. It's gonna be a scenario where I should have just killed him.
Hey, you here? Are you good? Kill me. Take my house. My cracked hut.
Where do you live? Where do you live? Where do you live? Oh no. Where do you live?
Okay. Rusty key. Like where? I don't know where you live. Oh, these mushrooms rotted because
they took too long in here. Fuck. Are they worth anything? I got an axe. How does it swing?
Pretty nicely. Oh, pretty nice actually. I don't even need to build the damn thing.
I have an axe head. I can just sell it back. Oh, I can upgrade the axe. Holy shit. Now this is
getting interesting. This thing's going to be insane. Hell yeah. All right. So I got, let me
look at this. I've explored the doctor's house. It's a complete ruin. Now I know that what seemed
like nightly terrors is very real. Still don't know how I escaped this place. I suspect someone
must have carried me out. I found some code in the doctor's house. I don't know what it's
for, but I hope it opens the door to his current hideout. So I have the doctor's hideout. Go back
to the tub. Check tub. Under the tub. Check under the tub. Rub-a-dub-dub. What's under the tub?
You're supposed to be helping me. This is what I think of your little tub joke.
I didn't break the tub. I broke the door and almost destroyed the shovel.
Mean chat. Well, sorry. Look, sometimes I look over here and it's like,
holy shit. Read chat. You stupid idiot. You're so stupid. How could you not do this? And then
that's a lie. But other times I can't see the word going on the screen. So it's hard
to determine. Like, he's blind. He's an idiot. Oh, the word was going not good if you just read it.
But then you guys can, because I know I do that, you guys can get me so easily with shit like that.
Let's put it this way. You guys are a coin flip if you're legit or not. Why is it? Why did the
time change? All right. Where the hell am I? Where am I? Where did I just end up? Okay, right here.
Back to the house. I'm not. No, no, no. Gun. I don't care. Give me the gun.
It didn't hit. Pretty good dodge, I'll tell you. But I don't have time. Rotten mushroom's not worth
anything, right? Yes, I know. It was a good dodge. Stupid, bald, manlit idiot. Why are you guys so
mean? All right. Imagine, okay. Imagine if every time somebody said something in this chat that was
even remotely anything. You could say anything. Imagine if I referred to some of you guys as,
oh, hey. Hey, what's up, you bald, manlit idiot? How you guys doing today? You're all bald,
manlit morons. How you guys doing? Don't you think? Don't you think you'd kind of be like,
hey, hey, what? That was a little rude. All right, I'm gonna fuck this up. Just go down.
I'm out of gas. Just keep the gun out. He's yelling it. No, I'm not. Sometimes I think it's funny.
This is why I've kept the gun out. Let me try the axe. Imagine you went to work and your boss
greets you at the door. At the door. Okay, I don't want to die. Guys, I'm gonna die.
I'm dead. There's fucking three dogs here. Again, two of you came out of nowhere. Two people from
chat. Why are these open? Why are these, why are these open? Why are these undone? What the fuck
happened? I'm sorry. Yeah, two dogs just literally just spawned out of nowhere and a third one came
and killed me. Why are these open? This is, this is horrible. Actually, this is terrible.
This is awful. Why are these open? Why are these? I don't understand why these have been
done. Did somebody come in here? What I was going to say is imagine you like went into work and you
boss the first thing in the morning. I'm gonna pause it for this. You walk in. Oh, hey. Oh, hey,
hey, boss. Hey, you bald manlit idiot. That motherfucker is getting sued for like harassment.
Can you imagine that like instant lawsuit? It'd be fucking immediate. Did I lose my rifle?
Oh, I'm gonna do everything possible to get that back. No, I still have it. Okay, I'm gonna get my
stuff though. Why were those traps open? That's a bug. All right, get rid of this shit. I don't
even, I can't even use this stuff anymore. Store the hunting rifle for now. I need battery.
Don't scrap metal. That sucks. Why is it? Why did they do that? That's actually aggravating.
I died, so it activated two of my traps. All right. Oh, fuck off. I don't, I am not ready to take
off his stuff right now. I don't have time for this. I have to go get my stuff. Did he come in
here and step on the traps? I don't have time for this shit. Every single individual item needs to
be ration stamps. What the fuck is this? Give me a break. I have no idea what to do here.
Take these. Put them here. I'm gonna take the gas out. Put the shovel back. Nails. I mean,
just combine them. Why are they not auto-combined? What the hell? Anything else? Get rid of these
bottles. I don't even know what this rear view mirror is for. I'm afraid to delete any of these
items. I feel like I'm gonna need them. Where are those? Take one of these. Take these bottles out.
Make a few more healing things. What? What? Use the auto-combine key.
Phone on me. I'm gonna throw this off a cliff. I'm literally throwing this off a cliff, the next
cliff I come to. This thing is going, I'm going to throw this as fucking hard as I can over the
horizon. Okay, torch. I'm just gonna bring it. I can't combine that. This rotten meat is useless.
I'm gonna cook this stuff right now. I can't believe that those traps aren't there. There's
still one. All right, let's go. Oh shit, okay. I can make like gas bombs? That's pretty ridiculous.
Metal pipe. I'll take the bottles with me. Whipping this off the cliff as hard as I can.
And let's do another lockpick. Here we go. Let's do
bear trap. Upgrade item. Let me look at this. I need eight scrap for a greatly increased weapon
durability. That scared the shit out of me. Holy fuck. Why is that so much louder than the game?
All right, I gotta get out of here. Store this for now. I need to go get my stuff
before it gets too late. All right, I have, where's my axe?
Fucking god, that's fine. All right, get me the fuck out of here. I gotta get my stuff.
It's right next to the house. I can't believe I died there.
Oh, hold on. Fucking full moon. This has been a full moon chat the last three days.
Have you guys been drinking shit under the sink? What are you doing?
All right, don't, I can't fuck this. I need my stuff. I, I know, I'm gonna get to those bits,
but I, it's 15 o'clock right now and I can't fuck this up. I don't remember where the hell that was.
Oh, you piece of shit. You are so, what? Fucking hell. Oh, where's my bag?
Crate? Oh, there's, no. Oh, I just found my stuff. Did anybody remember where it was?
It was like over here somewhere, right? What? I don't have time for you. Somebody can't,
I don't have time for you. It's under the tub. Where's that? There it is. I got no more bullets.
This is a horrendous scenario. Leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave, leave. I made it.
Woo. Oh, fuck. You guys are fucking with me. You guys are like, fuck with my head.
All right. You broke them. You got, all right. They were, 5,000 bits came in from phylactery
lidge. Thank you. First of all, that moment's going to be forever remembered because you have
a face cam. It's all right. It don't matter. Uh, Hey, Jeremiah, I'm glad you're streaming
cause I had a pretty bad day at work today. I got to work and said, Hey boss. And he called me a bald
idiot. It really hurt my feelings. Do you think I have a case for harassment? Yes. Yes. Absolutely.
100%. Oh, you guys are fucking too much. Thank you for the 5,000 bits. Oh wait, I forgot. I have
to do this before it becomes too dark out. I have it in my inventory, right? Yeah. Get it out of here.
Watch this. I'm just going to whip this shit into the woods here. Oh, what's that?
Something's going to chase me. It's a body of precious bone. Okay. 17 o'clock.
Oh, this is such a mess. This is a mess in here. I'm just going to make these until I can't make
them anymore. I have like toxic fumes now. Okay. I'm going to make these bear trap. I can only make
one bear trap. This sucks. What a disaster. What a disaster. I have healing here. Don't need the
lock picks right now. I have to, I'll do this tomorrow. I need to repair. Do I have Canada?
I can't repair this. I need to scrap. Not good. That's all right. I don't have any bullets either.
Yes, I do. I have one. I'm going to piss my pants. Okay. Where's my wood? Make sure everything's
boarded up. Get these bottles out of here. I have reorganized this shit tomorrow. I just don't,
I don't know what to do with it all. I'm going to fill the generator. I've got my axe and I
have a full clip and now that has to blast me. That has to blast me till tomorrow. That's just
all there is to it. Let's go. Can I cook anything else? No. Chad is a vicious mob. I'm telling you,
people don't think the full moon shit is real. It's not. You sure? What time is it where you are?
Look out the window. There's a full, if there's a full moon and okay, if you look out the window
and there's a full moon and the last sentence you wrote in chat was like peepee, poopoo, bald,
mad streamer. I'm just saying it might have something to do with it. I need to move. Watch
out. Watch out. Watch out. I need to board. I don't have time for this. Oh, I'm so screwed here.
That's at least closed. I'm not in the room though. I'm not in the room. I have to get in the
room. Get in the room. 19. Ow, my hand. Good. This is blocked. There's a trap there already.
Close this door. Board it. Okay. This trap is going right here. Right like in front of me.
Because if somebody comes in this way, they'll get hit by it. Somebody comes in this way.
I don't know. It's this way. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know
where to put this. Should I put it right here? Not yet. I have the scream still. He looks strange
today. Come on into work. How are you? Good to see you again. Good to see you again, Dick.
You look strange today. Okay. Bald idiot. I'm going to go to my desk. Yeah. Idiot. Bald head.
I can hear him still screaming. And he's just sitting there. He's sitting there with like
under the sink cleaner in his hand. Bald. Whoa. This is fucked up. And then he goes,
oh, there's a fucking full moon behind him. Okay. I don't want to die. I don't want to die.
It's been one hour. Can't do it. You can't do it. Uh oh. I got a good dent. What's that sound?
Oh no. Don't put, don't put the gas in here. Don't put it right under me. Don't put it right
under me. If you put it right under me, I'm going to lose. Dog is just like smashing his head.
Eventually, maybe you'll get it. Um, what happens if the ghosts come and turn the light off?
What's that? Why is there a nuke in the house? Why is there a nuke in the house?
I don't know what that is. What does that mean? Why is there a nuke in the house?
Where is it and what is it? Something's trying to move this container and it has not successful
yet. Hello? What is in the house? What is in the house? I need to heal. I need to heal.
This motherfucker moves around the house. Get out of that room. Get out of that room. It's trapped.
Oh fuck. No, no. Move the, move the pre-hero. Please. It's 5 30. It's almost time. It's almost,
hey, hey, come on. It's almost time for work, Gerber. What was that? My house just shook.
I was trying to go around this way. No.
No. I got halfway through that and I realized, stop. That's what happened to my brain.
In my mind, it was, I got halfway through and it, I, my brain went, stop. Don't do that. Stop it.
I want to see that clip. I want to see how fucking embarrassing that was.
I need to know. This is why I don't do face cam. It's like turd alert is coming up here.
That wasn't even it. That's not, it's a baby. That's not, that's not, that's a baby. This is not it.
Leave. Leave. Leave. What the fuck are you looking this for? It sounds like a baby.
That's, god damn it. I hate it. I hate it. I hate this. I hate this.
Oh, I hate this. This image over here. Oh, I hate this. I'm fucking, I'm never streaming again.
This is the last stream ever. I'm going to go hide for the rest of my life. Got fired. All right.
Let's keep going. Turn off the generator. I made it. I made it. I, I tried, I, but give me a little
bit slack. I didn't, I don't know what that thing was. This red sun glowing nuclear bomb
just appeared in my room. I'm going to panic a little. I don't know what that is.
Imagine ending your career by a wooing. Imagine that really is the last thing I ever do.
No, we got a Halloween stream to do it. That's not going to happen. All right.
Ahem. Train wreck. I had a note to go to the train wreck. Anything cool planned for Halloween
this year? Yeah. This is going to be an incredibly elaborate stream. Me versus you. Secret slime
actions. You're going to try to slime me by, I'll go over it again at the end of the stream. It's
going to be a, it's going to be a whole thing. Oh, that's right. Like a bunch of people are here.
Long story short, there's going to be a channel in the discord that's going to be opened up
for you to give suggestions on secret slime actions from me that I do not know about.
There's going to be a discussion channel and there's going to be a suggestion channel.
Discussion channels for discussion. Suggestions for one sentence on what you think it should be.
Bingo. No discussion in that channel. By the way, at the 30th, the October 31st,
that's when it's probably going to happen. You're the 30th, 31st. One of those days,
I'll give you a good hard concrete one. But me versus you, you also have slime actions as well
because we're going to come up with some stuff that you're not allowed to write in the chat.
And it's a competition because if you write something that you're not supposed to write
you don't know about, then you are banned from that game and you lose points as a collective chat.
Boom. A wooing is going to be on there. That's fine. You'll know. I'll never do that again.
This is the first and last time you will ever see me or hear me do that. Do not suggest
the awoo as a thing to do on that stream because it will never happen again. I promise.
I 100% guarantee you that I will never turn and do the cookie crisp howl because that's what it's
in my head. Every time I've gone, the thing, I'm just thinking of cookie crisp every time.
I've done it like probably 10 times in my life. You still have to spin. I did. You didn't see me
go around a circle? Do it again. No. Okay. Okay. Okay. I got all the time in the world now.
I need to get this set up. So first things first, there are nuclear bombs now. Good to know.
Second things first, go to the trader. Third thing is second, sell the items that I want to get rid
of. Always pick up the items that I know I need that I want. And that includes rags, wood, battery,
magazine, mushroom, medium caliber bullet. Right? That's for the rifle. Right? He shakes his head.
Why not? Oh, because he wants something in return. These things are worth a lot of money.
I don't know. Should I give you an odd stone? These do anything? Don't ignore Jerma Wu.
Well, I'm going to ignore it because I just didn't ignore. All right. So don't give the stone.
Guys. Here, you can have a few eggs. No, that's too many eggs. You can have like one here.
You know, it's okay. So let's do a little bit of a thing here. Let me go. I'm time for a true,
get rid of the shit that you don't need. This is a closet cleaning stream.
Closet cleaning stream starts now. Cook. Don't touch that. I can't. I mean, I can't believe
because I was under a lot of stress. Gasoline. Fruit on the ground. Where is it? Gasoline.
Gasoline. Backseat the fuck out of me right now. What is this for?
You can eat it for health. Is it? What is this? Let's get some twos. Hey, look at that. That's
pretty good. We might be able to get a yahtzee. Get some. You know what you're like going to go
back in time and stop your past self from doing something. I'm going to go back and just be like,
don't do that. Do not howl ever again. All right. So jars of meat. You did it three times.
Yeah. Okay. So I'm me now is going to go back in time to tell me from like three months ago to
don't howl. Don't do it. This is why I use the time machine. I've done it three times today.
What? I have a shiny stone. All right. Let me, let me first of all, military flashlight is going to
replace regular flashlight. I think maybe I need to get these scissors for whatever they are.
Toy. Oh, okay. Flip. This is where we really just dump everything. I'm like, I'm like 20 minutes
till I'm like 15 to 20 minutes to complete in the game. So toy cell. Okay. Welder.
Sell. Wedding ring. Sell it. Torch. Sell it. Chicken head. Sell it.
Welder. Sell it. Okay. Dermot, there are two chapters. You're in chapter one.
Acid just got in my eyes. Welder. Welder. Wedding ring. $50. You should play Hitman some more.
Says Phylacter Lich with 5,000 bits. Play Hitman some more. I actually did see this
gift today of the flying helicopter briefcase on the guy with the, I have seen this. It's a
fucking lot of money. That's a hundred dollars now from Phylactery. Holy shit. You're still giving
money. Dev's never intended a player to take this many days. Well, that's funny because
I just was curious and looked up how many days typical did people have when they did their first
blind playthrough. And typically speaking, it's like 30 to 40 days is what I've seen.
So you just, I just had a legit research project that could back that up. Um, it used to make
about 30 plus days for your first playthroughs, but I've been told I don't appreciate that.
By the way, I howl at people that do stuff like that. You don't want the toy, but Phylactery,
thank you so much. Hitman is done though. Unfortunately. Oh, I think I got everything
I wanted out of it. It's a fantastic fucking game. I love every second of that game,
but I'm not going to be playing Hitman 2 anymore. I've done it all. I'm gonna, okay.
So that should be good. Give me your scrap metal. I want to upgrade this axe blade, but can I do
another upgrade here? Impossible. I gotta go back in my inventory. Play Blood Money. Well, I mean,
I could play some of the old ones, but not at the moment. Not right now. All right, back down here.
The axe. The axe needs axe head and four more scrap to do the big upgrade,
which I think I'll probably be taking that to the end of the game if I were curious.
Shovel. I think it's time for the shovel to leave. I think the shovel, its time is up. It was really
good. It helped. Goodbye shovel. Thank you for everything. Thank you for everything. Um,
making another one of these. Homemade shotgun. Do I have the shotgun? I do. Useless after fire.
I need to use this on something. I don't know what the hell to use it on. All right, so we got,
take the wood out, put the nails back, take the lock picks out, put these shiny stones in. The
bottles do not have a purpose for me anymore. What's the difference between the heel pills
and just the regular pills? What do these do? Do these do anything? This is for stamina.
Okay, well I'm just gonna, I'm gonna burn through them. Toy, I can't do anything with it yet.
Battery, I can't do anything with it. Is, I feel like battery, I already did what I needed with the
battery. Do I need to keep it? I'm gonna sell the flares. Bottle of gas, which stacks at three.
Unfortunately, yes. Rear view mirror, like these things, they're not, they don't have a purpose
anymore. And these are heels. So I'll take a couple of these, one of these with me. Okay,
stacks of two, bring the clip with me, put the rope back here. I have, where's my hunting rifle?
The new one, where is it? Where is it? Where's the rifle? Where's the rifle? Where's the rifle? There it
is. Looks like a toothbrush. All right, I'm gonna keep the bullet with the rifle. I'm not gonna use
it yet. I feel like I'm gonna need that end game. Weapons supposed to go up top. Batteries I need
to take for the flashlight. I'll eat the eggs on this trip. I have heels. Bottle, get rid of.
All right, somebody stop me. Somebody stop me right now. What is selling is getting rid of the
mirror. He doesn't want any of it. Okay. I have my axe, 50%. I have a clip. All right, let's go
back down one more time. Let me turn these into wooden planks. Do I have any gas? I might buy
another gas because I'm probably, I'm gonna fill it up. Let's fill it up, the whole thing.
I've got three batteries. Good. Back and I forgot to pee. I had to go really bad. It's okay. I can
wait. All right, let me bring the gas. Go to the bathroom now. I will before I go up for the next
adventure. I'm so sorry I just smashed you in the head. This is, I'm gonna do a full tank in here
and a full tank, fill up the generator over here as well. And then I'm gonna buy a gas can from
Mr. Trader over here. I'm going to cook, right? I am so happy that they decided that this game
was going to not have a time go right now. If the timer was going on right now, this would be
horrible. It would be so horrible. Pee? I'll pee like tomorrow. All right, we're good. Let's go
back and put the gas in. He's gonna have to do the ah-ooh during the green screen stream.
That is the only other place that I will do it. Because that's not, that, yeah. I'll do, I will do
that again. A full, like a full cookie crisp. I promise. And I'm gonna do it as hard as I can.
All right, how much is this? 68. I'll just buy one. Take these bottles. All right, back to what I was
just doing. Don't give us this kind of power. Well, those of you that were not here the last
time I did this, how that stream works and how that this whole thing is gonna work is I, you
are going to put, if you want to participate, you're gonna put suggestions on what you want
me to do in front of a full, like 100, like 50 foot long and like 100 foot tall green screen.
Anything. It could be anything. So when people are talking about doing a woo in front of the
greens, we're like, that's what they're referring to. And then everybody makes this shit. They spend,
why am I here? They spend a bunch of time and a bunch of talent. Very talented people in this
community make very, very interesting things from those green screen clips. All right, what was I
doing here? Right. Wood. I got this 10. Okay. I got to organize for a second. Scrap metal can go back.
Hills are going to stay here. I'm going to eat these. This is for health. Battery. I don't,
like, don't know what the fuck to do with this stuff. I already have three. Lockpicks. All right,
I think my inventory is good to go. I'm going to do this just so my brain understands, right? I
need my brain to know what this shit is here for, right? So it's going to be whatever is in the slot.
That row is going to be related to that. So for instance, acts first row, we've got,
I don't know, lockpick and watch because that's like you've stuck your hold and it's on your hands.
Battery and don't matter. It could be anything. Battery and meat. Gun. I guess
uh, that system doesn't work. So I'm just going to, who cares? All right, I'm ready.
I need four more scrap. Make sure I get some. I'm ready to go. The thing I'm going to do now is
I'm going to go from here. I have to go to this train wreck. Wake up now. I'll be all right. The
pill in the hot bar. You know, that's what I should die. That's what I'm glad to have you guys around
because that just frees up space and that's a heal. That's a stamina. I'm just, this is why,
this is why I make sure that I have like some fucking smart people around me surrounded by them.
I mean, like you're not surrounding me. There's a ton of you are just like locked in a cube right
here and I can just look over there. So I'm not technically not surrounded. All right, time. I
gotta pee. I will do that. I'll be right back. Hey, how are you? Good to be back. All right.
Hey, German cube genius here. Be sure to regularly check your...
Is that the new Bane? All right, I'm ready to go. No, I said, oh, like I hit my hand. How bright is
this? Oh shit, that's awesome. All right, I'm ready. Expedition East. We're going to the train wreck
and here we go. Collecting things along the way. Not rocks because they don't, I hate them.
Is this the same shit that I wore last time? No, this is like purple v-neck. I didn't wear this.
I, no. Holy shit, this flashlight is amazing. Why did I not take this? All right, train wreck.
Don't want to use it too often though. All right, be ready. What have we got? Hunter's house. All
right, that's a big gun. What the hell was that? Got to check it out, you know.
Best item in the whole fucking game. Fair trap. Anybody in here? Yeah, there is. One of those
things. I'm going to make them block up the trap. Fuck it. Fuck it. No, no, no, no. Fuck it. Fuck
it. Fuck it. Watch this. No, fuck it. Does this blow up in your hand? Does this blow up in your
hand? Does this blow up in your hand? Does this blow up in your hand? Oh shit, I'm on fire. I'm
on fire. How do I take the fire off? How do I take the fire off? Eat the pills quick. No, I just
watched Ryan look at what it does and how long it's on for. Oh, I hate it. Why did I do this?
Turns out that was a terrible idea. Now, I wanted to see like if it stayed, how long it stayed on
you for. And while I'm doing that, I'm like moving this way. Oh, for the love of God. Hopefully,
there's not two of those in here. There probably is. I hear like gurgling sounds. Stuffed links.
Can't wait. What? There's nothing here. Don't, please don't pop up. I got an important message.
Please read. Neck. Hey, let's see me at 35. I don't know why he would like read that.
I whip out the gun for this because these guys suck. Trophy. Oh shit, found a trophy.
Holy shit, he's alive still. Okay, take the gun out. I didn't know. I didn't know. What's this?
A photo of a dog eating something in a magazine. I can't really use the axe anymore. One more hit
of the axe and it's gonna be destroyed. Start using moisturizer. I, I do every single day.
I'm not gonna read any more of those. Something is still like clicking and clacking.
Oh, I can make armor again. Wait, let me see. Let me change what I got on.
Uh, forget about, who cares about the wire. I can make armor. The tube. Like, no, it's fine.
It's all right. All right. Anything else back here? No. I think I've looted this whole house.
There's a place to go to the right. But have I gone over here? Let me just check this. I have,
I don't know. I have not gone this way and this is blocked. I can't move it so I have to go up
and around. But there's plaques. What the hell is making, there's a lot of traps in here.
What is making that noise? What the fuck? There's so many traps right here. Wow. No room in inventory.
Well, that has to change. Get rid of the, oh, the nails, the wood. Search the traps.
This is everything I wanted. I'm getting rid of the eggs. Eggs and alcohol. Eggs and nails.
I'm so glad I came in here. This is the exact thing I needed. A bunch of scrap and traps.
Bunch of scrap and traps. Is it all in good fun? I hope he doesn't take it to heart.
No, no. I'm just fucking around. We're just, we're just messing around. That's what we do here.
He's sad. What? Now we're not messing around. That's how you get me. That's interesting.
Another wedding ring. I don't want this. It's not worth taking. 50 bucks versus 225.
There's nothing here I want to get rid of. Somebody remember that's here.
Hello. Somebody in this, this bunker thing over here? What about like under? Is somebody like in
a basement or something? I don't see any way to get under. Can I go around? No. Somebody's under
here. Check the tub. After this I have to go home. But somebody's clearly clawing at something.
Like right here? What is over here? Is it just Creaky House and the Creaky House makes Creaky
House noises? I mean this, look at this, but there's something in here. All right, I'm going
back. I don't know. If I miss it, I miss it. I do have enough scrap. All right, we're just going
to go to the left. We'll go there tomorrow. It's time to eat pills to run. Watch out for the
mushrooms. Straight across. Mushrooms, mushrooms, mushrooms, mushrooms, no mushrooms. We're good.
A few hours to get settled. That's the logs if I need them. There's a lot of logs right outside
of my house here. So let's go down from the house. Fortify. Let's go cook quick. Shit,
I barricaded that. You idiot. Don't, there's no traps in here, right? Okay. One, two, bang, bang,
bang, bang, bang. Almost there. So close. This needs to be changed. This is still secure.
There's a trap still up here. I got to go to the workshop quickly before it gets too late.
And I'm going to do, first of all, we're going to upgrade the axe to be sturdy blade,
greatly increased weapon durability. That's the axe head and a bunch of scrap.
Make it beautiful. I can also do attacks use less stamina. I'm going to do that too. I do
need to prepare it. I'm going to do that first. Okay. Upgrade light materials, use less stamina
for attacks. Do that too. This thing is now a powerhouse. What? Oh, so I'm going to get a full
Todd Howard. Damn. But can you do a full Todd Howard with juke one, juke two or juke three,
juke four? That's going to be tricky. All right. Back here. Let's do, I need to make bear trap.
Hot bar upgrade. Good. Light armor. I need two rags. I don't think I have any access to rags
right now, but get this tape in here. I still have a magazine. I got nails. Okay. I'll figure
this out tomorrow and we'll go back out. We do need a full inventory rearrangement. Take this
for a heal. I'll take them both. Alcohol, magazine, toolbox, pills. I don't really need them.
Flashlight axe gun, board, shell. I'll take, I'll keep one meat in here. So I have, how many do I
got? Looks good. I'm ready. Let's prepare. I need to board up a window. So let's take that and let's
take like 20, 30 nails. Right. Okay. I have to do some more boarding. I have the traps with me.
Turn on the generator before it gets too late, which is all the way out here.
Yeah. I'll do the traps last. Boink. Okay. There's a trap still up here. This is boarded. It's got
full health. I just have to worry about the door. In fact, you know what? Like I should really just
do this to all the fucking doors and windows, shouldn't I? But it's too late. This is good.
All right. Get this shit over here. Oh, come on. I don't have time for this shit. Like get out.
Let's go. Whatever. It's, that's fine. And then this, this is actually all right too. I don't
mind this. I don't mind this at all. All right. Trap going down. This shit's going down right there.
No. Yeah. Like right there. I trapped myself. Not yet. Because I'm going to do this. Something gets
stuck there. I'm just going to move this and smash it. Don't move. By the way, I got the rare one.
Do you guys know these are rare? Did you know these are rare? I got a legendary cup. That's right.
Fucking raise a death at her. This glued on piece of shit. I need a new mouse.
Do you have to ask if somebody knows if something's rare? Get an Amazon basic mouse.
You better believe it. Okay. Here we go. In fact, I'm not going to mess around at all.
Let's just go ahead and do this now because I know you're going to get in here.
Here it comes. Here it comes. Here it comes. Okay. Here it comes. No, that door still exists.
Why did the dog not get in the trap when it came in the door?
Why did it not trigger the trap? He just got in and just just appeared over here.
Does dying at the house even matter? Yes, because you don't get the money. Unfortunately,
you don't get the money. I would have had it too. It's just I, my thought process there was he was
just breaking through the he broke through the barricade. That's fine. But when he was breaking
through the door, I just figured I don't want to replace that door. So why not just open the door
and let him walk in the trap. I opened the door, it got stuck on the fucking bureau. And then he
teleported to the other side of the screen. And then I got in the trap. I got wily coyote,
like the roadrunner type shit. This happened. And then the game like just made him go here.
Whatever. I got a goal. And I'm like, I have all my stuff on me. So I can just go. He jumped
through the door. Well, I opened the door because I was trying to save time and not have to redo a
doorway. All right, don't matter. No, not sell this stuff. I want to I will actually I'm going
to level up here. All right. All the necessary things that I want from you. Didn't even get a
chance to use my axe. I didn't get to swing it once. I'm going to buy another medium caliber
bullet, a couple of rags. And that should be all right. No, I'm not going to buy the red egg.
Oh, I do want a magazine though. Very nice. Spin. Now that was only that was only that was the deal
for when I got that's not every trap. 4200. Here we go. Do I get to pick another one? Okay,
I can pick appetite. I would be able to restore my health by eating wood. I mean, that's that's
good. I'm going to do that. Like, that's just good. The trap. Once a day, you won't trigger a trap.
I know this is so much for me. It's so much more useful. But still, eating the wood thing is just
health forever. No, eat the wood. It's health forever. I can eat. I never have to worry about
health stuff. Where are we? Every time you... Okay, this is me, I think. Turn off the light.
Well, I don't know. I want to sleep. All right, fine. I don't want to go out yet. I need to wake
up first. I don't want to wake. This is breakfast breakfast and egg stream. It's too early to cook.
I don't want to go outside. It's too early to cook. I need to wake up first. All right,
we'll go take a shower. Sweater and clothes. All right, put on the sweater. Put on the clothes.
I'll run myself a bath. Franny of washing machine. I spent two days in the queue to get it.
I'll run myself a bath. Oh. Don't wake up and step in the trap. Oh, that would have been so
horrible. That would not have even been my fault. And you all know it. All right, it's back to
storage. And then I'm going for the train. Make another bear trap for later. Okay. Light armor.
Let's do it. Bingo. Batteries. Magazines. Traps. Put them away. Put the wood away. Put the nails
away. Keep the pills. Pills can sit out here. That's fine. Put the scrap away and put the
bullet away as well. I got two hunting rifle. I'm going to hold on to it for an emergency scenario.
I'm ready. Let's go. I'm out the door. Need to go to the train wreck. Wood for health.
That's true. The generator is just blaring. Turn generator off the generator. What about the
generator? I know. And is it any wood or it could be wood planks? Like, can I just take like three
or four wooden planks with me? Does that like work? Try a different room this next night.
Yeah, I might. I might come back out to the hallway strat.
Um, all right. Can I eat? Just, just, can I just bear wood? I can. All right. I'm just gonna bring
five. All right. That's fine. Cool. And we're out. Bare ass. Over here. Let's check it out.
If we come across any other bullshit, I have an upgraded axe. The thing is meaty. I can swing it
a bunch of times. Don't have to worry about it breaking. We're at the hunter's house. We've
already went in here. Uh, I'm going to take some pills because I want to be able to run
for a little while. Straight over here. Location found? Question mark. Is that a camp? I don't
understand. Why is this a question mark? I like, but to be fair, like this, it's it's the same
color as the ground. It's, it's easy to miss because look at all these rocks. These are,
it's the same thing, but they're not rocks. They're whatever. You get it.
I'm not the only one. It's a train. What's up? What's up? Give me those shrooms.
Train. What's up with the train? All right. Just checking the perimeter. There is something.
Get all the stuff. Okay. Cool. Got everything. Now what the hell is, what do I do with this train?
Can I go in here? So why is this such a big point of interest?
I thought it was like, go to the train. There's a train. What do you mean use my mouse?
Like that's a door, but I, how do I get to, how do I open it? That's a, that's a door. This looks
like it. This is, this is the door. Okay. Um, right. What was the code? Note with the code.
Found some code in the dark times. I don't know what it's for, but I hope it opens that door.
So what the hell? 8909. What, what are you doing here? Photo. Okay. And alcohol. Don't
come near me. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. The doctor is lying against the train car's wall.
His face is covered in sweat. An intense odor of alcohol hangs in the air. Don't come any closer.
You rotten dog. I won't give you the key. Can't you understand? I saved your life.
You run away. That's clearing. If it wasn't for me, you owe me for fuck's sake.
The doctor moves closer to the wall, grotesquely kicking his legs against the floor.
You think I don't know who you are? Rack. I've managed to get a good look at you.
Your kind visits us whenever you please. You hide behind the trees, you watch us from a distance,
and then you disappear. You have no idea how it is to live here. This place, these words, everything
is fucked up here. I won't take it anymore, do you understand? I won't bear a look at those
deformed, reeking bodies anymore. I know the cries of those wretched villagers. First they begged for
help, now I need to hide from them? I've just snored every doctor. How the fuck was I supposed
to help them? His face goes silent. Now hugging the wall of the train car, he looks truly pathetic.
Can you hear it? It's the walls. They speak to me. My little girl is calling me. I know she's
waiting for me. I must come back to her. She's so close. I want to go back home. Please. This key
is my only chance. Help me escape this place. Help me or kill me. To the underground entrance.
That's the guy from the start of the game. This is that bastard. Kill him. This is not a decision
I can make. We'll save him. Choose wisely. Let's go. What are we doing to this guy? Pretty unanimous
to save him. Kill then save him. Kill him and then be like, all right, I guess I'll, I guess I'll
let you know where it is. Yeah, kill him and then show him on the map where to get out. You know,
like stick the axe in his chest and then show him the map and go, this is how you get out.
No! And it's his last thing he sees. All right, we're saving him. Thanks for voting. Show the
underground entrance on the map. I take out the map and show the doctor the location of the abandoned
house with the hidden underground entrance. The doctor stares at the map for a long while without
lifting his gaze to meet me. Thank you. He removes his dirty glasses with a trembling hand and freezes.
I will wait for you there and better take the essential things with you.
Looks like returning here will be impossible. Found the doctor. Where are we going? Found the
doctor. I've agreed to help him escape the woods. We are to meet by the door inside the underground
passage. The village? Oh, there, underground entrance. Oh, right, that, with the key and the
21 at the beginning of the game. Right, okay. How did I get there before? So I gotta go all the
way back here. Oh, that's not, that sucks. Okay. Well, doctor, I'll see you at the ex. It's getting
late, so it's time to get the heck out of here. It's noon. I could go through here. I'll go through
here and send my stuff here. That's an easier place to hold. Let me see if I can do that.
Noon is late for boomers. I need to take drugs, like, seriously. Give it a rest. Come on, man.
Let's go. Can I go down? Leave me alone. A natural wall. Burned house. What? Oh, fuck.
Where is this thing? Why does it have to be these, like, giant logs everywhere? Down all the way
around. I've walked by it. What? I, I know, it's right here, but I can't, how do I get around this
shit? Down here? Yeah, all right, there's, there's one spot, there's one parking space worth of space
for me to go through the unnatural wall. I don't like this vision shit. Key to the burned house.
I need a key. I just got it. There's shit over there. Okay. It didn't do anything. Oh, there's
no chests here. It was a lie. Just checking around the whole house. Relax. I'm just checking around
the whole house. Relax. Relax, Jeremy. I'm sorry. Don't relax. No, I'm just saying that out loud.
Made it. Look at that. Shortcut to this old house. All right. Dry meadow. Here we are.
Oh, hell yeah. I remember this place. This is my first house. Does my stove still work?
Oh, you better believe it does. Light the oven. Ten essence. What is this bullshit? All right.
We're good. Um, I have to survive in here. Does this place have gas? What about a container? Do
I have anything for the container? All right, this has got plenty of gas. I don't even need
to fill it. All right, but I do need to, I do need to fill the thing to make some boards and try to
board up a couple of windows here. I have to live here. Are you guys cheating? Wait, is everybody
cheating right now? Why do I know that? Should I know that? Or are you just cheating? It was
under the thing. This is cheating. You guys just cheated. Exploding barrels? This is, I, this is
cheating. I have an exploding barrel. All right, wait a minute. We saw that code already. All right,
I believe you. I believe you this once. Exploding barrel. Okay, I'm gonna have to check that. I'm
gonna have to set that up tonight. That's cool. All right, let's store some of this shit. I need
to keep the wood out. I still have plenty of, put the fabric away. Keep the, let's do a bear trap
and then single shot pistol. Who cares? Fire it once and just throw it away.
Knife is going to be for an emergency scenario. Or actually, I don't need the, that's okay.
I have heel, exploding barrel. Let's put the exploding barrel up. Nails, I need that to
board up some stuff. Let's do that right now. This is boarded. This is boarded. This is going
to be boarded as well. This is a great place to do this. I need, I need that light. Turn the
generator on. Turn on the gas. Yeah, so that will come in handy here. There's only one.
Fuck did I say? It's like smashed my face against the door. There's only one lamp in here. All right,
this is not going to happen. Like why, why can I not have a level up scenario where we're staying
here? This is perfect. This is amazing. Holy shit. This is the best room in the whole game.
Oh, barrel. Um, let's put the exploding barrel. Um, no, not yet. This is a cool item. I'm going
to save it. Let's go. Don't let that lightly go. It's, uh, I know you're right. It's like too late
to move this shit. I wish I could like activate a thing that made it so I could move stuff
not like a toddler. You put me on the back of this thing to move it. And if I need to move it,
if you know, I don't care about scratching the floor. I'm going to sprint and fucking be able
to move this thing 100 miles per hour. The only reason why people move furniture like that is
because they're concerned about scratching their floors. All right, hang on. Here we go. This is
where we lose. Is he going to cry? You drinking lemon juice is my secret slime. Don't forget your
rifle at the other base. Oh, I won't. I plan on actually on going back up there. In fact,
no, just use the axe. Take the bell. Oh yeah, there's a bunch of stuff. I need to,
there's a bunch of shit up there. I don't have the bell down here. I can't ring it.
There's a light of flare. Okay. I mean, it's just sitting there.
Best emote coming through the room. I've done a pretty good job of sitting still
and I'm going to scrap all these traps. Somebody running around outside over here. Can you hear it?
Wait, this is the part. Doesn't one of these like spawn something.
I got plenty of room to move around here though. So I should be fine.
And I got the axe. Best melee weapon in the game. So don't worry. I'll be good.
The bell's not going to work in chapter two. Well, whatever.
God, this is so much better than the other place. Angel, angel thumb. Not yet. Not yet. Two more
hours. Shit can go horribly wrong at seven 30. There you are. There you are. All right.
Let's break them down. All right. Move. Dismantle.
Revealing his chest covered in horrid growths.
It is fused with a porous helmet pulsating to the rhythm of his breath. I'm starting to feel dizzy.
Although loosening his grip, the man raises his left arm, bringing his forearm to my face
and forces a dab out of me. It's pale as paper and reads. Okay. Do not open the door. Let's stick
together. Do not open the door. Medium caliber. I don't have any junk for you.
I have here that I don't care about. I eat this wood though.
Just hold on. I will store some of this stuff. Don't leave the trader. Well, eventually I have
to. I can't just. I'm going to save this scrap. I might need it eventually. I'll sell the fabric.
Let's store the bear. I don't know. Single shot pistol. I don't need. What the hell am I going
to do with that right now? Nails. Boards. Just give me a second. Mushroom. Scrap. Magazine.
Medium caliber bullet. Okay. That's what I want. And then you can take. Just take this meat. I'm
not going to use it. Yes, I will. Can I upgrade my hot bar again? Or is it over?
I can't craft any more. I can't craft any more of this. So it's going into the trash. I'm just
going to sell it. Weird Jupiter. All right. I have to go back to the other hideout and get
myself ready for the final boss. Hook this. Keep the scrap. Take the rags too. And the nails.
Yeah. And the gas. Replace the gas with this three wood. Who gives a shit. All right.
Here we go. Cook that thing. It's funny. Essence. Boy, what a waste of money.
All right. This is the part. I'm going to go back up to the old spot. Which is here. Get everything
I want. Meet the guy down here. Sounds like a plan. And I have to. I'm probably going to have
to last one more night in the. I'm going to try to. No, I'm going to try to go up, get everything
I want, come down, last a night, go over here. That's the plan. I'm out. Let's go. Make it quick.
Straight up. I'm coming back down here. So I want this to be full of gas. Let's go. At least one
more night over there. Any, any drugs? If I have them, take them. Food, drugs. No, let's go. Hurry
up. Food and drugs. That's all you need. In this game. Not actually. I need to go up through this
little, this little hut, right? Sit over here. There. Where the car is. All right. Making good time.
The house. And then it's just up into the left. Oh my God. Jeremy.
Hey. No woods. Okay. Almost there. Hasn't even been two hours. We're good.
What the fuck did I just double take it? I'm here. Let's go. All right. Who's walking?
Who's walking? Stop walking. Okay. Good. Let's do it. The traps in here. How did the dog get in this
is what I want to know. How did the dog get in here? All right. Let's go. I need my important
shit. Ah, there's so many things that could be important in here. Rifle. Rifle ammo. Magazine.
Healing shit. Um, should I make my armor put it on? Why does the game do that to me? All right. The
bell. Does the bell work? I don't think, does the bell actually work? All right. I get a gun.
Batteries. Big flashlight. Heals. More heals. Take out the important shit. Bring the, do I have
alcohol out here? Put the trap away. I'm going to, no, this is not important. Two clips. Five
batteries. The watch. I can only, I'm only taking things if they're in like at least a stack of
three. You fucking stupid ass thing. Like I'm in the menu. What the hell do you think I'm trying
to put it? Now where the fuck did it go? Okay. Three, three. Get the rope out of here. Scrap is
probably going to be important. Take the scrap. Only a stack of two though. Put the weapons up
here. What time is it? Okay. Good time. We're hunting rifle. Block picks. Bell. Battery flashlight.
Alcohol. No. Watch. Scrap. Nails. Maybe some wood. Wood. Yeah. And how many nails do I have?
Take 50 nails. 20 wood. Don't take the bell. All right. Bell is staying. Maybe more wood just so I
can make sure I can get, what about maybe gas? Some gas. Gasoline. This looks all right. Scrap.
Gas. Shovel. Rifle ammo. Rifle ammo is up here. No knife. Give her the knife. Exploding
barrel is a funny laugh out loud moment, but of course it has to stay. Gun. Light. Melee.
Ranged. Healing. Gun. Okay. Rifle ammo. Magazine. That? Okay. Shovel. I think that's good. I think
we're good. Full tank of gas. Armor. Heals. Heals. Heals. Batteries. Flashlight. Gun. Magazines for
gun. Hunting rifle. Medium caliber bullet. Nothing else is standing out to me here.
Do I actually need this shovel? This is already upgraded. I have to leave. Repair it. That takes
too much scrap. I'm gonna need that scrap for something else. I'm out. I'm out. Ditch the
barrel. No I can't. I have to take it. Let's go. Back down. All right. I'm ready to take on whatever
is gonna be taken on at this like end game stage here. I'm not stepping in any more fucking poison.
Beautiful. I'll take the extra scrap. Why not? Oh you dick. Hurry up. Why do you exist?
Why can't I just walk down? Why can't I walk down? Why do you have to have this gigantic
wall of thing? Oh my god. It's a sneeze. That was a sneeze. I have to go through the house.
Fuck you. Fuck you. Seriously. You can't have like two. What's this music playing for?
Was that a sound clip from the movies? He's like a half-life scientist getting hurt.
Jesus christ. Okay. Fuck. All right. Let's live another day in here.
What do I got? I want to. After this day is over I'm gonna repair everything.
We're just gonna exist in here and I'm just gonna kill everything that comes in.
I'm gonna just attack it. It's going to be killed. There's enough gas to last one more night.
Anybody that comes in here is going to be killed. And this is right there but it's not it's night
time. I could just go right here and meet the doctor but it's 17 o'clock. Should I just do this?
Do I have time to get over there? I need to repair my shit. Wait wait wait wait. No. Do I?
No. Let's go. Hold on. Let me repair my shit. Okay. I'm going. All right doctor. The doctor's
gonna explode. He's gonna turn into a giant monster. Do I have time? Let's go. I better find it.
Already. Did I use the runner already? I did. I don't have any drugs.
Oh I hope I. Yeah. Here it is. Made it. All right. Where's the doctor? I should take everything I
need with me. Coming back may prove impossible. Way ahead of you. Way ahead of you. Do I have
everything I need? Yes. Do I? Oh shit. I have to do this. Backpack. How would the doctor do
this by himself? There's no way he would. What's up? Are we going? Locked. It's my only way out.
I won't be able to open it without my key. Ask the doctor to use the key. Look at the handle.
Hey you open this in case something's back here. That's bad. That's funny. Hey you do it. Look
through the keyhole. Is somebody standing there? All right doctor. You go first. I think someone's
still moving there under the rubble. Man. I stumbled upon something amongst the rubble.
Strange soft item. The tunnel has collapsed recently. The reinforced steel protruding from
the debris has not been covered with rust yet. When I gaze into the tunnel I notice a silhouette
of a man on the ground. Suddenly the man snaps to life as if woken from a deep slumber.
Who goes there? I hear a faint, unnaturally distorted male voice. Are you one of them?
The man attempts to get up but fails. I can see him desperately flailing his limbs around. It's
as if his back has been glued to the ground. No please. As I approach him he shuffles his legs
nervously as if trying to retreat into the collapsed tunnel. I didn't do anything. I beg
you. I just wanted to pass to get back to my family. The tree is blocked. The only way out.
The only path home. A huge talking tree. I begged it to let me pass but it wouldn't listen.
I could not understand what it was saying to me so it came here. The man props himself up on his
elbows with a huge effort. He tries to straighten his body but something is firmly holding him by
the back and the neck. I can't. I can't do it. I can't get up. The man drops into the rubble
then goes silent. He clenches his fist. My head hurts. The man places his hand on his forehead
and feels a strange dent above his left brow. He breezes. What? What is this? He carefully inserts
his index finger into the hole. His eyelid twitches. My stone. I hear a sound as if an
eggshell cracking. The forehead bends under his hand. The stranger pushes another finger into the
hole. A thick goose pews from the wound. I can hear his skull cracking. My little stone. The man
slowly removes his fingers from the hole in his head. A colorless ooze dripping from them.
He's holding something. A round object. That's why. He swings his left hand and throws the object
at me. A small irregular ball bounces off my arm and lands at my feet. Looks like a bullet but it's
soft. Okay. This this is what put me to sleep. His head lifelessly drops to the concrete floor
of the destroyed tunnel and goes still. Suddenly I can hear the bang of the metal door followed by
the sound of fading footsteps. It's the doctor. What do you mean it's the doctor? A big sign on the door
reads closed ahead. Where's the doctor? Where'd you go? Oh yuck. I just wanted to pass. Return to my
family. I think I got this military flashlight. Oh shit that's a lizard. Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it? Roats? Some strange organic growths. What the hell are you? Eyes? Soft organism growing
out of the ground. Oh shiny. A shiny stone tied to a wooden cross. You're playing a challenging and
unforgiving game. You will not be led by the hand. Respect the woods. Be patient and focus.
Still on first island. Tutorial complete. Where'd the doctor go? Chapter two. How long is chapter
two? The swamp. It's twice as long. It's 10 hours? Oh shit. Broken compressor. A damaged compressor
used to refill oxygen tanks. I should be able to fix it. I don't have that thing. Oh fuck there's
like a whole area. All right let's go. There's only two chapters right?
Rusty oxygen tanks. Rusty oxygen tanks. They're useless. Generator. Well here's the house. Good
thing I brought the gas. Dumped the whole thing. That's why I brought it. All right is there a
stove in here? Gas tank. Hitting the tank will release the gas under high pressure. Note day one
the compressor is broken. So is the lock on the trap door leading to the underground? Had to use
a blow torch. Fucking moisture. We took photos of the tree from observation point in the vicinity of
3C. It grew twice its size in a month. Really quick even for a local standard. Okay. 1520 hours. I'm
slowly running out of oxygen. I've sent two men to search for nearby junkyard. Maybe we won't have
to go back for spare parts for the compressor. Watch out for the cottage near the junkyard
marked building on the map. Someone could be living there. At least 10 locals lurking between
the trees. How do they know about us? We won't be able to gather our equipment in time. The risk of
getting detected is too high. You need to evac. What the hell? There's a stove. Radio. It's covered
in a thick layer of dust. Looks like no one's used it for a long time but it still smells of warm
plastic and burnt wires. Okay. I gotta get this place ready. Where's the workbench? New house.
Stop doing that. Can I throw like a grenade down here? All right. This is a bigger house. What's
up here? Hey, what's that? A crate covered in a strange organic black shell. I won't be able
to open it until I get rid of the substance. I can only decipher individual words. Shell,
thick glue, light. Fuck out of here. Where's the workbench? This place is enormous.
This looks like a good spot to hide. Yeah, this is definitely the spot. Here it is. I need a key.
No. What? Where's the workbench? Is there no workbench? It's right there. All right. Hold on.
This is where I need to store some shit. Battery. Put the shovel away. Actually,
I'm gonna need all this because I'm gonna board up the doors and everything. All right. Scrap
can go in here. Nails can go in here. This drug can go in here. All right. I'm gonna actually
keep the nails because I'm gonna have to start boarding stuff up and figure out what I want to
do. Wardrobe. Okay. So we've got light. Door. Window. Window. Window. Opening. Opening. I think
it's potentially here in the workroom. Window. Window. Open the gook. Hold on.
This might be not a bad place to do it either. Like through here. All right. Let me go to that
crate. Nothing even in here. All right. I need to prepare the compressor. I have a cottage near
the junkyard. Village. These are marked on the map now. All right. Where do I want to go? Maybe
here. This is not terrible. There's a door. There's already a barricaded window. People can get
through this though, I think. I don't know. Or in here. I would say down there is probably the
safest. Let's go ahead and start that process. This is not bad either. It's it's in here. This
is the one. This is the one. Okay. So looks like the only real reason to come through here.
I'm gonna board this up. This can be there. That's fine. Let me just take a look outside.
Exploding barrel. Oh my god. I have a bunch of these. Oh I feel like this is gonna get hard or
something. This is where it gets hard, right? This is where this is where it gets very hard.
All right. So let me check down here. Let me make sure it doubles. I hate when that fucking thing
does that. This is not ideal. Actually it's not that bad though. I have to just pick one. I have
to pick one. The workbench room is good but it's too small. This is too small. Too small. I don't
like it. Too small. We're going up here. This is the one. This one's a little bit bigger. This one's
already barricaded. Let's do this one. And there's already a lamp in here too. We can board this but
not yet. I could even board this. They can only come in from one way. Let's bring this up here.
I went to the store and came back. Is he still? Is he still dying to bear? Is it time to save bear
traps? And exploding barrel right here. Let's do it. Exploding barrel right here. I'm gonna wait
for someone to come in. Boom. Good night. Okay. What's going on? It's raining. All right. Wardrobe.
We got matches. Rag. Where's the generator? I gotta keep burning that into my mind. Up, right,
down. We got gas. We can come through here though. Pick up the gas tank. No.
Make some traps. Let's make a few traps. Yeah this is where I wouldn't like being in here.
So that's how you get the generator on. This is a long way to go except for right there. But it's
all right. I'll explode these motherfuckers when they come in the door. Or like you know that's a
yep that's no it's not that's a dad that's that's a that's a dead end that's a bad strategy
all right bear traps let's go i gotta i keep getting new places bear traps make two or three
though looking good pull them out let's go this is the final new place that's true
got plenty of gas stop with that board it up board it up bear trap here this is a good place
for it to be couldn't i could not ask for a better place to have it because then i really
only have to worry about this side over here and some random psycho that just like comes in the room
that's secure that's secure this is not secure but it's about to be because i want to show you
oh i do it check this out i'm gonna put a bear trap here and if i hear that get activated oh i
open the door and blast although i can't leave if i do this so that's the plan that's the plan
put the gun back here flashlight back here i'm gonna keep that in my inventory heels can stay
now i'm gonna go store this stuff because everything's been boarded i just need how
many do you need to board what is it it's uh three and seven so i need three six nine wood
and then 21 nine and 21 because in case these break so stick that i need nine of these
it was a really stupid way to do that but whatever all right nine of these put the barrels back
clips can stay and i need 21 of these okay don't need matches i might hold on to one of these just
to do it here's the heel and i also have bandages i'm gonna store these
store the flare battery's fine 921 a panic scenario might be all right all right we're good we're
good okay i have a plan i have a plan there's one of these down here too actually i'm gonna keep that
this is bait because when this turns on it's gonna be flashing through the window
this is gonna attract so many people into this room i think that's not a bad call
i don't want it all right is it it's almost time thank you for coming through this door
because um i wouldn't have known it existed here we go i'm gonna turn on the generator
just wait i don't want to waste that much gas surround yourself with explosive barrels and
traps and just let the monsters come at you go out in a blaze of glory you don't get debated here
i won't but what's gonna happen is when i i'm gonna keep this door open when i hear the first like
i'm gonna just open the door make sure i can how big of an explosion radius is this
can somebody help me out here is a huge i'm gonna get this in the corner so if i have this here i'm
gonna make sure i can open the door all right so let's do like a little rehearsal here
what's that somebody right there boom because the traps are gonna be right here all right time
turn generator on let's do it i got time i got time i got time i got time i got time to do it i
got time to do it up there to block the light fuck you i almost it's turned out to be four i found
new signs 17 kilometers west of the hideout 33 points 12 circles cataloged pattern unattentive
simple scribblings and a madman three shotgun shells okay get this why is this chair here get
out of the way got it good okay pull this back here so i can still open trap put it down let's
go this is gonna move in the corner 20 20 20 20 20 20 20 20 coming up 20 come up 20 coming up 20
coming up don't move okay i'm ready remember trap outside we hear it open the door boom
i'm not moving move the chair what do you mean move the chair i can't i can't move anything guys
is it the radio e f w r a f ra us to us come back to us come back to us i'm close just chill
the reason why i would i don't want to move the chair is because it's gonna make noise
all right hold on i can still see out of my prep what are you doing
why is this stuff moving why is this stuff moving fuck no my trap my plan you've ruined my plan
don't move it's bait to get you to scream so they can know where you are it's just a dog
you're not gonna get in no you won't get in you got that and you have the door to do as well
by the way if you do get in i'll get you uh cazzie thanks for the five community subs cazzie
five drop there all right i gotta be ready this dog is not going to go into the trap
it will if i go like this though oh shit oh what the fuck there's an area in the room
oh the dog didn't even get trapped
does the eye see me don't get comfortable yet that was horrible
here's how that happened well first of all it shouldn't happen but the reason is because
you can see this object that's movable this object that all the objects in the room
and that one's not here but the other ones are and it's the only thing that doesn't show up
and i just whatever that's still a good strategy and i'm gonna do it again well maybe it's not i'm
just gonna keep you know you know fuck that i'm gonna keep this door open because when an alien
like that comes in the room i need a way to okay i'm gonna put a trap like here and like run through
this door and like bait him into the trap i'm not just gonna stand in a cube this is the thing
that needs to be boarded this is the thing that needs to be protected and if somebody comes in
you bait him around the trap anyways i where's the trader usually they're right here no trader
didn't you say i had a reputation with the trader the three it's fucking pinwheel three visitors
stare at me in silence as i'm waiting for my move i can only hear the heavy breathing of the
tallest figure holding a giant bag as he opens a bag the room is filled with an intense smell of
mushrooms apparently they wish to give me something well you're very loud whatever you are let's go
with um how many nails do i have let's get some more nails some drugs get some more no no get these
drugs medium bullet medium bullet i want the medium bullet okay all right now get out of here
show item i have nothing to show them okay so i now have four bullets for this rifle or five
technically right because i can shoot it once let's put put this stuff away until i come back
not sure exactly what i'm going to be looking for but i know i will be looking for something
food shotgun shell i don't have any shotguns i'll keep those all right i'm gonna go explore
it's gonna cook this stuff i don't i almost just jumped i almost just jumped through this window
and landed on this i'm gonna do the well maybe no broken computer where's the um
where's the oven it's down here look look holy shit that was a lot
nine thousand each damn all right so i got this village i have this cottage the village was
a point of interest found an abandoned journal in the swamp hideout i managed to mark the village
with a tree on my map thanks to it okay let's go to the let's go to the village let's go for it
i have healing i've got everything upgraded and let's it's right here body of a man wearing
a helmet his head has been severed off severed what weird book and key to tunnel 21 and a severed
head someone scratched out the word liar on the helmet's viewfinder let's go so it is going this
way i already hear a dog what happened to the dog that was strange that's right here
oh hello hello hello what does he do he does like a swing swing throws shit
holy fuck dude are you kidding me you gotta shoot him in the eye it's not enough to heal
listen i use there's another one what i wish it would stop raining so i could hear anything
i wish i could hear even any i can't even hear the sound of my own fucking voice
oh it's the doctor you again what do you want from me want to put me in front of a firing
squad for desertion the doctor snorts ironically hiding his irritation i'm not going anywhere with
you i'm too close i can hear her just as if she was standing beside me my little was shaking hands
he re he reaches for the cigarette butt between his yellow teeth i'm sure someone's waiting for
you too he spits out the rest of the tobacco how do i get to the road why are you showing this to
me you better tell me how to get there i don't know i thought you might know the peasants broke
through the wall of trees i could not believe my eyes i tried to do it many times i couldn't
manage to cut the trees fast enough it was as if the woods were healing the scars the motherfuckers
were growing back right in front of my eyes i was afraid i would get stuck between trunks
losing that sow made their blood run cold they escaped fearing starvation
it pops the cigarette out of the frying pan and into the fire they have a camp in the old quarry
in the southeastern edge of the swamp thanks i used to come here to treat people i pulled out kids
milk teeth delivered babies and then came to diseases i've never even heard of i was the only
doctor in the area he cut us off from the outside world first you then the woods no help from anyone
last time i came here was three or four years ago and the trees blocked the path
i'm gonna kill him it just didn't fit okay so he was curious uh the doctor looks around it's
different now the fields are flooded everyone in the village is dead so much work for nothing
embryo weapon farm a tape how much does this give me should i take the embryo a hundred dollars for
the tape first your dog killer now a doctor killer when will your reign of terror end
all right some of the flooded areas hide underwater passages recently i fell into this
underwater den in the western edge of the swamp okay i have no idea where it leads i'm a shitty
diver i've seen similar one in the northeastern edge of the swamp too we just got all kinds of
information to give me an info dump on me i've realized something that came to me when we were
walking through the tunnels oh you mean when you were running from me from the tunnels and
two heads are better than one i could have handed you like a rifle
idiot you're like a disease you and your kind the doctor takes a step back as if he was afraid
of me at the same time a sinister smile appears on his face you don't belong to this land you
weren't here when the forest was born you're a splinter a foreign body a vagabond and then
the forest and everything else here these are the antibodies even the morons from the village
raging white blood cells and an infected bloodstream that's the reason we hide from us
doctor is visibly pleased with himself in his theory his hands are no longer trembling
he produces a hand-rolled cigarette and lights it logical isn't it this sucks
taking every bone in my body to not just attack but anyways um stuff marked on the
the peak something must have scared them off from the huge tree shrine
the figure of the shrine bears the signs of teeth it's partially eaten i mean i eat wood
nothing wrong with that it's all good a big tree hold on i don't i don't even want that
adorn that with a flower pattern hold on it's my it's my daily uh it's my daily
never ever buy a razor mouse ever under any circumstance part of the stream there we go
we just re-reattach the glued on piece okay the glued on piece that comes off let me make sure
i get that on let me make sure i let me make sure i let me make sure i get that that piece that has
that comes off that's glued on just that portion of the stream because it's like irritating me now
that's hurt that's happening to mine too somebody said what a fantastic product that you should go
buy as soon as you can buy all of them in the store if there's like four of these mice buy all
buy every single one why do you not get logitech i don't know because they all i all death that
it was great and then they glued pieces on all right i gotta be careful none of my keys fit
all right well i can't get in here can i go another way i guess i can go this way
oh shit it's one of those things
oh
i'm just keeping out the gun axe is not i'm just keeping out the gun man like the axe is not doing
it for me right now these things are scaring the shit out of me uh what's happening who's walking
holy fucking hell where did it go oh shit there's a mushroom where am i going
just like somebody camping over here i'm i'm lost in here i'm lost in here
shit i don't like this i really really don't like this part there's a person in here
who are you who are you wait bloody hell you're alive the old man extends his hand blindly trying
to reach me enough from around here hey you can't be all them lads are dead it's only me me and
he finally finds my arm and grabs it for a moment he clutches my hand in silence then i
hear him mumbling under his breath i don't have anything made only this this chair bloody hell
his gaze stops somewhere under the leaky barn ceiling what the old man suddenly jumps up what
are you saying i feel his long fingernails digging into my hand ain't no fucking tree
it looks like a tree but those faces i know of buggers every single one of them so close
and so fake they're not real they're not from time to time i thank god i went blind
i don't have to look at him the old man lets go of my hand to lean against the broken back
of the chair he sighs with relief it disgusts me it fucking disgusts me this buggery this fucking
scum all the time i have to listen it's pathetic blabber complaining all the time as if i was
supposed to believe it's human that it's me soca yeah right he suddenly reaches towards me with
both hands almost falling off from the chair he grabs onto my sleeve i feel all his weight
you lad you've got your hands and legs strong arms i beg of you get rid of that filth from my
village i can't bear another day of that abomination whiling and sobbing i want to
die in peace fucking hell i want to die in peace listen to me i thought about it for a long time
i've had a lot of time to think for fuck's sake his eyes widen his pupils are milky white i can
feel him climbing my coat you need to find a basement jesse's basement i remember it
it's right next to the tree the tree is too large so if you can't reach it from the top you've got
to try from the bottom find the basement and there surely you'll find the tree's roots the bloody
thing must have roots that's where they are destroy them hold them drag them twist the fuck out of
them you'll find a way i know you will the old man slides down my coat straight onto his destroyed
wheelchair for a moment he searches for his stone which he uses to prop himself up against the muddy
floor of the barn thank you thank you uh what's road the old man grabs the photo feels it and
then takes out a small glass object from his pocket and puts it to his eye the road home
what a load of bullshit the road of madness is what it is no one lives around her anymore
everyone is dead only sometimes sometimes i hear footsteps they wake me up at night
sound of bare feet against the floor and bells of sort they come out of nowhere they move towards
the trees then come back they pass me and fall silent they're like a nightmare a bloody nightmare
if you come across some wheels two little wheels so that i could fix my chair maybe
you'd benefit from it as well two wheels i had tires years ago when my eyes were good
people used to pass through here they would leave their huts and go there where that damn
tree grows they would often leave at night so that no one could see them they went into the
deep dark woods and never came back some of them would say they are going home but most of them
were silent i don't know the land has changed those trees have cut us off from the rest of the world
but home for me has always been here and that monstrous morning abomination grew out of the
ground it blocked the passage and that that no one has managed to pass through since then
maybe people found some other place maybe they died at the swamp just like us
what are you going on about again the wheelchair oh the war took me legs then those wankers burned
my house and me pigs but it was years after the war they said it was to fight the disease so they
said and my zocker the disease took her from me all i have is this wheelchair and this land
used to be different here first the woods changed trees start sprouting up everywhere we got caught
in a water flood in our fields people went crazy out of hunger they fall out of food they don't
they don't eat those what about what about their legs so destroy the tree i'll handle this grandpa
you got any stuff forks sickle this area is huge here's the tree destroy the tree all right i'll
take care can i get in here basement hatch oh fuck this is like a side quest the hatch leading to
the basement is blocked from the inside the marks on it suggests someone tried to break it open
how the fuck do i get in here is there any other way to go over here the tree is gigantic its bark
stays in constant motion it swells up and collapses into itself as if breathing i see human
silhouettes growing out of the tree trunk they're also moving as if gesturing in slow motion
dozens of miles repeat their lines simultaneously creating a uniform noisy murmur between the bows
i catch a man's gaze it's fixed on me his body similarly to the other beings
seems to form an integral part of the tree his limbs are gnarled and his face is grotesquely
deformed he's the only one to acknowledge my presence his hand slowly raises pointing to
something on the horizon above the roofs of the destroyed village the man's lips are moving but
the ghastly murmur of the other voices drowns out his words kick the tree hoping that the voice will
go silent try to climb the tree look at the lips of the person talking to me
even though the figure speaks sluggishly it is too high for me to read the lips properly
i think one of the words is radio the bark is slimy and soft its creases move away from my
shoes and hands i feel the arms that protrude from the roots tugging at my clothes i'm not sure if
they want to drag me down or pull me closer i barely break free from their grasp climbing
up is out of the question kick the tree i kicked the tree trunk with all my strength breaking a
branch sticking out from between the roots it hurts i hear a silent voice coming from beneath
my feet it's a face of a man who's grown into the root he's completely covered in bark his
lips barely stick above the mud and his raised arms resemble branches one of them is broken
in the elbow the stump leads a white gooey substance instead of seeping down it slowly
flows upward forming a new arm so just like a soul tree examine i notice a little smiling
face of a girl gazing at me from behind a cluster of sleeping heads oblivious to the chaos around
her she studies me with curiosity just next to her a massive man calmly humps a melody the lullaby
drowns in the overwhelming noise surrounding the tree i'm barely able to make out any conversations
and squabbles from the horrible noise of the tree boughs you took everything from us the shouts
come from an old man only the tip of his head and one of his arms stick out from between the
tightly crowded bodies you stole it thieves may the dogs piss on your faces right next to
him a woman's head wobbling from side to side repeats we were hungry we were hungry another
figure hiding its face under an enormous root lets out a chilling shriek quiet fucking quiet
leave us in peace shut up he is interrupted by a man next to him his intestines hanging up from
his stomach it was our common good it was meant for all of us you stole it are we going to go
through every single branch high above there's another guy that says hey fuck you how dare you
high above the top of the crown two silhouettes hanging from side to side from their hands and
legs grown to the trunk are trying to bite each other's faces off no it was mine it was mine it
actually was mine it was me it's me that was me this is you all right is there anything else so
the tree is made out of people potentially lots of people okay so the real question is
what the hell do i do now uh it's time to go home i've really collected very much stuff although
i will get another clip tomorrow hopefully nothing else i got a couple of things burn the tree i mean
if i can get down there i'm gonna put some gasoline on it and get rid of the damn thing
okay that's the idea all right i think i've i've got to get back i need okay the shovel
rubble dig in the rubble okay i can bring the shovel up there wow that's i actually did need
the shovel okay i don't even think about it that thing is huge i do not want to fuck with that
thing not at all no thank you no thank you stay in your swamp please i need to get the fuck out
of here it's like giant maze over here no there's no way anybody saw that like it was parted look
at this this is like the same exact this is this let's get out here i'm gonna go back to my house
and then try to find a way to get back into there's a couple of things that they said i want to look
at the journal the next morning i'll take the bear trap back home hooray let's craft antidote
not necessary let's get rid of the rest of this gas i'm gonna cook bring out the traps
explosive barrel and i still have a battery so hold on where's my
okay so how are we doing make another one use this fill up okay this thing's pretty much empty
let's take up space bring the shovel back there tomorrow no i want to go check out the thing
all right i gotta cook first why are there so many bear traps but no let's get the fuck out of me
again why are there so many bear traps but no bears well because they're not made for bears
in this game they're married for people well there's the radio remember it was radio radio
that's a lot of acids ah so close i need ah damn it so that's barricaded that's cooked
tank is empty let's begin the process of what i wanted to do last time last time
there's two traps here this needs to be re-barricaded i need three okay i need more
of that shit of course i do and it's all the way down here three six nine and then i need like
21 of these just to have an inventory okay and what do i have for heals i'll take these three
magazines lockpick don't need to be in here now i'm just gonna try to survive i'll make another
one of these and that can stay here i actually don't need it i have pills okay boarding stuff up
putting stuff down all right i'm gonna max out my credit card laughing my ass off
i would advise against doing that something tells me that's probably not a smart idea
laughing my ass off let's board this up all right this is full health full health
how is this one doing didn't get touched i'm gonna remember the the idea is i'm gonna keep
this shit open and i'm gonna board this one up over here that's the idea i have to pee again
really badly so hopefully this goes well i want to get this here we're gonna put oh god damn it
it just creeped up on me right here board this one up frequent urination problem well i've drank
almost two full containers of this so it is a well-oiled machine it's pretty much what i do
every stream you just don't see it because i don't usually i'm not on camera but this is scary game
day the last four days in a row have been scary who's like okay i pay attention trap the only way
they can really get in is through here which let's just put one here i would know no i want
this here right there because i want to be able to stand behind it let's do another one no i don't
need to let's get the heel on there so i have i can heal all right i'm ready now if somebody
chases me i can run up here go around this corner and make them walk into this i might even no not
to this that's not that that's too much these are good down here this is barricaded here
the chair is going to move actually just get the damn thing out of the way
because it's just going to cause a problem when the guy eventually comes through the ground
we're doing gun here we go what about the centipede man centipede man spawns i'm running into this room
and baiting him into the trap go pee you'll be fine well that would be bad if i were just to leave
right now and that trap is not sitting right in front of the door so i should okay we'll see
well we got three shots in this before i have to reload it is lemon water intentionally you're
just that bad at making lemonade uh no the lemon water is it's intentional because i'm currently
on a fodmap diet and i can't have fructose corn syrup i can't have a lot of fruit shit but lemon
juice lemon juice is fine i can put a little bit in water lime juice and water and it's
like it's like drinking it's like drinking a soda let me have this okay i know it's not the same
thing is it a dog if it's dog it's getting the hammer all right why did i move is that making
noise i think that's loud okay something's coming into the ground i don't know what that is
what the fuck is that thing i just got dropped on that second that door opens
who opened the door how did you get in that room
multi-room strat works same deal putting trap there if i get diarrhea on i can go up here
anybody chases me i can go up here say vice versa throw go down this is a good spot i think
i'll be all right so for this day uh i am going to i need to look at the journal for a second
destroying the top he claims i first need to get the cellar to the cellar located near the tree
that's how i find its roots which i need to burn according to him it's the only way to get rid of
the abomination uh and advice from a blind deaf old man with no legs the only lead i have so far
it's not much but i've grown accustomed to it okay i saw the village that's the village of the tree
spare parts for the compressor the old journal also included information about a college cottage
located near the junkyard according to the notes i would be able to find some spare compressor parts
there they might come in handy broken compressor i'm going up that's all i got right now that's
literally all i got why no rifle because i'm afraid to use it because it has five shots
and i'll miss three of them and i'm not going to use it until the credits roll
because that's what i do in games like this would probably come in handy
or the shotgun you know what shotgun's coming with us we're gonna give you we'll use it but
i'm gonna pee because it's time to go to the bathroom i'll be right back hello wait every
break you gotta apply a little bit more balm what if i just turned the whole thing up like this and
just bit the top up and swallowed it i don't think this is low fog map slime action okay
so today we were going to uh this i like the strategy this is good we're gonna go investigate
cottage upstairs we're going up here cottage near the junkyard that way why does this feel
strange it's like it feels different is it backwards i was worried okay uh i'm ready to go
i don't have to do anything i've got heels i've got i'm gonna have to cook this stuff and
we should be fine i thought i stepped in a trap again i don't want to remove the uh wood here so
i'm gonna go around this stuff i don't need to dismantle it what's the point of dismantling it
when i can just go like this and push this back tonight good turn off the generator
level up we're at probably the final level adrenaline i will deal double damage in melee
when close to death my vitality will increase once a day i'll be able to become invisible to
enemies if i stay still healing items will be less effective and my accuracy decreases
oh no this is okay probably the vitality or invisibility how long does that last
my accuracy will be less effective in shooting how much more i wonder done so i've got a little bit
more health there that's pretty good i thought i was really expecting a full cube i don't like
a half a cube feel a little uh feel a little ripped off all right i haven't even looked in here
so i need to craft a few things for instance i need to talk to the trader down here
buy my daily magazine my daily scrap my daily magazine my daily bullet my daily rags and
that's good i'll do the pills too yeah you can have a sickle my daily vroom
all right let's get the shot i don't even have a shotgun i've left the shotgun doesn't is not here
here i don't own a shotgun single shot shotgun where do i get that those pliers i haven't seen
them at all single shot shotgun so i need i had need the weapon i don't have the weapon parts
either i'm gonna have to keep this blade is i'll bring the hunting rifle this thing has one shot
i'm going to take one bullet with me extra
how many pills do i have three uh i'm gonna bring some wood to eat
i left at the last island yeah just eat this now it's not a great heal actually it's pretty bad
that's really bad well unfortunately for me that's gonna have to do
okay i'm bringing a barrel too yeah and no i'm not going that way yet i'll bring yeah
just in case of something else lock picks a couple of batteries my watch i don't think
i need this many magazines but uh yes i do do you ever looks like the guy who gave me the wrong
order at olive garden i would get your order right every time that looks good i got some
pills i got pills i've got bread i got i got now guys i've got i've got never-ending garlic bread
from olive garden we're going up here let's try it see what i can do investigate up here we go whoops
that's just good stuff i'll take it
i don't know why i did that just eat some fucking never-ending garlic wood i used it at least i
used it all right no more wood don't need i don't need to take anymore all right look for a compressor
thing right that's a hidden bear trap i'll take it starting to run out of space already no no don't
take the wood i can i can go on like a scavenge if i need to put the wooden
i can i can go on like a scavenge if i need to put the wooden
and the mushrooms and shit no no it's not necessary he spits
die motherfucker i used it it's too hard to see that shit it really is how many bullets does it
take to kill one of those how i gotta go up really is that that's not even that's out of the bounds
that's out of the map this accuracy is actually really really starting to be a pain in the ass
i can scavenge for it another time i oh i'm i'm here now this looks like this is out of balance
eat a piece of wood what the fuck is that what is that poisoned i ain't fucking with that thing
just put it on the hot bar i'm gonna be chewing on wood this whole time
oh i can't do it from the hot bar it's an alien artifact all right there's apparently some
cottage near a junkyard over here another one of these okay i'm at the sawmill i don't understand
what i'm supposed to do about those things this map is lying to me right now i got it mushrooms
i have to watch out for how's the doctor again he looks bad this land hides more secrets than your
little fucking rat brain is capable of understanding the doctor digs through the mud i think he's
looking for something deep underground there's a current of electricity fucking electricity
he starts flailing his arms around wildly throwing pieces of mud everywhere around him
and it flows underground from tree to tree the doctor suddenly freezes staring at me with his
arms mid-air and it powers everything it connects it all if i had a light bulb if i just screwed it
into one of these branches it would light up i bet it fucking would it bends over a small hole
in the mud and continues digging maybe this is where you're hiding maybe this is the way bolt
handle should i get the bolt handle or a weapon part i don't know which one to do do the embryo
instead the bolt handle is a weapon part that's a shitload of bad that's like two thousand three
thousand essence what whatever i can make with the bolt handle i'll try to make it
let's go got it can you hear the trees sing they're calling us they're showing us the way
they're showing us the way all at the same time blocking it i can't understand it he kicks a stone
are they trying to tell us something are they putting us to a test i don't know maybe they're
lost too and don't know what to do he shakes his head dispirited and goes silent still got that
cigarette though after a long pause he turns toward me his glasses are so dirty i can barely see the
eyes hiding beneath them i see you haven't regained your speech you need to find another
doctor i haven't slept a wink in many days i don't think this is good for me i hear this voice all
the time can you hear it her heavenly voice the doctor stares right into my eyes mud drips from
his face he hasn't blinked in over a minute no you don't why would you you don't know her
he steps towards me and lowers his voice i'm a bit fed up with her i've bit a little tiny bit
she must know i'm heading her way i'm doing everything i can i don't eat i don't sleep i
search under every rock under every fucking bush she must understand it she must give me some time
some little time off tell her this will you kind of losing it here the doctor is lost in thoughts
a cigarette sticks out of his mud covered mouth he's in what remains of his shoe he draws lines
on the ground they seem to intersect in completely random places i'm waiting he doesn't stop drawing
he moves away a bit and makes a wide arc with his heel four the doctor flicks his cigarette into
the dirt stomps on it and drags it along the ground creating the last straight line
you fuck trying was never my forte okay doc goodbye fish come on oh shit all right i can't
that uh who are you who are you i'm here are you trapped i'm here i'm here i'm trapped i'm
i might be trapped i'm trapped i'm here i hear hear her i hear her i hear cut me loose i can't i
tried what is that a giant snail what the fuck is that apparently this is the cottage
the shell is cracked maybe i could break it open should i do that what if it comes out
whoa rook beneath the shell is completely destroyed the snail shell is probably also
badly damaged maybe i'd be able to get inside the cottage through the skin on his belly it
seems quite frail are you the snail speech is incredibly slow creamily and slurred he moves
his jaw with great effort it looks like it's about to fall off his eyes sag from their sockets they
dangle from side to side trying to keep me in their sight why are you disturbing my forced
rest his right eye raises with great effort and wobbles your face what happened to your face
your hair looks like shit today man let me sorry i've been drinking the chemicals
stove again the snail's jaw falls so low it almost detached itself from the rest of the body
you scared me you barely resemble a human cover yourself suddenly i feel a subtle shiver
beneath my feet the snail's body livens up quiet you hear that do you hear that voice
the snail tucks his head inside his shell she calls to me can you hear it she's calling to me
i'm here trapped bound
the snail falls silent for a long above with the inside of the shell is almost completely silent
the snail's body suddenly leans forward the wooden construction of the cottage
creaks under his huge bulk i barely keep my balance cut me loose please i need to get out here if you
release me i will leave come back tomorrow and i won't be here anymore you can live in my home
you like it you just need to cut me loose the snail falls silent his enormous head slowly drops
to the shell giant gleaming drops of mucus appear in his slimy skin you need to understand my
predicament i'm unable to do anything by myself my legs are numb from lying here
i can't feel my arms at all i've been lying in the sun gives me this strange pleasure
but it's time for me to go understand i love you that's not what that says understand i have to
photo of the road you're going there too everyone is going there it's the world home after all
once there was a beautiful clearing now everything's coming in water and i've lost
my gumboots do you have any gumboots on you you're so ugly i feel like puking you barely
resemble a human being i found work today it was yesterday or a few days ago maybe a year
i woke up in front of the house i thought i was dreaming i took a step and fell down
i fell straight through the roof how did this happen uh so i have to cut him loose
the shells please throw the snow so how do i cut them loose pour salt on him you maniac
it was blocked by rubble i must find a different way inside
what is from his shell the shells completely destroyed the shells completely destroyed the
snail shells probably also badly damaged his skin on his belly it looks like a human hand
but it's sticky and grown into the shell the key grows out of the palm i should be able to easily
tear it off key found shed key key to the shed where's there a shed
i'd get them off maybe a knife some kind of organic cords they're slowly pulsating they're
surprisingly hard and durable board some kind of cord some kind of cord
organic cord is this like i can i just like to kill again i can't go anywhere else over here
i would think i'd have to follow this around somewhere oh look bear trap many nails and
planks some useful scrap metal gun oh this is it okay
useful scrap metal gun parts at sea ropes tapes antlers some tools scrap metal
an old an old compressor f f right here yep so what tools may be equals pliers
so i don't understand this though maybe can i just not do this or do i have to do something
it is a snail over here it's getting late i need to figure this out before i leave though
wardrobe door it's i mean i could cut him in the stomach but i don't want to kill him
isn't that gonna want to kill him that's a good everyone a bunch of people just said
a bunch of people just said just cut his stomach open it's like that's gonna kill him
let me see this one more time boots he says cut me loose dude i can't i i'll come back
that's i'm running out of time i gotta go i feel like there's something i gotta have to leave
all right it's something to do with this close now i i don't know what i'm supposed to do
am i supposed to cut this i i don't is this is this letting him go i i don't know what this what
i'm supposed to be doing i don't have time to know either what am i trying to do here
like block the light i don't have time to this to do this okay am i trying to have i don't know what
this i what then what is this this is a place to go up here what i gotta have to leave i thought
i was supposed to cut the cord i'm fucked what am i supposed to do now i am so much trouble
what's over here i'm dead cut it cut it cut the cut it cut it here it is cut it
a weird pulsating road looks delicate i freed the snail go what if i stay in the snail's stomach
what if i stay in here i feel free again when you return here tomorrow i won't be here tomorrow
i'll follow her voice and you'll be able to live here i promise
where's the house i'm dead hurry the fuck up and go through swim you fucking baby
i don't care i have to go the fastest route i don't care it's poisoned i'll get over it
i'm pretty much immune to it at this point it's happened so many times
i gotta turn on the generator turn it on before it gets too dark what is that it's an alien okay go
through house no i have to go through i have to go through this side because remember 48 50
right at the fucking last second oh fuck i got heels right i have one heel i have any more wood
eat it no you fucking fool you fool you fool you were supposed to board it
oh i can't i think i have to do gun for this yeah gun hello
trap a trap what the hell are you thinking jeremy somebody's pushing it who's pushing it who's
pushing it is somebody is he dead do i have no bullets oh this is bad i'm making so much
fucking noise wood eat wood i'm gonna fucking blow this place to hell
do the scream all right wait there's still an hour there's still an hour guys this ain't done
is it a dog coming in 26 250 rep all right i can't believe i did it i can't believe i made it
time to move my house to the snail house same deal all the things that i like
now i did get a weapon part so let me just let me check that out let's be chefs 960 essence it's
not very much the bolt is for a rifle i kind of already have one huh well i guess i could sell
it after i make it or i could just sell apart all right workbench it's not even i don't even
have access to it 225 though it sells for good ammo and the rifle i could i could use a couple
more batteries if i'm honest all right we have traps and two traps that should be good for the
next night i'm gonna use them to fill some gasoline up i need a couple more batteries
how do i make batteries can i no should i take i'm gonna take these heels do i have the yeah
actually they're right here i'd rather do this take the good ones and spare parts i got lots
of spare parts now rotten mushrooms oh shit they sat in there for too long didn't they
fuck whatever i'll bring one of these bringing the shovel too just in case we're going to fill up
the other we're going to use the gasoline heels food and bullets i'll take two that makes sense
to me all right let's go repair the axe i don't think no it doesn't need to get waste now i have
a new house this is true so should i just run with a bunch of stuff to the new house
is the cottage not a hideout now the cottage is not a hideout oh shit okay well that's good
to know all right that's good let's refill some of this stuff the rest of this and then let's fill
up the generator how much is in the generator yeah i could use it oh top this off all right cool
i'm good i've already dealt with you but there's anything else i need
i'll take a pill yeah yeah give me some more pills all right let's go up to the house the snail
house because now it's another day so it's technically you shouldn't be there anymore
let's go i want to examine that i turned off the generator right can two thousand of you confirm
prepare the windows oh smart smart how's this one doing i'll just put them all up i was going
to redo the whole thing fucking stupid eye ah let's get all the wood i should have enough to
do at least enough nails too okay kind of run out of nails see what i can do with this wood
what i gotta grind him up you know got enough gas for me to do that come on
general you ever think about taking the l like taking the loss i mean what do you mean i'm like
i'm like probably an hour or two away from beating the game why would i take a loss right now
it's good do i have enough i do not have enough do i know i need more nails that's okay i can
finish this when i come back because it's just these it's just this door here i'm gonna retrap
though because that's the way that we're going to do this i have two in there two okay one two
make another one three should do it i think i'm happy with three yeah three should be fine
so in the usual places i also wanted batteries too but i don't think i can i not make batteries
okay and then i do i want one up here please remind me that this exists again
i will cause a huge problem if i do not know and i'm gonna i have time to put this over here
you're gonna like it through we move how's my inventory look actually pretty dog shit so hold
on got enough bullets this is my healing boards my pills my batteries my shovel my piss bottle
it's a little kind of kind of overkill on the healing here yeah overkill on the healing get
this out of here off we go let's check out the snail hut see what's in there now
almost stepped in it but i didn't where the fuck is the snail he's gone he went away at least he
told me he went away he might have been a liar we'll find out what if he's still there yeah he
said he was gonna leave yeah he should be gone better be or he's got a real soft belly is what
i've been told i need some wood it's actually a good opportunity to take wooden nails okay
here we go let's see what's in this place up in the snail cavern here we go
did he leave he left radio this expensive shit no map location found radio tower
now leave the rope it's useless to me a lot of rusty radio equipment is turned on the floor
old recorders and destroyed tapes everything's covered in goo dripping from the leaky ceiling
dead body the dry corpse overgrown with small roots okay so i got the map i got the radio tower
oh my god that's so far away i guess we go to the radio tower well that was is that the snail
that's everything that's oh no folks we have nothing to eat since the flood i've caught some
snails and frogs better this than nothing out of the crosswords i found last year in the old
wardrobe at the junkyard the only thing that's left is to continue writing the journal and
listening to the strange radio in two days i will visit the junkyard again maybe i'll finally find
a tape recorder or something that will allow me to record this weird signal here there's some
meaning behind it i'm hungry i'm eating grass and whatever i find in the water i've seen some
strange men between the trees they're not locals they do not hide they were dressed in strange
clothes but i was too far to take a better look besides i'm alone and there were at least three
of them maybe i'm delusional maybe these old ruins aren't empty i found a blank tape and
a broken tape recorder maybe i can fix it and do something with it i've also found some other
useful things i've written them down and left them for father later i don't have the strength
to wear them all on my back is it possible that the radio tower emits the strange signal it's
been a couple of years since it's been turned over the woods have blocked the way to it
but no other signal reaches this place from outside it must be that tower i need to take
a break from this radio i hear this voice everywhere it's strangely familiar i can't
get it out of my head okay so i can't the radio tower i can't get to the radio tower
but the junkyard read this now where's the compressor parts the junkyard so that's like
down here well i need like my item of notes not this one this one scrap metal an old compressor
was f which is up here but is that up this way is it my in it right now or is that like up here
it's probably the map yeah that makes sense so i'm gonna go i'm gonna get the compressor
sticking with the plan or junkyard or map i mean the junkyard is right here
you might as well just take a look at it see what's over here junkyard it's a map of the
junkyard okay f so we need to go in the top right corner junkyard like up here oh i have to dig
need point three have point four is this the right spot though there's another spot over there
do it oh yes got it do this one too wait what else is up here uh f is scrap metal and old
compressor and clothes clothes broken axe empty bottles some fine quality clothing at h
f b one of these is h which one the one right below me a b c a b c d e where's that one
do i even have to do this again i don't i can't do it again i got what i needed i got what i came
for time to go fix the compressor nice go get the fine clothes like i have to dig don't i have to
dig in here i don't i my shovels i have to don't have to dig what are you talking about
don't i i my my shovel don't work no more i'm running out of space too i guess i pick it
no will you what the fuck happened to it okay i'll make a lock pick wait rocket wreckage
oh no oh no it's him he didn't make it he did not make it i'm gonna make some heals
an inventory what the fuck do i get rid of the stumps i have to get rid of this lock pick i
just made who cares that's sad this long gun take the scrap i want this long barrel let's just like
see what this does who cares long barrel weapon part scrap compressor i need the stumps though
and it either nails the wood for the weapon part this is worth so much money
nice all right i'm out that's sad he didn't make it unfortunately i have to go this way
all right come on let's do this i can search wait what i can search both wreckages what the fuck
i got no room for it though what is this thing tubular magazine i don't have any space for this
i just gotta come back i'll come back later it's getting late i gotta get out of here i can't i
have two complete items that i was looking for so bad it's not like it's gonna fly away
that's true that's that's terrible did runner already yes i did hello no just don't i can't
take it complete this down here bear trap watch it grabbing the nails that's all i'm looking for
right now board up the stuff live another day and then i'm gonna fix the compressor
and upgrade the barracks i remembered this time examine where is it over here let's just put this
away first let's upgrade the workbench i need three wires of course i do i can make a shotgun
now though that actually doesn't break okay let me go let's do that let's put the compressor in
the rag no give me the what am i doing i need to make this wood i need gas i need pliers later
hunting rifle can stay i need batteries
all right i have no idea what's gonna happen we'll find out cool six hours yeah um we're just gonna
go till this is done i feel like i it's i've got a little more i've got like probably a couple
hours maybe but we're just gonna go to this is done i think that's the best idea all right so
compressor here you are repair working compressor i could refill any empty oxygen tanks here
i don't have any empty oxygen tanks oxygen tanks rusty oxygen tanks they're useless
well shit okay i've got my weapons i'm almost ready to board up for the night i'm gonna cook this
store the weapon parts you know keep the wood because i needed to board up in case something
bad happens i don't need this many nails though not like it matters still have heals
batteries put the rags away and it's time it's time beater beater what are you what are you guys
saying peter i'll switch it on now no i don't need to do that now yeah yeah just do it now no
it's a waste yeah it's a waste it's a waste it's a waste it's a waste it's a waste it's a waste
let me make sure everything's ready to go so this door is boarded boarded boarded traps traps
trap exploding barrel thing over here same scenario gonna hang out down here put this back
don't want light coming through so that's a little bit of light going through i think that's good
it's that that's fine all right this is gonna be moved over here actually that's all right right
there here we go you know what board it up i don't want this walking in here close the doors
board it up i didn't cook the i didn't cook the mushroom i did not cook it i did not this time
i did not i did not cook the mushroom i did not i did not did i really say it like that i don't
think i did come on why am i not saying anything because my brain can only do one thing at a time
uh i have to concentrate when i'm doing something like this i can't speak i love
cynical germa what do you mean i'm incredibly optimistic i'm incredibly i'm incredibly
optimistic about this i i've got it cynical i'm not cynical cynical enfp all right just don't move
in fact if anybody comes in here they get in the axe anyways maybe they won't
i might get spawned on like three times and then the bear i'm just shooting the barrel
so while we sit here at night what's the game plan for tomorrow game plan for tomorrow is wires
to upgrade i need to get oxygen tanks i'm gonna say maybe ted out this way take a look over there
all right here we go this is where they come up finish looting the rocket yeah maybe i don't
maybe i don't maybe i don't need it what was in there that i needed i've got a hunting rifle
the thing is sick into the stream voice no i'm playing this until i'm done
no i'm not into the stream what are we talking about i've just got some eye goopies or you know
sometimes you just sit here and you get a blink a few times all right this is where it starts
i gotta get ready i have not heard anything yet i think i got some good light drainage over here
so that's probably why i fatigue are we gonna go a full night without anybody showing up to our
front door this would be phenomenal this would be great i'd be really happy about this don't spend
one single round swing an axe once in the swamp late game that would be fantastic let me get the
random dumb roll the one time in the nearly 20 hours i've played this game four a.m it's not
gonna happen six a.m hey come on over here i've been here trying to come find me nothing we were
250 dollars very cool oxygen tanks always buy scrap always buy things always buy magazine always
buy bullet always buy pill but wires too shit i fucked up a little bit here i may have fucked
up a little bit here what's shiny down here there are some footprints on the floor
the door handle is covered with slime
excuse me excuse me dead musician holy shit he's got a huge bag
he's got a giant bag this is awesome oh my god i'm gonna put so much stuff in here can i drag
him up here this is perfect whoa is that not supposed to kill that person what well this is
still very useful to me oh well there's a lot of stuff i can't wait to spread out my stuff okay
i need three oh thanks to the stone too shiny stone what's wrong with my brain
okay what else do i want to sell i'm gonna make i'm gonna make the single shot shotgun are you
ready three two one no i was waiting for someone to say something wait i was waiting for someone
to convert just to tell me not to do this okay good to know all right i'm gonna sell this and
now i'm gonna get some wires what do you need for the better shotgun i need to upgrade this
stupid workbench first give me the wires they shake their head no we'll take a shiny stone
instead i need wires i need one wire and i can upgrade the workbench probably for the last
time one more wire i don't have one that sucks big time um store that clip three shots in the
hunting rifle a bunch of wires at the rocket rocket ship time yeah we'll go we'll go let's
go loot everything at the rocket ship store everything i get to repair the shovel though
don't i yes i do okay take that with me i got my these this is overkill for heels don't need the
nails don't need the rags don't need those pills i need i don't even need the second clip in fact
i don't i don't even need i don't even the batteries either medium caliber bullets i'm
want as much space as i can let's go we're going right back to the junkyard i'm gonna try to just
loot a bunch of shit let's do it i remember being actually mad at germa for putting sun chips low
yeah but we both don't have to like the same stuff that's all right
that means we're different you know if you love sun chips
but i mean we can still you know we can still be friends i don't have any lock picks i didn't bring
any wasting time shut up
germa who would win in a fight you and me every time i don't care who it is
all right let's go open this chest i want the goodies inside that's a lot of stuff
a lot of stuff that i'm shouldn't i shouldn't be taking right now just take the drugs right now
okay just keep moving almost the junk oh sorry junkyard why is it the loudest thing in the whole
game that is that's louder than everything else in the whole game junkyard and i got my shovel
the doctor turns his mud-covered head towards the sun and freezes then he spreads his arms
along his sides warm a chunk of mud falls down on his exposed tongue he chews it slowly and
swallows it with satisfaction i'll take the embryo it's might as well try to level up
before it's over the doctor puts the muddy hand into his mouth premises and pulls out a yellow
tooth he puts it into his pocket of his torn trousers the tooth falls through a hole he does
not notice this the doctor begins staring at a nearby tree trunk paying no attention to the
blood flowing between his lips the doctor glances at me he tilts his head sideways lost in thought
after a moment he extends his hand towards me as if wanting to grab me by the throat but stops
he freezes slowly he bends down and grabs a thick branch from the ground he starts biting the bark
off of it he swallows the bark with an effort but also great satisfaction he places the stick
among the other sticking out from the mud-covered head out from his mud-covered head
doctor approached me i can feel him embracing me why am i letting him do this i hear his horse
breath and smell his odor i hear his whisper soon very soon not long from now
fucking alien oh wait it's back to the rocket ship i have things to dig this one says sea on it
what what does what does sea have gun parts tubular magazine sparts i could sell the watch
and here we go again life sucks in this game because you have to pick up every item
there the wire is son you found him son good work thank god i i can't i i'm full again
drop the rags i mean i could make a healing thing but what am i picking up instead
all right i want to dig where is the fancy clothes some fine quality clothing is h
down here wait wait wait where's c in relative to that c is there so i have to go across here
there's h fine quality clothes let's get them shit it's just expensive fabric
oh i can't it's i have to leave oh and i have a full inventory money i know i know but i have
so i just get rid of this meat do i even care all right i feel bad for you but i
i'm keeping the embryo what about the mushrooms the shell i need two of these for armor but
shotgun shell the rags the wood the logs all right i got it good backed home because i have
no more space the title is wrong what do you mean craft something i'm not i know i need these wires
no i don't have enough room kill the doctor not yet he doesn't deserve it right now we are gonna
run fast it should be dark wood two this is dark wood three well you guys have not been keeping
up with the with the stream dark wood this is dark this is dark wood stream number three
i've been keeping up i didn't skip two i did two the first copy is two yeah dark wood in brackets
one copy of dark wood is the second shortcut this is the third stream so the black it's three in
the bracket all right i need to do this now i have it let's upgrade the workbench finally it's
taken like 12 hours to get this far do it hunting rifle double barreled shotgun i need a second
barrel back to the junkyard let's go quickly cook this stuff back to the junkyard cook these back
to the junkyard i need the gun parts i've got my shovel i got my heels let's go hurry up
what's the next workshop upgrade good question another one of those pliers that i don't have
double barreled shotgun okay let me cook this shit then okay put the watch away
i need that i will never not be able to use that all right i'm almost halfway there back to the
junkyard quickly i need another barrel is uptime broken twitch i think is broken there's a lot of
issues on twitch right now i don't know um i know that they have like the view issue so maybe the
uptime issue is there as well i don't know what's this no it's a guy's head just don't i don't don't
pick up anything just focus on the task this is part of the task i need scrap get to junkyard
free money okay gun parts is what one of them said what's that damn entrance okay so what
did i leave on the ground here doctor is gone i can take this now i can take them both for now
gun parts at c barrel what are you dumb that's a gun part to you what about e planks nails don't
want useful scrap metal gun parts ropes tape antlers some tools what about e this is g that's
a just not a c that's a g that's g i thought uh we're c then all the way over here oh that's
annoying hope i have enough stability in my which one of these is c a c is right here give me the
mushroom here we go c damn it i'll be able to get it tomorrow though because he sells it doesn't he
all right we're good can i take anything else from the crash can take the watch that's expensive
useless i can take this expensive some more gas good day it was a good day back to bed as we used
to say just here to tell you that your mixer move is almost set up can't wait to hear from you
i ain't ever moving platforms ever again so uh that ain't gonna happen i did i did the i did
youtube for like six years moved to twitch it's been about four years four and a half on twitch
just before this is where this is where i stay i ain't digging up the foundations and moving to
another streaming platform these are both boards okay cool cool cool cool cool how we doing on gas
we're doing all right cook i have so much stuff to sell i'm gonna have
two grand from this trader can i upgrade this axe again oh man oh man yeah inflict more damage
more durability or more damage that means this pretty much means up damage all right i need four
rocks tell me to make sure to remind to get those tomorrow shiny stone wood let's get what i need
to board i'm all done i'm all done i did that already i've got my trap set up i just want to
make sure i'm good to go i've got heels do you see what i'm talking about everyone thought i was
crazy the shovel away magazine is fine i'm gonna make the armor time to shack up for the night
that's wrong it's also wrong kill the lights in here watch out it's back there okay
maybe a little bit more over this way come on in oh man sometimes you gotta stretch
just stretch it up can you please write how you like your eggs cooked in descending order best to
worst sure s tier s plus no match completely unmatched is a hard-boiled egg that has a jammy
yolk but not too soft jammy but not too soft and it has to be hot i'm talking right out of the
boiling water you peel it a little bit of salt hot yep s plus tier over hard no over medium
but like almost almost too hard very close incredibly close so from there a fresh
hard-boiled egg right there bang s somewhere at a is a over medium egg like fried on a flat top
i don't like over easy over easy is down somewhere at f i do not like a runny egg it gets everywhere
i it's it's not to me it is not cooked it's not fully cooked all the way but let me hold on
let me i know people are probably gonna get really upset about this but let me try to read right what
i'm trying to say here so there is over easy which is good where the egg is cooked but there
are people that do over easy where they they only cook the part of the egg that is the white part
that's i don't like that and you it's literally raw in the middle if raw egg in the middle is
not appetizing to me at all um an over medium egg with a jammy middle bingo that's a also on
the a tier i would put a poached egg poached egg sits right up next to over medium in fact poached
egg might also be up at s in fact i'm gonna have to say it is yes exposed by kim what did kim say
let me expose what what what what did she say poached his s yes poached egg on toast
he likes his egg well done no i like it i like it like like 10 to 12 minutes and hard boiled
where scrambled um scrambled is like b i think medium no no i like it like over medium to over
hard she said you like your eggs completely raw that's that's absolute horseshit no you guys are
that's that's a joke blue egg rare eggs there's no such thing as a rare egg you either cook an egg
or you don't all right you um you got me all twisted here hard boiled egg is at top fresh out
of the boiling water crack open peel rinse salt maybe a little bit of pepper and then blah over
medium best egg that's on the flat top cooked over medium sunny side up looks cool in pictures
no thank you i don't get that cartoon shit out of here looks it looks cool in pictures um scrambled
eggs are somewhere around the b tier i love them i'll lead them i love eggs by the way by the way
an f in my egg tier list is pretty high because i love eggs let's just click on the link i make
you ovaries eggs all the time no but you but you don't know you you do it hold on you do it in a
way that's not the egg is not like raw in the middle it's runny but it's it's malleable it's
jammy it drains out it's not just like water people do the water shit where you it's water in there
over media you know you know that over medium is my favorite you know that okay kim is over medium
my favorite where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it oh shit it's
moving around everything over medium is my favorite eggs you know that over hard over medium my two
favorites hard-boiled eggs are fantastic also something that's very important to know is
i'm i'm like a i'm like an undercooked weirdo i don't like undercooked food i don't order
hamburgers unless they're medium or above i don't like eating undercooked food i don't
like eating raw food unless it's sushi which exception what just happened
somebody's got like eaten outside all right here they come here we go this is it this is it this
is it this is it medium rare is is correct cook i don't like i don't like a bloody meaty steak
i don't like i don't like like red blood in my hand come here
is dead i don't like rare stuff i don't it just tastes gross to me i'm sorry people think
well you gotta eat that steak rare eat a medium rare steak it's gotta be rare excuse me sir i'll
throw up i'll puke if you hand that to me if i if you if you told me to eat a rare steak i would
throw up you do you cook your fruits before you eat them rare steak has a shitload raw meat has
an insane amount of foodborne illnesses e coli tapeworms worms bacteria viruses you it's not
like eating a strawberry rare is cooked enough to kill it i don't buy it sorry medium rare okay
i i wouldn't be upset about that i'd be like okay this is fine medium rare that's fine rare
though i've i've seen kim eat a rare piece of steak and man oh man sometimes that shit looks
like purple in the middle no i want mine to be cooked all the way all the way through
that's called flavor i don't like the taste of fucking blood i don't like the taste of like
wet watery blood i don't what i don't like blood when you eat like the steak oh cool look at those
juices it's a juice it's steak doesn't have it's blood you're eating blood and membrane fluid
the red shit in there at blood and membrane fluid it's fucking it's it's like all kinds of weird
gross fucking fluids oh look at this chat fucking flying right now guys i ate a i ate a rare steak
like fucking an hour ago when i went on brb i ate it with my bare hands i bit with my teeth and i
was like i'm a fucking animal now we can move on though i'll tell you i'll just very very clear
make it very clear rare red meat is gross i'm not it's just my opinion my opinion i'm not a
vegetarian i am not like a vegan i just think that rare i eat red meat all the time although
i'm trying to cut back on it because low fog map and garlic and all that you know that you understand
rare red meat fucking gross me out just like how a eating of an undercooked egg or
that's why i really need to explain my food preferences wrong onion wrong opinion he's a
las vegas he's a las vegan las las vegan wrong a pin onion i love onions so i can't have them
right now like wait didn't i just okay so i don't know where we got on this from but somebody said
you don't like sun chips and i'm like that's yeah that's all right because we both have we both have
different tastes and everybody agreed with that all of you guys agreed at the same time oh yeah
you know i if you don't like sun chips whatever you like pringles i like the pizza pringles they're
my favorite sour cream and not you fucking lazy banana chips those are my favorite everybody has
their own opinion the second you tell somebody that you don't like raw steak i thought i knew
this guy but i wouldn't even care if he was buried six feet under is what potato what's the
difference chat war have you have you fuckers don't eat steak meat meat snob opinion is wrong
there are no such thing as wrong opinions on food if all right what well let me ask you this
what do you guys think wait everybody quiet this is important this is super important i gotta ask
your question everybody everybody quiet for a second this is very important shit have you ever
heard have you ever heard of worm cheese it's the most expensive finest cheese in the world
it is the most expensive shit it's the most expensive cheese on earth it's incredibly delicious
but it's it's it's it's covered in worms there are fucking maggots and meal worms in it is that
would you eat it eat it it's that that's that that food is illegal
hey wait wait is it actually banned is it actually illegal food that food is illegal it's banned
my point is if you think that's i think that's gross right it's gross but if somebody eats that
and they like it if somebody eats worms all right forget about the cheese part if somebody just eats
worms do you think that that's gross your point just got decimated not entirely is eating meal
worms disgusting what do you say yes or no if anybody in here says yes don't tell me i don't
like raw steak rare steak absolutely yes okay well in about 100 years that's going to be your rare
steak eat up because this this this shit ain't going to be a last that long so in like 200 years
enjoy your meal worm patties and your cricket sundaes no one here will be alive
but if you were fuck all right i'm going back to if you all right i mean this this whole thing
came from i don't like rare steak are you going to punch me in the face the next time you see me
in real life fucking steak i would never hurt you 11 hour stream let's go uh i'm still going
we're good i might i might take a water break here if you want i'm gonna punch you in your stomach
because it doesn't like good food i think that's what somebody just said i'm gonna go get some
water i'll be right back
all right dude nobody i'm gonna get some
medium rare water i'll be right back and another thing what he's fired up you guys have you guys
have uh i like having fun conversations with you guys it's fun did you boil your water
actually that's a way to clean it that's a way to kill germs in water as you boil it
but what is this democracy what are you looking at what's why am i looking at this
is steak overrated let me do my vote for this there's only 13 votes on this poll what why is
this hey you gotta take a look at this what everybody thought it's like 12 people voted on
this wrong poll would you eat a rare steak my i'm not my opinion is not that unpopular
that's a 45 percent just saying well done is the only way to go now i what's that hold on let me
hold on hold on oh do you like your steak well done i wouldn't order that but however you like
it it do you like it like that enjoy it i like my steak the way that i like my steak and you yours
right cool okay we we can move on from this conversation i'm not gonna slam both my hands
on the dinner table with the fork and knife in my hand and be like rare steak rare steak rare steak
while you what was i doing this whole that's been on this generator's been all right what was i
doing compressor oxygen tanks journal what do i got for notes radio tower oxygen tanks
i'm just gonna go out and explore man legendary steak what's this candlestick
candlestick where's that dude what's the big backpack dude where's the backpack person
i don't i know he i know they're dead i know i killed him i know why are they not just lying
on the ground still i gotta i think i'm just gonna go wait it's a new day get all the new day supplies
and long barrel long barrel i could give you this nice watch i actually have a i have a ton of
things to sell oh yeah here we go keep that watch sell one two three four tubular magazine
i need to uh oh come on are you serious really well all right um anyways in the meantime i'll
sell this and i will make uh i need to get stones for the axe and buy battery and the egg too yeah
let's go cook the watch i have a watch i got a watch still see let's fill up the tanks and then
i need four stones 12 1600 almost there when's germa 986 gonna come out probably never the
generator yeah you gotta get germa 986 germa 95 is like kind of starting to get a little
a little weird for me okay that's good nothing else to cook no i need stones
and then we need to find an oxygen tank wherever the hell that is two clips that should be a good
lockpick battery okay i got heels don't need to take anything else i don't think so
yeah i get yeah i'm good take these so i can run need rocks and i'm just gonna head out this way
i don't have any really any more info should we go back to back to the village
and maybe talk to the old man i think i'm just gonna go take a look we can build a fence i'm
just gonna i'm just gonna explore over here i'm just gonna take a look that way look for stones
you know i'm just gonna do do a little bit of drugs and move on let's head west
hey stop one head kill now perfect beautiful stones fallen tree a fallen tree it's bark let's
shoot up what's going on in here what was that i can't see oh it's just one of these like weird
trees okay oh another stone where's the dog i'm just trying to explore leave me alone
things those things suck those guys suck they do suck they do they do stones take it for now
i still don't get this stuff does this mean something
means death i don't want that okay structure a little shack hello we're fucked up okay
oh you idiot i couldn't see the line of sight
so close the damn door i need gunner optics let me craft some shit out of here i don't have any
room i don't really care about the stone not really mushroom glade okay holy shit
oh fuck this guy sucks ass this guy's horrendous
okay i'm trying to heal that was just ridiculous just put yellow construction paper on the
what did i have in my inventory let's put this shit away all right new i wish i could just
it's the the wood collecting the wood in the nails is just such a pain in the ass like i
don't want to pick up logs anymore we're 20 hours into the game i still got to pick up
stumps it just makes me upset heck well back out to the to the wilderness to go get all my stuff
again and i'm shooting that thing with a hunting rifle i have heels um i should probably repair
the axe yeah just do it where's uh all my stones are on me all right uh let's go what else am i
gonna do what am i gonna cry about it i don't have any batteries either they were on me bring
out the rifle um that thing is dead it's so far away from here too is my run give me it
that shit's like across the globe don't step in poison either remember this shit
it takes me forever to aim to this accuracy fuck you i think that was the guy that was the guy
no it wasn't it's further back this way it was like right in the open too wasn't it
okay it was down this way where is he
me
keep going we're in the mushroom forest it was that one how many are there
what the fuck die dude there's so many more monsters that are so scary now good thing i
have these weapons i'm just trying to find a house or a new shed or a shack i don't even
okay i knew here's a shed i can't get in here i need to burn it i don't have anything to burn
damn it damn it well the radio tower is down here might as well take a look at it
okay i'm here where's the radio tower what the fuck is this
okay i've been so silent i'm sorry i just don't want to die is the stream live yeah it's called
i'm trying to win this is what a winner looks like this tower the fence has been torn to shreds
all right this is the radio tower can't really get this out of the way if they're sleeping but
any noise can wake them up what what are you talking what do you mean don't make any no i'm
not i'm trying not to make any noise just getting out of there mushroom make noise make noise make
no no what's even down here i think that i think i have there's a snail down here it's the snail
what happened to the snail he got eaten well that's not good oh turn off the light um what
is that on the ground can i climb this is it a snail is it a slug look at the time i'm trying
to go home i just want to step underneath birds heads oh i dinged it it's all right i've already
done my runner oh i'm dead find a nice place to die no way i ain't gonna make it through this one
i could scream i'm not even close i'm gonna get my scream ready and i'm gonna keep running around
running too straight an intense sweet smell of mushrooms fills the air great i hope you like it
i'm gonna get lost in the mushroom forest don't i location found holes holes what do you mean holes
go in i don't know what they are i don't have time to know what they are where these holes go home
i can only go so fast i'm not making it great lake at least i'm finding shit i'm dead i need
to find a great i don't want to die here because this is this is everything has to be so dark in
this game everything's got everything has to be a fucking forest dark wood i know the name's
yeah the game is called dark wood what holy shit that's a dragon i don't want to die in here this
is a bad place what is on me get off me oh my god this stamina is so annoying i just want to go
but i can't because you can only run for like four old shit oh good coming across all kinds of cool
stuff this too where's the house dude i would pay a hundred bucks to increase that stamina bar by
even 20 like where's the stamina upgrades and i can't have a stamina upgrade the whole game
i ran past no i didn't i ran below it and now i have to go out here to pick up these fucking tools
i think i got all these pieces of like dog carcass whatever the hell these are
i'm doing chameleon do i have to actually no i don't have to pick another bad one do i
all right i can be invisible i'm at max level so all meat is now worthless so i don't pick it up
don't i don't need to go to the fridge anymore so therefore take everything out of here that has
anything to do with food and throw it in the trash okay i still need one of these i don't know where
the fuck i'm supposed to go right now do i have any notes or anything i hit the wall of the
junkyard i mean there's mushroom who's in here talk to the old man okay he's making a statement
against me it's called it's not good anymore it's rotten all right come here can i even sell this
i guess i could still sell it uh well they're my rocks but i can't use them you didn't actually
get inside the tower you hit the crow boss and realize you had no time whatever the guy was
that guy was fucked up uh all right let me just do the things i typically do just buy this stuff
i already have that don't let no one pull it wires yeah buy some get some drugs too because i ate
them all okay he just stepped on his babies i didn't mean to i need to go back and get my
stuff all right i'm gonna go talk to the old man let's take a clip take two clips even
let's reload the guns and i'm gonna go see what the hell i need to do because i kind of just i
just like literally i just walked in a straight line this way and died can i burn the radio tower
down instead i'd rather do that i want to save the fucking tree that that trek sucks well it
already is destroyed so somebody already did it okay well that's fine all right let me get my stuff
hopefully not die who's right here is that me is that my body let's go get rid of it
deposit all this crap keep the lock picks i gotta get rid of those but i don't what the hell am i
supposed to do them now uh bottle what else get rid of that uh get rid of the rags get rid of the
scrap okay let's go talk to old man these holes are a shortcut to your base what upgrade the
axe i have the stones right right right uh inflict more damage there it is axe is now better let's
hope it's good all right let's talk to old man i need i need some direction here because i feel
pretty directionless at the moment he's he's just mad at meat and eggs yeah i'm just really pissed
off about poultry just really gets me going it makes me so aggravated where's the entrance
here it's like a weird spot isn't it isn't like a it's like a weird entrance get in here up here
yeah it's this way all right let's go talk to grandpa grandpa help me tell me what i need to
do location of marked holes new journal holes right well i found them all i think i actually
found them all where is he he's like deeper in isn't he what the fuck he's not dead
what the fuck is this thing made out of what
i shot him seven times where did that guy where did that thing even come from
he had the black shells that need light to die oh for the love of god i don't have any bullets
so what i have to shine the light on him oh my god this is painful i i have nothing in my inventory
i have a heal shine a light i don't have a watch anymore either yeah that's great who knows what
time it is right now okay do i don't have any batteries either i don't know thankfully it
keeps those maybe it realized that that would be awful if it took them out so i have to shoot them
oh my god i'm about to exit the game the screen the door seems blocked from the other side
oh he's getting mad well i i don't want to do this i was already doing this here comes the
fucking diarrhea face come on up what happens if you die twice i'm not i'm not even in the same
spot i have no idea where to go i think it's i have no idea shine the light on him shine the
light on him trying to what the fuck is happening right now is this a monster i don't have any
the word thieves has been scratched on the floor i'm not i'm not in the right spot
i'm not in the correct spot i wish i could have a compass or something
don't do it please there it is again all right here's the tractor but where's the entrance that
i went in before i've i'm lost i'm actually lost i don't know where to go there's this part
this is where the backpack was i remember taking this and then did i go this way no i went up
well done steak sensitive no it's fucking hard and i'm at like a nine out of ten for anger
so like i am i am breathing in anger fumes so it's just like right now i don't even have pants on
i had to i had to be gone for this so then from here i went it's just such a blur because
everything looks the same everything's like the same piece of wood and everything's the same
everything's the same come on out do it then stop making flashy sounds and get out here
there's nothing even there it's a joke you know it also might be that i've been playing this game
for eight straight hours like eight straight hours of playing this game i think my brain is
fried where's the one little fucking entrance i hate i'm gonna stand still do i go down from here
down okay going down wasn't i just here nowhere through here through through this through this
two inch space this tiny two inch space is the only place i can go to get down here oh i'm
fucking taking out the guy i'm gonna i'm gonna shoot this fucking monster in the face 50 times
i don't have any all right i'm good you want to see the pants i'm wearing today they're pajamas
i actually just put these on god that thing like what the fuck there's a hold of light on
him until i can drain him and then shoot him but he just is biting your fucking face off the whole
time and the dodge honestly dodge mechanics shouldn't even what's this what's the point of
this it just waste stamina and then please hurt me what happened in the last fucking 30 minutes
of this game did somebody get into my game and like turn the dial to like 10 all right i got two
packages over here that i have to go find even playing for too long i'm gonna try this one more
time and then i'm going to bed reload the gun does he still uh oh i gotta do it with just sheer
will okay i gotta do it with just sheer will i have to kill it with the axe because i don't
have anything else to kill it with i thought that's it a well seasoned something i just wanted to
talk to the old guy why are you still in this room dude go like come come to the cathedral
all right what's over here reload the gun please fuck you get the fuck out of here
oh my god you're the worst can i talk to the old guy now can i please just talk to the old guy
i just want to there's another one of these i don't even know where you came from
but you're dead all right now i want to go like up here somewhere what's in i don't think i even
went in here have i never been in here oh shit there's a lottery ticket okay now uh i want my
backpack the other backpack was was it up or down yeah it's up i already got everything
watch out you down right i think it's time to go to bed i don't think i get i think i've burnt out
completely down to the left of the eye up right down left straight back left up right like down
here that's no that's my i don't see it in here go up right of i i wonder how many people are just
fucking with me right now oh jesus christ almighty just give me my stuff
i don't remember how to get out of here it's like a maze there's one way to go through a whole area
please tell me this is correct i don't care if i don't care is it down from here over here
yay eight hours omega low oh it's just killing me right now all right i've made it what a productive
day of walking in circles trying to find two backpacks on the ground and i'm not even set
up either i got one trap this doorway is in disarray oh i'm dead oh i'm fucking dead guys
not a chance in hell i don't even have the generator turned on let's see if i can kill
stuff with an axe if you die this night then it's gonna bite the save uh i i might have time i think
i have time just to at least get like one thing built up here i mess it's like a kid's fucking
toy box where i just give me wood and nails and i need i need wood it's like it's time to get
rid of some of the toys son this is all the same image to me this is the same image i
why do i have so many logs that's a great question because i spent two days trying to kill
a guy with egg i'm dead no i'm not i'm let's go fucking come on the house get in the house
it's time nails are top right it don't worry i'm gonna kill everything with the axe
ah fix the window i i physically cannot unless i get the nails a senile old streamer kills over
and dies from a calorie induced religious nightmare like i've been fasting for like eight hours
that's fucking funny all right let's go
go
i mean that's a pretty long time do you need a snickers
i can't even eat a snickers low fod map it's in the it's down it's right there
here come the ghosts you can't be serious oh no what if he sees me
oh my god oh you don't kill the banshees
all right uh let me take a second hit and run part two no no no no no i'm not gonna let it get
that far okay so no i'm good i'm good i was using that as an excuse time for bed no can anyone tell
me realistically how much time is left in the game like what how much how much is left for me
to do about like two hours give or take about two hours okay between like 20 minutes and two hours
one to two hours we're gonna do it we're gonna do it so here's what's gonna happen i'm gonna
go eat a piece of lettuce i'm just gonna go i need to walk away from it for a minute we're all good
everything's good i just i'm gonna go eat a piece of pop some i'm gonna eat like two three peanuts
and then let's go i'll be right back don't go anywhere unless i mean it's might be getting
late for you but see you soon all right got some peanuts it was that smoke monster thing
that fucked me all up that was like the catalyst for the near meltdown we're supposed show us your
peanuts they're very boring but if you want to see them again it's just default planter's peanuts
nothing special peanuts are not nuts what do you mean they're legumes
contains a peanut oh here we go oh here we go here we go again here it comes again
i wanted to fucking pee my pants man at that stupid smoke dragon but i didn't get it
it's all good not eating raw peanuts well let's think about like okay it's been like eight
more than eight hours should should i call it no because realistically speaking look at this map
well i'm gonna come back and do this for like an hour and 10 minutes like in a few days
no i'm good to go you gotta go all in sometimes not every time he thinks he's done in two hours
finally some relief for his protein star to bring
me i can't i can't see anything i can't see i can't see anything where am i oh my god this is three
hours if you know what you're doing really wasn't it two hours two hours ago well then i got stuck
for like 40 minutes one to two hours tops okay well whatever let's just do it it's been a long
time since i've had like four streams in a row and like this stream like this where it's more
than eight to ten hours it's been a while we also stopped a fight about steak that's true
just don't get stuck in your own traps that's never not going to happen i could have eaten
i love the protein star brain that's hilarious i mean it's true my diet's been fucked up because
i haven't been able to eat certain things but that was quick did you see that was like a lizard
see okay ready check this shit out guys we're taking a little break watch this one
we think i can do day can't do two in a row my teeth are too big do i eat weird what do you guys
think no not really you eat like a duck ducks are cool i'll take it actually people used to
in high school and a little bit beyond people would call me a bird they would actually say
you eat like a bird because like i i go like this like the i don't know what that why there's a bird
i don't know how that i don't know how that's a bird
i swear to god this is real i'm not making this up but birds don't have hands
i'm just seeing like the pelican he like picks up the seashell on the beach and
did they do that oh i'm fucking having a blast all right i think i think the blood is flowing
back up to my brain again i just keep thinking of everybody that was watching
like 15 minutes ago and i'm walking in circles that's fucking making me laugh so much
i don't know where i am where am i you all right dude you need to take a break
protein starved brain maniac oh that's fucking hysterical walking in circles screaming
i wasn't screaming let me see let me watch a clip of two before i get gone
this germa psycho i was not screaming i was not screaming i may have laughed loudly oh no what if
he sees me i don't know what the fuck was wrong with me it's pretty good water that's not water
is he all right kim go in there and check on him okay one more two more holy shit i
fucking oh wow holy shit this fucking naked guy wasn't kidding when he said that it gives you
superpowers okay hi i'm back so here's what we're gonna do i'm gonna give my stuff okay i got a
minute here i love how his hair gets worse the longer stream goes well because i'm sitting in
like a hot room for like eight and a half hours yeah i'm existing on earth in like a hot environment
everybody hang out for a minute let me take a 50 of them up here too it was look it was all the
same image i'm not kidding every single one of these icons was the same icon rub chewed peanuts
in your hair no stop stop it i'm gonna organize for a second god damn it we're gonna pull this
together it's real easy to fuck me up right now i'm telling i'm gonna be really honest
like it's very simple i got a lot of crap i'm gonna sell this we're gonna take i need to
why do you have so many logs oh my stomach it was too funny okay let's do this let me get do i
anymore gas it's like it's taken over it's the goblin feeder it's taken over i keep thinking
that one comet the calorie induced nightmare okay let me get those nails let's board this place up
i have a couple of traps just make a trap make two or three okay back to reality like we were
40 minutes ago that's fine repair this door this one's okay too okay let's do some traps
here we go and then i want uh one more do i have one more i can do the last one when i come back
so this is all set to go it's good it's ready for a night now i want to go here to the small
cottage anything else i can do with you guys and gas because i'm burning out yeah very good
do a nut chuck i just did so that can be deposited i got three clips this shit has to be sold
battery gas hunting rifle reloaded sell the knife too and i don't need it i got a great axe
and the fabric that should let me just essentially buy shotgun shell just now i'm gonna need it
eventually you're gonna get stomach ache if you eat too many peanuts i mean i i eat peanut butter
all the time peanut butter is like one of my favorite things in the world it's got tons of
protein tons of vitamins for you peanut butter is incredible you know you can live off of peanut
butter do you know that okay i'm ready to go i am prepared i got all my shit i got some heels right
that's one thing i don't have my heels yeah i'm gonna bring some more too just in case
bingo now i want to head down here to the swamp cottage everything's done crunchiest smooth
i don't have anything i don't this is not one of those like here we go he's gonna here we go
no it's uh i like them both but smooth is um i like it better just like i eat it with a spoon
incorrect it's okay all right let's go check out and see what this is this guy with the mask on
i need a mask i need a mask holy shit i need a mask let's go that's the power of peanuts
i must just drop my mouse this has to be a way higher still have this sorry it is that
i was wondering what the fuck that was it's little tendrils okay remember i didn't know what was
going on there now i know i just have to see and look where the things were coming from
and i was able to focus on it very clearly because that's the power of peanuts
look at i'm already back all right where's this cottage right here no down further creamy or
crunchy i like creamy peanut butter better than crunchy it's not i love crunchy peanut butter
but if i had to choose it would be creamy i like it better on sandwiches if you spread uh peanut
butter and fluff it's an all-time classic one of my favorite sandwiches pretty much ever when i was
a kid i have a soft spot i have a soft spot for peanuts um a second here damn you guys take a lot
of hits i'm just keeping the hunting rifle out i mean i'm here how do i get in here
what the hell have you done i thought he was in front of me
i really thought he was in front of me that scared the fucking shit out of me
is there a better way i can get up there here we go gas tank watch out for that thing you got a lot
of these what okay just me that's me doing that the cottage is surrounded by a barricade
made out of old furniture and rusty barbed wire probably stolen from some fence that's a lot of
scrap metal what are you doing to me is it one down here too barricaded i still don't understand
that's another trap i'm so i'm panicking about these things i don't need to be panicking
those things are not that big of a deal yes they are yes they are yes they are are they
i still don't understand what they what what are they doing when my back is turned they
destroyed generator what should i do this did one come up through the soil
am i getting pranked intense smell of flowers fills the air i need a key thank you for fixing
our generator you can come in what elephants the air is filled with a suffocating sweet odor
of rot who are you the woman is wearing a heavy ruined coat her voice is suppressed by the cracked
gas mask she's wearing can't you speak did someone take away your voice two children high behind the
woman one eye in me scared standing there other one scared enough from around here would recognize
you we may keep ourselves but i know everyone here i would never forget you a mug can't make
the joke i don't have a mug in the room the younger child eyes your gob looks like that because of this
fiendish air do you know but you can't speak because you didn't keep your mouth shut when
walking through the woods the trees and plains are simply beautiful here and the bushes bloom
gorgeously this time of year but don't let the charm of this land deceive you the devil lurks
the devil lurks between these trees and he gets to you through your mouth and nose
so can i just make the devil mad the older child's grasp on his mother's hand tightens
he does not lift his gaze from one of his hunts walls and you're just gonna stand there i know
you want something you leper demon you're not getting anything from us i don't trust you leper
gob do you hear me i don't trust you anyone who breathes this filthy air the woman stares at me
intensely through the cracked mask did you take my marsenek was it you who kidnapped him talk
no that cannot be the woman stares at the floor her greasy black hair drops down on her mask
it's impossible stupid child he went out never came back he was on about how his granny will take
him mushrooming i have no idea where he i told him he cannot go outside i told him that he the
devil i told him that the devil will find him take off his mask and take him away i would look for
him but she lowers her head even more as if observing the dead fly stuck to her coat you want
my trust bring my marsenek back my stupid marsenek find him and bring him home here's the key to his
room he was spending a lot of time there recently maybe you'll be able to find something there that
will lead you to him what do you think about this road i remember this road the woods devoured it
about three years ago used to lead to our village i walked it to school the road home my road home
home something exploded in the northern part of the swamp made the ground tremble
devil knows what it was i see you're curious investigate it if you have a death wish i think
it happened in the junkyard oh i've been there already lady the youngest child hidden behind the
woman's back until now finally finds the courage to make a small step towards me one little bear
ate a little soup then another one came in quiet the woman smacks the boy in the back of the head
the punches so hard the hood of his rubber cloak lands on his mask's visor
not now i'm not in front of a stranger it's just like these lunatics who run around the
woods searching for god knows what there used to be more of them i guess most of them starved to
death i remember when they appeared not far from here must have been around two years ago around
two dozen of them they were led by these three weirdos dressed in old rags they set up camp at
the marsh there between the trees they watched our house stared right into my windows the oddities
i thought they wanted to kidnap my children or harm them in some way but when the night
fell i lost sight of them there was no one there in the morning apart from these two here and
marsenek there's one more boy of mine my precious darling a blessed child the woman rests her hands
on the oxygen tanks the children standing beside her this love fills our tanks with clean air for
this we are forever grateful to him for the clean air for the oxygen tanks for these beautiful masks
and the book in which the devil after just making the devil mad has revealed his true image along
with his evil plan my son took it away from the trees of his own hands brought it here to us
okay i'll be taking those masks now lady quest time junk okay use the kid's key odd looking
mushroom old doormat drawings creepy mushroom drawings in an old doormat an old doormat i
think someone uses it as a bed fold small bundle is a map a simple map scribbled on a piece of
crumpled paper judging by the drawings it was made by a child it's very inaccurate i will only
be able to find the approximate position of the spot indicated on the map somebody open up wow
head for me i made another fucking wow reference i don't even play that game what the fuck is it i
don't care where is it i don't care just tell me where it is i don't care wait my generator is still
on okay where is it mushroom glaze where though just like exact location i want exact location
here right here right here the map is randomly generated oh wonderful all right time to go find
kid and get the mask turn on smart clicks not a bad idea genius that's it okay i have a good
general idea of where it is thank you appreciate that i'm gonna say it's right here looking for a
kid all right i still have some time i'm gonna go up i'm gonna go this way anyways i'm going for it
let's go right now wait this this is this is on them right should i turn it off that's on them
right that's on them all right let's go see if i can find them right now quickly go back home
i'm literally right there i'm gonna just try it we're going power peanuts right now
this shit is crap i don't even why i'm picking it up anymore all right here we go finding the
kid in the mushrooms at 16 i'm out looking for a kid looking for a kid okay here i am looking for
a kid and he leads right here come on right here right here right here he's right here there he is
what footprints footprints what what whose footprints are they where do they go footprints
but where are you just do them all do them all quick do them all right now it stacks it stacks
it stacks it stacks oh oh my god it stacks where's this kid fuck is this kid where the
fuck are you get over here come on kid i don't get all day everything inside the car just covers
mushrooms floor even though it's like hey hey what's up colors goo seeps in the ceiling what's up kid
mushroom granny an old woman sits on a weathered rocking chair her sleep is deep and peaceful a
handful of ripe mushrooms grow up from her thick hair wake up the old lady slowly opens her eyes
from when she stares into space with an absent gaze finally she becomes aware of my presence
wait you're not her empty eyes now take on a questioning expression i didn't expect yes she
throws a nervous look at the door on her right kids in there she then gazes around the mushroom
infested house she relaxes a bit i suppose you won't tell me what you want and you want something
since you're standing here in front of me point your finger at them what are you doing get away
i bite into her the mushroom juice squirts onto my face i feel the woman's feeble hands trying to
push me away but oh i'm my hunger is too great i bite her face i swallow a chunk of her body
what the fuck matt hey look at these drawings whoa hey what look at these drawings you got here son
wow oh hey i just want to help you here i'm not gonna i just i want to get you out of here son
will you come with me son boy standing under a wall overgrown with enormous mushrooms
he's visibly scared his lush mop of hair veils of restless wide open pair of eyes the kid is
whispering as if reciting something under his breath the boy cowers and presses his back against
the softball which starts to ooze with a white goo hey just hold on there
the boy is terrified slowly he slumps down from the wall to the ground curling into a ball
the murmur turns into a loud recitation little bear ate a bowl of soup then another bear came
and there were two four little bears made a sudden poo wow on came the fifth and took a little bow
you ain't very good at counting son the boy on your back and lead him to his family
when i take the boy into my arms he starts screaming reciting the rhyme over and over
there has been a sudden pile along in the fifth and took a little bow it's going to be a long
journey as we pass the remains of the old lady the boy stops reciting i feel his hands tightly
clutching my coat granny as i cross the cottage's threshold i can hear him sobbing quietly
you brought back my child the woman leads towards the boy marson where have you been
the boy stares at the ground in silence come here marsonic walks towards the woman nervously
plucking at his old torn sweater look at you where's your mask and the gas tank from your
gracious brother his love protects us it fills our lungs with clean air and this is how you thank
him young man your childish behavior made him very very angry now we'll have to apologize to
him for your stupidity the two kids standing behind their mother flinch the woman grabs the
boy's hand and disappears in the hallway after a while she comes back with an oxygen tank take it
it's a thank you it's a tank you hilarious um okay it will you're gonna pull out like
fucking dad humor right now it'll protect you from this devilish air the devil's breath
and other evils lurking in this foul place it's the only thing i have and the only thing i can
give you the tank is a little rusty but it seems intact on the side i could see some
unintelligible scribblings the valve opens with a little resistance but i don't hear the hiss of
air it's empty do not open the valve without need you will only waste the clean air she pushes my
hand away from the valve and close it hastily may it serve you well i need to find oxygen
time to go home now where is oxygen take the oxygen back the granny could have made you a
sweater then another bear came and they were two four little bears all right i gotta leave
back to the hideout i can't believe you could eat people in this game that's kind of insanity
this way be ready for anything i'm not getting stuck out in this goddamn wasteland by the way
uh run your calorie deficient brain saw granny and only thought run
they eat i'm i'm currently running so that was the thing that came out yeah remember i killed the
guy in the village for being a cannibal well i didn't have very good influences here this ain't
my house is it what happened down here oh they broke the wall okay the fucking every time there
is no cooking anymore generator has been running this entire you were right i didn't believe you
then i should have it was running all day oh fuck i got plenty of gas it's okay
i got time and the room's all set up anyways oh yeah that was a good nut chug easy i know you
guys are fucked up all right i don't have time for this grab a few nails all right let's go turn
it on i gotta go in from the other side compressor yeah i know i figured out that i might from
whatever probably what it was looks good okay so now i've got trap trap light we're gonna do trap
here i didn't bring one with me just gonna have to just get good at the game sounds fun to me let's
do it it's honestly better if i don't have it i know i know it's been a little while
oh oh no shit oh whoops the lipstick the lipstick joke is this 24 hours no probably another one
hour i got gas tank i got compressor and i'll get oxygen in the tank and then i don't know we'll see
it don't want to have dry lips so i'm not reading that one let me not react to some of these
oh i thought it was gonna be a huge strike i really actually get like i didn't think it like a sound
thing from my stream deck so i can have like fucking lightning sounds and i'm angry with chat
where is it that sounds like a that sounds like a big one coming in down here
no this is my time this is my time to do it
that sounds like a big one this is my time to explode this this is it don't move it's been here
for like four hours he's in he's dead holy shit close it close it close it close it
oh stop please you gotta be kidding me i try i was so careful i was so careful i was so careful
i was so careful oh fuck can you see me through this get out of there get out of the room
kill it heels heels heel heel heel heel heels heel heel heels heels heels heels heels heels
heels do a heel heel heeling heels i don't have a heel do a heel gotta get a heel heeling heel
am i gonna heal i don't have a heel heel nope moth scream double power come on double healing
my god holy shit that was wild okay let's fill up the tank got my it's in the workshop
where's my tank let's see empty oxygen tank see this doesn't i refilled all the empty oxygen tanks
okay a tank filled with oxygen okay so if it's just oxygen it won't be good
go back to the village of hell that's where i was planning on going not yet though do i have
any more bullets i have two more bullets for this i didn't i didn't make it to the shotgun
but i think i'm gonna make a shotgun antidote no no don't make it don't make it stop making things
bring the heels like these okay i still have do i still have armor i do not that's not good
how many clips do i have let's check this out i'm gonna repair everything buy what i can
let's go with magazine bullet and shotgun shell i'm gonna make a shotgun i don't think i'm gonna
make it to that i'm gonna make it i'm gonna i think i think it's am i at end game here
i'm about to click this pretty much pretty much okay i'm making a shotgun i have enough slot i have
a bunch of slugs i'm gonna use it single shot yeah but i can reload it let me make sure i'm
ready to go this game is so advanced so many cool things to do in this game i got plenty of heals
i don't i didn't make i never came across a machine gun prepare everything even if i don't
think i'm gonna use it can't be for upgrade any upgrades so they can't do upgrades to the hunting
rifle nothing everything's done shotgun uh here are my bullets i have any more clips
not no i have three clips three shots in the hunting rifle seven shots in the shotgun the
oxygen tank some peels some drugs all right am i coming back here or am i about to finish this
game go to the tree and burn it come back one night okay so i've got what i need let's just
make sure that this place is not going to fall apart completely i'm going to use all of my
materials that i have are you ready for this are you ready for me to fuck this whole thing up
you're in my house now oh this whole time i played this game the ups and the downs
the the the frustration sometimes the anger the fun the ingenuity the great game
this whole room is going to be a trap and i'm going to stuff myself in the corner
and good luck you monsters because you're going to get in this room so let's strategically do this
it's going to be this room i need an absolute guaranteed path to be able to come back in here
the escape route is going to be straight up out i need to bring this the lamp is going to be right
in the middle here's your free bingo space and then i'm thinking we got here's my safe spot
they come in through here they come in through here they need to be just like boom boom boom boom
boom but i need a i need a space like this to be able to run this way and walk this is the escape
up here i'm going to leave this here here we go so if i need to go this way let's start
with here and i'm going to give us i'm going to give myself plenty of room do it you know
like i'm preparing for the final goddamn battle i'm preparing all right okay then here so this
is my i bet this is still safe this is still safe here right i have to hug the wall this chair has
to get out of here times three what is the triple jupiter stop with the jupiters i want to watch the
stream what the fuck then look away from chat all right just don't how many more do i have
i think i have like three or four more one two three four can't make any more only four right
okay these have got to be in a good spot i can now no longer leave from here whoever decides to
come in this room good luck you ain't fucking making it okay it's good it's safe this is going
to go in the corner i want to build a door good spot for that lamp this is still i could use a
little it could use a little work but fucking who cares they're not going to make it anyways
that door needs to be sealed so does this one so i have to come in through this way
seal this door seal this door yeah this one gets fortified this one does not it's the only way i
can get in let's go fortify the door holy fuck i must have walked in the room three planks
do i even have any planks i did not all right i
sorry i got a plan it's all right i've got a plan and you're gonna be part of it i swear
that's pretty good impromptu dutch shit fucking nine hours into a stream that was shit let me
tell you something arthur i have never seen somebody like you trying to come and tell everybody
that they can't now i'll have to tell you that's just now turning into mr satan a little bit
it started all right but then i just went into this that's kind of how it starts i guess
pretty good mr satan from nine hours bald get that guy out of here can't do it fast enough
all right uh what was it doing stop getting distracted have to keep more peanuts i need
some peanut power pretty good pretty good stuff all right the plan is to put these up here
because who cares i don't even need a door who needs doors when you've got barrels of liquid
destruction check this out oh what's that did you come over here oh no watch out for you
you just do this home alone home alone but macaulay colkin is like vengeful because he
stepped on a mousetrap too many times so the whole house is mousetraps let's get the final
battle secured oxygen tank my watch heavy healing handgun my um my where's my my never mind
i was gonna do my fucking bow my this and then i was gonna say and my axe really close to the
microphone too late tried thought about it you can't mind astute me for a joke that didn't happen
i'm already telling you that it didn't happen because i didn't do it shit uh shotgun's going
in here hunting rifle here i have plenty of guns hunting rifles just put it together where's my
where's my flashlight is that i'm gonna bring the gas somebody told me bring gas so i said okay
i guess i will bring this too where's my heels okay i've got healing pills that are gonna go
in there first okay store everything else i'm ready to go it's time time to end this
it's time watch healing ammo batteries lock picks big weapons oxygen tank gasoline more
i don't need these gas tank let's close this to the tree how much gas does have fill that up
do i have peanut sweats oh i'm sorry it's not disgusting meat disgusting meat sweats
meat disgusting what happened i thought i was getting attacked the last vegan that's me i
realized that i've been realizing that that's one step away from being like i'm a bunny rabbit let's
burn this tree down what do you guys say what's going on with this what are you linking right
right that's exactly what i'm talking about i'm ready let's go i'm gonna remember where i need to
go nice bingo i'm ready just get the rifle at the ready i remember where to go
i'm going full on peanut jacks mode red shell just gifted 10 community subs thanks a lot red
shell appreciate that thanks for the 10 community subs holy shit it got late too it's almost 11 30
pacific that's late for a lot of you guys thanks for sticking around guys really hope you're
enjoying the stream all right i went the wrong way all right didn't i yeah because this is going
too far up do the run so i don't have to do this um okay is it did i have it right the first time
where's that little piece this again well like actually though like i'm so confused how this
was that this one like tiny is for was it did i miss it down there's like a little spot where
you can go in is the yeah the auction tank is full it's like isn't it right here yeah it's right
here right and then down here um we quick do a nut chuck am i am i this way off no oh no i was
way off it was way off yeah it's all the way down here okay let's get in here i'm gonna put a
battery in just because i don't feel like having to die on me if one of those monsters comes out
all right old man is old man down or old man up this way oh i this is where i could have done
the digging damn it all right i gotta be prepared for this because there's probably some things
scary here this is the tree old man's up here right other room which room is he in
basement hatch wait what he's not here wait i was already here i'm down here a hole in the
wall of the basement he must have been made by the growing roots
i throw the throw the gas tank in there where's this motherfucker's brain is what i want to know
who's there what do you want leave cellar under the tree my feet are slowly sinking in the soft
woggy floor i can barely move someone's holding me by the ankles what i have the oxygen tank in
here okay so wait how do i burn it what giant barrel a huge rusty barrel judging by the smell
still gives a lot of gasoline i need a match what if i how do you explode something underwater
i don't have any weapons or anything do i nothing another one huge barrel gasoline
that person's very big that person's huge um why are these people so big what was in there
there what's going on axe oh no are you serious just blow it up why is this here i could blow it
up right barricade makes you barricade blocking the entrance of the basement and uh someone is
something trying to break through from the other side what do i do anything hell do you think you're
doing wait you'll kill us all stop it what's in here the item is no longer usable i need to
repair it that makes you barricade what the fuck what what do i do what do i do get me back out of
here you're supposed you're not supposed to die what the fuck am i am i back on do i get to do it
again let's do it again i could i couldn't go down the way what the fuck is happening
now don't pile of empty rotten crates overgrown with roots oh that was just a that was just a
dream valve the barrel's valve is rusted but it seems to be working judging by the smell that's
gasoline inside gasoline starts to leak out of the barrel it slowly flows down the tunnel
this tunnel looks different it was carved up by people sloppily and hastily it's a miracle still
hasn't collapsed yet the further part of the tunnel is blocked by rubble looking through a
crack i see giant pulsating bruise maybe i can find a way to destroy them let's light it up
will i die from this should i leave this way just just leave i want to see what was down here
where's the hatch i forget about the 30s well i um when somebody tells me leave i think okay
i came through this door so that's the door i came through that's what i'm gonna leave from
i didn't happen it didn't happen the dream was not real life we've been having dreams
all fucking night i've been having dreams for 30 days i thought you guys said to come back down
here i can't see a goddamn thing i can't destroy it i can't break it did you guys
did you guys seriously seriously just make me do this and god and call me all kinds of names
it was just a joke don't pretend you did that on purpose i i did i was trying to leave the zone
you guys are fucking too much all right let me get out of here it's burning i was going the right way
no whether it's real not yield to the flame sleeves they tried to smother the fire with the
fruits it should be all over tomorrow
come back tomorrow ah see that we'll come back tomorrow it should be done by then
hey hey hey dude you want to uh you want to go to sonic they got these bomb tater tots of sonic
yeah except i might put cheese on mine yeah dude get out of here yeah you're a funny guy
oh it's the old man come here now come
i'm sorry i didn't mean to i just
what the fuck why did i do that
uh
okay i'm gonna uh i'm gonna fucking puke screaming please man
i didn't think anybody
no no i'm not laughing at them i was i didn't think he was an important story person
and i really didn't mean to do that either it was i was sitting there like this and then i
pressed it i think i thought it was far i thought i was far away i didn't think i was close enough
to kill him i can't talk over this the guy did oh of course he gave you the quest
okay i'm gonna fucking actually die don't board these windows
oh i'm not gonna restart the game oh my fucking whole body hurts what's that
oh my god that's that might be like that's that's that's i thought that was i have to
get the fuck out of here you're gonna make me use a lockpick to get out of here every day i can hear
him more clearly we don't believe what are you talking about i have to get out of him now
there's nobody there's nobody there i didn't kill that person three i mean three murders
i oh my god i have to heal i have to heal before i die do i have any heals
that's like that was so fucking funny to me i'm sorry it was everybody freaked the fuck out
i thought it was just a guy i didn't know it was just everybody's reaction and
oh i finally i'm out of the screams it was just too much you just kill people
or you you also you just kill people first no no you killed him while he was admiring the fire
i thought he was gonna die oh my goodness you guys are fucking hilarious um like seriously
that's the hardest i've left just at what you guys were saying in at least a month i kept seeing
like nut chug and stuff like you need there was so much going on there for my brain and i'm like
already like kind of tired i didn't that's like the one person god damn it man that's okay let's
survive another night um i may have missed some story there unfortunately but it's okay because
i almost threw up i actually did i would have actually i probably would have been suspended
from twitch if that went on any longer it would have been like just let's go let's go turn it on
i don't even anything else for me to do you literally asked the story
i need to sit here for a minute this game was fun this was a fun game i'm glad you all got to
experience it with me thank you oh okay i'm just gonna i'm just gonna i'm just gonna sit here
i need like it's good that i'm not gonna be streaming for like a few days
because that actually took like probably a year off my life just laughing at that
right okay peanut coma let's just get it going uh fill it up and you know what let's just let's
just go full blown who cares you want to see some shit i'll show you some shit i almost walked in
the room drew a dick oh my goodness i'm just gonna go in a circle i didn't do it again that's very
that's a cloud that is a that is a that is a cumulo nimbus cloud i want to use the shotgun
eat the shotgun no oh right all right boot it up you ready this is the last night
i'm gonna torch this place wait i didn't get any wood oh fuck it watch this shit oh no
oh it's not good very bad it's okay i don't even need it i'm going completely insanity mode here
you think i need a doorway i have a shotgun silent creepy germa it's okay is this time going slower
shouldn't be you will not leave this room without stepping on a trap maybe i think i'm in a good
spot though because whoever is getting where's my rifle that's probably a better bet to have
oh yeah for sure definitely the rifle because i'm just gonna put it between the eyes my accuracy
sucks shotgun better spread e f where why did you kill me why did you do it is the house on fire
wait didn't i do that what huh what happened who was it what oh shit um i think i did it
all righty cool i did it now get me the fuck out of here what the fuck well the eyes are gone
what about that tree tree everything's dying all this shit's dead you did this yeah i know i know
i know i know i did it um where's this up here right no down here can i go this way
oh i need a lockpick where the oh yeah i remember this room this room was fucked up everyone's
whatever and everyone's freaking out explore thoroughly explore thoroughly explore thoroughly
in the end area i'm that's what i'm doing i'm i'm exploring what's this what's the code
fabric why do i have that one two three four one two three four no i gotta go back this way
wait where am i is it not this way that's the same code on my luggage
uh no gas in here that's all right i just need to look at it for a second
this is not all the way down can i get in this there's a chest in here there's a chest not like
it matters but i mean like pretty cool i guess i would have been great before wait wait wait can
i go up i don't think so i don't care i don't care just go to bed okay this every time i come
here i i get lost every time it's the only place in the whole game that has happened
every time it's the only place in the whole game where this has happened
i'm gonna i'm actually gonna die here keep passing the way i need to go it's through here
one goddamn sliver of fucking one sliver ashes well i'm bringing out the shotgun just in case
something happens here okay can i get in the tree destroyed well only ashes remain
i was told to look at everything the hell am i in this house
did i miss a room or something before i leave i was told to explore heavily i think i'm just
gonna go battery hello this goo sips from the craps and the asphalt this is the road i made it
i did it it's the road it's the road from the photo i did it i don't have a car though
this is gonna suck the torches and a sign the crossed out sign reads dark wood that's the name
of the game skeleton oh shit the crippled old man from the village he's alive he's alive i just
i just nicked him i just nicked him right here he's fine should i talk to him will he make it
the road the road i know i know finish the job if you live with an axe to the head like that
i mean like it reminds me of bloodborne bear trap him this doesn't work does it
no it does not tell me it doesn't he's dead just kidding
no i use your scream to wake him up guys i have to end the game he beat you there i beat him
i beat him there he's dead 25 kilometers to nearest town i'm actually getting lost on a
straight road i'm not lost i'm contemplating whether or not to throw a rock at that guy
it's a truck right here i used my runner already kind of abruptly stopped epilogue
i don't have an inventory anymore this is the next town what's this town called shady trees
look at me look at me obscure forest electricity interesting that's the first actual like poles
i've seen that's interesting it's uh building houses quite an entrance and they're gone who's
going to eat the bread now like a city neighbor my first floor neighbor good day good day to you
first floor neighbor i live in like an apartment complex i go in the building and put people to
talk to i feel like i'm going in circles i think i am going in circles this is my staircase
this is my bike weird that no one ever tried to steal it dupa it's probably the work of
that little punk from the third floor someone finally evicted them boss got any spare change
i don't i need a key geez relax man relax awaken my kid get the hell away that was a kid
stupid cow this is freaking me out it's too late for this pleased to see you mister i haven't seen
you in a while let's check downstairs i'm a little after this this is but just this is normal life
they're still green even though i've never seen anyone tending to them maybe they feed on the
discarded cigarette butts i go downstairs can i go downstairs i cannot go downstairs anymore
ah elevator doesn't work as a oh apparently someone was too lazy to bring it down the
stairs and throw it in the trash old rug the flowers are still green even though i've never
seen anyone tending to them yeah yeah yeah okay what about up here okay this looks important let
me just see if i can go over here i cannot what does it say it's probably the work of the kids
from the neighboring apartment block dupa doors blocked from the other side wash your face oh i
will go ahead this is not my apartment bike the neighbor's bike he could do something with it
he's been lying in the middle of the corridor since i broke the kickstand not my apartment
not my apartment okay that's apparently home sweet home home sweet home
okay this is my house my wardrobe it's my wardrobe take off your coat wait what are you talking about
you need to explore take off my coat hey hey it's suzerick missed me pet dog my tv said the black
and white rubin real luxury unfortunately it's broken folding couch i'm very tired i prefer to
lie down in a regular bed i can just drag this these roofs are growing up from under the floor
panels it won't i won't be able to tear the floor off with my bare hands there should be some tools
in the kitchen bedroom key fabric fabric tools in the kitchen oh where's the kitchen bathroom
washing machine the frania washing machine spent two days in the queue to get it
i'm barely standing on my feet i'll take a bath tomorrow did somebody knock at the door
some note is lying on the table i've made you some soup heated up covered under the sink
stove the rusty old gas stove there's still some soup in the pot don't turn that on covered
the sink large screwdriver there we go okay oh it's emote only it's emote only mode that means
that there's something going on here to avoid spoilers oh okay that makes sense um sure let's
turn it on i guess smell fills the entire kitchen cook i grab the largest dish from the closet
under the sink and pour myself a bowl it's not much but it's enough i don't remember the last
time i've even eaten a home dinner that looks kind of good that looks pretty good not bad
okay so i have a screwdriver now bathtub no what about toilet what else
okay so remove flooring wait wait wait hold on fold the rug what the fuck is under here
here these roots are growing up from under the floor panels are they going they're like a person
under here what the fuck why are there roots in this house i thought i burned the tree
didn't i burn the tree should i water it i think i got it all did i get it all search no drag
okay so i'm going to the bedroom i just took up all the roots in my whole fucking house
i'm scared to go to bed this thing's under the bed it's my bed the white crumpled sheets look
as if i've just woken up at last i feel my sore legs buckling underneath me a body becoming heavy
and overlooking overwhelmingly lethargic it was a grueling journey 32 days of human torment
closer fighting off sleepiness with difficulty i lean over the bed the springs creak noisily
under the weight of my hand as i cast my glance on the light brown construction from plywood i
notice familiar features they are elongated and arched i can smell the fresh sheets in the
pleasant warmth of the quilt look under the bed i feel a gentle draught coming from the dark gap
between the bed and the floor reach under the bed my fingertips brush a thin layer of dust
coldness moisture i'm touching something rough but my arm is too short to catch it
i think i need to move the bed move the bed was it bugs rats what the fuck is this
sleeping man the man is fast sleepy smiling he's hooking his knees with skinny dirty arms
this one flies is covering a black sore in his back old weathered clothes the steep slope blocks
the way ahead there are some tunnels at its base it's a meter wide tunnel covered with a slimy
membrane further inside i can see pulsating growths blocking the way ahead i won't be able
to pass through this way my trousers they're completely destroyed dirty clumped hair cover
the woman's face she's murmuring in her sleep clutching a rag doll filled with straw now the
moon has faded the night is here the sleep stole over my doll so close so close your eyes
uh i'm at the bottom of huge valley i feel the dry dusty earth pulsating into my feet
it hums something quietly in its sleep swaying to the rhythm of a simple melody
i'll wake up figure he's dead asleep i'm unable to wake him up shiny stone talking in its sleep
moving his hand as if caressing someone with affection shiny stone what's going on i hear
a faint whisper stasiak my little stasiak sleep stasiak sleep face is covered in mud and sticks
it clutches shiny stone figures dead asleep i can't wake them up looks like a skeleton
coated in skin he smiles wildly the figure sleeps on a muddy ground resting its head on the chest
of a skeleton lying next to it everyone's sleeping clutches a muddy brass cross in both hands repeating
some incomprehensible words the figure speaks to someone in his sleep squeezing an old man's
photo in his hand the emaciated figure sleeps soundly embracing the remains of a child
another sleeping figure hands okay sleeping figure sleeping everyone's just sleeping sleeping
sleeping sleeping sleeping they're asleep they seem happy even though they're emaciated and dirty
some of them lie dead sleeping all of them sleeping sleeping stone what is going on right now
sleeping figure all of them stone stone god morbid cross this way everyone's just kind of
dead or asleep the earth is covered with thick bundles of dry roots that creak under my feet and
old broken trees all right more skeletons no i just want your stone just give me your shining stone
i just want the shiny stone just give me the stone give me the stone just give me the stone
i can't get it pleasant warmth washes over me what are you doing being the the being
i'm standing in front of an enormous being place hand on being filming soothing feeling of security
and happiness vast valley at the bottom of which i stand curves upwards closing over my head the
rust of distant trees turns into a single silent murmur feel i'm coming home to my flat to my room
with a window in bed i feel heat emanating from the being i sense my pulse slowing down
calmness i want to rest come back home to my bed i want to lie down to fall asleep
get pull the hand back pull the hand back pull the hand back pull the hand back i don't want to do
this i don't want to do it i still my hand pushes the beam away the warmth that was emanating from
it disappears replace my piercing coldness i've beaten you all right i'm out of here
it's the it's the doctor the doctor finally came it's the doctor he's fast asleep you made it
nice job nice work should i do this what am i what am i should i embarrass the being
or do i leave the tree nay nay nay nay nay nay draw your hand let me throw my hand
do i have a bullet or something i can i kill it how do i kill this
i need to make i'm like a caveman i can't make that how do i make that no i can go around here
i love emote only mode it's fucking so much fun all right i can go this way oh shit wait my sake
the man mom was in his sleep he's emaciated and dirty but his face is radiant and calm he
clutches a rusty object covered with old beads some weapon but what do you got the man is talking
in his sleep he's the only snippets of sentences single words spoken gently and slowly it's hard
to find any meaning in them leave without opening his eyes the man clumsily waves his hand at me
then covers his head with it and freezes give it to me give me that thing leave the man waves his
hand again this time he grabs my arm without opening his eyes he turns his head towards me
i recognize him he's one of us give me that thing leave can you fucking hear me i won't let you
take her the man clenches his teeth with the fury of a maniac saliva flows from his mouth
it's hurting her you will tear her arms out don't leave her no holy shit give her to me
what are you doing that's four people okay that's four i'll take the fuck five six seven
huge roots blocked away even if i manage to climb them everything is surrounded by a steep slope
overgrown with thick roots there's no way out oh yeah what are you doing i'm gonna take out the
trash now step back everybody get out of the way i don't want to add a ninth and tenth person to
this list once you get past 10 people killed that might be innocent in a video game you're a psycho
just move that's way more than 10 all right can i get out leave i'm trying to leave
i can't leave am i out of gas
it's too many it's okay sprint how do i skip the cutscene that was crazy a great fire consumed
the woods for a couple days gradually claiming many of its inhabitants you're a sicko that's
the first thing i saw the fire consumed the last road leading to the heart of the woods
the doctor who did not wake up even as the flames came closer the doctor made it all the way through
that's at least one npc that got to live the three outcasts wearing old rags and scrap who
brief stricken under the enormous completely burnt tree didn't even attempt to run the elephant
family who did not leave their house at the swamp even as the flame started consuming it the chicken
lady who set out into the woods in search for her sister and lost the way not everyone perished i
think i got the bad ending i didn't get the true bad ending heo trek did not live to see the fire
before the flames appeared he rose above the treetops and his rocket made up scrap as he looked
through the small spaceship window he smiled for the last time the milky ways and stars looked so
beautiful even now and moving away at a huge speed slide he was exploded on the ground
incomprehensible whispers and calls ceased forever they saw incoming helicopters above the destroyed
land wolf snout remains unknown there it is that was a good game first impressions uh first
impressions of the game this is good i think um my first impressions once i figure out the
inventory management i think i'll start to give a better idea because the stacks are weird so
some things don't stack about when i figure that out i've only had like three or four items in my
inventory so far so i'm sure it'll get easier last impressions this was a solid game i feel like um
at least for me chapter two that this last like hour was great but there was like a little tiny
part of chapter two that i just i it was killing me but sometimes it needs some peanuts and we're
good i wonder how much of that portion that like 20 minute portion of chapter two that i was getting
straight on and i was getting frustrated i wonder if it's because i would have like low protein brain
it's probably it's probably pretty accurate no that was good that was really good i'm glad
i got to finish the whole thing on stream thanks for watching i will see you guys again
on uh let's see i have a couple things oh by the way i want to talk about the i want to talk about
the just really quick before you leave but you can leave if you want but uh halloween there's
going to be a special stream uh whether it's the 28th 29th 30th 31st i'm not sure yet we have to
lock it in there's going to be a secret slime channel in the discord and what's going to
happen here is all you really need to know is on 31st you're going to be able to slime me
or maybe you won't maybe you will but you're going to have a channel in the discord to come
up with actions for me that you think i'm going to do without me knowing so oh scratch your nose
if i do that and it's part of the first round like probably about 10 rounds so probably well
it's hard for me to speak i just have to search for words up here but uh you guys have to come
up with things that you think that i do but that i will do on camera to dump a bucket of slime on
my head and also at the same time you are also going to be up against some bullshit here too
because i'm going to come up with shit that you can't do and if you say it in the chat you're out
for the rest of the game it's happening on halloween those of you that want a good um
indicator of exactly what this is go watch an episode just even one snippet of figure it out
from nickelodeon back in the 90s that secret slime action is kind of what this is inspired by so
oh and i am i am going to win everybody in chat is worth one point i start with like 10 000 points
every time i get slimed i get reduced by about 500 to 1000 points we're not trying to get those
numbers correct every time somebody gets snapped deleted from chat you guys lose a point so 100
people say the thing that they're not supposed to saying at the end of the round found out though
that you said it that's minus 100 points each person's worth one how many buckets of slime is
it gonna be gonna make we're gonna make like a a big batch of just random easy slime i want to i
want to make like a slime that's not like dog shit for the environment so i'm gonna look into that
try to find out like a good one that's not gonna be a problem because i know that a lot of slimes
are just like absolute poison right so i'll figure it out that's the one thing i when i looked up
stuff about slime oh you're making slime slime stuff it's this stuff is like styrofoam 5.0 so
i don't really want to make just like that's kind of i'd rather try to do something a little more
eco-friendly but uh that's what's gonna happen we'll talk about it some more obviously when i'm
back and had some sleep i will see you guys on tuesday so uh one two three i'll see you tuesday
we've beaten dark wood there are like two or three scary games that some of them aren't even scary
but they're gonna be here for halloween look under your bed oh i'm gonna make sure that there's no
pulsating twigs under my bed i'll make sure but that was dark wood and that was my stream
thanks this is a long one 11 hours almost thanks everybody for staying if you just i mean there's
still a lot of people there at the very end thanks i put it up with my bullshit you know the last
vegan you know what i'm saying and i will see you guys holy shit does it work does it actually work
maybe it does oh my how much did why is there a countdown this thing is so
fucked up
has this been counting down since yesterday this has been running a sub train in the back
route for the whole stream and hadn't even been on that's so funny just let it go i'm just gonna
leave it there i'm gonna i'm going to spend these next few days especially probably tomorrow i'm
gonna figure this shit out and make sure it works but uh let me see let me see how many bits we have
here here comes a time gifter if someone doesn't gift a sub in the next 90 seconds this channel is
gonna get deleted i don't know if that's how it works uh we can do the bits i'm gonna really just
kind of go through them quickly though because it is very very very late thank you to marvosh
magali for the 250 they showed the halloween map with j elbertson's thing that's so awesome by the
way i'm absolutely fucking floored that i have a banner on a tf2 map that's awesome oh i'm stupid
i need to close this and put on the music there we go but uh yeah if if you weren't here earlier
in the new tf2 halloween map there's a reference to the carnival stream that's crazy it's really
cool i'm probably gonna go check it out and see and just take a look at it yeah holy shit
somebody did it somebody subscribed wait did it reset oh that's what that means right
hey it's time for slime thanks for the 300 bits our username will finally be relevant when this
halloween stream comes yeah it's gonna be great also thanks for your five community subs as well
uh cyrus dexter thanks for the 265 appreciate it thank you family kidneys for the 500 bits
they say free hong kong we're in a pretty terminalistic world at the moment but yeah
it's it's really odd to see just at least in my opinion when when shit like this is going down
germans can get banned unless it's gonna fire you my senator was talking about it yeah no this this
shit is fucking really coming up to a head here and hopefully hopefully this gets resolved in the
good way you know obviously i'm a proponent of democracy very much so i mean i live in the
united states i live in hong kong and it's very sad that this is happening yeah but the thing is
when when i'll give you my just short 30 second blurb of this whole thing i really don't know why
blizzard would take prize money from someone i've like that's just it just seems ridiculous
like i was talking i forget who was talking about this but it's like okay if you ban somebody from
a tournament but they win the tournament you know what i mean like you you didn't ban them from the
tournament you're like just banned them from winning you banned them from winning the tournament
it's like oh hey i i've got i won some money on this tournament you're banned from that
tournament well i already is in the tournament well you just shit you're banned from it though
that's like it's like getting arrested it's like a it's like a police officer asking you
son have you ever smoked marijuana before in your life it's like yeah you're under arrest
did you smoke marijuana yesterday yeah you have any on you right now no you're under arrest
what but also i'm also of the opinion that if let's say if somebody is like a fan of hearthstone
let's say somebody loves hearthstone there are way more people in blizzard than just the top
five people that make decisions and it's a problem at the top not a problem with the people that care
about those games so anytime somebody says well you stop supporting blizzard stop supporting
hearthstone stop supporting warcraft there are people that have put their whole lives into those
games dedicated their whole lives people that have built those worlds you know and they probably have
the same feelings that a lot of people do they still get paid for that you're not hurting them
no i know but but still you just you got to remember that there's this there's a lot of
people it's it's not just it's not just you that feel this way and there is an issue with
essentially people running companies that decide everything for everybody else kind of
which i mean that that's what happens when you run a company even if it means
they're going to do something that's not seen as right or it's wrong or it's sensitive but sometimes
the bottom line is what matters to a lot of these companies so it's a weird position that was a
long 30 seconds it's like a full five minutes but i do i do want to give i mean obviously
i'll tell you what's going to be blizzcon is going to be very interesting
because it's almost like they've i don't know what the fuck they're going to do
what are they going to be like hey everybody all right hey here's uh here's diablo four
right isn't that great that's great right that's good shit isn't it right most people still gonna
go yeah but think about that though right like imagine that's in like two or three weeks imagine
you already booked your hotel you booked your flight like it's okay to still enjoy things
but i severely disagree with all the stuff that the people at the top have decided to do
severely completely but we'll see i don't know maybe something happened here maybe
maybe like the head can get pulled out of the ass and maybe we'll see some it's actually something
good come from this i don't know did they put a statement out today i'll have to read it after
but yeah pull heads from ass i really like this music it is very good it was it was it was a
garbage statement it was a non-answer it was it was it was just like a corporate copy paste like
alexa wrote it yeah that's unfortunate we'll see what happens we'll move on from that though
germa please say something extremely controversial i don't i don't think anything i think i think most
of the things i said it would but a lot of people think i'm not a very complicated person guys you
know i'm pretty um i kind of see things the way that they are and that's kind of the way that it
is and that's it he's a simple streamer but he has bad taste in ice cream and steak oh i always
see blizzard ads when i load up your stream well that's i mean that's a twitch thing though
i mean i make i make wow references all the time but you have to remember i played
i don't play blizzard games anymore i don't the last time i opened up overwatch i think was like
two years ago i downloaded wow classic when it first came out got to like level seven and realized
holy shit i don't want to do this again it's like wow this is this is i remember what this was like
i still thought it was interesting though i still thought it was cool
but i i kind of just don't have the time to do it anymore to do that but yeah i i'm not really
i don't really have a connection to blizzard at all but you said you play hearthstone every
night on your ipad maybe a while ago maybe maybe one of the adventures came out like
three four five months ago i did i played hearthstone yeah like a few months ago yeah
i don't not anymore and before that not for a while we aren't 16 anymore feels
fucked man what but i'll uh i'll move on from the kind of controversy that's going on in the
gaming world we'll move on because it is getting late he won't say nevada what are you talking
about why wouldn't i say even that but i feel hopefully i've tried to articulate some of the
things that i think hopefully i did i have been streaming for 11 hours so but here we go sad
vega thanks for the 250 you know what that full moon thing how do you explain every other day
of the month i'll agree with you you've been extra weird today i have not been extra weird today
hey cream corn thanks the five community subs i wasn't extra weird today i was just normal weird
i was what do you mean because i did the cookie crisp you killed an old man and laughed about it
for 20 minutes no that wasn't what why i was laughing at i was laughing at everybody's
extremely quick reaction to it no you have to understand i saw like a bunch of random messages
that were just pushing me over the edge oh god that was fucking ridiculous i just didn't understand
the consequences of my actions everybody knew the consequences
he's still everybody hey he was crawling at the end of the movie you saw him uh this community
fucking cracks me up every time you guys are great uh thank you putrefashioned grow clown
for the 600 bits how did anyone know that everyone left the streamer still has zero viewers there's
still nobody watching this it's a twitch problem thank you jack the mac for the 500 bits hey germa
i've noticed you've been playing some pretty spooky games to get into the holiday spirit
you should check out dusk on steam it's like old school doom i'm sure chad would like it
i have heard of dusk before seems like an interesting game uh thank you co hillen for
the 300 bits germa could you ask jeff bezos why he added rpg aiya as an official twitch emote
what is it it doesn't work i'm doing right oh you have to unlock it oh rpg i don't know
i don't know jeff bezos bullshit bullshit the only thing that i know about jeff bezos is he's bald
and he has like 400 billion dollars you have something in common then yeah thank you shelby
kun for the thousand bits hey jerry i just want to say that the fridge drawing i drew for you was
a joke thought i needed to say this after your reaction so i don't think you took it seriously
fridge drawing what it was a fridge drawing don't ever take anything i say seriously it's
important to know i'm a licensed comedy clown so i mean 80 to 90 percent of the things i say are
just licensed comedy clown material they also say i had a dream a couple nights ago i dreamed that
you were doing another christmas dream you had gotten a reindeer plush and suddenly chat was
flooded with messages adding me saying it's you and stuff like that it was pretty cool it's you
it's you click the link let's see but thank you shelby kun for the way more than that actually
uh there's 3 000 bits from shelby kun they say if you got to mention this cool thing i found out
leon kennedy from resident evil looks like the quiet man i almost shit myself when i realized
this ps you're the goat love your streams man always make me happy thanks shelby and they also
say one more thing remember when someone told you to play half-life and you freaked out is
there a reason do you hate half-life or are you just scared of the immense backseating that'll
happen um no i mean i've just i've played through half-life and half-life too so it's not i just
don't have a reason to play it and i don't hate half-life he hates streaming
uh no i don't have a problem with half-life i just i would love to play a new one and they also say
one last thing for 500 bits can you sing a song for me one that's worth 35 dollars however much
i gave you i lost count sing a song that's the power of my voice that's power of pete's voice
i'm gonna sing a song that's the power of my voice that's the power of my voice that's the power of
song that's the power of my voice that's the power of peanuts actually you did that joke
don't tell them don't tell anybody how you reuse material all the fucking time the power peanuts
peanuts you've done that joke probably five times i've done that okay i've made that joke five times
in 10 years what's the what's the the the half-life i'll give you a cool word there
what's the half-life on being able to tell a joke that maybe other people may not have heard before
i've said five i've done it five times in 10 years you guys act like i'm the guy at the bar
that keeps telling the same joke every weekend you do look at me that's not a joke that's an issue
you okay hey cvfd thanks to the 250 munch munch good work thank you c4g again thanks to the 250
i saw in your previous bit messages that they added rpg aiya and if i don't get it off these
bits i'm unsubscribing i'm sorry great lord walden thanks for the thousand bits just the top two
jupiters thanks with 10 bucks appreciate it sad vega thanks for the 250 i've had beef tartar
before that's raw meat and it was wonderful i would not eat beef tartar not even jeff bezos
could get me to eat that and he's got a billion dollars worth of it i'm sorry look at me i have a
look at me condition
oh it's four am wrap it up okay
oh the bar is closing uh all right we're almost done thank you genie for the 500 bits you'll get
500 more if you can get another in your mouth also play divinity tarnum peanuts okay there you go i
got another one sage the ghost thanks with thousand bits thanks buddy thanks to you actually
thank you let's put the credits on the screen i will see you guys on tuesday we've got a few
more bits to do oh the map creator was here i'm the map creator for that my partner and i are big
fans we even met you at packs we met you even met you a few packs ago a partner made the grandpa
set for scout if you remember oh shit wow that's awesome so i can't sometimes i can't believe
that people you know like oh i'm a fan of yours it's like i'm a fan of yours man
some of you guys are so fucking talented and doing such interesting shit that you know that's it
goes both ways who's my fan me feels 64 you got a new fan right now me too and a bunch of others
too look at all these new fans but that's awesome i'm absolutely floored that that's like i said
previously i have to check the map out i want to see what it looks like boot up the old tf2 engine
and just stick around for an hour but that's awesome thank you again let's get the credits
on the screen if i even can it's been a while since i've gone more than 10 11 hours and it
feels good sometimes you know sometimes you have you got to have a long one thanks for the subs
everybody i will leave you with these last few bits we had buff mix slab chest gave 2000 bits
20 bucks been meaning to give you something for a while having fun yeah thank you for the 20
dollars i'm having a blast jobs can do thanks for the 250 to be completely honest i was really
annoyed with how bad you were playing but you did the impossible and got the true ending without
help i'm proud of you though it was stressful like watching your child play with a grenade
somebody says oh there was help yeah but i mean i i was all right playing a scary horror jumpy
game for that takes a lot of non-hand holding for like nine ten hours my normal gaming sessions
even when i'm not on stream even before i was streaming were like four or five hours tops so
but i had peanuts and i was good to go they say i forgive you for your boomerness thank you
those are rookie numbers now thanks a lot dubski and then future gamer thanks for the 250 as this
channel grows how do you think you will handle a regular everyday chat of 10 000 or 20 000 people
i do not think that will happen i mean i've had 10 000 and close to 20 000 before but not every day
i'm not sure that'll happen the amount of time it took we'll think about it right it just go by
it's taken a long time to get here that i've been you doing youtube and streaming for almost 10
years and there are a shitload of people that are even here now so i don't know i i can't predict
that i'm gonna have 20 000 concurrent viewers on this stream i mean you're talking about like the
top like 20 channels on twitch top 10 i don't know i the doors are open but i'm whatever happens i'm
comfortable whatever happens happens but how would i handle something like that which is will you know
you change a few rules you make it a little different and not try not to change anything
really that much i mean going from 800 to 1000 viewers nothing really changed that much in
regards to how i approached a stream 1000 to 2000 to 3000 three to four four to five five to six
i just i approached my approach is the same if i have 10 000 viewers or a thousand
i don't really change how i do anything but i appreciate the 250 thank you we also had uh
devakitty thanks for the five dollars here they said go back and check you missed my message pepe
hands you're right i did and here it is sick streamer used to be wholesome and righteous and
while we suspected things had gone array before it was not before the dark wood stream that it became
clear uh jeremy shot a child point blank only concerned with the backpack then he ate a grandma
alive while her grandson was next door and finally he chopped open the skull of an innocent old blind
the streamer is truly fucked manka s what are you talking about what do you mean
who did i shoot okay i ate the old lady i hit the guy in the head with an axe when did i shoot
somebody point blank that was when did i do that the music the musician oh but the oh the villager
guy yeah that's a that was a villager guy you show the music kid and you hide out well what
the fuck was going on okay go back and watch that clip it's like right at the end of a night
it no it was during a night wasn't it i just like broke down my door and started screaming at me
with like hands up the air i mean like like he had like ten tendrils in the air and his hands
were flying around and he's like there was this loud noise playing i'm gonna go back and watch
that clip because that was in my house no npc comes into your house besides the traitor
why all of a sudden is he coming out of the ground like why is what's he doing there
it was a surprise but uh i will see you guys on tuesday thanks for hanging out for this long one
because it has been a long one it's a good one to go out on though i had a lot of fun
am i gonna play any book connect i still have like four or five connect games
we might do just a fuck face stream and um a few weeks or something just do a bunch of stuff that
we haven't done we'll see but i'm gonna get some sleep i'm gonna go actually i'm gonna take a
shower first i'll just kind of wash the uh the layer of uh gamer on my face off somebody's
getting away what do you say uh unclean unclean sepik thanks for 300 bits can you still do this
no i cannot this is the 500 subs video of me curling 30 pound weights no i can't do this
anymore i used to be a strong strong son of a gun i couldn't even attempt to do one of these right
now what is this video uploaded july 3rd 2011 is it saying bad form bad posture what are you
kidding me are you kidding me that's some of the best form i've ever seen a human do
all right good night guys i'll see you tuesday take care we're gonna do more horror games when
i go live next maybe it depends i have a few other things i'd like to do we i want to break
it up a little bit we've done four streams in a row here of scary stressful stuff and hold on a
second is um it's late but is is tip of the hat still on right now oh it's rerunning right now
okay so i was gonna say we could yeah i'll um i was gonna say raid the rerun but can you do that
can you like raid a rerunning channel does that work when they when do they start up again at
nine nine o'clock tomorrow nine eastern okay yeah if you guys don't know go support tip of the hats
we talked a little bit about uh tf2 earlier but it's a great great group of people awesome
organization i'm gonna link the channel here that's where the original germa is short joke came from
yeah there we go vr josh has got it go support that they do a lot of great stuff for kids yeah
i'll see you guys on tuesday i'm gonna host him tomorrow yeah star got sick right yeah that's
unfortunate all right guys see you tuesday goodbye good night take care