Oh, you can hear me. I'm just sitting there like silent on my phone tweeting. I was just like,
I'm muted, whatever. That's why I always have the mic muted, because I'm just sitting there like,
okay. But hey, how you doing? How's everybody doing? Sorry for the delay. There was a lot of
strange technical issues. Talix had problems with his capture card. The lobby system in the game is
really, really strange. It's kind of a weird roundabout system in EDF 5 to play together and
joining off of each other's sessions and stuff. It's very odd. But Earth Defense Force 5 today,
tonight, and depending on how much fun this game is, you may see it again, because I was a huge fan
of the last one. Played it at least three or four times on stream and I played a shitload of it
off stream too. So without further ado, because we've been kind of sticking around and waiting
around, I think we're pretty much ready to go. Let's go ahead and see who's available here to
speak. I wonder who's here. Hello there. Anybody there? Hello there. Hello there. I'm here. Are
you eating? We're gonna have to wait like 15 minutes because I just got food. What'd you get?
Sounds good. What food did you get? It's, you know, rice and vegetables and pork.
Okay. But, but is it, did you make it yourself or was it? Ashley made it for me. Okay. Nice. Okay.
Sounds delicious. Because I'm an imbecile. I mean, I don't know how to do that, you know what I mean?
I don't know how to spell it out for us. Well, now we can start. I can eat and play because I'm a god
gamer. Cause I'd run a start because you're in, we're an hour late because of you as always. Hey,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. There were, excuse me. Hey, yeah, there were a lot of
problems. Yes. Yes. Italics his capture card got fucked up, but he's got enough control over that
and you couldn't figure out how to add friends and you couldn't figure out how to invite me to a
lobby. Beyond that, I wasn't told that maybe his eating schedule was happening beforehand. So I
didn't know to prepare a head for dinner. All right. That's it. Stream over. I'm going to go
play. I'm going to go count peanuts down the street or something. Every time you beat Cloud
Amari, you grow one centimeter. Did I just turn my, I'm like naked and I think I just accidentally
turned my webcam on. Did I do that? No, I didn't. Thank God. Are you naked? I don't, I don't wear
clothes. It's Alex. We live together. Can you please vouch for me? Why do I need somebody to
vouch for me for this? Hey dude, you like vouching, man. I don't wear clothes, right?
You don't wear clothes. Is that what you were asking me right now? I want you to confirm or
deny the fact that how often do I wear clothes? Is this really the question you want to be asking
me right now? I really want to know. Can you give like an example of talks? Give us an exam. When
did you first find out he doesn't wear clothes? Um, before we even moved, he was like, by the way,
I don't wear clothes. I'm going to have to start wearing clothes now. That was the first thing he
said. It was pretty immediate, like full nude or like boxers or underwear. Well, obviously I've
never seen the full nude, but I was told the stories. No, listen, I, I, I, all I said was this.
I said, I just want to make sure that you're, I want to make sure that are you okay with this? Are
you okay with me walking around shirtless? Like, yo, yo, you okay with that? Like, is that okay?
And he was like, yeah, I've seen you shirtless. Yeah, I can vouch for this actually. Cause now
that I think about it, you take your shirt off whenever you get the chance.
I just have the opposite of a never nude. No, it's good. You're very comfortable that way.
Like a lot of people would be shy taking their shirt off in front of other people, but like you,
you push past that. It's a, it's a, it's like a sweaty comfort thing. And I make sure I know,
but okay, if I told you that it's Alex before we moved in and you were like, nah, man, that,
I don't think, I don't like that. I would, I would wear like a fucking shirt. I need to make,
I want to make sure that you were like, okay, like you cool with me, like hanging out like with on
the couch, like no clothes on, like no shirt on. I've mentioned, I never go swimming. Like I never
go to the pool. I've never seen another human being. No, the amount of times that we've like
shared a hotel room and you're like, I'm going to take a shower and you just take your shirt off
and then you start another conversation and stand there shirtless for 10 minutes. This is how
fanfiction starts every time. That's not every time. Probably every time we've had a hotel
together. It's happened at least once. I'm going to need to install Microsoft word after this.
And you get really weird towards the end of the conversation. You like flex an arm and kiss it.
All right. All right. It's time. Are we ready to play the game? Yeah. I think we're finally ready
to play. Hey, welcome to EDF five. Uh, this has been doing the first mission.
Are we? I mean, you're the guy, the guy with the fork and knife in his hand.
I'm eating with what the fuck are you writing here? Oh, we have a valiant infantry. We are
the alpha team with passion and I'm not nice. That was a great, but are you writing this?
I keep trying to change controls, like, like, oh, go to prepared and then complete the mission.
But I'm using the D pad and if you touch the D pad, it's like, cause it's a dialogue.
I thought you were actually typing this stuff in being like weird. No way. Okay. Okay. No way.
Yeah. I mean, like, I'm saying, okay, I have to, how do you ready? The top option preparation
complete. Yeah. All right. So let's go over our classes. Looks like we're late because of italics
again. Oh, okay. No, what? No, it was a collective. It was a collective star. Couldn't figure out
how to use the PlayStation. It was also the last one to use the bathroom and he's eating right now.
Yeah. And by the way, when we used to have hotel rooms,
yeah, he used to, he used to eat in the bathroom. He used to bring,
I do that. You're right. Basically. Yeah. You're next to the two queens. Just one was enough.
And he takes every time. No, no, no, no. You don't have to use trash bags. If you get next to the
toilet, no, you would sit there with the fork and knife of the plate on the toilet. And it was just,
it was, it was chaos. You would leave trash around. You would let you would just, uh, by the way,
the shower drain is not a garbage disposal. You don't dump the leftover shit that you don't want
to eat down there. I don't know why you would do that. Do you, do you understand how much
throughout my lifespan, how much plastic I've saved and how much I've helped the environment
because I do that? By what? Doing what now? Putting food down the sink. All right. Yeah.
All right. There we go. Fight the aliens guys. Stop, stop talking.
If I have to, if I have to talk one more time, I just realized the bugs and then you shoot the
bugs. Yeah, I know, but I've got like a mega shield. I don't know. I don't know what I do
either. Actually. Yeah. Well, I have this cannon. I've got throwing so much shade and look in the
mirror. Look in the mirror. I cry for like an hour. That's why you never go into the hotel bathroom.
Okay. Make sure you pick up the red cases. By the way, I'm coming to a realization that playing,
like you said, wing diver on console is probably not a great idea. Yeah. I'm, I'm already using
sad control scheme. I get to shoot a lot of bullets. So mine's working pretty good. Yeah.
I mean, you're like slow and dumpy anyway. I am. Yeah. I got to figure out how to go fast.
All right. So, um, this is the one I need to be using. I need to be using the plasma cannon
for sure. More like street corridor defense force. This is just the first level. I put the bombs on
you. So you have to go in. Okay. Um, hopefully they're pointing the other direction pointing
the other direction. We have a GPS right now. Put the food down. There we go. That's the stuff.
Okay. Hey guys, head to the ground surface. Yeah. Look, have you got arrows? Yeah. Hurry up guys.
Team leader. We have to go fight these dinosaurs. They're not dinosaurs. They're not
fucking dinosaurs. I just hurt myself in the other room. How, how's that possible?
I just hurt myself in the room. Did that just happen? Hey, what do you, how loud are you?
I don't know. That might be too loud. Oh, okay. All right. Yeah. I've been needing to get a new
headset for a long time because my audio leaks and you're a streamer. I know one thing about
you. Is there actually like a sprint button for me? Uh, left L3. Well, actually I think you get
like a dash. I think I can go by the way. I'm definitely going to get all the points here.
Yeah. I remember his dash being cancelable. I think your bombs exploded. Unfortunately.
There's health containers too. Oh, you guys are just making it over here. Hey guys. Yeah. You're
a lot faster. Yeah, I know. I forgot about that. Also my character only gets to shoot
like once every five seconds. Oh yeah. You're using like the vehicle guy, right? Yeah.
Do we get our own Diablo three loot systems part looting system here or is it do it? Am I
picking these up? Like if you pick up armor, you're taking it away from us. Am I actually?
And you're, yeah. And you're going to be picking it all up because you're way faster. Never going
to get looted. Oh shit. Well, you just need to get good. Oh, I can push the bugs around.
Doesn't, doesn't fence or have a, um, a dash like you go rocket feet. I do that once
armor is shared. We'll get there eventually. All right. Hey, the armor is shared.
So if somebody picks it up, it's shared between us all. We're going to just get in here and just
fucking lighten them up. Oh, oh, just defeat these enemies. I don't want to die like that.
Is health shared too? If I pick it up, is it like share between everybody?
Probably not. What did you just say? So it's not like I'm hurt or anything.
Wait, what are you? What did, what's that? What's the last part? Oh, okay. I don't know what those
are. Is it in the hive? Oh, they're on the ceiling. You killed them already. What do you think I'm
trying? So what is, what does flyboy do? What is it like? What does your class do besides glide?
Uh, it's like rockets for us then. Oh, fine. I'm fine. I'll do everything. I'll do it all.
So is armor permanent? Like, yes. Yeah, it is a permanent. Do you play it on?
So if you don't like the, this character, then very soon you need to figure out if you want to
switch. So there's four classes initially. What does that turn into by? Only four. There's like
a thousand weapons. But you unlock new weapons as you level up and stuff like that. Yeah. There's
only four classes, but there are hundreds and hundreds of weapons in the game. So it is not,
oh, only four classes. I get four abilities and an ultimate. Uh-uh. You get an ultimate. I don't
know. Why am I making like a MOBA reference? You don't like even play those. I want to play
those. It's not just MOBAs anymore. Uh, every single game has an ultimate ability now. That's,
I mean, that's kind of true. You know what? I'll hear that and raise you on every game. Also,
including like a boxed open. Is there loot crates in this game? There are. Oh, we have to go the
other. Why does he keep debating us? There are, because you just see I'm picking them up on the
ground. They don't have to pay for them though. So can I get those on the free to play model?
Yeah. Well, it's, it's free. It's free to play after you pay $60. Well, I paid 60 bucks. How
many keys do I get? I don't know. That star knows that more than I do. The reason my star is not
talking. He's got things to do. You got like a piece of ham stuck in your throat or something
there. Sure. I'm up. Pay attention. Monsters are coming from the hole. He's eating with his
mic muted. No, you're doing that. No, I want you to eat with the mic on so you can call out shots
to talk to my viewers about the questions they ask without interrupting your important conversation
that you were having. It was very important. Oh, there's the dash. Oh yeah. And our weapon boxes
that you need to find. Yeah. So here's a question for the chat room here. Uh, is, yeah. Are
because I've been, I picked up at least three of them. So are they shared to share? Good sick.
Nice. I've never played this game before. Uh, I figured out my dash. So far the tutorial was
definitely the best part. Earth corridor. If I complimented me like, oh, you can, you can talk
on the radio and you can summon vehicles and you can do all this. Someone must really trust you.
You must be a high ranked officer. And then you made me look left and right and told me I was
impressive for doing it. Well, you got a participation award. So I just had to get a
medal. So, well, I, the boy scouts watch out for monsters. Don't worry about stealing loot. All
right. That's cool. Right. You guys point them out. I'll get up there and I'll fly up there.
This base is too big for humans. It must be designed for mechas. I was about to say basically
they made this facility exclusively so it could be invaded by giant. Yeah. Yeah.
But it's a, it's supposed to be like that. Don't worry. I'm going to use the gun.
I don't like EDF because it's bad because they say bad dumb dialogue. That's part. That's part
of the allure. That's part of the lotster. They're singing. Be respectful.
Isn't there any response from the ground? That's what your character does.
You just have a big lunchbox. Oh yeah. I got lunchboxes and inside the lunchbox is a gun.
Oh, how do you chant EDF? That just scared the shit out of me. What you just did. I thought you
were yelling. You have the, uh, the touch pad on PS4. Yeah. You're playing with regular menu.
Oh, there's that. Also, I think the d-pad has all the stuff in it. I'm sorry.
I think to do the whole song, you need the
voice so much louder. I like your pink Power Ranger costume by the way.
It's the lore. Oh, that's come on guys. Don't you dare. The least annoying voice in the game.
Part of the lotster. Oh my God. Your gun looks like you're about to refuel a car.
Gas pump. I'll see you have high heels, which is really, but I fly. I fly. So why do you have
high heels to get up to the air quicker? Touch the ground. So they're very comfortable because
he never has to walk. You don't know what those are. Those could be springboards.
I don't like playing this character because when I fly in the air, I don't hear all the fun dialogue
because why I don't hear all the fun dialogue because I'm too far away. Does it have simulated
5.1 surround sound boys? No, it's too far away. I'm just flying around and I'm up in the air and I
can't hear what he does saying. I feel like I need to be part of the amount of ammo and everything.
You just keep standing. No, I don't want to do that anymore. Thank you. All right. Shout out crates
if you see him because I got nothing else to do while my gun reloads for 30 seconds.
Console controls. Come on. Health pack. That's why I'm playing Air Raider Man
because vehicles don't feel like garbage to drive with a controller. So is the Ranger the only one
that can drive vehicles or? Oh, fuck. They're monsters. I was wondering that myself. I think
I can drive them and Rangers can drive them. Yeah. You can spawn them. I think Rangers can also drive
them. Yeah. Don't like Flyboy and you won't be able to use my wheel. I am the wheel. That would
be silly. All right. Shout out crates. I gotta eat this food. Will you stop eating? I haven't been
eating. I don't see any extra crates. Fun hating streamer refuses to spam voice lines. I'm a fun
streamer. See? I'm a hilarious streamer. See? And I apologize to you guys too. All right. I think
we've just beat level one. Quick, go into the light. He thinks if he doesn't get your attention
with one type of voice or like change his tone. Help. We did it. Ladies and gentlemen, that is
EDF. No, it's not. That's like bullshit. That was just like a shitty walk around in a hallway.
Mission complete. Game's over. This is what you play for. So it looks like we got a missile
launcher for the Ranger. Do we have the same screen? I think so. Yeah. Just total items acquired
here. Look at all my items I get to use next round. Yeah. You will launch a lot of new things.
Are we sure? Are we sure? I got three things. All right. Short range. I'm gonna take a look at
those. We got armor up. The power lance. There's so much text. Hold the trigger to fire it.
Power lance is in the short term. Yeah. There's a lot to look at here.
I just look at what the numbers are. You know what I mean? Yeah. But there's a lot of numbers.
I know. But like, yeah, like the rank of your equipment actually. Yeah. Is very important.
So if you have like one that's a four and one that's a zero. Just charge the casket.
It's a big deal. Long range laser gun. Actually I kind of like this.
Also snipe distant enemies. Firepower was lower but can destroy a target by continuously firing.
Accumulate energy by holding it down. Okay. Plasma core that specializes in flying.
Board acceleration has increased. Damn. There's so much. Dude, you can read. I look like a
disgruntled construction worker. Let me get here. I'm just orange and yellow with the
like safety vest. I'm ready. Whenever Jerm is ready because he's the one we're waiting for.
But I'm the one that just got like seven new items to look at. I think the items that we're
getting by the way are um, we all get the same amount but what items you get are. Oh okay. Yeah
because I got a whole bunch from me and I didn't see any for your quest. Let me try this thing.
I guess there was one new fencer item and two upgraded ones for me. I'm just gonna sit here
and eat while you guys talk about your little weapons you got. Hey I love the new Diablo
expansion. Oh you don't have phones? Just armor. Wait you can you can bring your armor down? Why
would you do that? I think it's to scale your slight to lower level people. I'm gonna make
the Jerma colors. Hold on. All right. Um I'm ready. Mission two. Um you guys ever use a
mortar before? Um mortar? Wrong colors. The light mortar. You don't think I know my own colors?
What? Try it out buddy. All right. I will. Yeah but I mean I can't. It's not gonna work guys.
There's not an entire that's as close as I'm gonna get it. More pink but there I can't select it. I
was told that I was the last one not ready. I'm being screamed at right now. Hold on. Oh you can
do triangle for whatever. I'll fix it later. I don't want anyone to yell at me. You will not fix
it and you know it. Okay everybody's muted right now. I just I looked over and the discord was
just muted. So I'm gonna mute too. Fine. All right what's this new weapon I got? Can I zoom in with
this? Oh how do I let go of this? Oh my god are those dinosaurs in the sky? How do I? Holy shit.
Okay this now. Welcome to EDF. This is a yes the proper mission. I'll get it. I'll get it.
Look at this guy. I don't remember how to come close. All right so this is like a little.
I actually like this gun. Please. What do you want me to do? I wanted to see if I could drive him.
Christmas presents hold on. Oh by the way for those of you all you guys watching right now
we are playing this is on normal difficulty because you want you have to really play
to collect the boxes first. Once you get enough boxes. Yeah that was a pretty big mistake too.
Because you could beat the starting missions on like very hard but after a while
you didn't have enough armor to beat the later missions. So what's the like highest
difficulty in the whole game? Inferno which is insane. God. Well that gun kind of is terrible.
Hey uh hey hey. Holy shit. Hey germamites am I like crazy or has that gone terrible?
Oh it's pretty bad man. I'm watching your stream too while I'm playing.
Yeah that's new. Did you just drop like an airstrip of bombs? Well you you you pressed
a call on the bomber and it gives like a it zooms you way out and you place it on the ground now
before you just like threw a smoke and guess where it was gonna go.
How much does first aid heal? Um does it heal everybody or just like the no it depends on how
big the box is. It's like maybe 10 for a little one and maybe 25 for a big one.
Let me see. Does this gun suck or what? I don't get it. I mean no guns should currently suck.
Just seems like it takes a long time to kill anyway.
Here we go. I'm calling in. I'm calling in the thing. I can't wait to see this. I'm so
excited for this. I hope it kills you. It's not gonna kill me. I'm not even over there.
Yeah also it never used to show allies where it was coming in before. Did you do that sir?
I did. What a cool character. I did that.
I wonder if this is like spear gun. Oh oh oh oh oh I like lost audio. There were so many explosions.
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Are you doing the green lasers?
I am. The green laser is not good. I'm doing it wrong. There's so much going on.
So well are all these like friendly mechs here pilotable or are they just like decorations?
I think they're decorations. They're sad because they're funny. Air raider you get like vehicles
later so I can summon those for other things. There's like megazords and crazy stuff. The
helicopters. My eyes. Oh hold on I'll get these. You guys stick with the plan.
This is a special news flash. There have been accounts of UFO sightings everywhere across the
globe. So how the hell if you don't have a winged diver in your party how on earth do you collect
items? You don't. You kind of just don't huh? I think I think like if I had a tank or one of
the jeeps I could do it. Oh yeah you can get a ventral now. Should I get them all?
Okay incoming another way. Ranger can sprint and get to the loot radius now. That's cool.
And these upgrades to aerator are really nice.
I'm just realizing this is using my jetpack. That's why I don't like it.
So I guess you have like a limited amount you can just fly around and just get to like land
birds. Yeah it's it's kind of like it's like a standard jetpack in video game where it has a bar.
It's clear. Yeah I like this thing but I don't like the I'm gonna replace this button.
Don't for some of you guys. Oh my god. Some of you guys would like the long range I think.
You'd like the longer range and a little more direct control. But me I'm not like that. You're
super cool. Thanks man. Hey why don't you pick up this armor? I'm going for it. There's a lot to
pick up. Oh my god there's a lot over here actually. Get that weapon. Oh I got it. I got it.
Okay we're good. Wow they give you five seconds after the mission's over huh?
Look at oh okay it's definitely shared but there's quite a bias here. Okay I'm I don't know about
that. Hey uh who's the new player? Is that me the fencer? That seems like pretty heavy bias. Oh
really? What do you mean? I think I picked the correct class here. Uh do you not see the items
acquired? I'm gonna need about uh that's what I said earlier is that there are minutes or so if
that's okay? It depends on your character like I got a whole bunch of air raider stuff. You did?
I got a whole bunch of fencer stuff. Yeah because of what I'm playing. I got a couple of other
classes things but the majority is it is going to be the class you're playing. I got combat
bombers out here. So we've got class specific loot. Yeah that's plus one letter grade at least. Oh
okay but don't call me down. No one listens to me. No I was listening to you but then like I heard
you listen wait wait wait listens but Italics last mission you were like just ignored you but
last mission you were like oh I didn't get anything or I didn't get shit. Didn't you say
that? I did not say that. I got three new things. What the fuck is happening? You're hallucinating.
Oh this is better. So they actually have the star system here. Everybody make their new character.
Yeah the fun thing about the game is that like pretty much every mission you get
pretty much every class plays with. Yeah pretty much every class. Yeah it's really she had it
fine. Super well balanced. I can't wait till the PvP mode comes up. There's so many items.
It's just like a giant toy box of different weapons. When are they going to release the
cowboy character? Thrown by hand. Shotgun. Oh I got to use the gun. You can't be ready. We just
got eight new weapons. I can only put like one of them just come on man. The game doesn't even
start until I get a vehicle. This thing I don't like this thing at all. So let me change this
thing at least. Yeah I basically am Bob. I'm playing Bob the Builder. It's probably a shotgun.
Like why the heck not? Charge. Maximum energy. Maybe you can tell me this. I have two hammers.
They're close range weapons. If I'm so slow how do you use melee? How do you use melee? Yeah I have
two hammers. I could do like dual with the old hammers. I'm telling you like one of the items
that you got I think it might have been the shield. Someone who's a brilliant gamer at this
game let me know what that brilliant gamer the uh the big boy do the dash cancel so you could
fly around everywhere. I think it was any melee weapon you would need equipped and then you would
have a a dash cancel ability. Lances. Yeah I remember lances being able to do it maybe. Shield
lances yeah. Shield lets you dash cancel. Yeah so mess around with trying to trying to do that.
Yeah it's lances. This game is fucking fun as hell. We're saying deflect shield. Don't you guys
think this game is just fun as hell? No. They patched the dash cancel apparently. Says somebody
over here. They better not have. Fucking blizzard is always like ruining their game with fixing
bugs that were fun. Oh by the way we didn't even get a we didn't even get a star underscore
reaction to Diablo Immortal. You didn't? No we didn't. We played like Lethal League and then
you rage quit and left. I thought I talked to you about it. We didn't get like an on camera response.
On camera response? Yeah we played Lethal League and you rage quit and I haven't talked to you in
like three weeks. Oh it's been three weeks? It's been when did Lethal League come out?
Well I didn't miss you. I said that it was clearly Mike Morhaime did the right thing
by stepping down and he picked a very good time to get out and it's only going to get worse.
It's sad. Are we talking about blizzard drama? It's sad. Yeah sad. Look at the sky. Dude you're
fucking huge. That cloud looks like a like an ostrich.
I was trying look at how cool that is. I gotta have a new bow. I think we have to destroy it.
I don't know. Okay this is this is my move now. This thing is cool. This is also my move.
I only have 10 bullets each. I'm bombing them both. Get out of the way.
Get I trust you'll get out of the way. Get out of the way. Oh that way. Get out of that way.
You missed me good. Can I go in the red circle now? I'm out of juice. Mommy yeah.
Eat shit. Watch this one baby. That's so fun. I can just charge them up. Doesn't seem very effective.
I missed this game. If I knew we were going to be fighting pylons I would have gone like the
single target mortar thing. Should we be focusing the pylons or the ants?
Probably the pylon at this point. I'm shooting the pylon. Well I'm getting the stuff.
That soldier just said body shot. Like he was something I fucking body shot me.
I'm calling in more bombs. Oh come on. I only have one booster. Does that mean friendly fire is on?
Actually I don't think friendly fire comes on until like on the higher difficulties.
That might you might have you might be on to something there. Oh yeah because I was
boiling up explosives on italics when he was fine. That's true you did line me with explosives.
Yeah I don't think you need to worry about it. The lightning gun is actually really fun. It
spreads everywhere. It uses a lot of resources though. I'm shooting a stationary target over
and over again. My stream is loving this game. This is a fun game. Oh my goodness there's a herping.
Wait you have herpes? Oh I can charge the hammers. Don't wait on me. Wait what?
There's like so many goodies in there and I can't get in there. Charge it all the way up.
All right I got them all. Another pylon. I love the dialogue in this game. Will we bring in more
monsters? I think this is it guys. We kill them we save the world. What is that song? Yeah what is
playing? I thought one of you was like playing. You got to go to the other pylon. I'm on the way.
It is said to be 10 meters long, extremely aggressive, and will most likely attack humans.
Stay tuned for more updates. Uh oh something's going to attack humans. Something's going to go
after the humans. I swear to god if you're not picking up all the weapon boxes Jerma.
I am doing my work okay. All right so attack the upper part. Yeah yeah dude the purple thing at the
top. All right I got some time here too. Let's get up there. Watch this point blank eat shit.
Watch this one. You're doing the objective. Oh god I had to have done at least two damage there.
Guys had you been hitting the bottom part of it? No I was yes. Hitting the bottom part of what?
The pylon. Yeah I have. Yeah we both have it. So it's not just me. Yeah it's not just me.
To be fair my weapon can only hit the bottom part of the pylon.
Yeah how's this for the bottom part of the pylon?
Oh I thought you were talking. Yeah I just did it. I thought you were being naughty.
What the fuck? What where am I? Yes sir. All right I'm good. All right did I get all the boxes in there?
It'll cause casualties but not only that casualties.
All right I gotta move. All right there are boxes over here. Sorry guys.
Do you think I'm supposed to travel abroad next week? All right now I can actually help.
I'm coming. Oh no. The last EDF like four the monsters had been dormant but this game now
like everyone doesn't know what they are again. What are they? It's a full reboot.
We rebooted the lore. It's true. It really is true. Man and I read the whole wiki before
this game just to prepare. No it's monsters. Weapons.
I need to get some more fuel in the tank.
Also I think it's safe to assume that in this world ants don't exist
because no one knew what ants were when they showed up. They said they were dinosaurs.
What are they? Dinosaurs? They would technically not be ants unless they were enlarged by some kind
of reverse shrink ray right? They would be like because they look the same doesn't mean they're
the same. I think we get it.
I love this game. Here come more pylons. I love the double hammers you got there.
Oh my god. I imagine if we started on hard. Hey guys start on hard like we did last time.
Yeah that's the they said we got to retreat. I wonder what we got what's inside of our boxes.
Dude you didn't pick up any weapon boxes. There weren't any.
There was a shitload of armor boxes. We only got four weapons this time. They weren't they were
only like three or four. Look at the amount of armor. Look at the HP that I gave you.
I got another spark vine. Is this new? Could you get better versions of the same weapon before?
What? Yeah. You could? I don't remember this kind of upgrading part where you can pick up
better versions of the same weapon. Yeah one of the reasons we never noticed it is because we
started on like the hard difficulty so we had the best versions of every weapon. Oh okay makes
sense. So what does a star mean next to level? I don't know. If level is the most important
factor. This thing is cool. There's like an empty star number too. Yeah I've been looking
at it. It's been confusing me. Okay literally the first weapon of the that I see here in chat is
what I'm gonna pick. I don't care what it is. Like there's something on this list. Sparks. Okay.
Flog. I'm really confused. Oh it means it's for me. It's a star. I like the the shotgun's really
cool but I'm gonna try the grenade. I'm gonna try missile launchers. I'm gonna try readying up.
I don't know how to do that. Chut up. No you chuddle. No you chuddle. It's always a talent.
I can't help it. You gave me too much power.
Why can you do that? Why are there like 30 different versions of ha ha ha?
Ha ha ha. Go to it. Look at it. Yeah I know. It's for how you want to express yourself.
My apology. Blink ball. Let's see what it does. It is just a grenade huh? Oh man that's kind of
cool. That takes a long time to recharge though. Oh yeah this is the one that I actually have to
shoot I think. I get it you're sorry. Oof. Oof. Oof. Roblox. Roblox. Oof. Roblox? No Roblox. Oof.
Oof. I'm really late to these memes. I'm fucking old. Oh we have to destroy pylons. Okay.
We're talking about like. Yeah pylons. Oh check this. I don't know what an ion shield does.
Off the top of your head. You remember how many times we did like the first mission and the last
one? Oh everything about that was what I liked. Everything about that is what I liked. Oops.
Twitch chat is all chat. Twitch chat boomers. Twitch chat is all twitch chat boomers. All right
did people call you guys boomers in your chat? I've never called them boomers. Oh I found my
favorite weapon now. I'm actually becoming a Gundam. Dude. That's just kind of hard to aim on console.
It doesn't matter it's gonna go bot. That's what I was trying to do. Bingo. Um I'll just for well
yeah this film's really good at killing pylons. I'm on I'm on pylon duty. All right I'm gonna be on
collect. Get these damn bugs off me. Hey get these damn bugs off me.
Nobody calls you guys boomers. There's a weapon crate right here. I'm trying to figure out where
they fell. There's one right here. I know. Does anyone call you boomers? Yes. Why would they call
someone who is like seven years younger than you boomers too? I don't know. Oh what? You can't
stand on the tank. I don't know. People just say it to me in a very in a very mean way.
I hope you can still put z gun on the tank. Check it three two one action. I did that. That was me.
I did that. That wasn't you. Yes it was. That was some guy like sitting at a computer somewhere.
Hey so what we're doing. Yeah why don't you ask anyone. It was me. No it was me. I made
you. Okay fine. You ask me anything guys. You too. AMA. We're doing an AMA right now. Not not chat.
I'm talking with YouTube. What direction is the gigantic ship in? North. I feel like I know
everything that I need to know. Yeah you probably do. This is really hard to aim. It just kind of
is and how. Wait that didn't. That's L2. That's really weird. Watch out there's a new pylon.
That camera switch is like. Yeah. Like it. I feel like you probably got asked a lot of questions
and didn't AMA. Oh you said it was just for us. Yeah you said it was just for us. That was the
only question in my AMA. What is this indicator. There's nothing that I care enough about. Are you
sure. Yeah. There's nothing that you want to ask anything. I mean I'm talking anything. This is
ask me anything. What's your twitch password. What's your stream key. Oh oh oh. How much money
would it take to play the new Diablo on launch and stream it. The Diablo immortal. I want to do that.
Dude if like someone gave me a way to stream from a phone then I didn't have to figure out myself
100 percent. It's very very easy. You just need to get them down. Just get the it's just the HDI
it's the HDMI adapter for like apples. You just go to the apple store you pay like the forty five
dollars for this piece of plastic and you just plug in HDMI to it and plug that into like a
capture card. That's it. I'm ready. Oh dude I actually you tried to play with me one time
20 years ago. The media and Excel. Yes. You know media and Excel is getting like a
an HD remastered kind of thing coming out. Interesting. You know that I downloaded that
like four like five days ago. Not even good. I'll prove it to him. He hasn't been pitching
about the Diablo for at least three weeks now. That's correct. What's the Diablo. All of it.
What what do you explain yourself. Diablo mortal thing and I was like what the heck.
Oh well media and Excel things coming out too. Hey I look I'm going to prove to you.
I don't know what you're proving. That I like downloaded it. I have media and Excel installed
on my computer. I swear to god right now. The new Diablo was revealed. Diablo 2. Oh well they're
coming out with like the new version of it that has like it's the HD remastered better than
Blizzard could ever do it version. Really. Yeah it's getting like the skills are being remapped
like all the UI is on. They built a new engine. It's a widescreen. I thought it didn't just release.
It didn't that just happen or is that something else. No they just announced it so that's coming
out in January. Um okay. They've been working on that for a long time. That sounds like fun.
I would highly recommend you try it with me because I'm down to.
And I know all the you need the ins and outs. Yeah I did install the the original one.
The original one I know I can I can prove to you know what despite what I said the day that the
Diablo thing was announced I also installed the game except I installed path of exile.
Yeah well median xl like the guy who made median xl did a lot of work on path of exile.
What is going on over here? It's a lot like path of exile. You should try it too italics.
I'm converting everyone. What are we doing? Is there are we waiting for something?
Shoot the UFO or they're dropping bad guys in.
Building just collapsed and I'm standing. Yeah I've launched rockets at it. Hit it.
Hit it right in the middle. They're dropping down like CDs. Yeah it's just a disc shooter
from like the 90s 90s boomers. I mean there's a game that was on ps2 so. I missed a weapon
crate I was too big whatever. I can't do all the work. You know he missed a weapon crate.
Uh people is see it. If they show up his w's on the map. Plasma big. We're about to get this w.
Oh I didn't get anything new. I'm ready. An up way. Oh another one. Oh another one.
All right so I did but I'm not going to be the last one to ready this time. What am I doing?
Wait does it say what we're fighting? That would be really nice if it did.
I don't know. Oh the flying objects. Oh god. Pulse machine gun. I kind of want to try it.
All right the first thing that I see in chat. Uh machine gun. Wait this is the two different
it's just this one. No I want to get rid of this. It's too hard to aim on console.
All right I'm going to try that again. Oh god Jerma. I got a lot of new stuff.
I'm ready. It's going to be flying enemies. You're not even ready.
Why are you complaining to me? Because I'm waiting for you. I was looking at things
because you were looking at things. It perpetuates itself. You can't be mad at me
because you were also looking at your equipment. Isn't that the whole point of playing this game?
Kind of. Oh new weapon. Spiders. I remember these. I hate these. New weapon spiders.
I hate these things. I fucking hate them. They're so scary. Oh the ones that like shoot webs
and everything. They make really creepy noises. Plasma big cannon. Yes this spaceship was made
by Russians. That's a big cannon. What are those? Oh god actual boomers in chat. Zoom in.
Oh what are those? I don't think this is I don't think I have a good load-up for this level.
Actually laugh at that. Dude I said it was going to be flying enemies like three times
so that you would be ready for this. Shut up you fucking boomer. Fuck.
There is nothing that I like about you. Actually this is this is pretty good.
I'm taking out saucers man. Oh we're taking this. Plasma big cannon.
That's the kind of noise you would actually make if that happened to you.
So what does air support do right now? Don't you have like jets you can call into like
How do I turn this off? I think they were shooting through the thing.
It looked like they were. Oh it's where okay. I kind of enjoy just one-shotting all these.
Yeah it's shooting through the big ship. I like it's not there.
That wasn't boxes. I don't see any boxes. This one. Why does my shotgun have knockback on these?
That's cool it like tracks the saucers. Holy shit that was scary. I'm gonna I'm going to die.
I'm going to die. Do I need to come over? I need I need to find help is what needs to happen.
How do you shoot a major pulse cannon and miss every single enemy that are disconnected and
if they did again. Maybe if you were just picking up boxes like I told you to dead.
I'm dead. I'm down. Taleks to your right. We may have another problem.
Taleks is almost down too. Yeah that's why I'm running over to a stir. Star. Star.
Yeah I'm right next to him. At least I was like. Can I press you guys?
We got annihilated. They're just crashing into each other.
They're just smashing into each other. Press the vehicle rescue button. What the
fuck is the vehicle rescue button? Look just press every button okay.
Thank you. All right now me. Now give me some heals. Are you in support?
They're just crashing into each other. Thank you. I'm gonna die because you're dead again.
Well there is health right there. You just got it. I'm dead. What's the rescue button? It's circled.
Or they will attack civilians destroyed. Yeah we're in a lot of trouble here.
Any more health? I can't tell. I did enjoy being alive for an extra 15 seconds.
I get it. Ataleks you're dead in your bed. Excuse me. I'm coming. Wait.
Who's being resurrected right now? I'm coming. Not me. What are you talking about?
Then why do you have one HP? I have three.
I'm sorry. Did I get you?
You gotta be in this underhang. Oh I have three health. You actually do just have to be in this
underhang. Yeah it's actually been working really well. I'm coming. So there is friendly fire
if you do the explosion on yourself. So are we just gonna just cheese under the fucking sneeze
guard? Okay I see health. I'm going for it in a second. All right I'm back to kind of normal here.
What just happened to me? What did you just do? Did you just shoot a...
I just had 75 health and I'm at zero. What happened over there? Fucking guys are on your own.
Because it's your fault. Okay you aggroed all the enemies. If you had been picking up more armor
we wouldn't be in this situation. Oh he's shot. I can see them from here. Oh yeah? I don't think
we'd get them if we lose the mission. We don't. I'm dead. I'm on the roof too. Good luck getting me.
No one's gonna get me up here. I'm done. Nobody's shot me in a long time so I might just stay here
and not come get you. Yeah. Fucking roof. Oh god. I did so much. Figuring it out. I killed myself.
Hang on. Hold on. I got a shield. Welcome to EDF. Can you guys destroy the building behind you?
Come to me. All right go find another safe place and blow up this building.
No we're winning the mission. Yeah we kind of... this kind of worked out. You're not gonna beat
this. They're starting to get under here. Yeah they're like going. They're surfing on the concrete.
We're gonna beat the mission. Uh no. Remember last game too. The first mission where we started losing
was when they uh all the fucking flying things. Oh yeah I remember. Retreat or restart. Waiting
for the host to make a selection. Yeah retreat or restart. Um just try it again. This time we'll be
prepared. Just get ready for the saucers. I wouldn't mind switching weapons. Oh okay well
then we'll switch weapons. I was a bit rushed. Oh well we did get some armor. Yeah that's not
that idea. Maybe lightning bow. Lightning bow or that spark vine is good. I think I can just I
I don't know. I'm gonna get the bombers and hope that they do things. This thing is too big. Um
no it's got its use. It does. I want a vehicle drama. So pick it up. Or no you're right hold on.
That would be good here. I just got a bunch of zigguns. First one ready. Let the court know.
So what'd you guys do on your Sunday? What's today? My Sunday? What'd you guys do on your Wednesday?
You realize we live in the same house right? No I'm not. I know what you did today. It's today
Wednesday. Today's Wednesday. What'd you do on this Wednesday? I did a lot of stuff. I cannot
talk about it on the stream. People saying that you're quiet. How is that possible? Speak star.
Speak. I'm speaking. Speak. Speaks. This is an example of speaks. Now Alex you talk. Do it
right or I'm coming over there to scream in your mic. I'm gonna be loud and then quiet and this
is normal okay. I'm coming over to scream as loud as I can on your mic if you don't do it.
Oh I'm just what did I just do? Oh he did it okay. We're good. Go scream EDF.
Oh also we do only have three people. Scream as loud as you can and see if you can hear it on mine.
Let's see if this helps a little. Let's see if it helps. Go peak italics' mic. Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
Hold on. Oh fuck. All right you guys should be good now. Oh fuck. Are you ready? Oh fuck.
What are you doing? I am. I am. I am. But fuck. I'm changing stuff. I'm good. Uh oh. No. Good. Good.
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Everything's good.
I guess I'm a lefty now. Okay so I got the shot. This is going to help a lot. I will take care of
the monsters coming up from the ship. I didn't hit one shot. All you have to do is just like
hit things and also not die. Oh this is definitely the weapon. I'm not even going to equip the other
one for any reason. Yeah. I think we just hide under here the whole time to be honest.
Start. We're dropping bombs already. Yeah. So if the aliens attack but the air support specialist
bombs the entire city anyways. Yeah it goes through them. Did we actually save anything?
Um no I'm bombing the street and the street is fine. That's just uh. Like as long as we hang out
under here and I bomb the street then we're good because they kept bunching up on the streets.
I'm in my own little world over here. You guys have fun. It feels like playing a different video
game. Yeah that's that's always how that class feels. Humans. Humans. Uh oh. Uh oh.
I need to recharge for a second. Did he just say if we let them run rampage?
They're gonna run rampant. No he said run rampage. If we let them run rampage.
I don't know if it's such a good idea under here. Oh my. Ow. I don't know if this is a good idea.
Which part? All three of us standing in the same place.
We can risk each other very easily. I'm going out. Don't worry I got knocked back. See that's why
because we just got fucking collateral right there. Well you keep flying around then and just
don't get hit. Do you know how hard this is to do in that game? I kind of just have to stand still.
That's a weapon crit I gotta get. That's sort of what I do. Attacked. Oh we just got permission.
I don't know what we've been doing up until now. Attack the flying saucers. Let the government go
ahead. Ow that hurt. I can hear that all the way over here. Good. And it's starting to bug me.
Get it? Oh get it. Do they really just give you like constant news reports?
This is like um playing fallout where you get all the like data disks.
This is how they tell their story. We're doing a lot better.
Oh come on man. Don't embarrass me on my own stream. Everything's getting very quiet. Yeah.
I thought I was losing my hearing. Easy. Here come more. You're just singing down here.
Why do I have a different voice every time though? Because you're like Darth Vader. It's muffled in
Oh. Oh no. Oh no guys. What? Are you fine? Are you losing?
Is it your fault we're losing? No. What? There's a med kit. I feel like my deflection shield isn't
really deflecting much. Yeah it's because you're. Oh my god. Oh my god. He's not fun for me. I even
have a shield. I'm still dead. Oh my god. I just took so much damage. Oh I died on the
fucking roof again. Oh god damn it. Yeah there this is the wave where it's not possible currently.
Well we can run the other missions get more armor and you know maybe get better
equipment. I don't have the best anti-air equipment. That is correct. Get the clean
crates. It was hard when you get out of cover and a hundred ships surround you and you die in three
hits. Are you making fun of me? What? No I'm just saying our strategy is flawed. I don't have a
strategy. I think you're. Oh dude yeah I could use the bunker. Standing in the same place but to
spread out. Haven't you guys ever seen harbor before? We don't need to spread out. I have the
electromagnetic bunker. It creates a shield that can't be shot through but we can shoot through.
So it can. And we all just stand in the same spot. Well shut up italics. No one likes you.
Whoa no one likes being wrong either apparently.
Hold on a second. What did Ashley put in your food earlier?
Poison. It's rat poison. Hold on a minute here.
Hold on. Here guys we're going again. Not rat poison. What do you mean? Wait wait wait listen
listen to this listen. We go again. I also have I have a life vendor. You know what that does. It
supplies hit points to my allies. Your voice is very loud and fucked up right now. Why is my voice
fucked up? I don't know. I don't know what you did. You like plugged in a different mic. He's just
leaning in. Can you ready up italics? Why are we doing this again on the same level? Yeah we're
doing it again. We go again. I don't know. I told you this. Listen. They can't shoot us. I have
healing. We stand under thing. It's fine. What is exactly what we did last time except there was a
healing item. You're gonna be in big trouble after this. The barrier and the healing. What do you mean
we go? I'm ready. If we lose this time it's just probably italics. No it would be you actually
because. Will it be you? You're the one that we're depending on. Will it be me or will it be me?
Nice whiffs man. Okay when it gets to that phase we all have to we go under the thing.
Okay get to the phase go in the thing. Get to the phase go in the thing. Dude this is
on normal difficulty too. You understand? I understand this is normal. I understand we're
missing a player because you don't have any friends. Wait is that some kind of jab?
There are two players currently here in the same household. So where's your second? Because there's
a plus one invitation. I invited you and German didn't invite anyone. Was I supposed to invite
somebody else? Okay okay let's get under. Everyone under. We're gonna test the strat. I don't know
how this gets deployed. I can't wait until we all die. God that's it. Yeah great girl. It was
actually I who invited you by the way. Just so we're clear. Can we shoot through this? Yes.
All right this stupid strategy is gonna work. How often do you put those down? How long does
shield last for I guess? I have no idea. I have to get out there and pick up stuff though every
on a periodic basis. Well once it ends all the stuff to pick up is gonna be out here.
All right one shield down. We're gonna someone's gonna blow up. I'm gonna kill us. I can already
guarantee it. I gotta get out of here. I can't stay near you guys. You claustrophobic or something?
No I have like explosives. What's what? Why don't you have one over here? Hey what the fuck?
Got destroyed and I can't place anymore. Here have a have a heal. I put the heal. What do you mean a heal?
I put the heal drone thing down. There's green. Why do you why do you why have you know you've
been using that since the very beginning? That's a great one. I was using artillery
and it's more fun. I don't want to be the fucking support for you. Interesting you picked a class
called air support. Yeah and I have nothing that comes from the air. Also it's called air raider.
Whoa raid my health bar. Whoa that's what you should be doing not raiding the ground.
All right I don't know how I get more barriers. This is my chance to get some stuff. I might have
to pick up like a weapon box to get more I don't know. It doesn't oh I do press reload on it and
then they'll go away. Well I'm not gonna have them for a while. Oh no you're not? Okay well
then this strategy yeah what's your cooldown on the on the deflection? It's like 20 percent
reloaded. Here comes the big wave I think. I still have more health I can put down. Yeah I
think this is the big one. It's incoming in a second. How?
All right here it is. I hope you guys are prepared. I'm blocking this guy on the left.
Oh my lord. All right here it comes. I'm so scared. Don't worry this is easy. This is the easier
mission because there's so many you can't miss. Did you switch the difficulty for the
oh shit and we have we have the healing station still up. Powerful countries attacking us Jerma.
Ow. Keep it up. It's almost I almost have barriers. Good because we're gonna need them.
Oh god. It's pretty good for my shotgun because they're right on top of us. I don't know if I'm
hurting myself or they're hurting me. Oh no I got some down. I got some down. Awful.
You guys aren't even using them. Get behind my shield. I see it. Get behind my shield. Move
with the grace of someone wearing perpetual ice skates. I do best Reinhardt impression. Go
italics now. No. Stir. Overwatch sucks. I can't. What are we doing? Why are we?
It's trying to show us the new thing but we're all dying.
All right I'll go.
That could have been like a lot of characters.
The silence is what's getting me right now. All right I gotta get that. I'm focused.
Retreat. That means we did it. We did it. I can't. It's too green.
Why is there a nuke? The building's gone.
What? The building's gone. Our only source of cover just vanished. Hey there's no doubt they're
aliens guys. Any green crates today? I'm trying to get the fucking crates. You guys are laughing
having a laugh at about it a little bit over here. I'm trying to collect boxes. I don't think it's
over. No it just got way harder. We gotta find a new building. Yeah we gotta change position here.
You're dead? Yeah. Oh boy. Hold on. I'm coming. I was boosting as fast as I could to keep up.
Does that take health from me? I think it does. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. If I put my back to another
building I have more bunkers. I'm almost dead again. I got you if you do. Trying to just stay
close. Hostile forces. No way. I can't believe they're trying to kill us. Do you have a heal?
I don't. I can't do any more heals. There's a couple boxes. That would be very convenient.
Where are they? Like on the road there's some. Heals? Yeah there's a couple here. Well
if I could move faster than five miles an hour I would love to get. That's the worst part about
the character you're playing. Holy shit that takes half my health. Yeah you have to split
your health with me so I'm just a liability right now. Oh look at this. Find some cover.
Look at how many are here. We need to find a way out of here.
Holy shit. I'm stuck on a rock. Star any right ideas? I'm trying to get to a shield.
He's got super shield over here. Oh help. My health. Oh shield's already down. I don't know dude.
Yeah there's health right next to me actually. I'm down. It's just germabot. Yeah there's a health
box right next to me and there's a health box in front of star. Oh okay. All right just don't
pick me up. Your health is better spent like right now shooting things. Holy fuck. Are we
getting reinforcement? They're talking about reinforcing us? I don't even know what to shoot
at. There's so many. Oh boy this is where I die. This is where it's all gone. Holy shit. I'm dead.
I didn't actually mean to say thank you. My headphone hit it. It's just you man.
Well this is easy. I have no way I lose this. Ah there's a health crate. I'm in. I walk inside of a
ship. I think we hit the gear. I think we hit the gear check mission. We did get at least some more
armor. We did it. BMing. No I accidentally touched. Because we're still like finding loot and stuff
right. So you just get a portion of the shields that are better to shield cancel for movement
than others. I mean you can always go back and we can do another one and get better. I like still
don't have a vehicle. Dragon Lance. Interesting. Single shot great damage however it requires
several times the energy of a standard power lance. Longer charge time. Okay might be worth
using. Bolt gun. Okay let's see. What did we get? This one. I should probably mute. Everyone else
is muted. All right. Bolt gun. What to do. New type of gun that fires multiple electric bolts. I want a vehicle.
Bolt gun and then dragon lance. Um maybe we should try the dragon lance. High output. Look at that
thing. It's like a drill. Try it. All right. I'm ready. Are we doing an older mission? What are we
doing? We should probably just let's go back to the last mission. And so. Can you do the last mission on heart?
That they fixed my dash cancel and it doesn't work anymore. I heard people saying that earlier.
Um we can do that mission on easy and then just keep playing. On easy? But don't we want to do
you want to do it on easy? Do you want to go back and do one of the missions on heart? I kind of
just want to progress. Also yeah I mean usually before you could do like the first mission on
heart and get higher level stuff. I think that that's still the case isn't it? Probably. Want to
try that? You want to go back a mission and just do it on heart? But usually I think like in normal
in normal difficulty there's a there's a weapon level cap of like you can't use high level
shit in normal. Yeah it might be. But some sometimes here we're gonna we're gonna do it.
We're gonna we're gonna do it. Hey naked face game. This is the uh all the little bugs are
gonna rush us. So I'm gonna change my shit. So how the heck are you? Me I'm good. I'm ready.
Waiting for italics. So this is the last mission on heart. No this is one of the first missions on
heart. Please don't tell me this is the corridor mission. No not that one the one after that one
because the corridor mission is stupid. So well what kind of support equipment do we eventually get?
I have like two empty support slots for example. Um I don't for fence fence or I don't know. Yeah
I don't remember them having support. All right let's try the bolt gun. Oh okay. Oh you're hurting
me. I am. Oh it's this guy. EDF teaches you pretty early on to go back and farm now that repeated
weapons get upgraded. So I guess if you find the same weapon again it upgrades. That's cool.
All right so uh I guess two auto cannons is better than one. Oh this this thing is actually
really great. It's a great single target weapon. Dragonlance was a good choice. Whoever suggested
it thanks for the suggestion. It doesn't go that far though. It's still in normal? What?
Did you not change it? I definitely set it to hard. Did you confirm it? I don't know how you
could tell that it's still in normal. I'm not seeing very many crates. It's so slow. These are
so heavy. Wait what? It says there's one right here but there's not. Oh boy. Well I'm just getting
the armor. All right well there's a weapon crate. Well this definitely doesn't feel harder.
Does this go through everybody? I think it only goes into one person. Yeah it does.
It does but I am collecting.
This thing. I'd rather just use the other lightning gun. Wait why are our combat suits
acid resistant? I wonder if we ever had to deal with acid things before. Listen acid. It's in the lore.
I don't think so. Wait they're not. What? How do they not.
There's a weapon over here. It's so hard to aim. You don't see it anywhere to buy? Yeah for some
weird reason. This game is not featured anywhere on the PlayStation Store. You have to go looking.
No you have to like look for it. You can like purposefully search it. Oh god in 2018 you have
to search for your game. Well I mean you actually have to go into like all games. Actually though
if you go to the Epic game store then there's no search bar so I think they're figuring it out.
That's 2018. You shouldn't have to search for games anymore. What's with what's with this?
I don't want to talk about stores. I want to talk about monsters to shoot with our monster guns.
All right basically no one buy this game. That guy just come on comments and say it's okay if
you're a civilian. What? All right I'm searching. I'm searching. Scanning the area. I'm scanning. I
see one red box. I can't wait to get a good view of this. Look at this one. Nice dude. I want to
see a I want to see a mock-up of like who got the most kills. A mock-up. You don't want to see that.
You'd be very disappointed because it's not you think it's you it's the destiny not me.
It's going to be a talent. What? What are you talking about? Oh dude I'm gonna mock up. We're
talking about the Epic game store and how. Excuse me I thought we were not talking about game stores.
Yeah you just said that. Yeah you did just say that. Well we're talking about Epic games.
You guys know that I installed Fortnite yesterday and opened it to the menu. Doesn't it make you
install Fortnite? I did. Why? Because every time I died in Hotline Miami I was going to play around
to Fortnite. Oh. And then I kept getting very I died like 335 times. That's a lot of Fortnite games.
Yeah that was a lot. It was a lot. The stream was like 65 days long. Oh you're the W. God I
thought the W was weapon. Hang on. Fortnite and W is in the same sentence? Excuse me. What? What
stream am I on? What are you talking about? On the map for me you're a W. W. You are a W.
Star is an A. Oh yes. I'm not even on the map. No you're an F. F. That's that's accurate. So he's
the A for A student. F for F student and then W for weirdo. Can you please not? You said today
you were going to be good. I did say that. I did say I was going to be like good today. What is good?
No I didn't. I didn't fucking say that. I'm not even going to perpetuate that bullshit. I didn't
say anything. You just lied twice. Don't you know that 85% of everything I ever say on stream is not
true. We've already talked about this. Is that true? I don't know. Is that in the 15%? I don't
know. You have to figure that out. So is this part of the ask me anything? Could be. It is now.
No I'm not going to go peek at Alex's mic. So how much truth are you doing right now? Is that a lie
too? You need to watch Interstellar. Hey don't spoil that movie. I haven't seen it. I'm going
to change your parameters. Holy shit there's so many things over there. Get it. Got it.
Okay there we go. Now that's what I'm talking about. Mad weapons. Mad weapons.
Yeah I got a bunch of the same shit. Mirage zero. Homing weapon. Leveled up. All right that's pretty
good. Turbo core. Level up. Yeah you have to click apply settings when you change the difficulty.
Spark mine level up. Energy cost is down. That's good.
Why? More capacity. Lot more capacity for the machine gun. So do you want to try and do that
on hard or no? We could. Okay I'm putting on hard and I'm applying the setting. Also this means
there's friendly fire now. Okay which mission is this? Sorry. It's the same one we just did.
Okay so interesting. All land based. Grenade. Bolt gun I'm not a fan of. Maybe when it's upgraded
it's better. Oh I feel like this would be not. Looks like we're waiting on a couple other people
to ready up right now. Yeah but hold on. Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. Yeah I'm gonna
kill you guys. What? What the fuck are you talking about? All three of my equipment are artillery.
Oh fuck. Do I get like a friendly fire on in hard? It shows you and then you can move. Okay
That was just that was really that was a weird way to start that. I'm gonna go kill you guys.
I'm gonna kill you guys. Stop. Stop this. I'm the one that's supposed to be good today. What?
What does it have to do with anything? You get you both are talking about killing me.
Yeah well you haven't been very good. There's only one of us that would actually do that though.
Whoa. And it's not me. But I you know I don't have motive but I do have opportunity.
Oh I accidentally did the other one. What do you mean the accident? What'd you accidentally do?
I had moved the mission forward and I didn't I didn't approve of it. Why are you doing these
schools? Are we restarting? No. I wish I could shoot my Gatling at the same time as the mortar.
Because I should be able to destroy these pretty easily with the shit I have.
Well yay. Actually I kind of don't mind. This is really this is really just brainless gun.
It just locks on and homings. It's a matter of class weapons.
So do weapon boxes actually appear on the minimap or do you just have to spot them?
They appear on the ground. That's I know they're on the ground. I'm asking if
okay well you think maybe the green dots are you were jokingly saying I'm going to kill you but
you did. I didn't mean to. You bet you did. And that did not last very long. So I wonder
is Star the one that's killing us? No I'm the one that's winning the mission. You have heals anymore?
No. Oh I guess I'll just die though. I just got I just landed on my neck.
I just got blown up by your extreme explosion.
All you gotta do is not stand next to the pylon. Hey all you gotta do is not lay it down on top
of our name tag which is visible across the entire map. I'm not. I keep throwing them on the pylon.
Fucking boober. All right pick me up. I'm picking up the weapon chest.
No I think we get shit even if we fail.
Don't die forehead. Just don't die forehead. Let me get full health and I'll come rescue you.
I can't damage these myself. I like only have artillery. I'm trying to get as many things as
I can. I think even if we die we get them because last time where when we failed that um
the air the ufo one we still got shit. I just need like a second. Boom. All right I'm just
gonna stay up here for a second and just take a look. Any more crates? I can get down over
the pylon. Just crates. I'm gonna try to get some. Singular ants can kill me. Yeah they do a lot of
damage because it's hard. Okay I don't have a cool guy dodge roll. I have just I jump one time. Be
aware of that happening. Oh my god. Okay are you doing it again? No okay. Jeez Louise man. If you
want me to I can. All right I'm dying over here. I'm coming back there now. I had to pick up stuff
with the pylon. Oh what? Walking dead episode. What the fuck are you doing? What? You just panicked
me. You panicked me. You maybe pressed my button and I fucking hurt myself. I meant to cancel the
throw but it doesn't. It didn't. Stop calling me a civilian. All right are we okay? No. No there's a
bunch of ants coming at me. Well do something about it. I don't have any guns. I'm a civilian.
Yeah are you actually? Oh baby. You just laser yourself. Yeah. I'm just gonna hide in this bush.
I'm almost out of power. I'm out of power. I need more power. Can you kill like one thing?
You don't understand. It's very hard for me to do what I'm doing right now.
I have to wait. If you kill one thing I get more bombs. I mean yes I did. I killed five
okay and now it's gonna kill me. No don't. Oh I see. That's why I can't dash or jump because
those are my support items I have yet to unlock. I'm just gonna break my fucking controller in my
bare hands. Do we get any items? We did. All right look at these though. That's a level two
pulse machine gun R. Yeah I didn't really get anything good for me. Same shit. Look at that.
Smaller range but better. Pulse machine gun R. R for really good. The big cannon is kind of hard
to use. Yeah look at this. This is a huge increase. Nine damage to twelve faster rate of fire. Okay
we're doing the not pile on one on hard. I feel like I'd rather just use the let me see what this
thing does. I think I'm just yeah I'm just gonna keep shields on permanently. I'll go back to the
shotgun. Yeah shotgun seems pretty decent here actually. I also have one. Jerma should play
Dante must die. DMC. Oh did you hear the drama about the new devil may cry? No I did not. What
drama? I don't think there is any. Well let's make some. Wait hold on you you're just making that up.
Well there's this really weird intro sequence like scene where he just starts like slapping
women and saying like really sexist things. What's wrong with your brain? What's wrong with Dante?
That's a great question. I hope that team ninja answers for this. All right here we go.
All right grit shot. I can hear that. Let me see if I can hear again. I could I could hear that.
Like they say only people under a certain age can hear that noise. Only dogs. Dogs are if you're
young enough you can hear that. Dogs. All right I'm gonna do something tell me if your dog does
anything. I'm gonna put that as my ringtone during class. I'm gonna try and not kill you.
Please don't. That is what set me down the death spiral last time. This thing's actually pretty
effective. Look at the boxes. Fobos. Fobos. What? There's a bunch of weapon crates over here.
I'm going around collecting them. Okay I'm bombing these guys.
All right I'm staying near you because I don't think you'll bomb yourself.
I mean he would. He already did it. He did already do that. Did he bomb himself? Oh yeah.
Yes he did last mission. No it shows you. I actually I did last mission. Yes he did. That
was an accident. So it happened at least once. Hold on I see a weapon. All right collecting.
Two weapons. No I want them. Okay can you guys kill these ants? Like these dinosaurs?
Oh yep yep yep yep yep. I'll try. I'm calling you. Oh god that poor guy.
Shit I'm right. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. Oh my god this is not what I'm aiming at.
Oh you're dead dead. Watch out I'm bombing you. Maybe actually good. Maybe that'll knock me over
to near a tower. You're just stealing all the guns. It's sharing. I am putting myself. See it
helped. I'm putting myself in harm's way to get all the items. I'm coming. And then I get bonked.
Oh I almost shot you. I may have shot you. All right I'm here. Someone just said I'm good.
I want you guys to know that. I mean you are but you you are good but like yeah only only at very
specific things. Like what? Table tennis. You were good at table tennis. You are? That's about it.
I heard that. I heard that. Okay easy. Anything over there? Yeah they survived through my earth
right. Oh boy. Oh jeez. Oh boy. Oh jeez. There are too many enemies. I would agree.
I gotta stay in the air. I'm also trying to stay in the air. I got another. Okay it's time to do
or die. Are you bombing yourself? Yes. That's a sun suit tactic. God damn it. God. Danger close.
I'm coming. This is danger close. I feel like this game's harder than last game. Personally.
Oh my god. I got you. Get up. Because we need. We need you. I'm dead. I distracted a bunch of
them though. Now they're all coming for you. Sweet. Hold on. I can still get stuff.
Yeah just pick stuff up. They're all coming over here. All right. Just pick up as much as you can
then die. I have an idea though. What if I bring them all over here? And then we're going to go
for it. Here we go. Ready. Hold on. We're ready. Oh this is not going to take long to just die
again. Yep. Welcome back. Red wizard. And then don't worry about me for a second. Welcome back.
Is playing a man down change the spawn or no? Like are we playing a four player tuned? Yeah
we're playing a man down and nothing changes because of that. Oh yeah I guess that helps
explain. Any more items? It's like seeing a monster hunt a world without the cats.
I see that explosion about to happen. Is that done? Is the explosion over? Yeah you'll see
the red on the ground. I'm sorry. Oh my god. I mean if you just fly forever you should be able
to kill them eventually. That's true. This is the last wave I have. Yeah this does seem like the
final wave. You just have to get good. I'm handling things don't worry. Do you want to
resurrect anybody? Just so you have to stay good. Oh they're up on the building.
I can still like see the vomit of projectiles. God damn it. Stop singing. You're covering my
screen with like fucking notifications. You've got like annotations all over my screen and it's
fucking me up. There's cheese puffs following you. God. Yeah. You got this. I need to wait. I need
to get. Look just don't get hit. Oh no what did I do? Mistake. Mistake. Mistake. Mistake. Mistake.
Mistake. Oh I like playing this game with the soundboard enabled by default. You just jump by
me. Look how much health you got. How many times did I say help me? And you just go right by me.
Yeah don't res me. Res him. He can call down an airstrike. Do you want to be resurrected?
I thought I was supposed to just run away and kill them. There was no reason not to get me
up. Okay well then fucking there we go. One two three. I panicked. Hold on. Let's count to three
again. One. Listen help me too. Two. Three. Do it. Help me. Oh nice airstrike. Look at all those
ants get demolished. How many more people are left? Dude I am the GPS. I can get you. I can get you.
All right. Where the fuck are you? Oh you're. Oh I'm over here. Hey what's up? Oh I'm down again.
But there's like there's not very much. I'll be down again in about two seconds as well.
There's only like six. There's seven. There's seven. Don't put pressure on me. Save this like
a hundred. There's a hundred. You have to res me. Okay I'll get you. No fuck this. Let me prove
that I'm capable. Quiet. That's no noise. Oh my god I'm losing my mind. You can just do it.
Just get over here. Both of you. I don't even care. Wow that was that was like an anime
resurrection. You just whizzed by me. It was crazy. All right well I have a shotgun and a mortar so.
All right I'm coming. I think you did it. Oh no.
No.
There's another wave. Oh god. No. There's it's the double wave. It's like the super wave. I'm
going. I'm running away. I'm going on a building. Oh no. I'm making my last stand. Oh my god.
What the fuck have I done? Well the mechs are online or whatever that's worth.
All right hold on. Hold on. This is this might not be terrible.
There is a health pack right next to me as well. Okay hold on. Oh my god. What.
I have the wrong thing. Health pack right next to you Tox. Yeah coming in. Honestly then I get my
artillery back when things die. So because there were more things I could just I just spammed them.
We did it. Oh fuck. I see a weapon. Get me. I can't get it. What the fuck.
Three weapons. Did I get it? Oh I almost pulled my whole monitor down. Level five items.
I got powered exoskeletons. We're good now. We did it. Atalix. High five Atalix. You did it.
You did it Atalix. Okay but now we have better stuff. Like you couldn't have won without me
distracting half the enemies for the two seconds it took me to die each time. You might consider
switching to ranger just because like fencers are so you need to like people are saying you get
you get movement things on your support options later well what did you just get because you
should have got some higher level stuff for um special i did get enhanced boosters add booster
one well it sounds good atalix that's a lot better better version of the post machine gun
are the thing we were just using better though if you do want to play ranger i can also summon
a exoskeleton you can try it now that kind of sounds fun top secret super weapon its very
existence is classified there's oh i think i want that oh that's better in the core that's called b
are we doing the aerial mission again or want to do another one on hard or something
you want to try the one we just did a bacon discharger discharges cooked bacon okay so same
mission did you say bacon launcher yeah can i get a confirmation same mission i'm trying to decide
if i want to switch classes yeah let's give him a second figure that out because i have one extra
booster is there really going to be like the difference maker in my whole class well what was
your the other stuff you've leveled up did you get better for that mission i only got like a
i got a level five shield and add one booster um yeah i don't know switch play ranger okay
i wonder what i should use right now well then yeah we can do the same mission i can summon you
the mech and you can play ranger lightning bow 100 per second things are better across the board
let's try the super weapon and then their upgraded lighting bill i wonder how cool this thing is
oh shit that does so much more damage i was like i don't want to use some dumb limpid gun but it's
like a level three and does so much more than everything else i'm ready yeah are you going to
try ranger it doesn't hurt just to try it for one mission yeah it really it's a lot of um
like projectile explosives rocket launchers grenades that type of stuff machine guns
as some of their weapons are okay but they're basic it's a very balanced basic class that has
good weapons you know the fencer is oh wow dash around you got your huge you have these big
arm cannons and lances you get to fly if you play the the wing diver the air raider vehicles and
big explosions rangers just i have weapons and i shoot them and i'm that's it all right let's
you can just ride my mech you can just do that the whole mission okay we'll give it a try because
it's a level five mech i'll be able to actually walk without um ice skating oh no this thing is
going to be slow as hell yeah you guys but you come on you got to put like whooshes in the middle
whoosh like that's if there's a storm there's gonna be rain lightning wait so i i let's see
how this thing works oh i can't summon the mech yet i think it's a long oh my god okay
how long does it last it lasts a long time this thing just shoots myconykes everywhere all right
okay i'm gonna get used to these new controls here this thing's pretty cool now you're good
you're good guys oh you're good that's like a insane person time for revenge time for revenge
this thing this thing is so inaccurate this thing is so this thing is so do i have to like not be
moving i can't zoom with it you just shred i think this thing shreds why am i using that term
civilian um civilian stir how do you choose between jumping and dodge rolling uh you have
to hold left to dodge usually okay so i'm holding l2 and sometimes it rolls and sometimes it jumps
yeah yeah it's rolling is left and right oh i see jumping is and weather i cast off these petty
illusions so where's that uh awesome mech i i have to kill enough things like we have to as a team
fill enough things before i can summon it it's about 75 percent oh no no no what are you doing
to me i don't even know you're doing this oh did you get bombed almost it takes a long time to
come in your time that's good initiation procedure get initiated watch out behind you're actually
like crazy glad you know yeah it's really good because their projectiles are so slow by comparison
get out of the dirt it's kind of like dark souls hey i play that you're playing it's like the the
souls of ants sim the souls of ants sim yeah what the hell does that mean there is like a sim
ant game right yeah i tried to play it yeah good games it's very old all right that's the it's
identifying characteristic it's old sim ant yeah i played that once it's old right through the front
door one two get it out there okay i'm i'm almost sort of kind of at the point where i could maybe
summon this thing that i wanted to have it looks like um does it matter if you burst fire or just
hold the button down uh for accuracy yeah for accuracy that's a good question oh i'm just
stinging get away from me okay i can summon the thing all right i guess i press circle
i'm going to take this opportunity to pick up this stuff that's a lot of health over here
just make sure if you need health you come over over this way i need that diffuser such a word
blown out it's terrifying i'm coming eat it i need it oh yeah yeah walk into it come on
i'm actually way better at killing things as a ranger
where the fuck is my thing
i try to keep them around this thing so they just die eventually and not summoning it
okay what i assumed it was the same button to revive people because it said that the
vehicle button oh i'm going towards the smoke stand ball for titanfall
stand fall i'll come back to you guys under it will i get smashed i think so
okay i kind of want to do it sure nope it didn't smash the bug there it is well go get it yes
all right let's see it powered up why do you have like silly spring on your hands
i think it has limited ammo so be aware of that what is it may i
my is it the same buttons to shoot i think it's so slow yeah they're really slow but as long as
you stay there anymore armor oh boy any more crates that i didn't see before there's a jump button
what does r1 l1 do
i don't even see my grenade game supposedly firing dude my game rate just went down so
my frame rate just went down so much my game rate my game rate just went down all right time
to collect how are you supposed to walk in a straight line like mech is drunk oh my god i
gave my mech to the fucking newbie to be fair this has two guns on it one is a grenade launcher
which all the grenades have a fuse and the second gun is like dragon ball z
start picking up boxes oh that's what i'm doing don't don't kill them all box time
that's what i'm doing for the last like two straight minutes if i pick up health in the mech
though i heal um maybe but yeah there's two separate control schemes here all right i got
buster nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice oh i got different ones now and i got the armored
vehicle grape i'm just playing scout in man versus machine um in a sense dude i love the grape
the glep near the gleap near that's a level five special okay the destroyer blaster well looks or
the lightning bow m2 we got some toys to play with why can i hear myself every time sorry that
was that's me i could just hear myself every time you got very loud well you keep peeking your mic
no i don't power lance more range that's a lot more capacity oh boy i just found six new weapons
so many toys numerous beams over a wide area okay okay yeah yeah one raven okay uh salt rifle
is the m2 uh pump action shotgun all right damn plasma fault damn mirage zero damn the gleap near
discharges a ball of energy this is missiles that home and on nearby enemies um okay scout bomber
all right so would you like to go back and do the aerial mission i think we're ready i think we
might be ready so i think i agree um for the aerial i'm debating between taking a second assault
rifle or if we're gonna hide under the building again a shotgun are we gonna do the like hide
under building thing i want to try my new toys i don't know i think we might be strong enough
to not have to hide but who knows i'm gonna take the i'm gonna bring the healer with us again
destroy your blaster um i just need class people only one capacity though
that's just too big i'm gonna try with this the new lightning bro and then this crazy weapon i have
a heal now i think heal subordinate soldiers i'm gonna try the new weapons you hear that
subordinate can you put on actual armor uh no armor just health and you pick up those little
red boxes to permanently increase it that's the only way oh wait yeah i had i had the grape
is that just uh transportation what do you what do you say about grapes i have the grape what's
the grape oh no it has a howitzer on it and it carries four people do you have to be a ranger
to get in yeah oh i think so anyway oh sorry the heels only for me listen i'm on a new character
class and there's a gun called anti-aircraft impulse that i guess i'm gonna try you're eating
like gum in in your mic like unwrapping it in your mic in yeah i'm unwrapping it inside the mic
are you marked as a oh god we have this on hard why did you do this to us accident also i didn't
even select the mission did i oh non-rangers can be passengers in the grape cool no i mean
you protein bar i mean these little snack replacement bars all right what if the prince
was a it's the wrong mission anyway i have to change it i don't have the shit for this
oh i thought we were doing the air control mission we are i just i'm a bad host and all
complaints directed at me look at all those items we got get on it man come on that's when we ready
hey get on it it'd be great if like the telling me that germa has selected an item isn't covering
up the options like what i can't ready because apparently i'm not allowed to oh no i can't use
this i can't use these two things ship it's the same problem as last time yeah you could use oh
yeah you could use them on the other mission because that was hard oh like you can yeah i
have to lower my level looks like up to level three is all you can use hmm okay still ready
i'm gonna try plasma fall fuck it you know what i mean um i have a destroyer blaster who cares
it's really chewy chewy i hope that plasma fall is good at shooting uh airborne dart
i hope it is too i don't think it is i remember that weapon really chewy though so that's where
that's one yeah it's pretty chewy that's one good thing can you open another into your microphone
god are you beating i saw all of them by the way i'm testing the new weapon i have never used it
i saw 100% hey jerma do you need jerma to come back do you need any gatorade ah jerma you need
gatorade no no we just won the championship no what's happening don't dump it on me oh what
good joke this thing what the fuck look at the range on this thing wow plasma plasma falls like
you fly up into the air and mortar down on people who made that i thought this thing would be
doing more damage so what does this thing do i got a little blinky red boy yeah this thing sucks
for this god we are we're in bad how long does this stay put all right yeah that thing's not good
oh does it only shoot one enemy i'm i am holding it that's as far as it goes that's a single
aircraft claymore yeah this is not good let's kill nine aircraft plasma destroy is not bad
it's got a good range and it doesn't take my uh jet pack yeah so i have nine of these why wouldn't
i bring with the homing things that i have i want to try the new weapon worth a try see if there
were they had a homing thing as well but it's only a single shot this thing this thing's good
this thing sucks oh fuck i forgot it's using my am i wall that's that's a surprise that's a surprise
egg it's you it's white no one will ever know all right i understand yeah i'm like useless right
now this does have decent range oh you can reload these i'm dead there's a giant health pack next to
me though there's a large we'll we'll spread out coming don't pick up the health before no i have
to because otherwise i'd be at like two health isn't it group heal oh whoops i've no i tried
to swim no group kill the yellow reduces damage you take oh well i'm just gonna only use these
impulse grenades from now on i can't even just i can't do anything this gun is super bad just
germa's character screaming in pain it was supposed to be better it was a higher level
is my thing actually doing anything i'm just gonna go get weapons
i don't think we've got this one in the bag as they say i mean there's so many people here i get
to summon the uh stop reloading they live here okay i feel you well okay no substantial information
about the flying object the other weapon i have is really not great at all there you go i didn't
reload now i'm fully protected against all ufos right here
oh come on destroyer somehow this is working well this defense thing seems really good
we're barely we have double defense because i'm putting down nine separate anti-airs like
shotguns that's the red flashes all right here comes more all right time to reload
oh humans anymore if they were attacking any other mammal we would not be so concerned
basically i love that series what series any other mammal no he's talking about your
basically series oh so he's being a sarcastic cunt whoa whoa my god what the fuck it's a reload
i was just in shock all right here we go uh are you in the mech yeah cool oh my god i think but
it's dealing a lot of damage also i'm almost dead easy easy there what people say that in
england like it's the word serial you're fine demonetize yeah this thing shreds that guy's
already dead all right here it comes that weapon crate but i guess i'll just look up we have to
move from here and die we gotta move from here oh my god they're destroying everything here
it's okay i have a dodge roll his eye frame get me in that little zone
it's still this is actually working i really can't believe you said that on stream star
what like you said serial on stream why are you gonna be so tight you can't say cereal
oh that that green i'm shooting at us what happened to me why does that happen to me
that shot a super giant green laser i love that line i gotta get to this heal there's what there's
a healed station down still where's it in the green where i am oh no it's gone it disappeared
right as i got shoot i'm almost reloaded my guard post though which is the defense this is a pretty
good little weapon here for this mission oh my god okay here comes a shit load where are we off
to and people said this class was boring all right you got it down good i don't think they had anti-air
beacons before i gotta get this health let me try and drop something here
so much going on this actually might work
found the heel the gigantic ship god damn it what happened they're all relatively quite large
i oh my goodness this is what it would like to play far cry five this is what it feels like to
choose right dump sponsored all right i'm gonna start collecting audio back is it really gonna
take this many shots to kill you what the heck was that there's no crates really anywhere i'm
gonna fly over me i dare you okay seriously this thing is a machine gun that like one shot sees
what is it yellow force field uh like our just our health up like she like we resist damage better
yeah yeah there's this damage quite a bit which is i think a big reason why we weren't dying
all right let's see a couple over here did we beat it i don't know it seems kind of quiet seems very
quiet you see any crates into teams of hundreds i don't see any great danger now there's two down
here he's all right we're gonna play laser tech uh there's still something coming this way
let's just race ships over there i just thought you might want a disco party what is over here
since you've got these big red uh flares coming out of your gun these things are remaining
these things are stuck in the building i would have so many points right now
it's gonna stuck in the building you're not allowed to look at me he's desperately trying
to get over here look i'm gonna protect you i'm gonna make sure not a single alien ship
gets in i should uh i should reload my stuff just in case we're not done
i think we're good there you go stand in that circle you'll be safe forever
hey we finally beat that mission what do you know all right i got the suppressed gun
oh dude you try out this new silent gun suppressed gun we finally beat it
well what difficulty was that on that was uh that was normal that was the normal that we couldn't
take it before closed laser turbo car grit shot up okay what did it do though this mag blaster
so every time you get a level up it increases the star counter right
i yeah this doesn't go level up just because you got an up no it's just i think it's a randomized
chance to have like a better roll maybe depending on how what level it is oh i think if you just
look and don't immediately press x on every notification it tells you exactly what it
did yeah it shows you what like what yeah increase too but i just have to x fast because i don't have
time to look oh you're you're you're mashing x yeah because because i'm the last person to like
ready up so i gotta go fast well don't listen to him he's a fucking psycho i'm not saying anything
all i'm saying is that you guys better watch out for my suppressed gun i'm gonna try this i'm
going to suppress your audio well does it doesn't say what the next mission is
heading into the city i think it's more air things we need to so many is the same healing
the quiet threat weapon level up to level three armor limit 320 or less the plan was to head to
the city through the industrial area but look at those flying saucers in the sky we need to be
careful all right so is this like a primary error should i keep my anti-air yeah load up
sounds like it shouldn't do that i'm gonna use my suppressed gun on them i mean you did you have
said that four times now i think that's because the mission name is the quiet threat i kind of
want to try a missile launcher they're fun oh actually i have a my class has an item that
puts like homing beacons on things so that your rocket launchers will home them i was told not
to pick the air tortoise quiet sequel but the reload is two seconds you're gonna listen to your
chat oh the lock on time you know let them decide what you do uh do you have a problem with them
just use a suppressed gun all right i'm just gonna need access to your playstation account see there
we go see that that's what they changed item collection range is higher on the ranger it
makes sense it is the ranger here we go wow i like your uh net gun from the how far does this go
yeah this gun isn't gonna do anything look how far those bullets are spread apart dude this the
dentist directly up again i don't like the dentist gun very much hey come down here i knew this was
gonna be bad this thing sucks i think the ufo's are faster than my rockets
okay just gotta wait for them to come down here and then boom get suppressed
and not even destroyed get like slightly
inconvenienced we may have we may have not done the necessary research every start like retreat
hold on let me just see if i can kill one flying saucer i broke the bridge that was me i got one
i can't do i'm i'm not here don't fight them all at once i guess that's what they want us to do
actually this thing's not that bad i don't hate this anymore i can't like lock on to anything
because nothing is dude let's just run forward into the city they say one by one let's go
forward and i'll drop down the beacons why would you go against our intelligence my stuff
don't listen to chat don't listen to the game either so at full power i get it i figured out
the like speed run tactics here to die forward right at full power this thing does a lot more
damage
you guys just hit george george okay let's take let's take a stand here all right seems good
and i'll use my suppressed gun okay i've got anti-air claymores surrounding us
i have this gun where if they come into like melee range of me i push them away and then they
keep doing us a wind gun this thing i actually like this a lot this is perfect for this michonne
michonne walking dead wait what can't just come down here and i don't even need to go in the air
yeah we're playing um i wish i had a mouse for this man versus machine right now
once i get my own neck will be good well i'll just do something you guys can kill the
ufo's faster than my rockets can get there
yeah why do you literally have like the beam weapon that looks probably the best of this
weapon mission i know it just is i made the right decision somehow and i was just trying it up
watch out they're gliding in well i suppressed it have any of my rockets hit anything no
they like don't hurt us at all i think we found the broken overpowered weapon which is your thing
here you just got to kill a few more and then i can be useful it's fun just hovering around
just dentists and people look at that guy over there looks like he belongs there okay how far
can that laser even shoot across like the whole game oh but at 50 percent ammo it's kind of
worthless well i'm just the guy that makes sure nobody actually gets close because i can't really
do anything else i think i have to get out you're doing a pretty good job of just doing that
there's a couple of strays over here why would i even put on the other weapons so the blue ones
are just background yeah they fly is actually well when my rocket does hit it's really good
is this uh building gonna go down anything
we have no choice but to suppress you you mean like the gas refinery next to us
yeah that thing's gonna blow right all right i'm gonna go collect i'm gonna be useful here
i haven't been collecting anything they're all scattered around so far though it's hard to
collect anything i gotta get like a better view all right what we got anyway okay now i know to
jump up finally not really are we like done did i get my mech and then like the mission was over
uh i don't really see any ufos in the sky anymore so possibly unless there's a phase two
can i try the mech next time no that is not my mech no though i was told that it could be if i
chose this glass well like you actually have guns that do things why does your why does your mech
have such a big dick what your mech has like a gigantic dick oh it's like zone of the enders
where you you are you're in the cockpit you're like physically in the cockpit you know i'm out
of here like seriously it's even got like a discoloration on what do you what do you mean
what do you have a discolored dick what are you talking about like dickhead yeah but why is that
what do you tell what do you mean this that's like that adds to the realism what are you talking
about oh i got the dexter automatic this is the d and edf i gotta get out of here i gotta go
dude didn't you ever play zone of the enders i didn't play zone of the enders yeah zone of the
enders like you have a giant flying mech with a head but the guy the pilot is in a see-through
cockpit oh well when i played i was like 13 so i didn't really put two and two together now you
know is this uh flying again um it doesn't say we're safe here trust me it says monsters attack
mission seven so i'd assume okay monsters attack time to not do air stuff then time to never use
the suppressed gun ever again try the this thing every time star comes around we just
the conversations they just go off the rails i think you just don't like me anymore
like you're done with me cast me aside he's too vulgar we only make jokes about being short here
wait who's too vulgar me i didn't say any of these things i love the completion rate 0.7 percent 0.59
percent completion rate how do you have a 0.72 percent completion rate oh he played offline no
no you me you have almost a one percent completion rate probably how many items i found
yeah because he found items on two classes so maybe oh two for one completed it not even one
percent okay so i'm good to go german deny it i did deny it that's not true you guys want me to
be like uh is there any reason i should take a heal gun uh not yet once we start having trouble
it's based on mission completion with the different classes okay um yeah so that makes sense
you guys ready i'm ready oh hold on come on you're the expert you have more completion than both of
us i can't pick my level five gun throw up puke do it puke oh my god everything just goes off the
rails when you start hearing someone about to throw up wow talk about vulgar it seems safe
so how is this thing compatible anymore this thing can charge how much does it use
nice okay i get it let's get in there destroy the monsters oh it's the spiders
it is the spiders well this thing is fucking awesome i'm gonna drop them
these things are always scary yeah this game's too scary beware of the thread
yeah the thread comes out and goes it gets you disgusting really mute are are your anti-air
guns hitting them when they jump sorry these are like the same as anti-air guns except i pointed
them down they're effectively the same weapon but they're different loadouts so this is like my
ground claymore i don't even need guns you want to just die i'm stuck be honest this is really
effective games is fun to watch i'm not numb to it yet because it's my first one since like
the playstation 2 but i love how nonchalant you guys are about like oh yeah it's just this is
default yeah these are spider ones oh this is hey oh yeah the spiders i remember them oh this is
nothing just wait till just wait till the the game goes off the rails yeah especially when you get
the megazord happens to play this is this is off the rails for me they gotta up the anti every
no no no you're playing wait you got the bumpers on in the bowling alley man
well my point is it's fun that is a very good point i would agree can you not shoot me please
i mean i could where's the fun in that i want to have fun watch it here it comes it's going
to open up it's going to be saucers is it crashing i don't know i'm sorry going in a really weird
direction where is it going okay so the vehicles i get the pilot are they all from the support guy
or are there going to be like vehicles in the game that the this guy can pilot i don't know
if you here it comes that you can use it's opening something you can use my mech if you want right now
i'm kind of having fun with my uh my other weapon i'm melting your whole face off what the hell
we're supposed to be going somewhere i think we have to wait like ride on it with you that'd be
pretty cool what happens if you step on me uh i don't it's just in the air isn't it i think
i can try jumping try pressing on here here it comes here they come no i thought that was
gonna arc hey push right defeat all monsters so do you get to keep like a an armor buff on your leg
yeah so i'm bringing that also doing that rain hell it's on top of the mech oh so i place it on
the mech and it gives me the defense what if it went through them can i put like anti ground
on your feet uh if you jump up on my hind leg you could probably put them on there
oh boy bad kind of move i gotta reload i'm just gonna go in and fly through with like a full
phalanx here let's do it hold on i'm dropping i'm dropping oh you can't dash when you're using
that okay that makes sense if i'm honest i got one of them on i have like my own spider webs
uh all these edf guys they're following us yeah i got another one there we go hey you're very
well defended from a close range right now i don't know what that means that those like red beams
will auto kill anything they could pull oh all right i gotta collect lots of weapon crates you
gonna do something about it i'm getting them attention i am collecting them as best as i can
i don't think they used to like squirt purple goo everywhere i was about to ask if it was like
bad to stand in or if there's any acid damage or anything it probably is i would not stand in anything
that is on the ground it's fine god it's fine did we just win yeah uh why was that mission
significantly easier if there really is such a place the flying levels always are a pain in the
butt until you get shit like you had the anti-air stuff i think i got all the boxes over here too
i think it's a bit easier also uh germa's flying class has like
homing lasers that make it a bit easier yeah the power assist gun long range bolt shooter
three plus level two let me try that one short range more range not that much though
i keep getting upgrades for this but that's the the dentist beam lightning bow less energy
cost pretty good more range on the bolt gun and faster shot speed this is new we got a long
range weapon developed for use by winged i fire super high voltage bolts of lightning from a long
distance accurately they can snipe distant targets because the weapon is an early model
its trajectory may not be very accurate i don't know that we need garden posts anymore actually
i'll try okay let's go let's go try it um ready that thing is good but oh yeah you you did you
play smash you're you like smash i did play a little bit of smash not on stream though
oh so you're already over it uh no it the the online was the online was pretty terrible
it just you'd queue up nintendo i mean the game is really fun for smash it's like hey queue up
one v1 let's do some one v1s and it's like oh you want to do four player what type enemy types
for this particular mission it says monsters so cool maybe more spiders i'm gonna put this
back on this thing is really good capacity nine nine target lock on i feel like i'm the only one
that's like it just feels like move me same thing what the fuck it's a new smash game but it just
it looks it's just the same game i i probably don't know enough did you look account get hacked
what no i'm talking about one of my mods oh that's how he is
jesus christ all right let's see how this thing is i'm so ready but oh pylons pylons
oh look at this thing how far does it go and i wonder what how much energy does it take a lot
and it's very slow to reload oh hey i got that wait wait wait wait wait wait stand still italics
stand still that gives you extra damage you're good thank you very nice i think that thing
actually is a fun weapon whoops i accidentally targeted some civilians but you know what they
say about civilians this is really fast reload but they're all missing where did you come from
oh do you want damage bonus jarama oh that sounds like fun coming to me stand still
i'm standing still and still i don't even have to aim with this gun just power the dentist i just
let it do all the work i wonder how much damage is that they're doing can these people shut up
no they say they don't want to die one more time i'm killing them why are you so sadistic
oh well you were yelling at me earlier for spamming help me and listen to them
just barely had a range with that is your uh i probably should have picked a weapon that
was capable of doing damage to the big pylon boom i did good okay time to collect and what
do you say with what do you say we pick up some weapon pick up pick up some weapon crates
watch out for the threats i just blew that guy's teeth out of his head here we go
my frames my frames oh with the power of ps4 pro i have 15 extra frames per second
your mind okay mission's over oh look at this what is that supposed to be somebody will
fuck me right stand still stand still stand still you fucking stand i'm gonna shoot you out of here
what do you want hold on stand still are you like attaching c4 to it what the fuck are you doing
what the hell all right go what do you mean go there's nothing here yeah there's a pylon over
here why are they attached to me you they're attached to me yeah now you're like you're like
even better at shooting oh my god why is this possible like a glowing red this shouldn't be
possible that's not disco different era come on look at dragon ball z new grounds animation that
was powering up oh no i've read that i've juke it's distracting to me get these tools off of me
why do i feel like this is easier than like the first mission yeah because we powered up
man maybe we should be playing on horror well no it's just like one pylon at a time
i'm getting webbed oh my uh sorry it's alex hi there's something on me i need to go collect
these things take a lot of energy and i'm kind of wasting my energy here
i really need to conserve my energy you're putting things on me there's a weapon crate right here
oh that will never stop being entertaining to me here comes another oh god that's so far away
i need health where are the bad guys down here look at your mini map holy shit well you look like
you're doing some stuff over there don't you that's i'm doing some stuff yes i'm doing some stuff
like we're just trying really hard okay we don't want to have time for jokes yes i'm doing some
stuff shocking announcement from staff
mr pilgrim no don't even don't do that you know that what that makes me do that makes
me do the whole thing don't make me do that yeah why did you have to say that oh journalists hey
ask me anything what is it who says mr pilgrim don't make me do the whole thing don't you know
i'm a fucking tune from who framed roger rabbit you start playing like a song and i'm gonna start
doing it shave and a haircut and i'm gonna burst through the fucking your wall and i'm gonna scream
it it is i got you you did got me that was a nice shot ana thanks all right i think there's a weapon
cradle right next to italics there germa got it he's really good thanks really good fly so
all right uh they got more uh more more of those things that we need to get okay i'm really slow
but i'm getting there i'm just gonna sit on the building it is aim and just hold the button down
and just be at uh just i'm just gonna sit on the couch okay that's gonna show me how that works for
you because there's room i want to sit on the couch too play from down like on our couch yeah
we got a couch get a problem i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming there is a coming i'm coming
i'm just taking out the uh final on here i'll get a shotgun i feel like i should be i i'm not having
fun doing this though what i'm gonna do is necessary did you just say what i think you said
what go fight the bugs i can destroy the things real good well i just i already did it
very effectively i'm really good at killing bugs now i'm mr crowd control oh my god that
civilian is powered up i can't see and i i gotta go no don't charge that i
what these requests are being yelled too loud we'll get to everyone we hear requests but now
yelling oh oh mr crate over here i'm sorry guys don't get wet basically from the air
metal gear online someone say metal gear metal gear wow i made a gundam joke you made a metal
gear joke we're basically on the same page it's not fair out your corny references
hey does anyone here think metal gear is a good game oh wow i think it's a good game i think
sure school sorry we don't make metal gear games anymore yeah they do they made metal gear survive
i forgot that that game even came out it did i think i played it i regret playing it wasn't
it really bad yeah oh dude you can jump i knew you could jump that's what i was telling you to
earlier i don't know that and you can hover something in the water guys don't talk to me
you know i don't know anything new i don't drink water so no nothing new for me
i did get a bunch of upgrades though we will reach the city once we cross the mountain
we should be safe there i know i'm asking a lot but you have to keep going you can rest when we
get to the city bolt shooter that got a lot better that got a lot better look at the range increase
i'm looking at it dude nudes try it again great shot too damn these are all good
i'm looking at it and okay and i'm just gonna keep i think i'm gonna keep it on because it
just got way better but i will put the dragon lands back on still i need to get more of these
this is the one i have oh man i'm looking at it uh this is called escape okay so they're giving me
too many toys i don't i got c4 now too many toys you're going to have like probably two or three
times the amount of toys that you have now um well who are we fighting this time we don't know we're
in the mountains okay in the mountains c4 probably ants yeah i would bet ants and we might it might
have to start making us destroy ant holes so maybe the c4 will be good i could also do grenade
launcher tier two oh man here too ants don't live in mountains i had to buy that one for dlc
ah dude dude mountains are just big ant hills so um did anybody buy like the anime waifu vehicle
skin by chance or the pillow oh no i didn't buy i did not buy any of those things i bought the base
game not the 199 thing both shooter yeah they have um skins for all the vehicles that have
get a fire that goes on them what does this take 20 30 40 takes a lot if you charge this i can't
use this that often dragon lance can be used holy shit that's powerful i think i heard it was really
cool to see the the generational gaps in edf games or like the last one was a ps1 and this
one's a ps2 oh yeah it's watch out ants listen there's so many more polygons now
single target may have been a mistake it's made been a mistake i shoot green smoke grenades
all right what is the range is bad i took you the same surprisingly my smoke grenades are excuse me
my grenades rival your uh air calling i'll be using i'm using the wrong air calling
but yeah getting close yeah i'm gonna end up accidentally shooting one of you i'm gonna stay
over here whoop you can get eaten by the ants does anyone want to shoot the ant that's eating
me currently right next to stir um i can have artillery shoot it don't worry he spit me out i'm
fine he even gave me a first oh yeah yeah the red ants can pick you up and grab you help me help me
help me you are saved the range is terrible on this thing although it does kill in one hit
the red ants watch out for the same that guy vanished oh i'm gonna get overwhelmed get out of
here dude we're being ambushed that was almost a beefy um they're grabbing me they're grab i need
help he's grabbing me i need help he's grabbing me i'm shooting him i don't know you are really
far where the hell are you i took like no damage it's okay dips dips on this god i have no ammo
oh you took my thing hey finders keepers move your seat lose your seat finders keepers move
your feet lose your seat this is an official statement i really need i i have a bad loadout
for this sorry guys i'll take the alpha okay i know because there's so many ants i have another
neck really well then we can both use me i just gotta get in there if i get in there but i don't
want to get in there my artillery is getting in there if i had the plasma yeah that'd be amazing
right now i could just fly over and drop missiles but i didn't do that
look at all the shit in the ground all right i'm gonna go and collect dirty no
all right one two one me i don't think it's over dude oh you just killed me from what you just
murdered me me he did who i don't know i got i went to 100 to zero shooting i don't think how
did i get to zero percent health in one second i dropped out really there like a year ago
don't worry we'll get to you eventually
edf just made a major announcement hey if you're dead when the mission's over you don't get any
loot running through he just ran into the artillery yeah but i'm trying to i'm gonna collect just wait
till it's not the whole ground what are you some lone shark is that hard is that too hard am i
asking too much you're about to get fucking booted from the lobby i mean what are we doing
all right that was that was kind of rough is those we're gonna get a lot more of those now
bolt shooter combat bomber complete use this thing again it's too long it takes too long to shoot it
you can only shoot every 0.6 seconds it takes almost a full it's almost a full second to
shoot this thing damage is all right but it takes too long to reload ready do you even change your
gear oh wait no large flying saucers yeah thank you is it saucers yeah all right i'm going to use
the uh oh wait no it's saying large flying saucers and drop monsters in the sea all right i might
be the big ones hold on so unclear mission directive on cursor and proto reverse
yeah i'm gonna put the big cannon onto this um do we think there's gonna be more flying or ground
i think i'm gonna go close range only shotgun and anti-air i have a dash wait a minute i know
what mission this is use the diffuser oh i'm ready yeah i just i feel like i wanted to level up
oh kiss me am i taking a break tomorrow yes i am what you're gonna take a break tomorrow oh wow
really you told me we were gonna play this multiple times and you're you're immediately
gonna bail out on me all right hold on yeah we're gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna view you guys for a
second or was it salty swamp yeah i talked about that a bunch of times yeah it was like an old
flash animation that blordow made i've yeah we've talked about that before
all right back oh back into it thank you for explaining hey you're very welcome all right so
let's talk about what strategy is here strategy is okay um kill the ants kill the ants don't die
instead you could ignore the ships but the shotgun is awful for reload time i gotta go do this i
gotta go in the air for this thing oh dude is this the air shotgun one it is i got air shotguns
no i do that's my classes thing it could be everybody's thing but it'd be just your
thing it can only be one of ours that's true hey german german stand still german stand still
german stand still yeah thank you do you want to do more damage keep standing still come here
now what what are you coming over here with you coming up with a briefcase
what guys that has happened he didn't even get on me my little bird there's only one guy to shoot
you're anti-air capable now so you can fly completely uncontested through this guy
coming at me with a three is a tool what what are you talking about get him out of here
i was making fun of your chapter for but i take it back
is it the kid there's like one yeah imagine if we didn't have you and we had to climb this mountain
to finish them off for the den of evil to be completed i know really that would be a pain in
the ass all right dead den of evil and alex hey hey hydrate i don't know i'm not going to
i've also got something for you i'm gonna go inhale dust and like make sure i get less hydrated
that is well that's not it okay i am the tool master is that the whole mission
i i don't know um they're acting like it's over it does sound like a celebration is happening right
now i'm gonna go just get a bottle of salt and just chew on it and then run around in
a circle as hard as i can they shouldn't be shooting these no they i can't shoot them
come on get there got it at least he's only chewing the bottle
no i'm good i got the drinker all right what's your favorite song let's see if i can do it with
a beam never mind fun's over oh we like went in the wrong direction because of the cut scene
come on guys see you there dropping bugs see you guys there this is no one in this situation
never mind that was a very bad display of video gaming right there this thing is so
fucking weird don't you gotta tell me you're gonna do that hey you have plenty of time
to not be influenced but stay calm all the shotguns are powerful in the areas where evacuation
is required in order to act rapidly in case of evacuation please start so long reload
right so what is edf end game you want to know about edf end game yeah he doesn't know about
okay what would you like to know uh just ask me anything are you gonna lie to me
yeah a m a yes sir the end game in this better or worse than kerosene
uh this is not world of warcraft so it's a better game
still alive damn what wait what i said that was mission sucks what oh god okay
guys i put like 10 years into world of warcraft how does that make you feel
i mean it was fun but isn't uh we can't find it was like what's the name of the new expansion
boa bad bank of america i think i think it's doa doa yeah same joke clap i had to drop my
controller to clap so it took me a second world of warcraft bank of america can i get one in the
air let's see oh i'm gonna try and bomb you i'm being i'm actually being bombed are you gonna
bomb me oh you told me to tell you now you're mad that i told you hey star what do you what
do you do i'm gonna bomb you this thing is just really inaccurate that's the problem here it's
not me it's the game uh well every gun has an accuracy rating so um what was the red on the
ground for them that's the air shotgun geez inaccurate it's inaccurate that hey can you hit
anything i just killed count at the end of each droid so many things not carrying their weight
don't left for dead me i was about to be number one i wish we had one i wish
i want to know because it would definitely be me at the bottom with my shotgun currently
here comes another tv news report all right i got equipped
i'm running the juice since we are at war negotiation attempts have ended the edf
saved me let me on let me on your foot it's missing that's not even a these guys are also
trying to jump on your foot should we continue to see are you gonna talk still friends um
i don't know i mean it's like talking sometimes but this is the first time i've talked to you
since i moved in yeah all right i'm on your foot this mission is terrible
that was a lore mission that was a valley valley 2 the sequel oh no actually that's what are the
i like the grid shot more radius let's try it this next time you start making noises you are
going to get muted real quick um speaking um it's ironic coming from you great shot put it back on
and and we have any indication on what this is going to be uh more saucers dropping ants
there weren't any saucers in that mission but they like that you could kill what's your favorite
sauce um i mean barbecue sauce can't go wrong barbecue sauce there's like 80 kinds of barbecue
aren't there i don't know which kind i i still haven't been to like authentic texan barbecue
experience oh man mine's a tie between is barbecue sauce though i don't know
ketchup Worcestershire and salt and seasoning you're welcome yeah you're welcome you're welcome
is what i'd be saying if you know we could play our game no i've been okayed shut your mouth
i paid six hundred dollars for this also you're in the equipment screen yeah because i was waiting
for you uh alfredo sauce you're it is probably the last one for me or tabasco does that count
those look like condiments right those sauces uh i don't think those two are mutually exclusive
i said Worcestershire sauce correct yeah i cook every day uh excuse me what uh 85 lie detected
dude i made us all perfect fucking medium steaks i was eating them all too i was educating you guys
on proper you made me what now i was educating you guys on proper you know storage and use
for that's a hold on i'm busy how do you detonate c4 probably l1 it is l1 this is by far the best
weapon i probably have right what is happening what are you doing who are we killing i just see
laser show going on over here what is that did somebody drop that what the heck but it was just
as an alien device i think what the what the fuck is that thing you're good i joke well done
well done steak i mean i'm like a medium to medium well well done i mean
no i don't know if i would i don't know i don't really eat that much steak i don't even
have a lot of red meat did you guys eat these fish like i told you to um you told me
doubts even with the succulent salmon that i made first last night excuse me i can't hear you the
game got very loud you say salmon last night remember the succulent buttery salmon that i
made last month i mean there was a fish about a month and a half ago succulent it was a while
do you remember it though yeah how can i forget the only time you've cooked so far
that's not true what about the sausages not true what about the sausage yeah well that's true
about the shrimp that i made sausage and then i had to i did make two more after that what about
the shrimp that i made i didn't eat any of that why not he won't say it he won't say was it meant
for me he won't say it say it i have a shrimp intolerant i don't think i can cancel this
cancel i'm like in in the bomb dropping menu ready to drop oh there it goes
he just dropped like a train can i get in that oh i can actually yes i can oh i can too
me too monster carnival that sounds not so bad actually that wouldn't even happen in a monster
carnival well we kind of i mean that was basically twitchcon last year yeah actually it was
well it looks kind of like they're all dead all right i'm going on collection note here
it's the whole world like this that was just health i think c4 is a little dangerous
i got them but i didn't know what c4 is not dangerous i have tons of it and i've never
gotten hurt a little bit of oregano a little bit of garlic chop it up some butter what are you talking
about what are you just dreaming about cooking somebody people are asking what are we talking
about instead of reagan that was me yeah that's what i'm explaining oregano white wine a little
bit butter a lot of butter actually what are you making the thing that i made like last night
oh saute make sure you like here's how you're gonna like pretend that a cupcake
this is how you pretended to cook guys you just like put stuff in there and even if you're not
supposed to move it around just like shake it around like push it up in the pan stuff shake
swirl swirl swirl flip flip shake swirl swirl you do just kind of you're supposed to flip it
and stir it no you said my name ice cold snowy top hat santo what the
fuck are you guys doing in this chat room snowy top hat center snow ice this goes really far
uh there's a lot of bugs yeah this is a pretty good gun oh look at that diffusion
install btt all right here we go you ready for this you have better twitch tv do you have bttv
yeah yeah fuck i've had it for like three years oh come on no you don't
okay i'm almost actually gonna die well yeah you are helping okay i'm coming i gotta come back to
you guys keep dropping monsters the idiot has exterminated more than the game got hard all of a
sudden whoops which will be able to turn the time more crates i am right next to you sir
oh boy taliks down
i am indeed you're really ragdolling you good yeah he we're wiping dude i told you not to bring
him in here's gears his gear store i think world of warcraft get this out over here anybody here a
wowhead
look at all those weapons well i'm going for anybody go to wowhead.com everybody did because
you couldn't get used to you could not see the quest before yeah is that a real website i thought
that was like a oh that's a very real website that you had i thought that was like an sfm sfm
porn thing you would just go there a safe to complete your quest a safe for work what is a
source filmmaker oh sfm porn thing yeah wowhead no i don't know anything about it i got cruise
missiles i got the deathcrawler what the fuck short range taliks false machine gun a little
bit better bolt shooter a little bit that's congratulations you are enrolled finally a new
turbo core we fought hard but as long as the large flying sausage remain out there our days
of hardship will not be over is there even safe for work of porn i don't yeah you saw that scam
show right where the guy made fully closed porn the scam show there there was a guy for a little
while that did a show where he would scam other people on his show like as it just and it got
canceled because he was doing like illegal shit but one of the episodes was that he convinced
a whole bunch of people to show up to like a like porn movie reveal party and he got like top
executives from like porn industry and his movie was like they just keep putting on more clothes
they like start in jackets they just keep putting on more and they like put pillows
between them and everyone is very upset and he leaves that was the whole episode was that just
like a h3h3 video is that nathan for you that might be nathan for you got we talked about this
like a few years ago i've seen the show yeah but i'm pretty sure it got canceled like through season
one i i did it i'm pretty sure it's still on hey thanks for the facts star hey sorry you can't all
be you know geniuses want some gum like some of the people here in this column right now are geniuses
all right all of us but who is it though and how many also not a scam show wasn't canceled
fact scam show fact wasn't us oh it's a game it's a show we scam people that's what i thought it was
be one of the other episodes wasn't it he like pretended to be brad pitt or something to get
free food from a restaurant how's that not a scam you're thinking a con man from comedy central
like 10 50 20 years ago it had to be done at least once maybe i'm mixing up shows i don't know
all right just is it not just a restart button that's a guy that used to say to spray paint
fucking like mile per hour signs if you get like a ticket that show did get canceled the guy used
to talk about hey yeah that show got canceled i don't even what is nathan for you am i are these
two shows yeah the guy was doing illegal shit yeah okay i don't know what you guys are talking
about what does this have to do with pornography i don't know ask stir the boomer one of the
episodes he did like a fake porn thing and he got all the executives to show up are you sure you
think okay we're thinking of two shows you're combining them together why don't you just
google it google fake porn thing and and then he puts the cushion in between them and he says more
cushion for the cushion oh you fucking god damn it google fake porn cushion thing this is this is
what happened on the show who are the pornics i don't know they like ran like hustler and stuff
i mean you like got important people to show up just a fucked up dream you had like three days ago
no someone didn't fight chats and they remembered it i don't want to die attacks by the new types
failed oh that pig is gonna die kill it monsters we lost 20 percent of the total population missed
yes mr hustler was there nobody's gonna laugh is anybody 20 well i just got out boomered
it's like somebody said what the fuck i hope we don't fail this mission and have to listen to
these people talk again hey you want some gum oh fuck you made me do that because i was doing
are you chewing gum i'm i keep i'm eating gum are you eat gum you don't chew it nathan's show is
going to businesses and giving them really weird advice that works somehow yeah no what i'm i
definitely that porn thing was con man so what's this proto ship doing here
get him get him get him let's see what this thing does get him get him oh look at that get him
how it works i don't oh boy oh that was a large rocket oh shit yes who shot that missile
hey i'm also dropping this oh whoops i'm gonna kill them all before you can my frame rate
is having a bad time
can we just there's hell right here get it all right they're telling us to shoot down the ships
now are like we shoot allowed to do that now or have to do that um i guess it has to open
hey watch out i knew that was gonna happen eventually all right i'm gonna go do something
just hold your horses i'm gonna do a little cry okay i think i need like turn you way up
me you're very quiet yeah well what's up do we actually have anything to shoot up into them
i mean i can do it i have the i don't have very good stuff
has become a battlefield and people everywhere i wanted to use my spider bot against the alien
spaceship remains in effect hey suck brick until we can watch out it's me spider bot
did i get it not yet this is a tough war i'll focus on the ship you guys focus on everything
one two three four you stupid bug why are you maybe exploding you i'm sorry
you managed to deftly avoid each of my explodes here it goes stupid dog you make me look back
uh are you encouraging right now oh my god it's lining on me we're talking about shows that used
to be on cartoon network yes that this new generation doesn't appreciate only boomers
appreciate this doesn't even make gun sounds what is that nice crab nice crab they don't have
their crab okay check this out one two three got it watch the fireworks go off now oh my god
oh nice crap oh you've got a crap yeah he's got the crap oh this thing's opening up drama i'm on
it already i want a cool crab thing oh shit oh shit that's scary back it up i'll just go
pick up stuff on the ground and be useful i was just going to i was all right well actually i
got to focus on the saucer so my hand hurts i was that was happening seriously that was happening
to me too your claw grip i'm getting a cramp you're getting a playstation 4 cramp i am getting a
playstation 4 claw grip clamp cramp oh i gotta get a fire that's how you know you're trying
just hard enough perfect level to be at and this spider can only jump higher than that
oh it's opening oh no it just closed wait did it i got some shots in there i gotta wait i gotta
get up i gotta fly up there i need some i might actually be able to use this it's opening it's
opening actually hitting it or is it just stopping short fuck i gotta get way higher than that i can't
do anything till i have full charge here i don't this thing is like tilt so much uh there's a lot
to your left yeah does anyone else go from the shelf i'm just gonna say that but i don't think
i knew what it was a metal gear wow i love these references i'm done with it i'm done with it
i'll try it thanks for your hand me down man this thing doesn't want to go down
yeah chap doesn't realize like i watch literally anime every day
okay you don't even realize how much anime i watch i watch i watch so much
um you guys don't think i watch all that anime watch this one you want to see fun i'll show you
an anime we found the 15 truth colonel take a look at that i'll show you an anime so just wait until
i send my giant big red rocket in can you just call it anything here here it comes here it comes
i did that it's very uh there it is can you call it anything else killed like two bucks
let's go killed like two bucks so my jump sucks wow i'm gonna need a little bit of help here
we'll just run towards me you need me all right we're like playing in our toy spiders
oranges in the toys spider well you guys kill i'm gonna collect the fair they're pretty good
at what they do it's opening i i dude there's so much stuff that i need to pick up this is
the we can't just i gotta get it so don't you think we stay here and we farm this farm farm
and and farm and we're getting it star have you ever seen jojo's bizarre adventure oh god
no never heard of it okay well let's see didn't you make a reference earlier
hmm no you didn't make a jojo's bizarre he definitely did i think he even said the words
jojo you did say that you did do that explain no i have a i have a friend named joanne and we call
her jojo does she happen to know someone else named deal no why do you know that because i've
seen the first two episodes oh which is more than you've seen don't shut up man i said i watched it
honestly i don't know how like you can continue having a twitch channel and like people will
watch you and you haven't seen jojo's bizarre adventure shut the fuck up man shut up people
people haven't realized you're a fraud yet shut up 85 lie detected where is this thing
just i screw this yeah do we both exit the spider with the exact same time don't worry i'll take
care of this thing until thing that's really far away it's gonna take a lot of flying to even
shoot us once why don't worry this is the third time i've referenced dragon bhaji but the the
pink thing is just it's coming whose pink thing is that no like fourth of july fireworks weapon
that's me it shoots homing missiles at everything it's like it just is super special it has a
like it's like a five minute wow cooldown all right i'm back on collecting duties it's like world
of warcraft just you guys figure out what you want to do because i need to collect i don't have a gun
that can shoot up into that it's opening again it's really i also do not have a gun that can
shoot up into that i guess i have to get back into stupid spider hey i will join you well what do you
want me to do do you want to win the game for us or do you want me to collect items win the game
win the game but do you want weapons and armor or do you want me to beat the game for us all
i want you to beat the game for me we've been here for like a million years we have kind of a
million killing ants for a long time but we need all this stuff we're gonna get this stuff if we
like beat this level okay all right slow down oh my god sometimes this thing movement accelerates
out of nowhere what the spider yeah are you hitting l2 no no i mean like the aiming will jump like oh
yeah all right i got i got one shot in i have to wait till i get full charge again
okay let's do it again all right nice in sync shooting here
i'll be fine my god oh only one of my guns has ammo what yeah that was the old one that i like
jumped out of and you uh you only shot with one side no all right here we go what's your problem
it was like that when i got it i doubt that i doubt that very much look i got it from the pawn
shop the pond open why is there a third spider i called another one in did i do it i did it we
did it i i did it actually smiley face smiley face in all capitals all right now i'm surprised we
haven't done like a hive mission well there are like 175 missions in the game i don't know but i'm
just saying i would have thought there would have been one by now but we're focused on these stupid
flying teleportation vehicles with their golden armor look they gotta pace the game you know they
can't just use all the enemy types in the first five missions they got all the boxes i mean it's
ants i'm saying they're usually usually in there pretty early you guys are gonna be so happy when
you were upset earlier with wow is it doing upset with you were mad that i was i wasn't destroying
the saucers but wait till you see how much health you just got and wait to see how many weapons you're
going to get from this and it's a thankless job right smack just kill a fly nice work i got a
suppressed gun thanks jerma i got a bunch of upgrades also i noticed that it's raising hp for
all the classes not just one of them that is true interesting maybe they got but i got like more
for my class directly but that would be nice if if they made it so that you can actually change
characters in this game bolt shooter i keep getting upgrades for this but i don't i don't
really like it it's too slow how is a grenade more accurate i'm gonna i'm gonna grape it up
this thing's cool but i'm gonna go back to this thing it's my clock what do you mean my clock
i wish you get an upgrade for this i'll keep it on whatever he's eating boogers
what the fuck are you talking about booger eating stream do we know what kind of enemies
we're gonna fight or just monsters i think it's monsters i think they might be introducing a new
one no maybe they do ant hills in this one i don't know you don't know what you have right now okay
i'll pick a gatorade um i know what you want hold on when do i get tanks what should i call it what
do they call them pina coladas no it's no slam a blue gatorade right now hey you got green like
from fortnight slurp slurp or blurt slurp you a fortnight guy yeah whatever
slurp juice actually is what it's called slug jug slug jug chug off that's what i was thinking of
slug jug chug off yeah he did it it's up in the hat we got a slug jug chug off
well this thing did someone just call me a newbie yep oh yeah in this game don't they call you a
newbie up to like mission 100 i think they do let's start the fire let's go this thing is
really really great yeah but i can't fly when i use this this is a residential area well we're
kind of did ruining everything yeah i'm calling in a lot of bombs uh here are the spiders
yeah those are spiders it's coming up from the ground this thing is really actually really good
better than what you're have better than what you have better than what you have
run that by me again i'm sorry what are you saying no don't worry about that
i am afraid of confrontation so oh she had my homing fireworks right now this thing can just go
this thing really just it just goes it didn't i you could see my screen you'd know what i'm
talking about what gun my electric oh my electric faucet gun the pink one um no no my plasma balls
plasma balls yeah it just goes dude why do you get all the like toy trucks
and everyone can get in it everyone fits in it oh okay first person mode engaged wait i want to
play you really don't like there's nothing to do back here yeah but this is like to get everyone
to a new spot this is for the viewers though man hey come on in and at least i'll have someone to
look at okay not exactly what i wanted i want to get in i can't look down all right get get
start getting again if i look down then i'm gonna get banned on twitter i'm gonna i'm gonna drive
you guys to the next mission oh you're gonna i can't look down run into trees you got a mask
over your eyes so i don't know where your eyes are germa can are you looking left and right
you're just doing this little yeah i'm looking left and right because i if i look down
you're you're not decent just like in real life in where are you taking us we're just driving in a
circle no i'm driving us to the enemies get out it's enemy time so you can see me too no i don't
want to get out nope away i need you i'm not getting out you do i really need help
oh you got it ding dong dong that's the doorbell oh they've got me i tried to line up a bommie
they're they're red i got you i got you i got you i got you almost got you oh they have more hp
all right collection time to go yeah i don't know if you heard me germa but uh
this character is not decent down there well
you gotta warn me in this stuff star hold on don't do don't talk to the chief commander
really the mother ship i didn't i reacted building oh boy
so if we destroy that thing so every time you get an armor it permanently adds it what's like a good
amount of armor to have uh hundreds is it just damage negation or is it like hp it's just hp i
think it's just hp at least that's what i think now maybe does that h see it says armor in here
but it says hp when you finish the mission but i'm pretty sure it's damaged negation
hmm it depends on the class the other game depends on the class yeah what class you are
it would mitigate damage different amounts here comes an air strike goodbye i would like them to
use some of the air vehicles because i can kill those um behind us it looks like it's like some
kind of currency thing it might be we're missing somebody is it one ant over there
yeah i got it i'm gonna do some driving i'm gonna make my way over this way it looks like
just a handful of ants i'm in oh yeah we're coming whoops so daisy okay watch out here comes the
grape is there a mother ship i don't watch out here comes the great happening i think it's just
these ants over here at the moment i'm glad this mission is not gonna show my kill i think i'm gonna
switch back to the class i think that's it because you guys are carrying right now
what are you you still on um i'm still on the uh soldier guy ranger i thought i was going to
get my radar whoa that happened i don't know where good thing i got this ranger before they
were coming for the sky now they come to the ground i'm being eaten very slowly oh boy they
have a lot of armor yes they do yes they do i'll save you oh boy juice because i don't have any
ah now i'm gonna get picked up it's inevitable it's inevitable uh yep it is what i just got picked
up but i can probably get are you down no i'm like i can i can get you i'm not gonna i can i can come
i'm coming ragdoll's pretty great my god stop eating me i yeah yeah i just got eaten again
who's with me inside the airstrike
did we just go into outer space oh no you're on the ground i think i'm trying to get to you but
i'm underneath a giant red ant ass you know you can still shoot while you're being eaten
yeah that like helps you free yourself yeah i killed myself with explosives
well that was a little hairy
i got you on the floor did we go into space well initially that initial explosion i thought i went
over the mountains this isn't just a world war it's a space war it is a space war any other
this isn't just a ground war we're from space plasma fall up we did get napalm though maybe
we should be playing with grenades plasma fall i just i need a corridor i need a long stretch of
land for it to work very well okay um we might okay this might be the destroy the mothership
mission it's a destroy the mothership mission then i'm going to pick so you have to shoot up
into it but i think it also drops stuff um so i need this to level up what's the best thing
i got probably this i oh you can use level five stuff now yeah bolt shooter no plasma
falling i'm gonna get rid of these special right now i feel like it's good but i'd rather have
more things to shoot so i'm gonna go lightning bow m2 i haven't got any more deployable guns
and go with this thing for the ships this is a stream what why what again why is everybody
quiet ready you know what i need to actually why is everybody doing dot dot dot what's happening
why is everybody so quiet what everybody's just doing dot dot dots everyone's just being silent
in this chat right oh we um i don't know he doesn't know resident boomer that's how you know
you're muted right yeah i was muted on purpose because i was just like hey what am i going to
switch to here talking like stuff you don't need to hear you know oh oh oh well you might need you
don't want to hear switching back to the other guy because i have a new exoskeleton that makes
me faster my ass off he should uninstall what i am ready to go all right i'm going to switch
my class entirely don't tell what do you what my webcam is not on first of all um who are we
fighting we are fading the mothership the mothership destroy the giant ship to bring something that you
can use we suspect they keep themselves low in order to drop monsters the damage will be
incalculable if we don't do something need to know if the socks have arrived no they've not
yeah i'm playing as the fencer again new and improved you are so cute when are you gonna shave
wow that's a great question i was gonna shave today but i didn't very big
sir do you even have to shave never i've never ever shaved attack the monsters
of course we'll handle the mothership okay i'll handle it oh they said we don't have to deal
with the mothership but there's why you boys anyways flying saucers this could get really
really bad and hello there sir what are you doing up here where are you up where
boom what the hell is it trying to do who cares take out the monster but
oh don't worry like hit really hard too my art my artillery is gonna hit the air guys don't worry
oh i don't have a dash with this easy easy airstrike maybe i should not have switched yet
i would love your anti-air guns here yeah that way i didn't realize that that was switching at the
bad moment i'm gonna get up oh my god oh you're dying too so i'm not the only
one any health gotta reload my sword i don't see any helmet you're gonna die oh yes i am
i'm trying to find a health before that happens inevitably you have you have swords i do but they
attack aerial units see look at that he even goes he ah before he does it
so we have to actually fight real like humanoids
how are you guys gonna turn me on oh god are you guys all right you know i'm doing okay
doing better now it's like game audio keeps going off game audio is going the heck is happening
there what the heck i don't know man trying to figure that out no hell what's with no health
drop it's all armor surprisingly these swords can kill flying saucers you know i'm getting like a
20 times damage bonus from jazz from jazz from jazz giving you a 20 percent bonus
no not chat jazz he's listening to jazz okay are you listening to jazz i am is it like that
oceans 11 scene where he has to go through the like lasers but he like puts in his headphones
and he turns on his jazz music oh boy uh sword battle i i think we're gonna okay we got canisters
of monsters with swords can i shoot him out of the air probably i don't think so
so
what are we supposed to be shooting right now i think we're just supposed there they go
oh it's the ninja turtles oh boy so is this yeah there's the frogs oh my god this is awesome
holy shit this wrong don't go ahead on oh jesus christ i'm dead it's frog champ
oh my audio i'm fucking dead oh you yeah i looked down the hallway you died pretty far away didn't
you i'm down here yeah uh i'm summoning mech frog channel come to you oh i think he just used a
building as cover like he put his back to the building that's so stupid oh my god oh they look
like humans says the guy i was fixing my earphone frogs but not nice just like you
yeah i'm also trying to heal you this dumbass headphone fellow
sorry live comment oh you're in the mech
there's still a lot they're just circling the building oh my god they're like arms come off
yeah these things are scary that guy has no arms he's running around with no arms
he's just screaming and running away
oh they regenerate by the way that guy regenerated all of his body
they're hiding in the shadows of buildings germa how can we fight this enemy blow his arms off
jeez damn it am i not getting these rockets are they hitting the mother
shit oh it's an accurate fucking thing like half the things go through the motherships
all right i'm coming to utah thank you so much oh boy oh boy no what the fuck
i can't maneuver like this oh there was health up there not anymore
there's soldiers my gun isn't doing it like there's nothing about okay what i missed that
one apparently okay oh we all no wonder we're on all sides right now fuck okay this is definitely
better even though i cannot block anything uh we you know we got to focus oh my god we have to
focus on one of them at a time they're regenerating yeah the frogs regenerate i think the wrong time
to change classes shit oh shit i'm not my gun isn't doing anything fuck i'm dead goodbye
i guess they're joining you shortly yeah we have to focus we have to focus on one at a time
otherwise they're just gonna keep undertaking back up i have my gun stopped doing things
i'm gonna get my shotgun back that thing is just too inaccurate for me are they talking there that
was weird all right yeah all played all played did your mom i would do that so i could just sing
the theme song over and over again oh wait i had a sniper what oh my god dummy um it's not a big
fat dummy i think what else do i want though what would be good against those guys maybe something
like this what what's the thing that just goes which one's better probably power lance or spark
spark mine hey could you do me a favor what's up can you leave the call and then come back in
me oh is he's hearing staticky to you too yes he is i'm staticky yeah you're just static guy
hello i was apologizing yeah wait am i still was hello yeah you're still bad how i don't know
is either discord or i don't know yeah it might be that discord problem i had because you sound
normal stir yeah hold on i know the fix for it and because you use uh scarlet solo right yes
yeah that call hold on let me try and remember what the fix is wait a minute wait a minute wait
wait am i am i statically statically on the stream no it would only be on your discord
so go to voice and video settings on discord yeah on discord okay scroll down to where it says
audio subsystem yeah oh my in the advanced sound options okay echo cancellation noise
suppression automatic gain control quality of service uh lower lower audio subsystems
below that standard show a warning when yeah set it set it to legacy legacy yeah okay all right hold
on what the fuck is my back hello yep how do i sound you're better i sound better you sound
great crisp as clear as kittens so what what the hell was that that's strange all right well
but it yeah it really would be like that sometimes i think i like my preparation here i'm just gonna
fully charge this and drive right into their face i'm gonna just drive straight in and just
uh did you fix it i think so i guess cool when did this start happening like 20 minutes ago
it like slowly got worse and worse it did yeah i thought it was the same thing as italics i
thought it was my capture card so i just ignored it that's odd i have the capture card interference
too it would have been fine on your stream though because it's only discord that happens
it's very odd all right i'm gonna try this again yeah all right let's try this again i'm gonna try
to take damage modifiers up what's the range on this thing again so does each one of these
stack on me how much damage boost is this i don't know one all righty two that's two hits
oh boy well you're flying real low whoa oh dear watch out for the frogs okay when the game audio
gets real quiet and it just people going get me away from this nonsense i'm with tank boy
are you riding on the thing uh no i put the damage boost on it so i'm just following it
i'm gonna come back to you guys i'm kind of getting overwhelmed i'm getting overwhelmed
i need to come back with the team oh i can do a booster that's pretty cool
yeah you i haven't like seen anything you just like flew over there in a bit of fighting with
everything yeah it's turning around i'm buying you guys know drink drink drink oh boy you're
playing a drinking game in chat what did somebody say drinking game in real life
every time cat takes a drink we take a drink that's the game yeah that's the whole game
that sounds that sounds good who's drinking right now all right ready here we go
butt chug why do i always pick the worst fucking things to read
did you read butt chug i just read that out loud yeah i wrote that i wouldn't be surprised we did
since i don't know like you think you're being such a jokester
extraterrestrial beings similar to humans i hate that they say frogs are similar to humans
they are though you know that they stand up on two feet that's the only enemy so far that only has
two feet and they regenerate and they are giant and they're frogs wait you guys hold on you guys
actually he said almost identical to humans that's what you guys don't know that frog dna is actually
like genetically like the genome is as close as to humans as anything else say chino oh chino
oh you know you're not wrong yes frogs are genetically as close as possible to humans
almost identical yeah we're growing in batch just like those i'm just as slimy as them
that's because i don't shower i got an idea what are those i love that my idea stands directly next
to one of the canisters all three of us my idea is just get uh get the f out of here you know
i mean and wait till they spawn and then hey germa pick your head up pick your i want to see you
i got you i want to see you something is coming out here we go gotcha i don't think we're supposed
to defend from this like open no cover courtyard where they come from all sides oh he was like i
didn't even know he got shot in the head he just was like i'm ready to go guys break discord again
oh my god wait was i thinking that my gun last round was a mortar but i had the sniper
i think my brain broke last round okay i switched guns and i'm also actually killing things now too
so all right do we have to how much of their body has to be destroyed is this like um
oh geez man dragon ball z reference no it's a like a zombie reference they have to destroy their head
or i don't get it the whole body i'm dead are they aliens they look like humans come on
that looks like grandma just like humans they look just like come on
all right i will come rescue you eventually oh we have permission to attack them uh what do
you mean you permission to attack them they've been here for two three straight minutes on the
ground they said we have permission they're both alive i expect a full recovery here look i'm coming
i even jumped over the hill nice wait i blew off one wiener i actually got both of them in from
airborne funny funny funny i can't like lost its leg i got a trophy for that thank you
i was looking for that one what the fuck was that backflip me sir just need to move your leg out
of the way that's pretty good fight between me and this guy uh-oh uh-oh but still alive
that guy's still alive oh god damn it really
all right i gotta get some collection this one dead
the one that we were just shooting like five minutes ago is still alive
don't get caught up in the crossfire guys these guys
crossfire yeah yeah this really they know they know techniques that is a um you know they still
sell crossfire in target they actually yep why have they ended up there's never been a commercial
i don't know shooting for those old boomer games they still sell like oh shit ran out of firepower
all right got them
shut up guys they're just like humans
so do we have to the nutcracker is it time for the mothership or what
i'm waiting for this to open they said ignore the mothership well here's more of these oh god
okay i don't know what i'm supposed to be looking at my bed's cool it's more of those
frogs oh shit no wonder my head was hurting like all this yelling all right we need to focus
because we need to focus on least which canister we're going up first uh i don't know there's so
many how about oh my god who knows you choose i don't know all right why later over here with
you guys we need to do that later why later stop waiting for orders the ones in front of us
what okay okay we did it we did it good job good nice work grenades and support equipment okay
i like i'm not getting anything new anymore now that's a victory let's go it's you it's
really good to see you in one piece yeah the minigun was doing well i kind of can't take
this thing off but this thing got better yeah i'll try it again the galleon i haven't tried
this yet i'm gonna give it a go oh i never summoned my capacity 19 what version of fortnight is this
um season seven one it's a good version dude did you see the storm king no do you play fortnight
didn't you play fortnight for a little while i played save the world when that's all there was
so why didn't use what type of enemies uh it's probably frogs frogs i would assume it's probably
frogs because we just got overwhelmed by frogs okay yeah i think it's frogs then i won't pick
sword guy uh but yeah if so did you ever play any of the battle royale for fortnight played like
one day when it the first day it came out i played at first and then i first impression
oh what was my first impression yeah well what's your first impression first impression was that
the random bullet spread was way too extreme and i quit because of that and then they fixed it three
days later and i never played it again anyway okay okay they fixed it three days okay i wait i
zoomed out they're like they're like roaming as if they don't know we're here so we i think it's
assuming that we're going to like this guy's still fucking alive he's still alive i'm still
talking how is this guy still living okay we need to stick together so when germa flies away and
does his own thing dude well i can actually keep up with you guys now all right so because i have
two behind us down the road down the road behind us i do see they're roaming but there's one
actually behind us yes there actually is one behind there is actually one behind us
he's dodging a lot actually to our right my god the accuracy the inaccuracy
that's that's the pinpoint accuracy i want things actually really good
dude they're just like humans well i feel like i'm killing people when i kill them that's going
to leave me with some severe ptsd oh fuck i just too many here why am i doing what am i doing over
by myself i cannot dehumanize this enemy i'm going back to you guys class dismissed i just need
to get my mech so that i can be a big human then you'll look just like them even more yeah all
right let's pick up some of this shit what do you say go for headshots really yes because they're
just like humans is that why that's what i've been told they are zombies oh i'm pretty good
at those headshots his head does come off and i don't think they can regenerate them oh my god
behind me what the just watching the giant frogman collapse is pretty humorous
they're just shooting walls oh dodge good dodge man
a lot of power services
uh any more boxes that i missed anymore maybe back here
i don't think i've seen a single
okay why is this one like easier than the last one yeah it really is
because they don't spawn in a circle around us all aware of us maybe true
headshot standing right next to it okay never mind wait what what i do
there's a big health box right behind you if you want it i got full health who am i next to
star no i'm next to an mpc that is just you but without your name this is a special
you were like really good at fortnight weren't you what are you talking to what are you saying
oh i forgot i was the stupid grenade
who's the last person in this call to play pubg it's probably star no it's you
no but are we counting pubg on mobile yeah because is that not also called pubg i mean
that's the first part of the title the second part is mobile why why did you play pubg on mobile
i don't know why does anybody do anything forward and i wanted to try it that was a well-timed
stream i got that was a double headshot that was worth it right there bingo i'll get all three of
them oh man i could smell it from here they're not singing anymore they were screaming but they're
not singing with me oh there they go i just come on blow the guy's head off he's like this is like
one of the strongest chorus this is the strongest thing i have is that kind of floating all right
fuck it wow that guy's dead i saw that so do you get to choose what your mech weapon loadout is
uh there's different mechs oh yeah can i land oh fuck what that just get the shit out of me
i think you're gonna slide off yeah you can fly so much longer than me mommy mech i'm going down
this side street it's not worth it i'm gonna go check for health found an enemy finally
yeah i'm doing more like walking around this yeah than anything yeah i keep accidentally touching
the touchpad the touch screen and they like run away and hide i don't have the time to go over there
here no he's dead don't worry i got it whoops my finger hurts there's one more guy down here
getting cramps too i feel like if my guy's so slow and floaty that if i just push the thumb
sticks harder i'll go faster look how far away these last two are well i'll see you guys uh when
the end of the mission happens now i'm gonna hit him from here i think you're the fastest one aren't
you well yeah i'm like i'll be there in like two seconds touching a touchpad is what is yeah the
touchpad makes it go emote you do like a random emote this is actually a lot down here i probably
can't do this by myself well may as well play with the civilians i'm getting there
this stream is my stream is jazz plus help me help me you're gonna finish it by the time i get
no i'm not i'm not i'm not i'm not i'm not i'm dead every time i say thanks i think they emote
at you no i hit the emote accidentally i think like after they killed you they emote taunt it
this is like the perfect gun for killing them nothing like the good sea shit his arms are
flying into the screen that guy with no arms rolled backward looks so cute
hey i finally made it pick me up pick me up before it's over so i can pick up all the stuff
i'm coming it's really not much stuff here is there
well that was not a fart i i would okay oh big plasma can i got leveled up nice
oh a dash cell okay how much not farting
pretty decent damage upgrade i'll keep it on i don't know more frogs of course ready
i want a helicopter already mom maybe we can go back into a hard mission
yeah we could stuff should i do that um can i pee after this mission or before the mission
go pee right now because italics takes like 20 minutes to pick what he wants all right i'm peeing
i'll be right back i'm gonna put it on the hard i like to have fun and i switch my weapons sometimes
peeing what was a quick easy one this was a nice one also i don't understand the difference
between booster and thruster enhancer but this one blood storm i'm gonna use blood storm we're
gonna fight a bunch of ants okay okay hard difficulty ants and red ants well then this
is probably not a good weapon um the swords actually might make sense here then
if that's the case then i would want the dash cell okay i'm also gonna pee because i'm ready
and you can start whenever you want oh maybe i should pee and be the last one to come back
maybe i should be the last one to pee and the last one to come back all right they put here well
looks like it's just me they all left hi no no i'm here oh i was the last one to leave and
italics is taking a poop he must be yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna go go to the bathroom i'm gonna
go to number two we'll be back in 45 minutes yeah and you can go check on him like just stand
outside the door and like knock and ask if it's okay what am i potty training him no smell under
the door to see if you really want to go oh my god you are fucking revolting you are revolting
oh everything about that was so vivid and and descript oh god well i'm not the one who's uh
not showing up he told me i could start whenever i wanted to but we're doing a hard mission
german with ants okay hard ants we're doing the the mountain ravine mission with the ants that
came down the hill are you really on a hard on hard okay okay okay do you have their correct
equipment uh i'm gonna put on the plasma fall then because that's really probably pretty good
here can i get a high five keep that three two one okay we do all right one two three
all right ready high five high five ready one two three high five that bit me the mouth what the
fuck oh can you stop saying that you're so vivid and descript people are just all imagining
violence domestic violence someone's calling the cops so vivid and descript he's the vivid
and descript one he's out of his mind italics is back he just said help me in chat perfect timing
all right this one's hard was not the perfect time oh perfect timing what's the perfect timing
like 10 minutes ago you're really gonna go do number two while we're all streaming
um that would have been the fastest number two in my entire life if that was the case
watch what i can do dude it's hard come on don't kill all our guys oh whoops okay okay i'll try
and remember to pick up weapon boxes i i'm gonna be on it i'm gonna stay with you guys though
because i don't want um how come you don't have the star colors what i'm i'm this color so you can
notice me tell us how come you're not your channel colors what are you talking about why are you not
your channel you're what you're you're not your channel colors your guy why are you like aqua
blue because that's my channel colors what i can't believe you guys didn't do you like a green
no i'm not have you even seen me have you seen my channel so what i have we have you already are
like my color you're like a you're supposed to be like a purple fuchsia but you're like a hot pink
the whole game i don't think you've ever even seen this channel i see it right it's all you've got the
logo on the discord i can see it right here look at the look at mine look here i just
this domestic violence is just i need help it's it's unbecoming help help i'll nuke you i'll nuke you
i'm sword guy now it's pretty fun well it wasn't till i died because of the nuke
i'm sending another one why are you doing this again let me get him you just can you just pick
up the boxes i'm trying to get italics because he's dead and now you're dropping another nuke
on us and this is going to be your fault when he dies again in five seconds how is he going to die
again from that somehow i can you help me instead no help you by helping us stop nuking me what the
fuck what game are you playing are you playing like trying to kill your friends
i'm killing the ants check these ant kills on me bud come on i'm picking up boxes relax
there's so many ants and so many bombs being dropped
i got i'm they caught me i can't even see i'm dead you're just dropping newts in this tiny hallway
i don't see how this is my fault i have gold damage right now that's right that's absolutely
right did you pick up any boxes i i got like two okay well if italics doesn't screw this up
what am i doing oh oh you're all dead yeah so it's i'm the one that's gonna screw this up
yep because he's he doesn't tell us well like when he's gonna drop a nuke
it we just see the red telegraph warcraft boss wildstar boss sorry what like the red
telegraph on the ground i can't i physically cannot kill this ant if you if you keep like
the longer you stay alive the longer i have to look at this guy's fanny all right well i'm
i'm trying to come to you but i i only i'm just a little guy i have boosters this is an emergency
this is just such a joke spaceships were discovered and presumed to be owned by
extraterrestrials well it was fun i think we may have gotten a weapon we got a weapon
free yep let's retreat yes oh oh that's new let's say my meme oh why my name homing weapons
guys what wait it's not i got three weapons but i only got one hey i got one weapon i got a new
weapon didn't just say three uh but we didn't win so i picked up three boxes but we lost that looks
cool does it split between us things uh i can be the jackhammer there's a little six holy crap
try okay we're doing the mission again ready up okay i just got to change from force blades
because they suck and i want to be very clear it's three split between you all
is this edf any good um here's what we're doing asking us i mean that's what people have just
want to know what do you think this edf is good it's edf they're all the same game
what's new in this one versus edf 4.1 it's on playstation 4 only that's true yeah that's what's
new it's not on pc anymore we need guys listen come with me down to the other side of the river
and then when all the ants come down the hill and fight these scumbags i'm going to bomb the
scumbags can you please come with me i just you just took off i'm so sorry 30 percent of my health
okay i hit you one time uh i didn't mean to okay we're gonna hide behind these rocks sure
and when they come down there they're gonna be the ones complaining oh can you stop with the
dildozer that's a great name by the way what did you just call hey sir what were you gonna do
uh you ordered me right i'm here to please you think this is so slow moving but i wonder how
much damage does oh boy this is actually this is i'm dead help turn around these aren't you
are you out no i've shot it like three times if i shoot him again can the guy with the jet pack
not get grabbed next time you told me i got to stand behind you didn't say anything you said
stay behind here let me do this so now i got thrown across the whole map okay so if i just
never switch off of the jack well it's called the jackhammer so i mean the hey stay back here stay
behind here don't come that way stay back here you have a minimap that tells you the location of all
enemies but it's my fault stand behind this rock no no let everyone stand by me now thinks he's
some kind of fucking quarterback oh my hands are so big don't worry i will get to you eventually
thank you i can't this like this weapon's physically impossible to see anything
hopefully he has epilepsy why were you standing behind the quarterback
what are you talking about i need help we need help now do you
find it unbelievable um where are all these how many is the case but unfortunately it's
how's that thing still alive that thing takes so long to recharge
wow no one can pick me up while i have this pretty strong
leave me alone bugs all right i'm gonna try to get some stuff there's a shitload of things down
there uh wait till everything's dead because i'm i gotta keep summoning these otherwise we're never
gonna kill everything no just defend your quarterback this is an emergency news flash
just made a major announcement okay now we i now now so again shit i'm not gonna do any more after
this one okay on it i'm trying to help you they got me the enemy is coming from the sky
there is nowhere safe on earth the earth is turning into a battlefield
and if i shoot it i'm dead so i'm whatever i'm coming
i know they're dead i'm dead only left is germabot we're all dead i'm coming
this is not a promotion for a film or a tv show
extraterrestrials this is not a tv show
it's pretty far apparently actually
man i should have summoned my mechs a long time ago yeah probably isn't that your special
forgetting i have them is that it we love it i'm just having bombs all the time is there anything
else is that the end of it i thought that's a good farm pretty good farm level alien alien ant farm
you guys like that band well i got level zero items from that hard mission that was really
that was good i got some really great new shit i did not spark find that better stuff
almost my first level eight guys i'm so excited class we can't be this might be too high though
a little six well let's do that one more time rapid mirage so i didn't get anything and then
the vibro hammer i didn't get anything so i can use rapid mirage that's a lot of rockets
oh i can use this too both of them and they're both really good 15 targets very cool let's try
it watch your back this time as you level up you get to wear less armor um i don't think so no i
think it's just you pick up those armor boxes and that's how you permanently increase your armor in
hp or will your armor my character looks like a toothpaste max spot don't let them drag you down
this is a double dentist is it i'm looking forward to this then rapid mirage oh fuck holy shit
next mission this mission sucks because after you beat that one it does one forward even though
you already have that unlocked what are we doing what do you what happened to you that was the
wrong mission oh okay that homing rapid fire thing seems pretty cool although it took a while
to kill one ant though that's really good on the flying swasses yeah i did get a better plasma
cannon though plasma cannon b level six oh oh yeah tell me more it's a level six it's got a radius
of 20 meters oh all right i'm not doing this now i'm not doing this anymore like that okay remember
stay behind we got to get ahead of these losers stay behind me oh i have no movement with this
remember to look at your mini math and know if there's an ant right behind you
shush come on alien ant farm under the window on the window a crescendo dude a crescendo on the
window oh boy let's try it out how do i use all that already well how long does this take to
lock on is this anti-air is this anti-air farm is this only all right i have not used this at all
so i'm kind of aiming in the complete wrong direction there's one on us hey what happened
can you guys see anything on my character oh boy punch him in the face um sir can you look at me
when i hold this button and see if there's like an away to assist me with it a way to
see anything right now no i cannot fire this weapon i need a beacon or laser target from an
aerator oh yeah i have to equip that then okay i didn't realize that that was what that was
but i now have a weapon that is compatible with it this thing looks really cool punch boy for now
drains me all right watch that watch the sides both sides why are you guys going up into the
river into the river it is a river star thank you ant for saving my life i mean oh my god
how he just how is this thing still alive i've shot this thing point blank seven or eight times
that's um are you dead i'm dead oh where are you up the mountain i'm so he threw me up there he
threw me as far as he fucking could no one listens to sir making the calls what was the call you died
why'd you die we we did the same thing that we did last time and you guys went forward into the
shithole don't blame me how can i not blame you because i'm only this far forward to try i was
gonna try to go up the mountain to resurrect i got grabbed by buck and he ran away and he threw me
hey why don't you relax buddy no i can't relax i don't know how to i physically don't think i can
get up the mountain uh i don't think you can either wait maybe you can only have a dash i have no
airborne i can see you trying i'm trying my darndest here hang on there we go i'm getting
closer don't worry talc is gonna mvp this right now oops hi hi oh okay i'm actually well equipped
for this scenario he threw me down the mountain oh god damn it and the edf has started battling
in some regions this really is like world of warcraft mountain climbing i'm just barely faster
than them oh you're getting collapsed on they're all over here oh are you gonna get thrown down
you're gonna get thrown down again aren't you hey i mean i'm not on top of a mountain you could
you could get me if i fall down again then i will
there will be evacuation oh my god yeah the red ants are the fucking worst
i was
no you just like skied by me no i didn't mean that thanks i that i the button just hits it
every time when i accidentally oh fuck get the fuck away from me okay i'm coming for you star
i'm coming oh no oh no don't ragdoll into the way somehow still pulling this off i cannot be caught
yeah the fuck away from me what's the left there are you dying drama oh i'm fine i'm staying back
it's okay you're back all right i'm gonna go save no not yet all right i'm going for it
okay yeah these are the last folks we need all the boxes yeah don't try not to kill these last two
oh they're dead there's a box right there well done well done hey well done salty if i didn't
have double dash that would not have been possible and also the the fist gun you made fun of me for
is what won the mission see i didn't make fun of you you called it a dildo sir i am going to
blame you because i got going to blame you all for that's all i heard
i mean if you're gonna act like that then we're doing the mission again
a splasher what is a splasher uh i was i supposed to pretend you did you like punch me again sorry
i wasn't listen i wasn't paying attention let's see well done guys well done yeah can you equip
that beacon so i can try out the missile launcher uh yeah we're doing that again or you want to go
back to normal and do the stuff um i don't really want to do that mission again necessarily but
let's check this one out i wish i had a better one of these i didn't really get anything oh i
can't use any anymore can i oh yeah looks like you can't we're going back to normal level right
now i have no one will give me any instruction what are we just moving on like to the next
mission yeah i wanted to get some higher level stuff we i don't we can't even use it in normal
oh this is the most current normal mission we can do oh it's this weapon one that yeah it tells
you there uh well i can use these too should i know can i use the new core i can rush core
so what what mission are we doing the newest one that we haven't done yet in normal okay
try it should i use the missile launcher or swap to something else
i can't use it because it's a little late never mind so unequip your marker where are my pants
okay let me see that she's wearing the reverse of what i'm wearing yeah i got no no shirt on
and pants she has no pants on but shirt you've been talking a lot about how few clothes you're
wearing this train i talk about that every day anything you're trying to arouse some suspicion
in your chat we open and close every stream with are there gonna be flying bugs frogs looks like
the alien infantry so i think that's frogs okay looks pretty froggy then i will just go
i well then i won't equip double melee weapons there's too many gear sets that i need to be
worried about all the time hey just don't worry you'll be all right okay that's that sounds good
let me try this oh wait he gets the helicopters the air the aerator the ranger gets the helicopters
fight a bite fight a bite you can aim even while you're being bitten aim at the enemy and press
the attack button to shoot you can escape from enemy that's biting you by defeating it great
the monsters are here oh that's wonderful man artillery would be nice here but i kind of switch
characters i love this oh boy great oh my god this is single fire uh that's fun i'm looking a lot
like a mech now oh they're up here yes they are oh boy the building is gone yeah i can't
i can't the playstation 4 was not equipped to handle this no it's not normal or hard
is it friendly fire uh it should be normal i need like a better gun than this yeah i should
just start with my other loadout actually i should have stuck with artillery yeah i didn't know it was
a fucking ant swarm mission yeah get miraged i don't even know what these grains are doing
there are frogs it's almost like pellets i'm throwing hey buddy i feel bad killing this frog
he's so much like a human he's just like a human there really is this purple slime oh my goodness
i'm getting a little test in the body guys what the hell is that this thing just absolutely rips
through i've been using this before the red ants eat this it's my butt
i have to press the button every time
no he's not no uh down this road here the monsters my channel colors like you said and i just look
like a raspberry and blueberry popsicle just watch out for the monsters it didn't work out
they're in it together what's the difference between the aliens and monsters the aliens came
from above and the monsters came from below um no one knows i don't yeah what i'm doing
pretty far off i gotta get back here look like i came out of the frog i was in his stomach i need
to fly up there and do a little bit of spray i feel like i'm just like throwing marbles being
being effective i can't even see what i'm throwing well we're not dying as fast we are not
electricity melee yeah i'm shocking this guy's brain i saw that oh missed one yeah
well we're using these stupid grenades because it's so annoying to shoot my stupid gun
this thing's all right but i don't it doesn't seem too effective maybe when it gets a higher
rank of level because just yeah long as taking me to kill this regular just
ray and yeah that's how i feel i'd use like a level one weapon for this yeah i think i don't
know about that thing it's cool but it is cool but it's not as good as this not even close
let me get some stuff i hope this mission is over soon i don't want to use this anymore
probably close
what should be on a lead a pet yeah they're pet they're on our pet planet
where am i missing this one box above me or below me watch out there's humans over here
watch out these things are like humans my thumb like i keep pushing my thumb so
far up on the left joystick that it touches the touchpad and my screen keeps showing me those
options oh red ants bad uh man i wish i was other guy i wish i was ant kill guy
i'm gonna get the fuck out of here yeah i was really good ant kill guy last time as well i'm
sorry i just shot you three times only my hitbox was so large on this weapon
oh fuck okay like time to really get the fuck out of here i am basically the tank now though
there's so many raw guy back go to hell ants don't go to hell or anywhere they go to
ant heaven why why would they do that my grandma was an ant my grandma was a queen ant
can we deal with the frog over here please what the frog are you pulling a uh you know who right
now yeah i can't say it the joke is off limits why are you doing off limit references you got
you do only only references that are you got the syllabus you got the syllabus before the stream
you know it's allowed it's not allowed i didn't read it no one reads their syllabus
and that's what happens when you get punished for not reading the syllabus that's what
now you're in trouble because you want to make references that are not allowed
you're all right my gun is capable of freeing me from from the ant i'm on my way so you're
all right i'm all right but i'm gonna die soon if i don't get healed i'm dead i feel like every
ant has ignored me because i'm not doing anything those are some cool flips you did there to get to
me thanks man i was impressed i kind of need this oh fuck and this is where it all goes to hell
this is where it goes to hell squad following me true flipping around all over the place
all right so am i crazy and saying this in chat some some chat people actually know did the air
raider used to have the tanks and the helicopters and i was told that the ranger gets tanks yeah he
does and his equipment there was a spot for tanks like it doesn't like i don't know your name is
air raider you don't get the helicopters so air raider does not get helicopters no that's all i
want maybe because ranger was kind of just default and maybe a little boring for people they
decided to give the ranger some other stuff are there any more classes by chance no okay
they just took the four and were like let's just make up a bunch of things last game the jetpack
one was new wasn't it um i don't remember i mean i only played the the last one i played four i
think i played the third one or i didn't get it at all yeah air raider only gets land vehicles
and and apcs i feel like the ranger would get the apcs depending down for you know i got the
minion buster new stuff nice better plasma cannon watch out better grit shot get the minion buster
that's my cannon oh and i never used my collector thing that i had that's not really that much of an
upgrade but oh and the dinky motorcycles oh we're doing it we're doing a cave is it a cave
all right i'm gonna put on the uh anti-ant gear coming where is it this thing and
i wonder what else i should do maybe this should add a shotgun just leveled it up anyways
oh yeah this stupid thing this is perfect 1.5 completion rate yeah this game is absolutely huge
what wait we're just in terms of how many things there are to find i mean we're on level 17 on
normal yeah i believe like 1.5 percent through the content well because i think it's every level is
a piece of that percentage every difficulty so there are like 170 there's like 170 levels
each one of those levels has a different difficulty and there are yeah there's a
hundreds of hundreds of am i crazy or did the last game have like a dlc that added like 40 levels
um there's one you want to use the laser you want to use the laser guide kit for this or no
oh no i'm playing radio each difficulty with each class so there are four classes and let's say
there's 150 levels and five difficulties per level so you're doing that's five ten fifteen twenty
just for the classes two or you don't know you'll see that added like the dragons and stuff
dude i'm telling you it's italics every time that's because i'm being falsely accused of things also
you were the last one literally the last mission so no never happened literally can someone back
him up his claim because i think it's baseless anyways he distracted me from what i was doing
i like at least i got time to like stand up and stretch like if every time i'm waiting for
the game i'm gonna be jacked you only have one weapon per slot for your new character
should play something that doesn't pad the game yeah but this is really good just
it is fun just to kind of run around and shoot bugs
there we go oh i'm gonna love this level stupid bounce gun oh man
that is the thing is awesome all right here we go monsters just melt melt melt melt
holy shoot these grenades are huge going down the toilet drain compared to the little tiny fire
cracker things foxes do we get them holy shit it takes like 300 bullets what's my other gun
a rocket launcher the blood storm very edgy name i like it i think these the web spiders are down
here no they are some kind of spider the tunnel behind you dude this gun is so weak
just fill the holes oh boy fill both holes watch your language what oh whatever you know what i'm
saying yeah you're saying to fill both holes well what do you want me to say oh and i just
fucked up i want you to say there's monsters coming from every direction
dude these grenades are like bigger explosions than the airstrikes i was calling in
we're gonna have to use full force in both of these holes you really are you are quite a comedian
what a comedian no i want that help i am just you know repeating my favorite joke that i heard
from one comedian german 985 when did i make that joke when did i make that reference ever
in my entire life oh you're gonna sprint what yeah ranger has a sprint yeah press l3 hold it
wow welcome why is it zoom into my asshole because you gotta fill holes and then you have the longer
radius around your body yeah i'm pretty fast now actually i'll scout it out looks like we got
um and it like hurts to hold this down it looks like um there are frogs down here
are there frogs in these holes that is a wonderful question
and why does it put my camera in my butt there are aliens underground did you know that watch
the other side they're probably gonna come to you to the right that frog is dead dude i love
this grenade i'm sure the frog is dead yeah this missile launcher is way overkill for what we're
fighting plus it hits the my rocket launcher hits the ceiling weapon crate over here
well that was a useless item don't step in they will certainly become a terrible threat in the
future we must eliminate should have just been dash man i wonder when the bosses do you remember
playing this and we fought the gigantic lizard oh yeah that happened right now there's also
i'm like a queen in one of these caves come on burn them burn oh i'm dead dead yep i threw a
grenade just as a one of them jumped in front of me this thing really is so good this like super
grenade shotgun explosions hurts my eyes makes my eyes feel pretty great oh boy i'm gonna die
fall back falling back falling back dude they're dealing a surprising amount of damage
i just got him in their weak spots i'm just relaxing on the ground don't worry sorry you
didn't happen just to throw like a grenade over at us did you nope are you positive about that
can you do me a huge favor and pound this hole with all you've got like are you are you certain
of that i was are you sure you were giving it all you've got oh there's a bunch of help now we're
i'm taking it all if i get some you can have that one you can take that one oh that's a weapon
got a lot of weapon crates this time man hope i get some more level zeros what a fun game just
to kind of chill and play with friends you know what i'm saying yeah are we all just chilling
right now or like i'm just like chilling playing the game and i'm having fun with my friends
my friend you're chilling right um up here like destroy this uh i don't know i can't get up there
so what am i supposed to do should i go look can we go this way okay well i can't get up there either
uh i don't think there's anything over here oh yes there is um what the hell am i supposed to
do about this there are people fighting in here maybe i can just bait them over here i like how
you just holding the left thumbstick as fast as me r1 r1 switch r1 switch r1 i have to do like a
like a sequence of modifiers to go this fast well this really hurts my phone
through any consolation a new species
species
70 meters long we're asking about bosses maybe this is the queen ant
probably
so
urgent if you don't call it like enemy omega well i'm very close so i think we're about to fight
uh the bad enemy the big one the scary one that uh it does sound accurate dude this room feels
like just this room feels like oh i'm just begging for a boss fight in here up top there's gonna be
it really was so dark in the last game actually i remember we had some of the fights in rooms
like this you couldn't see anything huh well we can really only go one way not really at all
actually do we have to keep going down we might have to keep going this way uh aren't they below
us according to the mini map i mean this we can we can go this way i think we have to keep going
the direction we were coming hopefully there's no fall damage so back towards me let's see if
you're right it's just on the other side of the map i'll be there in a moment it's just no i don't
see anything are we i think we might be lost in the tunnels should do this for us is that a dead end
oh down here oh that's just wrapped around really yeah i think it was the other way
but we came from that way did we so hold on split up hand hurts so much with splitting up actually
help if we get lost and can't find each other anyway there's nothing over here so it has to be
that way is there like a map of any kind up top right well i know that okay it's not what i was
asking maybe we just have to keep going that way wait what about over here can this is this kind
of like let's be shot down uh it just looks like a dead end is this just a dead end it looks like
this water here the x button so are they all up or down according to the mini map
that's a great question because there's like a line pointing up
and i'm about to be right under or above them i'm not sure which think we're going the right
way we are going there they are they're right here well i would have got there first i'm sorry
that was all my fault and it's a frog do you guys forgive me yeah it's comically uh inaccurate
watch out they're trying to get up top damn will be more monsters i just barely didn't run out of
the fuel there i can't see anything no idea what's happening annihilate that's all you need to know
annihilate annihilate annihilate all right let's get the stuff chad is arguing on how to pronounce
jupiter again jup it's jupiter you're being contrary on purpose that's not what it is
it's jupter yeah i think j is silent jupiter what is it j is silent can you are you making
marker jupter how are you making the markers jupiter oh um i just sent the location to you
yeah how are you that's if you press if you press your um oh that's very handy your thumb button
the touch screen thing down if you just touch the touch screen uh this is big again we've got
frogs or such seems how many things are there to say gestures frog dead really sad watch out
for these enemies we're fine yeah yeah yeah oh dude he's gonna show it to me all right where's the
boss um there's a hole no that's not a hole what there's a hole this way found it right in his
mouth come on i bet this cave is big enough i could shoot this missile well keep trying i guess
all right are you dead not yet his body is everywhere i love how i literally can't help
this is where i can help that i almost feels like this shouldn't wasn't supposed to happen
jesus whoa watch out watch out they're everywhere now they're behind us yes they're everywhere no
god they brought us into a trap i'll watch this hole you guys watch the other hole
holy i can't throw my bombs from here oh my god i'm getting out of here i'm going up somewhere
oh yeah all right i got all the stuff oh the tunnel is clear so you can like the tunnel is
clear back on the funnel yeah don't be discouraged no i gotta go i gotta get out of here i mean it's
just like a four verse 100 don't be discouraged hey is this that new indie game that i saw um
dwarf game what's the word it was playing
i can't say this pun dwarf court what yeah it's like divorce court but with dwarves
the new indie game the war for the new indie game there's a lot of weapons about the other
dwarf game were you in the tunnels and you dig minecraft not not dwarf quarter not dwarf fortress
the other one not dwarf do what why would you say that pun like a dwarf
divorce court you would say you would say dwarf force court okay okay i guess you're just better
than me dwarf court dude you're like your own chat now you know telling people how to spell
how to say jupiter deep work the way i want to one it's uh and by the way it's deep rock galactic
that's why galactica you said galactica body
clip it i feel like i'm aiming down and i'm in the sky that's gonna make me throw up i need
stuff doing that well instead what is up ahead what is up what are we doing are we going down
this tunnel we got a tunnel over here tunnel it's too dangerous to move on guys yes we've killed
every enemy in the game time to retreat holy shit i just broke my playstation excuse whose
playstation i'm in your playstation you uh did what to it i broke it um i smashed it with a
hammer as hard as i could and i don't know what happened to it i killed the frame rate all right
star how you doing you're right frames are dead are you good frames are dead yeah well you talk
about how much you were in pain oh no my my thumb hurts a lot because running is hard okay plasma
big cannon can i get good weapons what are you playing on harder difficulties secret of the
cave this sounds kind of like a boss we've confirmed a cave that could be the monster's nest
a rat at monsters are spotted wait what oh this is the next level i'll see you at dwarves court
i'll see you in the war warf i'll see you in warf's court let's see
hmm i guess i'll try it again this thing is new up to level six though i need something better
than that i'll put this back on i'm gonna use the reverse one this thing is a level one i don't
want to use that shit all right i'm glad you can't beat i didn't i didn't like this thing though
i'll try and use it again i want this all right everybody oh please excuse me who's last this time
i was for the first time in like no two hours no i was waiting to be done until i heard that
journal was almost done uh-huh all right commence the operation looks like more ants
ah looks like we're fighting some ants i thought we were gonna be in the tunnel again
i thought we're gonna fight a boss in the tunnel i see what this is i want to pick up a weapon
this is a long reload time oh my god all i have is grenade and heal all right check this out
i don't want to waste it i really want to get a different better version of this thing this
thing is so good if it was it did more damage it would be perfect did you do like the chef
finger kiss i did but i didn't use any fingers so i was just implying to everybody that's what
i think you jumped in from that it didn't hurt you but it hurt me oh there yes yes who is this
guy it's a kaiju it is actually is kaiju look out i think the j s island in that though uh kaiju
there he's gonna do something crazy blast him oh push him right in the face i can't see what i'm
doing but i know this oh he's just he's sliding down all right i gotta get higher ground it's so
human-like can you stop hitting our buildings oh oh he hit all the buildings what legendary
already better than monster hunter world legendary pokemon i'm gonna get him right his eyeball
with the story in him hey let me mark him in case you don't see him check that eat that oh
oh my god are they all flying around oh yeah come on get closer look at this that looks
beautiful let me take a screenshot and put it in the background a boy edf get us the guy with
the infinite amount of grenades and like the football arm how much health does he have
the bullets are tiny mosquito bites he's going up he's going he's going crazy
gonna get you guys with it no he's looking at me i don't like a lot i can heal you german bot
again i just landed on him i have a heal gun this is insane it has nano machines
let's do it you're nowhere near me you're the fucking fast flying idiot you're the idiot hit
the brakes whoa yeah he got me breaks i'm alive i think he really likes me okay stand near me i'm
doing it and i have not received a single heal did that really not heal you and i like can't
reload it it didn't heal you all right don't worry guys i'll kill don't worry the the monster
that's destroying the whole city is just stomping around don't worry i'll heal you man he's so fast
tickling him right now hey if you get hurt don't worry i'll heal you charge again so i can throw
the late near charge again come on holy shit look at all the paint far away did he just
puke all over the whole city look at the city that's insane he just slimed you
there really is just purple slime everywhere yeah yeah all scream that's crazy it really is
everywhere but really imagine there's a giant godzilla you call in the guy who throws grenades
that's what you do like we need him for three of us there's a guy who throws grenades in the
avengers um you're the hawkeye of our group yeah are you guys playing i'm playing as the
the fencer in a mech suit oh so you're gonna go punch his toes or i did punch his toes now
i'm also shooting like explosives on his back and shooting it with a shotgun get a big all
oh here comes the electricity roar we'll be shooting the scales the blue ones
what does extra damage do you think i would think the three on his chest but i have no idea
i think you have to aim for the butt here he goes that's a big belly flop
didn't hurt me nothing's gonna take down grenade guy oh that hurt that actually did hurt a lot
yeah don't worry i'll just keep throwing the new godzilla movies looking pretty good
no come back over here they still reach right no no mine half of my loadout that takes
three minutes to recharge he's gonna kill me i'm dead here i just almost watched my own death
man i'm holding a cruise missile so i just got grenades just kind of stand here
oh he's trying to run a spot at you well i you know we finally got to fight a boss i think it's a
perfect amount of ant killing yeah i mean they're they're great let's put this be real here be real
the game is an absolute grind fest the whole game is a grind oh yeah but but there are interesting
something new every single mission i don't well you switch classes i don't like i stopped
getting new things like 10 missions ago because we're not playing on the harder
difficult since i've switched i've gotten nothing new well i got something new every mission so
it sounds great for you italics that's great for you i think they were jumped on skill so
oh i got nickelodeon splat it yeah i think it's based on how many kills you get oh don't
oh that was not oh boy i need to aim way higher with that also got a grenade launcher are you
telling me there's a device that can shoot these i don't have to throw them all
uh where's it do you have a heal still no no no i don't no no one drops med kits anymore do they
okay i love watching a dinosaur in a swimming pool he's just having so much fun how can you
kill this guy maybe you literally can't kill this guy and we're just going to retreat it's
possible well that's none of those kids actually the first time you fight it in edf4 it walks back
into the ocean and i think the mission ends yeah i think this is just like do enough damage for him
to leave cut the tail cut the tail cocktail nice i got it wow dude get him on his back
this guy honestly has an incredible arm he's looking at me oh oh fuck he's gonna jump all
right this time i'm gonna be prepared go see me in baseball all right i'm prepared now here we go
get it over there now i'll get some damage done is he still far away from this no he's coming back
why is he just there we go yeah right into it yeah well that's great shoot the what he said
shoot them dead once they're in range that's what the soldier said that that's what you want
yeah that's what i was wondering okay uh oh i think he's getting close i'll get some jack
hammer in there dude what kind of gear do you think he's gonna drop what if it what if like
mission ends if you kill him he drops like six green chests and you don't get to pick any of
them up fades out how mad would you be hold on i think we've got some reinforcements here
there are a lot of humans on the ground all of a sudden can you imagine this on inferno
it sounds like the dandelion witcher one voice actor this is a dps check yeah i'm too close to
him i mean it's not hard it's very difficult for him to hit you well you say that but okay i
need to land this one time i need to wait till we go somewhere which is well there he goes all
right now get hit by that i thought here we go nice finally oh nice mate oh wow germa look at
your dps well at least i did for a long time my dps meter needs to be reset by the strongest
enemy on earth just look how big he is
yeah how could this creature sustain these attacks there he goes again bye there's not
going to be any city left who even protecting anymore no stop jumping around i can't catch up
to this oh no i meant to say sorry to all the people that just died get over here wow this is
better than sea of beads when they play all the instruments at the same time so when do they
bring in like a new uh instead of small arms fire i don't even know where i just went is that
just i framed that are there any i friends in the dog it's really actually the dark souls of
monster games you get a mech that's big enough to fight him really as a fincer as the air raider
oh but you said you like i know i'm saying like i'm just saying you as a player like we as as a
team is he gonna jump can we do like a mega zord where we each sit in one of the seats
i wish come on i'm waiting for you to do something come on jump i too am waiting for something to
happen where's it going jump move you tell me i gotta throw this already jump here we go i've
been at like 10 health for a long time now yes me as well 72 after yawning there are way more
verses to the song how do you get to them hey honestly ask yourself this as you're shooting
him you see how many people are shooting at him how much dps do you think you're adding
like what percentage of dps compared to the amount of npcs there are well depends on if
they nerf the npcs or are they as strong as the player that's what i'm saying this on inferno is
just like how the fuck are you supposed to do this retreat uh pick me up i killed myself no i didn't
for health i'm good bye hi thank you he's running away don't worry he's retreating he's retreating
retreated the monster and then he leaves that was easy oh yeah i'm gonna get out of here
yeah well we need to retreat okay it's leaving yeah well he heard how scared we were and then
he said look i'm gonna go terrorize someone else he only cares about fear
ah he was in our dreams or maybe maybe it's one of those scenarios where it's like honey i shrunk
the kids or he doesn't even know we exist he's just kind of walking around oh i i got level zero
items for my character well we didn't really get any weapon crates no now i'm dropped whoa hold on
a minute new thing to play with every game good job guys now return to the base along the shore
safe journey where was the 20 uh oh i'm gonna replace a couple of these things what's the next
mission bolt shooter encounters on return return to the base along the shore what do you think
guys what do you want to play with what do you guys want to see that is what i'm wondering i'm tired of
my stupid shotgun i just want to kiss pants i can't put those on i'm actually getting real tired
you're getting tired which is strange because i've been not getting tired you know what i mean
what's the damage on this 250 plasma cannon is more than this and it's only oh yeah you can use
items up to level six now chat reminded me can i use my new stuff i don't have anything that's
level six i have i have one thing that's level six i think three end end of the stream stir voice
uh oh i have level zero i can't i'm gonna use the splasher if the monster retreats through your
city and destroys it do you still win yeah i'll try the lightning bow again who cares about those
turn off your webcam i know the joke is you're you're trying to get me to think
my webcam is on so i go oh fuck and i press the webcam button to turn it off but that turns it on
but you have to remember i have a preview of whatever is on the stream over here on a monitor
so i already know what's on the stream i'm playing from my stream view personally are you actually
yeah really why there's no delay what do you have for a capture card
live gamer extreme hd or something the live gamer extreme yeah it's really uh
live gamer extreme hd 2 hd 2 uh i just remember the beast level with the weird robots that lasted
like 40 minutes for that one that was the worst level you just bought the same 100 robots and the
you had to like go across there's other mission to destroy ant hills like oh the beach that's
what you meant yeah i fucking love the beach level i've played the beach level over and over
and over again me and arcade and played the beach level like a hundred times well here we are enjoy
so what's so good about this nothing oh i didn't do as much as i wanted to i'll be honest
it's like the air raid is doing the majority of the damage here yeah what's new the beach level
please reply please respond i sent a message at least 10 minutes ago please respond all right well
these guns suck like just terrible they are lower level but whatever so yeah now i remember why you
like the beach level because it drops a ton well yeah you get a shit ton of loot and there's just
so much stuff to fight are we playing the same game i'm confused what do you mean i didn't what
is this this is edf5 right yeah no the beach level was different the other one was it
i mean they do kind of bleed together but do you happen to know what did they change
i mean it's definitely new stuff no this is very different you don't i know i'm just i'm making a
statement well not very i don't want to say it's very different but yeah i'm just making a statement
if the last one was edf 4.1 this one's like 4.3
hey you don't know what's in the end game could be anything
i'm not sure these are going very far oh okay i'm gonna sneeze i hope you're ready for it
i can't mute because you heard the man hide behind the tanks let them handle
big boy job that sounded like something in the game dude if i don't get a new weapon this time
i'm gonna complain about it and sound like a whining loser put it on the forums for the game
forum complain to the devs okay they'll fix it before it becomes out of beta i remember this
this level is it goes pretty quick though doesn't it so i have to like be on top of this i mean
there could be another wave i don't know i'm gonna need to move the fuck around because this level
was just a shitload from this it's pretty similar i'm very stuck honestly it no it's not the same
map but like no we're really trying to be the same mission i will let you get that gun because
it's very far away i'm just kind of skating around collecting the things that i can get
it's over okay so how do i do the full song of what's apparently there's a full song
if you do it around other soldiers they sing it with you
oh i ran out of power you might be in the gesture of d-pad options
it's probably a bad time for this and i'm i can't move oh hey i think i got most of them
yeah i deserve that i don't know i know i deserve this
holy shit god that was oh my goodness that was a lot danger close oh what happened again i got hit
again you can get in the mech if you want i'm calling a lot of air strikes oh okay i need to
get some shit oh don't grab me he's right above me who is able to stand against the enemies
the situation is becoming more we have the upper hand yes it is the situation has become stagnant
i'm gonna go back to the beach to collect yeah make sure you persist i'm being very persistent
on my collection
yeah one of the classes does just kind of call airstrikes what do we have for like a standard
weapon do you have do you have a standard weapon um they have the limbic guns which is like you
shoot detonatable explosives and they have like smaller airstrikes they can call them like
individual ones that reload pretty quickly but uh the way the airstrikes work is when
they take points to call in and you get points for killing things so these missions where there's
like a thousand ants like every airstrike refills your airstrike that's cool that's very cool
all right i think i got most i'm having a bunch of these like flying girls dancing like flying
all over my giant mech saying party time wow i'm married and it's really hard right now
made it in time is it we suffered heavy casualties we saved several survivors
well see if ashley wants to get in on it so you know that she doesn't she never does
look at all those weapons i got for us do you see how many i picked up
oh i got i got some it says new i got new stuff for other classes so did i
but it's like the same thing all level zeros though but some level ups please unmute your mic
your phone is muted and i'm going to mute you prize attack at night bolt gun
do you want to do that one again i think we're fighting frogs this time for the record okay
i got a pretty good frog killer i don't radius that's better this whole opportunity
i don't think i'm gonna use that plasma cannon b i don't like plasma cannon b
i just don't i'm sorry i do want to use the power lance right oh yeah power lance me what
yeah it was power lance i don't think enough i mean i have a shitty version of it but it was
really good oh dude the suppressed gun and then the grid shot 116 118
let's get some more light what do you say jerma there's a technical issue
please tell me what it is and i will try to fix it jerma wake up spiders spiders
your shoes are untied i'm not wearing shoes oh my god this is ugly oh i thought we were
indoors or something i had a whole bunch of airstrikes what are we doing up here i don't know
this is a very ugly mission though well it's night time so that oh i see the frogs frogs
i don't have any booster yeah just like sitting over here they're just this is their natural
habitat man all the way down i've destroyed all the industry mission complete see if we can
lock on that was pretty cool yeah god oh i can't just stand still like that i guess he's dead
because the rocket stopped yeah it is midnight it's too late oh yeah that's growing red i keep
forgetting that you were two hours behind you yeah but it's not that means i haven't like gotten to
shoot at something yet well then maybe you should try harder it's pretty good no i'll get that guy
i lit that guy up that guy's just rolling around can i lock on to two okay there may be a few too
many people here that one hit this air shot i have to log on to them one at a time i want a better
version of this i want this thing at level three or something yeah this one was like even more
rockets would be amazing this thing is so good against these guys in the head
how i think i'm a lot more of these you know i want a better version what the fuck is happening
oh dear all right i'm not going over there watch out it's gonna explode wherever you want
can you believe how good this guy is whoa that didn't look good all right i'm gonna go collect
have fun have fun kids what was it on the game we played a long time ago where you had like somebody
always had to go gather stuff every few seconds like there was always someone in charge of going
together someone had a machine it probably was man versus machine actually yeah you had to go
like yeah yeah yeah plenty of time played it we played it a bunch everybody had to gather like
pick up the drops oh don't kill me please yeah that's a scout when the scout everyone that's how
you get money and the scout then gets healed and overhealed the more money he picks up damien
you really get out of the way where's the moat what i'm going to get the frog over here
so i'm not saying a lot there's a lot of frogs everywhere the one that's being annoying to me
this one getting this one get him the one that was marked the one that was just being annoying
to me now you get this shot it just makes me randy oh yeah okay i gotta back it up
oh yeah i'm dropping the bombs okay bomb street bombs street that was close
air shot got it don't you even fucking talk to me about air shot now there's a giant frog behind us
don't worry i'm on the case oh another frog i'm on the case i don't know where the hell he's going
see anything right now when i'm circled by this red bubble is getting out of hand okay sorry for
trying to help you i'm gonna die the performance of the three are you i'll protect you guys got
fucking with my shield annihilated space after all it's unlikely they brought submarines with them
i heard submarine yeah it's unlikely they brought submarines with them
to take advantage of this opportunity well they are from outer space didn't you hear him he
clarified that he made sure you realized that such an overkill for a spider is it wouldn't you like
have an orbital missile destroy the whole house down i found one spider don't worry germa i've got
them there you go scorpion burn the house and he's already dead he is dead uh-oh lots of stuff to get
uh-oh and i don't have any power uh-oh uh-oh stuck on this pole uh-oh
no no oh wow you're right oh yes i got the dude i got the bulge laser level 20 this is surprise
attack at night come see me i got bulge laser everything how you guys doing you guys still
down to play you want to break uh things how are you doing i'm not i want to use my bulge laser i
just i finally got a newbie gun just checking in i'm just checking in on everybody to see how
everybody's doing but but soon i okay we found a giant building in the city i'm gonna please
approach the building give me a level two or three or five of the power lines it's like my
favorite item right now ow i wish you could like dust some of these items you know all right so
we need to be able to kill um buildings i think i don't have anything good kill bill kill buildings
can you do the can we just try the oh wait what class are you right now are we going to come
buildings or what do you mean we could do it can we try the guide kit or are you not playing that
class no no no i'll do it i'm doing boy i'll get rid of my bomber so that you can shoot this one
time and realize it's bad it probably is bad the lock on time is 31 seconds
but it does 4529 damage okay now yeah let's do that no i'm not i'm not bored i'm that's my like
this is fucking awesome kill the building just we're playing with somebody right now that it's
getting late for them and we need to make sure that they're still ready to play what are we talking
to be in germa made a commitment to each other i think i'm gonna hold on let me change one more
look at the big cannon um yes me too actually are you doing anything for like christmas
anyone coming over to your house uh i'm going to your house for christmas yeah no all right go see
it your house christmas christmas christmas with the cranks isn't that a movie uh probably
not surprising oh my god no well i have the wrong loadout for this but it's all right
that's a i think we have to destroy the giant rub from smash oh is this a ufo one
yeah i really don't have this stuff for this either yeah i don't either here let's at least
try your thing i'll put a laser on one of them well it's gonna just 4 000 damage it should be on
like a larger than a single ufo don't you want to at least see it and i'm gonna reset yeah
this thing is really really good i see it hang on locking on i will be don't kill it guys
okay what i gotta wait 30 seconds to lock on to this
hey it's ready there it goes this all away that was a big missile i think someone just blew it up
those things very good oh there it's running away it just hit a building
that thing was stupid that was comically slow that really was that's the worst thing ever
all right let me get the high ground killed all those people okay we get to use it on this
building up here oh my god what is shooting out here i have my bulge laser watch out for the
5 million cannons all shooting at the same time what is this lightning from zoos that's my bulge
laser the zoos cannon look at these bubble lights i mean at this point we're like
there's a bunch of jelly beans coming at us all right mark uh mark one of those like
forward cannons on the big machine are we even destroying them i don't know that's what we're
advancing to i think they're all shooting yeah give it 30 seconds all right i'm going in
oh there's too many insects oh did you already lock on to something yeah okay there's a lot more
swarms coming in a second wait you dropped it i had to restart because you lost the laser
so
ready and there's a mech in my way fire you firing to where you're firing towards the
cannons i don't know wherever he's marking it's going to shoot one of those cannons
all right going which one where the laser pointing can you see on its way it's wiggling around
hopefully it goes down where i'm trying to get a good view there it goes i think it actually
oh i didn't even see it it actually worked it killed that whole turret
that uh let's do that another 30 seconds that hey i'm already over here don't worry i'll get
all the turrets you guys just take care of them watch this even have guns check it ready tell me
when you're ready for me to paint or when you're painting i'm not doing it i'm doing my laser on
all these freaking hands firing my laser don't worry guys boomer mean you take care of you you
guys just stay you guys stay well stay you guys just stay you stay i go i can't see far enough to
get what is this pink was it is the pink what the other laser chases i yeah i'm pointing my laser
and it's going towards that how inaccurate is this gun got it got bullet drop what do
you mean this it is i'm i'm shooting at it right now there's a lot of these
it is though we've destroyed a lot of turrets that was way too low it's not working
i guess they mean like i have no activity whatsoever i can't even get up there is the
big blazer shooting no all right all the turrets that are shooting in that direction there's a
bunch shooting in the other direction but the ones that are shooting towards you guys are all
pretty much gone i'm going to take me 10 years to get over here i don't even know if i can get
up there i said two drums what about the big cannon should we be aiming at that
i wonder how effective that is are you kidding me how are you going to get up there well
uh-oh yeah yeah i can't get up there well here they come what is it trying to make me look at
drones a lot of them holy shit okay i'm gonna try to take out all the saucers that just came out
give them the bulge because it is one hit with this holy shit what the fuck is firing right now
uh which what are you talking about like a giant laser beam just came out of the sky
jesus christ germa that was like the first thing i asked when we started this mission but yeah
what i mean i i've been away from you guys the entire time i i have like a giant purple beam
coming down from the sky so it's not like the view distances i've been i've been taken out
i didn't mean to say oh he's been so busy being productive oh yeah what do you think what do you
think the cannons just disappeared on their own we killed like two of them just the two of us
well great i killed 14 look it's only because you're faster not because you're stronger okay
you can't wait to see your new movie that comes out soon faster not stronger what is that the
sonic the hedgehog movie all about you what the hell is what been asking at the whole game
giant cannons germa you didn't even destroy those i can't can you not destroy the big
turrets i don't think so not alone no this is just that we have we got the retreat order which means
you win yeah we won it looks like you can hurt them and then i'm like doing damage to it you sure
all back um is it dying or are we dying that's a great question if we let those drones chase us
hey wave three oh my god shoot down the drone do it any other requests
okay he did have another request as it happens yeah shoot down the drums oh my god i'm getting
how is that like zeus laser working out speaking of shit i need to i gotta go collect
don't get those yeah i'm dead no i'm dead you can't be dead because i am i'm fairly close to you
though you guys you guys doing okay i'm not dead i'm wiggling around i hear your screams what
bothers me is it's a different voice each time yeah but that's what i also like the most about it
yeah but there's some viewers in here now from six hours ago so they haven't heard it before
everyone i've had the same amount of viewers the whole time i've been streaming
yeah but there's different ones no they're the same people people don't leave my stream
i mean like your viewers are probably like a lot less
my viewers don't leave my stream or else i ban them the ones who are still here just the ones who
didn't get star why do you have to be so mean is there any reason that was mean that was a direct
attack that was a direct attack to italics it was a direct mean comment all right let me get the
rest of this listen i don't need anyone to defend me you do we're not going to this christmas party
anymore i would have loved a real answer about where you're going for christmas but you don't
respect me enough i guess i don't think anyone's going anywhere is the sad truth i think we did it
there's two ants on top of this laser and that's it all right let me just make sure i got most of
the stuff let me go back here i think you gotta kill those two ants i do but i just want to be
just taking a quick look to see make sure i didn't leave any boxes can we kill these like
purple turrets yes you can i see one box that i didn't get down here two actually
i guess i don't need to anymore ah i got it come on come on italics what come on a debuser
just one more damage come on hey no new weapons wow did you curse me we're fighting
pylons in the mountains okay let's see um my six i'll try it is it pylons right
i did say pylons i did say pylons i did say pylons oh you can use rank seven stuff now
hey flaunt it if you got it put this back all right how do you kill pylons with missile
launchers can you lock on with missile launcher yeah well mooned on laser target it well i mean i
have i have missiles that don't require that yeah sure yeah sure yeah sure oh yeah sure oh yeah go
back to club penguin no we're not playing club penguin kiss yourself all the sad faces yeah
what drinks do you guys drink coke like your your average drink water water
probably water uh coke coffee uh that's a lot of pylons those are the three things i said yeah
you guys look the same you answered that i mean i answered it because we're different we're
different people so it could be different i should have got airstrikes and you're like there already
i was i drink a lot of green juice too though two hits to kill these things
you know i'm a fan of green smoothies just like green gatorade i like green smoothies
i like green shakes anything green really yeah well that's pretty accurate there are frogs
this just reminds me of the scholar of the lost sins whatever it's called there's just
enemies fucking everywhere in random places enemies everywhere there are i can't see any
enemies because you can fly i'm leaving me to the pylons okay i got i got all my stuff is pylon
shoots yeah i can just kind of sit back here and just kill pylons actually i'm pretty good at it
except that one actually pushing me down the hill i'm out of ammo let me get a little closer
more fuel or i'm not gonna be able to do anything
dude he's not dead everybody robs he was
lots of armor good why are we naming the pylons now
what are they called now teleportation anchors isn't what you just said we're calling them that
now most you've been calling them they couldn't take the same pylons the whole game i guess well
no they're not called that anymore now they're called teleportation anchors well they needed to
research it for a few weeks we needed to change the name because it was offending some people
how it was insensitive i'm summoning a creep grapes do you like frozen grapes no thanks
they ain't no friend to me i've never had one all right red ants careful don't get grabbed
you must construct additional teleportation ink it's a good one chat boom no he didn't explode
what this gun's actually really good for this mission i am just the sniper now i don't puke
i'm not going that fast i'm the bad are you in an apc oh yeah can i get an apc as a mech boy
you can get in the back but you cannot drive it that felt good
okay i mean i think that happens in one movie i've ever seen in my life oh god
that four guy hey it's okay they're gonna get they're not immune like us
um attacks you want to give me apc i'll drive you
i need to pick up weapons i haven't been doing it i guess there's not anything no i've been back
there wait okay we're good we're in wish i had like a proper window nope this is as good as it
gets more bad guys this way oh we're graping it but yeah that that comment made even less
sense when you consider one third of the monsters are literally frogs they're gonna die when it
rains oh boy that was a hole in one this day appears everything to land them there's a lot
of things over there well hold on italics i think i'm gonna get out of here come on got it it's so
fun to watch just the long range i feel like i'm playing tribes ascend but with way more players
wow yeah game this game's not dead hey actually that's not a yeah that's what it didn't hire us
say now we're done something like that right
here it is again for a newbie uh-oh i'm being eaten i am also being you are both being eaten
i can't see a thing and the only thing that i can do is is have artillery shoot this ant i'm coming
rescued boom i love the boom here comes the boom ready or not well that's because you're a boomer
please lock on what is shooting me there's a lot behind oh my god let's come down from the road
watch out they're all gonna be pouring down here that was not worth it
um i'm gonna play yo there's too many i'm going in i'm going in i'm gonna go for a frog kill
what's even the objective here oh there's a bunch of frogs yeah uh we're supposed to be on the
pylons this guy's just sitting on like a fucking couch watching me i was supposed to be on the
pylons but i was being attacked by ants who were eating oh who's on ants oh program yeah
lock this thing kills and less shots than the plasma rifle does one down next one on the way
guys any more of these i'm comboing him i'm comboing him he won't land i'm comboing him
oh there's a lot going on over there hey that was pretty good for a newbie
down which leads to lower employment rate i'm dead hey the employment rate is going to go
way down when every business is destroyed on earth oh there are lots the employment
rates going down with all the dead people you're alive you're alive they're doing great
yeah mortician army jobs way up uh also way down when they die turnover rates really high
look out he just gandalf that fucking ass he just gandalf that ass yeah i went
no no you the marine one you shall not pass dude i'm so ready to use my gold
someone just said log out okay why dude just fucking log out already
i don't disagree hey uninstall okay you're so bad uninstall his name is radigast lebron and
he's not even good
come on grape i'll get this last one let me get this last one i need this come on
damn it let me get this don't touch him don't touch him he's mine nice see i just like we
were in the circle and i pulled up my lights every and everybody stopped i kill steal
oh look at all this new stuff i finally got a higher level z gun holy poop it took that long
spark pine pretty cool better charge time so this is the a1 uh it says alien ships are this
i think this is yeah this is like ships and people landing i'm putting this one back on
yeah the frogs are doing their landing the thing and i have a flamethrower look at the range the
increaser okay um what else did i get vibro roller i don't sorry we but by the way we definitely
can't stop on this one because level 23 just to let you guys know what does that mean that's
23 is this is the devil's number oh yeah we can't stop here then i remember that now you can bring
it up about the devil i might i might do ranger this level i don't know but i think all my shit
still sucks what's happening oh god are any mods around to figure out what just happened
hey what just happened guys i think somebody uh somebody linked porn how did you how do you
accidentally do that if it was safe for work then you know accidentally linked porn well he thought
he had something else copied he thought he had something else copied and you then you
did you put control veed entered not gonna lie i almost did that in star chat once
what how how do you accidentally have porn copied like that would insinuate that you like what are
you copying it for are you sharing it with friends look at this thing how does this work
where is the ship oh oh no pizza oh my god i want pizza don't say that oh my god i want pizza
stop saying pizza you're making a lot of people angry right now especially me oh my god
oh i don't understand how this works but okay did wait you don't share porn with your friends
like hey let's keep it all to myself this one's a must watch no i gotta copy that one for the later
all right are you saying you do that you stay out of my room or shared anything with me
well i didn't know i didn't i didn't know this takes like three minutes to warm up but when it
does it just goes i thought you meant the porn you were linking it takes like three minutes for you
to get into it but man it's all storyline all right you gotta watch i really recommend the
storyline though listen the writers for this was the same as the writers from the last one
i mean you mentioned pizzas it's okay it got me they got me on this workplace
man i really do want pizza yeah i just ate pizza and i want pizza i had pizza yesterday i think
it's still open for me by like another like 20 minutes well i mean like you guys got this
covered right this that was the number 23 we can't i mean you guys got this covered i could just
order this pizza oh i mean okay you're gonna order the pizza i see what you're saying okay
man this frame really got off the rails at when i am yeah this is just one of those
chill streams we just hang out talk about pizza talk about porn
porn pizza we got it all here you know we got it all just doing a quick vlog i just had a few
things in my mind felt like talking about something that understands me i'm put it listen
wait how do i undo that this would be the worst way to die i'm sorry it would
frogs stuck to this building this is a meat lovers name your pizza does this do anything
no thanks what using you named it no thanks i don't want to name it like what if they can
see what i name it like if i call it like the big dough burster like that's creepy
i think no thanks is funny though if you write no thanks that's like an insult to
whoever has to look at that oh man i don't wait i want to set this guy on fire like uh hey what's
the name of this guy's pizza no thanks like okay dick i i freaking i'll be right back everyone's
really enjoying the view on my stream here i'll go like there now you can see what's happening
get a nice crotch shot pizza is so delicious i oh my god i really might just not even care
and eat pizza tonight i can sense what's going on in your mind like i haven't had like real
pizza in like three months i don't even think i care i think i'm gonna eat pizza we have
red frogs here wow guys can eat pizza and doesn't even care yeah out of context that's like okay
you're gonna eat pizza tonight all right what's you don't even care it's such a good boy haven't
eaten pizza in so long but you know tonight i'm really gonna let myself go what a rebel he's
gonna eat pizza okay i'm sorry this is taking so long but the moment ashley had the opportunity
she stole my credit card and it's like all wet you report it what'd you what'd you do now
uh well she she took it and it's all right i didn't do it we have a super frog here you
understand like this is super frog and we're like dying she's screaming i'm dead thanks a lot
thanks a lot we thanks a lot for going to get your pizza hopefully it's a good pizza
i hope the dough blaster is good i'm not gonna make it honestly germa i hope you open it up and
sit on it why would i do that sit on the pizza it's safer work it's the store's closed
that's not funny that's like sucks i'm sorry you can't get food that's not like cool i'm not
close 30 minutes ago you know sometimes you really just have your heart set on something
i did get homing i got rapid mirage upgrade i like how you only have one pizza store
all right yeah the pizza place is closed you know how sometimes you really have your heart set on
something should have moved to vegas pizza pizza everywhere he went there you guys smell
we're gonna smell like pizza tonight baby i'm ready let's do this
hold on i'm not let me let me check there's gotta be something on there i'm super hungry
super hungry let's go back to new york new york city somebody just wrote i love this shit man
somebody just wrote hey uh beater wait what it's like this there's nobody said it hey uh beater
you said it but i didn't say it everywhere's closed i just there's no food they said it whoops
there was no uh you but you said it i didn't i didn't just say we were talking about pizza
so what is somebody just wrote hey beater like is that a pizza reference no that's a joe from
fucking family guy so you but your excuse was we were just talking about pizza yep somebody just
wrote in the chat hey beater you can't tell it's kind of you kind of had to be there i feel like
i am here this happened of all i was here yeah this happened when you were you were right here
but they wrote it with a b that's why it was funny right no but you don't you don't you had
to be there you had to be there like a year ago the emoji no you don't you would be there like a
year ago oh god yeah you had to have you had to be there you had to be there i don't get it
it's all right why is this guy shooting to me from a reclined position
while also sniping me isn't that what you're doing right now though come on this is just like
oh this is just us we are these fucking frogs just lying on up sitting on our asses shooting
i mean i'm inside of mexico sort of i'm kind of crying about this pizza like there's actual tears
it doesn't sound like i'm crying crying on the inside see that they're just like humans
oh my god the talks did you just mark me yeah thank you come on land it right in the chest
excellent come on can someone make me a pizza like someone in one of these chats has to be able to
make me a pizza something on that i don't like something moscow
i don't think this weapon is very good there's a mind melter yeah what am i gonna do
we can't end on this mission satan will get us it's safe is gonna get you if you end on 23
we have to end we'll end on 24 that's not how many hours are in a day that's how long the stream has
been so so it was what there was a super frog yeah there's a super this there is a red super
frog reclining eventually there's a red super frog i don't believe you there is you didn't see it
oh boy yeah i chose the wrong weapon for this my chainsaw axes are not doing so good they've opened
five here they come top of the building before i lose it oh i got it i can friendly fire
i can aim from down here this should be good uh my deflection shield i'm still taking damage through
this would suck oh that sucks oh you knocked the building down oh she had to bring race into the
fucking invasion you're just full of fucking you just she said it like why did you have to
pull a race card on this i think she was just saying that the red frogs were here
i'm dead well why didn't you use your dialogue that alex i mean i'm coming i'm coming shield
but it doesn't block me you shouldn't use your words then i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming don't
worry see i'm a good teammate and i'm gonna help you he's a fucking pizza sitter you would
have done the same thing see there's the red one something we're seeing on the scene
no that's not see the dialogue you hear it with your heart holy shit there are millions dying
every you just annihilated this frog that was almost sad i feel bad for the frog that you just
unloaded you feel bad for frogman last second weapon didn't matter holy shit oh i got i got
the blacker okay let's see wait wait it's an aerator tank i thought i couldn't get tanks
24 that was rangers all right i want to replace one of these all right so how this is the this
last one oh i can get them too last one for the night don't don't say this is the last one and
then you can go do whatever you wanted to do well no i'm just trying to gauge what you want to say
you just set us gate we'll gauge it when the mission's over because i just got the blacker
okay okay all right double co-op jupiter that was that wasn't oh whoa that was an ultimate
co-op jupiter no yeah it's impossible i mean like seriously i can't believe somebody actually got it
use these i'll use the lightning gun and then
hmm i wonder i'll go back to this this is fun
i'm sick of being ready first all the time i was here i was here for the co-op jupiter
all right bingo how far does that go not far enough oh boy this looks like it's gonna be
tough can this tank go shreds hey look at me guys i'm the thread ripper
in video thread ripper close it's not quite hold that font
you have to negotiate screaming up with them hey
hey stop doing that okay the aliens have not responded to negotiation tech
we've been trying to use dialogue for three weeks for some reason it's not catching on
oh jeez what's that from somebody said and you get you get nothing on a german stream
nope german 985 on twitch tv somebody's gonna get it subscribe now stop subscribe now subscribe now
now hey uh you guys heard about switch front action league now look at stan and fire
you get you don't get anything you get hey nice work that means that you get the reference
people are subscribing now hey guys let me tell you about switch front okay you guys do it every
single month okay even if you stop watching the channel oh they can't look behind us hey nice work
i'm a still busy lifting great so i didn't steal anything remember action league yeah
kaboom that was such a great that was such a great variety channel all right where are you i can't
even see now 50 followers left until i can drive what like i can't move what's a lot you bumped
into the ceiling was now needs to be washed and sterilized but charlie charlie and i didn't
understand my tank won't move okay now it's moving look wait now you got a tank
but community stuff just came in from ahon i did that that's you i know i did that i know i did that
charlie i was the one that said just so if i didn't say anything would that have happened
all right i think you by law have to pay them to me oh my god it doesn't drive like other things
dry and suddenly i begin to see there's a little light for me because i got a golden ticket it's
horse chump come on don't do it somebody and do it shut the fuck up listen that's a good song
you're making me angry hey well
that's all the time you really are why are you such an angry person
what if it happened to positive star is that what happened when was i ever positive
i don't know you used to do positive only screams remember oh yeah i remember positive yeah it's
coming back to me now positive only so what the heck is coming back to do that
hey does someone want to drive this for me does somebody just drive this for me
what was looking at driving are you in a mech i think i'm on a small pickup truck are you hold on
oh legendary just dropped um i can't drive it we can just sit on the back to ride on oh my god
this thing's already going to get destroyed what are you guys doing nothing i was riding in a
pickup truck but it didn't really need help with the whole but i was being very alien invasion
thing i was being very i think we killed so many at this point that uh they don't really concern
me anymore i think we have some larger problems at hand like uh the economy yeah the economy
and opening up new dialogues somebody said i need this on pc i know if i could snap my fingers
and just have it be on pc i would if i could snap my fingers again after that i'd delete it
from the pc afterwards that wouldn't make any sense no this is not on pc this is ps4 only for an
indeterminate amount of time nobody knows because only the ps4 is capable of rendering these
graphics i mean it is because it's the only platform is on all right i have to collect good
luck i there's so much shit here that i want to map and if you get otherwise we are not going to
get anything you know what germo we're never going to progress
select that's what i'm doing uh-oh dual shock battery low uh-oh dual shock battery low no
how much is a dual shock charge from full charge because this one is fully charged
i think it's like 10 10 bucks no no no i don't know how much is it how many hours how many hours
does it how many hours do you have when it's unhooked i don't know mine hasn't said that yet
this is fully charged been what seven hours ten dollars of charge you've been gaming harder than
me i mean you gotta pay for gas pay for electric gas i think that's it what do you think the
electricity comes from um the gods in the sky is zeus that's right i'm calling me newbie yeah i
don't know why we're still newbies it doesn't make any sense where's this guy she anything yet
help start building getting on the pizza what about pizza dude i want the pizza i don't know
someone said that you're supposed to give sam h 9900 pizza i have the caliban support vehicle
range weapon blink ball up still not over the whole zero why i don't use it plasma fall up
plasma fall went up a lot actually oh it has that like a health recovery room
in the vehicle 25 artillery unit artillery unit bolt gun
hmm i'll try it again what's the bow we have to destroy artillery to destroy artillery all
right well i have a grenade for this i probably shouldn't play ranger you can't undone 25 that's
bad luck it's a quarter of a hundred oh fuck okay i mean shit yeah how old are you star i don't know
i don't know i don't know recently like like seriously lately i've been thinking
how old am i i think i'm 29 you don't know how old you are i don't know how old you are
you don't have you don't actually know how old you are i was doing i was doing the math like
a day ago there's only one generation that forgets how old they are on purpose or on accident no i'm
28 are you though 28 yeah i am come on i just did the math are you though i think you're all
the i thought you were 31 no i was born 1990 i think you just made that up is that what you're
the one you're the you're the only 30 here that's may be accurate uh okay oh just wait hey just wait
you two you two boys just wait just wait yeah hey hey two boys here uh gonna be waiting for a long
time i guess just you guys wait you know a couple years before you're as old as i am now yeah and
then you'll see what it's like to be 30 over 30 well we'll just we'll just be regular 30 and then
eventually over 30 yeah and you you tell me how you feel on that next day
well even then though you're gonna be just as much older than us as you are right now so
whatever oh yeah these artillery things didn't they used to be like robots but now i guess they're
fraud instead of robots that's right now how is this one any different than the other one i mean
again maybe it's more damage for long range support what's the objective kill this thing
is kind of good but it takes a ton of power it's not that good
everyone's getting old you're not old until you're forgotten my plan for this show young
and i'm old yeah i mean we're not gonna be 30 for at least like 12 years
i'm dead yeah i didn't know you somebody help
somebody come back that was pretty good oh he's old oh my bad sucks like
we got to think of what to say at your funeral you don't have that problem with us
you get to just opt out way before us yeah i just i just wave my death rights
i never read the end user license agreement no guys what do you mean what's gonna happen
to the funeral i'm going to use whatever money is in my will and rent out an entire carnival
then invite everybody that ever wants to go to the public it's free all the rides are free and
then at exactly like 4 p.m sharp right no yeah there's rides and shit and at 4 p.m sharp exactly
they're gonna put me into a giant fucking slingshot and slingshot my casket in the
atlantic ocean that would be cool that's uh i think the pacific's closer now though
so which coast are you planning on buying though
it's a big slingshot just saying that's that's dope
oh i like being a sniper just wait 800 years the atlantic will be right up against vaguest
oh that's dude too soon wow yeah it is it's gonna happen real soon how come they don't have any
infantry defending their artillery um what if they're the infantry and we just haven't seen
the real artillery yet 800 is optimistic oh my god right in the head oh beautiful shot
oh man no i got i couldn't even move man somebody get you're welcome i'd love to but i'm gonna like
die before i get there i threw a grenade right in his head too and it didn't matter
i couldn't move i got double tapping around they really do love these frog enemies though don't
they i got him with his own gun
yeah i'll get you sooner or later what's your problem is he is he peeing you started grunting
he's uh this is he's aiming right at the ground why am i staring at it
i i can't help but i have to stare at it die i don't know what to do i have i've hit this guy
with so many missiles all right let's help are you still alive oh i'm good okay thanks for the
help magic and one pixel damn it looks like a watch that coming the whole way
oh indeed right in the head oh right in his head again oh i went through his head
true it oh no he doesn't have any weapons so he's useless and somebody killed him
seems like it might be painful that he didn't keep walking no am i dead i don't like the green
gun coming for you i'm coming am i dead i think there's only one dude yeah i'm trying to deflect
the artillery shots but it's difficult to aim why did he just watch that i'm dead we're all
almost dead jerma acknowledge me what's up wow senpai dude welcome to the germs moon unit
what's happening i helped a little jerma with a weapon box i got the weapon box i got a lot of
them actually i got at least one plasma fall again rush core again bolt shooter again
hmm aggressive alien species species b all right up to level eight now perfect i can finally equip
this dumb thing that i haven't seen all game the splasher the splasher that's what it's called
some of the stuff has really dumb names like jerma
uh did i miss something nope not really nope okay just checking um i like this thing
keep it on i don't know what to use funny funny how you don't know let's go hey remember when
we were going to do the last one three missions ago it's alex you know what i can't i can't wait
for us to split a large delicious pepperoni thin crust pizza with that kind of with the greasy
peanut not peanut butter the greasy peanut butter all along with the greasy pepper whatever i
fucked up hey chad does anybody else uh Reese's on their pizza pepperoni with the greasy crispy
pepperoni slices dude i swear to god every time i switch off of artillery guy we get a mission like
this what is this uh that okay i gotta be in the air for this i can only shoot this nine times the
whole mission this thing sucks i picked the wrong loadout guys i have 18 shots same see if it's
even good leader it's not even good is it somebody leading the monsters who is leading okay if you
only get 18 shots of something don't you think it should one shot a frog yeah shot a frog
there's three shots a dog i can kill how many frogs uh one that's six frogs i think
there's so many particles in the screen i can't even tell which particle is mine
this thing is just totally spam and it takes so much energy i just want to apologize for my
reckless behavior do you want to retreat yeah there's a lot of spiders there
um you've chosen to retreat why would you retreat are you not paying attention but but we can do it
have to retreat we can do it one of our players had a weapon that didn't do anything literally
i had nine shots per weapon and it took three blasts oh no reload to kill one frog oh
oh i can hey do you want a guide kit me no that sucks because i have i have one that's not
i can go to 15 targets no 15 at the same time i'm just equipping a bunch of airstrikes
do you listen to your teammates i mean not really no pretty much what i hear is this like
it's like i don't know i had this cool co-op thing and then
i just hear no co-op moments here that's all i hear it's like a it's like yeah how about we
all go into our own separate solo games and do the same mission and like stop talking to each other
animal crossing all right which one of these guns is good for killing lots of people
okay i'm ready i'm not but i am i can't find the gun two flame throwers isabel is that you
all right let's talk about a real pizza not a thin crust pepperoni please shot that's the best kind
of pizza thin crust crispy crunchy greasy it's got to be greasy cheese i'll eat that as like a
secondary pizza but it would it certainly wouldn't be the main course you know what i mean oh no no
no no no i'm like peanut butter i like peanut butter crust yeah peanut butter full of crust i
think pizza hut did that first and when you bite in it goes and the greased and like oils goes down
your chin and all of your clothes all right i gotta get close for this unfortunately
i gotta shoot him look he's been looking look at that mouth he's been eating a lot of fucking
good pizza that's what i tell you if i use both flame throws at the same time it's actually
impossible to keep the screen down i can't tell if that's doing anything i honestly can't oh no
i'm in trouble i'm down hell hell hell hell get out of the way hell oh my god now why does
flying throw have recoil because it's insanely powerful and it has a lot yeah i don't like this
thing oh let's reset oh retreat no no what are you talking about i didn't say that can we retreat
retreat he hates it nice we're not on pc great little like escape sound
what you made like a i'm trying to make a loud escape sound how do you sing the next verse
i want to hear the rest of the song i think you just have to say there's slumbers in this
game then they start singing that's a deep head slow down it's unfortunate that i decided to go
only close range weapons and forgot my mobility ability you better be picking up boxes what do
you think i've been doing i've been making it part of my routine here i figured it out
pick up all the money are you dropping bombs here i think you're dropping bombs right here but it's
okay not a single soul look how strong this now i'm really hungry this is why it has recoil
i'm starving i'm talking about food well you he's i you mentioned the pizza thing
and then i just i kept seeing an image to die italics die and are you killing me yes that is
that yes is the answer to that question i mean you deserve it talking about food but now you're
gonna have to revive me unless you want to restart the mission again all right let's do it i love
restarting go ahead i dare you this guy's unloading for free on me i'm so embarrassed
i knew you couldn't do it i'm just gonna die again actually i was like i have a face still
because all the spider again good he's dead and we are getting late here aren't we it's like two
what two a.m eastern time flies we're gonna kill bugs i'm gonna get some what would be a proper
weapon for this class for this mission well the kissing one the bug is nice i mean i do like
kissing spiders i do too oh my god who doesn't love like a hot dryer did you hear that there
was a scorpion in the house i heard put it there i'm scary i bought it from the pet store and left
it there that's not cool oh yeah you got you got a lot of shit to pick up
now i am just running around it's you again that's all i've been doing that's an extra armor
kissing live for just over seven hours by this point you should have consumed at least one mortal
soul interesting is that the secret to your eternal youth all right hungry friends
all right do me this favor you know what you know let's call it there because this next one is a
a drone mission here can you do me one favor yeah can you just start the mission with the beam i just
want to see what this my highest tier missile launcher i've had the whole game done i'm not
even fucking hungry buddy just want to see what it does i'm not gonna do you don't have to do
i gotta get the targeting lasers what you want me to get you want me to be your bitch
i mean you are the support character he's leaving he's leaving the character killing all of everything
i'll be around for like another well a little bit you do i mean call down all of the support
vehicles and then instantly get in them so what was that sound it was like so i had to switch
classes to someone who could fight for himself okay let's see what it looks like
she makes them even more nice let's see dip is it gonna hit it oh i don't think so
they're just flying are they coming back where are they going they're coming back
at us they're just going straight at us oh you i could do like 30 missiles this way man
those are gonna hit us too wreck them all right hit who what are we even doing here
they're not attacking we gotta kill these drones this is a drone mission okay well it's up to you
to mark them and you guide the missiles this is a drone mission i think it's time these things
reminded me of pizzas all right these just look like pieces guide them why can't they shoot with
my other missile launcher right now i'm not sure i can handle this i mean it's not bad it's like 18
missiles per launcher it'd be good probably just requires two people to aim them yeah i cannot
catch up with any of these guys yeah this mission is gonna suck it is required this is gonna require
a lot more objective kill all the things kill it's always kill all the things yeah but they're
you always ask and it's always kill all the things so we had to walk forward so the objective is walk
forward then kill all the things are we saying yeah
look sometimes it's man sometimes it's saucers sometimes it's pylons sometimes it's red ants
sometimes it's green frogs sometimes it's time to go and make your own pizza
pizza how long did you how long did you wait to do that five seconds okay all right well
edf5 that's fun sapiens i'm glad i got that last line out there just before the end no items
acquired well that was fun well that's a fun game yeah most armor highest completion rate
highest weapon i'm just putting the microwave in the pizza this second here okay just putting
the microwave in the pizza guys don't have a pizza all right well uh it's alex and stir
thank you for showing me this game it's very fun it's a very fun game it's very grindy and
it's kind of just like a little hang out fun game with some friends but you're not gonna play
tomorrow wait do you want to play tomorrow off camera though i don't know dude what's the does
anything you do actually matter if it's off camera i'm i'm just kidding hey webcam's on by the way
webcam is on oh i copied it from germa's chat somebody in there posted a porn link
did you really did you get no don't do that i honestly thought that look i need it for my
start a call after you know that i'm doing all right well i'll see you guys well you could
screen share yeah i was gonna say that too well you guys have fun have fun doing that
uh i'm gonna spell it out f-u-c-k-i-n-g space w-e-i-r-d-o-o-s so bah he's gone star's gone
he's already gone so thanks star for coming and uh we have to have a discussion about this
pizza yes we're about we're about to both turn our streams off here and have a pizza discussion
but uh see you later thanks for playing i'm hope you had fun italics i'm in the next room
in two rooms over what do you wow what i almost just dropped another coffee on my desk i'm at all
right i left hey i'm sorry i left abruptly i almost dropped a coffee on my desk um hey don't drop a
copy of my ps4 that's already i've already like goodbye all kinds of shit goodbye other porn
posting chatter not gonna let you finish that one anyways thanks for coming out guys just a
edf is a lot of fun hopefully it was interesting at least to watch for a little while i know we got
pretty late here uh it's like 11 o'clock pacific which is very late for everybody else so let's
go back and do the bits uh it should not take us very long thank you tod tod flowered for the
one dollar squash them bugs hashtag charity oh yeah so i believe if you give bits and you do
hashtag charity they are running a twitch is running a campaign i think right now right
so that's good but thank you tod thank you marvish mcgally for the dollar and 10 cents i find this
stream inherently satisfying edf is inherently satisfying to play it is a very satisfying game
uh we're wed thanks to the one dollar jackbox marathon with your friends when um i don't know
i mean edf was we've all been kind of looking forward to the game so that's why we did that
tonight he needs friends for i got plenty of friends okay come on thank you divas for the
three bucks hashtag charity thank you thank you divas luke warm soda can thanks for the one dollar
bugs are scary i don't like them either bugs are just they gross me out they freak me out
some bugs i think are okay but i don't know spiders are weird anything that can poison you
or sting you some bugs can put you in the hospital you know that's scary i agree thank you mostly
lost for the one dollar hey everyone psa don't forget to add hashtag charity to your bit donations
yes absolutely thank you mostly lost for the reminder sly 161 thanks for the one dollar hey
germ thanks for the streaming edf looks good so far and i really want it but i'm waiting for a
pc port of it to come out hope you enjoyed it i wish it would come out on pc i was actually
gonna wait for the pc version as well but there's been no announcement at all that it's coming and
i think the last one when edf 4 came out wasn't it almost a year before they even talked about
it coming out on pc it was something like that it's gonna be a while so if you really want to
enjoy edf 5 then you unfortunately and you can't wait you're gonna have to buy it on ps4 but it's
a very fun game lukewarm soda can again thanks for the one dollar i don't like bugs hold me i'm
scared lukewarm soda can again ten dollars ten bucks from lukewarm soda can thank you
so much for your ten dollars wish i could stick around but i have finals to study for college
and responsibilities also bugs are scary nope and then hashtag charity thank you and yeah good luck
uh you guys aren't going to see me for a couple of days here the next stream is probably going
to be on saturday and i'm going to be building a bird house and something else that i've i it's
going to be the worst thing ever but i feel like i want to just do it because it might be funny it
might be fun after the bird house something else is going to happen and i don't know how you guys
are going to feel about it but it's going to happen because the bird house is going to take
me probably 30 minutes no it is not a video game it's it is it's not something anyone's going to
want to watch it's going to i it's going to take me 25 minutes to make the bird house that i got
and like paint it and i'm not going to do a 25 minute stream but see you saturday and good luck
on your finals everybody it is currently wednesday or thursday for a lot of you and hopefully you do
well thank you mr sneak man for the dollar 80 just went through the most stressful day at school in
a long time and i think i just hit the stream jackpot excited to watch you dorks played this
and keep my mind off of impending doom that the midterm tests coming up next month thanks as always
and keep up the quality streams germa hart hashtag charity thank you mr sneak man good luck to you
on your midterms glad you could come here and unwind today was like if it was just chill you
know i screamed a few times but edf is just a very relaxing game you just kind of burn through bugs
uh wild fox thanks for the one dollar do you eat ass no seriously though please listen and watch
this this is gonna be something about me eating ass make sure this is about not about like me
eating ass oh let's see it's time to kick gum and chew it's time to kick gum and chew
it the title is just meme is this some kind of meme is this is this you is this is wild fox is
this you doing this that's me is it some kind of meme it's a classic meme well it's classic thank
you for that wild fox hey garfield the monday killer what's happening germa aliens are attacking
garfield residence oh my blizz germa what's garf gonna do can we talk about this right now
germa reads all these garfer graphs and very rarely complains about how weird they are you roll with
the punches germ i respect that that being said uh already board up the windows and doors they're
coming for me and germa they think monday's are sacred or something and they want my head i need
a christmas miracle i need grinch's green pancakes only and i hopped up why would you eat green
pancakes just order regular pancakes all the grinch's green pancakes are is just pancakes
with a shitload of food coloring in them that can't be good for your body make salmon 425
degrees in the oven eight minutes what 15 minutes just find a recipe thank you garfield thank you
valk for the one dollar devil may cry 5 releases on march 8th maybe we'll play it timmy tim tan
thanks for the one dollar fall is my favorite season hashtag charity thank you fall is your
favorite season let's see oh it's one of these okay not a cloud in the sky what a beautiful day
yes thank you noob king for the three bucks it's 70 degrees i love october me too it's not too hot
and not too cold fall is my favorite season mine too the weather is almost perfect and the leaves
are very pretty when they change colors not a cloud it's like 5 000 hours of content that you
could probably pull from there it's 70 degrees thank you noob king for the three bucks they say
hashtag charity thank you felix felis thanks for the five dollars hey germa do you remember the
time that you forgot to turn off your webcam while going to take a pee break when you took a
huge bottle of elmer's glue the value size and fucking dumped the entire thing on a rack of
freshly baked cinnamon rolls and ate them all 15 right there in one sitting chat was recoiling
for a full 20 minutes after that and you ignored them like nothing happened you just made me rub
my eyes when did i do that i didn't i did not do this this didn't happen hashtag charity thank you
felix for the five dollars dark star 700 000 games thanks to the one balla when i woke up this
morning i realized i forgot to buy an omega 3 filled fish at the store so instead i just gulped
down a few goldfish out of the tank i aced the exam thanks for the advice no it's got to be
well good thing you did great job acing the exam but second of all it's got to be salmon or it's
gonna be tuna omega 3 high on omega 3 and don't go crazy don't eat like 10 pieces of salmon over
the course of three days you'll get sick and you might not get sick but then but just be careful
eat one or macaroni a little bit of olive oil fresh carb up but not too much don't don't just
don't go overboard but thank you for the one dollar thank you the long egg you should have a
movie night where you stream a well this uh oh sorry this is i read this this is 99 you always
got me i've got me with the 99 top hat why is everybody ha haing me what are you ha haing the
top hat are you ha haing what i would meet what i do uh thank you the long egg though for the 99
bits not supposed to do that i'm not supposed to read that purple rose tattoo thanks for the five
dollars thank you purple rose thanks for the streams i teach children from trauma and they
really help me unstress make me laugh and help me sleep even on my toughest days keep doing what
you're doing uh you as well so thank you so much purple rose tattoo five dollars glad you can come
and unwind thank you thank you elizabeth for the one dollar i've accidentally messaged a friend
porn on steam because i thought i had something else copied however a month or two later he did
the same to me so he laughed it off you guys you guys saving pornography to your clipboard
what is what thank you leather jacket for the one dollar i feel as if leaving the accidental
porn link is a better punishment it's like when you get caught passing notes in class and are
forced to read it in front of everyone that's fucking funny that's true though
yeah thanks leather jacket hey drosophilia thanks for the one dollar can i have a hug
yeah okay thanks for the one dollar thank you drosophilia kaleb thank you kaleb five six oh
six for the two bucks why do you hate australians when did i ever say that we're talking about time
zones uh is this pacific time as far away from australia as possible because okay if it was
three it might be no what's the furthest time zone from pst what would like what country is
the furthest from my time zone i'm not sure it's six p.m in australia right now that sounds pretty
huge that sounds like it's 12 hours december 13th 6 p.m in australia holy shit that's wild
what time is it on the sun there is no time on the sun it's timeless
but thank you kaleb i don't hate australians what are you talking about come on i've done that a
lot today come on hey garden of eden thanks for the 10 dollars garden of eden thanks for 10 bucks
germa i want to send you mail do you have a p.o box uh hashtag charity no i've been i've thought
about doing that before but that gets really messy because you never know what fucking somebody might
send you so i've stayed away from it i have stayed away from it so probably not but i do
appreciate anybody that wants to give me something but don't don't worry about that thank you for
even considering though and thanks for the 10 dollars right now garden of eden uh almost done
dinky duper thanks for the one dollar i couldn't think of a joke for this donation every time i
tried to think of one it would always end in calling you a boomer well i guess i just did
that anyways the game looks like a lot of fun while it has some questionable voice acting which
actually reminds me a lot of michigan report from hell i can't wait for the compact gaming
birdhouse stream even though there's no birds in vegas but until then i'll see you next time
germamites thank you dinky duper the compact gaming birdhouse does that have to be the
title of that stream it might have to be honey chain thanks for the one dollar they only want
you when you're what is happening they want you when you're 17 when you're 21 you're no fun
you're 33 loud p hashtag charity i don't know what this means but thanks for the one dollar
thanks for the charity thanks for the hashtag charity uh let's see art art van delay exporter
thanks for the dollar of 10 there's a lot of fun tonight thanks for streaming hashtag charity
no it was it's always fun to get it's always fun to get the gang together every now and again
right it was fun timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar hey would you ever stream symphony
of the night i'm playing it at the moment and thinking i'd love to see you play it
talk about castlevania castlevania there's a lot of castlevania games i don't know that that
i can't say that i would be completely into that when you're gonna eat your death adder
well i'm not going to but i mean the castlevania games are amazing
but i don't know if i would stream them but thank you for the suggestion of i'm not against i'm not
against ever doing anything but i work in the present my brain works in right now and that's
something i'm probably not going to do right now but thank you thank you fishy froy for the five
dollars i'm usually at school or work during your streams but a new release on second germa is always
an event to celebrate me and my friends all gather around to watch and it's always a good time thanks
for the laughs thanks for the five dollars fishy froy and thank you to holy mac for the fantastic
job that he does editing those videos so thank you so much really appreciate it clueless sniper
thanks for the one dollar what's your favorite pizza topping hashtag charity i'm just a pepperoni
kind of guy just thin crust pepperoni there's no bullshit i'll eat the whole pizza or buffalo
chicken pizza and when they do the big blue cheese swirl around the middle okay i gotta go
thank you just be for the one dollar it's almost our three year anniversary and i'm still waiting
for a proposal you could make it up to me by telling me your favorite sports teams boston red
socks and that's pretty much it i really only am like a red sox fan i would say the patriots
but i don't i don't really watch the patriots i don't really watch football so the red sox
and that's it and with that we're gonna run the credits all the new subs that came in
talks and i are gonna go get a pizza is there some reason why i cannot move over here now
let's see if i can do it from here stream labs what are you doing there we go all right thanks
everybody that subbed and resubbed we are we're at a huge amount of subs to alex is starving waiting
for me to finish the post stream now this was this was quick tonight this is not even like
25 minutes 20 minutes it's very late thanks to those of you that stayed up we'll see you again
soon saturday is the day mark it on your calendar we're gonna just we're just gonna have a chill
bird feeding stream almost a 200 000 followers to less than 30 followers away from 200 000
that's a lot of people a chill bird eating stream enjoy pizza time yeah i'm looking forward to it
and then i'm gonna get i gotta get a lot of stuff done around the house and i gotta get some
doctor's appointment stuff settled because i have to go get i need to go get like a celiac test
and like or like a gluten intolerance test because that's it's been really weird i gotta
go figure out what the fuck's going on with that shit so i'm gonna take the next couple days off
and i'll see you guys on saturday because i just i just need to know you know i want to know because
i've been avoiding all bread and gluten kind of products for a couple months now
fancy bartender stream yeah mark that on the calendar too that would be really fun
i feel like i would need a bunch of people here though you know what i mean i feel like i would
need to do that somewhere and have a bunch of friends come out for that and they have to try
my cocktails then goes and eats pizza well if you heard me earlier i was talking about i how i
i was i kept hearing the word pizza and i'm like i have to eat it but actually
it's gonna be a pretty good indicator because it's something that i eliminated i started taking
like a probiotic and i eliminated all gluten from my diet and i started feeling kind of fine i
started feeling a little bit better and i mean i don't know it's been so long that now if i eat
a shitload of pizza and if i like i'm keeling over like oh in pain and then it's that's the
fucking deal is sealed you know what i mean at that point i know and then i just gonna have to
figure out what the hell i'm gonna do about it i'll be fine it's i've eaten plenty of bread
so don't worry just not in the last like month or two or a gluten-free pizza that's true but
that's my time i'll see you guys saturday have a great rest of your night have a wonderful rest
of your morning where whatever time it is where you are thanks for sticking around hope you had
fun i did it's always a blast see you this weekend