Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, playing on Bonblitz as the Scout! Get that Scout! No! Help me!
Ooh, thank you Harlow. Thank you. Oh wow, cats, cats, cats, cats. That's a lot of different cats. Oh well. Watch out for the Spy!
He's still alive. He's probably going to be right here in a second. No, maybe not. Let's go around. Let's go around up top here.
Okay, you're real. You're the real deal. Cool. Let's go! Oh! Oh, get me out of here! Maybe not. Let's go with a Dubb. Dubb Cheeseburger.
Who else? Who else? Oh, Heavy? Heavy? Pyro? That guy's going to take mini crits! Goddamn! Oh, good shot. Good shooting, man.
We only got to hold this for like four and a half more minutes. Come on, dudes. Server Clearing Sapper. Wow. That's pretty cool. That's a lot of buildings destroyed.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Medic! Medic! Medic! That guy's going to get the full health kit. Yeah, he is. Oh, you want to go? Oh, you want to do this?
Is that a Spy? No, it's not. Alrighty. Just another couple minutes. Yeah, it's just another couple minutes. Wee! Oh, goodness, they know up here.
I could just hang out right here for a second. Cover them in the mad milk. Like this guy right here. Oh, I'm missing. Over and over again.
And there's a Heavy. Oh, goodness, Heavy. Oh, my God. That guy was like tracking me like a freaking radar gun. Go.
All right. I'm about to eat this pretzel stick that's been sitting here for at least three weeks. Gross. Why did I do that?
I don't know, but this Spy is still here. Yeah, there he is. There he is. Is there an Uber coming in? No, there's not a Spy, though.
Spy? Just... Oh, he's right here. Get out of here. No! No, don't let him get it! I'm going to have to eat another raw pretzel.
Come on. Come on, I have faith. I have faith, guys. Come on, get that Heavy. Get him. All right, undercover Spyro. It's up to you, baby.
You're going to... Anybody, anybody want to go with the Scout? Grill cheese, baby. Get it before I get hit by the Saw!
Oh, I thought that was a Spy. Reverting capture, reverting capture. Don't get hit by the damn saw blade.
I'm so scared right now. I'm going to get like backstabbed. No, we're good. Let's cap this thing. We got some... Why does it say five?
Oh, there we go. You are a Spy. I could tell. Well, capture the point, capture the point. Get it. Yeah, that's not a Spy.
That is a Pyro. And that is... I don't know, I can't even tell. Whoa. Whoa. No, you're real, you're real. Shit. Get him.
Now run. Run away. Give me the health. Give me that health, too. Oh, hey, you're a Spy. Any other people here? No.
No, don't land on the saw. It will kill you. Oh, run. No. We're playing Scout on Sawmill. I need to re-heal.
I need to heal. That's got a Mini-Sentry somewhere over there. Don't kill me with that. Oh, hey. Oh, man.
Give me this health. It is very important that I get that health. Stay alive. Hey, Spy. Hey, Spy. Hey, Spy.
How are you? Don't get hit by the blade. It's all about dodging these blades. Oh, my God. I thought that was...
I thought that was the saw blade. That just was like a scare moment right there. I feel like I just got hit by a car.
Let's go. Don't let them get it. Don't let them get it. We got this. We got this. Make our way out here.
Kill this Scout. Kill this Demo. Get hit from behind by God knows what. A soldier with the original.
Only one more minute. We got it. 33 seconds. Come on, folks. Come on, folks. Spray. No, I did my second jump already.
What? What are you doing up there, man? I'm going to kill this guy up here. Come on. Come here, you.
Are we going to win? I hope so. Yes, we are. Maybe not. Demoman, please don't kill me, sir.
All right, guys. Well, that's going to wrap up Face Game Fortress 2. Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.