What an awful name. All right, save her color. I want that to be green like Luke Skywalker.
All right, let's see if there's any weirder ones.
This guy's all ugly. I think it's gonna be that guy. What is this like photoshopped Darth Vader?
This guy looks like somebody photoshopped Darth Vader's face on like a cookie.
Where I don't- where are you? You're not even in here. Oh, there you are.
Yeah
Oh damn, how are you still alive?
That's not how this game works. This is fucking bullshit. Why are you still alive? That's not how this game works.
What do you mean? That's not how the game works. I was putting a lightsaber through your body and you would stand-
I just feel like we're both shit faced.
Did we both- did we both share a bottle of Jameson before we decided to play this? Like seriously.
All right, this is- this is stupid.
This is stupid.
All right, can we go into like an actual server now and no more- like
No, get out of here with that stupid move.
Do it
Oh, yeah, hey mace Windu is in this game. You better be careful. I think these are bots.
Probably. Who's playing this game? Emperor Palpatine, Bidu, Lieutenant Cable, Leia, Mace Windu. Yeah, these are fucking bots.
Okay. All right. Well, you ready to get your ass kicked by bots?
We're- yeah, we're the only people who readied up just there. Yeah. What?
What?
Why did this just turn into a first-person shooter? Because you have a gun now.
You don't start with a lightsaber. Why is it an FPS?
Who am I supposed to be shooting? Is it- are you guys shooting? No, we're leaving. This is- this is a bad server.
Is this me and you just like standing at the side watching this?
Can I get this thing off my screen? This like message for the day?
I wanna-
This is stupid.
Who's this lady in like the pajamas?
Is that like Princess Leia? Well, I don't remember playing Princess Leia wearing like a nightie.
How does this guy have negative one?
This is so stupid. This isn't how the game is supposed to work.
Oh.
It just spawned us all in this courtyard.
There are legitimate game modes where you can have like guns and fight people with lightsabers.
No, screw that. I want to play like the pajama pillow fight mode like this.
I'm fairly certain. This is not what a Jedi master fight looks like.
I don't think this is what it looks like when people become Jedi's and fight each other.
I don't.
What else can you say?
This is real, real dumb.
Are you just like standing back watching? Yeah, I don't even like want to get in there.
This guy with the green saber is freaking the fuck out.
I'm wondering why this isn't a one-shot kill. I thought maybe the shift was necessary. I'm curious if I can just walk through here.
This guy's like freaking. This guy wants to kill us so bad, but he can't kill us.
This is not right. This just shouldn't be a thing. All right, can somebody please win?
Ew.
Oh, you're gross. All right, well you want to get this guy?
Watch out for this guy.
Did you just see?
I don't.
What even just happened?
I've got pushed off somehow. So did I. We both got like thrown off.
I'm surprised
and appalled.
I gotta end it on the backstab technique. That's I have to end this video on the backstab technique. Have to.
You taught it to me. It has to be done.
Come on. I have to end the video on the backstab.
This guy's trying to do it too.
I just don't.
That's not happening.
Remember all that training we did guys?
Let's just freak the fuck out and swing around in circles at each other.
Jedis, we're Jedi masters.