Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here, and MLC Stealth.
And today, Untimed Chaos Build. You can't start yet.
I wasn't, I was hiding.
Today we're going to be doing another Timed Chaos Build. We're going to be building Sonic the Hedgehog.
Because we haven't done really any gaming related things.
I mean, the only thing we came close to was the Super Mario Cheetos freaking like Pringles Man that we did with the first episode.
So, we're going to end up doing an actual gaming, iconic gaming character, Sonic the Hedgehog.
And we've got seven minutes to do it. So are you ready Stealth?
I am absolutely not ready because it's going to be bad.
So let's see how this goes. We've got seven minutes in three, two, one, go.
So we're starting his feet?
Yeah, I'll do the front leg.
Let's try to not make him like as tall as Andre the Giant.
That's probably a good idea.
We always make their legs like ten, like a hundred feet apart from each other.
And then it's like, oh man, this guy's going to be huge.
Alright, so wait, is Sonic the Hedgehog's whole shoe is blue? I mean, blue, red?
German, this color is red.
Okay, yeah, that's fine.
Here, make his feet a little bit longer, like that long.
Okay. Well, he's like running.
Yeah, this, yeah, no. Well, he has, wait, no, it's too, that's too long.
No, it's not. It's fine. He's good.
Why are his feet going that way?
Because he's going to be like running.
What?
No, just go. We don't have time.
We don't have time.
Which way is he facing?
I don't know. He's facing that way.
What? Okay. He's facing the other way.
I don't know what you did with this sideways foot over here.
He's plieing right now. That's like what he's doing.
Great.
No, because this is going to, this leg's going to...
This is ballet Sonic the Hedgehog, apparently.
Look at him, he's plieing.
All right, this has to be a little bit shorter, like this.
All right.
Dang it.
One, almost one and a half minutes have gone by.
Oh, boy.
All right.
We made two feet.
That's fine. That's fine.
Have him come up.
We never give him any legs.
He could go straight from like knee to freaking body.
I got to do the spikes.
I'm going to do the spikes.
We don't have time.
I can't even finish this.
I don't even know what this is.
Is he on his knees?
Why is this leg like two inches long?
Look at his left leg.
I have no, I have no idea how to do the spikes on his back.
I don't know.
I have no idea how to do this.
Look at how long his legs are.
Screw it, straight to the head.
The head is like the most iconic part of him, so I'm going to make sure at least that's there.
I'm like losing breath, man.
All right, here comes the spikes.
Doesn't he have white in the spikes, too?
Sure.
All right, it's head time.
Yeah, you do the head.
What color is his mouth?
He's got a giant hand.
It's a giant hand on legs.
This is not Sonic the Hedgehog.
We almost three minutes have gone by trying to make it remotely Sonic the Hedgehog.
How long do we have?
We have like four minutes.
All right, he has white on his stomach, doesn't he?
Kind of like a penguin?
Oh, crap.
You have the wrong thing.
Hold on, I'm getting wool.
All right, I'm getting the spikes to come out of his head.
All right, it's starting to look like space bug Sonic the Hedgehog.
Wait, his mouth is somewhat like that.
All right, arms.
If you had to take a guess at what this was, you would never be able to guess this.
He's supposed to be running.
I still have no idea what the heck you did with his right leg.
I thought we were going the other way.
He kind of looks like the Mass Effect alien race.
What's that Mass Effect like alien girl?
What is her name?
She's the one with like the space suit, I think.
No, I'm not. I'll never be able to guess that.
All right.
Oh, cool. Good thing we got Scorpion Sonic the Hedgehog.
The actual bug Scorpion.
Four minutes have gone by.
That's his hand.
He's broken.
He is completely broken.
He's broken in so many different pieces.
I don't even know how to fix this.
I don't know. I don't know how to fix this.
This is so broken.
This is so screwed up.
Look at how many directions his body is going in.
You know what he looks like?
He looks like you took his head.
You twisted it.
You took his body.
And you took his legs and you twisted it in completely different directions.
And that's how you left him.
Like imagine he's on it like all like he has head and his stomach and his legs are in a 360 degree plane.
And you spun him in random directions.
All right, we got we need more spikes.
I don't he doesn't have this many spikes.
Well, it's all right.
He looks like a character.
Okay, let's give him eyes.
First off, give him the eyes.
It'll look like normal with the eyes.
And then he has to have like the hair come up like this.
Normal with the eyes.
Five minutes and 25 seconds.
This is if I was this Sonic the Hedgehog.
This this guy is in like I know we've said this before, but I would be in pain.
I would be in so much pain as this character.
There is no words to describe what we have created here, but it absolutely is not Sonic the Hedgehog.
No, no, it's not.
Sounds like it's going great.
He's ET.
We have a we still have a full minute and I don't even know where to go.
There's no fixing this.
Oh, check it out.
It's ET with giant.
I don't know.
All right.
Come over here.
Let's at least fix this.
You said he doesn't have these spikes coming out all over the place.
You know what he is?
He's a maze.
He's a standing up maze.
I always make the hands the same way.
They look like four fingers and they look like pitchforks every single time.
It's going to be more like glove based.
Oh, that did it.
That fixed it.
Germica job.
It's made it ten times worse.
Like Sonic.
There you go.
All right.
Let's just make them have like a giant tongue coming out.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, we have plush toys that you get like mad at and you like squeeze it and everything just pops out.
He really looks like a squeeze.
Looks like one of the squeeze toys.
All right.
Well, we have three seconds.
Three, two, one.
And what's up?
Let's set the time.
Wrong thing.
We like even tried.
Oh, man.
There he is.
There is Sonic the Hedgehog.
All right.
So if you want to give it a different name, by all means, go ahead.
Let us know how we did.
That has to Sonic is that they're both blue.
That is literally it.
That's the only that's the only similarity.
All right, guys.
Cool.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
My goodness.
How did this happen?
Seriously, just like two inches long legs.
It went from his feet to his body.
Oh, well, see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
Thanks for watching.
Oh, my God.
This is hard.
This is insane.