Hey, what's up everybody? We are doing some Left 4 Dead here with the group from Method Gaming.
We've got of course Burger Boy here, even though he's not in Method.
But we've got Roxy, Boo, and Stealth in the call, so introduce yourselves, people.
Hey, baby.
Hello.
Stealth, what about you? You're like in this game right now.
I'm like watching American Horror Story right now.
I mean, I'm playing Left 4 Dead.
Why did I just do that?
It's like go kill zombies. I'm like in the game with you guys.
Oh, I have a question. When I pound someone with a hunter and I'm clawing away, how do I do more damage with my claws?
It just does it automatically.
Oh, I thought you could tap a button and it would do it more vigorously.
Yeah, you gotta hold L and R and you have to tap A as fast as you can.
That's how you capture the Pokemon faster.
Did you say hold L and R?
Yeah.
This is on the PC there, buddy.
Oh yeah, forgot.
Alright, let's make a little bit of a plan here.
So Burger Boy's going that way.
Don't let Burger Boy get out around the corner.
That's the main plan.
I'm gonna go like this way.
Stealth, what are you doing?
I'm like sneaking up on these guys. They don't even know.
What are you guys spawning in as right now? What are you, Roxy?
I'm a hunter.
Because they're like trashing us right now.
I am in the worst of ways. I am a boomer stuck behind a fence. This is a disaster.
Oh, if you can boom one of them, try and boom somebody.
Because I'll be able to launch on somebody right now.
I'm too close.
Oh, I missed.
Oh, come on. Boom somebody. I'm waiting for the opportunity to do it.
Did you get someone?
I'm gonna get Burger Boy.
Oh, shit.
Oh, sugar.
Well, I just got pasted.
Oh, really? So it's just me?
Good luck, Jerma.
Oh, what do you know about that one right there?
That was a sick pounce.
That was a sick pounce. That was really cool.
There's an old man. Let's get him. Get Grandpa.
What the? Get away from me.
Alright, they're gonna win.
Hold on, let's see.
I'm gonna wait for one of you guys to spawn. I'm not gonna just jump in there.
Why do I have the worst feeling that this man's ping is gonna be better than mine soon?
Let's go. Why the fuck not?
What? What?
Oh, damn it. That's right. I have to climb up this. Okay, I get it.
Inconceivable.
Oh, come on. Come on, come on, come on. Charge, charge, charge.
I'm a spitter.
There we go.
I'm lost.
Oh, damn it. Yeah, I got him. I got him. Nice.
How do I crack the hunter?
Control? I don't know. F? Maybe H?
Fucking PC is the shit out of me.
I'm so used to Xbox.
Oh my god, that was such a... Oh my god.
I'm just watching you.
Roxy, I'm just watching you just launch around.
Hardcore parkour.
Did they get like 50% of the way yet? What's the deal here?
He's healing. Just bitch slap him. He's about to go down.
Alright, this guy's going on his own.
Oh, he's healing. He's healing.
I'm going to get this guy right over here when he jumps over here.
Francis is healing a pup.
I think I'll be right back. I'm going to go watch a TV show.
Dude, you can't leave. You're still in the game.
Oh yeah, I'm playing.
This is bad.
I'm on Bill right now.
This guy knows I'm right here too.
Yeah, this guy knows what he's doing.
Come here.
There we go. There you go. Good, good, good.
Oh, look at that teamwork.
That's exactly what we wanted to do right there. Perfect.
Anybody in capped?
Zoe's about to.
She's a bitch slap away.
Oh, I got Burger Boy.
And all his teammates are nowhere to be found.
Try to get the next guy.
Sick.
Try and grab somebody.
There you go. There you go. There you go.
Come on, spawn in, Bufu. Get a spit big. Get a spit over there.
Nice.
Francis is chasing the hell out of you.
He's dying in the spit.
We're coming back here now.
We got him in cap.
I thought he was team killing him.
Rigatone is going to do something epic right here.
They don't have any more health packs. They're all out.
That's good. No.
Oh, look at that leg.
What are you guys spawning in as right now?
Boomer.
I'm a hunter.
Try and get a boom on somebody, and then in the chaos, I will try and...
These two are going to die.
If somebody can just hit them with something.
Burger Boy is dead.
Oh, here's a witch.
If you can pull them into the witch, I can grow up on them.
Oh, I don't know where the witch is.
The witch is right here in the middle.
Oh, you mad?
Ah, got him.
Come on, in cap.
Damn it.
Oh, they started the witch?
Yep. I get a boom on it and push them right into her.
Oh, she's an angry lady.
There you go.
TK, TK.
Do not let them beat us.
We can't let them win.
Just do anything.
Hey, baby.
Good, good.
What?
I think I hit one of them, guys.
Oh, if I get this guy, it's all a good game.
Oh, gimme.
Oh, I got him. It's over.
Oh, nice splits.
Oh, come on.
Damn it. No.
Oh, times 24.
I thought they were all down.
Oh, crap.
Oh, he has a medkit. Cheeky bastard.
All right, well, if they complete this, we're going to do it faster than them.
Oh, he's going to throw me on fire.
Oh, shit.
Wait, that's you just on fire running over here?
I figured I'd try and do something.
Did they get in?
This isn't the safe room, though.
Nope.
No, they got around the corner.
As soon as they jump down, there's the safe room.
All right, well, all right, boo.
You got to go for a boom.
I'm going to try and catch somebody with this.
Can you spawn inside still or is that glitched out?
I don't know.
To be honest, I don't know.
Just waiting for somebody to drop.
I got this guy.
I got a smoker.
Yeah, I got a guy in cap right now.
Wait, is he dead?
Is he hit?
Oh, no, he's on the ground still.
I got her.
There you go.
Nice.
I'm good.
There's the vomit on a couple of them.
All right, come on.
Somebody just get in there.
Yes.
Oh, that's a nasty piece of work.
That's the safe room right there.
They made it.
Just hopefully.
Oh, can we just like totally screw them right now?
Just take them all out.
I'm still dead.
I have fit.
I love Lewis's scream.
Look at burden boy.
No.
Yeah, they got it.
They beat it.
All right, well.
Get ditched, Lewis.
There's no zombies around.
They just left.
Oh, well.
How long do they beat it in?
I don't know.
I don't think it's...
I'm not sure.
All right, we're going to do better.