Yeah, let's play House of the Dead. That was Dinosaur Fossil Hunter, and it was a really interesting game. It was really cool.
But I want to play, I want to like, shoot the zombies right now. NA infrastructure, Omega LoL.
Um, Nevada, Las Vegas is like, one of the top five in the country for infrastructure, so excuse me, take that back please.
Nevada, like, honestly is like, number three in infrastructure in the whole country.
I just, just, I mean, I have to correct people when they say something incorrect.
Alright, House of the Dead. Do I play this with a mouse? It's just a mouse aiming game?
So this is a House of the Dead remake. Hopefully it's not loud. Please don't be loud. Please don't be loud. I turned it down, but please don't be loud.
Okay, here it comes. I need a game capture, new capture. Let's go, where is it? Right here.
Don't, there it is. Okay, why's my camera all laggy now?
Uh, the wind. This game does not want to be captured. What the fuck is happening? Watch out for...
What is going on? Okay, I think we're alright. What the fuck just happened?
Options. Game, is this the, did I open the right ga-? Hello? Who's there? Oh!
Um, shadow quality medium? That was very jarring. Okay, so display. Huge scale. Um, hide the HUD.
Brightness, I don't know, here. Quality, what, what frame rate is this at? Gameplay. Use vibrations.
No. No. AMO on crosshair? No. Like, maybe? No, that's ugly. Automatic reload. Quiet!
Automatic reload. Aim assist medium? I don't know what that means. What should my player color be?
Outside thickness. Crosshair speed? I don't know. Sound. Alright, I think I'm ready.
Keyboard, mouse, sensitivity. Turn it down. Alright, let's go. Let's go!
Welcome in the House of the Dead remake. There are many ways to play the game, so make sure you
review all options and create a session that suits you best. Okay, got it. Original. Okay,
difficulty normal. Classic mode. Multiplayer mode. I don't want to play fucking multiplayer.
Alright, this one. Chapter one. Tragedy. Just, I just shoot the fucking zombies. I bet you can't
name a field of research this is based off of. The morgue? Alright, let's go! Uh, can one of the
mods change the game? Jesus Christ. Nice. Alright, let's go. House of the Dead. Sensitivity's not
bad. I might need a little bit higher. How do I reload? How do you reload? R? R. Oh, fuck you.
Is the calibration wrong? Yeah, guys, I'm holding up the gun like this and this is where the gun is
aiming and here is where it is on the screen. God, these old machines are such pieces of shit.
Turn aim assist off. Okay. That always sucked the most. Every time that you went with like the
two or three of your friends and there was like a time crisis or like House of the Dead
and you were the sorry motherfucker that got the one that had like seven inches of wrong calibration.
It was such a pain because you had to cost money. You had to spend 50 cents for a life to do that.
That's not fair. Alright, turn off. Turn this off. Yeah, I don't need, I don't want that.
Alright, let's go. I think sensitivity needs to be a little bit higher.
Before my whole, before my house blows down. Okay. Like, honest to God, I'm like, I feel like,
I feel like the zombies are coming for me right now. I feel like I'm pretty good at this.
This music. Does the game feel like it's in times two speed for anybody else?
Got it. Extra health, right? Nice. I wish I had a light gun right now. Whoa, close. Got it. Frog.
Jesus. I feel like I bought extra coffee. Shit. I feel like I drank too much coffee.
Did I have way too much coffee? Everything feels like it's a hundred miles per hour. I
drank way too much coffee. No, I got to shoot that bug. Oh no, I just got the Giga Chad.
What? I freaked out. Why did I do that? Why did I do that? I sat there for so long.
And I like knew what was happening. I was in slow motion. The only part that was in slow motion
was what just happened. Now give me some health. Got it. Ah, fuck you. I'm going to die. There's
like skin all over my mouth. Skin all over my mouth. We're good. Who's this? Holy Jesus.
Carry type weak point in the chest.
I got him. I did it. That was insane.
Why would I take a picture? Why did I take a pic? Oh, these are all the people that are left alive.
Okay. All right. Not bad. This hidden treasure somewhere in this area.
Second chapter. All right. Stop panic firing and just shoot down here. I got it. Excuse me.
What was that? What are you doing? How did I die? Shut the fuck up. Continue. How many credits do
I have? 10. I got 10 coins. Hardy Kroger. Whoa. Damn it. This game's terrifying. It's too much.
The worst part about playing these games alone is there's not three other people in the room
that I can like pretend I'm playing and they can actually shoot this shit. I have to actually kill
everything. I can't miss. I have to kill them. Got it. Give me that health. I shot him in the
head like three times. It's bullshit. Oh, shut up. Whoa. I missed and I even pre-fired him.
Oh my goodness. Treasure chest. Oh, there's a person behind there. Thank you. Oh, I hate that.
In midair, you go all the way back out. That guy didn't even know what happened.
Peace. You're welcome. What's that? Whatever. Oh, I'm good. I'm good. Nice. Oh, we're good.
Don't run in front of me. Give me a treasure chest. Oh shit. How am I supposed to fall asleep to this?
Hi. Weak point. Top right. Okay. Let's go. I'm going to puke. I hate this. I hate to throw up.
Oh, wait. Auto reload. Five seconds? Every second?
Okay. Okay. I'm good. What? The title is reload?
We won't let you have it your way. I think auto reload is probably worse.
Afraid of spiders. Oh God. Truth. Yeah. Auto reload sucks. Can I turn off the guy saying
reload? You can mute reload. Okay. You can mute reload. That's funny. Okay. Now I don't care.
Nice. Go back. No, it's, I don't want to go back. The bullets bouncing around the room a million
times. Duck, man. Get out of the way. That was pretty good. That was pretty good shot. Wait,
what? I don't, what happened? I don't get it. Whatever. I threw like a handful of change in
the dryer. Okay. That's like, this is fucking crazy. I can't even play the game. All right.
See if I can do it. Am I winning? What happened? Oh, dead. Bring back reload. No. I don't like it.
Isn't there machine guns in the game? You can like click on it. It's like,
that didn't even hit me. That's such bullshit. Oh, come on. Get out of my way here. This is a
classic game. Can you play the classic version without the updated graphics? No? Hit again. I'm
gonna run out of coins. Say reload. Fine. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload.
That's better. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Reload. Are you happy? Reload. Reload.
Fuck you. Who cares? I'm just going to play the game. Who cares? Watch out.
What is that weird voice? It's hard for me to even hear what I'm even saying. I'll be honest.
The voice changer is not still on. You guys are making me waste continues and I don't
want to fucking have to use it. I'm like, I'll fucking, fucking say swear. I'm not swearing ever
again. Is this the last level? All right. Right in the head. That was easy. Wait, was I supposed to
win that fast? Holy shit. That was really loud. That was scary. All right. I only have seven coins
left. You're not using a dysfunctional NES light gun. This doesn't count. I mean, okay. I have
some thoughts about this game. I'll zip. I think it's hard to make a game like this when you use
the mouse. When, I mean, the difficulty in this game comes from being able to actually aim the
light gun. Zit? What? What are you saying? Zit? Where? Where? What are you talking about? Where?
Where? Where do you see a zit? What are you talking about? Photo mode. God damn it. Oh shit.
Shit. My arm hurts. My fucking arm hurts. My fucking hand hurts. All right. I'm good.
I don't want to fight the guy that flies, right? Do I have to? Of course I do.
Oh my god. I can shoot with the space bar. Everything has changed.
Everything's changed. I can shoot with space bar. Ow.
Find reload to your mouse? No, man. That's not happening. Ow. I'm gonna run out of continues.
Zit?
I don't know. I think I could take it.
What did he drop? What happened? What happened?
Uh-oh. Unknown. Oh shit. It's Mewtwo. You gotta shoot him in the muscle tissue.
This game's giving me a headache. I actually have a headache again.
This game is so fucking loud and like the sound effects. It sounds like an animal got into a
fucking restaurant kitchen and started running around and smashing stuff. Somebody get that.
Somebody get that fox. Somebody get him. Somebody grab that fox.
Oh my god. I can't lose here. I got four continues. I can't fuck this up.
Oh shit. I'm gonna lose. Fuck. No, don't lose. I'm getting weak. I'm getting weak.
Guys, I'm getting weak. One of the chefs. One of the chefs comes out of the restaurant.
Comes out of like the door of the kitchen and the fox is on his face and he's like running around
like bumping into tables and shit. Is this as loud as it is for me as it is for you?
Okay. No, don't fuck. I have two continues.
Oh, I'm getting weak. Oh, I'm slowing down. Actually, I'm slowing down.
Okay, I win. Well, no, it's not gonna be phase two, right?
Everything is over. Nothing more must go on. Goodbye. Farewell.
I did it. Accept. How do I accept? Accept. Tab is accept. I don't care. That was crazy.
That was just crazy. I feel like that was weird. A new chapter came out? New chapter?
Okay, wait. New campaign. Oh, I can do horde mode. Let me try this and then maybe I shouldn't.
Hey, my head's killing me right now. Let's go into chapter four. Horde mode. Take a break.
I'm probably gonna end the stream. Honestly, I was laughing at like...
All right. What does horde mode mean? I just want to know what it means.
Oh, no way. It was kind of... Dude, how the fuck are you supposed to do this?
I used bit rate? What do you mean? All right. Yeah, I'm done. I'm done. This is like making it worse.
This is making it worse. This game's fun. It's all right. It's cool. They remade it. I mean,
I would like a light gun in my hand, but you know, whatever. I just want to see what makes
this horde mode. I'm done. I'm not playing against this guy. I'm not playing against that guy.
That was kind of fun. That was House of the Dead remake. Okay, so here's the plan. I didn't stream
yesterday because I had a bad migraine and I was like, I'm gonna be careful today because I don't
want to make it worse so I don't like fuck up the rest of the week's streams. So I'm just gonna stop.
I'm drinking water. I'm all right. That was kind of fucking wild. Short one today,
but I will be back. We will do a full one on... Where's today? We'll be back on Tuesday,
probably Tuesday and Wednesday. I have a lot of games to play. We got Later Alligator,
Bloodwash, power game shit. We got Murder House. Oh my God. Hold on. Listen to this shit. Okay.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday. We will do Later Alligator because that's what pre-stream chat
voted on. Sorry, I'm only here for like three and a half hours. I kind of planned on only
streaming for like three or four hours today just because of how I felt yesterday. I had a good time.
That was a lot of fun. A dinosaur game was fun. That was cool. I thought it was like an interesting
game. The House of the Dead remake. It was all right. I mean, I think it was a little too intense
probably. It was, I think, fun. If you had a like on it, I think it would be way better.
This guy hates streaming. I don't hate streaming. Zit, by the way. I developed a zit from that game.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday. Thanks for watching. Quick one. I'll be back on Tuesday, Wednesday,
maybe like Tuesday, Friday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Saturday. We'll see. Whatever. My schedule is
all over the place, so we'll see. Thank you. Wait, I didn't want to do that immediately. I
want to do this. There we go. Yeah, we'll rate somebody. Let's see who's live right now.
Who is currently live? Is Connor live? Yeah, we'll rate Connor. That sounds like a plan. Jesus.
You can hear that, right? Mouth sounds. Because my noise gate is off. So you guys get to hear like
yeah, this is why I have a noise gate. This is why all streamers have a noise gate.
There, I fixed it. Everybody has a noise gate so you don't hear the weird mouth sounds.
Yeah, like, god damn it. I fucking hate that. You just saw me naked. Okay, let's rate Connor.
What is Connor doing? What are you up to? Just chatting. Oh, I think Connor's in the process of
rating, doing a tier list of all the consoles, all the old consoles. That should be pretty
interesting stuff. Pretty cool. I look forward to his absolutely incorrect opinions on everything.
All right, I'll see you guys on Tuesday. Thanks for watching. Bye. Take care of yourselves.
Call your mother. Mother's Day, especially. Take care of yourselves. Good night and goodbye.