Is me tweeting 3DO trash heap rude to the 3DO? Is that uncalled for? Is that mean to the 3DO?
Well, maybe a little. Yeah.
Because I'm like, oh, like 3DO trash heap. Imagine like, okay, imagine 20 years from now
on whatever fucking hologram internet entertainment platform you guys are using.
Imagine like going back and watching old creators was something people did.
Oh, let's go watch this old creator. He's old.
German 985. Oh, German 985 trash video night. Like I'm
I made that stuff. Oh
Hey, I'm gonna I'm gonna be a little bit easier on the 3DO. I feel like that's uncalled for
already old
kind of a trash video night
What are we starting with? Oh the German 985 channel. Oh my god. There's there's like 700 videos here
Let's play the 3DO. Oh my god. There's like 700 terrible games here
It's the same shit
Are you gonna play spider-man? I didn't even know the new consoles came up. I had no fucking idea italics had to tell me
He's like, oh, it's gonna be like a busy weekend for me. I'm like, oh busy weekend. What are you talking about?
Say, what do you mean? I'm like, why why you have what do you mean a busy weekend?
It's like ps5 comes came up. It's like a ps5
Oh my god. Oh, oh fuck. I didn't get one
So not only do I don't have a 30 to 80. I don't have a ps5. I don't have an xbox series s
I don't oh i'm going into john oliver here
I don't have a ps5. I don't have an xbox and it reminds me of an iguana with a little hat
Where's the ass emote? I don't think you can get that
Are these comments or of these live comments? Yeah, dude
Did I get my height calculated?
No, I need to
Do you understand?
That conversation how that goes
first of all
I don't tell my doctor
That i'm like a fucking streamer
Oh, yeah, mr. Albertson looking at your chart here. Oh, by the way, i'm a twitch streamer
Okay, don't care. I don't fucking care about that at all. Uh, it says here that you have some stomach problems
Why would I do that? No, I don't want to be like hey, can you take like a video from like my audience?
That's automatic your douchebag like that's automatic shit head
Hey doc, I know we got some hey ready get me in frame. Oh shit. I knocked something off
That's okay. Nothing in there
Get me in frame doc
Hey, what's going everybody? It's me germa. Hey, why don't you measure me doc?
You don't want to be in the fucking video, but get over here. I don't care
No, I don't want to do that
I I would not like to be on camera. It's not it's cool. It's cool bro. Come on over here. Hey, this is my doctor
I put my hand up and I like make like a mouth with my hand. Hey, I went to school for medicine. Ha ha ha and
He throws me the fuck out
I don't want to do that shit
I have to find somebody that will measure me
That is it that I don't know. Maybe i'll just i'm just gonna do it on the fucking wall
Oh, I am a doctor. Look at me. I am so smart
Now go ahead stand over there doc and again put put the tape measure up
Yeah, yeah right there right there
Hire someone on task rabbit. What the fuck is task rabbit? What about your cbd doctor? It's not a there's no cbd doctor
a cbd doctor
Cbd doctor, yeah, they can any doctor can prescribe
medical marijuana license
They feel like it would help you
Or you know, maybe a doctor wants to just you know
in the office
With you. Hey, man, I got this sweet sweet Mary Jane. You want to give it a try?
Oh, absolutely. I love this doctor
Hey
Hey, what'd you what you having back problems or something?
Yeah, man, my back's killing me. All right
Go get you an x-ray
There was a drug addict
No, is this just you when you went to the doctor?
No, I don't go to the no. I I when I do marijuana products
I sit in my chair or I lie on the couch
I'm just staring into the fucking wilderness
Or I play hearthstone battlegrounds
Which i've gotten pretty good at by the way
All right, I gotta I gotta ask everybody
So I have i'm gonna i'm gonna say a number out loud and I want to know if it's any good. Okay
This is my battleground hearthstone ranking number
Oh shit. No, I don't want to tell you this
Because specifically you guys will specifically make your rank this number and queue every day to try and find me
No, never mind
It's high
What's his rank? Okay
I'm gonna make i'm gonna lose and win the amount of games it takes to be at that exact number
And I know he plays every night pst before bed. I'm gonna find this motherfucker and i'm gonna troll him
Uh, this is the die dallas encounter as you can see in the top left
This is the first thing i'm gonna play this 3do night. Welcome everybody
Uh, this is like a five cd
adventure game
should uh
Should be interesting
This is one of the ones we left on the table
Last time we played 3do
Pause the stream. I have to make tortellini. We don't have like 12 minutes for you to do that
If you said microwave tortellini, sure
That's like a minute
Make tortellini. That's too long
pause pause pause
No, I don't want to rush them because if you rush tortellini, you're gonna screw it all up
There's al dente and then there's no
Six minutes five minutes. He's gonna rush it and it's gonna be chewy and he's gonna be pissed at us
You can't rush pasta and you can't
Have for too long
Seven to eight minutes. Take it out. I don't even care. Just take it out. It doesn't look like take it out
Eight minutes take it up seven minutes. Take it out. You heard me. I don't know. This feels kind of hard
Shut up and take it out. Take it out now
Okay, let's do it. This looks terrible
It's not ready. It's not done dude. Shut up and just wait
I strained it. Okay, it's it doesn't it's it looks a little springy
Try it
Oh
Oh, that's nice
I fucking listen to me more often. Okay, seven minutes. What's wrong with you today?
Okay
I am like intubation, but I am like kind of weird today. I agree
What is wrong with me today?
Are you stoned?
No, stop
I hate how you guys can tell by the way. Well, I mean obviously if I can't read an analog clock
That's a really good way
I know but no i'm not all right. Are you ready to play? Let's go to die dallas and encounter
I'm drinking a coffee right now
Relax
Here we go
in three
two
One go
Wait for the pasta. No, i'm not waiting for pasta. Okay, he'll show up eventually
He's gonna rush into the room with this hot bowl of pasta. He's gonna burn himself
That's not my fault. By the way, I didn't tell you to do that
the years 2135 ad
planet beta triangularly
six
final days of the first
interstellar war
Oh, it's kind of like star wars
Casey anything on the scanners?
Are they setting up a couch?
They're riding a ride at disney
Get him
Why do they look like burger king employees?
He's got a burger king hat on
Can we get out omega l got him?
McDonald's versus burger king interstellar war
He got hit pretty bad but the med techs are trying to fix you up with life support and artificial senses
You just hang in there case. Okay, and when conglomerates get that big and mcdonald's owns planets
It wouldn't be two months later
Audio link is activated cutting in visual in three two one
Wait, am I the ship?
Casey it's airy. I'm the ship your mind has been placed in a cerebral support mechanism device
That when she's trying to say you're a brain in a box case asmr
You are a air. I can't even fucking say it. You know what i'm saying. Look at yourself
Now you may not look the same on the outside, but I know it's you on the inside
And we need to know if you can respond use the virtual interface in front of the transmitter. Yes
Don't be now, please don't be shoot me with a gun. You have a gun
Shoot me with a gun, please
Wait what interface help use the yes no buttons to communicate perform analysis on certain objects
Use to send stored analysis data use to acquire loose objects activates a general purpose flood light
Activates your multi-light transmitter initiates the probe system perform system diagnostics launches your onboard probe boost casey's onboard thruster. Oh shit. Okay
activate virtual interfaces are
Select and navigate is that activate navigation control? I can I can fly around. Oh this
This just got way more interesting. Okay, go and help. Oh, here we go. I can say yes and no
All right. Should I say no?
What did I just do?
You didn't give me no, don't shut me off
Shut it down
Did I just get the one of the endings of the game by accidentally not doing anything? Shut them down?
How long did it take to build that thing?
And we need to know if you can respond if you can use the virtual interface in front of you transmit a no
Yes, you probably haven't heard but uh the war is over we flame their butts at exeter three
Baccar lost a third of their fleet
They went running with their tails between their legs straight to the taladarans practically begged them to negotiate a peace treaty
We won
You know, of course that put us out of a job, but you know, hey war is hell, right?
So right now you're aboard the artemis finest salvage vessel in the sector
Zach and I cobbled her together from a couple of surplus alliance transports
Oh, not to mention the engines that we sort of borrow stall stall
May not look like much stolen engine detected self-destruct
We thought we'd help salvage some of the vicar ships. We helped disable. It's the very least we could do
We see it. There's a lot of uh, very tasty salvage just floating around out there
All right. Now let's get really really personal
We liberated you from the lab
Zach wired your interface. Are you two together?
Are you dating?
I'll be back casey. Are you two dating? What do you say guys? Let's do some hunting. Oh, I can't do anything
It's reverse c man. Yeah, i'm the one that responds the draillac system
50 hours later
So we're why can't you just say like
Two days three days
50 hours
What's the point of this? What are we what are we supposed to be doing around the sector for two days now?
Maybe we finally got something activating view screens
Okay, we've we got something we have to go out there and clear this
Hey case, what do you say you want to take your uh new equipment for a test?
Yeah, let's go. Why don't you go ahead and activate your remote control probe casey
See if you can get us a better look at this derelict
Probe where's the probe? All right
Which was the probe data?
Is this like oxygen? All right. Did I just turn it into hydrogen? Okay, start up all subsystems now
Oh shit start up subs. Wait, wait, I need the help launches your onboard probe
Okay, here we go. The probe is down here
No probe data and analyze. Yes on
Okay, grapple arm system
um launch
Probe, what am I doing? All analysis system. What the fuck am I supposed to do? Did I do it?
What's happening? You didn't give me very good instructions
Analysis, what's the analysis one? All right analysis. All right, put the probe on run your diagnostics run your diagnostics
Launches you perform system diagnostics on the probe. Oh, it's this one. All right
Diagnostics thing what we got. All right launch probe
Diagnosing what does it what it would look like? Okay at this point you could have done it yourself
Why are you trying to get the toaster to do these very complicated tasks? Okay, deploy the probe casey deploy the probe
Opening probe bay doors
Now it's me
Is that the dallas?
I miss these old cg cutscenes. They look so strange and almost terrifying in a way
Casey I gotta ask you
What does it feel like having your eyes and ears floating around in a little ball while the rest of you is back here with us?
It's fucking horrible. It feels like shit. It's not even funny to joke about
Your guidance system is pretty much automatic so you can concentrate on the job. Most other functions are up to you
Yes, oh wait what close call there buddy
Collision avoidance seems to be working grab. What do I do? All right, let's try your computer link. See how it works
Why don't you run?
Uh an id check on this pile of junk see if you can get the name of the ship
Id check what the cargo might have been am I pulling them over id check?
Which one is that?
It's a
I can't read that. It's so blurry
What is it? You're pulling them over
You know how fast you were going?
14 light years per day this is a 12 light year per day zone using your laser torch upper right hand switch
Should pump enough juice into the system pop that door wide open. Be careful casey
Vakar have been known to booby trap their hulks. Come on. Give me that one
Wait, wait, wait
I missed all of that. It said wait. Can you
They booby trap the hulls
Casey I warned you about traps. You just blew our only pro
Now we have to go back and start all over again. Thank you
It looks so sad
He's dead
Thank god. You could just start from right here though
Okay, so this is a booby trap. All right analyze
Collect use the floodlight
Put the thrusters up launch the probe
What?
Casey I warned you about traps. You just blew our only probe. I'm like a dog that gets the paper towel roll
Put that down
No, i'm not gonna put it down. Give me that and then you get it back and then somehow he gets it again
Hey
No bad computer
It's the dotted line
It's not the dotted line
I warned you about traps back and start all over again. Thank you
Okay, do I have a device I can use
Well the plug in the hole
I mean, what about over here?
They try I can't like do anything
I can't analyze any data. I can't attach I can't grab I can't fling. I can't scream
The bullet hole
It's down here, right?
I can't activate it. I can't activate this either
Is there anything else I can grab?
I can touch this
Casey I warned you about traps. You just blew our own back and start all over again. Thank you
Does anybody understand yet?
I warned you but yeah, it's booby trap. So should I just leave can I not open it?
I can touch this I can touch this and I can touch this
Nothing else is uh, it can be grabbed
The dotted line i'd already grabbed that
Wait, what about like wait?
Fuck casey. I warned you about traps. You just blew our only probe now. We have to go back and start all over again
Thank you. What my uv light I tried to activate it
She warned you about traps. Yeah. Well not good enough. You can't just say oh, hey
Uh, this is this is trapped. Why don't you tell me what device to use? Where should I go?
By the way
A shitty alchemist blames their tools, right? Whatever the I am their creation
So they are controlling me in a way. So therefore like fuck you
A shitty blacksmith blames their tools
All right uv light
No, I can't talk. There's no data to analyze
Wait, let me see. What was analysis on it? Wait, wait, hold on analysis
No
Harp into you idiot blacksmith does it too black. Come on name a guy that uses tools
You could say a dentist does the same way a craftsman. There it is. All right
Builder. Yeah, right. Right. Right. What do I touch?
I don't i'm not gonna get soft locked here in this if I haven't even been in the game for 10 minutes
I can't use the grab hand
Wait, what's that?
Activate navigation control
No, just get a guide
This actress is from wayne's world. Yes. Yes. She was very very famous back in like the 90s
Anybody have anyone have any idea what's going on here read the manual you dipshit the fucking manual
what
There's no manual. There's just a
Please send products and other correspondence to this it's a panasonic thing in here
It's like a that's smart to register. This is more than a product registration card
It's your key to a new and exciting panasonic product. I don't have a manual
Hold on. Wait this one here
Okay
dips log
encounter
Welcome to the encounter step one is virtual control
Step two is to probe and then diagnostics
Step three analysis of the ship blow the hatch
You'll need to use your laser torch to open the cargo door when your laser arms itself aimed on the upper left door controls
Why is this just a guide?
This is just a guide how to do every fucking puzzle in the game
Who is the laser torch?
I don't have a laser torch. What the hell is that talking about?
Hold on. Okay died
died dallas
encounter walkthrough
Put the blue thing near the door
Nice job fucking kidding me
Really?
Dark in there better kick in the floodlight. I can do that
Oh scary actually did kind of scare me. I always thought you found aliens quite
attractive
Hey, hey, hey drunk that night, you know that and besides it
Swore to me that it was female
Casey stop there really happy for you. Look around this place
Let's get a good look around this place. All right
What are we looking for?
aliens floodlight activate
What have I looked all the way down and there was just two shoes and legs
I don't see anything
analyze
Analyze the current environment launch the probe
All right analyzing the ship fucking blows
Yeah, this actually sucks. It's just a giant hallway. Where's the
Kitchen
There's a sleeping quarters. You just float around in here. Where do you go to the bathroom?
This is a tube and you know something. Wait, what's that tv shows and movies?
Get this fucking wrong every time don't they?
Anytime there's an alien spacecraft or an unknown encounter, right?
It's always like this
It's never like a kitchen. They never show like this like the cook
There's never a kitchen. There's never a living room. It's always just weird and oh abnormal
There's no bedrooms
Scary ship is just scary ship
There's no actual rooms good
He's so high
All right analyzing at least we got a nice souvenir. It's gonna be some kind of magical power
As well come on in case he's just not our day
Wait, I just throw it down the hallway
Didn't she just say that that belongs with the dead?
I'm just gonna toss it down the hall
It's kind of disrespectful
This whole sector's why not like put it with this body
I agree a Magellan cluster
Why just frisbee it down the hall lv 426. Oh, not there what I was thinking about
What time we surprised the hell out of that wing of the car cruiser just leaving the wheel?
Yeah, my star system, right? Yeah, and I never saw so many ejection pods in my I feel like such a third wheel right now
Not only my third wheel in this current friend group
They turned me into a fucking like task robot
That's extra third wheel
What is it food? Yes
Uh 10 community 10 community subs came in from the foolie. Thank you foolie for the 10
community subs
Yeah, welcome on the new stuff
Thanks the stuff
Talked me into something else. Hey, uh case what do you say my czar? Yes
You talk me into something else, I mean we got this robot
Yeah, we're going this way self-trained make him sing I don't sing so
All right tutorial over
We're going story branching here. We could have said no
What?
Yeah, instead of like zirking off. You probably should have been watching the out your windshield
Oh no, uh analyze the situation
Oh god, damn it. Give me a fucking break. What?
No, why why why are you in this? I don't want you in here. I don't want you to do this
I don't want to do this game
I don't want to do this one
Why is this here? It better not be timed
Okay, what do I what? Okay power
power grid
All right
They've all just turned wwe into the turnbuckle move
Hurry save the ship. Is this what it wants?
power
Okay, power one power two
Power three
Did I do it connect multiple systems failure? Where's the other one?
Is this one this one up here I can't is that one up there
Is that is that is it? I do it. Is that it? I think that's it
all four sides
Well, shit. Okay. Hold on
Damn it. All right. So this has to go
Fucking can't believe this shit is in here right now
No, that was right. But then how do I get this one?
I fucking hate these things. I hate these
Why of all the things does it have to be a light puzzle?
What happened?
I why
I hate these things
If you told me that I was gonna have to do light puzzles like turn the pipe shit again
I would have shit my pants on camera instead. It's not too late to do that. No, it is too late. No
No, no, no, no, no, no
I fucking hate this shit
No
God damn it. It has to connect to this one, but I can't get that one to do what I want it to do
Work backwards work backwards hurry before the time runs out up this way down. Oh my fucking god
I hate this more than anything calm down and concentrate. I'm gonna but I
Calm down or concentrate or drop kick 3do through my hallway. Fuck which one of those bolts sound pretty good to me right now
That's not it. Okay, uh analyze say no
No
No, no
no
I can't wait for one to turn to the camera and there's one small scratch on the forehead with a tiny bit of blood
I'm gonna blame me
They were asleep they didn't even crash and get hurt
We're dead in the news bad news first, what are you crazy bad has taken us with it there's no way to get clear without our thrusters
We can do it. Do we still have short-range communications? That's me
Send a distress call
To who what you think this thing is a ship zack. I don't know but maybe whoever or whatever's on board can help us
Yeah, they're not too torqued at you for bashing. See they don't know but
I mean this argument's going up to the amazon cloud and they don't even know
Id check seems to be of some type of composite material surprise unknown any response to a distress call
So either we figure out how to alter our course we're toast
I hope that we eat first
Casey there activate your probe. Let's see what we're dealing with out there. Okay
Oh, that's not the probe. All right probe on
Get ready to launch probe
launching probe
Keep voice
I will but when I need it propulsion systems activated
Analysis system activated launch probe probe ready
analyzing data
sending probe now in three two one
zero
I just said that stop trying to overstep me
Always needing to one-up me. There's no way to continue further our relationship
Careful out there a better robot voice. Is it not good? I can't I don't know what it is. I can't tell
It was stuck in it. There's a big black hole here
Do a fart with the robot filter. All right, this better be worth like five million from that one guy
I don't even know what it sounds like
This looks like a cake. Is this even a ship?
This is a fucking calzone
What is this?
Harry never seen anything like this. Yeah
Either of I some kind of composite
Alloy or secreted material, I mean did they they build this stuff or grow it
Right. This is a complete unknown
Wait, did you say galaxy is full of unknowns my young son
Is that what you said?
Yeah, and her sunk a shaft right into the main colony practically wiped out the whole race before the exolinguist established communications
Yeah, well, let's be careful because you're no exolinguist. Hey, I happen to speak 27 languages
Yeah, three phrases more beer. Where's the head and if you want to come by
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah
Reorder I have placed a pack of beer on your episode. How are you here? No, no, dude
What the fuck alexa hold your position casey zack and I are joining you what what we are
You got a better idea
I guess we don't have much of a choice. All right, let's suit up. I'm going in
Wait, they're going in
They've been computer generated those aren't even real faces anymore
That's not video footage. That's actually 3d in the game spy kids
It's like it's 3d
Be careful if you if you trust too much you'll just incinerate the person behind you
Uh, that's just uh, where's the gravity field? Where is this gravity field?
They're gonna go soaring into space
Oh, but don't forget me
That's definitely a ship take off can I shine my light in there?
Okay
I will I will do the one or two buttons. I've been able to press this entire game. What do you say?
This looks actually pretty scary in here. It's fluid on the wall. What is that?
See that
What's that? It's like a tail
the ship
It's gonna be face huggers. I feel so
Like not needed
Why am I just the peter dinklage ghost that they've re-recorded all his lines. What's his name?
I just come up with tutorial messages every like five hours
Actual side character. I can't even say yes and no
This is a pretty good dvd menu game
It's a dvd menu
It's a dvd. This is just the special features on prometheus. All right, what does it want me to do grab it analyze?
That is basically the 3d. Oh, yeah
Something in there is an egg in there the egg in there. There's an egg. Please insert disc two
Oh shit, this is disc four right here
All right. Hold on. It's not gonna break, right?
DVD game
All right disc two in
What did I just press?
I did like a code blue
What is that?
Okay
So now what? I'll just say now insert disc one just needed to load the video into cache. I did it
There's a brain in here. Oh wait
Oh, that's not even me put your face in there
I wonder what this is
Take the helmet off and sticks her head in it. Take it off
Wait, they're actually gonna take these up. It does not seem like a very firm seal
The disc tray on the fucking 3do is more firm seal than that
Retired they didn't feel like animating that anymore too much 3d work
Why is she still 3d
She's still oh, no, no, no. Okay now they're not anymore
I don't think it knows what a gun is
Why would you touch this what are you doing?
This doesn't know what a gun is what you this is not the triceratops from jurassic park
That's the reason for the hole in the other room
what
Ship's been invaded by crin cringe. Oh what you just said was so cringe kind of like piranhas
It could be thousands of them in here
Thousands of piranhas great
Something in the head built-in flashlight. No, it's gonna explode
Maybe it's one of the ways they communicate it's gonna explode
It's dead
See that was a last ditch communication like tell my wife. I love her
Stuff is harder than a drill sergeant's head crin can do this
We have no idea
That could have been the password that could have been like the password to the laptop that has all the btc on it from like
fucking 2004
We'll never know
I don't think this thing's dead
No, it's not it's good. It's wagging its tail
We just get duped
Well wick always said the most terrifying thing he ever saw was a full-scale crin attack
Old man hard wick actually talked to you
Actually, we got along quite well
This just really is what it's like to be a side character
Like a party member that gives advice sometimes that doesn't do any of the game playing
You just kind of walk around and look at walls and stuff
Yeah, i'd say so let's try opening this thing careful
Yeah, I have my list of tutorial messages I can show up
uh
Did you know that if you press tab you can get to the map?
Wait a minute that casey can make it through me me me
Go ahead casey see if you can make it through
Come on go squeeze in there. I found the heart
There's gonna be some kind of jewel in here. We're gonna take the jewel in indiana jones style. The whole thing's gonna collapse
Pods, this is where they burrow their larva
Alexa I was just gonna yell like alexa order this but I
It was a joke like as if it's here, but it's not here and I can say that out loud
But I don't want to say that out loud because some of you might actually have it
And you might i'm up on your tv speakers. I can't do that either
Alexa order of jewel pods
What's that jewel pods there's a crab in there what casey
Casey what happened right there? Yeah, did you see anything that looked like navigational controls?
Oh, uh
Yeah, um, um, no
Guess we better try another one of these doors
Yeah
Hey casey, let's try this one
slow robot
Come on. Give me a break. They built me with parts that they had lying around
How many like random graphics cards do you still have in your closet? I thought casey was the only one that could open these
Guys I held on to a gtx 270 for like six fucking years
Sorry, I don't have the latest hardware built into this guy
Why I don't know because just in case I needed it for something. I don't have it anymore. It's gone now
I hold on to a lot of computer hardware like you're supposed to hold on to your tax returns
seven years
And then and I get rid of it. Oh my god. Why are you drinking like the random acid?
what
What the fuck?
You always didn't know how to make me laugh
Why don't you walk up to a random?
What the hell are you looking at cyclops?
What is happening really what is happening in this game
You don't know what's so damn funny, right? That was an honest mistake. Oh, trust me for my angle. It was hilarious
Can can we just go now?
This is turning into an snl skin first now that you're all refreshed
Hey
Well, all of a sudden i'm r2 d2
So let me okay. I gotta break this down. Let me get this straight guy walks into room in an alien spacecraft
And it's all this weird shit around it
Immediately drinks out of the first liquid
That you find the first thing that's holding liquid you just start drinking it
Is this a dnd campaign?
with new players
There's no sign of any weapons whatsoever
I didn't even put up a fight. Maybe they didn't have any weapons
They built a spaceship you enter a room with a strange fountain
And inside I drink out of the fountain. I'm saying maybe it shows not
Okay, roll I guess um
But this one is different roll for hydration
Oh, here we go. This is the real this is the room now. Oh, we really did it now people are porting into here
Get the weapons ready
What do I have? I have robot fork penis. I'm ready
Looks like some kind of central hub
Seems heavily reinforced you think this would uh, keep those crayon out
I don't know maybe
But we're not staying here to find out
Gotta steer this thing away from the star. Remember?
Yeah
These symbols over the doors might tell us what's on the other side
Oh, they're not porting in what are they doing?
Why am I so interested in this game still I kind of am don't you want to know what's happening?
I kind of want to know the story
I'm I want to know
I'm getting a little invested. Yeah, me too
So this must be the died alice
Should I say something? Hey casey, we can't come up with anything here. All these doors are sealed
We need your help to open them. Let's start with the one to the left of the door. We came in
That one
Oh no, it's gonna be a puzzle
Okay
w o i
bulk
bolt
Analyze the door. Okay. It looks like there is a dial in there. It's gonna be a puzzle something maybe
alien pattern found
chroma symbols
Take a look at this
possible language
Take a look at that data. Okay. Can I open it? What else can we do?
Enhance it the playstation language
Yeah, it is
Okay, I have the data so now I go back
I've got hey, yes, I found something
Okay, so this is what's this look like?
So now how can I move this around?
Analyze it again
Press the button. I can't press anything
Press no, I have this
This is a color scheme and an alien language, but can I go back and say hey, I found something
Use your fork
Use the rainbow
Oh shit
Okay
uh beige orange
pink
beige
orange
Oh my goodness orange
Oh, okay. Um
What is it doing? I have to make what do I have to make?
One of those symbols, but I don't know what symbol is supposed to make just complete the whole thing
Uh
Like that
Come on
Hold on
Okay, hold on
All right, thank you not this shit i'm missing the top right
Right
Fuck up right use top right I can
Robot stop robot stop. What what are you talking about? I'm supposed to just make the whole um thing, right?
This is weird
That's not it
Fuck it's it's so close fill the lines. Yeah, it's it's close. It's close
It's so close, but not really. All right. Wait, wait, wait
That's that one
Then we gotta go
Hold on
Okay, then which one of these can go to the bottom right, um
Wait, hold on now that stays there I need one to go across
That and then I need this one to go this way and then I need
Shit this sucks. This is I just said sucks and I didn't even mean to
I had it I did but I almost
Wait, hold on
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Shit, it's this one little section down here that I can't do that and then
That and then
I
Know this one is definitely down here, right it has to be I had it
Did I though? I don't think I did
wait
Uh
No
No, uh
Yeah, I have to do it again, I don't want to do it again what okay, um
Um, oh lord, this is gonna be hell this is gonna be horrible
I need one that goes this way. Okay. All right. Hey, hey, hey, hold on
All right, wait, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey done it's done. It's done. I need
Shit shit shit shit
Shit
One iq don't even what do you mean one iq this shit is fucking weird
Don't one iq me
Oh you motherfucker, it's so close
No, no this one line
I need one in the middle
I don't know. I'm just cheating so i'm cheating. I don't care. This is stupid
I'm not doing this like saturday morning sunday morning paper
Bullshit puzzle. It's stupid
That doesn't tell you how to beat it. No, it just tells you that it exists
It's simple
It's not simple. It's stupid. It's I hate it
Wait, maybe it is simple. Hold on
Oh
Just press them all fast
Hold on. I think I got it. I think I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
Just relax relax
This walkthrough doesn't work
Come on the walkthrough king. He's gonna get me
Purple door. What this isn't even
What the fuck? None of these these are all doesn't make any sense
They're all this one's not even a paragraph long. I beat this puzzle when I was four
You didn't even own a 3do. None of you did this radio like sold 400 copies. You're not one of them. It's randomized
No, it's not
Wait, oh, here we go. There's a play. There's a hold on this walkthrough. I don't know
I hate it
Where's the just it's just not even a puzzle
All right, the didalus encounter walkthrough part two
dude all these
Where is this part of the fucking game? Oh, it's on part four. Okay match each one
I know I know it's probably easy but like I i'd rather fucking eat the disc than do this
All right. Got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Here we go
Wait, what this is?
No, I just skipped to the next video. Why is
YouTube fuck youtube. Why is next video?
Two pixels away from the play button fucking move that shit your website sucks
This walkthrough doesn't even have this part because it's on easy this
Walkthrough i'm watching is on easy. So it only has the first part
The only reason why we have part two is because the game's on medium
Hey
God damn it. Not even the walkthrough could help me because the walkthrough is on easy
You had it move the bottom left one
No, no, no, no, no, what do you know what happened top left the top left one
Oh
I don't want to do it again
That one wasn't even hard
No, but yeah, fuck you too. Fuck your dumb sight with oh, let's put the play button right next to the skip button
That's a good idea. Why not?
You know, I just noticed something you're giving an awful lot of orders for civilian
I do outrank you
You did outrank me and the only reason you did was because you were a lot better at kissing ass than I was
Everything I got I earned the hard way just because you kept getting busted for insubordination. Oh, hey, hey
I know what you're talking about. Okay, you know, that wasn't my fault
Oh the hell it wasn't you went out of your way to disobey the orders. You never could accept ranking authority
Let me explain something to you. Okay?
If I take an order from you, it's because I choose to got it
Okay
Where the hell are you going pissed at you too?
I really am r2
Another door puzzle. I don't want to do another door puzzle
Let's try this way I do play as the camera
Oh, this this room looks interesting. It's it's it's read in this goop
Do an r2d2 scream? I did that like two days ago
What was that?
I don't know
It's coming from over there loss fight
Oh shit here comes a print
They're on germany at eight five stream, there are thousands of using these air ducts to get around the ship
It's great, that's just terrific
It's a little too close for comfort for me. I agree. Let's get out of here right in front of you
I really hope there's a fight, please give us a fight
All right, we're fine
Don't forget they're hurtling they're going towards the sun. Oh, that's true. Yeah
Not enough for a budget fight
Hey, are you getting a weird feeling like the hair on the back of your neck wants to stand on it?
Yeah
Kind of like we just walked into an intense electromagnetic feel
Harry wait a minute. This looks familiar. Look
generator power comments
Emergency cooling this is this has got to be an engine
You just may be right this time
You know, you don't have to act so surprised I am
Okay, let's split up and look around Nintendo. Okay, so you take the left corridor
That's what I thought she said too, but I figured I was gonna get minus two if I said that
All right, what are we looking for? Minus two for thinking
Come on
This is an early movie game
Yeah
This is what all your favorite movie games
Are sort of based on
actor in the golden age of the 3do
early pc game
They made these all the time because graphics weren't that good the real life looked great
That's why there was a shitload of fmv games
Oh
What did she get this
What what happened to him? He didn't even touch him
And why is she about to like crack his back?
Did he pass out from fear?
Oh, he cringed so hard at that last joke, but he just he couldn't go on he passed out
One of those little flying things made an r2 d2 noise and he cringed to fucking death
Just wrap why why can't I help don't forget about me?
Oh, that's yes it is
Um, you're like you're like 25 in this video. I believe you're like less than 30 in this
38 really
Alive but not you case I was not talking
You never changed
Is this like the the monologue where she describes to be the villain of the story?
Always there for us
Straight and steady and now you've changed too
I'm gonna have to put you down
Do you still feel?
Yes
I do
It would be nice to hear your voice again
I think the med techs were working on a speech interpolation system when we pulled you from the lab. I'm sorry
We weren't such a hurry pull me from the lab
I don't know who i'm supposed to be
You know when we get out of this thing, i'm gonna find you somebody that can
Somebody that can build your voice
That's a promise
You're okay was I wait was I a robot the whole time?
I was another passenger on the ship
Oh, yeah, I was on I was another crew member, right?
Long elevator
Does that mean fourth floor ladies lingerie
Mall joke
Casey why don't you see if you can figure this thing out
See if I can figure it out. All right. Oh, no, I can't wait to not
I can't wait to get very angry in about 45 seconds. Let's analyze it. It's gonna be another ship
It's gonna be another robot communication thing and we're gonna communicate with each other
right
That would be a pretty cool twist
If I end up talking to the robot in here and I get like the story and it's not bad
The robot's just doing you know what the rope this robot's doing and i'm owned by these people whatever that'd be kind of cool
All right, I just pressed. I don't know what I just did. I got it. I opened it
It's beautiful. Yeah
Maybe some kind of sundial sure sun harry
If you're through fantasizing about me, i'd like to find a way out of here. You want to keep looking around
Why did she just nod like goes off controls?
Uh casey, why don't you keep working on this it might help it was weird
Oh shit. Okay
analyze this
um, okay press this
Okay, red
red
Red activate
I have to match the colors if they're in
They all have to be the same color blue everything has to be blue. No, everything has to be blue blue blue blue blue
Turn to blue everything has to be red red red red red everything has to be orange orange
Red everything wait
I have to just put the colors in the right spots, but there's no green
What color am I supposed to make this?
I don't get it either red purple make you make it purple
It's blue blue. Oh, it's all purple. I got it. Everything's purple did I win?
I don't I don't know what it wants me to do
Oh
So this is this the outside is has colors and then the inside has colors I
Okay, I get it. We need to combine whatever is in so this like, you know, for instance yellow and green makes
Blue no yellow and blue makes green right? So this is green going into here. What does
Red and yellow makes orange. Okay, so we have blue
Or I don't understand. I have no idea what this wants me to do. You're overthinking this like crazy
I don't know. I don't get it. What does it want to do?
Just match the colors to the outside. I can't do that. There's no green. There's no green
There's no green and there's no blue
And match the other ones
All right, so I did
They already are done. There's no orange
This is I already did it. I've matched it. What about the manual?
clicking on the outer ring of the hemisphere
Oh, never mind. I thought I had it clicking on the
outer ring of the
Clicking on the outer ring of the hemispheres causes two of them to change colors
The goal is to change all of the hemispheres to yellow. Okay, great that I would never have known that I had to make them all yellow
I made them all purple
Like how was I supposed to know that all of them had to be yellow I made them all purple
We have to drive this thing. Listen, I think we've done enough looking around here. Don't you?
Yeah, okay. Let's meet up and move out. Yeah
Yeah
Wait, wait, wait, you hear that it's in there
It's the cringe yep
You killed him
Oh, no
I don't think that's the first time they've given me an opportunity to shoot anything
All right. I need to shoot her shoot her next
Ah
Listen, I think we've done enough looking around here. Don't you?
Yeah
Look, do you really expect the robot that takes 40 minutes to complete a children's
Match puzzle to be able to aim a weapon correctly
You killed him. That was more funny to me than anything else
Look right in the camera right in my eyes. You killed him
He's shooting he tried he's killed me
His last ditch effort was i'm gonna kill this motherfucker. He got it. He got his final thing his final wish
What a way to end that I kill her he gets stabbed through the throat and then kills me
This is this is a tarantino movie
Listen, I think we've done enough. Don't you?
Yeah, okay. Let's meet up and move out
You killed him
Wait, wait, wait, you hear that coming from the bodies
So I have to shoot the aliens that come out
Here we go
This is so lame. This is what you look like when you play vr
They're everywhere
I got one. What was he doing?
Oh, wait, what is he doing? He shoots behind his head like three times
He's aiming at the ground
So
You know what you can't blame them for that either though like these actors they're in front of a green screen
They have no idea
There's somebody right there going and
Action shoot all around you shoot shoot shoot look out behind you behind you behind you get that one
Get one duck duck duck duck. They're everywhere. They're everywhere. They're on the ground. They're everywhere
There's one crawling on you
And then the effects artist has to take all this thing that the director told them to do and be like I
What am I supposed to do with this shit?
They're supposed to be flying around the ship. They're not supposed to be on the ground
You can't blame the actress they're doing they're doing their best
For all things considered they are
Listen, I think we've done enough looking around here. Don't you they're doing their best for porn actors
Tia what's her name?
Tia
What's her name?
She was famous actress
Tia carrera tia carrera
She was in wayne's world. She no. Yeah, she was a very she was like an a-lister at one point
Oh shit
Shit, oh shit
What does this game have for a rating?
Shit you say shit the t game
Did you just grab one off her shoulder?
All right, there's how many how many what do we have to do? How long is this?
I want one of them to stub their toe on something
Just look at somebody that's been in front of a green screen doing this exact thing this exact thing
It's fucking tiring and it's painful
In fact, I hope somebody puts me in this scene
Now they are they are they syrup?
What am I doing? What do I do?
I have to save one of them
Extend the hand
Turn the thrusters off
analyze
data
Wait, did I just hit my head?
In a panic I ran around and scoopy do shaggy somehow
Saved the day
What do you want me to do analyze the damage? Jesus christ. What is this?
Okay, this connects
Connect them connect all of them
Shit, okay. They have their color coded. This is yellow when I press the okay
So that yellow is gonna make all the ones that are yellow move red is gonna make the ones that are red move
Blue is gonna make all the ones that are blue move. I just did it. Damn it. I didn't hold on. I did it
That's it. No, what that's not what that is
But some have two colors. Yeah. Yeah, but okay when I press this yellow one ready watch
You would assume that all the ones that have a yellow square are the ones that open or close, right? Okay, so then
With this theory it's done. These are the only two yellows, right?
For this one here. Okay. Now we need to do this one and then we have to have one that's ripped to do a red
Now it's it's done. I did it. Wait. No, I didn't. Hold on. Wait. Hold on
Shit, but we'll open. Okay. This will open. I need to okay
Open the yellows and then close all the blues and yellows shit red or blue. God damn it
I think that's it. Did I do it? No
Stupid blue the stupid blue one. I had to press this one
Now that's it
Right. Hold on. I need to do so red red will this will close all the reds and the yellows. This is open
Why why does this one have to be open? All right, wait, wait, wait blue and yellow you stupid motherfucker
It doesn't help that it's wicked ugly, too
It's this the ones that the doubles the doubles would just fuck everything up blue and red blue blue and red
That's it. No, it's not god damn it press the one red one and then the yellow blue one
This is the kind of ipad game that I download sometimes
I play the first three levels and I go nope and I hold my thumb on the icon and I delete the app
So why even have the greens here? They don't do anything. It's all this yellow blue red shit
Now if I do this one, it'll close all the yellow ones. I don't want to do that. I want to
do um, um a
uh, and then um, I don't even I don't even care a puzzle. I don't do puzzles. I've run wicked fast
You know what I mean? Like that's that's not what I do. I don't care. Hit the blue one. No. Oh I did
You gave up at the finish line looks like everything's up and running again
It's a good thing too because we need you to open another door
Go to it case
What?
I've repaired myself for them to make me open a new door with another puzzle
Is that all i'm worth to you guys?
I just saved both of your lives twice. Remember when you got sucked out of the window and I had to come to your rescue
remember when
You were being swarmed by aliens and I shot all of them. Not one of you
Got one kill
Okay, so put it up. Please insert disc three
This one is gonna be hell. I can already tell
We're already at disc three. We're this we're gonna beat this game. I think I think we're actually gonna beat this game
And for all for all the the naysayers in here
um
If I have a sort of a gauge of how I gauge if i'm going to complete a video game or not
If you get to disc three out of four
Just do the whole thing
It's probably like another 40 minutes in this damn game. That's not sunk cost. That's I want to see the end
Virgin interactive. What about it? All right. What am I trying to make here?
Uh, am I supposed to fill the whole thing in a certain color?
What does the manual say manual says?
Well, this would be the uh, the blue door, right? Okay
When you rotate the outer hexagons by clicking on them, the corresponding shape is also rotated in the center hexagon
If any of the colored shapes intersect in the center hexagon the overlapping triangles turn gray
The goal is to rotate the shapes so that there are no gray triangles in the center
Easy, this is not going to be easy. All right, that one fits up there. Wait, that one fits in there. That's right there
All right. We got something wrong here
Something wrong here. It's this guy
Get it. I what there's more. Oh dear. No, no, no, no, no, no, there's gonna be three of these. Yeah
No, I don't want to do this. Okay, there's everyone. Where can I fit you? Wait, wait, okay, that's good
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, is it the green go to this orange?
Orange you gotta go this way
No, no
No
No, it's wrong. Yellow absolutely goes right here. Red is absolutely right there pink. Oh pink is absolutely not over there
Or is it it might be? Oh, yeah pink is absolutely over there. Okay. What about over here? Wait, absolutely
What goes here though? Nothing fits in that spot right there. Does anything go there?
That does but what else can go there? Okay. Wait, that is I think that's the only solution there yellow you moron
All right. Hey the next time you're doing like a sudoku
I'm gonna stand over your shoulder and when you when you do one wrong and you like erase it with your pencil
I'm gonna go like you idiot. You're stupid and you're gonna go fucking around with my puzzle man
Leave me alone then i'm gonna drink the rest of the coffee that's on the pot
And fucking walk like upstairs and then you're gonna go for a coffee like around two second coffee. I'm gonna be fucking furious
That's enough left. I did it. I drank it. All right. Hold on. What's this? No, this is right. That's okay
What should red be down here?
No, red's right
Blue is not right
Yellow's not right either
Hold on. I don't know orange and green orange and green orange and green orange and green
Yeah, that makes sense
That makes sense. But what's taking up this spot over here?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
That's
I didn't fill one in
What's that little space right there? I didn't fill in I was trying to fill that in
Casey
I guess you need to leave one spot. This is amazing. Look at the size of it
Harry can't even see the bottom here
More monkey noises now. All right fine
Did you just try to grab his gun
You both almost died twice this is not a place to fuck around
like
He's spitting on me
But am I not allowed to hang out on the platform with them?
Die now let's encounter
The bones
50 chat message trying to help the stream and all he does is call us morons
All he struggles finish the simpleton puzzle. You know, the streamer is the moron. He's being mean to us. I'm not seven
Give me back this ship isn't that big
It's gotta be a projection
Or an illusion
Hey, hey, wait, maybe that
Yeah, see you tomorrow feel we went through before somehow, you know
Transported us to the home world
Transported
Yeah
Why can we breathe out here star trek reruns what happened to the space suits
Fresh air there's even a breeze
This is an illusion. It's pretty damn convincing
It's actually kind of funny if they found a little door over here and they opened it and it was like a big set
Cameras and stuff and they were like, oh shit
Closed it is real. Yeah, I guess we are all right here
It wasn't real it was a mirage
It was fake
Don't put your face that close
You had to do make like the jokes and make the condescending remarks and now he's dead
What I let go of him when did I let go of him I didn't press anything I didn't I I didn't
Jesus christ, I didn't press anything
He grasped me. He says, oh, thank god. I love you. And then I what do I do? He didn't give me a prompter
thrusters
All right thruster press. Yes
No
What is this is thruster, right?
This is thruster right here, right?
This is thruster. Let's go
Well, look this has like the lines on it. That's the thrust line
What should I do something and have to dodge anything?
Uh, I think we're just going
Wouldn't he have fallen? Oh, okay. No. Yeah, he would have he would have just fallen right through isn't the ground here
Child a child
Is this the
You rented like the 45 minute hour like that. It's not even an hour and 30 minutes. It's like 48 minute long porn movie
And they just do this the entire movie until the last 12 minutes
And all of you just fast forward to the last 12 minutes
You're speaking from experience
Yes
No, i've never seen a pornographic film in my entire life
That's disgusting to me what you just said, how dare you ever even assume that i've seen one of these just disgusting
revolting pornographic films
Oh, I drink water and I do my uh chores, you know, are there anything else?
I'm glad that let's take a look around. Yeah. Yeah, I can manage that remember this time. I know I know I know be careful
Doesn't do taxes. He just admitted it
What how do you where do you get that from?
Chores is watch porn
Sometimes it feels like that. Don't it? What is this?
like
All right, what's today? Today's uh, thursday. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I did I got the mail
That's yeah, I did I didn't work I just got back from work, I guess yeah, I got the mail I washed the windows
I jumped I guess time to do this
I'm not tired yet. What time is it?
Oh, it's like it's like 8 30
I'm not gonna fall asleep for like another six hours or so probably
Wow, thank you. I mean, I mean I guess
I
Stop talking
I can't wait. I can joke and make fuck around about like everything else but not about like be careful
Don't talk about this
it's the one thing that's off limits besides politics and that's even bullshit because you've heard me do like
Every politician's voice you've heard on this stream. Yeah. All right. This is a crystal puzzle. I know this one
Your son is watching
Is do you know this is a you had to click the yes, I mature audience filter it's on
You had to press that button
Uh, am I doing I think i'm doing this right somehow accidentally
Let's do it. Um
Solve this puzzle. You must freeze the objects in pairs of matching silhouettes causing them to become highlighted
When all the objects are highlighted the lock will open in pairs of matching silhouettes feel like triangle triangle
diamond diamond
Uh, please need to stop watching it's been an issue for quite a while
We're aware of it, but you keep watching this sort of material on stream. I'm gonna have no choice
But to unsubscribe what what you what why am I watching this on stream?
All right, is it pac-man?
No, it's not pac-man. What is it then circle you to match the silhouette. It's the shape
Yeah, okay. Hold on. Can I get a little tab in the middle there? Is that even I think this even does that
Moon little half moon. Not really. Oh, it's not just shape not color
Ah
Okay, i'm gonna find the star
Where's there a star or not a star maybe something else maybe a cube. I got this one right here. Check it out
Yep. Oh, what about this cube?
Oh, that's a star. It could also be a cube. It could also be a star. No, I can't
No
Wait, that's the only one that's been matched so far
shit
No
No, dude
I can't get it right. How is that not the same? It has to be the exact same thing
Oh god same deal with this one. Okay
Whack and then
Whack did I win? Oh, you don't have to you only have to do it for three of them. No, dude
Was that an alien talking or did they have to record somebody that was in the sound room and not the actor
Because they needed something there. Yeah, that's what it was
I think maybe on these guys, uh planet one of the audio engineers had to do that
About eating these aliens
Have some respect why because they're dead this guy is a genuine asshole
We don't have a song
If there is a nav console and all this stuff we'd have to tear this place apart to find it
Assuming we'll even know it when we see it
I think we shouldn't take a look around. I think you should die dallas
Let us know if you spot anything casey. I will
Thanks for including me by the way
I know you don't have to
Well, unless you're having better luck than I am. I think we should keep going didn't even
I didn't get one second. That's all the time you're gonna give me here
I'll say one thing about those crin. He sure as hell do a thorough job
That room must have been I think we'll ever find any of these guys like a 10 by 10 cube. I sure hope so
You know, it's times like this
I wish I just stayed home and went to business school just like mama wanted
This looks the same in 160 that doesn't 1080. I'm sure it does. Well, it just so happens
I have a pretty good head for figures. I can't add
Uh information for the bitrate to take
Puzzle door
All I can do is upscale this
I can't add data to what's being presented
orange red
green blue
Does this even count as a video game?
Well, I mean it depends
Does the back of your cereal box?
Consider itself to be a video game. I mean, it's a game
But I mean it is this is on video
So yes, it is technically let's take a look where this one is
Okay
The objective is to route a colored light so that it reaches the flashing point of the same color
Okay, you can deflect the path of light by clicking in the cells
It is all right for the colors to mix at the position where they hit the flashing points from blue to blue
That's not cheating. This is how it's what I've known what to do. Wait, what's this like goo? I'm putting on it
Oh, no, that's a mirrors
Oh, dear. These are mirrors. Oh fucking Jesus. This is gonna be hell. This is gonna be horrible
Uh, take this off. It's gotta be here. These all get to get all these mirrors off
Take all these mirrors off. All right, we're gonna go this way take that mirror off. Get this one off this way
We're gonna bounce it from here to here get that mirror off. That one's done. Now. We need green green
Where's green as a oh, okay green so green is gonna go
Down here. We need to have a touch down here. No, how do I erase?
Erase erase erase erase erase erase erase. Okay down and then right here. We're gonna bend it this way
I don't know. I don't know. Oh jesus. Okay. No, it's got wait odd watchers. Do your taxes
I mean you could if you wanted to this goes this way. We need to bounce it to here. There it is
Okay, so that's that now. We just need red shit. Yeah
We do it again red to red blue to blue
Uh blue is already blue is already there one so I have to hit green has to wait. What the hell's going on green is
Already there red and then red and then red and then red
It red and then uh
Shit, this is gonna get ugly. This is gonna get really gonna get this is gonna get ugly
Okay, blue is already blue
Shit shit. I'm blue watching this
ha ha ha
Flashlight in the top right. Oh, that's not what you said
You said something else. All right blue blue now. We need green to green green green
That's it. That's it. I gotta gotta see red right here. Shit. It's so close. That's it. How's that? No, it is
Blue needs to go up here. This is very bad
Delete everything delete delete delete delete delete it all delete it all delete delete delete delete delete delete get it
I this this too many fucking mirrors. There's mirrors everywhere. Okay, I did it. All right. That was there's another one cool
um not cool, um
Blue is blue blue's gotta go over here blue going up and no I don't want to do this one
I don't want to do this one. I really don't want to do this one
I I have to you said you would finish the game of who said I was gonna stop playing the game
I was just gonna go to the walkthrough and wait the walkthrough is on easy like dallas encounter walkthrough medium
All right. I'm almost there almost at the almost at the end of the game. All right, here we go
This is the one i'm on right now. I'm just gonna follow it word for word. Okay. Hold on. Hold on
I'm just gonna follow word. Wait, this is not right blue green
Right. This one's not right. Why is this different than mine blue on the left blue on the top?
This is different than mine. God fucking damn it. I I can't change the difficulty and I it's randomized
Why do you have to have to be randomized? All right, I have to that means I have to just do it
That means I have to do it. Here we go step by step. That's one one is done green green is gonna go
From here to here and then from here to here. Nope one more down one more down
Green is done. No, it's not now. It will be this is not good. Wait, hold on
69 69 viewers watching. Okay
That's kind of cool. I guess they have to I gotta go down here for this one, too
Why did I make this medium? Why didn't I just put it on easy? Who cares?
It's my own damn fault. Oh Jesus. I i'm just gonna try
It's gonna be really sloppy, but it might work green blue needs to go
Wait, why is this this is red now? What the fuck happened? That one's done. There's any there's another red right here
Get rid of everything. We're doing red first. Okay green
There's only one green on the right so we go bounce bounce bounce done. Okay, red is done
There is no more red except for down here. Okay, red is done. It's now time to move on to green green
Where's the other green over here?
Oh shit what how am I supposed to get that how am I supposed to get that one colors can mix at the ends
Uh, this has to be
Blue somehow need to go back to the fourth grade
No
This put this is fucking like difficult and annoying. All right, i'm not gonna sit here and take that
This is like an annoying shit puzzle blue blue. Oh, hold on almost there. I got it. I'm gonna get it right now ready
Oh, hold on. Yes
Does that count does it count this is a mess. No, it doesn't I thought you said I could complete I could combine them
Such a fucking mess
There has to be a medium walkthrough. Okay, but I found one. Oh, this is only the first 20 minutes of the game
You can do this. I believe in you. I don't think I can I I think i'm too impatient to even spend 10 minutes on this
I can't do click map. See look at how many spaces there are. What did I what did I go wrong? I did
I did I have no idea play something else. I'm almost on disc four. I can't all right
What if I can I change it to easy sunk cost?
It's like so stupid
Oh
I'm so pissed
Get me out. What happened?
Medium no, no
No
Jump to scene 24 on easy
It's too mean
Easy
scene 24
Let's go
No, I don't want to change the game. I want to see what happens in the end. I'm i'm on disc of four
Wait, I still have to actually do this. It's supposed to be easy
Hold on. I think this person was playing on easy. Yeah, they were all right. This person was playing on easy
I got it. Okay, so then it goes like this. Okay, there's this blue blue blue blue blue blue red red
Green green red red like it's it's hard to even tell where the mirrors are because this thing is at like fucking 200p
We don't have to do anymore. We're done. That's it
Thing what what were you thinking about? I was deciding what to call the ship when I read it up in the log
Man, what's that? Hellhive crin motel?
Deadless what?
Ancient great mythology to escape from the labyrinth deadless made wings out of feathers and wax
And then you fly too close to the sun and squirt his ass
Marlon brando
It kind of is
Yeah, the dead listen kind of
Hey to find a way out of here, i'ma leave
In plant life, I guess
Yeah, but for what?
food supply oxygen supply frump and marlon brando are yes, they are one step away from each other
Fogs
It's like no don't shoot me she shot it around this thing maybe you can figure out a way to open it from the other side
The hell was that with the gun pulling thing?
I'm sorry
Dude, she's sus
Don't you love on my stream when is he streaming command is not ruined forever
That's supposed to be sense danger in sorcery. And now it's like hey i'm sus as to when he's streaming found something
Here comes a puzzle. I can't wait to do it very very quickly
It's all an easy
Me like what was it in in?
Well, isn't sus short for like suspect like you suspect somebody
Yeah, it's I mean in
Sorcery the spell was sense danger not like you are suspicious
Sort of the same. It's a little it's a little the same not completely the same though
Um, how deep does this go at what point do I lose walkie talkie frequency?
Uh, look down should look down there's something down here. Oh, no, it's a maze
Of course it is
Okay. So now we're gonna go
Maybe should I maybe analyze should I analyze the area analyze?
Data analyze thrusters. No, I just have to get it right
I just have to guess this is your colonoscopy. Yeah, pretty similar
Except it'd be kind of weird to have multiple ways to go in your intestines found it lucky there. Wait, I didn't really
This is no good. This is no good
I got to start keeping track of where i've been but I have no idea where i've been every hallway is the same
Can't go up or down, right? I need a pen and paper
That's not a bad idea wall
All right, should I get out the pen and paper? I can't look up and I can't look down just use microsoft paint
So what i'm back? Okay. Wait, wait, wait
Okay, i'm gonna do paint. It's probably helpful. So that's a wall
There's paint shit. It's on the monitor behind me. God damn it. I can't even click it
It's on the monitor behind me like behind the like i'm on a different source right now
Not behind me. I mean like behind the game. I'm on a different source about hdmi. I'm not on dvi because i'm capping it
Shh follow the right wall
I just tried to all right jeff. I'm gonna follow the right wall
Follow right wall. Okay, i'm going
Wait wouldn't going right again put me in a circle. Okay, right again s video scaler hdmi. That's the one I have a retro tink
so it's s video into the retro tink and then
hdmi from the retro tink into an el gato and then el gato into the tv or the monitor i'm hugging the right wall
By the way, the retro tink is incredible
If you have an old console, it's the best one i've used so far
Without a doubt. I'm gonna try going this way the maze has pillars. You're fucked with the right wall
I didn't how does it even end up there? I'd rather watch you clean the bathroom than this
Just wait a minute. I'm i'm interested. I need to play
This game sucks. All right, I know you don't think I know I need i'm
I'm enjoying it. I'm wonderful. I gotta get to disc four
I can't just not see disc four. Otherwise, that's so bad for me. All right. Hold on. Does this guy have the walkthrough of this?
Where is it? Come on. Show me. All right. Here he is. Okay, so he goes
straight
Straight, how would you even figure this out straight right ends up going down somehow actually physically down
How much of this game add to the germ of debt take no. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. I went down
I went down. I went down. I just went down. So wait when he goes down
I want to see what he did what happens. I want to get to the point where he goes down
Okay, he just went down now. Where does he go?
Every resident sleeper removes the debt by five million. Okay, and he goes left. Okay. He goes left and then
After he goes left he goes
Straight he goes after going straight
Imagine being 12 and trying to do this on your own. Okay after going straight he goes
Straight again, and then it's a dead end for me. It's
Not a dead end for him. Why?
No
What the wait dead end behind me dead end to the left?
So I can go straight then so right is a dead end behind me to dead end this left this way right straight ahead
Straight ahead. This is it. This has to be it forward. Come on. Come on. Okay, so
No, what?
Where do I go?
Left or right
Left try right. Okay. I'll try right. Oh my god
Okay, so then if we go straight straight would have been left so we're gonna go straight or right right
We're gonna go right from here
Right. No, we're gonna left. I don't know straight right from here
It's straight from when we first came down straight from here is left when we first came down
Yeah, let's go right. No, I was wrong. That was wrong. Go back back back. Go back that way. That was wrong
So now we're gonna go left. Well, this is not even the right. This is not even correct
This wasn't underneath this before what I was just here. Okay, we're like from here straight
That was the worst noise. No, it was me clearing my I don't know left
Left from here. I'm gonna get a fucking t-shirt for completing this game
That's dead end man. You got that wrong. Not left. Your brain is made for bug snacks
Okay, we're playing bug snacks tomorrow when he said left again, dude. This is
How is this
Even like 30 years ago, how why is this fun? I understand like little puzzles
But the like guess which way you're going maze first person thing like this not like this. Not even fun
How many people gave up at this maze? I even followed the walkthrough and it wasn't even right
You made us do three mazes. Yeah, but that was different though
Because there was like a thousand of there was like 500 of you that could find it
It's only one of me here if 500 other people were doing this somebody would find it, okay now
We get out of here
Get us out of here, but not yet. Hold on. I gotta get to that fourth disc
We're like fucking 20 minutes away from the end of the goddamn game. I want to see it so bad
Don't you know none of you do but I know you might you maybe you do
This is a screensaver once if we go down then we're on the right track
That's not down. Fuck watch it on youtube. I did and I followed the exact instructions
Stop turning. I just went straight twice
I just went straight twice
Go to the menu and start the maze with the walkthrough
Okay, I will I will but one second. Hold on
The game fax has a full map. It does
walkthrough
by anonymous
Okay. Yes. Okay. All right. All right. Where is it green? Okay click
Next time into the hole and click the floodlight. This is the maze. Okay. Holy shit. This thing sucks
Are you kidding me? This is horrible
Okay, so where where do you start?
Hold on again
Okay, I can't paste it in here
Joe on screen. Hold on a second. Can I do it in a text box?
That would be actually pretty funny if I could hold on. I hope I can yeah, I can this is so funny
There you go. Here's the here's the maze
That's why that's what I have to look at
Hold on. No, it's not quite correct the spacing, right?
Wrong font. What font is this? What the fuck is this? This is the map that's on the game fax
This is him, right? No, the spacing's wrong. The spacing's wrong. Hold on. Let me just take a screenshot of this
Hold on. Wait a sec
I gotta check. You know what? I'm gonna take a piss. I'll be right back and i'm gonna get this on screen
I'll be right back pee time go pee
Okay, i'm back and i'm ready
I'm back and i'm ready at the map. I'm ready to rock and roll
This is what it's supposed to look like not like that
It's supposed to look like this
So I have to i'm gonna restart the chapter
What is farm?
That's even worse. This is the maze
There's a map of the maze
Okay
What do you where do you start?
This doesn't make any sense. Um, no, I don't think it does but maybe it might
What do you mean who made this? Somebody like 20 years ago. Thank god they did
Otherwise, we'd be here forever and i'd have to turn the video. I'd have to turn it off and I don't want to turn it off
All right, let's go
Thank god. They did
Okay, so let's restart go to the menu
And restart and what is farm?
Taking ascii is true dedication
And this is scene 26. That's what we want. Let's go
All right
so where
This is where are we now farm?
This has to be farm, right?
All right, we're in
Turn on the flood light
Here we are
Okay
So if we go straight we can only go straight the straight puts us if that's cube
Where are we trying to go?
I have no idea. I yeah, where does this go?
bottom right
Okay, straight
Then right right?
We're trying to go to the corridor. We need to go straight all the way and then left so we have to go straight again
And then straight again and then straight again
No, what right now we are on cube. I don't know where we are. We're on. No, I know I know
Right now we are cube two above farm straight up
so if we go
Up we go straight again then left and then straight
Straight again puts us to the third square above farm
This is where we're in square three above farm
We're going to go left
Left will take us to that next one here. I need to be like marking this. I don't think I can though
Now we are on the one right before the long hallway up top
And now but wait, hold on. Does this is this direction? Does this take into account direction you're facing?
So is this technically straight on this one or is that left?
No, it's straight, right?
Straight takes us across the pond, correct?
We're gonna go across the pond here. We're gonna go across and around and down and through and that's not right
What I don't know where I am. Okay. Now I'm I don't know the way i'm facing started over
I don't know which way i'm facing. I don't know idea
Okay, so the idea is you go straight and then left immediately
That's why we were walking in circles guys because look at the look at the four cubes that are above farm
How are you ever supposed to figure that out?
Okay, here we go. I am going to go
left
Immediately that puts us right here. We're gonna go straight straight here
That should take us across but that the line on the left
No, all right. We're going here we go. We're going down. Okay, we've made it now. I need to go
Um, I don't I don't understand if if if positional direction is it makes any sense straight again
No, it would have to be right because that's we came in that way, right? It would have to be right
And then we go straight
Okay, so now straight
Not right into the trash then we go straight again
Look at the chutes and ladders bullshit if up here if I take a right it takes me all the way back down
Straight again and then right and we go right. Okay, I forget I forget where we are
No, okay when we go I forget I don't know where I am. Can we go right?
I don't I have no idea where I am
We go right which puts us to the one right before the the the candy cane touches the top of it, right?
Right and then we bang a left
And then that should be into the top of the candy cane
The left should go into the candy cane and then we go down through the candy cane
And we end up right next to the corridor
Now we go
That's not right
Oh, I don't know. I don't know straight. I think it's straight from here now, right?
It's going don't say right if if you're agreeing with me say yes
Straight is the correct way now, right?
No, don't say right straight is the correct right way. Yes
No, don't say right straight is the correct way. Yes
No, are you saying are you saying right lesson to go right? I don't know where I don't know which way i'm facing on this map
Okay, so if I go straight here, I don't know. I have no idea where I am
If I go right i'm gonna end up
Stupid go straight
straight will
um
No, it's not straight. Is it it's straight it is and then now we bang a left
We go left from here
Right and now left
And then straight and that will take us through the corridor
So technically
We are okay now straight
Straight this is it
Yes
Wow, that was awful. That was terrible
Screen so messed up. What the fuck? All right case you did it
They keep saying I love you
Does another dead end come on zack we've been in bad before remember that time on tacos 7 when we were pinned down by
Two back our squads
Insert disc four such thing as a hopeless situation rigs the engine to create a plasma burst and boom took them all out
Yeah, all right. Maybe you're right turn off r9k. All right, this is got to be close
What's this one?
Open this door
All right, this one
Yep, I knew it. We're so we're getting to the end. We're so close
I'm so glad i'm gonna be i'm gonna be the only person on twitch to have ever completed the died alice encounter
No one else has beat this game on stream and I will put any amount of money on that like
But i'm not gonna bet any money because it could be wrong
This is not a bet. This is me. Just stating a statement that could be real
It's four going on
Let's go disc four
Yes
Why am I so excited about this?
This is called the purple door
Clicking on one of the black lines causes it to turn blue
The lock responds by turning one of the red lines red. Um, you know what just give me the walkthrough. I don't care
Okay, uh
Like uh, this is really this is a really a game
You must form a closed path of four or longer before the computer does it's very difficult. What did I spoil the game?
Wait, i'm just gonna watch the video. I don't care. I just read a spoiler
For like the end of the game. I think on that walkthrough
All right, let's get it. Here we go
I just want to get to the end. I love it. I love it. Okay. So how do I do this puzzle?
Oh shit, it has been three hours. Why do I feel like it's been like 10 minutes. It's been three hours
Okay, i'm just gonna just go i'm gonna follow word for word the video or stream 2020 no way
I disagree a thousand percent. No way i'm just gonna follow step by step in the video
Play the game i'm about to i'm about to play it very fast top five get out of here. No, it's not
I've had a this has been fun. What do you want about this is the video's wrong? Of course it is
I just I what just happened. This is like tic-tac-toe
What this is really a game you must form a closed path of four or longer before the computer does
What the fuck it's like tic-tac-toe, but not
shit
Uh, oh my god, give it to me. Give it to me. What don't do it. Don't you dare don't
I win
Fuck you. No
What's the connect for the guy say?
Get off my back. It's something weird like that, right?
Shit. All right. I'm trying to get this way over here. Fuck man. Yeah, did I win?
This is gonna be close ready. You dick. Wait, this is it right there go for the bottom go for the top
Go for it
What he says something weird it's something like that
Yeah, what does it say somebody yeah, give me it what is it
Tell me zack. Do you complain just to make conversation or do you honestly enjoy it?
Geez, erry. My dogs are aching. Okay. Have you no sympathy worse boys?
Not that one of the connect four has an eyes mouth and legs and stuff and it talks it says something
Casey
See if you can figure out what these panels are for
He's high
Hold that thought
I'm about to prove all of you
connect for
commercial
Everyone's about to be like oh fuck. I'm so wrong. You're so right
Okay, here it comes. I'll take a that shaves at the very least
100 million dollars off the debt
100 million has to
Because I was so wrong. I was on drugs. I was high. I was fucked up. He's imagining worlds again. Nope
All right, I gotta find a panel. Is it gonna be like a painting on one of these walls?
Analyze
Slug found slug amorphous polysilicate comp auto reactive substrata
Okay, open it up
ooh
Blue I get it green. Oh yellow blue
green
Analyze we've had a good plus two streak in an hour. I haven't tried to have a plus two streak, dude
I'm trying to get a streak
All right blue
red
Green did I analyze this the like the big penis?
Pattern data saved. All right. What do we got? I think those are the only two on this panel
Or this one green. Oh scan that del swim is streaming samurai jack on youtube right now
If you guys want to head over there right now, no, don't go there stay here. Okay now orange
Oh scan that
Okay anymore just lost a bunch of people. No, i'm fine
They ain't going anywhere. Okay, they ain't going anywhere then no one's leaving. Oh cope cope. It's not cope
No one's going anywhere. I kind of don't understand what this wants me to do though
All right. Um now what data I have like all these pictures in my data
Dude, that's a weed leaf. That's I know. Yeah, that's a good one
How many more pictures are there
Everyone left but you and me that would be so funny
It's just me and you
Nobody else just us
Okay, that was orange. That's it. There's only two pictures per panel. I think that's it. Oh, there's one more panel here
Oh another panel. You can't even say hello to his only viewer. I'll be honest with you
I don't remember what their name was. Okay, what's the walkthrough say?
Each panel will show you two pictures
You have to click various colors to make the pictures appear click analyze on each picture and translate each using the numeric code
We've been using with the doors
What do you mean translate?
uh
What do you mean translate x?
You missed one. I did
No, I don't want to why do you hate us so much? I don't am I gonna play something else?
Yeah, once I get to the end of this we're putting in blade force
Take a round for that one. Uh, I don't even I don't understand. Okay. I'm just telling you guys right now
Uh right after this next sentence in the walkthrough. I see the words finale
so
We just have to uh, literally watch the video of how the person doing this
Yeah, well the finale is right after this whatever it is. All right. What the fuck does this even want me to do?
All right, so you go you you go to each panel you scan each picture and then I think I leave
How do I just leave? How do I get away? I can't leave
Leave how do I fucking leave? What is this game called? Actually? It's called the die dallas encounter
I got them all
This is horrible. Yes. I know this game is
Absolute utter dog shit. I know but i'm at disc four and i'm gonna i'm gonna win
Is there one that I didn't scan? Did I not scan this one? Did you get it?
At this this just
This no like what?
What how would you even know what to do here?
How like what?
Translate
What do you mean translate? What am I supposed to be translating?
I wish I could just
Fucking get a save state and skip this because this is this is just why would you ever know what to do here?
This is stupid
On their video that this is easy too
And they have like a weird interface I don't have like a pc interface data. How do I like even do this?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Okay, green blue yellow. Yeah, sure. What the fuck do you want me to do?
Huh grandpa hit the enter key
If we scan this one
Maybe you have to scan them all. I don't remember the guy leaning over the sphere
German this is painful unplug it
Yeah
Symbol pull the plug pull the plug. Is it weird that I I I can't because I have to spite finish this game
I definitely didn't see this one
Okay. Now I got that I got it
sunk cost
Well, it's not sunk cost if you eventually get to the end somewhere somewhere in the world that somebody really embarrassed this game exists
Like they they like fucking designed and programmed this game shit faced every day
They probably don't even remember that they made this they hotboxed the office
I can't dude. This doesn't even make any fucking sense
Even the walkthrough doesn't make any sense
Patterns saved. Yeah, I mean, I know I have like these patterns in this but what am I supposed to do with them?
I can't even leave the slabs enhance it. I have like I have this data ship, but I can't even interact with it
All right. I'm getting close. I'm getting close to ripping it out. You're right. I'm getting really close. Is it gonna happen?
I'm getting close to ripping it out
But we're at we're on the last fucking disc i'm so close to ripping it out and just frisbee-ing it
What the fuck is this?
Okay, hold on. This is where he is in the story
And then he moves to the left
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I think I got it. I think it's over. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. This is where he is
He scanned I did I scan this one. This is all we're almost done. Check this shit out. Here we go
I've got it. I've got that one scan. I'm gonna scan one more scan this one. That's it. That's it. That's it
I fucking scared. I scared these already
What does he do?
Translation wait, he's doing the same thing. I'm doing he's just going around in circles for like 15 straight minutes
He leaves how do I leave?
How do I leave?
How the fuck do I leave he he clicks down with a mouse and clicks the bottom of the screen and leaves
I can't do that. How do I leave?
He has like a I can leave button. How do I fucking leave?
rust
Please let me leave
What the fuck?
Why would I finish stuff like this and not resident evil 2?
I did resident evil 2 on my own plus this is resident evil 2 is like a nine hour game
This is like three and a half hours
Okay, how do I physically get the fuck out of this fucking? I'm so mad right now. How do I no
You don't have the achievements for clear. Shut up
No, that didn't just happen. Did it god?
Why can't I just back up from the fucking podium?
Did they forget to program it into the 3DO?
I don't think I think they forgot to program that into the 3DO version of the game
I'm not even going to go over here. I'm not going to click on any of this shit
No, no, no, no, shut up
No, I refuse
Okay, I did it. I'm done. That was fun. Now get me out
Oh
I'm so mad
I feel like I have to quit this
fucking
Trash can of a video game
Just wait, hold on. Good job casey
My feet are starting to hurt airy. Why the hell didn't they put in moving walkways?
Everybody relax everybody relax everybody relax
Or do you honestly enjoy it?
Geez, ery, my dogs are aching. Okay. Have you no sympathy ready to relax? I'm saving my
You when you'll really need it
When you run out of things to complain about wait, hold on everybody relax for a second casey
See if you can figure out what these panels are for
Okay, hold on
I already have all this data
I already have all the data
Okay. So now
I've got the data
forgot it all
so now
I've got i've looked at it all. Yes. Somebody has a youtube link and wonder what what is it?
It's better not be like a screamer puzzle tutorial. Hold on
Nobody has a link to the puzzle. Hey guys, we're gonna do a quick, uh puzzle tutorial on the like dallas's
Encounter whatever this is fake. This has to be fake. This party got
I knew it. I knew it
It's part of the same guy that made the the monkey one
My mic muted
Actually muted. Oh, I think I broke something. Did you hear me? Mike was muted the whole time. Did you hear me? What keeps happening?
Was I just cutting in and out over and over again? That was weird
Uh, all right. What do I do though? I've already scanned it
Data data. Wait, hold on all the one of the tutorial
I can't because he just he he goes by and scans everything and then he leaves. I can't leave
I dallas encounter give me another walkthrough
The game facts one doesn't help at all. There's another one
No, i've already seen that one. I'm one for the 3do. If I could even if it even exists
You found one
All right. I'm not i'm gonna find it myself
Dallas encounter walkthrough maybe the walkthrough king can help we tried walkthrough king before
Okay
At the panel in front of you click each of your colored buttons and a picture may be displayed
You are looking for one with three symbols beneath it orange green and yellow
What I think the walkthrough king helped us
Walkthrough king has got us
We're just gonna find them with orange green yellow underneath it and I went about that one stop saying fuck you to me
Don't say that. It's not nice
Orange green and yellow orange green yellow. That's not a nice thing to say to somebody you should be saying is you're great
Uh guys
I'm turning the ego stream on right now
And you have to adhere to it because I just said it it's happening right now
I have activated the ego stream for the remainder of the evening. So now
What are you gonna do now?
wizard
Oh that'll do it that i'm a funny character
Oh my god, i'm gonna make the worst jokes ever. I can't wait. You cannot minus two anything for the rest of the day
This is awesome. This is so good. I can't i'm so happy about this
Oh, wow. Thanks guys. You guys are awesome
I can't wait you guys are
You guys are being so kind to me. Oh, would you wow? It's a joke that everybody fucking hates. Oh, I know
Hey lois, how can you make can you believe these people on twitch chat are having a ball today?
Did you guys love peter everybody loves peter
orange green and yellow
Analyze this this is it right? Thank you walkthrough king
analyze
and then
enter the code as
Finale and click save
What?
What code what are you talking about? What enter the code?
Use analysis on this enter the code as finale and then click save back away from this room when you are done
Quickly select your saved purple code and click send to save aria and get another orb
This is pc tutorial but hot to what possible language pattern detected
Are you supposed to do with this information?
What are you supposed to do with this info click on an egg at the bottom?
Egg
All right. This one's in russian, but I think it's a 3do. This is disc four disc four
It's a it's in russian, but it doesn't matter and this is in fact on the 3do. This is on the 3do
Okay, what does he do? He goes to his what did it skipped pattern found?
Okay, and then he goes to the hand. No, he goes to the light and he why does it skip his video actually skips
Hold on a minute. Why does nobody want to show me this? I don't care if i'm here all day
I need to figure out why this is happening with this. We're at the end of the fucking game
Although his video says this is disc four of five. Wait, what? I don't have a fifth disc. Okay. Here we go
So explain to me what's going on here and why is this the worst video game ever made like ever made?
Okay, so
He goes over here. He okay. I'm gonna go this well. Yeah, maybe I have a good what happened
What what happened? What happened? What did he just do he scan? Okay scan?
He scans this and then then possible data language and then it skips again
And then it skips again in and way out of this puzzle. It's like this shit
What's this a die dallas encounter one? Somebody's got it. Somebody's got it. Somebody's got it. Somebody's got it
What is this? How did you find this video on twitch? This is disc four. Oh shit. This guy's on disc four
We don't why do we need to walk through we don't even need to walk through. Okay. What does he do?
Okay, here we go. He goes to see scans this one that I just scanned pattern data save language found and then
He goes to the next one he goes to the one on the left and then it just disappears
What how come my game's not doing that?
I'm gonna fly and fuck. What the hell are you talking about?
Shit, you just you I don't I don't know what happened
I didn't do anything. I just went left three times
Ah
That's what I just followed exactly what he did I can't believe you guys follow what's this guy's name
Sharfers
All right, go follow sharpers and thank him for his in his walkthrough
I don't know who this person is but like you thank god you did that
Save her. Wait, what?
He's speed running the game. It's he discuss a speed runner
Speed running die dallas encounter. All right, that's a good content
I would say I really I that I like want to watch that
I actually would love to watch that
Wait, you're dead. Hold on new offer. This is a terrible offer
This offer sucks
Stop playing for a hundred thousand. Are you kidding me? No make that a billion and i'll do it. What do I have to do?
What do I have to do?
Stop what?
No deal
deal
Now you can take the twelve thousand or you can go for a hundred in one of those two cases
You weren't the first to beat this
fuck
Oops, okay. We're good. I just made I just hit my desk and I made the thing skip
All right, wait, this is the finale i'm ready to win be careful do I just press the button whoa
Come on die dallas
Die dallas is just fun to say isn't it?
All right. Now I just press the button
A purple bowling ball
Or candle pin bowling
Who are under arrest?
All right work this panel all right activate the panel get in there
Analyze analyze no. Yes. No, can I press the button? How do I what do I do?
What do you i'm trying what do you i'm trying i'm actually trying to hit i'm trying to press it
I don't
I just I clicked the fork like five times
It was a red light that looked purple
I pressed all the I pressed all the lights now. I have to watch her fucking walk across the fucker
Just watch the speed run
I don't need that right now. Oh my god
If you have a big red button you say press big red button and I press it and doesn't do anything
But then I have to play simon says with the button. How am I supposed to know i'm supposed to do that
You need to you guys are not being incredibly nice
Just always assume it simon says
Okay, so just match the color of whatever is on the screen if this is wrong
And it's your fault if we have to watch her go across the balance beam again
Fuck you. I'm gonna go watch a furry movie
Um, I don't even know. What is a furry movie just any movie that has
Looney Tunes count
Go watch space jam
Here we go
Red didn't work pink didn't work
None of these work actually none of them do and I can't control anything fork fork fork fork data any of the data analyze
Yes, no press every button. No, no, nothing works. Absolutely. Nothing works. No buttons work. Yes. No. Yes. No, can't move a cursor
I can't do anything
I clicked the fork probably 30 or 40 times
Froster hold on is okay. So explain to me what's going on here
While we watch the cutscene for like a fifth time
What's happening here i'm gonna watch that guy's walkthrough again
We linked to that guy's speeder
This guy has no idea that he's like saving this stream
All right. So what happens?
It's so close
Okay. So here we are the lasers
Okay, here we go. So he he has like a data thing up what data wait, what's that? What is this data?
I don't have this one
I don't have his the the one he has on screen
This is his pink
green orange
I don't have his data thing
Work this panel see if you can stop this thing. What?
I don't have that
Am I actually soft-locked? I think I might be orange green yellow. You mean wait what I do have it?
I don't have it watch the speed run again. He just has it open
It has pink green orange
Pink green orange is what he has for like a thing for data up and then it just completes it. I'm so mad
Why do I not have this like data?
Disc that he has where did he get this and why don't I not have it? I do
His he has pink green orange blue
Yellow red for his data disc. I have it. I do not have this
Pink green orange, this is yellow orange
pink
blue pink yellow
I don't have it
Yellow orange pink
I don't fucking have this
You're on easy
Yeah, but what does that mean? What does that matter?
Pink green. Oh, stop fucking gaslighting me. I don't have this one
And his is a purple outline
This one has a blue outline
Yours is yellow orange green. What are you talking about? Leave me alone
Leave me alone. I don't understand what's happening
Try them all i'm yeah
Not gaslighting. Yes, you are. Of course you are
Okay, i'm gonna try them all
Try the ones with the blue outline
It's not gonna work here
Okay, here we go. It's up
I don't have it
Every holographic that I have doesn't work
I can't there's nothing works
What the fuck?
What is this?
Please stop
I don't understand
What's happening?
I'm I feel like i'm losing my mind on stream, but and the dog's barking at me
You guys are yelling at me. He's yelling at me
Should I put it on medium? All right. What if I put this on medium just for this scene? Will it change?
Okay, I put it on medium. No, it doesn't matter
I'm soft locked the solution was right in front of your eyes
It's not your fault. You have to go back and scan the purple door. What?
What do you mean scan the fucking purple door? What are you talking about? Go to the previous scene?
No, hold on auto. It's like let me in
Go to the previous scene
scene 28
What hold on i gotta let an auto in good job casey
My feet are starting to hurt airy. What the hell didn't they put in moving walkways? What do I have to do?
Tell me zack. Do you complain just to make conversation or do you honestly enjoy it? I didn't scan my dogs are aching
Okay, have you no sympathy? I'm saving my sympathy for you when you'll really need it. What? Okay
When you run out of things to complain about then scan the door scan what door casey?
See if you can figure out what these panels are for
I can't scan a door scan the blue rune. I need pink green orange
Purple door. I can't scan anything. I have to go back another scene
No
Scene 27. Oh, are you kidding me?
I have to go
Have to do this again
Wait, why?
No, this is not right. This is not right. It shouldn't be like this. No, it shouldn't be like this
I don't want to do this. I just want to win. I just don't I don't want to do these stupid puzzles again
I can't believe I fucking softlock myself
I'm so angry about soft locking myself
That I am distraught right now. Okay. I can't I I can't scan anything right now. I'm in the middle of a puzzle
I can't scan it
I could I had no option to scan it
No, I have to go back and fold disc
I can't
What happened?
This is bullshit
I didn't scan
One of these doors so therefore the game is softlocked. No, no, no, no
Nope
No, i'm not doing this again. No
No
It's not softlock
Wait, what was it?
I was watching the ending on youtube
Yeah, yeah, fuck this game
I'm not gonna no i'm not doing this again
I'm not doing it again. I'm not doing it again. Why?
It was you
No, I need the three data cubes
Hold on try this
Spoiler.com. I I don't know if I want to click that's that link looks shitty. I'm afraid of that link
But you're so close
Everybody everybody. All right, i'm gonna put on like some just everybody relax. Wait, just wait. Wait, wait, wait
I
Just say like some soft piano music. Just hold on. I'll be back in a minute
All right, just keep um, just just just soft royalty free. I typed in royalty free piano music
Just watch for a minute. All right. All right
all right
Scan the okay. I'm ready to
I'm not ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm going
I'm ready. I'm beating this. Uh, I saved over the image
of the map
fuck
How did I save over the image of the map? How did I saved over it?
With this fucking image
Okay, i'm being quiet and i'm gonna beat this really quickly. Here we go
And i'm scanning that stupid ass purple fucking door. Let's go go go go go. I can't what I did scanning
I'm quiet quiet
Oh, I did it wrong. Wait. No, no started over started over started over started over started over started over started over started over
I wasn't supposed to go left immediately
Go go go. Hurry up. Please hurry up
Oh go go
You it's left straight
right
Left
Okay, quiet. I go right straight. I i've already fucking lost my place
Oh, I
And then I don't know. I don't I don't I forget
I forget already. Oh
I forget already. I think it's right. No, where is it? Where am I?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I went straight
This is at the end of that hallway. So I go right
I don't remember. I don't remember that. I can you imagine making this game?
Oh, just stop don't like talking shit and just do it straight
straight
Right, so right right
I don't care
This is so fucking stupid I can't I can't do it anymore
Go left for correct. They're trying to follow this map. It's
I don't I don't know where I am now though. Where am I now people are trying to follow along with their own maps
I don't I have no idea where I am in this map. You finished what you fucking started
Here is a map with the starting location
If this is a picture of my ass, i'm gonna be mad
You made this bed now lying in it
No, I didn't I got to the end of a game that was made 25 years ago when they forgot how
Whatever
This is like the stone age of making video games. They were hitting they were they were bashing their computers with fucking stone tools
That's how old and shitty this is
Go into the maze and turn on the floodlight
This is so much easier than a fucking map
Go into the maze turn on the floodlight forward forward left forward left left left right forward. You're out of there. Thank you forward
forward
left
Forward wait what I just do is forward right left. No forward. Ah left forward
Forward left forward and then left three times
One hop this time
Two hops this time
Freestyle
I forgot where I am left three times double dream hand put your hand over there left left
Left, how many left is that? That was two lefts, right? I forgot. I actually do i'm so fucked up right now
How many left is that there's one more left, right?
That's it left and then a right and then forward so they go right and then forward
Okay, right and then well, let's just relax. You know, let's just chill
Before I swallow my own head and now forward stop playing this shit ass game. Jesus christ
It will I will
Forward. All right, and now we're out of there. Okay now scan the fucking door
Begging you to stop
Just hold on. We're almost up
Scan this door. I get the cube
I will not forget the door. Not this time
Are you in someone's intestines
Our squads
Chat is so divided
That's like please I hate this you'll have chats like you sleep in the bed that you made
Scan
That's actually what I had. You've got to be kidding me. I can't believe that this is like what I had to do
I just didn't scan the door
I'm sad
Possible language detected
It's some kind of alien language
And there it is
That's the I have the three. Oh
It's all right. This is it
It's time to end this
it's time
for this end
I think I just put in just two
Thank god. Okay. Now I know what to do. I've got everything settled and ready to go
Turn the music off. Oh shit. Okay, sorry
we're good
We're good
Just have to do this puzzle. Don't let them beat you music was good put on guin's
You want to put on then?
Maybe I will I am the fucking best put on come on gwen
Good job casey
My feet are starting to hurt airy. How did they put in moving walkways?
Tell me zack. Do you complain just to make conversation or do you honestly enjoy it?
Geez airy, my dogs are aching. Okay. Have you no sympathy? I'm saving my sympathy for you when you'll really need it
When you run out of things to scan that that one and then we're good casey
See if you can figure out what these panels are for. I will I will yes. Yes me me me me me me pick me
Pick me pick me pick me pick me me pick me
Pick me pick me pick me pick me. All right, uh
Oh
Do I have everything scanned? I think I already have all this shit. Yeah, I think I already have all this stuff
Don't I it was the important one right here, right? Yeah, I have I already have it all
Just go left three times
Shit, okay. Hold on
I already scanned these though. I've already scanned these I have to do it all I have to scan them all again
But it's they're already in my database
Praise yeah, the shit's all in the database already just activate them
Yeah, I just I think I just have to have seen them and then we can finally move on to the end of the game
But okay, we've seen it seen these
I don't have disk five
That doesn't exist and it yell at that person everyone yell at that person. Okay, good. We got that one now
Look at this one. All right. What are you doing? Everybody yell. All right, there it is
All right, we're good
Okay, see if you can figure out what's going on here. Okay, what look they're starting to read
Stop reading don't read in my face ever again
Okay scan this one. Thank you scan scan scan scan if we go left then we go left then we go left and it's over
Wait, I have to look at these
Okay, we're done. That's it
left left left left left left left left
The mca what what happened? He's already scanned. I already scanned them all. They're already in my database
You have to left. Okay, i'm gonna do exactly what I did last time
I scanned that one and then I just went left three times. This has been quite a journey. He's still here
No, um, this game sucks asshole
So if you do not do a very specific thing of sequences you cannot finish the game
So let's just get that really clear for that person that just showed up
Where's the one that I have to do exactly?
Game sucks. Gotta finish it. Well now it's kind of like remember um, remember clock tower
and we got like
Two-thirds of the way through clock tower and I was like, I hate this but I was like, oh, this is kind of fun
At the same time though. So I've had I had to finish it. Where is that stupid panel?
With the symbol that I have to scan this and then go left three times
You're having fun yet. Okay. Here we go. Ready scan this and then move left three times. That's what I did last time
Here patterns say left left left left
You didn't scan the blank object this all these things have already been scanned. I'm like replaying it
What's wrong with the mic quality? Oh, apparently things fucked up. I guess
Okay, so last time I did this I went left three times and then it just went to the cutscene
Now I did left three times and didn't do anything. I just went left twice or three like
Don't go into the menu
What do you mean go to the menu?
Wait, wait, wait, hold on a second
Are you telling me that you think that I now that I have this in the in the computer system that I can just skip
To the next scene
Wait a minute
Oh shit, I think we may have just found a loophole
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go you guys fucking how you just pumped
Purple, what was that demon noise? Somebody's my mic was messed up
It sucks fucking get out of this game. Um, we will
We're so close to the end
Worst noise from the worst stream
That's not even accurate. Can't you guys not you can't just say every stream is the worst screen
It's not how that works. You're all in big trouble
This one actually is omega low
All right, here we go
Thank you
I did it
Let's see the end
Quick. Well, i'm taking her gun and putting it in a bag
They're gonna fall out of that bag
That's what happens when you put the milk
and like
Oh
That's a bad grocery backpacking. So if you put like your your milk
Inside of a bag like that
And you don't have anything else to put the weight on the other side. You're gonna fuck yourself up
Now full thrust you guys thought this was porn week, this is torture with I torture you on screen
Same thing
I can't wait for bug snacks tomorrow. I still i've got a lot of 3do games to play. Well, maybe we'll go back to 3do on sunday
I'm playing bug snacks tomorrow
Some of that bacon wine you like so much hell tuba. What is he even saying? Tell me you could pass up
He's talking about bug snacks
Oh, he hates bug snacks
I don't know what you guys are talking about. He hates it
Okay now
Where are we going now? Why are we going so slow?
It's very
When there's no sense of urgency at all
Uh, are we gonna get a final boss reveal here?
I guess that just about does in case you haven't noticed eric. We've done all six doors
We're fresh out of options. No more options. No, we can backtrack and find the things we missed the first time around
What we don't have time to go through this entire ship again get close to that sun. Remember?
Um, I don't do that might as well face it area. This floating mausoleum is taking a plunge
And we're going along for the ride. No, i'm not doing without a fight zack
You know your problem is eric you've never known when the fight is over
Why are they giving up
You're actually once
What I always hoped I'd die in better company. Oh, yes. No. Yes. Yeah, I mean too
Squeaky clothes have you figured that out?
What uh, okay, wait yellow
blue
yellow red
Where am I supposed to go?
red green
Red, all right, we're gonna go to red scan that
All right. I have red
alien pattern chroma symbols
Why is it not over?
Uh, I I think it is
Oh, thank god. I scanned this fucking door. That would have been horrible if I didn't. All right. Um, what are you doing?
This is the we're at the end. This is disc four, man
I warn you jeremy beat this game and one billion is added to that. I don't agree with that
I don't agree with that. What are you talking about? I was just telling me to insert disc two
What what do you mean disc two?
I don't understand
Why do I have to this game's not 40 hours long. We're on the final disc
Wait, this is you can skip the red door if you already have the orb from the crew quarters
Did I get the orb from the crew quarters? I got a orb fuck if I know
No, what the hell is this?
Is I didn't I never went in here. Oh, i'm really good at these. I'm really good at these i'll do fine
I already know what it wants me to do
This is a little bit harder than I thought it was gonna be but it's all right
All right, I have to make everything on I got it then um
What is it what does it want to do?
Oh, this actually is the fine guys. This is the final puzzle of the game. Wait, what the fuck I have to do that
I have to do this
Holy it's yours top right no shit
Hey easy
Okay, hold on
It's close
Can I fuck it up?
Hold on wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Oh, I did it no
And then
It's the final puzzle of the game I got it
Hmm
None of you got shit on me
Ain't nobody got shit on me. Ain't nobody got shit on me
Now what?
Uh, congrats. You beat it on easy. Who cares?
Eat the bug. I don't think I can eat the bug
Uh, what am I supposed to be doing bug? Wait. No, I was already in here. What happened? Did I get an orb?
Did I get an orb? I don't remember getting an up an orb in here. Snap the disc. No, there's no
Does anybody remember if I got an orb in here? Can I tell if I have one? How many do I have?
I can't even I don't have that info. Is an orb an egg?
I'm so fucking close. I've got to just get I have to end this. I'm so close
It's something in this room. Is this the room where you paid no attention?
Absolutely, this is open. All right. This one doesn't open. Does this one open the whole game? You mean have I been in here?
I don't think i've been in here. Is it an orb? I can't select it
Orb orb orb. I can't get it. No, I can't get anything in here an orb in here
I don't I didn't there's not one in there
Is what happens when poop wine gets in your veins somebody you didn't say that. I just said that for you
Do I already have the thing?
You can skip the red door if you already have the orb from the crew quarters
But you're assuming this walked was assuming that I paid attention to anything that happened like four hours ago
I have this sneaking suspicion. He's nowhere near the end. No, this is the finale what they said's
Backtrack you added a backtrack section to the finale you assholes
Okay
This says go to the crew quarters kill the alien and get the orb
Uh, this is what is I don't see an alien. Didn't this alien die already?
Did we pull an orb out of this alien?
It didn't it was like oh there was something glowing. We pulled an orb out of the alien's head
Remember the alien that came down and died and the thing glue was glowing on his head
Didn't we pull it out of him? We pulled an orb out of his head. Didn't we I don't remember
It felt like it was like two weeks ago. No, you did not do that. Well, what the fuck am I supposed to do?
Glowed but I didn't interact with it. This is obviously the crew quarters
That's obviously an orb up there. Here we go. Here we go. Let's go. I have to look in each one of these holes
No way
I see something in there
No
No, I don't wanna
No, I have to look at all the holes
I'm gonna get jump scared turn on the light. I can't just be ready to kill the bug. I'm ready
I'm gonna laser this fucking thing the second it shows up. Oh Jesus
I'm gonna absolutely laser the fuck out of this thing
I try to think of the logic when you make a game like this, right? Like, okay
Let's have like 40 holes that you look in and each hole takes
Like six or seven seconds to look in I try to imagine the the the functionality here
Is it is it in is it in?
Turn the light on. I don't I have no light you have to activate night vision. There's nothing in the holes. What?
Bullshit, why would they have you do this top row top row top row top row?
You're doing it. Please need to check all the holes twice. No, you don't
The best part about this is the walkthrough just says go to the crew quarters kill the alien get the orb
They didn't they left out the part where you have to look in 100 holes. Is there another walkthrough?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait
Enter through the partially open door into the crew quarters and cross over to the far side come back to the door side
Swing right to the second column of triads click on the lower triad than the upper right hole
Can you say can you say that to me like in english?
Like come back to the door side swing right to the second column of triads click on the lower triad than upper
I can't I like I I can't understand what that's saying partially open door come back to the door side
Swing right to the second column of triads click on the lower
What?
Wait, go back towards the door
Okay, swing right
second column
lower ones top right
I can't believe this is in the game. I can't
I can't believe it. This is the guy that actively tortured his viewers
Yes, because what I want this should be a lesson and that you all right
Those you guys that are like teaching game design in college or whatever some of your professors here
Download just get this whole game and then make your class play it and say don't fucking do that. Don't do this ever
This is educational purposes at this point professor professor elbison. Why did you make us do this?
We had to look through all these holes
Yeah
Sucked didn't it?
Yeah, it was horrible and like the the part of the game we had like
scan the the
Scan the wall and stuff. Yeah, that part was bad too. Wasn't it?
Why did you make us do that?
And then I take my glasses off and put my fucking feet on the desk
Why don't you tell me?
You'll be the teacher and I have the teacher student cup. No, not bare feet
All right, where?
I'm told i'm getting tortured too. You know that right like i'm but I have to finish it
This is one of those torture streams where I torture the fuck out of myself for educational purposes only
I missed one
Okay, this is towards the door swing, right?
Was spam that coffee pasta again, please watch the speed run it was fake
Back it back to uh back to the channel that speed running it
Okay, let's see
he comes in
Torture, this is the definition of sunk cost fallacy. Yeah, but eventually okay
So you go towards the back and then bang of right?
It's almost over and I can't wait for it to be over and by the way, we're not done
Like i'm not done streaming after this
So it's the you go to the second one and then
I didn't already do that
Top left one. Oh my little one. I didn't look in I can't imagine sitting here and doing this not having like a walk
Okay, attack it. That was really scary
Shoot him. That was scary
You know
Give me the orb
Let me open give me the fuck out of here
BDSM stream show us your webcam and yeah, you're gonna get a bds
I turn on the webcam. I'm in like a bunch of bdsm gear. Now that would have been funny
That would have been really funny. It would have been worth the four and a half hours of torture
Okay, can I get the can I get the orb that fell out of his head?
Okay, I got it. We're done. Let's go you guys getting pumped. Here we go. We're out
Now we have to go to the yellow door. We're done. Watch out for the revved up heavy
That was
That was really good
Very very funny
Okay, yellow door. That's a brass beast. Not just any minigun. Oh natasha. You're right. No wrong. That's wrong
Why does that take my favorite thing of the day?
Just around one of these corridors it's just a heavy
That person made it all worth it. They really did
Here we go
Let's go. Let's go yellow door yellow door yellow door. Look what I found guys
The game fax walkthrough
This says go left straight straight right left straight straight right down straight left straight straight right straight down
Isn't this fun?
All right, uh go to the yellow door
yellow door
Yep, scan it. All right. They don't already have this
I already have the yellow door
Yeah, I already have this door. They did the puzzle already. Yeah, this shit just opens man
This this says go through the to go through the next door and then turn left
Okay, go through this door and there's apparently an orb in here and then just to the left of this door
There is an orb dispenser right here. Oh the other left. Oh, hi
Hi, all right
Uh, this is right. I can't really interact with anything even with the guide because it's like go
Okay, i'm gonna read the seal out
Click yellow to open it go through the next door turn left go through the door and turn around just to the left of
The door I was right. All right, then it says send it yellow
sent
Grab it. Nice orb number three
Pick it up. Everybody. Just pick your hands up
How did you stand up?
Everybody put your hands. Um just stand up. Put your hands up everybody just stand up
Everybody just stand up
What everybody just put your hands up everybody everybody you could just stand up
If you put your hands up, everybody just stand up
everybody put your hands up
Everybody to stand up
Now we go back to the hub and we have all three orbs and then we can finally end this
I
Don't even know which one of these doors goes back to the hub
We're gonna click on random ones and if we find the way back to the hub, I have no idea. I'm crying. I'm crying
I'm crying. I'm crying
Well, what happened? I'm not gonna that's like a sexual thing. I'm not gonna put that on screen. This is not the right way
Is it I'm lost wait? No, I'm lost. How do I go? What do I get out of here?
I don't know. I'm actually lost you can sit down here. This is the wrong way. Yeah backtrack
Absolute bullshit. I fall off here and I swear I'm gonna be so upset. What the fuck are we doing here? What is this?
How did I get a hair why am I here go back get me the hell out of there I'm rage finishing the game
This is a case study. This is an educational stream some reason they decided to put us upside down
Actually like this one you can't add any debt unless I agree to it I have to agree to it
Is there even a door here isn't this the way that I just came oh go to go that go to that blurry direction
Wait, this is not you see the link yet. Is it it's the wrong way again
It's just
unclear fucking anything
Just reload the last chapter from the menu, I hope this works
Wait, does that it's gonna work. Is this actually gonna work? I don't know man
Should I've not have done that?
Don't know I don't know if I should have done that. Oh my god. Should I not have done that? Oh my god
Oh my god, what do I do? What have I done? What the fuck did I do?
Please don't tell me I fucked this whole thing up. I'm not I'm telling you right now
I'm not going back and doing this shit again. I would rather eat my own hand
I'd rather you cut my fucking hand off and put it in the oven and cook it like 350 for two hours
And I eat it on stream. I'd rather do that then go back and do the like last 45 minutes
I know I said I'm gonna shit my pants like shit all over me and then before I just gonna go on back and beat it
I'd rather eat myself. I'd rather fucking pull it myself. Right. I've said this like three times. Do I have the orbs?
Please tell me I have I don't want to go back. I don't want to go back. I can't go back
I can't go back. Is there with me to check? Oh my please god. I hope I don't have to go back
I hope I don't have to if I I please I have all the orbs, right?
I got them all and I just went I just did different scenes
Definitely keeps it stored in the cache. I know it does
Stored in the cache because the other ones were stored and we jumped around to different sections of the game. It's ready
It's here comes the three orbs. We have them. Oh, wow. You found them. Wow, you got all the orbs put the orbs in here
You did a great job Casey. Excellent work. We all love you and you're all very you're smart. You're very smart
We don't did it and here are your three orbs
Here are the orbs
Hey
No, it's not even
Why
Why why why why why?
Why I know it I know what they all are. I'm gonna eat my fucking hand
Add this to worst meltdown of the year. I don't care. This job. I have to I'm gonna eat my fucking hand put it in the oven
Open this fucking door right now. I know where they all are. I know where they are. You're building the guillotine
I'll put my head in that thing
Open the fucking door. What are you doing?
What? Oh
Man, this this game probably costs like 30 million dollars to make crack each disc in half when you're done
Why I don't even know why I listen somebody said hey skip but it was perfect in perfect reason though
It was very reasonable thing to say like go to the menu and skip all this and then you were right
You were so right that would that made perfect sense. You're a monster. I know that's okay. I'll wear that
I'll wear that today
But we're like of one cutscene away from beating this game and I cannot I can't get to the end of this shit
And then give the fuck up. This is perseverance. I know exactly where it is. Just get it
I know the other one is just get it and then just keep track of where you are. I bet this left not that way
Okay
Okay, so when I come out I take a left and leave
Done shoot the alien in the head. This game sucks though. What the hell I know I know and I knew it
Okay, after our number two, I knew it sucked but it kept me here. It
It's forcing me to beat it with like radiation rays
I don't know what this thing's emitting but it's making me want to do it
See this look at how much fashion this was this time. We're good done. I already got one. Why is he dead?
What are you talking about? So I have wait I have this one. I have this I have it
Why do I you need to go yellow instead? But now hold on I didn't turn I'm not softlocked with the exit over here
Default return scene. No, no, it's because the yellow one. I didn't turn it in it remembers that I turned in this one
I didn't give the yellow one yet. That's true. Okay. All right, makes sense. I have to change fucking discs again
There is no God I know this now
this is the evidence of it imagine if you're one of the game developers and you happen to stumble upon this stream and
this guy watching it and seeing how much everyone hates this and
Then you hear somebody you you read somebody in the chat that says there is no God because of this game in this frame
Like you gotta click the X and just like kind of go like take a shower
like you can't
Somebody's playing the tidalis encounter. I like was a game designer on that. There is no God because of this game
Oh
What the fuck? Holy shit shuttle down
What's wrong with you guys? You don't understand. We were working on computers that had like 56k motive
And loading up one of these FMVs into our program took three days
Fuck all of you assholes. How dare you this game was like
Gold back 30 years ago. We're gonna let this asshole talk shit about it. I mean, they're right there. You know, they're right there
All right, let's get it. Let's get it. Let's get it. Let's get it. Let's get it. Let's get it
And the left the orb. All right, bang a left and when we come up with being in a right remember that
Let's get lost Omega Loaf
There it is
Excuse me. Give me that orb. I'll take it who tis grab that shit. There's no skipping cutscenes
I wish I could add up. All right out of here bang a right straight through that door
Get me the fuck out of here and the game and it you're aging your chat by playing this look
It's only been like, okay
I have probably like six thousand hours on stream four or five of these are day Dallas encounter
That's like zero point zero zero zero one percent of all the streams I've done
That's not so that means a ninety nine point nine nine nine nine nine percent of all streams were fucking incredible games
Well besides half of them that we're not very good. So I'd say like
Forty nine point nine nine nine percent are very good games
All right, he keeps doing he keeps playing trash games over and over again, but they're the most charming except for this one fuck this
I'm gonna stream I'm doing a spite stream. All right, whatever fine
Well, you're gonna you can upload pictures of me like then talk shit to me on my own new stream
You're gonna talk you're gonna do like a shit talking stream
He's gonna restream my stream and then talk a bunch of shit about me
Yeah, yeah, you're gonna be a big trouble if you do that one
Now what what that's all the orbs go to the orange door. He didn't know
New offer, please stop. Oh my fucking god, please stop stop make it stop
Why do I look like that what's wrong with my eyes? All right, let's go. This is the final door. I know it
This is the last door. I know it for a fact
It's free after you end the game on disc three. That's kind of weird that an hour ago
I'm just going by what the we're in the finale
The finale was two hours ago. Yeah, it's a long finale
Orange door go to the medical center. Wait, isn't this the and we already been down here
I think I was so excited for the stream came a whole hour early for this
All right. Well, yes, you know what? Oh, we've got something over here. Oh
Something over here
Was this I didn't I didn't scan the orange door
There's only like five sentences left in the walkthrough guys. Don't worry. We're gonna get through this together
We're gonna get through this. I know I'm like talking like this a zombie apocalypse right now
We're gonna get through this just stay together. Oh, fuck you. Oh, please end the game
I'm done going as fast as I can. I'm going as fast as I can Nevada stream
I'm going faster than that. I don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't okay
Why don't you get up and help why don't you get up and help me skin the door?
I can't believe I have to scan another door. How did I not get this skin?
7,000 people were tortured today in a freak streaming accident
How would it be a freak streaming accident if I'm deliberately torturing you? There it is. Okay, go on in
Or a freak streaming accident where a guy
Tortured seven thousand people for five hours
No, I didn't like leave the stove on
You're the Joker. I'm not the Joker. I'm the Riddler now anybody that says they're the Riddler is actually the Joker
Anybody that says they're the Joker is actually the penguin that recycled joke. Well, maybe okay. Wait, what's this?
I touch anything else in here before I end, you know, we're in the last two sentences of
the
Game, you know what I mean guys, you know, I mean, I actually played penguin in the show Gotham. You're pretty talented actor
He's actually pretty good that what's an actor's name that actor seriously really good or but number four done got it
I have all the orbs
Now what return that go back with the orb you're fucked dude four of ten
You need six. I mean six. It's not six orbs. There are six doors. Therefore. There are six orbs. No, no, no
No, that's not accurate. That's not accurate. It's not true. That's not I have the I have the guide right in front of me
The guide is right here across the guide Pepe left. Yeah, why wouldn't I first stage?
I thought you said first disk of grief, which would have been much funnier
Just you guys
The five discs of grief wait, what do you mean? No, I don't I don't know there's no more discs
What do you mean? I have to get well, I don't know where they are
The guy didn't say to get these these spheres the guy did not say to get the spheres. Where is these other spheres? What?
Ah
Ain't worth it. It's been five hours
Six orbs who is this for you hate playing and we hate watching
It's not for me and it's not for you so who is this for I don't know who this is for
I can't even tell you I wish I could say it's for me. It's not
What what's this for? It's just it's to complete it. It's just playing itself turn it off
Stop then. Uh, but what I
But I'm busy much time in here, but there's so much time in here. Well, wait, let me just see how quickly this could be
I'm already at four out of six stones
stones
Guys, my go XLR is broken. I can't even mess with any of the settings. Does it sound like this the whole time?
All right, what we where are the last two cubes? There are five orbs. All right, there's only five
Where's the last one? Where's that last one blue hole?
Was that last one guys? They're not seven orbs. This is five blue hall. Hold on
Okay, I'm facing the statue click blue and see the orbit. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
We go go go go go go go go go go go go go. This is green, but fuck. It's okay
Go back. We're gonna go through the blue door. I got the I know where the blue one is blue door
Let's go. I saw the blue
Orb up top. I already have the blue door scanned. I got it. Okay, so we go through here. Just go in
I'm trying to hit blue. There's three you got it quick. Now. I know exactly what I'm doing
There's so many fingerprints on the bottom of that disk. I don't care
Okay, so when we're facing the statue click blue and see the orbit puzzle
There's a statue in this room. Look for that statue and then the orb is in the statue
This is very is huge room. The orb is inside of Casey. Well, you just fucking ruin the game
Okay, there's an orb inside of this. Here we go. Use blue
How do I use blue trying to use blue when facing the statue click blue and see the orbit puzzle
Shit. All right, we go. Now what?
What did I just do?
Okay, what four of the planets are directly movable call them a B C and D
Okay, or the planets are movable. They're ordered in the bottom right selection window
You must move the fifth planet over the Sun move a to 11 o'clock
Which one is a move a to wait analog move a to 11 o'clock. I need the analog clock
Hold on move a to 11 o'clock
I don't even understand what the fuck you're talking about. Am I move am I moving the planet right now? Okay
Well, here's like 11. I can't like directly touch them. Okay, so this is this one's here a at 11 o'clock
be at
C to 430
C to
12 1 2 3
430 what the fuck are you talking about put it in 120? What? I?
Don't like understand what where's this fifth planet? Look at the bottom left. Yeah, but this am I how I
Don't even know what I'm looking at here. This is the planet in the middle, but I'm not moving this planet
How do I do how do I move the actual planets instead of just but why does it put a to like 1130?
Like what is even talking about?
ragget like
Jesus what the hell is this?
Okay, put a to 11
Alright a at 11
C 430
See it's like that's like kind of 430 right B to 120. Where is it? It's kind of 120
It's like 11 right up here
Now what move to face the statue and click send that's for what?
Isn't this the one I'm moving up here? No, look at the yellow dot. What planet am I actually trying to get to?
This is too fucking much
This is just this is just bizarrely set up. This is put this to 11 o'clock. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
Wait like this like put that there. Let's see 430
Wasn't I I was already doing that. All right, this is like 430
D 120 it's already there
Wow, what this is C C is that 120 a at 11 C at 430 D at 120
Oh
I'm too drunk for this. I feel like a microwave
Then send it. Well, no, this this has to be doesn't have to be I have to be over the this right
It doesn't say anything about B
Solution move a to 11 C to 430 D to 120 you might need some minor adjustments
But you do not have to move C at all
What B is they it's wrong. It's a typo C to 430 a B to 430
C you don't have to move C at all. So where was C in the beginning?
It literally says solution move a to 11 C to 430 D to 120. You don't have to move C at all
They meant B at the end well, how is it a to 4 a to 11 a to 11?
C to 430
E to
They're already so you don't have to move B at all. What what what is that it?
All right, send it. Oh, it's wrong. B was good. So the so the so the guide was wrong make minor adjustments
That's not 120
12 what this is 120 right here
By the way, there is no minute hand. So what are you talking about? He's been looking at the wrong guide
Give me give me another guide. This one's fucking wrong. There's no minute hand
Omega lol stacum's brain
Somebody just had it planet 1 to 430 planet 2 3 planet 3 3 planet 4 of 330
That's completely
Inaccurate from the guide that I'm looking at right now. I think you might have a case of a CD
Remember chat left an hour ago. You're talking to nobody. This is on easy
Reset the puzzle. Hold on that reset. What is it? What this is? I don't think I can even reset
I don't I don't think I can reset this. I literally can't reset it
I have to turn the console off or restart the chapter. I'm not doing that. I'm gonna do it for him
Read this and it's a paste bin. I don't know what the fuck that is
Why does this have to suck? I can't stop
No, the guides were written like 25 years ago. So, of course, they're gonna be fucking inaccurate and messed up
There's only one walkthrough of this game that exists on game fax. It is one person on PC
Alright, what's that guy? Give me that guy again. There we go. Let's go. Let's go. Here it is
What does he got? What's he got? Let's see how fucking wrong this was. Okay, the one is completely wrong, by the way
So a is down here. See is fuck
Okay, a is actually right here a is literally right here it was completely fucking wrong
B is also right there
The guide was
1000% wrong
C is down at around 6 o'clock
Where is D? D is top left D
There it is. Count
This counts, right? I'm watching his stream. He's having trouble with it, too. Almost there. What happens when he gets it?
He's having trouble, too. Yeah, this like sucks. He's having trouble. I'm getting it too. I'm right there with you man
Oh, is that not it? That's not it
Yep, bunch of you guys had it wrong. Okay. What the fuck is this doing? What's this? What does he do? Quick, tell me what you do
What do you do? Use the blue code. It's the infinity stones. I
Can't believe I'm fucking still here doing this. What am I doing? Am I what's happening? Am I doing this?
Hey, this is it. I need one more after this is the green door
That green door man
Well, I need green hall. Okay. Okay. I know what to do. Oh, would you what would you rate this game so far?
What would you rate punching yourself in the stomach as hard as you can?
We're like a zero ain't I'd read it higher than this. Yeah, we lost like a thousand viewers. It's alright
It don't matter. They'll see you tomorrow for bugs next. I am need to spite-feet this game
This is the worst game you've ever played it might be but at least I can say I finished it
I'll be able to wear that on my sleeve forever. We have one more door to go into you haven't finished it yet
I'm about to the worse than saw to a thousand times worse saw to is would be at the game Awards ahead of this
All right green door turn around when you get to the black opening there's an orb dispenser
It's the worst than watchdogs Legion that stuff
You know why because I'm still playing this screen was fun, it's just awful in every way
That's so
It's chaotic neutral. I have green right now. I don't I don't know. I don't have a green door
I
Pair budgets with a current Ubisoft game
Friday the 13th. Oh, it is Friday the 13th. Maybe that's why I'm so fucked up. Is that why I'm so fucked up right now
I want to do this and like did they torture myself? Is this why it might be?
Actually really might be why yeah, this is like a scary screen screen. You're right
Well tomorrow's a Friday the Saturday 18th. Okay, I'm concerned now because of what I just said
Tomorrow's Friday the Saturday 18th tomorrow's Friday the Saturday
I think I'm concerned now what I tried to say was tomorrow was Saturday tomorrow was Saturday
For it. I don't know what I was trying to say there. What was I doing? I don't know
How often does a Friday the 13th come by the way is it once a year once every like few years once every few years
Does that happen every year happens yearly? His brain is rotting
Someone should check on you
Okay, so here is why this game is dumb. This is where you get the orb
These my children are crying German. I don't want to see this anymore
This shouldn't be here anyways, this should be studying or something
be
playing
Friday yeah, they should be playing should be making like a fort in the house of
pillows
mattress toppers
Cardboard. All right, let's get out. How do I get out of here?
I flew in this way. You don't I don't have to go through the maze again, right?
No, I can't probably just walk forward from here. I don't know why everyone hates the stream. I'm literally. Yep. Thanks
I have to go through I actually have to go through this. It's alright. I think I still have the
Escape right was it somebody give me link it to me. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Okay forward
forward
Thanks to the stream. I have a really bad toothache and watching you suffer helps
Well, I'm sorry about your teeth. Hope that feels better soon. Let me go left three times
Left again. I just fed my cat and took a shower. I thought we were on disc for we were
Originally one more and then we go right and forward build a Ford on stream
That should be kind of fun. Can you hurry up? My sister's giving birth and I kind of want to be there
Oh, don't worry. You're not missing much. It kind of looks like this. I
Made it. All right. I'm out of there now. We're gonna go back to the chamber is this way. It's for let's go
I got all the spheres. It's time to end this the dead
Unless Ted has the dead ass encounter. It's me the fucking task robot here with all the jewels
All right, put them in the device and let's turn on the ship and leave who dare summit me
Well, that was I thought it was gonna be much bigger and scarier it's a Furby it's Elmo
Did you summon me mr. Noor?
What are you summoning me for?
Hold on a little while
Put them into my sphere
The goals you see you're a genius
I'm getting a little it's getting that's turning into Eddie
Yeah, dude, let me try I don't have a human hand. Oh, all right, it's not me
Guys guys you're accidentally bowling under my name
My can I get to
slot on this thing
Let me do it thanks, I think Casey do it I'm the one that got them all I
Can't even do one. I'm the one that actually wouldn't make them all up
Now what I don't know go to orange door the guide says I have to get like an alien hand. I
Have to go get an alien hand didn't get the alien hand who will activate the final device burn
Yes, it was the whole thing was like a paragraph. Look, this is what it says
This is the end after that. This is causing me mental harm
But what what look why don't you just mute the stream for a minute and just go open up another tab
just go to like
relaxing puzzles or
relaxing music and
We're gonna sneeze go to Pornhub. Look, I cannot tell you what you can and can't do on your own computer
Some of you guys write this is the weird thing. So you might be on Pornhub right now on another tab
I don't know
You really might be there and you might be listening to me talk
Which is kind of weird turn me off turn me the fuck up turn me off right now
I don't do that X out of my window and just did go out of here
What does it want to do do not have me on turn me off with that?
I want you to do that like red then blue what click red then click
Red then blue then are what I mean click up left up high is a control device
You can close in on to operate it click red then blue violet orange and violet. I can't touch this color
I can't touch these. Okay, click red then blue violet orange violet. Oh
Okay, let's get it
Good MPC sound. Oh
It is cut it out. Quit it. Oh
Stop. Oh, oh
Stop that stop that. Oh
Quit it. What do I do now for this stream? I loved Jerma. Hey for this dream
I thought I said the same thing about you and now you said that and I don't know how I feel about you know
Okay. Now I have this hand. Okay now I go back with the hand eat the hand. All right
Cut my nose hasn't been cleaned yet. You're losing viewers. Look, I know look
I've been losing viewers for the last like three hours. I don't think I'm aware of this. I mean, all right
I know here's the career ending stream. Sorry. It's fun. It's fun. We're outlasted
What did I fart oh
Right, right
As I said, you both blamed it on me it's one of you two wait, that's not what I had to do
No, what the fuck?
What was the hand? Where is it? Look up you fucking idiot? I'm not looking up because you told me to insert disk one
Why are we doing earthworm Jim where did that come from I'm bashing my head against the wall auto-tune
I thought I thought I'd sit on this is it. This is the end. We've made it to the end of final cutscene on disk one
alien hand
Why did I play this for six hours?
This was supposed to be like a 3DO grab bag stream not die Dallas encounter full play through
Job let's go Casey
We just got going into this thing's mouth
Is a case I got a bad feeling about this. We've gotten this far Zach. Just stay cool. Stay cool. I'm gonna stay cool
It's gotta be 85 in here and rising
He was disguised all along
Yes, I have one case check them out Harry. You see that. What was he disguised as a navigational console this guy?
I don't mind if we hijack his ship see what Casey comes up with. I shoot him
Looks like he's studying some kind of readout
Why he's adjusting those light beams?
What's that thing in the center? I don't know things are starting to heat up around here. Look we gotta do something we can do something now
Oh shit he sees us. Go for the nav consoles. I'll cover you. Wait, don't shoot it. It's unarmed. We gotta try and communicate
How come on this thing isn't exactly happy to see us Harry. But that's the statue guy
Lower your weapons Zach. Show it we mean no harm. This is like the guys. Oh, he's putting his hands up
How does he know that?
Harry it didn't work. Get to those consoles
Hey, whoa, I guess we're killing it. What?
I shot him in his brain. Is he dead?
What what am I supposed to do? There's another alien?
There's two aliens. This is like the this is boss two
Zach get up
It has sort of giant egg. All right
Tighten the light beams
What Gator what on the weapon on overload? Oh, no
You took a gun to the grenade what the fuck
I didn't think I look I did it right. Whoops. Okay. All right. No, no, no, no, no, I have to I
Can't even react to this shit man, it's just so stupid. All right interact with the console
Doesn't sack a dead, okay, I'm moving to moving to art. Okay, I got it red orange red
Green blue green blue
violet blue
Okay, touch. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do analyze? Yes. No, no, press this button press green
What do you want me to do? I can't
This is Ridley
Doon doon doon doon doon doon doon doon doon doon. All right, but I don't know what to press go back before Zack is dead
I need more orbs
Okay, the nav console redo the other scene
Go back you have to talk to the art. Wait, I did okay go back and talk to the alien
Talk to the alien
Talk talk to the alien
None of you work after the elevator ride
You will see a live alien when when they ask you to talk to it send four five two
What is four five two is okay, I have a question is this four five two, this is four five two, isn't it?
All right
Ready, how did it gain viewers?
Don't let them shoot it
I shot him in the brain his his brain just evaporate. Let's go Casey
Sacrifice your friends. I did that twice
Okay, here we go. They all fly away. We go into this room
It's really not that hot there is talk to it
I see what Casey comes up with all right talk
He's adjusting those light beams four five two
Four five two
Now I'm pressing a
No, no talk talk talk four five two, I'm pressing a communicate communicate
Send it. I'm hitting a
Something's coming out. Is it is it angry?
Chrysalis this is fantastic
We must be the first humans ever to witness this
Hope we don't look like appetizers
It's different from the other creatures. We've seen
Look, the other one is bowing
Maybe this is the new queen
Uncut gems music. Oh
I miss log the force field created by the creatures which called themselves study
Protected us and the ship from the intense heat
The cranny there fled or were destroyed when we passed through the stars Corona the newly born Queen possesses
race memory and incredible psychokinetic abilities
She improved Casey's translation abilities and then answered many of our questions
Why is she talking like Cartman?
Say void, friends. May our paths cross again. Farewell.
Here comes like the rock song.
For a second I thought Tia Carrera was a developer in the game.
I was like, are you serious?
Sorry, sorry, can you hear me now? Sorry, sorry, I'm trying to get you out.
Wait through the credits. You should feel ashamed of yourself for doing this.
Look, I feel fine. I feel great. I just feel, I just kind of have a headache now.
Best boy.
Troubles are far too greedy.
Cheers.
Time for Windows 2.0. That's very old.
There you think you are. Get to those consoles.
Did I shoot her accidentally? That's not what I wanted to do. No, that was wrong.
Okay, I turned it off. I just turned it off. I turned it off. I got out.
Wait, the camera's on and I got no clothes on.
I think that's kind of where I have to end this stream. It's been six hours. I gotta go.
Alright, we're gonna go back to 3DO on probably Sunday.
One game, Andy. 3DO was your greatest mistake.
No, I'm playing 3DO. I love this console. I just don't, I'm playing 3DO later this weekend. I'm gonna do it.
We're playing Bugsnax tomorrow, and then maybe Bugsnax on Sunday. Maybe 3DO next weekend.
I don't know if that, there's still like, well, there's like 20 games on 3DO.
I just made everybody, I just tortured everybody.
You literally, you literally made a stream of Die Dallas Electric Boogaloo.
Okay. Yeah, Bugsnax is tomorrow. Yeah, I've played Demon's Souls. I don't have a PlayStation 5. I forgot it came out.
I didn't pre-order one. I didn't even know it came out.
Italics told me that it came out. I didn't even know it came out.
I forgot it even existed, which is fine. Don't worry, I'll get one eventually.
I will get one eventually, and I'll play the games on it.
There's only like three games on it anyways, and the first generation, the first generation of new games on a new console
is always, always just games that were already in development for the old console
that they ended up just pushing forward to the new one anyways.
So I'm fine for like another six months. Don't worry.
There's a few games that were made specifically for the PS5, but besides that, I mean, whatever.
I'll get it like in a few months. That's COPE. Yeah, it is.
All right, I'm going to send you guys to, I'm going to send you guys to Joel actually,
because you know what Joel is playing tonight. Joel is playing Half-Life Alyx.
So that's pretty pog. That's a huge pog.
So I'm going to send you guys to Joel. It's actually a good streamer.
All right, you're banned for life. I'm, I'm, no, you know what, let's go.
Let's go. Where's that comment? Where is it?
You're getting banned for life. I'm going to do it myself.
You're going to be the screenshot German out of five banned you for life.
Good ending or right? I already got the good ending. We just did it.
They like solved all the world's problems and we got all their like devices.
Let's actually, let's go make sure I didn't miss any money or anything.
Thanks for watching everybody. We'll see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Bugsnax. Playing that for a little bit.
Give a very special shout out and thank you to Sharfers, the streamer.
Speedruns Die Dallas encounter. The only reason why I was able to even complete the game is because he exists.
It's the only reason why. Without that we would have to rely on 20 year old game facts write ups.
The MVP. Let me minimize this though.
Let me minimize that. I think I X'd out of a ton of things. Hold on.
Yeah, I did. Just want to see if I didn't want to miss any, if there was any large bit drops or donations or anything.
There was. There was a shitload of community subs too.
We had 10 from Putrefreshen. We had 10 from Niershu. We had 10 from Anonymous.
We had 10 from TheWheelOfRime and then 5 from Illusiary.
Thanks guys. Thank you, thank you, thank you. Thank you for your community subs.
And then there was 50 bucks. There was 5,000 bits from Scrumpleton.
Thanks for the 50 bucks. A gigantic bit drop.
He wasted his ego stream on this. Yeah, I did. I did. It was in a panic. It was in a rage.
I need to look at this. Why is it Peter?
Don't go to twitch.tv slash German 985 on November 13th, 2020.
Worst mistake of my entire life, Lois.
It wasn't the worst mistake of your life. Eating the McChicken that you put in the fridge.
That's been an uncountable, unrememberable amount of days.
But you hope it was less than 5. And you eat it.
Was the worst mistake of your life. So don't even be cute with me.
Alright, I'll see you guys tomorrow. Go say hello to Joel.
I played through that game. I beat Half-Life Alex. Let's see how Joel does.
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Good night, goodbye.
And thank you for joining me on a stream that a lot of people were very, very happy with.
I can't even fucking talk.
Alright, I'll see you tomorrow for Bugsnax. Eat em up.
Good night, guys. I'll see you tomorrow.