Good morning, what's up? Welcome to another stream. Today, we're gonna play the Chronicles of Riddick
Assault on Dark Athena. But actually, it's the Chronicles of Riddick Escape from Butcher's Bay,
which is Assault on Dark Athena, is the game. It's a remake of Butcher's Bay that added a
campaign on top. Some weird development issues happened. This game is a remake of the last game
with a small campaign added on top, so we're playing the remake. This is bullshit. Dark Athena
is the sequel. Dark Athena is the sequel, but it has a remade Butcher's Bay in it. Go look it up.
There's some, there's a lot of things with how assets were being sold during, I believe, was it
was a THQ? I don't want to make this up. Let's see. I think it was something to do with that,
right? Saw waiting room? Well, don't worry. Saw 2 is going to be really soon. Uh, yeah, we're
gonna play. I have a confession to make though. I have never seen any of the Riddick movies at all.
I have no idea what this is. I don't know. All I know is that the character wears sunglasses. I
have no idea what's going on. I remember watching the trailer list for this movie back in the day.
There's like four of them or three of them or something and it's, and they were pretty
people liked them. From my understanding, this game is not just a movie game. This is a completely
new campaign that Vin Diesel himself oversaw. Am I getting that right? So this is not just a
movie tie-in. Vin Diesel made this game. Like he made it happen. He's in it. He voices it. He
wrote all the dialogue and he programmed all the encounters. So can we give it up for Vin Diesel
for just a moment, please? All right. Are you guys ready? I'm, I'm ready to go. I've been ready for
about 25 minutes. It just, I have no references to make for the Chronicles of Riddick. So making a
title was impossible. So I just reached into the YouTuber handbook and I got a good one.
Okay. Here we go. This is Escape from Butcher's Bay, but it's Dark Athena. See? See? See, I told
you. There were people in chat going, you idiot. Oh, who's the idiot? Huh? It ain't me. Literally,
no one did that. I'm making up somebody to be angry at. No one did that. Not one person. I'm
just making everybody think that there's some, some person in the chat room that I'm angry at.
This did not happen. I just want to make sure that's pretty clear. All right, let's go. This
is from 2004, by the way. Oh, we got to test the audio. One, two. We synced up. Sounds good to me.
Slightly off. It's delayed. My voice is early. Hold on. This is really important to do this.
Otherwise it's going to be fucked up the whole stream. All right, hold on.
One, one, two. Here we go. One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two. One, two.
One, two. Butcher's Bay. I'm going to play on normal. I don't want to fuck this up. 2004 hard,
guys, is not the same as 2020 hard. 2004 hard is you get shot once and die. I'm not doing it.
No, this is 2004. This is Escape from Butcher's Bay. What even is this bit? What bit? I'm picking
a difficulty. I don't understand this joke. I mean, what, what is this? Is this like pick a door and
one of the doors is going to have like something funny behind it? Difficulty bit. All right. I'm
going to just pick normal. I don't care. Make fun of me. You can make fun of me all stream if you
want. All right. It's already done. It's that's too late. I can't go back. All right. Quiet. We're
moving again. They just transmitted a safe route through the minefield. You think Huxley's memory
is that Hannibal Lecter? What's going on? Look at you, Riddick and all is forgiven.
And I think you're bounding plus 50 plus 50. Greed is an ugly thing. You're in no position to
negotiate, Riddick. I'm excited. This is a very highly requested game. I'm excited to play this
one. Oh yeah. I forgot you don't like this part. Statistically landings are the most dangerous.
You got nothing left to live for, Riddick. I do. I shut up with you. You're already counting it,
aren't you? I said shut up. I feel like he could just like duck down and slip out of this.
He could just go underneath the bottom bar. All right. Here we go. One person. You're right. One
person requested this game. They're going to be really happy. Hey, hold it. You go where I say
when I say. What happened? Oh, this game sucks though. You don't know that. Who told you that?
You know, how do you have any idea? Walk up to a character and press Y to initiate dialogue mode.
Press Y to speak after selecting your response. Why did that happen? Did I game too hard?
Okay. Walk up and initiate conversation. Hey, don't fucking move. What about the guy behind
you? He's moving. Johns know he should cool down. Scare Johns about being ripped off. Scare him.
Today, Johns, you get fucked. You don't move until I say so. Hey, hey, hold it. You go where I say
when I say. He just stepped on his head. I just wanted to look around. Wait, am I not supposed to
move? Why? It's because I know why. I know why. I know why. I know why. I know why. I know why.
This is kind of loose. That's not good. I got to tape this. I don't know about you guys,
but seriously, I'm like a fucking animal when I have a controller and I have to tap a button.
When I tap right trigger, I'm actually pressing every button and I'm squeezing really hard.
The thing that's holding the battery on is going to fall off. Don't fucking move.
Today, Johns, you get fucked. You don't move until I say so. Hey, hey, hold it. You go where I say
when I say. I just wanted to look around. This is red light, green light.
Yeah. Wait, what? You didn't hear me? How do you not hear him? Info, sneak up behind Johns and
grab him by pressing left trigger to silently break his neck. You can also perform a faster
but louder neck break by pressing right trigger. Break his neck. I don't want to. Why don't you do
it? Oh, it should break his neck. DNA protection learns the hard way. We should get moving.
How do I get in? Where am I? Get in. Get in here quick. Oh shit, I got fucking killed.
What? Jump. It goes into third person. That's awesome. Oh, and you got a Dark Souls drag
down. Are you kidding me? Cigarettes. That's a pat. Yep. Extra content. Butcher Bay is now
available in the extra content menu. I think it's too dark. Did I make the brightness a little bit
higher? I'm not a boss. How? Make it a little bit higher. A little bit higher. 55. It's a little
better, I think. OK, so now now what do we do? Inmate on the run. Wait, you can fight hand to
hand with enemies. Press RT to punch and LT to block. Try to move in different directions and
punch at the same time to perform different strikes. Unauthorized. My god. OK, I think he's
dead. How can you be unauthorized to pick up a gun? I don't understand. Oh, security card.
They just showed you that they're locked. Yeah, well, I'm what do you want to do? They already
explained it. Yeah, but I someone said my controller was like falling out and I was I'm trying to be
very, very careful with the controller right now. Anything over here? No. On stealth mode,
press X for stealth. You sneak silently. A blue screen effect indicates that no one can see you.
Well, he can't see me. It's just me in the shower, man. Drop him. Yeah. Yeah.
Hide the body. It's completely dark. Hold the left bumper down and move left, right or forward
and lean in that direction. Releasing you will lean, do lean mode. Drag a body, stand close to
the body and press Y. Press Y again. You must be in stealth mode to do this. OK, there are probably
other guards around. Hide this body in the dark or his friends will be alerted when they find him.
It's like Hitman. Wait, me being invisible, does that make him invisible too? What am I supposed to
do with this guy? Air. Maybe a vent. Throw him in the vent? Leave him in the dark. To climb up
something, press Y. OK, well, I'll leave him over here. This is dark. You can tell when it's dark
because it gets blue. Yeah, he's good. The third person is, I love that. It's so funny. My games
stopped doing that, didn't they? How do I climb up? Use a hang rail. Look at it and press Y or
jump onto it for pressing A. There's a hang rail above you. Drop him a hang rail, press Y. OK.
Hang rail. What else you got? You can drop down on enemies that are far below to kill them and
break your fall to your best. That's so clumsy. I thought it was going to be like,
use your intuition to throw a batarang. No, no, no, no. Just fall on people and kill them.
I mean, I can't even see. All right, I got to hide this guy. OK, we're good. I mean, it's very,
you're going to obviously see that, dude, but whatever. Scan my eyes. What does he want me to
do now? Can I open this door? On the vent? He came out of here, right? Have something on you?
You like a key card? Let's climb it again. I'm sorry. This whole game looks like this,
like a layer of cooking oil put on it. PS3. No, no, no, no. You got it wrong. You got it wrong.
This is the Xbox 360. It's a much better console than PS3. No, shut up. PS3 is better. No, idiot.
Rating. Med station. Takes away the hurt, leaves the pain. It's like Half-Life style med stations.
I don't feel like I'm really small. This nano med health unit is empty. In order to refill it,
you need to find a refill cartridge and then replace the empty one in the nano med unit by
pressing Y. OK, what do I have? Two chunks. You can use this refill cartridge to restore an empty
nano med health unit. That's why it doesn't do the Half-Life sounds. I wouldn't want to use this.
Don't you think you'd like to have like a bruised elbow? Don't you think you just want to let it
heal in like a few days? All right, does this thing? OK, that's ready to go. That's horrifying.
All right, we got to be ready. We got to lean. Disarm our guard. Press right trigger when he
tries to hit you. It was a parry? Just take the gun. Got it. Shoot. Wow, you have a gun with no
bullets? What the hell are you doing? Is this just for show? Hold down right bumper and move around
to select a weapon. Oh, he did. No, that's a pack of cigarettes. He's got too many bullets.
Tools? He was on break? So? All right, let's go. Dude, I don't care if somebody finds him.
What does that even matter? While hanging, you can move sideways. Oh, no, somebody's going to
find him. I don't care. What are Riddick's superpowers? Press right stick to initiate
weapon melee attack. Oh, he's cool. Oh, he can see in the dark. All right.
OK, there's one. Is there only one there? Let's see. There's one. This guy's just talking about
how bad his day was. Just the same shit that I do when I'm in like a car and there's nobody with me.
I just like go off. Go off, dude. Let's see it. Let's do that forever. No, break his neck. Break
his neck. Put this gun away. Break his neck. Left trigger. Good. He's talking about this guy. All
right. I've gotten right. Oh, there's 47 bullets now. We went from zero to this guy has way too
many. Let's go on the sewers. Where's the way down? Sewers. Jump down. Cool. Oh, the gunplay. Oh,
the gunplay. You know what I mean? It's actually kind of terrible. Well, not my favorite. Do you
have a flashlight for those of us that can't see in the dark, Riddick? Yes, you do. Thank you. The
flashlight attached to shotguns can be used by person. Well, why does he need this? What are you
doing down here? OK, sewer guards. We got to make sure we guard the sewers. Wait, did I shoot him
or did he hit his head on the ceiling jumping? I don't know. Is he dead? Yeah, you do. You've got
to turn the flashlight off. Don't worry. He'll eventually turn this corner. That's Jake the dog.
Yes, it is. Wait. Shit. He turned the light on when he killed me. Why did I die instantly?
I was trying to put the body right next to him. How did I die instantly? I don't understand.
He killed me instantly. I had four health blocks. What did he say? I'm going to die, dude. This is
game. OK, something else exploded. Why is it dying right down here? I don't remember this happening
in the movies. All right. I'm fucking going for it now. I'm not going to fuck around. I need to see.
All right. I don't care if the game's about not seeing. Oh, my God. Are they dead? Wait, what is
that? I just got. What did I pick up? Like a hologram? How do you reload? You know, I can't
think of something in a more stupid idea than to put exploding fucking barrels down under the
gas lines of the town. Rising. Oh, yeah. Hey, boss, where should we put the sixth exploding barrel?
I don't know. Put it over the corner. I was asleep the whole time.
I'll act like you're asleep. You're going to be some money.
Is this like the evil asshole final enemy?
They already did this. Now play nice so we can get this over with quickly.
It's already over, John. Secure your weapon, Johns.
Good to see you too, warden. So the famous Mr. Riddick. The Hawks. Finally come to stay.
Is this a prison?
Vin Diesel does this thing where he like purr talks. He's like purring like a kitten.
Right, Hoxie? I think Riddick about covers what you owe me, Johns.
There's plenty other slams I can take Riddick to if you can't afford. Vin Diesel should play
a cool cat in an animated movie. All right. All right. Can't you see him? Cool cat with sunglasses
on. Extra. No, Riddick stays at Butcher Bay. Period. Full stop. Let's get him processed.
Yes, sir. I like that one. Johns. Better luck next time. Okay, so we're doing this again.
Pay attention, punk. You are now Butcher Bay prisoner 542. As to remember your number.
Can he just run? Oh, come on. Listen, outside. I feel like this is what the new Star Wars
experience at Disney World is going to be like. Oh, it's me. I'm the prisoner.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where are we going? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Lock me up. Oh, wow. Look.
Hey, I better be. I better watch out for those guards, right?
Just wait till they start doing this shit. I can't wait for that, by the way, that like Star Wars
experience where like you get like arrested and you have to like fight Kylo Ren. That's like a
$4,000 experience that I'm absolutely going to have. Look at that. Look at that actor.
On his resume said he could spin guns and shit. This is I love this. Come on. Give me shit. I hear
a large crowd. Why do I hear a crowd? This is going to turn into Arkham Asylum, isn't it?
That was a pretty sick walk. Hey, what are you bringing to me? Things his shit don't stick.
Well, I mean, I have been taking probiotics that's supposed to help with that. But whatever,
I won't correct it. Really? I'm barber. Come talk to me after the lousy. Okay.
This is your home. It's time for us to do lousy filthy ass. Don't breathe. And by the way,
the menu was on the table on the right. It's happy hour right now, by the way. Get in there,
scumbag. Oh, okay. Nobody likes the nobody likes the like Disney World experience restaurant. Oh,
okay. Cleansing routines. Wait. Dignity of slam life. Let some mercs think they're in charge.
Oh, I have to put my hands in the toilet. What is it? Okay. Flush toilet is I open the menu.
Arbor outside your cell might help you locate the weak spot of this slam. Remember that security
will notice and take action if you have weapons. I was crouching that whole time. Okay, we're
going to get why is the door open? Hey, come talk to me for a second. Will you? I thought I was
supposed to be locked in here. You're really right. But it's a guy named medicine talking
like he knows you. He's in the courtyard just by the pit. Okay. Thanks a lot, dude.
Wait, did he do that? Uh, that's, I, you can't, I love games that let me do that.
You know that if your video game allows me, even if there's a stupid little cut scene where you
have to run away, if I could just punch a guy and get like in trouble for it, like that's,
I like that. That's good that they did that. A lot of games don't care. I don't know what
Maxin wants with you, but I go check it out. If I were you, I can't break his neck though. Right.
All right. I promise I'm done. I'm probably I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I just want to see if
I could break his neck. Cause you know, you do realize that if I could break his neck,
I would have ran around and broke everybody's neck and the whole fucking entire floor.
He doesn't even want to talk to me anymore. He's just like, maybe if I don't look at him,
I feel like I have been unfriended. Okay. Who are you? It's the Kozak brother,
AKA the torture twins locked down yesterday. Managed to get hold of some poor side, obviously.
Okay. Hey, my advice, do like all the other fish line up. I can't, I have to,
I have to just take my hand off right trigger. I can't help it. You see this face,
all things to Molina waste him when they open his cell. Oh, I'll make it worth your while.
When they open his cell, what is he going to do for me though? I don't, I mean,
I'm not sure if I want to agree to this because this, this guy's going to be my companion or
something. It looks like he gets his ass kicked all the time. Uh, yeah, I'll do it. Maybe. Okay.
What was the guy's name? What cell is his? Hey, what cell is Molina's.
You won't ever walk into the infirmary punk. Maybe we'll drag you in when rust is finished
with you. Now piss off. Okay. When they open his cell, kill him. All right. Now I gotta go,
I gotta do this way. This game's pretty cool. I, I had some of this game. I like this game. This
is cool. All right. Let's go over here. Who's in here? All right. I'm the toilet guy. That's,
that's how people know me. That's how you'll remember me. Is it Arnold? All right. I gotta
find this, this, I gotta find this way to get out of here. Here we go. Yeah.
You didn't pay your damn long man in the first place. You got that right. You should see Haley.
He can help you out. You're going to get in trouble with the Aquila measures. I'll tell you.
Look, go on and talk to Haley. He's the wise man. He used to be a guard, but he turned over to the
good side. Okay. Everyone has a name. Oh, this Haley is red. I'm looking for the,
it looks like a way. We got a link here. There's some link spam here.
You're streaming the Chronicles of British ass. I mean, that's not that funny. That's not that
funny. If I'm, if I'm going to get a minus two for my Disney world restaurant bit, then that's a
minus two for like the word ass is in the title. Bugger. You got a problem, huh? Go fuck yourself.
I got him. I actually hit him. I didn't think that was even, nobody even saw.
Nobody saw me do that. Shit. Wait, they thought he did it. He did it. That guy did it. Take him
back to his cell. Yeah. Come on, dude. Give it a rest. Oh, I'm about to impress everybody
at the prison right now. You ever seen anybody do that for your whole life? No. Oh yeah. No,
no, no. I mean, I heard you were coming. You're going to want to ship and I can get you one.
Check my bunk and you'll find one. It's yours. I want this guy fired for heaven.
Trying to do a voice like mine. I'm the only one that has a low gravelly voice.
Get rid of that guy. What do you want me to do? What's, what's with the links today? Dick ass
gameplay. Cool. Yeah. You cropped it. Listen, Riddick rust pulls all the strings in this block.
Personally, I don't much care for that. He's a thorn on my side.
Child humor. Remove the thorn, get rust. All right. So I have to,
you give me a list of people I have to. Wait, they electrocuted him and it electrocuted me.
I was standing on his body. I was a conductor. All right, let's go. Open it. Who did he say to
kill? Oh, and even listening. Yes, I was. Okay. Promise. Mattson promised he'd put a ship for you
in his bunk. Go to sell a 40 and get the ship. Don't give me a knife. Don't give me a knife.
Don't do that. I'll never get out of the tutorial. It's not going to happen. If you give it,
if I get a knife, I'm not going to be able to leave. Don't give me this in the toilet.
Hey, what? Oh, you guys want to fight. Do you, or is this like a dialogue thing?
No, what do you want to talk about? Uh, or I'll do it too. I'm new here and, uh,
I think they want to fight. Do they? I don't, maybe. Whoa, I just parried that guy. Okay. Okay.
Watch it. I'm going to flush him. I'm going to try to flush him.
He's too big. I can't flush him. All right. Where's the knife?
Supposed to be a knife in here. Oh no, he lied to me. There's no knife in here. He lied to me.
He said there was a knife in here. So I could come in and get beat up and potentially fucking
killed. Hmm. Mm hmm. Go see what he has to say about it. All right, let's go get him.
Where are you? Is that in the courtyard? Is there sprint? It's barber. That's Jimbo.
This is shabby. This is Michael's. Okay. Minus two joke, ignoring the link. I'm in the middle of
something. Where? No, not Jack. He's up here. He's the writer, isn't he? No, that's red.
Yeah. He let me explain. It was rust. He forced me to, but, but I knew those goons were no match
for you. I'll get you a shift. Just have things right. You have my word. I want it now. Cross me
again and I'll have your life. Talk. I don't know anything. Not compared to Haley. This one guy's
just like, I'm going to hear everything. Used to be a guard. Let me set things straight. I'll bring
that shift to your cell. Just kill. Just go there and wait. Are there three guys here? This?
Yeah. Yeah. That's what's happening. Haley. It's all right. I got, I'm still going to do the thing
for you. Get rust and I'll help you. Go to your cell and wait for me. That'd not be lying to me.
Remember this is the last time. All right. I was the last link of this link. Cool down is going
into effect. After I clicked this, it's just Homer Simpson, like shoes is Homer Simpson, like mask,
sock feet things. Right. And that like the kiosk at the mall, they have like goofy
fucking slippers to put on. That's cool. I'll go back to my cell, which cell is mine. I don't
even remember. I don't know which cell is mine. This is a bad prison. If I don't even know where
I go, I don't know what cell is mine. I forget eight 34. This one. All right. Where is he?
I got the ship you wanted. Really? What do you think you're doing? You deal in without my
approval. You're in my cell. You need a blade. You come to me. I said my cell. What wrong?
All these cells belong to the Achilles. Include this one. Now you ain't paid me for that shank.
So it ain't yours. Come take it. You got a hearing problem. I said everything I see belongs to me.
I see this. It belongs to me. Release him, British.
Who's this? And I will personally bring hell down on you. Oh, it's one of the guards. Let's do
something like Tony Hawk create a character outfit. I thought you were the big dog, Russ.
Maybe he's more yourself. Yes, sir. Mr. Rabbit. Hey, that's my friend. You are messing with the
natural order. What did he just do? Why did blood come out of him? Well, as you can see,
people can get that was a ketchup packet that he spread on the wall. This is actors. I'm telling
you. And we don't want that. Speak for yourself. This better not be one of your killing boys.
I've been here responding to not very good guard work. This is that we could have had like three
or four opportunities just to grab the gun out of his hand. Like, come on, you can't get that
close. All right. Get out of my get out of my wall. Get away from me.
Rust is waiting for you in the killers block. He won't stop till you're dead. So you better find
a weapon woman can help. Okay. I this is just go around and find the one person that's actually
going to help me. Okay. Get a weapon. I Haley won't talk to me unless I get rid of rust.
And then Molina seems to have messed up shabby up a real bad client and kill Molina. All right,
let's just go to the I need a weapon. Oh, wait, what if he doubles the money? I don't know what
you're after. Okay. But Haley knows how things work here. Check the courtyard. Now he didn't say
like, wait, I'll double the money that you were going to get from that guy. No, sorry. You didn't
do the double the money meme. How do I do this without getting attention trope cliche? Yeah,
whatever. That gallop can pick his body up. Hey, hit him one more time. I didn't want to do it in
the open. Wait, is he gonna remember that? He crawled out of myself. He crawled in that much
time to hear somebody get this guy some medicine. Wait, is he going to be there? He's not going to
still be here, right? Does he remember that I did that? Does this game have like memories? What?
He's dead? All right, where's um, where's the guy that I have to turn this into?
Who who wanted me to do this? Oh, it was shabby. Oh, now Molina is gone. Go and get your Oh,
all right. What's up? Thanks for wasting Molina. This is for you. What is it? What is it? You didn't
give me anything. What did it mean? This is for you. You didn't give me anything. Thanks for wasting
Molina man. See, wait, the unofficial and universal currency. You currently have five UD secret code.
This is a four digit security code. It opens a locked door somewhere probably inside the infirmary.
All right. Take care. Thanks, dude. All right, now let's go into the yard here. I'm gonna laugh my
ass off if in like 40 minutes this guy's up here on the ground still. Russ will kill you unless
you join him. I'd like to see him try Jimbo. I'd like to see him try a new fish in the tank.
How do you like it here? I don't. Name's red. Tell me. How did it feel when you killed your
first? Oh, you mean Molina? That's between me and him in butcher bay. You know, I did kind of was
some men can get very much pleasure. You know, there are worse reasons. Some like rust. I'd be
happy to see you go. Alright, so red wants rust gone. Rust wants Haley gone. Haley wants Molina
gone. Molina wants rust gone. This is like a long math problem. Unlike my SATs. Okay, rust is waiting
for you in Aquila territory. I don't have a weapon yet though. Haley won't talk unless you get rid
of rust. Where is he? Get rust. And I'll help. All right. Well, where is he? Which one is he?
That's booger. I'm watching you. Well, I punched him. I climbed this. Can I like grab onto this?
We're gonna go this way. Wow, man. Okay. Yeah, let's see if we can find somebody.
Oh, here we go. This is this is the territory. Wait, is it don't come here until I had a weapon?
All right. Yeah. Wait, I don't want to be here. Do I? You got two weapons lefty and righty.
All right, we're looking for wah man. Red, Haley, Jack.
He's waiting. Everyone just keeps tipping me off on this. Do you think this guy's just sitting there
with a knife just holding it standing around the alley and everyone has told me that he's going to
try to kill me? I think it's time for a new strategy. I killed him. So.
All right. No extra content. Large alien is now available in the extra content menu.
Take it easy. Wait, wait, wait. Is this a weapon? Knuckle duster. Okay, that's a weapon.
Thanks. All right, let's go. All right, we're gonna go. Rust is waiting for me. He's gonna kill me.
I know this now. I'm gonna go to this territory. I'm gonna find out what's going on over here.
Okay, let's get it. He's here.
Walk it. Walk it. There it is. All right, you let's go. Was that who? Which one of you is rust?
Smash his head in. Good. Was that money? Oh, I got two knuckle dusters and cigarettes.
The Riddick team unlocked. Cool. Is it a healing station?
That shit is dangerously close to the eyes. Wait, wait, wait. I probably should hide these guys,
right? Whatever. No, I wanted to. Okay. That was a little scary, but it didn't do anything.
Don't you think if you were this guy, you'd probably be like, oh shit, it didn't work.
It was supposed to explode, Riddick. I'm sorry. I want that knife. Walk it.
There we go. This is a mistake. Oh, this is green sludge on the ground. That's probably acid.
I'm gonna snap your head off and piss down your neck.
Oh shit. That was, I just like slashed him. I don't know how I stabbed him.
Oh, I thought I killed him. Damn it. I thought he died from that. Oh, you want to have an old
fashioned knife fight, do you? Come on. Oh, sorry about that. Can I have two knives? Oh no.
This one's cooler. I wish you could do a weld. Somebody there. Wait, I know this guy. This guy
was in a cut scene. I can't believe that worked. Where is the principal? Where's the guard?
I'm dead. Where's the warden? Where's the warden?
Get ready to die. Come on, do it. I'm trying to parry him. I'm trying. It's harder than he thinks.
Get away from me. I cannot parry this guy. I don't think I can parry him. Where's he? Where is he?
You can't parry him. He's a boss fight. Oh, well then I'll just kill him.
Get ready. So fucking glad I'm not playing this on hard. Where you going? What's he doing?
Switching it up. I'm in my menu and he knows he's coming at me. He's so good. Why is he so good?
Why do I only have one stab? Just spam. He's going to kill me. Why do I only have this one
like lunging stab? All right, I'm just going to fucking spam. All right, I'll do it. Fine.
It's taking so long. So this is the beast of Butchabay, huh? Head of the killing gang.
Hey, just out of curiosity, Riddick, how many tries did that take you?
Looks like I need a new rooster. Let's say four. They respect you now, Riddick. I can make things
easier. Say something and take that as a no. Saying no to me is not the kind of mistake you
want to make. Oh, okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. What's going on right now? Am I supposed to be
hiding from these? But they have laser eyes. I don't know what we do. By the way,
this is my kill. I wish you could throw. Shit, he fucking looked at me. I was trying to break
his neck and run. I hate when games give me freedom because I can die. I just don't stop.
All right, I'm just leaving. Fine. Here we go. Goodbye. Hey, what? Oh, stay the fuck away from
me. He gave me cigarettes. Am I a bad guy now? Do people think I'm bad? Okay, where do I go?
Rust is gone. You should go talk to Haley. Okay.
Dude, I think you got him. Oh, shit. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh,
no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. I gotta go. That was something, man.
Hey, thanks. No, don't break everybody's neck. I need NPCs. It's gonna be like Dark Souls where
if you kill all the NPCs, like the game sucks. I'm done. Get the gun. I can't get the gun. The guy
electrocuted my... It said unauthorized access. I can't get the gun. It's locked. Break this guy's
neck. No, I can't kill everybody. I'm sorry. I can't. I didn't do that. Right? I didn't do that.
You did. I did not do that. He forgot. He blacked out and did it. All right. Where's my reward?
Where are you? Hey. I heard you rejected Abbott. That's integrity. So I'll keep my word. What do
you want to know about? Pit. Looks like a way out. Way out? Sure. Raise some hell. Raise some hell and
they throw you down. If you manage to stay alive, there's supposed to be a way into Pigsville from
down there. But it's never been done. I like a challenge. Well, then Pigsville's your place.
The space board hangers. This looks like space, doesn't it?
Because that's why I've been dying. Okay.
If you want to get through the infirmary gates, there's this hack names Boulder.
He owes me 150. Talk to him. What about you? No, I almost did it. All right. Talk to Boulder to get
into the infirmary. I have to start to remember names. Boulder. It was booger. Where's Boulder?
Boulder. I don't know where I can find Boulder. Do the Vin Diesel voice. Funny man. You must
have just, I've done it like five times. Fine. That's Snape. Let me change it. I can't do it
anymore. It's Snape again. I can't do it. It's always going to be Snape. I have to delete that
from my mind. No, it's I will see you in an hour. Just stay for an hour. You'll figure it out.
I can't. All right. Where's Boulder? Hey, Haley says you owe him. You should get that money from
you. Riddick. You screwed my bet on rush when you figure it out. Yeah. I don't know what that
means yourself, but betting against me now. It looks like a thumb and you look like how I
feel like shit. Okay. Go on through. Hurry up. Thanks dude. Appreciate it. Open. All right. Now
what do I have to go? I have to find a necklace that's going to give me powers. What do I do?
I don't, I'm not going to do it. What's going on in here? Uh-oh. Just wait here for the doctor.
Don't you fucking dare move. That sounds like a guy that never gets to say swears in his
parents' house. Hey, I'm still, I'm waiting for the doctor. What the fuck is wrong with you?
For all you know, I could be the doctor. Okay. Get out of here. What's going on with this guy?
Stomach cramps. Take care of that. Jesus Christ. He just lit that guy up. He lit that guy up. All
right. I feel bad now. I feel bad now. That guy ate all the bullets. I feel terrible. That guy
inhaled all of them. Okay. Hey, just wait here for the doctor. Don't you fucking dare move.
Okay. I have to, I have to address this. Somebody went snap fingers, snap fingers. Hey, funny guy,
do the funny voices like, get out of here. No, where's this doctor? Don't come over here. You
saw me do that, but I, you're, wait, what? I have the code. I think the door came down and crushed
me. Just wait here for the doctor. Don't you fucking. All right. I need to obviously distract
them somehow. The doctor's never coming. Or am I just so impatient that I can't do this?
What does, what does the doctor look like? Well, this guy, this guy doesn't have a gun.
Is this the doctor? All right. Don't break the doctor's neck when he opens the door. Don't
break the doctor's neck when he opens the door. Don't break the doctor's neck when he opens the
door. He's going to write it on the chalkboard a thousand times. I mean, this is dark. I'm in the
dark. He can't see anything. What's going on? What is happening? I think that guy's stuck in the door.
Okay. All right. Now you can't pick these up. Oh damn. Security code. Put them down. Put them
down. Put them down. All right. I got the security code. That means I can leave. Got it. What?
What are you just standing there? Die. Die. Oh, you have a code on you. That was the doctor. I see.
Okay. What's in here? Some type of weird laboratory machine. I use it. Use health station. Oh,
this looks like that thing at Dave and Buster's that you ride the roller coaster.
Why is that still in Dave and Buster's by the way? That shit was really, really interesting.
Probably 15 years ago that like that was this VR. Now you don't have to watch like a TV screen
while your seat moves. I don't even need the help. I should be sneaking around way more often. Can
I pick this up? This looks like an exploding barrel. He's going to turn the corner and shoot
the exploding barrel. Isn't it? And now I'm up top. All right. So is there anybody up here?
Oh, oh shit. Okay. Wait for him to walk by permanent health upgrade. Are you serious?
How do I use it? Oh, all right. Do I want to pick skiing roller coaster or I'm in an airplane?
That was all right. You're way too close. You're too close. Yeah. Don't do that again.
Don't do that again or you're going to be real sorry. All right. This is a safe point. So I can
doesn't matter service hatch, but wait. Oh, done. Done. I can't pick up the gun. The DNA.
Look, look guys. Look, ready? Look, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I cannot pick up the
gun. I don't have the DNA qualification, whatever the hell it is. Look, look at, look, stay. I love
it. Is he going to climb in the hatch? Are they looking for me? Like, can I just jump on people?
Where is this guy? All right. Keep going. Right. Going on. All right. Give me up there. I'm going
right, right, right. Going on, I guess. Hey, I'm just didn't even. Oh, I'll smart it again.
Oh, that's me. That's my cue, right? That's where I want to go.
Security code. Wait, I dump them down there. No. Okay. Well, I can stand up now. Where's the key
code? Grab the gun. You can't get the gun. There's no gun. Um, and who's killed me?
Got to stay in the dark. Security code. All right. I think somebody walked by. We'll wait for them.
Where is he? All right. Now, wait, no, no. Hide, hide, hide, hide, hide, hide, hide, hide.
Somebody comes from the other angle. Yep. Who's that? Somebody's pointing at me. Wait,
that's a spotlight. It's on me. All right. This guy have tranquilizer darts. I'm dead again
instantly. All right. You know what? Fuck it. Got to stay in the dark. No, I get it. This is a
stealth part of the mission where you can, you instantly die. I get it. I stay in the dark.
Why did he turn around? What? Okay. Can, does the spotlight move? Why is the spotlight move?
It just stays right there. All right. But eat, eat what? I don't have anything to eat.
I'm going to eat. I made it. I'm good. Eat a McDLT. I would right now. The main frame.
Security will be tight. Sure. Like a challenge. That's the kind of voice that you use when it's
like one o'clock in the morning and you're talking to like a significant other or like,
you know, a person of interest. Like we get laid at night and you just like talking like that.
Like what's up? Yeah. Just hanging out. Just chilling. I don't know why we people do that.
It's just, it's just sound like sexy. I don't, I don't know what it means. Why do we do that?
Like I very clearly could just put my head up and be like, yeah, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think I'm supposed to be down here. How does this guy happen? Give me the DNA sample.
Wait, he didn't have it on him. What was this random engineer with like a staff?
Oh, give me that. I want your staff. Hold on. I can use guns now. Oh yeah, they do.
I never had any gun training in my life. I lost the CQC training though. God. I'm so stupid.
Now things get interesting. All right. Well, I didn't know they were going to pour in here.
All right. Bring it on. Okay. Give me all the ammo. How do I reload the gun?
Wait, gun. Oh, cool. I got gun. Gun. What? Oh, I'm dead. Didn't come in. What are they? Oh,
that's, it's supposed to blow up a wall. Oh, health station. Debris. Oh, was he going to burn me?
I can't even see me down here, dude. You can't. He didn't see me down there. That's ridiculous.
You get a key code on it. Shotgun. Better. I'll take the shotgun over anything else.
My favorite weapon. Wait, was this a, oh, I thought this was a vent to go into.
Do I have to destroy this? I'm like trying to crawl in it. What do I have to do with this?
Did I miss something? Oh, use the screwdriver. I'm just going to climb. I guess. Yeah. Okay. Climb.
I just said open service panel. I didn't know what it was supposed to mean.
Oh, Cindy's. I'll get it back up there. Wait, I might be able to jump on top of people. This
might be fun to go that way. But wait, can I jump on somebody's head? No. All right. We're
going to just go from here to there. Who's taking a look? Hmm. Nothing here. Oh, he's right there.
Okay. Headshot. No, I can't see in here. Keep looking. Don't even, don't even do it. Just go.
Wait, it's my opportunity. I noticed something. I want to check who's there.
This is my opportunity to do it. Yeah, not here, but I know he's around.
Hmm. What? Why didn't that work? Didn't it say you could jump on people's heads?
I feel like I was lied to. Turn back. How do you have, there's no fucking way you have more
reaction time than me on that one. Wait, I get to try this again.
Melee weapon. All right. Walk down here. Come on, man. Let's go.
And I heard something. Go walk over here. Both of you idiots. He's being body blocked. He wants
going on here. He's so badly wants to go home. He desperately wants to keep looking, but this guy
keeps getting in his way. Just let him do an investigation. Someone's here. I didn't mean to
jump through. I'm going to die. I'm going to die. I'm dead. God damn it. Well, they wouldn't walk.
They couldn't get the guy to move. All right. There's a heel right there. Just got to kill this
guy. One, two. What? I hear another guy shooting. I'm going to have to prefire. Where is he? Oh,
did I get him? I don't know. Did I get him? I still hear the Metal Gear Solid music.
He's up. I don't know. Where is he? I don't know where he is. He's right. Okay. I see him,
but how the fuck am I going to aim over there? I have an idea. How are they seeing me? What?
Where am I? Where? He should have been through the, he tried to shoot me through the grate.
He's trying to shoot me through the grate. I got to take it fast. What would, what would Riddick do?
What a shitty movie. This is how I used to play paintball when I was a kid. I was so scared. I
didn't want to have so badly. Didn't want to get hit at the whole game. I would just stay in one
spot and just kind of peek out and go and then just immediately get back in. Am I dead? Okay.
You can connect again, please. Thank you. Okay. I can't shoot him through the grate, but he can
shoot me through the grate. I'm done with this bullshit. I'm just fucking lighten up. I'm just
lighten them up. You know what I mean? I fell through the grate. Come on, let's go. Get it.
Show it. Go on. Go on. Dude, I'm supposed to be able to see in the dark. Okay. But how's this,
does it make any sense? Riddick's supposed to be able to see in the dark. Not yet. Who said that?
That guy was blending into the environment. That guy was actually not a person. He was like a wall.
Uh oh. Gas. That was easy. Did you do that for fun or I don't... Okay. Wait, there's a little more gas
over here. This is not open. Can I... I can't go that way. Oh, is there a way to make the wall
explode? I get it. D-pad? No. I gotta get... I have to go down. I have eight bullets. What? Where did
that guy go? Give me a checkpoint. Can we go back to like punching inmates and like laughing at
toilets? All right. This looks like a boss area. All right. I'm gonna use gun. Okay. Thanks. Oh,
nice dodging. Oh, why am I the boss? You know what I mean? Like that's how you would dodge the boss.
I'm the boss and he just, he's the one that's playing the game. Why did he explode? Can I leave?
Hello? Everybody gone? Oh, shit. This one guy. Oh my god. He's right here. Oh my god. He's gonna
hit me once. I'm gonna die. Where are you? Where? There's another guy. Where's the other guy?
There's a... There's another guy? Oh, no. It's the space marine. This is so lame.
Hold on. Wait. Let me reload. Why am I holding the gun like this? Oh, come on. I have to shoot him in
the back? Oh. I have to get in a spot. There's the grenade. All right. I'm going over here.
I'm already almost dead. Give me the... Oh, I got him in the head. Okay. I got him.
Stand still for a second. All right. Nice. Now, is there a... Oh, shit. Okay. Okay. Wait, wait,
wait. Is that... Can I get the health back? He goes, hey. Oh, no. Where do I hide? I'm gonna
hide over here. Do I hide over here? Am I technically in the dark? I'm in the dark
right now. Okay. He can't see me. He's getting... Is he getting closer or further away? Destroy the
lights? Oh, shit. Where... Oh, there he is. He can't see me, right? I'm invisible. I thought I was
invisible, man. Just anything. I got him. Holy shit. He's so easy. Oh, you just have to shoot
him in the back once. Oh, okay. I think he's still in there. That would not have killed him. I think
he's still in there. I think he's... Can I drag the body? I need a heal thing. Check the bodies.
Get weapons. Get ammo. Set that thing up because it's annoying. Oh, you can. All right. I got ammo.
Good. Let's go. Lights off. Isn't there still a riot going on? Yeah, I can hear it. Hey, Xbox off.
It's not an Xbox one. They weren't smart enough back then. Special task forces are now entering
the cell block. Stay low and do not move. What did that say? What did that say? I had like a prompt.
What was it? You guys saw that, right? Why am I turning on? What did I do? All right. Let's go.
All right. There's some... Okay. Switching turret settings from tranquilizing to lethal.
Oh, that's a turret shooting at me. Where is it? That's just a big bright light. I don't even know
where it is. Is that a turret? There was a guy hiding in the shadows, too. I'm telling you,
more and more every day, I feel like an NPC playing the game with the protagonist fighting me.
Yeah. Turn this on. I don't know if this does, but it does something.
Let your big brother help you. No. I want to play. Switching turret settings from tranquilizing to
lethal. Turret down. Where's another turret? Is that a turret right there? Yep. Turn off the light.
Where's the guy that's here? Oh, he's dead. All right. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead. He's dead.
Where am I supposed to be going? Turn off all the lights. I need them, though,
because I can't see shit either. I'm just making the game harder for myself. I can't see in the
dark. Is that a good guy? That's a turret! Whoa. Who's who? Take your sunglasses off.
Hello? Holy shit. It's behind me. What? Where is it? Is that it? I'm so confused. I was
getting shot from behind. That's a shadow. Fuck. I got him. I need tape. Where is it?
Where? I don't know where it is. Why is it super dark now? What happened? Where the fuck am I?
Did I turn off the lights on my stream? Who is it? I don't understand what's going on.
How did I get over here? Wasn't somebody over here? It was a guy here. Where's my gun? What
happened? Did I do it? Oh, shit. Get that light off. Get this light off. Turn that light off. Oh,
wait. That's outside. You can't do that. Turn this one off. Who's the fucking turret? Of course it
was. Of course it was. All right. Did I get the heal? I have the heal. All right. Let's go. Wait.
Turn the valve. I still don't even know what this does. I don't instantly lose three bars.
I didn't do anything.
Oh, it's dead. Okay. I got full health. Good. Fuck you. Okay. I got it. Look at my health,
man. Oh my God. You guys are already playing on hard. No. I shot that guy like four times.
I still can't figure out what's happening to that guy.
Switching turret settings from tranquilizing to lethal.
This dude just explodes. Where is it? Right here? Oh, I got it. Good job. All right. Don't let this
guy kill me. He doesn't even know where I am. Holy shit. Wait. That's a speaker. It's over here.
Oh, why did I just panic? All right. I don't want to visit. Where's the turret? I know there's one
over here somewhere. Isn't there? Wait. There's a guy. All right. Hold on. Wait for the guy. Wait.
It's an explosive. Is that an explosive? It's not an explosive. Shit. I thought it was a barrel.
Those bullets came from behind me. Why? Where is that? They hit something behind me.
It ricocheted. Oh, dude. Fuck this. Okay. Good. Where is it? Is that it? Yep. Okay. There's another
one. That's not it. All right. I'm going to get the safety of the bathroom. I wish there was a
heal in the bathroom. I don't know what that is, but I'm going to take it. What is that?
Nanomed cartridge. Did I not even? You can't be fucked. How is it still hitting me? Oh, God damn
it. I'm just using the light. I don't care. I can't see anything. I'm using the light. It makes it
worse. Nevermind. Oh shit. He's coming down the hall. He's coming down the hall. He's coming down
the hall. Where is it? He's coming down the hall. Just wait for him. Why is this guy can see me?
That just actually hurt my chest. That just scared the shit out of me. Go back and heal. Oh,
all right. I'm going. I'm just fucking going fast. I know where they are. I'm
switching turret settings from tranquilizing to lethal.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Yep. Okay. Okay. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay. Okay. I'm not. Let's go.
Where is it? What do I hear? Like a ticking sound. The turret on my right. Oh, thank you.
The game has an auto. I can turn the auto aim off. That's the problem. Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it? Okay. Now go heal. Where is she? All right. I feel more calm. Did I get a permanent
health upgrade? Where'd it go? I don't have a permanent health upgrade. Oh, it only had one
charge. Okay. All right. Not going to let this guy kill me this time. Not going to blow it.
He's just waiting. I didn't get him in the head. All right. Hold on. He's dead. But now is I think
a turret over here. All right. Let's fucking go. Con the hacks into opening it. What? Who's the
hacks? Are you a hack? I think I needed that guy. Are you alive? Get up. Do you have a thing on you?
Does that guy have a thing on him? I need you to come with me and open this door over here.
My one hacker. You. This is so hard to control. Where's the other one? He's right over there.
Come on. Where? I need a hacker. Hacker. Wait, he just opened the door. Holy shit. He opened the
door. I got in. All right. Now that door is open or something, right? God damn it. Give me a
checkpoint. I couldn't. I tried. Okay. I got you. Checkpoint. Checkpoint. Yes. What?
I would love it if the credits just rolled. It was a slow close up to Vin Diesel's face. His eyes
are wide open and he's just fucking dead. I do have an, would that actually work?
If there was a person underneath you and you fell and you landed right on them, would they die?
Okay. What if it was like five people? I'm talking like you have one, two, three, four, five,
and you're like, you're like the sixth person. Still no.
This is a timed mission. What is it? Gollum? What was that? Oh shit. Oh my God. It really is.
Oh my goodness. This just turned into a completely different video game in the last 30 seconds.
I feel like I'm playing killing floor. All right. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Oh no.
Okay. What do I, I don't know what the goal is. Open this door. Why don't bullets work anymore
on these explosive barrels? Okay. I think it's scripted. It's not actually five minutes.
See, we're good. We're good. Don't waste ammo. Yeah. You're right. Make way for the messenger.
Justice and vengeance. Is this guy talking? Wait, was there a guy over here?
I don't know. I don't even know where to go. I think I got it. Did I get it? This looks new.
I think this is new. This is new. No, wait, which are you kidding me? This estimated time to failure,
two minutes. Get away from me. I found it. I found it. I found it. Oh my God. I have no,
where am I supposed to go? Was I not supposed to go down? Keep turning left. You will get there.
That's going to put me in a circle. There was a find the exit from the pit. Estimated time to
failure. Well, this is not good. Okay. So if this goes over here, I can go up, but that just leads
me back up anyways, right? Or should I go this way? Is it broken? No, that just leads me back up.
Wasn't somebody was just talking to me over here? Is there more than one ways to go?
There was a guy over here that was talking. Okay. Right here. So what's going on here? Can I jump
up? Can I like blast through this? Can I open this? The hole. Okay. I'm sorry, but no, no, no,
no, no. You're talking about this hole right here. This hole here. That's not, I don't fit through
there. I already bullets. I can't fit through this hole. You have to squeeze through. I definitely
cannot make it through there. There's a way up through the top. Is there? I don't see anything.
It's the longest one minute I think I've ever seen. Stop going down here in the first place.
Explore the first floor. I don't even have a flashlight. Okay. This is the first floor.
Please play. I have no idea what it felt. I have to jump up on one of like the banisters.
Okay. I found it. I went every single place, but here it's come on. Give me a break. I don't have
any bullets. I'm sorry. This is, I'm, I'm in a lot of trouble. Leave us be sinners. This lamb is
special. You need fighting. I'm fighting somebody in the dark. The lights could turn on. This could
end up being like a little kid. I can't, maybe it'll reload me with actual bullets and shit.
Yeah. Okay. Good. Good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine.
I know where to go. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Uh huh. Uh huh. Sure. Sure. Sure.
Give me the lore. Give me the story. I don't, I don't care about any of that. I just want to,
hold on. It's over here. It's over here. Hey, you open that up. Make way for the messenger.
I am the light, justice and vengeance of the universe. Okay. At least I have two bullets.
I have 50. Nevermind. I'm good to go. Okay. Good. We, we've done it. Leave us be sinners.
This lamb is special. That's not explosive. Five minutes. All right. What does he want?
Wait, did he just do the suicide squad Joker? You know, he is, he's going, ah, ah, ah.
Yeah. Aim better. You won't survive long dripping blood. The dwellers will
smell. He told me, he told me you would come. Come. We must travel up here. I live above.
Am I still crouching? No. You need that gaze that shows right from wrong and reveals the door.
Oh, what's this? Flares. What can you do with a flare? He spoke to me,
but how do I know you're not a simple imposter? Can you stitch me or not? Yes. Yes. But first,
get me back my blessing. Boys box, a dangerous task made more so by the dwellers.
It would prove that you are what he told me. I don't the boss box and I would tend to your wounds.
The flails in that box will provide the light you need. God, not another one of these.
How many do I have? How do they work? And they do anything special.
They don't last very long. I can get more than seven. How many can I have?
Oh, okay. Get my blessing. I think I ended up with a broken elbow after that one.
All right, let's go. You cured my, you cured my hangover, but you gave me a broken arm.
All right. You want us to leave lights, press the light button. I can't turn my flashlight off.
All right. So what does he want me to do? Pope Joe's seems to be able to help you. If you can
find his blessed voice box. Do we have to go down? It's a radio. All right. So I have 12
flares. So what the hell am I supposed to do? Oh, find his voice box. Just find it. Okay.
I'm gonna see if I can find it. This is what the flares are for. God damn it.
You know how awesome this game must have been to develop. Imagine being a game designer and a world
designer and you only have to make a walkway right here. Nothing else matters. Everything
else doesn't need to be rendered. You could hide so much shit in the darkness. Speaking of the
darkness. Somebody somebody right in front of me. Okay. I picked them back up. No. Shit. How many
people are in front of me? All right. I know there's a door there. Got it. Where is it? I can hear it.
I hear this damn thing. Thank you. Let's go out. What is this guy gonna help me do? Um,
shit. I don't know. I don't. Where's the exit? All right. Let's go. This is gonna he's gonna
give me night vision. Wait, is he gonna give me the thing that I can actually see in the dark?
That would be awesome. Here you go. Bring all blessings ready. Have everything prepared inside.
Nice.
Somebody got it. Thanks. Why am I thanking you for getting a reference to a game
here? Do not trust all that you see. At least not yet. Your destiny lies elsewhere. I really feel
like the only way you can talk like this is seriously if you lie down in bed with your chin
down, you have to have just woken up. You have to just open your eyes and put the bike in front of
you. I sound like this sometimes in the morning. So wait, I'm now it's very bright and I can see in
the dark. Now I can't look at lights. I only said auto voice. With your new shined eyes,
you can see in the dark. Press up to toggle night vision on and off. That's not very good.
Uh, why don't I just get night vision goggles? I wouldn't have to completely ruin my body and
have a weird surgery and shit. Just put on night vision goggles. They're better than this.
What year does this take place? Night vision goggles have to exist, right? This is 2020,
2020, 2203. It's going to be a real pain in the ass once we go up 100.
Like how do you say to like, okay, the year 2106, 2106, 2106, 216. So how do you,
how are you going to say that? Yeah, once it gets to like 200, like 2645, 2645. Yeah, I guess it's
not that hard. I really don't like this. This just reminds me of putting on 3d glasses and looking at
the regular world and not the screen. Can't talk. Turn up the gamma. I could. Does the character
even have a goal? Do I just have night vision? Find the exit into Pigsville. He's just like,
all right, get out of here. Ready? Go have some fun with your new 3d glasses. Okay. This is fun.
And what was it? What do I do? What's the point of this whole universe this way?
Wait, I came from this way. Fucking mazes. I just spit all over the monitor right now.
Whatever. This doesn't even help. This doesn't help. This doesn't help me. I would rather have
the flashlight on. I earn the gamma up. I will. I will. I will. I feel like that's cheating.
Oh my God. A ladder. Thank you. Go. That's an old link. Everybody's like, I'm going to get them.
I'm going to get them. Oh, light. Thank God. Turn up the gamma, you sardine.
Oh, that hurts. Don't use that up here. Did I have a gun? I'm still technically in the prison,
right? Something's going on here. I'm going to take a look. Wasn't that guy just really
came out of like the bathroom? The lights on? No. How could he see in the dark? Does everybody
have the Riddick 3d glasses power? Wait, he was actually in the bathroom. Don't turn those lights
on. Keep them off. Oh, but wait, I can open all. Oh, I can open all the lockers. Oh, money. What
do you even spend the money on? Well, you know, this actually really reminds me of this. I feel
like I'm really drunk looking from my hotel room. This one is two or one. No, I find it is up here.
Oh, there's a rifle in there. I mean, they close one eye and get really, really close.
Two and two. That's not it. Move. I want to open this one. There's going to be a secret in these.
Yep. Civilian outfit now. I don't even need to do this. I can just walk around, right?
Can't even shoot that shit. Stupid. I am now dressed as him. See? All right. Cool. I mean,
I know you. What's the point of having these clothes on if I don't wear a mask?
I'm very recognizable. This is why I need to get a whatever. Get a fake beard. These guys recognize
me. What is this one? Two. All right. That hurts my eyes. The gun. I don't have a gun anymore. I'm
fine. Six, 12, 17. Okay. You're a celebrity. I don't have anything on me. Look, I don't like
this guy's walking at me. Six, 12, 17. Can I talk? How are you doing? How are you doing?
I'm all right. Can we go in here? Whose room is that? Okay. Let's go over here.
Get me out of here. Can I get him? Hey, you're an inmate. He's an inmate. Get him.
The guy go behind him T-pose and die. What? Somebody's fucking with me. He's like,
don't get too close. That's how they see through you. I'm just being annoying. I'm just ringing
everybody's doorbells and then running away. All right. He's practicing his speech. Cool.
2012. All right. Get you go that way. Don't look at me. You'll recognize me as Riddick. Wait,
talk to who? What's up? Hey, can I do anything? No, you can't. What's up? How come this guy
instantly right? Because I had a gun in my hand. How are you doing? Oh, okay. Nine, seven, 12.
Oh, are you going to open the door? No. What would the somebody get? Have you heard anything
about that Riddick? No. Okay. See you. No, I haven't heard anything.
So if wouldn't everybody know that I have a really low voice, how does Vin Diesel do a higher voice
if he doesn't want people, you know, how does he do like the, how does it go like this? Can he
feel like Vin Diesel? I don't think he'd be able to do it. Hey, if you see, what am I doing?
Just get out, right? I just have to leave. Have you heard anything about that Riddick?
What are you doing? Can't open this. This is the find a way out. Does something to do with the
codes that I'm seeing like the hamburger codes? I feel like it is. It's a hole. Have you heard
anything? Oh, I'm saying hole, hole, hole, hole. Where, where, where? I don't see a hole.
Really? What the fuck? Dude, come on. I was just trying to show off on Instagram. Leave me alone.
We have a really boring fucking job. We walk in circles. I'm trying to spice it up a little.
Have you heard anything about that Riddick? It's definitely something to do with like the ham.
What? Why did I just do that? All right. Don't be weird. They'll kill you Hank. Okay. So where
am I supposed to go? And one of these were the computers. How are you doing? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. I forgot about this part. Get you out of there. 6, 12, 17. One of these doorbells is
going to do something. I know it. Six, nine, seven, 12. I'm just going to ring until somebody
answers. I'll find the right NPC when I ring every doorbell. What's happening? I found it.
Hey. Hey. Hey there. Hi. No, not the probe. No, no. Uh, okay. Are you, you all right, man?
I'm having a lot of butt head reactions. I'm noticing today. Uh, okay, man. Bye. See you later.
Uh, okay. An elation hatch. I can't touch it. I can't open it. Why is that locked up? Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? I need a tool. Shit. I need a tool. Where do you guys has a tool
on you? You have a tool. Hi there. This is not going to work. Why would I do this? Hey man.
I'm going to need some eyes. Okay. I need to find Abbott. Wait, can I use his head? Wait,
I need hit. Hey man. Okay. Give me a break. I need to get Abbott's eyes, but how am I going
to bring them over there? I'm not going to be able to bring them over here. Are you serious? I'm
going to drag them through the whole level where I'm looking for Abbott. So you tell me I have to
kill Abbott, bring him over, scan his face. Hi there. Take his head. Am I a sicko? What do you,
you want me to take the guy's head off? There's lucky. Yo, I'm going to get that guy's eyes over
there. Remember German nine eight five me. I'm the sicko. Right. I'm the fucking weird guy.
He just like cut his head off and bring it with you. Okay. Where is he? Brad low. You didn't see
this. Okay. As far as you're concerned, this never happens. Okay. Where is Abbott? How you doing?
Where are you? I need your head. Abbott. Is that you? What's up? Abbott. How are you doing? Nope.
That's Wakefield. Wait a minute. What about his? What about Abbott's room? Can I go take a pair
of his glasses? Can I take a pic? Wait, there's got to be like a picture of Abbott smiling with
like his son or daughter or something, right? Just take the photo and scan the eyes in the photo.
He has to have his own locker room thing, right? Up top. No, Abbott. No, that's Kispert. Have you
heard anything about that? No. Have you heard? We have. Have you heard anything about Abbott?
Do you know where he is? Hey, Connor. Tell him to calm down. Where is he? Hey, if you see Abbott,
well, shit, man. I don't know where he is. I can't relay that message unless I know where he is.
He's the guy behind the wait. It's the guy that's stuck in the door. He's the stuck guy. Oh,
well, how do I? Don't do that. They think it's weird and they'll kill you. Okay. He's the guy,
the door stuck guy. All right. All right. All right. I'll go to the door stuck guy to kill all
these people. No, I do not have to kill all these people. He's door. Okay. Where was door stuck guy?
This is he's down here, right? No, I don't know. Wrong way. He's down this way. I have to set the
I have to do the alarm first. Are we certain he's in there? Wait, so I have to actually do the alarm
first? Why would I? Why would that happen? I'm going to fight my way through everybody. You have
to just start killing people. Okay. All right. I'm going to just do it. God damn it. What's that on
my head? Take the lights out. There we go. All right. Riddick mode. Wait, this is open now.
Oh, this is open. I did it. Did I need to open? I don't even need his eyes.
All the same. First, they tell you how much they need. You didn't even need it when you look away.
Anyway, you can take this. Did you get me? Audible is 750 milliliters of cheap alcohol.
I could probably. Hey, man. Long time no see. Leave me alone, man. I'm on duty.
You can talk to Jenkins, but you can't talk to me. That's not fair. What's going on? Hey, Bondo. Hey,
where's Abbott? Abbott? Well, he's got the fancy place up there. He's not keen on visitors. Abbott
only answers for his delivery. Whose delivery? What deliveries? Mostly guns. Shipments come
pretty regular like. Okay. He needs, he wants guns. What can I do for you, sir? What do you have to
sell? What are you selling? I have only the essentials. Cigarettes and ammunition. Plus I
have a light. I'm a uniform. It's regular. Do I get the uniform? Oh,
shotgun. I don't want anything. I'm cool. Okay. Have a good day, sir. Buy the smokes. Buy the
smokes. I don't want cigarettes. Leave me alone, man. I'm on duty. But you're just really falling
apart. No one cares. I, I guess we're going. He hates cigarettes. Yeah. I don't want to buy
cigarettes. I don't smoke cigarettes. We're looking for Abbott and we need to deliver some
guns to him. What's happening? Leave me alone. I'm on duty. You have some liquor, huh? I'll give you
50 UDs. Sure. Sure. Yeah. Hair of the dog. Should I do that? This whole damn plan just sweats the
life out of you. In the last 10 days, four inmates hang themselves on my watch compared to butchers.
The end of a rope. Don't look so bad. Oh, he's personal guard. That's 50 bucks though. That's a
lot. Hey, hey. All right. So let's go over here. He said his door was up here, right?
I've got a hellish shift. 60 hours in the straight. Wipe that smile off your face
and leave me alone. Will you? I'm just trying to get information, man. Hey, man. What's going on
in here? Obviously not because he answered the door. Can somebody talk to me? Somebody open the
door. I just want a friend, anybody. I want anyone to open the fucking door. Just give me anything,
please. People must have cameras because they know I'm coming and they just don't like me.
Seems inevitable. They drop one by one. Nobody likes me. At least the bottle doesn't talk back.
Good day. Good day. Good day. Good day. Good day. Why would we went up to one on the Australian
floor? Oh, I don't understand. Why are they saying good day? Who butchers? You seen him?
No, I just heard what he looks like. Kind of like that guy. Right. Okay. Leave me alone. I'm on duty.
Hi there. Kind of like that guy. Okay, that was fun. I guess I'll pick up the weapon case.
I'm on duty. Abbott. Oh, okay. I gotta be ready. I got a package. The door before a door.
Can you believe this guy? Who the fuck's in my apartment? Me. I just, I just buzzed in, man.
Hey, look, I have a package of rifles for you. You just opened the door for me, man.
The person? No. He knows who I am. Okay. Who else is in here? It was a person. I told you it was a
person. He's not, he was the clothes.
You and I are leaving Butcher Bay. Yeah, what happened to the uniform? Not bad, Johns. Someday
you might just learn how to do this for a living. Going somewhere with my prisoner, Johns?
Oh no, the double, double cross. Well, now what? I should just have him put slugs in both your
heads right now. Thanks, Carmen. It was just a matter of time and I was gonna bring Riddick back to you.
About our agreement, Johns, I'm willing to give you 20% on Riddick. Oh, I'm going to have to fight him in like the pit, right?
Let him answer. Or should we keep negotiating? He's punching him in the fucking stomach. I think he wants to hold up.
22%. I'll take it. What do you say? 22%. Nobody steals my property from my house, Johns.
I'll get them. My slam, Gary. What? Can I get his 22%? I bet on myself. I've got entire regions rioting.
My slam has become a damn war zone. I'm losing men faster than I can replace them and all of this
unrest. Well, it began soon after you arrived, Riddick. 22% of what, by the way? I don't know.
What? It would be a coincidence. Oh, don't sell yourself short. I can see why you
earned your rep. Most killed my second-in-command today. The treasure. Just working my way to the top.
Even more reason for me to bury you deep. I'm sending you to the mine, Riddick. I don't understand
why I let him go. Just shoot him. You'll be the target of every comm, looking to make his bones
with the Achilles. I expect things could get ugly. I'll be disappointed. You're gonna do the
rifle in the head, right? And then I'm gonna wake up? No? Wow. They didn't do that. Shit,
that's in every single thing ever made. I'm surprised. I just got a slight push in the
shoulder. I thought it was gonna be, eat this bastard. And you wake up here. Have me? Oh,
fucking Riddick. A different voice actor? Why didn't you run? Riddick's dead. No, there I am.
Always needs transportation, so do I. I'm still alive. Hey, there's the fall joke. He finally
did it. It took him two and a half, three hours. All right, here's the question. Can I get this guy
absolutely riddled with bullets? But they're everywhere. Get inside. I can do this. Wait,
we have to all go in here? Shit. Brian, this is really good mime in here. Quiet. Let's watch the
show. It didn't give me fucking opportunity to make my YouTube joke. Oh shit, there is no talking.
Oh, I wanted this was gonna just turn and talk. Not now. We'll talk later. Talk to me. Not now.
I'm getting the fuck out of here. You think you can contain Riddick? Big fucking mistake.
What happened to that guy? What are you doing? I don't know. Okay, I have no idea. I have a
horrible, horrible attention deficit hyperactivity disorder. That means if there's
not constant action and constant conflict, I go. I lose my mind. I know some things you'd want to
know. Let's talk in here. Getting out of Max is one thing. After you show above ground, some even
think you're gonna push Jagger Valance down. But double Max is quite another. People are watching
They never see me coming. Tell us too late. Jagger is the one down here.
So far. Point is, this is a super prison underneath the prison. Your double Max home
ends with this hall. Unless you step into the circle and defeat a blue skin. Centurion arranges
all the fights. Talk to him and talk to dog bone. He might help you get down to like a third or
fourth layer. We're gonna get to see the Dante's Inferno of prison structure. Who's this guy?
Centurion. Hey Riddick, let's go. Time to get into the ring. What? Why? Set it up. Sure. A fight
will cost you five UDs. But I'll let you in free. Try not to disappoint. Just send me a victim.
I can't initiate any fights. Slam rules. So you have to find a victim, as you say. I suggest
Herman the blue skin at the gate. How about you? You. You. You. You. You. It's hard to say you.
I don't want any trouble. Stay away. Like that. Like that guy. He's that bad newcomer.
It's my dream to work in the mines and meet Jagger Valance.
Hey man, how's it going? Got a med station back here. I'll let you use it if you pay me.
Have to fight this guy? No. No need. Why would I need that? All right, you. Kill you. I get past.
He's always a deeper voice. Let Centurion know. I'm ready to beat the shit out of you.
This feels bad. This guy sounds like he's old. Why would I pick the oldest,
weakest, frailest guy in here? They stand better than you.
Great. You have a challenger. Prepare to fight, Riddick. All right, we have a fight.
We have a fight. The infamous Riddick against Herman.
The infamous Riddick versus this other guy. Who cares? He's dead.
Nobody cares about him. He's fucking guaranteed to die.
Infamous Riddick. The infamous Riddick. Mr. Riddick. What happened? Did I just lose to Herman?
Next time, come ready to fight. I can't. I have to fucking focus.
You can fight again if you want. For free? But don't make me feel sorry for you, Riddick.
Great. You have a challenger. Prepare to fight, Riddick. Why does he keep telling me to fuck off?
All right, we have a fight. We have a fight. The infamous Riddick against Herman.
All bets are off. And remember, 5% goes to Jagger Bell.
Do not step out of the circle. Yeah. Rule two, stay in the circle until one of you is dead.
Hey, rule three, she rule one and two. Where's the fucking comedy? You had an opportunity.
Out of the circle. He went out of the circle. You may have survived this time, Riddick,
but to get somewhere, you're gonna have to fight and win.
I did win. Oh, he's dead. He's dead. So, what, I just keep killing people down here?
Five bucks, and I'll suggest a new fighter. You win the show, you're 20 bucks richer.
Yeah. Bring me the next one. Next is Basim. You'll find him in the courtyard.
I am? I didn't do anything. What, I can't like wave my fucking arms around? What if I-
I'm gonna get so sick of this shit. Don't wave your arms around in front of the cameras.
Feed ward. No fucking in recreation area? What? What is that? There's like a fucking bug in here.
Come here. I'm trying to catch the fucking bugs. Just hide for a second. Okay, we're good.
Listen, Cricket's got the best sheaves you can buy. Okay, thanks.
I got a custom-made bloody sharp sheave. Cuts through a belly like a soft-boiled egg.
30 bucks? I'll take it. I'll take it. Here, take care, man. I'll see. Take the cash and
hide it in the usual place. Nice. Okay, don't take that out. Somebody will see it.
Where's this person I'm supposed to be? I didn't do anything. Wait, am I about-
He's clean. How? Where is it? Get out of here. Where is the ship?
That's the question that you need to ask. Where is the ship?
No, don't do it again. Look here. He's not gonna find it this time, right? He's clean. Get out of
here. I so badly want to take it out and just be like, haha, you missed it. Where's this guy?
There's a person here I'm supposed to be fighting. Didn't he say he was out in the
courtyard or something? I didn't see anybody. Aha, you missed it. Yeah. Hey, when does the
prison level end? After about 10 to 12 hours, I think. Hey, guys. Look what I smuggled in here.
Hey, I swear on my mother. Look what he's gonna fucking punch the bullets out of the air.
I ain't bullshitting, Trico. I promise it's true. Wait, which one of you guys wants to fight me?
You got a problem, huh? Hey, I do. So, Reno's blessings don't come free. $20? We gotta release
from the guard with the names of some snitches. Let some asshole grab them. Okay. I want to know
who. And I want that. Oh, boy. Okay. I'm like pants down. Also, he discovered the mind.
This is like fucking pants are down. Sure, I'll do it. I'll find anything. I'll let you know.
I'm trying to explain. Relax. Sorry, Holmes. Anyway, this guy, he like discovered the mind.
Who would I define somebody that stole the list? Toto Cuellas is in charge here.
Get out of here, maestro. Cuellas is our man. They talk to Cuellas, all right? He runs the show.
Get out of here, maestro. Toto Cuellas is our man. They talk to Cuellas, all right? He runs the show.
Toto Cuellas is in charge here. They talk to Cuellas, all right? He runs the show.
Um, everything is to talk to you. Okay. I guess I gotta go over here. Talk to Cuellas.
Hey. All right. Where is this guy? I want to fight the dude. Wait, do you have a secret list?
Stay away from me. I got the important stuff.
Who has the list? Do you have a list on you? I need a list.
I want you to talk. Hey, guys. Hey, man. You want to buy a few smokes?
I can sell you a pack of smokes. Sure, I'll take a pack of smokes.
Or maybe you need some info on them. For free.
What do you know? What do you know I know now?
There's a big mining area underneath us, right? It's off limits to everyone.
But Jagger Valance is down there, so I hear. Section D is an entrance, if you want to take a
look. And if you want something other than smokes, say hello to Monster in the diner.
Good link. And about, yeah, it's been 20 minutes.
This is not even me, though. You know what I mean? This is not even me.
This is just, it's just Riddick holding these. All right. Yeah, who knows what's going on here?
Okay, who knows? You know, I can kill it.
Why did I miss it? Stop, I'm not. Wait, this is the guy.
So you want to fight me? That's good, because I can use the prize money.
See you in the ring, punk. Can I stab this guy in the ring?
All right, I'm ready. I see you in the ring.
Okay, stay back. I need to get him, but there's no way
I can get the ship through. There's an old trick you can use.
You have an old style filter smoke and a lighter.
I'm going to smoke the bitch to death? No, you dumb fuck.
You burn the filter and work it into a needle. It's kind of fragile,
so you don't want to work it too much. Stab him in the neck and he's done, man.
Shit, I heard of that thing, of course. That's what I'm going to do.
Kind of like that. I did it wrong. I didn't even do it right.
I was supposed to stab him in the neck and I stabbed him in the ass.
I need to get him, but there's no way I can get the ship through.
There's an old- I've never seen you before.
Want to make an impression? There are two PPE members in section A of the courtyard.
Two PPE members? Those bastards stole the red tube that they
really need. Find out where they stashed it and bring it to me.
Okay, I'll pay you. Okay.
I'll check it out. All right, I have way too many quests.
Hey man, want to try your luck with the dice? Yes.
Bet five on two, bet five- where's bet 50? Pay off 16 to one.
All right, bet five UDs on 11. 16 to one.
Give me the yellow. Okay, let's roll the dice.
It's high llama. Hey man, want to try your luck with the dice?
Yes. Two or 12. On aces and boxcars.
Okay, let's roll the dice. Here comes a 12 right there, double sixes.
Is any craps or ace deuce? You lose, man.
Hey man, want to try your luck with the dice? Take the ace deuce.
16. Okay, let's roll the dice.
Bingo. Bingo! Bingo! Bingo!
What? I didn't pick 12?
You're Riddick, yeah? Heard you pulled off some stunts in the circle.
Say, you got a mining job? Nobody wants me to do something for them.
Need one. Impossible.
Unless you get assigned by the warden. Reason I ask is because I want to know if
Jagger Balance is still around. I almost feel like that every single
character in this game is doing a Vin Diesel impression.
They were told that in the voice acting booth.
If that's true, that's awesome. That's hysterical. I hope that's the case.
Hey man, how about you help me collect some debts and I'll lend you money.
I heard you're a pretty good fighter. Who owes you?
Binks. One of the K3 guys in the diner. But you can't do him with muscles.
I'm running. I have so many missions to do.
Drop it in Binks food. But don't kill him.
Get some poison? I'm the sender of that message.
All right. So I have to put poison in somebody's food.
Fight a guy. How many missions do I have? Okay.
Go talk to Dogbone. Go beat up the fighter.
Find out who took the list. Find the red tube.
Where Jagger Balance is. And poison a guy.
Okay. Uh, I'm going to go over here. Bye.
You know the vents go all over this place.
There's one that goes from the dying hall over to Zoda's land in tower 19.
Anyway, Padilla, the crazy mother. Hey, do you want anything?
The mines. Tell me everything you know.
You really want to go down there? Like Jagger Balance?
That's why I asked. There's a door beside the work pass
checkpoint. This guy locked. The only ones that have a key are the guards.
The all-ranking ones. Traffic. If you can manage a one-on-one with an officer.
One-on-one with an officer. And this Jagger Balance, he a problem?
Why is Riddick Brooks so small? He kind of does. He actually kind of does look pretty little.
You're right. I haven't even noticed that the whole time.
Hey, homie. You want to trade drugs? All right. Do me a favor.
Okay. Tell me more.
Okay. I need your help on two things, man. First, I need my injector back from the PPPs.
Look, Gulag has some history with him. He'll tell you more.
Second, Basim is really bumming me out. So I need you to waste him in the ring for me.
What are you going to do? How about it, man?
Let's go. I can do it. I'm already going to do that.
What? You want to front me? I am Sorrenos.
You want to see the PPPs? Check the A section.
All right. PPPs. I think I have enough stuff to do. Work? What's this? Work pass?
I have to go to the diner, don't I? Wait, I actually have to do work?
I'm not going to help you get down to the mines, if that's what you want.
It's impossible. The mines. I need to get to them.
You should talk to Flores in the courtyard. I just worked on it.
I didn't just say you can't do anything?
Just go off my glass and I'll be damned if I didn't forget my glasses.
If you're going down there, could you check around the big elevator in Upper Mines?
Sure, let's just do everything.
You have a quest? Oh! I just want to see if this guy has a mission to do. My God.
I don't know the code. I'm supposed to know every code.
I'm so bad they want to stab this thing in the back.
Do I know the code for this door? Okay, I'm not fucking around with this guy.
I have so many missions, I have no idea what they are.
I'm just going to walk around and aimlessly try to figure out one of them.
We have to go to the dining hall. I have to fight the guy in the circle,
go to the dining hall, poison a guy, get the red vial, talk to Gulag.
Where's Gulag? I don't even know.
Three people want me to kill two people.
I don't know where they stashed it, but maybe you can find a way to get it.
Okay, right. Now...
Hey man, want to try your luck with...
Give me the yellow.
Okay, let's roll the dice.
Let's go.
It's 11 or high limelight.
That's fucking, that's 16 to 1.
You win.
How much money does this guy's got? What, it's 5 bucks? 16 to 1?
I just made it all back. And then some. See you later.
All right, I could fight that guy. I got to go back this way.
I want to go to the dining hall, but I want to fight somebody in the circle.
Where is this? Here he is.
All right, let's go. I'm ready.
No, it's not you.
Gamble more feed ward.
All right, wait, wait, wait. I want to go here.
Fight the dude? I will. I just want to see in here.
All right, how do I like actually go in the feed ward?
Here we go.
All right.
Who the fuck is this guy?
Does he have to kill him?
Okay, nobody cares, right?
Oh, I got poison.
Poison is food. Poison is food.
Is that the guy?
Whose food do I poison?
Is this guy?
Okay.
Hey, by the way, can I tell you?
The slop is delicious today.
Fuck off, man. We're busy.
He's still, he's gone.
Hey, look, this is your food right over here.
It's so good.
This is eat. This is your food over here.
Eat, eat, eat, eat.
Fuck off, man. We're busy.
Eat.
He's so busy.
He's practicing whatever moonwalking.
I don't know what he's doing.
He'll eventually get there.
Well, can I talk to anybody else?
Hey, get lost.
Nobody likes me, right?
You want some free advice, buddy?
If you're carrying something, stay away from the guards in the yard.
They'll set you without a second thought.
Oh, he's eating the wrong food.
He's ate somebody else's food.
That's not even the poison one.
I think this guy just feels bad.
Tell him, tell him I'll pay back his debt.
Quest completed.
Dinah's closed, but life could be worse.
What's on your mind?
What are you trading?
Not much today.
I got a vent tool, a club, and a shiv.
All custom made.
I'll take a vent tool.
A vent tool.
Use it well.
I'll also take...
I only have a shiv.
I'll take a club.
And a club.
A club?
I'll take the club.
It's 50 bucks.
Here it is.
I'm gonna use my gambling winnings on something.
Oh, dude, I got a fucking club.
I just wanted to look at it.
How do we do that transaction is what I want to know.
So I can't look at it, but he can hand it to me.
Oh, god damn it.
This is for killing Harman.
Yeah, but I have a knife.
Big mistake.
How come there are no cameras over here?
Stop following me.
I got important stuff to stop.
Holy shit, that's a lot of money.
Wait, the...
This is the...
I got the...
I got the map.
All right, let's go.
Hey, get lost.
You want some free advice, buddy?
If you're carrying something, stay away from the guards
in the yard.
They'll set you without a second thought.
I can blast it.
Hey, I'm from fucking Boston.
God, gods.
Get those gods out of the yard.
All right, now I'm not gonna bother him or anything.
He'll just go right for it, right?
All right, here we go.
It's gonna be so hard.
Never mind, let's go.
Just get away.
He'll do it.
Turn your back.
He'll do it in one, two, three.
No.
What?
What detected?
Out of here.
Motherfucker.
Who's saying that?
All right, sit down and eat, please, so I can move on.
Eat your food.
Fuck off, man.
We're busy.
Eat the fucking breakfast, man.
Sit down and eat, please.
Fuck off, man.
We're busy.
Eat this.
Sit down.
Wait, somebody else is eating his food.
Hey, get lost.
That's where they take you if they don't want witnesses.
No surveillance there, man.
Nothing.
For you, watching...
No surveillance.
Hmm.
I don't even know who this guy is.
No.
Hey, sit down and fucking eat before I get bored and start killing everybody in here, man.
Dinah's closed, but life could be worse.
What's on your mind?
I would like, uh, love if I could have...
Not much today.
Event tool.
I got event tool, a club, and a shiv.
All custom made.
Event tool.
What did you say about killing all the NPCs?
I know.
I only have a shiv and a club.
He's soft locked.
I don't think he is.
Is he soft locked for real?
Fuck off, man.
We're busy.
I can't club him.
How did two people die back here?
I didn't kill two people, did I?
Want a trade?
Me and Monster run the trade market in Butcher Bay.
He's got the goods.
I gots the smokes.
Tell me about Monster.
Yeah, he's running goods from his spot in the diner.
He's probably in there with Chang.
So, what do you say?
How about some smoke?
Yeah, I'm like...
Give me the smokes.
Okay, here you go.
Ooh, good trade.
Come back when you have the whole snitch list.
I've got it.
Don't I have the snitch list?
Map.
This map shows the location of the secret stash
far back of the feed board behind a loose panel.
Really?
Loose panel?
Far back behind a loose panel.
Ah, and there it is.
And I've got a protractor and I got fake Halloween blood.
What is this stuff?
The tube that was stolen from Gulag.
Injector.
A syringe used by some drug addict.
He's not gonna eat.
Step away, okay?
I've done my rounds anyway.
I feel like get him out of his animation loop he's in.
I can't punch him.
I'm gonna get attacked.
I'm gonna reload the area.
Hey, look what I got.
Come back when you have the whole snitch list.
All right, I'm gonna come back.
You want me to actually softlock.
Your entire game is gonna be ruined.
What?
Where?
Fisher too?
Don't know.
No, these guys are all still dead.
No, he's just not gonna sit down and eat.
Fuck off, man.
We're busy.
Wait, he's moving.
Okay, hold on.
He turned.
Go talk to the nurse.
Hey, get lost.
Just kill him?
I can't.
I can't kill him.
All right, well, I'm gonna go turn in this shit.
Whatever.
If I can't do all the quests, who cares?
I can come back.
So I have the...
I gotta go talk to Gulag.
All right, what we got?
I got at least a few items.
I've got the PPP stash.
Got.
All right, who do I...
Who...
Where are you?
You?
Hey, Riddick.
You wanna buy smokes?
If not, I can't.
No.
Get lost.
Where is he?
Show me some proof that all the blue skins are gone
and I'll give you a reward.
Um...
Okay.
I see you in the rain.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You just made my day.
Here, take this.
Ooh, a whole lot of nothing.
Hey, man.
Good work.
I got the money back from Binks.
Hey, here's a little bonus.
Now, if you need...
I don't want any.
I want money.
Feel free to ask any time.
I'll loan you interest free.
If you need money, feel free to ask any time.
How about I just don't pay it back?
Got more than 10, so I don't borrow anything.
Not interested.
Okay.
Well, that's quite...
What else do I have to turn in?
Okay.
Speak to Dogbone.
Go back to Centurion and he'll start the fight.
A list from a guard.
Okay.
That's that.
Get drug.
Okay.
Two-Tong won't deal unless you do two things for him.
Get his injector back and defeat the guy in the ring.
All right, we have the injector.
Where's Two-Tong?
I'm good.
You?
Two-Tong.
He's in here, isn't he?
Hey, look.
Thanks, dude.
You don't know how much I needed this.
Now beat the guy up.
Now I just need Basim host and we'll have smooth sailing.
Hey, waste him in the ring for me, would you?
Oh, shit.
What, you want to front me?
I am so ready.
You want to see the PPPs?
All right, now I want to fight.
I want to go back to Centurion.
It's like I'm seeing the same thing over and over again.
All right, not this way.
All right, we got to go back to the tower, right?
Start the fight.
I just want to complete all the all the quests.
All right, not you.
It's like that first area, right?
All right, where is he?
Hour 17.
Well, he's like, isn't he right here somewhere?
Where's this guy?
I think it's this way.
Say something, cute streamer.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
I know the rules.
You didn't tell me I couldn't bring a weapon to fight, did you?
There was no rule that said I couldn't bring a spiked club.
Redo your rules.
I'm here to help you.
Five bucks, and I'll suggest a new fighter.
You win the show, you're 20 bucks richer.
Bring me the next one.
I got a K3 bastard for you to fight next.
He's called Sawtooth.
Well, let's go kill this guy.
Find him in the diner.
Yeah, let's go kill this guy.
Yeah, I know who that guy is.
That guy talked a lot of shit, but he didn't even read the rule book.
Wait, you mean I could have brought a gun?
Yep, you're stupid.
I'm gonna do I'm gonna try to finish it with a parody, too.
I want to try to I want to bury this thing in his head.
They still haven't picked that guy up.
Yep.
Okay.
And you I'll see you in the ring.
So you're really they talk about.
Yeah, you got yourself a fight.
You'll see you in the ring.
Nice.
All right, let's go.
It's just Vince McMahon.
You're gonna rot.
And by the way, you're far.
Local streamer stuns the entire McMahon family.
Okay, bring him on.
I'm going to just make a bunch of money.
I'll kill everybody in this prison if I have to.
All right.
Keep making them stronger and stronger.
Nobody knows that they can bring a weapon.
And there's 16 kills in the circle.
This guy has a weapon.
Oh, fuck.
This guy broke the rules.
That K three at one.
I'd have lost money.
So I believe I owe you one.
Oh, no, they're getting smarter.
Like three.
Wait, give me that.
Can I pick this up?
Is it illegal?
I got it.
Cool.
Wait, mine's cooler.
I like mine.
Yeah, I like mine.
Mine looks like a counterstrike knife.
It looks like I spent a lot of money on that.
Five bucks.
And I'll suggest a new fight.
You win the show.
You're 20 bucks richer.
Bring me the next one.
The competition's getting thin now.
Ready?
Only Kusa is left.
Oh, no.
And I doubt you're going to be able to take him.
But if you want to try, he's in the courtyard.
All right.
I'll take him.
Love him.
You don't think I'm going to club the next guy?
Don't go near that guy.
He's going to search me.
All right.
What's his name?
Uso?
Uso.
Hey, Kuso.
I'll see you in the ring.
I'll...
Hey.
Hey, Kuso.
Wait.
If you need money, feel free to ask anytime.
I'll loan you interest free.
Wait, isn't this the guy that wanted me to complete the quest?
Hey, Kuso.
Uso.
You.
Are you Kuso?
No.
Nice.
Here's a little thank you from me to you.
But I do really need a moth, man.
Can you help me out?
A moth?
Please?
I'll trade with you.
What does he want me to do?
Get a moth.
Just bring me one of those moths and I'll trade with you.
I actually have to collect one of the bugs?
I thought I was illegal.
Hey, you want anything?
How do you get a bug?
No.
Hey, Kuso.
Ah.
You want to fight me, huh?
I'm going to crack your fucking skull.
Now go back to Centurion.
I'll see you in the ring.
Okay.
Look out for you.
You're so strong.
Yeah.
Oh, look out.
He's so strong.
That's what I would be doing right now.
You'd piss him off so much.
Wait, put your both hands in the air with your palms facing out
and kind of shake them back and forth while you lean your shoulders.
Oh, yeah.
People fucking hate that.
Moth, moth.
Where am I supposed to get one?
I can't get a moth.
I'm in violation.
You see what's happening here?
I can't do it.
You have to press Y.
What?
What happened?
I have one.
I got one.
How did I get one?
I didn't even do anything.
Where is that?
Where is he?
It's two tongue, right?
Two tongue?
Two tongue.
Baby.
That's a fine specimen.
He's going to smoke a moth.
Check it out.
This is what I got for you.
Something good.
Buy one bottle of poison.
Buy three grams of G-Smack.
Somebody's going to fly.
I'll take it.
I don't even know what it is.
Yeah.
It's the heavy stuff, man.
Listen, just don't flash it in front of the axe, though.
All right.
Check it out.
This is what I got for you.
I want poison, too.
Give me the poison.
Here you go.
But I don't ever want to know.
And I also want...
I don't have any money.
Wait.
Where's the guy that loans money?
I want...
Wait.
Oh, he's doing the thing that says, like,
hey, man, the game's about to progress.
You're about to progress in the game, man.
Get ready.
Are you sure that you want to move on to the final chapter?
Club?
Yeah, I'm going to club him.
This guy thinks he's going to bring a knife to a crime scene.
Bring a knife to a club fight.
Or he might be the reason why he's the strongest opponent
is because he has a club himself.
We'll find out.
So you got your challenge.
You win, you get 20 UDs.
Get into the ring, Mr. Riddick.
Today, we have a fight to remember.
Okay.
The unstoppable Riddick against Cusa, the meat grinder.
Ooh, he's got his own little nickname.
So you've killed all the best fighters.
Nobody can beat me.
Now, there's only one remaining.
Only one?
And that's Bam.
And he's one dangerous-
What do you mean Bam?
Where is-
Where is he?
Is he down here?
Where do I find Bam?
I got a message from Bam.
He'll fight.
Problem for me is that you might win.
And Hoxie ain't going to like that.
Your problem isn't the Hox.
It's me.
Yes, you are a problem.
I'm a problem.
Hoxie will probably send Abbott down for you.
That is, if you win.
Will he now?
Abbott and me.
We have unfinished business.
Isn't he dead?
So what's the deal, Riddick?
You gonna fight or not?
It's five-
Didn't I shoot him in the face with a shotgun like ten times?
I'll fight.
Let's go.
Wait, they have to bring this guy down from upper management?
Does he realize he's about to get fucking clubbed?
All right, all right, all right.
I bet this is what you've all been expecting, huh?
Riddick versus Bam.
Need I say more?
You all fight to death!
Give me the club!
Okay, it's like-
That's the shit that you try to avoid at a kid's birthday party.
When you put the blindfold on him, you give him a big stick and it's like,
All right, spin him around!
And the kid just starts fucking swinging.
Oh, look out!
He's gonna hit one of the other kids!
I got a message from Bam.
He'll fight.
Problem for me is that you might win.
Did I win?
Hoxie ain't gonna like that.
I know.
Your problem isn't the Hox.
Hold on, I gotta settle that.
It's me.
I knocked him out of the circle.
You are a problem.
Hoxie will probably send Abbott down for you.
That is, if you win.
I did knock him out of the circle, though.
That's true.
We have unfinished business.
What's the deal, Riddick?
You gonna fight or not?
Of course I'm gonna fight.
Wait, the turrets-
I can't handle this much right now.
All right, the turrets shot him to death.
All right, let's go club!
Holy shit, this guy's good.
He's gonna beat me and have a weapon.
Don't let him win.
This guy-
Well, I feel like this guy should've talked.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Why did that guy not speak?
They dragged him out here like fucking-
What's the guy's name from Rocky?
Drogo?
He didn't even get to say anything.
Call Drogo, right?
No, what was his-
What's his name?
Talk to me.
Ivan Dro-
Oh, yes, Ivan Drogo.
Oh shit, a club.
I know what that is.
You're not still mad at me.
Let's see.
Am I still mad at-
Ooh.
No.
In fact, I'm feeling much better.
You're a hard ass, Riddick.
But we're about to soften you up.
God damn it, this is the nerf one.
Give me the real one, you fucking asshole.
Nice prank.
That is right, Riddick.
They don't know.
But you are going to show them.
There is a fury within you, Riddick.
Set it free.
What?
Okay, he does have superpowers.
You guys lied to me.
I thought you guys just said he could see in the dark.
Why does he look green screened?
Oh shit, club fight.
I have to-
Come on, I need to parry.
Wait, you can't parry bosses.
I-
I win.
No surveillance means it never happened.
Wait, do I want my club or his club?
My club.
The door is open.
The door-
It's an open door.
What was the point of that?
This guy keeps coming back.
Wait, there's a gun.
There's a gun.
I saw this-
No, that was a club.
All right, this guy keeps coming back.
So we're going to take him with us.
I'm not going to let this guy come back for like a third time.
Come on, get up here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
There's a ride.
There's a ride over here.
Whoever is editing this-
I want you to take a second.
Whoever is editing this video,
make sure you put in like a roller coaster going down
with a bunch of people screaming in happiness right there.
Very important.
What happened to this guy?
Oh, wait, this is where I-
All right.
Whoa!
Yes.
All right, he's still-
Whatever.
Because I had this stupid club out.
Club.
No club allowed.
Okay, but what about-
This is the ultimate test.
I can't bring my club in there,
but can I bring this dead body through?
Nope.
No clubs allowed.
Damn it.
I really thought it was going to happen.
Your head-
This isn't-
No bodies allowed either.
I have the-
Put the club away.
We're good.
All right.
All right, well, I'm back-
I'm just back here.
I couldn't escape.
What am I doing back in the prison?
You know, I just-
What am I doing back here?
I could have just got the hell out of here.
All right, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Lost his glasses in the mines.
They might be in the upper mines.
Okay.
Let's see all the blue skins dead.
I have to go down to the mines.
You've got a special key card from Abbott.
It ought to open some door
probably near the work pass.
Whoa.
All right.
I'm seeing a lot of German dot dot dots.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
I was supposed to delete channel points.
I forgot.
Thanks for reminding me.
I need to go to the-
There's a new guy over there.
I'm not going over there.
Hey, Riddick.
You want to buy smokes?
No.
I like this guy's voice.
Oh, well, I see that-
I see that they have successfully ruined the chat room.
It's on-
It's nothing there now.
It's just unreadable purple text.
Okay.
I really wanted to have a nice chat room,
but I guess that's just not going to be the case.
Okay.
Here's the key card.
Does this guy have anything?
If you find my glasses-
Okay, find glasses.
Go.
Who is surrendering?
I don't want that guy to be dead.
No, I did the Dark Souls.
It killed me so I can do-
Just kill me, kill me, kill me, kill me.
I don't want that guy to die.
I was going to break his neck, but it didn't work.
So what happened?
Access granted, and then he came after me.
Over here?
Dude, I just-
Touch the reactor.
Okay.
So, two doors.
They both have bad guys in them.
I have to get down to the mines somehow.
If I open this door, this guy freaks out,
so I have to go in this one.
I have to.
I still have poison.
I guarantee the people that have them.
And there's people that-
There's probably people that have-
Why is that hard to say?
That guy's hot.
You actually saw me through the wall.
If you find my glasses, give them to me,
and I will help you in return.
Did we fuck it up?
Are we safe?
I think we're safe.
Yeah, are you gonna punch him?
He's not gonna throw a punch, is he?
This fucking reset.
Okay.
So, should I just run through the door?
I think who cares?
I have to stealth.
Stealth.
Look, I just-
I open the door and the guy goes,
Here's the boxes.
Where'd he watch?
I found him.
Why do these guys all have laser sights on him?
Do I have to go over here?
Like, I'm gonna climb up.
Someone's here.
How would you even know that?
How would you know that?
There's no way you could have known that.
I didn't do anything.
Nothing here.
You're gonna die!
Wait, give me the gun.
Give me the gun.
Use Riddick mode.
What?
Didn't I get the DNA for this?
Wait, vent tool, right?
I don't know.
A real Wink?
It's been disabled.
It's not there.
You can't trick me.
That shit's been disabled.
Months.
Wait, why am I on an elevator?
Oh.
Did I make it to the mines?
No, no Winks.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Through the mines.
Jagger balance.
Straight to the spaceport.
I don't have any clothes on.
I cannot do what you ask.
Did I get him?
Holy shit, I got him.
Ooh, that hurt.
I need the DNA.
Okay, this is the Harry Potter ride.
The exact image of when Voldemort's sitting on the rock
and there's two or three people.
It's that ride at Universal.
You end up coming down.
You eavesdrop on a conversation they have.
Right here.
This exact spot.
I'm not making a joke.
That's just a reality.
I just had to say it because that's what I saw.
I'm just telling you.
That's what it is.
When you go there, you're going to be like,
oh shit, that's right.
Okay, I'll enter the correct code.
Minus two.
I've never been to Universal.
All right.
I was just looking at the fan.
Come on, stop it.
I didn't get him.
I didn't get it.
Close it, close it, close it.
Move out of the way.
What?
Why is the door closed?
They forgot I was in here.
Oh my lord.
I'm not soft-locked.
I got it.
I'll get it right now.
I don't understand why I can't pick up the rifle.
You rode the mines through Jagger Balance
straight to the spaceport.
Oh, that was pretty cool.
Let's dump him.
I don't want me to fall
and I know everyone thinks that everyone's waiting for...
I know everyone's waiting for it to happen.
So I'm just going to stop
because I know everyone thinks that's what I'm doing
and I'm not going to give you that.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not going to fall off.
No, that's not what I'm doing.
What's the point of this?
Why can't I get up here?
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Climb, climb.
Climb where though?
On the...
There's a gun on the bridge.
I can't pick it up.
Climb up there?
No, at least you can.
There's a door by the lift.
Is this a door?
No, this is not what you think it is.
Can't make that thing go up.
Just dodge the bullets.
Grab the gun.
I can't grab the gun.
I already tried it.
There has to be something with this, right?
I just don't know the code, but...
Can these be moved?
Why would they be here like this?
Can I go up here?
Flare the guard with some noises?
I'm just going to go fight them.
Give me that gun.
All right, good.
Did I really actually have to do that?
Hey, watch.
Can't touch it.
Security checkpoint.
I really do feel like I should have a gun at this point.
Is there one of those big things right here?
There is.
Dude, why are people saying piss and cock?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask them?
I'm sure you'll get a detailed write-up of why they're doing that.
All right, so I...
What am I missing here?
I can't take any of the lights out.
Wait, you're talking about me?
Can we go over to some other block and see if they'll let us in?
That makes sense.
Let's meet in the square half an hour after the shift ends.
All right, now you move.
Well, he looked at me.
What was that?
Okay, well, I'm obviously supposed to be here, but now what?
Kylo Ren?
What?
I feel like Spaghet right now.
Nothing here.
Okay, I'm just...
I can go through there.
Wait, climb this.
Is there a light switch in here?
There has to be, right?
Where's the light switch?
Please be behind me.
Is there a light switch?
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
I'm...
All right, I'm good, I'm good.
All right, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good, we're good.
I'm going this way.
Oh, shit, I can back-snipe this guy.
Oh, my God.
I need his body.
No, his body.
His body.
One, two, three.
I would have had it.
All right.
It would have had it.
Something quicker, the shift.
Why would you kick him forward?
Oh, my God, Riddick.
That's the...
Oh, he's stealthy, huh?
Why would you boot him towards the people?
That's the stupidest thing you could do.
So, we're going to not do any weapon.
We're going to just break his neck with our bare hands.
Oh, shit.
No, no, fine.
Just kill me.
Kill me.
Just do it.
I can't believe it.
It is kind of Kylo Ren, isn't it?
Wait, climb up, somebody said?
Holy shit.
Climb up.
It's still dark.
Nice.
It's dark over here.
Now what?
Can I jump?
Can I get there?
Can I grab that?
The bars.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to grab.
I'm going to wait until he turns around.
Wait, hold on.
Can I...
Well, keep looking.
Trying to do the Batman attack.
Am I actually supposed to do that?
Grab the bars.
There's no prompt, though.
All right.
No more hubris.
No more fucking around.
Just go on the bars.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
The pit.
I know.
I know, I know, I know, I know.
It's wild.
Can you believe what this guy Riddick did?
Yeah, I heard if he takes his glasses off,
there's a big red ray that shoots out of his eyes.
What?
Wow, what?
Did I drop?
Oh my god.
Everything was so blurry.
I tried to keep going and he turned around.
He has to be pretending.
Adjust your TV screen.
What happened?
Oh, who even shot at me?
I don't...
This guy?
Dude, he just ripped through one of his teammates.
He didn't even give a shit.
He blew that guy away.
He fucking murdered him.
Oh, did he forget?
Okay, now where?
Dude, okay.
I don't understand why it's doing this.
Press left.
Left.
I'm forward?
Okay, that's real dumb.
Why would they do that?
It's not left.
You have to hold up.
Where the hell am I now?
Oh no, but what if I cannot see where I'm going?
I've landed in a vault.
I get to bring that one back from like 2017.
But where am I actually though?
But I could go up, right?
I'm going to see me up here.
Is this...
Oh my god.
Oh, don't fall in there.
Was that hard?
Yeah, it was.
Because I was trying to press the up.
You have to press up instead of the left.
And the whole thing gets blurry.
Hey, look, this game was made in 2004, okay?
It doesn't have the same quality of life improvements
that we have in like 2020.
You can see me in here?
There's two.
Oh, they're not...
There's a guy in front of me too.
There's a guy straight ahead.
Fuck it.
You know what I mean?
Just go.
All right, guy up ahead.
I need a repair kit thing.
Should I jump?
Oh shit.
Oh my goodness.
Should I wait for him to...
All right, I'm going to try to go kill this guy.
Should I jump down and break his neck?
He might be the only one on there.
I think he's the only one down here.
I thought that was a person.
Wait, should I go now?
Should I just go now?
I don't think I can.
No, no, no.
I'm going to wait till he turns.
This is the loser's point of view.
What'd you notice?
You didn't notice anything.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You noticed what?
All right, motherfucker.
I'm done with you.
I've had it.
Don't keep looking.
Okay, there he is.
Just go?
You can't just go.
Do you see?
What?
Just go?
Just go.
All right, ban that guy for life.
I can run faster than the bullets.
Fuck it.
He's going to ban him for life.
Hey, don't shine it on my fucking face.
All right, this guy.
I got to...
Holy shit.
Okay, go, go, go, go, go.
Get through, get through, get through, get through, get through.
This is...
You got to go.
Are you serious?
You can do it?
Well, I need a healing location.
All right, so there's a guy here.
There's a guy here.
This dude right here is a pain in my ass.
And I can't get out here without him hearing me.
So, I've got to be very quick about it.
And I've got to Batman kill this guy.
Are you ready?
What?
That was a tuber reaction.
No, that was a...
Sure.
I was really annoying.
Whatever it was.
Oh, fuck.
Why would you climb that?
You guys want me to play this on hard.
Oh, no fucking way.
Maybe I'm going to go...
I'm going to make sure I go the other way.
Okay.
Am I lit up like a Christmas tree?
Am I just...
Am I...
Can they see my eyes?
Why can they see me from so far away?
What's the game plan here?
Do I have to get out of the window or something?
Just go.
Don't...
Don't listen to them.
All right.
Where is this dude?
There he is.
Okay.
I wish I could quietly jump out a fucking window.
The goal is to get to the other side over here.
Is he still there?
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
What the fuck was that turn?
That was an instant turn.
I'm ready.
Hold on.
I'm currently invisible.
But is he still there?
Oh my...
The other guy is here now.
All right.
This is my opportunity to go.
Right?
Fuck off.
Oh.
Is that guy facing...
What direction is he facing?
Did I save him?
All right.
I saved him.
Okay.
Thanks.
Sharpshooter.
All right.
There's a sharpshooter guard over here.
Is that the guy?
Okay.
I have to make it past this without dying.
Wait.
I don't know what this is.
Turn it.
Gas.
I don't know what I'm gassing.
I got the card.
Okay.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey!
What are you doing?
What's he fighting me for?
I didn't do anything.
What do you mean I aggroed him?
What are you talking about?
Wait.
Didn't I have to club out when I talked to him the first time?
Okay.
Cool.
Now what?
All right.
Place your bets.
Is it going to crush me on the ceiling if I get on this?
I just had to be sure about it.
All right.
I don't think this...
I really don't think this fall damage in this game.
I don't think there is.
Just a little.
Okay.
So now from here...
Lord...
Oh.
Right.
Okay.
Third floor.
What's that?
It can go up even higher.
Is there anything up here?
Is it just here for no reason?
Okay.
Well, that's dumb.
Mine entrance.
Ventilation hatch.
I think I just used the tool, right?
Sick.
What are my thoughts on duck meat?
I don't really eat it.
I'm not a big fan.
What the hell is this for?
It looks like a half-life map.
Now where the hell am I?
All right.
I'm...
Is it an elevator?
Am I getting this?
Okay.
Deeper down to the mining core.
This is not the mining core.
So why did I go in this vent?
What the hell did I go in the vent for?
Is that like a shortcut to get back?
He could have skipped all of that.
Hey, James.
Thanks for the 10 community subs.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
Well, it saved it again.
Great.
Wait.
There's a person out here.
Did they not see that?
He's gonna just fire a gun in the vent at me.
God.
This is the worst possible place to be right now.
I can't get out there.
This is sitting duck.
This is the worst.
I can't even run.
Okay.
Well, now I...
There's a guy here.
Let's wait for the guy to go by
so I don't kick the grate in front of him.
He...
He heard it.
He doesn't care.
All right.
Where am I?
I don't know where I am.
Wait.
Give me a key card on you.
I...
This is new.
Oh, this sucks.
Wait.
There's a...
Through like another dream tunnel.
Hell am I going?
Nothing here.
Keep looking.
What?
I don't know where he is.
Found him.
He's up there.
Oh, I...
I'm leaning is...
All right.
You know what?
Fuck it.
I'm going this way.
Okay.
What's up?
Holy shit.
I ground that guy up.
I gotta turn the fan off.
Wait.
The fan's off.
There's a body in it.
Should I go in?
Okay.
I'm going in.
I did it.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
This is the fan the guy was looking...
Why did that matter?
I want to turn that fan off.
Like go in the fan.
What happened?
Security check.
Wait.
I was already in here.
Am I fucked?
Yeah.
I think I am.
Just run?
Wait.
Did I...
I went through the entire...
Was that like the exit?
You leave and when you're done?
I can't just go.
I can't.
Go back to the elevator.
Okay.
So go back to the elevator?
God damn it.
Where's the elevator from here?
What the hell am I even doing in the mines in the first place?
What the hell am I doing here?
Do I have a code for this?
Oh fuck you.
Can I get up there?
Is there a way I can get up there?
Like jump up there?
Because I want to be up there.
I'm fucking confused as hell.
It also doesn't feel like that I have...
It also doesn't help that I feel like I have a concussion.
When I'm playing this game.
Star's D&D campaign was cancelled today.
So I'm going to peel off the sunburn and eat it.
It's pretty gross dude.
All right.
We're back here.
We're good.
Didn't I kill this guy?
Apparently not.
All right.
We're back here.
So now I went up.
I'm not going to go up in that vent.
What is over here?
First thing I need...
I have to go deeper into the mine.
Not climb around in vents.
Go the other way in the vent.
Yeah people must think I'm really really stupid.
Because I'm not touching the guns but I can't.
Okay.
So that's...
We're going this way?
That's just the door.
I went in that vent right there.
No this is not right.
Okay.
So here we are again.
Is there another vent?
Can I climb anything?
Because there's nothing here.
There's a tunnel in between the vents.
Wait.
Hold on.
Let me just check this.
Because I just jumped right in after this.
Surface panel?
Oh come on now.
Come on now.
I turned off the fan and now he is pretending.
I don't know how you would like know what to do here.
Jump up fan?
No.
Down the fan.
No I went down the fan last time and it was a big mistake.
There's nothing on...
Wait is there like a vent in the middle of fans or something?
Is there another way to go up here?
Use the panel again.
Go back in the vent.
Is there another vent that I can go in that's not this one?
Back through the vent.
Okay.
This is...
There's no other way to go.
I mean remember I kicked this and I freaked out?
Wait there's another...
Wait.
This is...
Vent Andy?
What?
No this is just...
I'm...
This is just where I was.
I have no idea where to go.
I don't know what to do.
You can use the service panel to turn the lights off so you can get past the robot.
Didn't I just do that?
I just did that though right?
Hold on.
I just did that right?
So technically...
I...
Wait that's a lie.
Okay.
Sides dot...
Hold on there's a guide.
What does it say?
Has this been nothing like a screamer or something?
I'm gonna be pissed if it is.
Okay.
Once you're...
Yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay okay.
Ignore the door at the end of this hall.
Go back to the junction.
Once the guard has been taken care of talk to the inmate.
Mosley will tell you about a possible way to get into the mines.
You probably know this by now.
He's one of the blue skins.
As a result kill him when you end the conversation.
This can be done easily by standing behind him and killing him.
Go back to the junction and choose a door to your left.
You'll have to be extremely careful here.
Because his entire court is being controlled by one of the guards.
Okay.
Check his body.
There's a key card on his body.
All right we're gonna go find Mosley.
We're gonna go to the door on the left and find the key card.
Wait I already did that.
Explore the upper balcony.
Just watch the ending on YouTube.
No!
Where was that guy?
This doesn't sound anywhere near where I am.
I'm not gonna watch the ending on YouTube.
Why would I do that?
I'm going in the...
Wait.
What's this?
What's that?
This is...
I think this is like a vent I can go in.
Look at this.
There's two vents?
No.
The link was two or three pages.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
Okay.
There's the elevator.
Oh Jesus.
This is...
This is not right.
Turn around and stand in front of the right elevator shaft.
Wait for a small platform to appear above you and jump on it when it's close enough.
You must now wait to be transported to a lower...
Okay.
We gotta go back to the elevator.
I...
This is all wrong.
Back to that elevator and go down instead of up.
All right.
Where the hell is that elevator from here?
Power, security, work...
I don't know.
Where's that fucking elevator?
I have no clue where that elevator is.
Nice map.
Should I just start over?
He doesn't know.
Dump down the fan and go to the elevator.
All right.
Are the elevators right here?
I just have to do this, right?
What do you...
What?
Wait, no, no.
I have to go this to the...
Right.
No.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But wait, does this take me to where I want to go?
Through the elevator thing?
This map is kind of a mess.
Okay.
Should I use it or should I climb up through the vents?
You missed it.
You're going backwards?
Wait, what?
Wrong elevator.
This is the bridge you couldn't get the gun on.
You were already here.
I walked past it.
What do you mean?
How?
I can't use this thing.
You need to go to the elevator that you got squished in.
Yeah, isn't it...
Don't I have to go through here though and like stealth to the left and climb up that thing?
Yeah, that's what I...
No.
Yes.
He genuinely...
I have no idea.
Dude, I'm half blind and every vent is the same vent.
And if I open this door, this guy instantly kills me.
No one knows.
Go up the elevator.
Go up the...
Well, this game is really fun until right now.
So climb up this shit again?
No, don't.
You're going the wrong way.
No, it's just the right way, right?
Don't go in the vent.
Just go up.
Go talk to vent Andy and give him the pack of smokes.
He gives you a map.
Go talk to vent Andy.
This has been such like a mess of going in circles.
I don't even know where that elevator...
That one that I jumped on that test squishing his self.
I don't know where it is.
Bring...
All right.
If it's...
Why?
I'm going to go over here and then watch the video of how to beat this.
Rick roll, but with a different link so people can't memorize it.
That's hysterical.
Thank you.
Turn around?
No, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where am I?
Okay.
All right.
All right, all right.
All right, all right, all right.
Everybody calm down.
How am I going to get into this vent?
Go up behind you.
How am I going to do that?
Go to the right end of it.
Oh my God.
Did I do that on purpose?
No, I did not.
I was trying to get the prompt to say to climb in the vent.
And it wouldn't happen.
And I can't jump in the fucking thing.
Oh my God.
Oh, he's not going to beat the game.
Well, all right.
In a game that's about being not able to see anything,
don't you think you'd want everything to be pretty clear?
No, shit.
That's completely the opposite of what we're talking about.
In a game where you can't see anything.
Oh, whatever.
I, it doesn't matter.
I don't think I can even get over here.
I'm really not sure I can get over to this.
Do I have to, can I press like a button?
You have to jump.
No, I don't.
Please tell me you're fucking lying to me.
You're lying to me.
I can't believe it.
I can't do it.
I can't get in there.
I'm fucking screwed.
I have to go through that door where the big guy is
and sneak over.
But the guy just has a gun pointed at me.
You know what?
Just, just go.
Holy shit.
He's finally not, don't turn.
Don't turn, don't turn, don't turn, don't turn.
Yeah, that's right.
Come on over here.
Come on.
Why don't you come over here and say that to my face.
Sick.
Okay.
Good, good, good.
I'm going to finally get there.
I'm not going to be soft locked anymore.
Oh, go, go, go forward.
Okay.
All right, I did it they do have indecent impression
Wait, no, there's this part too. Oh, no, remember this part
How much I hated this shit at least one of these guys has to be they're just in the same spot waiting for me
Damn it. He's still here. I know you've left probably for a while and I know I progressed but then I
Soft-locked myself then I had to come back here. Oh, this is gonna be impossible, isn't it? There's two guys just here
Okay, okay, okay
Impossible to when they're right there. I can Batman both of them
They just saw me instantly
Riddick is the easiest guy to see apparently. It's just really easy to see
Don't know how he didn't see that that apparently you didn't see me do that
Shot his own friend in the head
Thank God. Can you please come over here so I can just melee parry attack you?
I want to get out of this zone so bad. I can't run for it. He'll kill me
Now he's running the fuck away. Where is he? It's my opportunity
Go here. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Finally. Give me
Yes. Oh, yes. Thank God
Thank God. Yeah, there he had member this guy. This is the guy remember Mosley. Oh
Yes, okay, and then this cargo transport for the love of goodness
Okay, we have to go down now
Time for progress game progress game progress
Jump down
There's not a whole lot of fall damage, but I don't want to just die
Oh, I can jump on that bad guy a good guy
Dolan stay off my heart
What the hell happened to you?
Hey
He had a fucking train gun. All right
Do you want to buy the gun? Yeah
I will take the tranquilizer gun 30. Uh, I was just saying 30 quid
Here you go
Tranquilizer gun can be used to electroshock enemies. They will recover fairly quickly unless you neutralize them representing right trigger
Nice. Okay, cool. Now, what the hell does this matter?
Mining core finally my god
The air is thick smells of oil machines crushed rock
Something else
Yeah, we finally got some progress
There
He's screaming he's dead
Can I get a headshot from down here?
Oh, I can
Can I tranquilize the guy in the suit?
No, I can't
I can get the gun
No, you can't
Why is this guy walking over here? He's walking over here. Why why?
What do we do about this, dude?
I can't like smash the thing on his back. Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn off the lights turn off the lights
I thought that just trying to see if I could like smash the thing on his back because it took one shot last time
Yeah, yep. Yeah body detected
Yeah
He's actually moving get the fuck away from me, dude
Okay and go
Thank you, all right, we're good pretty good progress end to andy
Hey, I can't even you guys are too much
All right. So we got a ladder that way, but what's down here?
Super hard boss time
upper mine
No
Hold on. Did I just wait? Did I just go back up?
I don't want to do that. This is the air. Yeah, this is the same area from last time
Not using guns no this game does this fun thing that makes it so it electrocutes you if you pick one up
So what should I go up?
I was already up here
No, no, no, no, no, no, no the way that the big mech guy is walking is where I have to go
big mac
I didn't say that I said big mac
Big mac I do anything like that. He's not even looking over here
What was deactivated?
I'm gonna hide in this thing in here that my life support
Where is this guy going? Is this technically in the dark?
Okay, just stay right here don't fucking move
You have to be that I didn't do anything
I just didn't do anything
I stayed completely still
You didn't I was crouching. Yes. I was
What was that explosion?
What what did I touch?
It's there was a valve so I pressed the
Why is everything an explosion?
That doesn't make any sense
Is there a tripwire that i'm crossing?
Valve what the fuck I don't get it
Why is that there?
What is it there for?
You're still alive
That's just impossible
All right, i'm fucking out of here
Oh, no, i'm not
Okay, okay, I wasn't even close
Okay
Um, I can't open I can't do anything with the panel. I don't have a screwdriver
watch
Look look look everyone's screaming at me to open the panel. It doesn't do anything
Shoot the lights with a tranquilizer gun. It's not gonna do anything
Why is it electricity turn the lights off?
Okay, watch
See
It doesn't do anything. It just turns off the real defense and I got lied to again. It's okay
No, I want to deactivate it. Can I climb that?
Wait a minute. Wait explode them explode them. Good idea
Great idea got it. He's alive
Okay, i'm gonna do it. I blew them both up. I thought
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right. All right
All right, right, right, right
Listen listen, I know I tried to blow them up because I thought the explosion was gonna fucking kill
I figured that an explosion was going to kill people. It doesn't kill anybody but me i'm the only one it targets
Even if that guy's standing next to it doesn't do anything. Shut up. I'm talking to people leave me
Shoot the lights who cares? Let's go. Who's body?
Wait, who the fuck is this?
Get off of me. Uh, what?
I'm gonna take a look
nothing here
Where that's really awkward how they just kind of dump you and put it where like where the hell am I?
Do I have to go up there?
Okay. Wait, should I blow it up? I can blow it up. I can blow it up. I can blow it up. I should do it
Not yet. Where's the big guy?
Where's the huge guy?
I'm sorry. This is like top 10 ugliest games i've ever played
I'm sorry
Hey, do you see that thing in front of you? I'm gonna take a look i'm gonna climb this shit
I'm not no don't tell me to go touch the valve. I'm not touching the valve. I can't climb this. All right
I'm just gonna go i'm good. I'm good friend of foe friend or foe friend or foe
Um, it's the uh, the main character I didn't kill him. I didn't kill him. I didn't kill him
I didn't kill him. He's alive. He'll get up in a second. You're really kind. I'm jagger valance
Perhaps you've heard of me listener. Where's this spaceport straight to the point is it
Things down here work the same as up there redic. This is ron promen
Stop you give you get
You don't want to get what I can give jagger. Is that paper?
I suspect you're right. I did this to him
There's a sealed off area at the end of this corridor inside is a package that I need
But the area is filled with gas
Hmm
Hey, I guess i'm gonna go there's someone there's a chainsaw
Get into the sealed off area
I have a shield peek out your nose and you're dead selby
He actually he this is like a barricade
How did I miss that
Good, all right. We're good. Nice job. Uh, dude, look at all this shit over here
Shoot the lights
Yep, it's not a bullet. That's not what was that
What was that on dude?
dude
Okay, whatever fuck it. I gotta kill this light over here. I swear to god, whatever
I'm I just tried I couldn't can't get up this
Or this
Can't get up any of them. Anybody else in here one guy?
Oh good. Oh god, that was oh
That was not good
That was bad. That was very bad. That was gross
Jesus what the fuck why are they just
Please tell me I have a a checkpoint right there. What the hell is that?
Why?
Oh my god, you gotta be fucking
He's invincible
Why would they just put a guy just right there it's not like why
I can't even stealth behind that. It's just he's here. You're dead by shoot kill you. Where's the other one?
Kill this guy
Turn off the camera light thing
Tell me grinder. Sorry
Okay. Yes
Where is he?
Has to be dead. Yeah, everybody is good. Okay keep that keep what does it say?
Keep door shut at all costs gas leak
Uh, I hate this. This looks horrible. Just blow this. No, don't blow it up. Give me help, please
I don't know. I won't make a joke ever again. I promise. All right package delivered. He's dead. No. All right, what's up?
Where are you?
Hey, all right. Now give me the security code. You are as advertised ridic
Did you notice anything about the spot where you found the package?
That small cave is actually right above the home of a breed of creatures
Large and vicious ones
There'd be chaos if something were to open up a hole. I'm probably gonna call it here. I'll need a bomb
If you take me with you
No, nothing slows me down
Score ridic
See, I kind of want to play this zone. He's connected and can get you a bomb
Here's my good faith. I don't know why I want to keep playing codes. You'll need to reach him. I'll meet you at the space port
All right, you got it
Is there no fast way to get the hell out of here?
Get to tower 19 and get a bomb
Get to tower 19 head back from the mining core to the mine entrance then use the code to activate the elevator and go back
Up to the work pass
Oh, I have to go all the way back
Yeah, all right. So here's what's gonna happen. You're so close to finishing one hour max. Wait, is that for real?
In fact, no, that's not accurate
Is it true?
Like maybe 45 minutes 20 minutes
Is it actually true? Am I getting one guy because i'll just finish it now
You may be like halfway through. Okay. I'm not gonna lay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right, uh, we'll do this tomorrow
I'm good to go for three days in a row. I think
I'll be good for three days in a row. We'll do this again tomorrow
I I think this game is actually pretty fun
as
the juke as
goofy
That's why can I not say the word goofy?
What about saw? Uh saw two is gonna be played
But yeah, we'll do three days in a row
Well, if I beat this within like a couple of hours tomorrow, then we'll just i'll do something else for the time being
According to how long to beat you've got about two hours left. All right. Well, we'll we'll just do this tomorrow finish it up and
Maybe we'll do something else and just chill for like an hour or two
but for now
That's gonna be it
It's stupid. I gotta figure out I gotta tape this shit back. You won't beat this tomorrow dark athena. Oh, that's right
Well, let's at least get to the end of butcher's bay
Salt on dark athena sucks. Well, we don't have to play it
But yeah, i'll see you guys tomorrow
We'll finish this up. We'll maybe do something else
I'll see you soon
Hey, look if i'm still failing it tomorrow if I get to the end of butcher's bay tomorrow and it's like yeah
Maybe i'll just keep going
But that is the end of today
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Bye. Take care. Thanks for watching. I just had a lot of fun
I had way more fun playing this than I expected. So it's good fun
Here come the credits. These are all the subs
Every subs and gifted subs today going far away. Thanks all of you as always there also was a somebody just dropped
50 dollars
Thank you. It was gooberry juice. Thanks for the 50 bucks
a big five zero
Go and they say please play this this is oh
You didn't did you?
Oh, yeah, you did. I'm gonna watch this after the credits
Thanks, gooberry juice though. Seriously 50 dollars is a ton of money to give the streamer watch for the blog three clearly go
Totally not necessary. But thank you. I really appreciate it
Thanks for 50 fucking dollars and i want to say thanks to peaceful hailey for five subs
Insane like it blew my
Actually peaceful hailey gave 10 subs
I had a lot of reservations. I was worried about stuff like skill cap, you know
Like will the game and then 10 from james and then five from nay where you go in and it's just like can you click on?
Thank you guys that decides whether or not you're gonna win the game or not, but no really appreciate it was
So good, so addictive so fun. I mean like i'm like trembling right now. What is going on? It was insane
Do I still have like youtube videos playing?
Why did I not delete
Hold on. Why did I not delete this from last time? I don't know why I don't what's wrong with me
I don't know what is wrong with me. I don't know why I just turn the stream off and just fucking hold the power button
On my computer down. Hey guys, so like just take a minute after the stream just clean it up
Like what am I doing? Why do I do this to myself? Like it blew my expectations out of the water
I mean, I had a lot of reservations
Okay
Here we go. This is what you actually wanted to see
This is the reddit
It's nothing to do with reddit. My fucking chest hurts from laughing at this shit
I had to have a trial run to see if I really started laughing hard at something after coming back
um
Yeah
All right. Here we go. You ready? Three two one play it
All right, whoever is editing this I want you to take a second and whoever's editing this video
Get the fuck out of here
I'll see you tomorrow
That's good. That's worth it
Thanks a lot guys. I'll give you the link here. It is good night. Goodbye
We'll pick it up tomorrow when we left off
around 11 12 same time we've been doing it usually
Good night. Goodbye
And we'll see you later
Take care