Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grandpa here. And today, I want to show you my... how I run a restaurant!
So the game is called Papa's Berseria. It's a really fun game. You run your own simulated restaurant. It's a fast food joint, which I love those.
So let's get started here. Gonna get my first customer. Let's go!
So here's our first customer. Kind of looks like me. He looks just like me.
Alright, so you want a cheeseburger with some green stuff, some white stuff, and some onions. That seems easy enough. Okay, let's go over here.
I know we go over to the grill station. Oh, the only thing that's over here is bologna. Did we have... there's no such... I don't think we have burgers here.
So sir, again, I have to apologize. We do not have any burgers, but I gave you a bologna sandwich. Hopefully you like... you did like it.
No tip! No fucking tip!
You know, some people will say this game is hard. This game's actually pretty fucking easy. Like, take a look. You just drop the stuff on here. This is what she wants.
You got the tomato. You got the grunion. That's it. It's so easy. Put the ketchup on there. And there you go, missy. Hey, just take it. Put the bun on. Easy peasy.
This game is fucking easy.
What did you want, sir? Sir, I tell you, you can't yell at me like this. I just don't know what you want. You want pickles on it?
Hey, shut the fuck up back there, alright? I can hear you. You don't have to scream at me.
Oh, Jesus. Where... how much... what do you... Oh, God. This is so stressful.
That was a good dump. I'll tell you right now. All employees must wash hands, huh?
I never wash my hands. Let's touch some people's food now. Hey, how you doing? What can I get you, miss?
Yes, hi. How you doing? I'd like a regular burger with some tomato, some onion, a little bit of lettuce, a medium well burger, please. Thank you.
A little bit more onion, a little bit more lettuce. And can you please toast the bun, please? Thank you.
Yes, yours absolutely, sweetheart. Toasted fucking bun. I'll give you a toasted fucking bun.
Excuse me!
Where's my food?
Hey, I was having a fucking moment right there. Alright, just want to be clear on this right now, because there is some confusion.
You did not want a complete head of lettuce between two pieces of bread? No!
Well, what the fuck did you want? Look, I get it. I understand you're upset. It's taking a while to get you food. Everybody chill out and just listen for a second.
Nobody cares, okay?
They're right back at you, dickhead. But anyway, I am the only person working here. Don't you see that? My boss is a cheap son of a bitch.
He's not going to hire anybody else. I'm doing the books, I'm doing the cashier, and I'm doing the cooking. How fucked up is this? Right?
Wow, that's...
That is pretty fucked up.
That's terrible.
I don't. Like, where are all the other workers?
Seriously, all this game has taught me is how much it sucks to work in the restaurant business. Like, I don't ever want to do this.
I never want a restaurant job in my life, because that's how fucking awful this is. And I give two thumbs up to anybody that is doing a restaurant job right now.
And if you'll excuse me for one second.
Yes, I would like two large cheese pizzas, and I want them crispy on the bottom, not like last time when I didn't get them crispy. You understand?
And I also want them free drenched too, otherwise I'm going to complain to your boss. Dickhead.