Yeah, I'm addicted to Diablo 2. I know. I said last night, I'm like, I don't think I'm gonna be
doing Diablo tomorrow. Maybe just 10 hours and like, yeah, maybe we'll do something. Well,
no, I'm addicted to Diablo 2. This is hardcore still. I talked to Joel. We've decided we're gonna
talk about tomorrow is the day for bomb defusal. Just one more, I can stop. Yeah, when it turned
out that tomorrow was gonna be the day, I was like, all right, fine. We'll just do Diablo again.
But it's been tomorrow for two weeks. Yes, it has. It's been tomorrow since January
third. It's all good. It's okay. It's probably gonna happen tomorrow. Will it? I don't know.
Something happens. Shit happens. It's okay. But since I stayed alive last night, I was thinking
about it. Like, yeah, it's whatever. But those of you that are like, I'm not really into Diablo.
That's all right. That's okay. You don't have to be into everything we do here. But every five
levels, I'm going to do a tier list. I have 14 of them. Tier lists we have not done. So every
probably every like 30 or every like 30 minutes or so, there's gonna be another tier list. All
right. Well, then looks like I'm gonna have to watch if you're gonna do tier lists. We're going
full on double variety stream today. Every stream is a variety stream here.
Do one to start things off. All right, I could I could we could start one off with an easy one.
We're targeting all audiences with this one here. I hate variety. But yeah, the plan is tomorrow to
do keep talking and nobody explodes. That'd be funny if we've been doing this for this long and
saying, Hey, we'll do it again. We'll do it again. And we just play a different game. We just do a
different co-op game tomorrow. Am I going to play Temtem? I don't think so. I don't think I'm
gonna play Temtem. Oh, Freddy. Freddy. Freddy Dread. Yeah, it didn't even show up on the screen
because I'm on my intro screen. But that was $200 from Freddy. 20,000 bits from Freddy Dread.
Welcome back again, Freddy. Thanks for your insane contributions. And yes, this is Freddy Dread. Yes,
this is this is the real Freddy Dread. Some of you guys like it. No. Oh, yes, it is a real one.
They say, German, I'm in Vegas for my first time in five days. Oh, hey, dude, I've been in Vegas for
the first time since last week. I'm in Vegas for the first time for five days. Please suggest
something I should do or see. Well, do I've got something for you to do. I have a very, very
special place that you should go to. It is a restaurant. It is... Finish the sentence, guys.
It's in the... Where is it? You guys all know. Where is it? It's in the... Do you guys not know?
No, it's not in the link. Thank you. It's in the link. It's a restaurant. It's my favorite restaurant
in Vegas. It is Hash House at GoGo. Go to the one in the link. Oh, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Not the link in the description, the link on the strip. And if you like blue cheese,
get the blue cheese burger. It's right up there on their favorites on the menu. It's a huge burger,
double patty, thin, delicious, juicy patties. You've got to go to Hash House at GoGo and tell
them German985 sent you. The four of you that have done that so far. And when you say that,
they're not going to know who the fuck I am or what you're talking about. They're just going
to think you're a strange person and you're going to get charged extra. No, but for real,
Freddie, thanks for the... What are you doing in Vegas? What are you doing in Vegas? The German
fan tax. He's in Vegas doing his best. They will be like that guy who was eating tuna from a can
with his bare hands. Probably performing. That's pretty sick. You're here for five days? I might
have to... I tried to read it. Any news on keep talking? Yep. Tomorrow. It's always tomorrow.
It's always tomorrow until it doesn't happen, right? But that's a shitload of money to start
the stream off. Thanks a lot, Freddie. Have fun in Vegas. Besides eating, oh my God, I did another...
I knocked the same battery over on my desk every time. I have this exact same pattern where I go
like this with my hands. When I talk... So when I talk... You guys can't even see this. Nevermind.
Actually, yeah, you can. So when I talk, I use my hands. If you're standing in a vicinity around me,
just watch out because I go fucking all over the place. I'm like, let me tell you this.
The thing is... And people just think I'm nuts. But anyways, I do the same motion. I go out and
I go to the left. So I go to talk that way and then bang into the left. I do that forward and
left and I knock down stuff on my desk all the time. And you can do... Your hair looks weird today.
You know, I told myself that I was going to stop reading out one negative comment that I see in
my chat rooms. I'm supposed to be doing that anymore. Anyways, yeah, I talk with my hands a
lot. So just... Now I'm realizing why people stand so far away from me when I'm talking.
I'm just figuring this out. No, this is... When I talk to somebody, they usually
like at least seven feet away from me and they keep going like this. What does this mean?
What's that mean? Why are they doing that? Because you're a spit talker. Yeah, no, I'm not.
Anyways, so we're going to start... You want to do a tier list first?
Is that what you guys want to do? Is that the plan? We start off with a tier list? All right,
we'll get one out of the way. All right, the first one I'm going to do is... Let me move this over
here. First tier list is a lot here. All right, we're going to do... We'll do pet reptiles for
the first one. That sounds pretty good. Pet reptiles. I'm going to be a little smaller
so you can see all the reptiles. Okay, pet reptiles. Tier lists. Well, can I even do... Can
I do this tier list if I've never had a pet reptile before? It comes in my eye. Can you see it? What
is it? In this eye right here. It's wicked blurry. What's in it? That was weird. All my vision was
just blocked by like a floating thing. All right, a pimple in your eye. No. All right, can I do a
reptile tier list if I've never had a reptile before? Can I do this? Well, how about this is
just like what I would want as a reptile owner? No, I can't. No, no. So hold on. If I've never...
That doesn't make any sense. No, I'm doing it. I don't care. All right, turtles. For pets or...
I'm going to use this as like what I think is coolest or what I'd want. Unfortunately,
turtles are cool, but I don't know if I'd really want one. What is this thing? I don't know what
that is. These are all snakes. Where's the huge dragon? There we go. But that's a... Okay,
wait, that's a giant tortoise. That's kind of cool actually. I don't want a snake. They're cool,
but I don't want one. Bearded dragon? That's what I want. I want a bearded dragon probably the most
or a huge lizard that eats its own room. Yeah, I know the names. I've watched the reptile guy
and I know what these are. They're like the best geckos. Crested skull geckos. What are they called?
Crested geckos? Crested geckos? I knew. See, I knew it. I knew what I was talking about.
These are supposed to be the best geckos. Is this a chameleon? Chameleons seem kind of fragile to
me. I don't think I'd want one as a pet. They're really interesting animals, but they feel fragile.
I feel like I would hurt it or something. You know what I mean? Like they just have these little
arms and I feel I wouldn't want to handle... I would want to just have them to enjoy viewing.
They're pretty fragile. Yeah, I just don't... I wouldn't want to potentially do any harm.
Um, we got a snake. What's with the turtles? There's too many turtles and too many snakes
on this list. What is that? This is skateboard. That's not even... That's not... That shouldn't
be on the list. I don't know what this is either. This is a leopard gecko. Those are pretty cool.
I like them. All right, let me refine this. Big tortoise is cool, but I feel like they take big
dumps. I don't know if that would want one. Oh, this thing takes big dumps too.
Okay, that's all right. Would I rather have a snake or a turtle? Where's the ball python? Right
here, right? This is a ball python, isn't it? Or is it this? Ball python? No, which one's a ball
python? This brown one here? I mean, I really don't... I don't know. Is this an iguana or
something? I don't know what these are. Turtles are a pain to take care of. I've never had one.
I don't know what these are though. I feel like if I don't know what it is, it shouldn't be this
high up on a list. I'd probably... But no, but if you have a snake, you have to feed a snake
mice, don't you? Remember, what's with the title and category? What? This is Diablo 2. We're playing
Diablo 2. Diablo 2 looking... Yeah, this is just starting the stream. Diablo 2. See, look at the
background. It's coming up. All right, I think this is accurate. What's with the quality of the start
of this stream? You mean high quality? That's what they meant. Cool. Big ass cup here. Look at
this thing. Isn't this too big? There's like 16 ounces of liquid in here. Why do they make them
like this? It's such a thick outside and they make it huge. All right, sick. That's a normal size cup.
Yeah, I think this is accurate. Why did you buy it? Because it fucking looked neat to me. I didn't
buy it. I'm drinking out of Kim's cup today. You're a thief. Yeah. All right. All right,
that's it. Bearded dragon. I want a big tegu, is that called? Or I don't... Tegu's the best
big monitor style lizards, right? Yeah, crested gecko. This is an accurate list.
He's awesome and I don't want a skateboard. Cool. Hey, you know what time it is now? Diablo 2.
Let's go. Dude, how the fuck are you guys? Welcome to Act 3. Where are the bone friends? By the way,
take a look at this. I did some work. I've been working. I made this much easier for you guys.
If you take a look at what happens, take a look at this shit. Ready? Bingo. Now look at not only
do we have accurate stats and everything, you can see how many points are in it and you don't have
to pick the category. You can just click on the one you want. For instance, like here we are
banging. Now there's two. I can take that away. Look at that. We don't have to spend so much time
doing this anymore and check it. We come right back here. Bingo. Done. What the hell does that
even mean? I missed. Oh, you missed the last stream. Oh yeah. Okay. So how this works? No,
everyone knows. Let's get our spaghetti. Um, eat some monster here. What was the last thing I did?
Didn't want to kill on Dario again. I'm so addicted to this. I wanted to play it so bad after
streaming that I went to bed immediately because I knew I wanted to wake up early to play it again.
Where are the skeletons? Well, I have to kill something to get a skeleton. We need to win
admission first. They don't know. All right. How does it work? Let me explain. So, uh, you level
up in this game with an experience bar. What do you fucking do? Okay. So you level up with an
experience bar. When we level up, we're going to get five stat points to put into these. And
I have 50 strength as a necromancer, which is, it's a little odd this early. 75 vitality. The
chat has been picking these. These are skill points, right? So the images that you're seeing
here are all laid out across here. Before yesterday, we were picking categories first,
and that was sort of a pain in the ass. So I figured just dump the whole thing out,
stop blaming chat. And this is what chat has selected so far. Uh, they, they really like
skeleton friends, but they don't like giving me any offensive abilities. So I'm forced,
unfortunately, to walk around with an axe and swing at it with a bunch of strength.
So, and not only that, they've been incredibly indecisive at what they want to do here
because look, we have points in skeleton, we have points in skeletal mage, skeleton mastery,
but also we're going multiple points down here into golems and golem mastery. They're not really
sure what they want to do. He's mad about this. No, I think it's fun. What are the skeleton's names?
Okay. So there's seven. So it's Laffy, Daffy, Sleepy, Snoozy, um, Grumpy, Hungry, and Ed,
whatever they are. Got Donkey? That's Shrek. All right. Well, let's get some skeletons.
Hungry? Really? What's wrong with Hungry? You missed the dark wanderer. No, I didn't. I knew
he turns into the slugs. All right. We didn't even get that. No, no, we got to talk to, um,
no, we don't. You act free sucks. Let's just be real. How long is the stream going to be today?
As long as until I'm satisfied. So he's very long. Yesterday. I was not satisfied for a long
time. Here we go. Here's our friends. Oh yeah. So actually it's 10 people both fight in Dariel
till you get a unique, but I got to make some progress first because act three really is such
a pain in the ass. And then we get to do act four, which is the best act in the game.
You started catching your streams live playing Minecraft. It's the dream. Well, welcome.
Oh, don't you have to find the weapon? Yeah, you got, I got to find a weapon out here.
The random event. How many players? Uh, five setting the players to five. You can say I'm
in single player because it doesn't have one yesterday. I got my account up and, um, I don't
know why it did. So, uh, I have a band fucking battle net account and I have to play in single
player. This is hardcore. If I die, it's over and I can't get this character back.
Uh, but when I do players, I can set the game to be harder. So the game thinks there's five
people in the game right now. So everything's hard. I think I already found it. Oh, how would I?
Oh yes. And by the way, every, uh, every 30 or 40 minutes, we're going to do another tier list.
We're doing a double here. What did I say? Every, every like, every like five levels,
there's so much poison in acts two and three. Yeah, there is. He's going to forget. No, what
the stream has been live for 20 minutes. So at minute number, let's see. So when did I,
what 10 minutes ago did I start? When did I run out here? All right. We need to find the spider.
The thing about act three is you have to find member of the cube and the staff and all that
bullshit in act two. Well, they decided that they wanted to do that, but make it add like three more
items to find. So we have to find the heart, the brain, the guts, the blood that we've got to find
so much shit and make this giant flail, which then lets us go to Mephisto's lair. We never played
this before and there's nothing over here. That's a spoiler. That's okay. Imagine explaining that all
to a boomer. Well, if you were, if you're a boomer, you may have played this game already.
Something that a boomer might know more than you guys right now is the necromancer skill tree.
All right. We can, we're not going over there. Oh fuck. I forgot about this. Damn it. It upgrades
the gem that's in your inventory. God damn it. I've ruined it. That gem shrine. If you bring any gem,
it upgrades it immediately. If it's in your inventory to the next higher quality,
I could have just made like a flawless. I'm just going to, I think I've probably restarted the whole
thing. Yeah. I'll restart from scratch. All right. Well, where do I, where the hell am I going?
Looking for the spider cavern. Ooh. Oh, that wasn't even a good one. You're saved scumming.
I'm not saved scumming. That was a stunted room. Here we go. There's a well up here. Thank God.
Ah, that's some good sight here. Make the top corner of all different face cams of you.
If people wanted me to do that yesterday, but that's, I feel like that's going to get old real
quick. That's, you know, that's going to get old very quickly. Do it. All right. Um, it's going to
take a long time. I got to go in a place that's safe. Okay. There we go. I'm safe here, right?
This is going to fucking break my computer and I'm going to delay them too. So when I move around,
this actually might fuck up the computer though. That's not, why is that not working?
No, I can't. It can only be one source. It can only be one source. It can't happen.
Just, I, I get, I'm going to have to like invert the colors and move them around. I can't delay them.
It has to be different cameras because these are, these are technically a copy
because now it's going to do it all of them. Yeah. Watch this. Ready? I can't. It's still connected.
Sorry guys. We tried. I need like six cameras. Worth a shot. Yeah. I can't do them individually.
Go get, go get six cameras. What did I do? I just became the green goblin.
Which one of these is real? All right. Get rid of this one. I'm still alive, right? No,
no, I'm playing Diablo 2 now. That's weird. You look sick. I look like I'm about to puke.
Cartoon. Hold on. Oh, wait. Hold on. Wait. We need that music.
Wait, wait, wait. We need, hold on. We need that music to play.
Someone that's like, what was it called? No, no, no. It's longer than this. Isn't it?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. How old is this?
It's a little, two days maybe.
Can I play Diablo 2 now, please? I don't, I, I don't know what to tell you. I don't understand.
I don't, okay. I'm playing the game now. I'm going to play the game. That was not, not even close.
Wait, I want to see that. Show it to me. Show it to me. I need to see what I, I need to see what
I've done. I need to see that. Please show me. Please. Don't show them. Show me. It wasn't that
bad. It was, it was kind of humorous. No one clipped it because no one thought it was funny.
Oh, really? Nobody thought it was funny?
If I die right now in hardcore, if I can trap somewhere. God damn it. All right, here we go.
A necromancer. What am I looking for? Stony field or something? I think my girlfriend's cheating on
her husband. What do I do? Um, I don't think it's going to, I don't think it's going to work out.
Um, why did I read that? Because it was the first thing that my brain looked at.
All right, come on. We need spider caverns. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it.
Why are we all spread out? Everyone join together. Wait, I need the, uh, the permanent stat point.
Do another joke, E-clown. How about you sit down? You've been standing this whole time.
You were waiting for an opportunity to point and scream during a lull in the, uh, in the,
in the performance here.
You bring a potion to this guy and he gives you stat increases. Stop reading chat messages. A
red spy is in the base. What? I had to breathe halfway through that because I went right into
it. So that's why it stopped when it went that fast. I had to breathe. All right, get in here.
Let's go. Big fight. Big fight. Can't just drop a track like that without warning.
I was about to turn the fucking cam on. He puked green and played sound again.
After every fucking bad thing that happens, I'm going to do that.
And I'm going to see how long it takes for a thousand people to leave. Found it.
If more people leave from Bugleberry than they do from that,
then Bugleberry really might need to retire as a hero.
Oh shit, need mages. I'm kidding. Why would I ever retire Bugleberry? The best character ever.
Is there a unique here? All right, we're looking for the eyes or the brain? What's in the cavern?
I forgot to look at all these potions. This is a joke.
13 to life. They're getting rid of these.
Still keep that. That's good. Add. Add. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Sell. Only big
potions. Uh, I wish I had a bigger belt. What keys do I have? Get rid of that. Get rid of, uh,
all right. Put these here. I'm sorry for backups. Get rid of that. Okay. Oh, I got six. One.
He's still... Why is he playing a normie build?
Is the title of my stream working? Is the title of the stream working? Hello? Hello? Is the title
working? I didn't pick any of this. Why did he pick a normie build? Hello? Are you calling Bugleberry
a bad character? No. Now he's mad. No, he's not. He's fucking glad. Bugleberry emote? Yeah, and
it's going to be 12 slots. I'm going to ruin my chat. All right, let's go get that side.
And it's going to be a screen cap of when he goes...
Oh! It's going to be like Bugleberry 01 through 12. Oh, he's got something there. H22. Yep.
Yeah. All right. How many slots do I have? Well, there goes... There's your April Fool's joke,
guys. It's going to be like 35 slots or like 38 slots. Oh, I don't know about that. I'm going to
have to get rid of it immediately though, because that would be a disaster because people would be
doing that and other people's streams and shit. And nobody wants like a 50 slot emote destroying
their whole chat room. I'm not going to... I don't want to be responsible for that one. Unleash the
plague. No. It's so bad. Hey, you want to know the quickest way to make a bunch of people hate
your guts? Ruin their stream with a 50 slot emote that people spam. What's this guy with
the mask on in the chat? What's this? Can we fucking take care of that? That's it. And now do
that across 5,000 channels. What the fuck is that? Jerma? Fucking stupid, man. That's it. That's it.
It's not going to be like, oh, that was funny. Fucking Jerma. Who the fuck's that?
Fucking dick. Holy shit. That was a big chest. Flawed diamond. Always pick up the diamonds.
Anything else? And then that person then goes into their Discord and gets in a group with a
couple of friends, other streamers or something. You guys see this like Jerma, bugleberry emote
thing? Yeah. Yeah. Who's this fucking guy? I think he is. That's funny, dude. You could like
take over a whole channel with that. That's funny. Imagine the fucking, imagine the fucking
what kind of person you got to be to do that. That's so funny, dude. Yeah. And I got it. And
by the way, that happened. No, no, no. Seriously, that's such fucking bullshit. I just got an ace
in CSGO when it happened too. And that's in the dead people where I just ruined everything.
I had to turn away from the computer, take the middle of it and ban a bunch of people and shit,
man. Who should fucking do something about that? I can't believe I still haven't found this thing.
Why do all the streamers sound like the E3 actual gameplay fake voice chat?
I don't know. That's pretty good. Come on, give me some, give me some unique.
F-rude. Are we missing anybody? I'm, I'm, I don't even, I'm missing like six people. I wish I had a
move instead of just D. This is guys. If you come to a Diablo two stream and you see the arrow
pointing down here on the left mouse click some, Hey dude, somebody help this guy. Omega low. Look
omega low, omega low. What is it? Halo and the Nancy Drew game were among the most popular
Steam games in December. No way. There's no way. No fucking way. What? I can't believe it. How?
Do we have a source on this? Hold on a second. This is PC gamer. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Okay. Hold on. I have to read this. I don't fucking believe this. I really don't. No, wrong thing.
Where is it? Why can I capture this? Horn tabs. Yeah. No. Okay. Here we go.
Halo. I can't fucking believe this. This is going to be fucked up for a second. We need to read this.
Okay. This has to be a joke. No, it's not. Red Dead. Okay. Valve has posted a list of the most
successful Steam releases in December. And as usual, it's a mix of the expected. Halo,
Red Dead Redemption 2 and surprising Nancy Drew Midnight in Salem. VR Paradise Gentleman's Club.
The list isn't ordered. So we don't know which among these sold best, but it's testament to
the wide range of games available on the platform. The list is determined by the amount of revenue
generated during the first fortnight of each game's launch. No, no, this is not this. This
is not us. This is a popular franchise. This has nothing to do with us. Even the screenshot though
is no, there's no way. It's probably just really popular. I don't, I have no fucking idea, man.
Don't ask me. All right. Anyways, weird shit today. Huh? Weird shit today.
I guess I'm real weird shit going on. Nobody else even streams that game, but don't people
buy that game? Is the Drew crew really that large? It can't be. I talked a lot of shit too. I said
there wasn't enough people on the Drew crew to even make a whole baseball team and it was the
second most revenue generating game on steam. Uh, reverse it. They're the ones in the stadium.
They weren't ordered. So you're telling me that VR Gentleman's Club could be more popular. Is this
even the right place to get the item? It's not. No, it's not. I'm not, I'm in the wrong place.
Yeah, I'm in the wrong place. It's the spider cavern, not the arachnid lair.
Jeremy, how many copies did I buy? I mean, I bought like 20 Nancy Drew games or something.
It's guaranteed top 20. Spider cavern, spider cavern. Oh, here's the waypoint. Literally just
you. You made it make millions of dollars. That would be something, wouldn't it? Not in the right
place. Apologize. What's this link? Nancy Drew midnight in Salem. All time peak 800.
How much is, how much is midnight in Salem? How much is midnight in Salem?
$20 was 800 times 20, about $1,600. That's not 1600. It's like, it's like 20 grand.
A lot of y'all getting that wrong.
And people, what people make fun of my math. A lot of y'all getting that wrong.
That's my favorite comment in the chat. All right, so let's just assume that 800 people bought it.
There's no way 800 of you guys bought that game during that, during those streams. No way.
I would assume maybe like six of you. Not a thousand. We all bought it. Teenagers play
video games too. That's what I'm saying. I think this is just a weird coincidence.
I don't think this means anything. It's very odd, but I don't think it means anything.
All right. Well, the next time I get approached by a brand and they say, Hey, Mr. Albertson,
we just want to know we're just so we can be confident that you could potentially help us
out with talking about our product. Do you have any, any kind of experience? And I'll just link
them this article and go fucking Nancy Drew was top 20 on steam. Nancy Drew was, and they'll go,
Holy shit. If this guy can sell Nancy Drew, he can sell any. You're a Scientologist.
What the hell are you talking about? Look at how big this forest is. Missing a mage. We need to
have a full stack of friends. Otherwise it's not worth it. Ring sucks. Charm. I'm sorry. Now it's
stuck. Somebody, uh, no, I'm not, I'm not going to influence chat. Somebody, somebody said,
we're doing this all wrong and I'm not going to influence chat, but we're doing it all wrong.
Just want to make sure everyone's aware of that. All wrong. All of it. Wrong. All wrong.
Now what? Nancy Drew is now the most played game in history of steam. And it's all
thanks to this wacky streamer. Yeah. I, I, you can, I can inspect and edit too.
Now this is all messed up. What happened to my skill tree? The Drew crew strikes again.
We go. Now I can see what the hell I'm doing. All right, let's go. He hates the joke. He can
inspect. He can edit. I'll get back to town as that only works on your parents. You know, you,
you could, you could edit a page that says that you were nominated for best actor in a supporting
role and send it to your mom. And she'd be like, what's going, what's going on? What? I didn't know
you, you were an, wait, what? You're an actor. Who did this? I know because I did it one time.
She was like, what the heck? I'm just kidding. And then she got real sad. She was like, oh,
you asshole. Not doing it. Everyone has expected it. Didn't do it. Didn't do it.
Now everyone's pissed because I didn't do it. All right. Oh, what's this rune?
Do I already have one? No, I can, I can select every single rune, even Zed or Zod.
The hardest rune to find in the game. Zod. That shit used to go for like 30 SOJ. It was the most
expensive thing in the whole game. It was insane. It was impossible to find. It was part of so many
rune words. Some of the best rune words in the whole game were because of Zod. What was, what
was Enigma? What was the actual rune word? Listen to this nerd. Oh, that brings back memories.
Almost a level up. How many people did you scam? With Zod? I didn't. I never had a Zod. Some runes
you can't get outside a ladder. That's right. It's not fair. I can't get them. How's that fair?
You, you, you reserve some of the coolest stuff in the game for like the best players and the ones
that come on. It's not fair. Blizzard doesn't care. Why isn't the Harajuku in the inventory?
Because I don't, I don't like it. I don't like it being in my inventory because I like it to
be a clean inventory. I like having structure. I know. Yes, there's been 20 potions. That's
because my belt sucks and I need a better belt. Just stay tuned. It's about to get way cooler,
but it's a cube. I know. Uh, what do I, what do I want to do? I want to gamble. All right. What
do I have? What's the worst thing I have? Boots. I need better boots. It's boots or ring. Should
I buy a ring? I'm going for it. I'm going all in. I'm just going to buy a ring. Here we go.
Level one telekinesis. Too bad. That's not teleport. I thought it was teleport and I almost
shit my pants. Get a belt. My belt's okay. I need boots. Well, I'm out of money. So we just said
your belt was shit. Well, I mean, we're holding stuff. There's only two slots. You can have up
to, I believe five slots in some of the big belts, big heavy belts. I didn't do that though. So that's
false. You know what that means? It's time for some chat interaction.
Chat fix everything. Plate mail. Let me stop this blunt junk. We're about to go into the
marsh I think. Still in the forest. Somehow. Somehow we're still in the forest. I don't know how.
Player jungle. Yeah, I gotta go back. Unless if the waypoint's right here, that's good.
This is probably as close to a pacifist run as you can get in this game.
Second unique in the game. And it's probably going to go right to Vic. Yeah, unique, unique,
unique. I used to do this thing where I would, I'm kind of a psycho about this,
but I would hold on to uniques as long as I could and then do just a mass unveiling of what it was.
This is back when I didn't really know the game very well. It was so much fun. Especially with
rings. If you got like four or five rings and you're like, all right, which ring is it? Because the
ring could be, it's only, you know, there's so much variety. Let's go. Oh, that's, that's,
ah, it's good though. 10 strength, 35% chance to open wound. 10% HP per hit. This is going to
the Vic. 10% health stone per hit. He's never going to die. This guy's never going to die.
That's 10% HP. Kyle would have used it. Kyle can't even equip it. So no, he wouldn't have.
Got to fight the monster here. Champion rat man. Oh, I must just fucking, I thought it was another
one. We got the, uh, the good bin though. This is a quest at a lack. I get this shit out of here.
I have so much crap. My inventory is loaded with free up. Um, I can get them later. Put them down.
How big is this? Actually kind of normal attack. That's kind of good.
Come back for it. All right. Uh, return to the good bin to Ormus.
Ormus congratulates you. Old spirits of Skatsim will watch over you for returning.
Bro, why do you, you have a big what? Ormus will now once again use his powers to protect the
innocent from the shadow. Yes. Tearless now? Nope. This magic ring does me no good. Here, wear it
proudly. Okay. What is it? Well, thank you Ormus. That's not bad. Oh, but a hunter to
attack rating. Holy shit. That's really good actually. Hold resist, poison resist, dexterity.
Oh, we're going to get rid of, what are we getting? Yeah. Let's get rid of this.
333. That's a good number. That's a weird 33% number. All right. Let's, uh, let's, let's try out
our new technique to get the skills. Huh? What do you say? 16 to 37. Yeah. It's time to get rid of
this. How much strength do I need? Don't I have that? Wait. Oh, it's 54 strength. Why do I care
about strength? I don't, I don't want you to do 54 strength, whatever. All right. Uh, so first of all,
when you do this, you could do me a favor and, um, click on a stat that you want. If you click
on the screen, if you, if you have extensions enabled, you can click on the screen. If you
so inclined, which stat do I want to do? Did derma stay up all night? Yeah, dude. Yep.
How come I can't see it? That's why it looks like you guys want strength, strength, the gang.
Equally as important. Let's, um, whoops. Uh, would that go equally as important?
I'm going to actually put this, where am I going to put this fucking thing? All right. So as you see,
uh, here are what we have for points right now. Skeletal mage. You get left is summoning,
middle is bone, right is curse. Don't have to pick a, don't have to pick a category anymore.
Just what do you want me to do? What do you want the point to go? Interesting. Very interesting.
Interesting. Let me give this about two seconds. Iron golem it is. Thanks for voting.
And we're going to go like this and iron golem now has one point in it. And just in case you
needed to know, needed to see it over here. Here we go. Iron golem iron golem. You have to transform
a metal object. So you need something, a weapon or armor and, uh, takes on the properties of that
item. And then also it has thorns. So 150% of all damage it takes, it returns it back to the attacker.
So, um, so the axe now, what do I lose? I'll turn, I'll turn him, I'll make him from this.
Just hope he doesn't die. Oh no, this is not, it's no, no, no, I can't wear this. This is two-handed.
I lose two to gray skeleton. Nope. I thought it was one-handed. This is not made out of metal.
I mean, it's, it's, yes it is. This ring. Watch this. Ready? Check this out. Uh, does that work
on rings? I thought it worked on rings. There he is. And he's made out of a rare. So he's
fucking awesome. He gets all the properties from what we just did. Good luck taking this down.
Just don't exit the game for a while and don't get him killed. All right. Well, there's that quest.
Now we need to talk to Asherah. I think it's down here and then believe. No, that's probably, uh,
where's it? It will carry over when you leave the game. Pretty sick. Our armor. All right. The act
three, the act three mercenaries are awesome, but I don't want to lose, uh,
Vic. How many golems can you have? Only one. But the more points you put into golems, the more
powerful that that single one becomes to the point where it becomes its own character
that is unstoppable. All right. So now I can hire, I can hire, but I'm not going to get rid of Vic
because it's good. I like the aura. Okay. Quest completed. Now we just have to find this stupid
thing in the spider cavern. I'm going back to the waypoint. Spider forest, spider cavern. That's a
ractid lair, not the correct one. What are you shooting at? Do the gold birdie thing? Yeah,
but isn't that, that's a random drop though. The gold birdie quest is a random drop outside,
right? From a champion. Where the hell can I go this way to the left here? List waiting room.
I wish I had a ding, ding, ding ready. Like you're the first person to say that we were waiting for
somebody. So you won. You won. What was the name? What do they win? Many people have said that.
Well, that's the first one that I've noticed from, I thought it was another one.
Raul or Tao. I'm giving you your first rune word. Raul or Tao. Remember that one?
Now we're in the great marsh. Where is the spider cavern? That's my lightning resist. Pretty bad.
He kind of looks like a skeleton too, the waypoint. No, I don't want to be here.
I need to go into, I need to find the spider cavern. Can you get a McChicken? I don't know,
that depends. How far away is the McDonald's from where you live? You have a car. You have Uber Eats
available or one of those other apps. And you walk. I mean, are you in an area where I can just take
a walk, the sidewalk so I can get there. And you can figure it out. I can't help you there. I can't
be the one. I can't help you. There's not much more that I can do. Google.com. You live at
McDonald's. How do you guys say McDonald's? Do you guys say McDonald's or do you guys say like
McDonald's? McDonald's. McDonald's. Which one? You guys say McDonald's. McDonald's. McDonald's.
All right. I think I'm going crazy. Where is the spider cavern? This has to be this way. It has to
be right down here. This is it, right? This is it right here. This is it. Oh, it's not it. Act three
Pepe laugh. Yeah. He's missing chests like this. I'm fine. Okay. I'm okay. Mages dying so quickly.
Spider cavern. I'm running out of stamina. It was really entertaining for a second when you asked
us how to pronounce McDonald's. Thanks. That was a cool conversation. You're right.
Terraria stream 2.0. You're walking around letting your minions do everything.
Is this what it feels like if somebody comes in to like the store you work at and complains
about something that you don't have control over? So I came in yesterday and there was,
I was going to buy this book. Why do you not have more than two of those books in your inventory?
I don't, I don't, we, I don't fucking know. I don't know. Well, why don't you? What are you idiot?
No, I don't, I have nothing to do with what kind of inventory we get. I just work here.
We just don't, somebody bought them. Somebody picked skeleton mages. Why did you do that? I
didn't, but you did though. Get me the manager. No, they've been so, that's been, that's been a
buzz kill. The rumors are really, that was going to be a huge one. And then they went,
no, no, no, no, no. I look forward to them now somehow. Yeah. I'm, I'm, I'm sorry. I didn't,
I didn't pick that. Uh, chat did. Why do you associate with them? Um, because they're here.
Well, why are you letting them in? It's part of what I, what is it what I do? That's what I'm
doing. We're in the flier jungle again. All right. Have I lost my fucking mind? It's been a while
since I played. Oh my God. I forgot about those guys. Normie build. Oh my God. Okay. Seriously.
I can't die to this. I will die. Yeah. I just, I was in here yesterday and it looks like you're
doing a normie build. I'd like to make a return on, on the bits that I gave because you're doing a
normie build. And then this drops. Oops. Well, I actually just did break something. It drops like
a big container. It's like shattered glass in it. Uh, man, did you drop this down the stairs?
Why does it matter? I have my receipt and no, it was an elevator shaft. Oh, are you all right?
How have I not found this? I'm going to lose my mind. It's not, how have I not found the spider
cavern? Dude, the golem's dead. He's dead. It always takes forever. I know. But how have I,
I look at all the, I've covered so much ground. Uh, he's not dead. He's alive and he doesn't get
to be as cool. All right. I'm going to say maybe closer to town. Let's go downtown. He's a washed
up Diablo bro. Yeah. I know. Down this way. It's not the one. It's not our favorite one.
All right. What about that way down here? Cause this is the arachnid layer. It has to be close
to this. Below it maybe. Cause that's the arachnid layer, not the spider cavern. There's no other way
to go that way. So it has to be over here. Down this way. Maybe over there. You need to look up
a walk through. No, walk through this. It's randomly generated. There's no walk through will help me.
Over here. There's some, yeah. Right here. I see us. Oh, this is a great marsh. Hold on. Let me
look at the full map. Is it down here? Cause the, the, wait, it might've, it might be down here.
Did I just miss it or something down this way? Oh, don't tell me it's right here. I've walked
past it. No, that was the arachnid layer. It's not the same one. Hold on. Let me stand still.
All right. It's probably right here. I probably just didn't see it like in the corner.
No, no, it would be purple. What a pain in the ass. Yes, I know. Search for his eye in the spider
cavern. I wish you could tell me where it was. All right. I'm going to walk out the front door
again. No, give me stamina potions. Be connected to the flayer jungle. Yeah. That's what I thought
too. Act three. It's great. You don't even sell stamina potions. Do I ever like to go through
another act to get them? Jesus Christ. All right. Let's go. Hey, what the hell do you want?
What are you doing here? Daryl's dead. Fuck off already. All right. What we got? Not here.
It would be over here. Nope. It would be right here. Nope. We do the left that way. I think it
might be somewhere. Me too. That's the great. No, that's the great marsh over there. Dermot,
you were already there. No, that was the arachnid layer. That was not the spider cavern. I already
went inside the arachnid layer. It's two different dungeons. Look, look what I found. Just a sliver
on the side and it's guaranteed to be right here. Spider cavern. What do you mean rude?
Wait, how was me saying fucking what the fuck? You fucking dumb. How is that rude?
I'm just making like a point. I'm saying like stupid fucking goddamn fucking comment.
But is that rude? Just trying to be like agreeable, you know.
You're being a bully. Oh, nope. You should put on a mature content filter. Look at all this crap I
have. I have so many stamina. I thought it was going to take so much longer too. If we can get
the eye. What's the deal with airline food? It's actually kind of good now. Snacks are pretty top
tier. I've had like those like eat up boxes from JetBlue. They're pretty great actually. They're
really good. It's like you can get like six bucks or something. You can get a like this like sausage
jerky cheese like crackers and they're like they're like nice brands too. It's actually kind of good
now. No seriously. When was the last time you guys had uh I mean obviously depends on what airline
you're on but by JetBlue you got a plenty of options. Oh did I mention more non-stop flights
than any airline in the country? Something like that. How's iron doing? Good. Rich streamer eats
airline food for lunch every day. That would probably not. I wouldn't want that. I wouldn't
want to eat airplane food every day. I feel like something bad might happen. Skeleton mages keep
dying. They're almost getting to the point where they're unsummonable. My airplane food is for
airplanes. Gasoline. I'm trying to lose health too. I can't just be an idiot. No wrong. Oh a scepter.
I'm not playing as paladin though. Unfortunately not a paladin.
Balanced. There's all knives should be. Give that person. Give that person a raise.
Lightning? No just wrong. Oh don't get hit. Don't get hit. Don't get hit. I have amplify damage on
me. It means I can die in one hit. There's a jade figurine. That's a good one to have.
There's the random quest. Man that guy just won the internet.
That guy just won the internet. Dude. All right we have the figurine now. Let's get out of here.
Meshef told me he had a fondness for jade figurines. On his trading voyages he could
put a strange little figurine into such small statues. Show him the ashes of Guile that
mixed with you a potion. Only it can reveal the true path to Mephisto. Is the game quiet?
Face the eye in the Herodric Cube along with Kaleem's other relics. The heart, the brain,
and the flail. I don't know. It is. All right search for Kaleem's brain in the flayer dungeon.
Now we go to Meshef. Say hey Meshef. What do you think about this?
Well it's still holy. I wish I'd never returned to this accursed place. Praise you. That jade
figurine will complete the set I was collecting here. I've had the statuette of a golden bird
for years but I consider it a fair exchange. I low sell high. Ask Cain about the bird. Oh
that's worth way more than what you came with. You should try to sell that to somebody for a profit
even though it might not be even worth a tenth of what you're getting for it. I've read legends
about a sage named Cuile who studied the mysteries of life beyond death. If I remember correctly
his ashes were ensconced within a golden statuette. It was a very strange tale.
Give the golden bird to Alcor. This is where you get something awesome. This is where you get
a cool item. The golden bird of Cuile? Thank you my friend. Busy yourself when I experiment with
the ashes within it. Then return and see what I've made for you. Return to Alcor.
And okay. What do you got? From the ashes of Cuile I have mixed for you a potion.
Got it. That potion is permanently increased 20 to your health. What?
Come on. I think I'm that dumb. 286? All right we're on the right track now. That's actually
kind of annoying to do these two in a row. You have to find the Gidvan which kind of sucks
and then this randomly drops from a champion or higher monster. So got them both knocked out of
the park right away. Now you've got to go to the Flare Dungeon get Gleam's brain. That does not
pick the loot. No. Otherwise I actually would probably not be able to even complete a single
mission in the game. All right you can pick a couple of these. All right Gleam's Eye. Rao?
We have a nice little rune collection here. Oh I already have a Rao.
I flood the market with Rao's and then dump it. Raar. Get out of here. Why? What's the point?
You know I look over and I envy some. I like want to be that person that just says like
Raar XD and some stream. You know what I mean? That's like that's just so you can do. You can
say anything. It doesn't even matter. Like I want to be and yes I have I've made plenty of
alt accounts in my on Twitch. You've seen some of them already like binary man zero one zero zero
one one one zero right? But I just want to be the guy in the chat that just writes like
laughing my ass off. When when do you get Gleam's poo poo right? Somebody said that. I didn't react
to it but like imagine being that person. Sometimes I envy you being up being able to do that. That's
the dream. That's the dream. Someone did say that. Yes they did and I looked over and I was like
mother fucker. But I was you know that could have been me. All right we're going to clear uh
where is it? It's closer. Uh what's stopping you? Um I don't know the respect of my peers
or something. He thinks he has respect. aircraft lost all respect.
So you're saying that you lost all your respect for me in 2012? What are you still doing here?
I'm here being angry. Why are you hate watching me right now? Am I being hate watched? Is that
what's going on? I look for the uh flare dungeon. There it is. Now look at how easy that was compared
to the other one. All right get in there. I'm not killing you. Take a look. 10 to 26. Uh he has a
unique on right now right? And this thing's much better. Notice how he has not been in any trouble
at all. He's healing 10% of his health per hit. This guy's this is going to be a perfect boss
friend. Four mages now and five still. What? Careful that the fire can melt you instantly
as you've seen. Very very dangerous. Sometimes I feel like we're all just the people who slow
down to look at the car accident. Um that's an interesting thought but no it's inaccurate.
This would be like you seeing car accident pulling over getting out of the car sitting
on the curb and watching the rest of the accident and everything play out and like the police report
and stuff. And it takes like six hours or so and you fall asleep on the curb. You just sleep in
there. Eventually cop comes over and he's like hey um you good? Oh yeah yeah yeah it was just like
glad to see that. I was oh yeah I'm going to bed. I'm going I'm going to bed. Bye Jerma.
Wait what are you talking about? While mocking the accident. Wait you wait you you know it looks
just a fender bender. Why did you not see that car? Look at his look at his bumper. You you broke
that bumper. And then you over here the cop. Sir I'm gonna have to ask you to step out of the car.
Oh oh mama s. All right I could die in here. I need friends. I know I have to I can't not I
can't just start talking random shit in hardcore. I know I have a bunch of people playing the game
for me. Okay okay. Okay okay I have to stop fucking around. This is I don't if I lose it I
can't just respawn. Mom said it was my turn. Well your mom is not my mom. Well I don't have
to listen to your mom. My mom said it was okay. Watch out for traps. All right it's down here.
Guys are dead. These guys are dead.
Watch out Jerma the the soul the killers the flares are coming.
Come on give me a unique ring. I think it's all worth it. Unique ring. That was I'm gonna put that
on if that was plus three to uh skeletons. A lot of death in there. That's a scary room.
Oh if. Cool yeah I don't know why but for a long time when I was younger I thought it was
re-enjuvenation potion. Level two here we go. Oh you were a stupid kid.
Paladin only. You know I can't I want to write that. I hate paladins. What about you?
Paladins are fun to play because you feel like you're contributing.
When you used to walk into a lobby and people would say like oh paladin yeah what kind of paladin
would you like? Oh all defensive defensive paladin. I don't even have any moves. I just
had 20 points 25 plus points is some of the best defensive or you just walk next to people and just
chatted. You're just a walking buff. Wow kind of like how you're doing this now. Kind of.
So take a rating. No I'm participating. I'm making them take a hundred percent more damage.
That's participation. Are you guys the skeletons? Yeah. Watch out guys.
We got a raid. Watch out. Here comes a raid from a channel. We did it. We defended.
Yeah I think you know what I figured it out. I figured it out. That is me chatting in a random
fucking stream. What I just did right there. I do that all the time. I do shit like that all the
fucking time. Though I do get to participate in that. No they all left. They away from the fire.
Look at he killed all the skeletons.
What streamers do you watch? That's a pretty cool question.
Uh I open up my own VODs and watch them back every night. I really like that guy.
Level three. Here it is. Out here somewhere. It's an ego. Um is it? Stop stepping on shit.
You're stepping on it. Oh these guys are running over all the traps.
Fuck. That just saved my life whatever it was. I don't know what it was but it saved my life
freezing because they all stopped. Oh my god I have to leave. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
I have to leave because these guys are going to come. No I'm kidding. Alright everyone get in.
Get in here please. Everybody get in. Jeez they all started standing outside.
If those two guys with fire came over I may have died. That was kind of terrifying. I have no way
to defend myself. I just have skeletons. I just have friends and death is permanent so I can't
walk around. It's called mess. What a mess. What a mess. What a mess. Wait doesn't it say hardcore
on the top right when you're in hardcore mode? What are you talking about? Well you watched me
select it right? Yeah you guys you guys watched me check the box. Does it? Oh got him. Okay don't
scare me like that. Not like it matters. If this character dies I could just delete him. Like if
it's not like that changes very much. I'm very paranoid in this room though because of these
things. These guys are a pain in the ass. Fire zero. Hey you should do a killed by enemy joke.
It'd be kind of funny actually. It'd be really funny. Come on where is it? Come on.
Come on. Come on. Explored almost the whole thing. Where's the chest? Over here. Bang on the left.
And don't go too far because wait for everyone to get here. This corner. There it is. All right.
There's a champion there and there's lightning and shit in here. Yeah I ain't going in.
Fuck that. You guys do it for me. Oh yep immune to fire. Just kill them. I don't want nothing
to do with that. Good. Nice work. That's another unique. All right. Hold on. Yeah. Is this shield?
Oh no. It's it's ethereal. It can't be repaired. It can. I can only use this until it breaks.
50% chance to block. 50% chance of open wounds. Tart it into a golem. Yeah probably.
I can't carry anymore. All right. Let me just put this. Damn it. That would be a pretty cool.
That'd be 50% chance to bleed. That would be cool actually. Let me make a ruby.
Time to clean up this inventory. Pissing me off. Okay. Time to clean my room. All right.
I'm cleaning my room. F. How many F's do I have? Um yeah. Time to clean the room.
If uh-oh guys. I can't make mules. I can't make more than one character to store things.
That's a problem. I love collecting items. Open bnet. I can't even use open bnet. Apparently I
did something so awful. So rotten and terrible that I'm banned from open battle net as well.
Even open bnet. Yes. Where hacking is legal. Hacking is legal on open bnet.
I ring scammed too many people. No. I don't understand. Let me clean my room. Let's sell
this ship. Cloud skull banned from open bnet as well. There are people that like speed hack
and teleport around in open bnet. There are people that have modded characters running around with
five million of every stat in open bnet. What the hell did I do to not be allowed in that?
Wait. Let me sell. I think it's time to. Yeah. Let's clean my room. Time to clean the room.
What are we doing on diamonds? We're good. All right. Keep writing. All right. Guys.
Let's take a look at the skills. We got a skill point to use. Please. Use it. You need some
reminders. Of course this is the summoning tree again. This is blood golem. This is iron golem.
This is fire golem. But I don't think we can't do that yet. I don't think.
This is just to make sure you can see. All right. You can see. Where's the skill point going?
Vote. No. Dim vision gang. Curses are important but we're neglecting them.
When I say we but I mean you. When I say you. I mean you. 212 of you that clicked on teeth.
I don't even know what you're clicking on over here. Make sure you try to differentiate so
the blob doesn't go together. Which one do you want me to do? I can't even do the guys.
Guys. Guys. Guys. Guys. Look. I can't do the fire one. That's level 30. I am currently level 26.
I can't do that yet. Fire golems not available. Fire golem receives but you got to figure out.
You guys. I think you guys are lost. What do you want? Figure it out. Skeletons. Powerful golems.
Do you want me to you know what I mean? This hit by the way revive is a thing in the game as well.
It revives any monster in the whole game. They fight for you instead. Fire golem. Iron golem.
They all get benefits from each other. Golem mastery. Okay. We've seen it. Also this is what's
available in poison and bone. This is what's available in curses. Iron maiden. Weaken. There's
also decrepify. Curses a group of enemies to make them slow, weak, and take amplified damage.
Lower resist. These seem kind of cool. These are cool too. All right. What do you want?
Pick it again. This time know that I can't go doing things in the bottom.
And make sure you're clicking in the correct spot to differentiate your vote from manipulating us.
Well. Still clicking on the fire golem. And revive. 20% of the people that have clicked so far
still don't get it. We are going to click on iron golem. Okay. Bone wall.
Another point in iron. Let's see what it does. Here we go. Just, you know, so you can see to make
sure that I'm doing, I'm actually clicking these. Remembering them. So this is going to bring,
it's going to bring the thorns up to 165%. Almost double the defense. What's the attack turn into?
Seven to nine. Let's see. Yeah. Huge defense increase and more thorns. All right. Stat points.
You know what to do. You guys are smart. You know what to do. By the way, if you don't know,
strength is melee damage and wearing heavy equipment. Dexterity is how often you hit
enemies in your defense. How often you obviously don't get hit. Vitality, health and stamina.
Energy is just mana pool. More mana. Getting close to a tier list. What is the right choice?
Um, if you're talking about a super duper min max build. No, why would I even tell you?
Vitality. Vitality. At least you guys are doing that. If you guys actually did put every point
to strength. Remember when I took that fire damage down to here without this extra 150,
whatever, a hundred plus health. I'm dead. Cleaned my room a little bit.
Stored some gold just in case I die. And then, you know, my heirs don't get it. All right. We
need to get the heart. Not the heart. The brain, right? Kaleem's brain. How many sloths are in
here? Three. Five to fifteen. Hold on. This is most fortunate. Kaleem's brain knows Mephisto's
weakness. Place it in the Herodric Cube along with Kaleem's other relics. The eye, the heart,
and the flail. The eye, the heart, the brain, and the flail. I don't wonder
what Wizard of Oz character wanted that. This guy's still alive. Wow. Yes, I'm doing fine.
All right. If I do, we do fire and ice. Fire, ice, and poison. All in one. All right. Yeah,
I'm going to do, let's go, let's go to the fountain drink thing and just get like Coke, Diet Coke,
Sprite, Pepsi, the high C. Let's just do it all. This is eight to twelve fire damage. The five
percent life per hit is not going to do it for me. Let's go. Look, later on in the game,
these are going to drop all the time anyways. Oh, shit. Five to thirty fire damage. That's
pretty good. Oh, shit. I got two of these. I got two of these. No, we're just going Diet Coke.
We're just going to go Diet Coke. All right. Eighteen to seventy-two fire damage. And I got,
all right, let's see. Oh, fuck. Yeah, let's go. Thirty-five to a hundred and three damage.
It's just raw, raw. What class are we again? We are summoning Necromancer, but Chad is doing this
laugh out loud scenario where they put most of my points into strength. So if I'm going to have
more than sixty to a hundred strength, then I might as well swing a weapon at somebody
because they have not given me any offensive move. I have a shield and a bunch of skeleton friends.
That's it. This is just what's happening. Look at this thing. See, like the red, the red. All
right. Colleen's heart is in the sewers under the Curest Bazaar. This guy's complaining even
though he's got one tooth. Yeah. No, right. I do have an offensive ability. Let's see how much
damage it does. Teeth. Yeah. Okay. Right. Okay. So that's that's comparable. All right. Wait,
wait, wait, wait. I got to go back. We got to go back up to the Flare Jungle. Not me. I want you
to succeed. That's why I'm clicking on Constitution every time. Thanks. Dentist build. You can do a
dentist build. You just put all your points in the teeth and then all your points into bone
sphere and shit. You can have like 50 teeth come up. Dude, I'm going to destroy everybody with this
build. I'm doing a lot of damage. It's not even without this is without amplify on. Am I really
out of stamina? Tier list stream. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Yeah. All right. Next level
up. I'm going to do the next tier list. We're going to keep going up to the Curest Bazaar.
I believe it's this way. This way. Poison. Uh-huh. That was the Gitvin. Hang on. Right.
Let's get to the Bazaar. I thought they were on the other team for a second.
Uh, no. Keep going up. We can't. Where are the trees? The weird tree enemies are scary.
Oh, I missed three times. Bone Master needs bone abilities.
This is the heart maybe. See the fire when I hit people. It's so cool. It's that little
explosion. It goes, why are you killing? This is a, this is a war for good. This is a war for good
and evil, man. Hell's demons versus the rest of us. Easy. This is demons versus me and you.
Everyone's still alive. This is pretty great. You're with the demons. How could you?
Traitor. Oh, Iron Golem's dead. I mean, there was too much overwhelming. Overwhelming.
You got to close the game. What? It's hardcore for my minions too. Oh, fuck. That was bad.
That could have been. How long until Fire Golem friend, people heaven.
Uh, we need four more levels. I'm assuming before we finished act three, you'll see, uh,
Fire Golem maybe ends. And if your fellow chat members also would like to see that
fight indecisive recently, we spread out. I don't like being spread out. Uh, Vic leveled up.
I was, you know, I forgot if I'm going to hold things in my inventory, I might as well just
see what they are on the way to Bazzar. I don't use Kane to identify things because on the fly,
I might want it. Plus there's not that much money.
This might be better than what I have on right now. I don't want to go home for this.
I mean, it's not, but it could have been, but yeah, it is. No, it's not. That's actually good
too. 5% chance to cast Frost Nova. That's where that's coming from. You're impatient.
That's what the point of the book is for. So I can trash it that I don't want. I'm going to
keep going back to town. That's too, it's too far. The F rune ring. All right. Do I have enough
for just even a shitty rune word? I know there's dozens and dozens and dozens of them in the game,
but do I have any of the crappy ones? Uh, two or three slot armor? How F? What about three?
How F, huh? It's called stealth. I might want to look that up.
Here. Stealth would be pretty good.
That's not even a real thing. What are you trying to get me to say? Okay. I'm trying to figure out
what you're, what are you trying to get me to say? Here's my heart. Heart. Okay, but wouldn't it be
just, uh, that's come on. I hope I don't miss anything. I still only have level one bone armor.
Yo, that's right. Mr. Peanut fucking died. We talked about it in the pre-stream chat.
We went over this for like 40 minutes, but imagine nobody caring about peanuts.
Go point where you have to kill one of the most iconic food brand mascots and not just like,
oh, we're discontinuing the use of Mr. Peanut. No, we're going, we're, we were going to kill him.
Super bold marketing shit. We have to go back around. Wait, really? Yes, really. Yes. We've
gone full, full kill somebody for memes. And I brought this up too. It's a really important
point. I'm surprised none of the other serial characters have died. Like doesn't Sonny the
Cocoa Puff Bird do crazy shit and like jump out of planes without parachutes and like
crash his car into stuff? How is he still alive? Like the Trix Rabbit stalks children
and steals from them. Should we be in prison by now? Okay. That was fucking close.
That fire move is so deadly. That's the run killer. I need fire resistance. I don't even
care if I put it on just even if I take something good off. That's it. All right, here we go. Player
jungle, finally. And from here, we're going to go to the lower cuirass and then cuirass bazaar.
Mr. Peanut Wiki. Yes, some of the other masked food mascots live so much more dangerous lives
than Mr. Peanut. How often did Captain Crunch get raided by other pirates? They had like swords
and guns and stuff. Tony the Tiger played soccer. He could have taken a football, a soccer ball
right in the mouth and like broke his face and shit. Mr. Peanut just dances. He just dances.
He just dances around. He's like, oh, Mr. Peanut, my PB crisps. It's not like he's
doing anything dangerous. Speaking of PB crisps, can they sacrifice Mr. Peanut to bring back PB
crisps? Is that what this whole thing is for? This is going to... All right, here's my prediction.
Super Bowl ad PB crisps is coming back and this was just a big thing for him to reveal that PB
crisps are returning is not really dead. This is a big marketing ploy to bring back PB crisps,
the only product that anyone buys from planters that ever did buy. And I have a theory that the
reason why they discontinued him and they're like, oh, maybe one day we'll bring him back.
No, they were delicious. What were they made out of? What's the big secret as to why everyone
wants them? Everyone loves those things. Why'd they get rid of them? Yeah, everyone loves PB
crisps. Yummy peanut cream in the middle. What chemical was in there? I'm saying like, what?
Why won't they bring them back? Ah, shit, we can't bring back the original recipe.
They were good though. These things are so awesome. I used to, in my mouth, I would separate the outer
shell of the crisp and separate the inside peanut butter, eat the shell first, and then I would eat
the peanut butter in the middle afterwards. You all did it and it was the best thing you've ever done.
Or I would peel the shell around it, eat it, and then take that solid creamy peanut butter
and put it in, eat it. I actually have to go. So you're fucked up. No, that these are coming
from the people that told me that they eat Reese's. They like stick their tongue through the middle,
push up, smear out the peanut butter, and then put it into their hand and eat it and then break
the ring in half. I told you guys that I eat Reese's just normally, and it was like, what?
But you're a serial killer. Like I, in Oreos, I talked about Oreos. I eat Oreos just normally.
I dunk them in milk and I just eat them. But you don't twist them and like rub your feet on them
and then sit on them and then blow your nose on it and then eat it? No, I don't. I thought you said
you dunked Reese's in milk. No, I dunked cookies in milk. I have another, uh, just sell it, whatever.
I'm gonna gamble. I know it's pronounced Reese's, but Reese's is how I say it. Reese's
with different countries, different dialects, you know, like Reese's. That's how we say it here.
A flawed skull in here. I have these greater health potions. All right, I'm just gonna sell it. I
don't want it. I haven't repaired in a long time. I want sweets so bad right now. I don't blame you.
They're really delicious. I don't blame you. Bagged milk, yes or no? Um, I don't, I don't know.
All right, here we go. You know what I'm about to do with this. Buy and be reborn. I can't,
it's not made out of milk. I'll figure out what to do with it. How do I speed up a stream? Um,
you leave the stream, you go to sleep, go take like a two-hour nap and come back to your chair.
That should do it. You need to go faster. You can't, there is no such thing as going
faster in an ARPG. You got to take it slow and steady. We're not trying to win any race,
just trying to continue. Wait, that was the right way, wasn't it? I'll get a pizza instead.
Isn't it up this way? God damn it, I need potions. Go back, go back, go back, go back, go back. I'm
going to buy stamina potions. Oh, cat, I'm not going to answer that question.
I'm going to just, I'm going to damn you. Did I, I thought I was there? Apparently not.
I need to know if I beat your record. Um, no, we, I, I used to bring the computer into the bathroom.
I used to bring either a laptop, I would bring my whole computer into the bathroom. A lot of
long-term viewers know this. When I was younger, I, I wanted to play so bad and just chill and
relax. So I would bring my entire computer into the bathroom, plug it in and shit and sit on the
toilet and have a little desk, a little card table. And I would sit there for like two hours.
There we go. And it would be so irritating because after I was done, I had to take it all apart and
put it all back where it was supposed to be. And it was the biggest pain in the ass. Can you imagine
being my parents? As I didn't have headphones, I had like little speakers. Can you imagine being
my parents and knowing that your son was in the bathroom and you hear a battle scenario? This is
what you listen to. What you're hearing right now. Can you come back every 20 minutes and still hear
this? Like, what is he doing? I need the, uh, curious, the sewers under the curious as are.
There's also a skill book here or a stat book. He must have eaten something funny.
Well, I don't know. My, you cooked it. Now imagine if I had the opportunity to be playing online
with a mic in there. You just hear that toilet flush sound. You couldn't mute microphones back
then. And people still don't even mute their mics anymore. I, you think that's some kind of issue.
How many times have you heard somebody's ceiling fan? Somebody comes into a lobby with their
gain up to a hundred percent. And it's just like,
it's a huge, just ear piercing, blow out the microphone a hundred percent and gain
cough into the microphone. And it's like, Oh, and you rip the headset off. It's like,
it sounds like they're just walking over shattered glass in your ears. I think it's
up here. Taco bell has potato chips. Taco bell has nachos. Ooh. I mean, they have corn chips,
right? I'm gonna be mad at me for not opening chests. I'm doing it for that guy.
All right. Here we go. The bazaar. I need to find the last piece of the puzzle here.
All right. Yeah. And then after this level up, we're going to do a tier list.
We're looking for the sewers, sewers. Aren't there like six of these? Why am I saying it
like this with all the S's? Sewers. It's in the sewers. It's inside the sewers. Fuck. Now
that sounds weird. This used to be a tier, this used to be a tier list stream. The S's are,
I don't like the letter S anymore. All right. What's it like being the number one Diablo
2 streamer on Twitch? Well, real easy when you play games that nobody plays.
It's real easy to be number one when the closest number next to you is zero. Wacky,
wacky comedy stream. Is this sewers? You should stream more Hearthstone. No, this is not the sewer.
No, no, no, no. Not the sewer. Look at all this crap. Yeah. And what have a patch they last did,
like two years, three years ago to this game, whatever it was, they had, they upped the potion
drops. It was holy shit. I've never seen this before. Even with the max players and shit.
I used to do lobbies with eight people. There are other Diablo 2 streamers. I thought you said I
was the only one. Never. No, I've never played hardcore before. Doors. I said you were number
one. Oh, I thought you said that I was the only one. Like I'm the only one. Hey sewers, you got it.
Look at the ego on this guy. Level two. Playing barbarian here was really fun because they had
leap. You could just jump over around and everything. It's cool. One of the first
experiences I ever had with this game was a childhood friend of mine was in the sewers part
here and they would just do leap as barbarian. I thought it was the coolest thing I've ever seen.
Hey, new viewer here. Are you the shpee guy?
Weird to be a new viewer when Jerma is in your name. Hey dude, new viewer. I've like been on
Twitch just like browsing around and your name is in my name. Coincidence. It's weird. Also Jerma.
Maybe. It'd be weird. So are you the shpee guy or no? No. I gave that up a long time ago.
Mace. Stay healthy. Stay healthy. Stay healthy. Is this a hardcore thing? Is that what it is?
Yes. Level two. Is this some kind of hardcore thing? I mean.
There's a head jump. I'm killed. I think I got Vic here. Resident sleeper. Where's the commentary?
People are fucking trying to sleep. Oh green green green green. I think it's the same one I have.
Berserkers. Oh do I have any Berserkers?
Not a skeleton. Why are people trying to sleep? What am I saying? People are trying to fucking sleep.
Um this is kind of better. That's fire resist though. I know who would wear this. No Berserkers
again. He's got 75 fire resistance. That guy's ready to go. Nancy Drew napping room.
Key filter waiting room. Not that way. I just want to get off work. I'm playing uh
Necro dude. It's really fucking odd. What are you gonna do? A bathtub stream.
Let's turn my camera on right now until it's time to go to the bathroom.
We get some hogs in the chat to wake up these these I was gonna say I was gonna say idiots
but if you're you know if you're tired you're not an idiot you're just tired almost time for
a level up which means almost time for a tier list a tier list you said it all right I'm getting up
hey I just shook the bag of dog treats what what's that oh yeah okay I'm ready shit
it's starting to get dangerous I really do need to find I might have to do some endarial runs
after this before I go to Mephisto I think I have to do a couple of endarial runs I mean
I'm kind of getting beat up if I get hit once it's like ow remember you promised me she's
impossible this bed lied about I remember that video a wink you got a wink oh yeah I'm green
oh this actually looks weird because it looks kind of real there you go red teeth I'm not doing
that okay as you wink you get blood in his mouth yeah every time I'm about to die I just
flinch down my teeth and squish hard to no upper cuirass get out of here your teeth
shouldn't be squishing no they should be right they shouldn't maybe I should see some the doctor
squishy teeth disgusting
sewers are so huge don't run that far without I don't have anything to do
I keep forgetting that I have I'm 100% useless I am nothing without a group of people with me
I can't run forward without everybody I don't even have any moves
I don't have any spells or abilities why would I run forward I run forward to run back
what's the next tier list I wonder take a look I think we got a Jim Carrey movie
oh dude the germa nine eight five face emotes no what the germa nine germa faces
I'm going to rate my own faces don't you guys call me an egomaniac all the time
don't you think that that would be solidifying what you're saying did I miss that up there
no that was to the upper bazaar do it for the love of god Mike hold on you guys like stamping
your feet do it do it do it I'm not supposed to reward this kind of behavior
yes I need the heart do it or we're all gonna leave this is one of those scenarios where you
say we're gonna leave right guys and everyone's like yeah and I don't do it and you're like fine
let's get the fuck out of here right guys everyone's like yeah let's go and you and two people leave
and then you you look back and you realize it it's just you two and then you can't come back
because that would be the one you can't oh well I thought everyone was gonna go with us
oh I can't go back there because that means oh I'm gonna sit back down
all right need more is my 5000 viewers gone under 100 now
oh where is this stupid thing it's not stupid I'm giving it a stupid I'm saying stupid
holy shit where is this beg for subs please
grovel grovel jester what do you mean grovel jester what I am
am I begging for subs or am I going to be executed do it grovel jester oh Jesus did I get it
it is dangerous
that's not that's not a round number I don't like it
cool it's definitely right over there right it has to be
really nothing else down here where's do I have to go I don't think I have to go to level two
I don't think there is a level two is there my goodness oh my goodness oh
oh bite him up NFL Street or Riot I own it I have it it's gonna be a stream soon
it's not right now what I just pressed I just pressed like five buttons I have NBA Street
right here it's right next to me ice hawk old enchanted out teleporting that's why we can't
kill it these guys are annoying there it is zero lever finally wait we gotta kill that guy where
is he teleport belt sucks it sucks all right level two let's get the thing we need and then
get the hell out of here and then we'll do a tier list after we level up what do you think
you fill in maybe Jim Carrey movies uh Jeremy's face up there too there's a lot of chests over
come on give me a rare unique oh I didn't even see what it was until I clicked on it
Leem's heart it's a gem shrine a gem shrine just automatically upgrades any gem in your inventory
to the next tier so I could have brought a regular gem here and it would have been
upgraded to a flawless gem and that's when I cry what we got first for Kaleem's flail and
in provincial beware of the high council Leem's heart and it still bears the courage to face
Mephisto place it in the horodric cube along with Kaleem's other relics the eye the brain
and the flail council now I need the flail and we make the super flail one two three skull
you put a perfect skull in a weapon it's pretty great especially if you have a bow if you're in
amazon they're very very good with amazon especially if you get wind force socketed wind force perfect
skull I know a bunch of people just are gonna say that I've ruined the item by doing that I don't
care all right spell spell spell okay that's got one there and uh do I have enough of these no
all right look at the skills we are level 27 for a reminder there is what we have available iron
golem blood golem golem mastery play golem raise skeleton skeleton mastery skeleton mage
poison and bone teeth bone armor what synergies help fire golem all the golem ones so
summon resist golem mastery clay blood and iron all give a bonus to fire just as fire gives a
bonus to all the other ones as well every point that is put into blood golem gives it plus five
percent health per level to every other golem same thing with clay every point that's in clay
gives plus 20 attack rating to every other golem purses I feel like you guys want to look at these
for a second because just just bear with me life tap think about this just for a moment you will
just I'm not influencing you um anybody that's cursed by this becomes a 50 life leech to anybody
that swings anything at them uh confuse confuses monsters to force it to attack random targets
attract it's just a taunt on somebody that didn't taunt the crapify causes a group of enemies to
make them slow weak take more damage iron maiden is 200 thorns at level one and we're getting
residents sleep all right what do you want it is up to date pick something nice
I can't collect fire we can't fire does not exist for three more levels if it's not more
friends I don't care people happy we got 18 what's the one above what's iron
iron what what percentage is actually clicking on iron and I know that some of you are doing
this on purpose when you click here that doesn't help any of us it's here or not here all right
it's going into iron what about the stats I'm just teaching you guys what a button is like y'all are
free like is that you guys more strength that's what this is big and strong
I'm the strongest person here in my group that has trouble fighting things I don't know where
what this is this is I think it was strength that's probably at strength to both
two and two and one streamer's choice all right make it more clear please look at look at this
look at the face somebody's and people clicking them right in the middle yeah make the giant
slug make the caterpillar can you make the caterpillar oh you did it thanks for voting
hey I gotta I gotta make a decision here that picks everything act that is what happened
you were having fun you were memeing around but we've got a destination so now our iron golem is
at 180 percent damage returned and a shitload more defense very good all right let's do the
derma face tier list uh where is it I wasn't trying to do that I'm trying to go back
I was hitting back on my browser to try to find the music I had oh well here list what do you
think I'm doing derma's face is fixed do the fixed one okay why does someone have to be why
is it fixed hey this one's fixed all right reptiles is done all right let's do it let's see what we
got I don't even I can't eat all right this is gonna be this is gonna take a little while
no it's not it's just my face like fucking 40 times I don't have time to change this I don't
care so uh this is the derma face tier list wait maybe I know demon eyes okay here we go
I'm normal now I gotta make sure I'm perfectly framed all right let's go that's fun memory that
I had love that image just like one of my favorites that could be a different person
this is a different person it's not even the same human being this is not even me all right uh this
derma rumble come on that's like some of the that's like one of some of the most fun I've ever had
that was when they announced that they were working on uh elder scroll six
I'm so excited for it is it six or seven it's eight turn off the music this music this music
is kind of fucked up this is like funeral music I'm keeping it all right I was a handsome I was
a handsome young man this is going up to fucking b tier but these are like both from this is
doctored why this is not even my faces these are doctored images this is just me playing a game
on facecam that's the worst one this is the worst one I hate this fucking image when I go out to
places and people ask what do you do or they people people find out that I stream right
hey oh you you stream oh nice now what's your channel name I fucking hate telling them because
that's the image that pops up if you type in derma into google that's just what pops up
so it's just so ugly and gross and just I look like unkempt and unwell it's just such a bad picture
that it's so bad and it has to be everywhere it has to be the number one image search
it has to be the number one thing that's like on every wiki like why can't it be I'd rather
be this one I mean at least this one's like a joke this is me scary looking into a camera
like I'm like I'm I'm coming and I'm fucking mad I this one's a joke you know what I mean
this is deranged this is humor and I disqualify this one's not even a face
this is just me oh this is bright because I wasn't this is me naked this is gonna take some
refinement this is up pretty high for me that's up pretty high for me so is this one this one sucks
this one's just a worse version of this one he can be the best of the worst it's not even my face
there's a lot of d faces here mustache hair has to be up kind of high
uh like a twitter picture I took one time this one's all right I'll just do some refinement
this one sucks this one's just like a stretched out image of my face all right what's the best
face it's it's it's my favorite image could be could be accurate it's accurate okay it's real
um just that there's a story behind this one there's a story behind all of these this one I
think has there's so much going on in this one because the circumstance all right let's get down
here um it's I like it but it's old you know these are these are new what even what's this
even from what is this this looks like it's not taken from here this is taken from some
other place from where is it the green screen the awards ah okay the awards all right it's
pretty good this one's so stupid is the clown better than all these though you don't even
look at itchy ear like inside your ear and I can't reach that far I want to take like
a little device and go in and just like scratch but that's so bad for you it's like no you don't
you're not supposed you're not supposed to put q-tips in your ears you're really not well
everybody does it's funny we all say that to each other now I don't put q-tips in your ears
yes everyone every single person does it everyone says don't do it but all of us do it why why why
can't we just come clean about that no don't fucking do that not good for you did it this
morning I'm working on it I'm working what's the worst the worst possible face is probably this one
it's just not it's just me these two no it's this one yeah what's the best all right this
one's really bad too so is this one so is this one so is this one it's probably these are probably
the best so is this one now these belong together because they're just like screen there's just
screen caps from a youtube video I wasn't making any faces here I wasn't trying to be funny or do
a joke this is just you took a screen cap from two different videos from like 2012 oh yeah that's
bad put these two together I could you could say the same thing it's funny when you can tell when
from the same stream was it this bad one day was it this fucked up one day what was going on on
this stream these could all be the same day all right that's accurate this is yeah this is accurate
because you have four shirts that way this green one all the time is it is the green one in any
of these thank god there you go there's there's me raiding my own face not a narcissist by the
way not an egomaniac by the way the joker face is too low are you sure the joker face is better
than mustache hair or scrunched mcchicken face yeah actually yeah actually it is actually it is
it is this one's not even that good all right you're right this is should be lower too no this is
this one should be way lower again this is the same stream you can tell look at the hair there's
no coal miner here that's unfortunate you're right it's been so long since I've seen this original
image what was going on why was the light blue you were doing the storytelling stream oh right
right right okay there you go there's your there's a second tier list it only took three hours to do
the second one we do one more we'll do one more we'll do one more uh whatever this next one is
there's your list what's this one uh okay this is water this is drinking water these different
waters this is water to drink what is this what is that supposed to be this looks like car this
is like car antifreeze fluid ice water but but that who cares what's the water inside of it
where'd it come from and that would oh this this is the sparkling water right water from the sink
gross water from the toilet water from the bathtub is this this is but if i don't drink it i love i'm
i take i'm a bath hobbyist we talked about my hobbies i'm taking baths as a hobby can i put
that up here i take i take a bath like three times a week i'm not making that up i swear to god
i love it and then i go like under the water and i just go not bad true gamer all right what this
is from a river no you're gonna get like a tapeworm it's probably safer to drink toilet water than it
is to drink water right out of a river you're gonna get like this is i don't know i know that's
actually true if you you could there's like all kinds of bacteria and contaminated this is
regulated i mean as long as nobody's shipping it yeah i would probably i don't know that's tricky
where's smart water i don't know it's not on here what happened to diablo we're going back to it
we got caught up what is domino diamond water not even close to being fiji i don't even know
what it is all right let's put the antifreeze over here all right what's safer drinking antifreeze
or drinking water out of a river river water is safer than of course it is i don't even know
what these are i don't i'm just gonna put them over on d d is like i don't d is don't care
d is don't care because i've never had it drinking water from a pool but all right hold on drinking
water tier list you don't drink water from a pool there's two things going on here all right
drinking water from a pool versus drinking water from a toilet the it the toilet's probably safer
uh is this a pool that is this a pool that just got shocked or chlorinated all right yeah so it's
it's safer to drink out of a toilet than out of a pool and we're not talking about oh you got a
little bit up your nose or you got a little bit in your mouth you know we're talking about like a
we got like a full 16 ounce glass of water right drinking like a full like 24 ounce glass like
downing it on the pool right so that's i would i don't know if i would do that but i would you
know what i'd probably do that before drinking water over a toilet this is just too much to bear
i would do a full like 16 ounce glass of water from a pool then i would have 16 ounces from a
toilet but i would do toilet before i did like a random river that could have like e coli in it
and i would do river after before doing drinking any freeze so okay out of the ocean you don't
want to do that either out of a lake you don't want to do that either and then i don't know
what this is drink water from this is much safer than than this drinking water out of a lake is
probably wouldn't because the salt water salt water versus freshwater they're both bad river
yeah what no no no standing water that's even worse i would drink a full glass out of a sea
then a full glass out of a pool then a full glass out of a toilet then a full glass out of a river
running water it's moving standing water is mosquitoes and i don't want to drink mosquito
eggs and then any freeze you would die if i drank 16 ounces of salt water i'm gonna die
uh sorry guys i i used to drink gatorade out of the just for no reason the same thing i would die
if i drank 16 ounces what is this the only water i get to have ever why is this the only water i
get to drink why is if i drink 16 ounces of water you're not gonna hydrate but it's going to kill
you if you if i drink 16 ounce glass of water from the ocean i die i'm going to die but what
if i drank 16 ounces of ocean water and then a fucking full like disani right what happens
they will negate each other but this is like what are the circumstances we didn't go over the
circumstances we didn't go over the rules am i like trapped on an island am i the only person
at the pool am i the only one using the toilet am i what there are no ground rules here we haven't
made them i'm not drinking salt water to hydrate i just is it safer to drink 16 ounces of salt water
or 16 ounces of water from a chlorinated shocked fucking pool they're both dangerous but which one
which one is worse pool is safer you know how much pool water i've gotten in my eyes and in my nose
and in my mouth i've drank probably four or five glasses of this water before and i'm all right no
i don't believe it this is the worst thing you can drink because there's mosquito eggs in like this
standing water standing lake water you just that's you could actually actually die this you're saying
it just it dehydrates you but if i'm not stranded on an island i would be safer drinking this and
then just drinking a glass of water and maybe like eating some bread or something the salt water
kills all the germs all right all right any that's done it's over it's over arrowhead arrowheads are
not better than evian and evian's not better than fiji and i love taking baths so that's this is
accurate i'm not drinking this you guys really gonna make me do this fine it's safer to drink
water out of your bathtub than any of these other things because who cares it's just a bathtub
there's nobody shits in their bathtub nobody pisses in their bathtub i like taking baths
it's not fair everyone pees in their bathtub so let's get this straight when i tell you that
i've peed in the shower before which to pee directly into a drain and you don't have to sit
in it that's weird but all of you guys are saying that you've pissed in your bathtub before where
you have to sit in your fucking bathtub and be surrounded by urine but you're not weird you're
you're not weird i'm weird if you pee directly into the drain if you pee directly into the drain
what's the difference yeah i just i need i want to know the difference what's the difference
after you take the bath you pee you're just sitting in a bath what are you talking about
this is done accurate you stand up and do it i'm never going to your house you put like the two or
three towels out for me and you put it on the bathtub and you just hang them over there and
you're like yeah you got a bathtub i'm not i'm not going in that bathtub bathtub is kind of just a
big urinal though i guess i get it i get it what's the next one i already did this one before i'm
gonna do it real quick who gets the coffee from all these places all right so this is what's your
favorite coffee just kidding where do you like what's your favorite fast food restaurant is
influencing all right that was fun what's this one all right i want i want to do this one i want to
do this one and then we're going back to diablo this is jim carrey movie the mask number one
all right jim carrey movies we've got ace ventura get up there where ace ventura uh two wait no no
where's ace ventura two ace ventura two is way better than one liar liar is all right let's go
dumb and dumber is really good i have not seen this i'm gonna put it down here
i didn't see this either all right he was in this it was all right didn't oh the number 23
here it is whatever ace ventura two when nature calls there it is bruce almighty is bruce almighty
was good what's this oh dumb and dumber two no uh kick-ass two does it count if i've never watched
kick-ass two i only watched jim carrey's scenes in the movie does it count no yeah mr poppin's
penguins didn't see it me myself and irene i mean it's a classic cable guy it's classic the majestic
the one with the other movie the movie theater one yes man the dumb and dumbers are backwards
oh yeah you're right batman forever s uh i didn't see this one i didn't see this one i didn't see
this one i didn't see this one christmas carol it's all right sonic the hedgehog movie we nobody's
seen it yet i haven't seen this one i don't know vermin show get up there man of the moon get up
there grinch it's all right i don't know oh no this uh fun with uh i didn't see it i didn't see
this one i don't even know what this one is i don't know this one is uh i don't know this one is uh
oh this is okay i don't know this one is i don't know this one is i don't know what this one is
all right let's get this right oh wait that was eternal sunshine where's where's eternal
where's eternal sunshine which one is it this one okay that's an accurate s tier
for jim carrey movies why would i put eternal sunshine next to the mask that's that's so far
below it that's better that's i mean that's that's inaccurate the mask is the best movie
that he's ever done it was incredible that everything we're gonna have to bump something
off i think no liar liar was good but i don't know if it was cable guy good the grinch goes
up no the grinch was like two hours too long you shaved like three and a half hours off that movie
and i would i would agree uh i like bruce almighty more than eternal sunshine what's the worst jim
carrey movie that i've seen i mean they're both not very good the grinch feels like it was a day
long yes that's what happens when you take an old fun children's story that was 12 minutes long and
you make it like a four and a half hour long movie remember that these are i just haven't seen these
so if you're like oh dark dark crimes that's great i just haven't seen it the upload two is in the
background it is that movie's an hour and 32 minutes thanks for proving my point that we all
of us thought we all thought it was like three and a half hours long again it was like three
hours too long great performance though it goes up fantastic performance by jim carrey preemptively
rate sonic s tier that's a safe bet i'm not sure that's a safe bet i would probably assume that
this is going to be up here somewhere though is is his dr egg man performance going to be as good
as his yes man performance that's to be seen yes man sucked well why do you think it's right
next to burt wonderstone i don't know maybe we'll see we'll see if it's a fun it's a fun
movie it could be fun it's one of the first jim carrey comedy kind of he's going back to comedy
it's been a while well dumb and dumber two was the last time he did he was in like a comedy movie
right in like three or four years and before that it was a while too six years remember the bad
taste in movies joke is getting old if you think that this belongs somewhere else besides s if you
think these three belong somewhere else i'm not sure what i don't know how to how to explain to
you these things this is like the required reading for jim carrey movies a s and a tier is required
jim carrey reading he almost got a academy award for this he got like a golden globe for man on
the moon it was great ace pentura is overrated i don't know i mean like the second one's the
first one is i like the second one better than the first one and eternal sunshine was i mean
whatever it's all right it's good he doesn't mean a bad movie he just means it's not it's not the
truman show there's your list and now let's do adam sam you don't mess with the zohan
happy gilmore s tier i saw this movie in the theaters me and burger boy saw this because we
were like oh this has to be like the worst movie ever and we it was hard for us to not get up and
leave we were just like let's go fucking watch this shitty movie and it was hard to say stay
and watch the whole thing the the only good part about that movie is the al pacino duncacino song
that's it so i don't go don't go don't i mean that's the only thing that was worth watching in the
whole movie the ad and it was just giant product placement i don't even care it was it was so
stupid don caccino is the only reason why that movie was even tolerable oh the gobbler no the
cobbler haven't seen it d is haven't seen it f is just like why if the first dates didn't see it i
didn't have a reason to see it oh this is this is a boston movie someone was like fucking talking
like fucking this all the fucking time this is a boston movie so it has to be at sea for me
um wedding singer was all right but i'm i really did i'm not like a huge wedding singer fan why is
hotel transylvania on here but not with eight crazy nights where is it all right i think this
is good big daddy better than uh yeah there we go that's accurate no uncut gems that movie just
came out like three months ago i didn't see this it's supposed to be kind of good i didn't see it
nothing comes close to happy gilmore no nothing does i would say the difference between the this
s tier and this a tier is probably it's probably like 60 feet probably like 70 feet actually that's
no that's great that's better zohan is beyond s tier all right let's go back to diablo 2
they're your tier list tier list hotel is not f tier no i hotel okay wait wait i didn't see that
okay i didn't see hotel transylvania i got upset that it was the only animated one on here um i
didn't i didn't see this i didn't you want me to put pixels anywhere besides f all right let's go
that's fun now i gotta pee so let's take the first break i'll be right back okay they're returned
i'm back what was the last thing we were doing in diablo i need to change the volume back to where
it was you can hear the game diablo tier list uh what all right i have the i gotta go to
provincial there's a little bit further up we gotta go to cuirass i didn't get the waypoint
i have to go up from the sewers yep anymore chests that's my favorite soap can you have a
favorite soap yes you can why uh i mean i guess there's so but there's so many that body of a
favorite soap like brand or flavor all right i need the tp here or the waypoint whatever all
right my favorite my favorite soap is probably uh i mean i i like i like lush's shampoo it's hard
to find i think my favorite actual so i don't know whatever whatever's on the rack at walmart
whatever i can just slime on my body and then shower it off irish spring i actually love irish
spring but kim hates it so anytime that i would want to use it kim is like no no do not
oh i don't use it anymore all right my weapon is broken it's all right i don't need to go back
it smells like chemicals
it does have a sort of a chemical smell it has a green chemical smell all right i need to get the
flail and prevention i gotta move actually i have this as long as i use it
don't go that fast don't go that fast it's seriously i don't have a weapon
and i'm in hardcore i forget that sometimes no i get off everything is made out of chemicals
yeah who repairs an act three it's still after yes we're getting to the end of act three
greeting we'll be at the end of act three after i get the flail we'll then be going to the durance
of hate and then be doing the most farmable thing in the game it used to be pinwheel not what's his
what's his name they nerfed him because it was so easy and what was it what was his name what's his
name his name is pendle or something right greetings here good day indel skin yeah you
used to be able to uh so there was this little mini boss in diablo 2 it was pendle skin uh he
was right next to the waypoint and you could kill him in one hit and he dropped in an amazing
drop table he had the same drop table as bosses so you would just remake a game kill him in one
second loot remake the game kill him in one second loot over and over again hundreds and hundreds of
times and then they nerfed it because it was way too easy to get anything and then i think that
they also nerfed mephisto too didn't they a long time ago they nerfed an easy to kill character
well they'd nerfed his loot table they made it so you didn't drop this thing
because i mean at some point people are just making in your battle net lobbies
a new game every five seconds or every 12 like 10 seconds to kill the same enemy and that's what
every single person is doing that's logged in at some point you look at that and go uh this is
kind of that's probably dumb we should probably do something about that do i eat mcdonald's it's
like one of my favorite places yes in fact i may even eat mcdonald's later because he just said
that you've influenced me influencer how would i know didn't you get banned oh what the fuck's
what happened that was weird what has happened huh yeah i lost chat too for like a second
it was like one tenth of a second almost hit travencel
yeah it was dead for a second this part is always such a pain in the ass but having
necromancer with summon is it's pretty great actually um do i like bath bombs yes i do but
one time probably two three months ago uh i did a bath bomb and i thought i had jaundice and i
freaked out and almost canceled the stream i was seconds away from canceling i think i actually did
cancel the stream i was like guys this is i gotta do something i gotta go i have to go to like the
doctor and i did like a mustard colored bath bomb and it stained my skin oh yeah almost went
to yeah we talked about it on the screen because we talked about if i had gone to the doctor
how horrible would that have been he would have been like what's wrong yeah i got i've got i've
got jaundice i'm not sure because we were talking about i've had i had like a liver scan and they
because remember when all these medical things were going on i had a liver scan so i'm sitting
there going uh-oh this is it this is it's my liver right as i go into the doctor and he takes
a napkin and just kind of wipes your skin
garamy what are you doing here uh the council can auto kill like you can automatically kill
have to be ready they sprint really fast and one of them has an insanely deadly move
you've got to be ready you're a hypochondriac yeah i that's what i'm saying it would have been
really really weird it would have been so hard to describe too it would have been like oh well
i have a liver scan coming up and i thought i had jaundice and i i don't i i should go
oh thanks all right we need to do a turban to waypoint usually pretty close usually
i'm gonna use that term pretty loosely because i am bad at this game you can see lots of fails
you're gonna see lots of triumph the council might get them no i don't think so if we come this far
i think it's gonna be something in act four that truly kills me if we've come so far i'm not sure
it's gonna be actually that doesn't act the ancients will get them yeah because i can't
leave that area i don't know it's going to be tricky i would be happy if i completed all the
normal on hardcore just because i've never done it before not that waypoint did i get it wait i
did get it didn't i it's right there any ftk news yes actually just had a meeting with the people
that are making it uh we are going to it's it's still being developed and it's going to be a lot
more we took all the feedback from everybody so it's gonna be a lot more it's not just gonna
be kind of random like hey leg let's go and i if you kill me kill me we're gonna be doing
lots of interesting things so it's not just gonna be a mess they just actually started working out
it again like as of tomorrow or like as of today and it's going to bleed into that server
after the next stream we're gonna do a couple of uh funds we're gonna do a couple of fun things
on stream and then that's going to turn into a 24 7 minecraft server at least for a little while
just for you guys to play on whoever wants to participate in that and i'm scared of doing
i cannot promise that that server will be available forever but i can tell you that
it will be available at least or i would assume a majority of 2020 all right here we go this is
the bad that these kill all right where are they where are they the hydra is the worst
i forgot about the hydras all right we gotta we gotta bait out some of the council members
all right stay back stay back stay back i with my i'm keeping my with this i'm not going in yet
i need a little mage did he explode where is it what's his body come on all right here they come
kill this stupid water thing when they come out they come out they just okay they're there they're
there okay this one who is that council member kill him good one down another one this is a good
pull oh fuck kill for a sec everybody alive still get the rest of them oh don't go in too hard don't
go into our pull back if you have to uh golem's dead bones dead is there anything on the ground
oh he's alive he's alive he's alive jesus all right that's three down i think this is seven
i'm gonna get a new yeah i'm gonna get a new one guitar what's that down made of a metal
fresh bacon my favorite scent ah these things do so much damage you have no idea
we gotta pull another one out oh look at all that fire all right we got two we got two
there he is flame ringer come on vic look at vic doing work his colleagues play up
got it nothing from the council i think there's one more in here
holy fuck okay there's another named one in there uh my favorite smell odd questions tonight
she's right in front of me all right get it we need to get in here somebody's to kill him
they're doing it there's another one in here how many more people are in here
an am room it's not too rare but it's still pretty good who else is in here oh there's another one
this on hell or night and night and nightmare temple's dark power is broken is horrendous
all right i got the flail combine everything together come back break this and then we're
going to be almost a third act boss and then act four is actually very short once properly
imbued him's flail can destroy the compelling orb and reveal the way to mefisto place it
into the favorite scent okay it's gonna sound weird his heart is when you drive around the
back of a burger king then transmute them to carry out kalim's will ridding kurost of the council
of zakka room was essential that burger king exhaust is what i'm gonna call it
brands mute everything make kalim's will are spoilers that was called the eye brain the heart
in the flail kalim's will he can only use this the only thing that works to break
the orb to bring you to mefisto so we're making our way to the durance of hate let's sell some
shit diablo and bale have surely found the temple city by now they seek to free their brother
mefisto who was imprisoned by the haradrim in the temple my brothers will not die in vain
sorry i can do that better and prevent them from releasing hatred upon the world
my brothers will not die in vain one of my favorite lines bash the orb dude was that
what was that was was that was stuff speaking can we get a bugleberry emote uh the idea is
maybe to have like a 50 slot bugleberry yeah we're all out of here who's with me
oh me me me me all right let's go birds of hate level one search for mefisto in the durance of
hate when we find two i've got to find the uh waypoint mefisto right hopefully i don't
get instantly killed accidentally somehow is he gonna kill mefisto i don't know let's get lucky
and have it pop up right here that'd be great earns of hate level two come on it's been a while
since i've been in here so you know these memories are coming back this door runs for better gear
yeah what was the orange thing was a rune socket runes and if you do let's say you have a three
four five or six socket piece of gear there are words you can spell with the runes that make a
unique item something that they did not have in diablo 3 i don't i don't really know why
because people really liked it people thought it was one of the best parts about this game was
collecting runes and making rune words i don't know why they got rid of it and we got fucking
lucky hey otto what are you doing the oh diablo mega low three yeah i i'm not a i'm not a major
gigantic fan of diablo 3
i did think diablo 3 was fun to play but i didn't think it was fun to continue to play
the part the original is diablo 3 was eh it was good it was okay
okay they had like the most uninspiring shitty item system the abilities were fun to use
combat was fun although it was sort of a little it was a little uh the word i'm gonna use here
is like nose bleeding you know what i mean i'm gonna get that it was just like you just kind
of sit back and just get noses bleeding while you just click the same button and just stand
into a hallway and go a thousand boring
you mean brains yeah it's a little nose bleeding all right be careful i could die here fire protect
me at all costs losing people the iron golem is still pretty good though it wasn't all right
there were like three enemies in all of act one it's just i'm an item person i like collecting
items there was no reason to do that in diablo 3 every legendary was the same like it just had
hundreds of stats up it was just that was it and i also would and i know when they greet
yourselves came out they approved that game a lot but there's only so many band-aids you can put on
something before um you know you have to go to the hospital one of the things i really didn't
like about diablo 3 was grinding for legendaries and then rerolling stats it added that rng on top
of rng on top of rng it just was it was just a madness you had to roll you to get the item
and see what it rolled and then you had to reroll something on that item to be better for what you
wanted it for and then after that roll there was another roll to see what it rolled as
it was roll roll roll roll roll roll did you get what did you get max now you didn't it
was a shitty roll on that roll oh sorry you were looking for a plus 15 to uh to to fireball you
got eight you got 11 i have to do it again i'm being like what the fuck am i doing this for
i'm good looking for that weight thing you only have one point and summon resist
hey we're okay this way i also like putting points in too i know that some of the argument
against okay you have to you could put 20 skill points in that but it doesn't matter because if
it just was based on your level anyways you'd see it grow you don't have to put it but i like
putting points in it's fun for me it's scratches and itch for me every single move you have in
this game can have 20 skill points put into it by you something about it is i like it well here
we go but i need the waypoint am i gonna play diablo 4 i don't know a diablo 4 really does seem
like they weren't really ready at all for it they saw all the backlash that diablo immortal had
and they may have been developing it but then they're just like all right dude we gotta fucking do
something because this is not even close like hey we're gonna announce diablo 3 it's not even
close you maybe you'll see it eventually over the next few like three or four years i don't even
know who knows it might have happened for five years and it looked like diablo 3 to me just looked
like diablo 3 but they put it on another engine kind of let's put it this way i don't have very
much confidence that diablo 4 will be a very good game now would i like to be pleasantly surprised
yes but judging by the fact that in that first itemization preview it was red light green light
attack defense and they're going back to what why people didn't like diablo 3 in the first place
and it was i i want to make dumb choices i want to have i want to be able to put 20 fucking points
i want to have like a bunch of crazy uh fixes you know what i mean i was thinking something
i didn't like about diablo 3 was everything was tied to weapon damage like no i don't want to
just have it be uh like 800 weapon damage 1200 weapon damage 375 weapon damage
just made it too it just yeah it's too samey not only that when you make a character in
diablo 3 you don't have to make another one ever again if you make a barbarian in diablo 3 that's
the only character that's the only barbarian you're ever gonna make if you can just be anything you
just do anything am i ranting am i ranting right now i feel like i am like i'm ranting this is kind
of ranty but then you have to think back too right so this is like also important is a very
important part of this conversation the people that made this game none of them are even gonna
work on it you know what i mean it's this game was made by completely different fucking people
but 100 different dev team 100 so it's well i really wish we'd get like a true sequel to
diablo 2 the reason why we're never gonna get a true chrono trigger sequel because
none they're not they're never gonna be together again where is this waypoint it's like yeah but
like dozens of three done how did you know i was gonna say dozens of different companies and three
employees but i corrected myself and then i freaked out that's kind of the nature of
game development it's kind of a kind of like a sad annoying reality of the whole thing is a lot of
times when a game comes out there's a lot of just layoffs and changing and you go down all right
thanks for making that game uh 30 of you no longer work here and you're going to go to different
companies and we'll never be on the same team again like all of blizzard north was gone after
diablo 2 gone i don't nobody knows really what happened or why it's like blizzard north did not
exist anymore after this game may we even working i think on a prototype for diablo 3 and then it
was like no you're all gone there you go all right you're never gonna get that same it's like the
series is not even the same series it'd be like if i made a youtube video right let's say let's
say like tomorrow i upload a youtube video i'm like okay guys here's my next video it's been
it's been like four years since my latest youtube video check it out and it's another person
and they're going like hey man what's up it's germa985 here and i'm playing uh i'm playing
apex legends i feel like this is not even the same person i didn't make that video
there's even my video still this is even my channel still that's where it gets weird
because we're led to believe that all these things are sequels but it's like it's not even the same
people and eventually there it is because eventually i'll find this fucking waypoint
do miss piggy's shirt
all right are you guys ready to take on bathisto and maybe die
86 000 i should probably level up one more time before doing this
anything that's not a greater healing potion is getting sold
and even some of the greater hand just sell them once we get to nightmare you're gonna realize that
this was all not even worth doing but it's okay all right let's go did i redeem a wink
nah nah save it trust me save it nah save it save it save it save it you want to save it
we have to find another council by the way which sucks this one's arguably worse than the last one
you redeem it no you don't be so right about diablo you make me mad kill bathisto
i need to what's my lightning resistance not very good i have lots of cold but no lightning
lightning is so important here all right let's be careful here comes another council
kill at least one of them come on pull back pull back back back back back back back back back back
i got no shame in this easy easy easy vick don't do it vick whoa whoa okay i gotta get the army
back isn't lightning resistance important yeah it's important for everything it's just hard to
find sometimes oh i need another item all right vick let's go i'm gonna make an army this is not
even mafisto either this is gonna suck hopefully he drops the button oh ah the nerves are starting
to come up because this might this might be the end would be the end how is it no wink ray missed
bits five thousand from guess who guess who bilaterally lich fifty dollars fifty five zero
back jerma i appreciate how good you're doing i understand that if you don't die like a failure
chat doesn't get to laugh at you wait wait hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
it is more of this message i can't see what does it say it says i appreciate how good you're doing
but understand that if you don't die like a failure chat doesn't get to laugh at you consider our
happiness it's been considered and i of course want you guys to be happy of course i do i want
to be happy too where are the bodies did i you have i used everybody where the bodies
what the fuck i can't do this alone i need bodies because i reloaded the area god damn it let the
bodies i can't you have to scream to do that how is that possible i talk normally for like
two hours my throat starts to hurt can you imagine
screaming as loud as you possibly could for like two or three straight hours doing a concert
oh they're invisible something's got to give up something's got to give up something's got to
that's an old song too how you can't read or count
all right i need a iron piece of material so i can make my iron golem come on somebody drop a
knife or a sword or a scimitar i do it with gold what if he's gold 50 more dollars just came in
right now uh five thousand bits from the lemmy thanks for the fucking huge money both of you
they say germa please stop making dial-up modem noises and watch the new nancy drew show
i'm going to be in the majority here that doesn't watch the nancy drew show we got our own
talk show no it's what networks is i don't know some network i need metal i'm just gonna apply
something in the store i'm gonna go press play lightning resist perfect
i don't want to take a waypoint because the waypoints are already where i want it
you know because something's got to give up am i just gonna walk in circles seriously
might as well get another level while i'm just walking around aimlessly
okay let's kill some stuff if you could stream the show would you watch it yes i would
just for the joke for one day just for the joke for one day and then never again
all right come on we're gonna kill like three more things
uh we'll get it from the council yeah we got a gang up on somebody careful when we go in here
kill it kill it kill it good come on kill it good good good good nice all right everybody
hold back hold back don't go in there's the level dropping bombs on us careful can you read the
nancy drew novels no there any more council members i know there's one there's one over here
this i'm gonna i gotta clear them both out because it's hardcore i can't fuck around
there's a council member on both sides
oh come chase me oh fuck all right out everybody out everybody out everybody out everybody out
face us god damn it all right we're gonna go in anybody dead all of that i can't even see
where he is various wan void bringer got it god oh yeah yeah i'm gonna put the waypoint here
this is a good place to do it i've been saying i i i a lot more i never realized that i'm not
going to apologize for it though a different fucking word all right same thing on the other
side we have good crew we're here i'm standing at fire whole team no it's not the same word
it's not the same word and it and it's actually the premise of the video that you it's the premise
of the video you're doing the premise of that video okay i'm not gonna get forward let's go
come on get it from both holy fuck i thought of my game just nice okay we are free to fight
the fisto without very much interference he's still alive what do you have for lightning
resistance all right you're gonna have to tank them it's gonna be up to you get better gear than
i do you have better stuff than me all right actually i'll put a portal here
let's get ready level up here's what you can choose from kill him for his stuff i will not
influence your vote here's what's available you already know this you already know what's available
let's just get it off with oh it seems uh it seems we're split here i don't know what the new ones
do well the new ones on the bottom you shouldn't be clicking because they can't be put in until
level 30 well it's definitely not summon resist so that means it has to be iron golem because i
can't click the other one thank you for voting reset it wrong what do you mean wrong clearly
16 percent of you clicked on the left side all right i'm giving you one more chance here all right
you can't tell me that i have to zoom into this oh yeah yeah oh yeah yeah there it is oh yeah
yeah hold on hold on hold on now it should be it should be real easy now do it again do i have to
go in even further this means most of you guys are clicking right here all right if you're going
to click on something make sure you click like over here or over here don't click like in here
zoom in more there's no way to mess this up now there's no way to screw this up now you're doing
it you've been doing it on purpose look at that it's on purpose look at that shit look at that
circle look at that it was there was no problem the whole time i didn't have to zoom in the whole
time it's all right it's iron that's iron golem that's iron golem you fucked around too much
that's 68 over now look at that that's iron golem streamer's choice no that's iron golem
unfortunately that's really that is iron golem look at this blob over here on the left side
all right let's go blame your fellow chatters or that you know they they're having a fun time
passing around kicking around they're really just kicking around uh iron golem take a look
so going from three to four will be uh another 15 percent damage returned and more plus 40
percent damage bonus i mean uh defense 315 defense and a lot more thorns do the stats now please
thank you do the stats now please thank you thorns omega lol vitality next time chat is stupid just
give it to skeletons instead good all right that was that was vitality it was eye tracker
oh look shiny blue globe oh what are we doing that's vitality that's it's vitality
vitality thank you thanks for voting appreciate it yes it was thanks cool all right let's go
let's go attack mafisto actually let me sell holy shit god damn man freddy freddy dread freddy just
gave uh 400 in bits that's 40 000 bits from freddy dread that is omega bits yes freddy
today has given 600 worth of bits there's a lot of winks uh they say i went to nobu tonight it
was amazing going to hash house tomorrow night though getting the blue cheeseburger and i'm
telling you telling them you sent me i hope i get kicked out i hope you don't get kicked out
because i don't want to tarnish my rock solid reputation in hash house agogo nobody knows i've
never told anybody well i didn't tell anybody i just go and i eat the food and i like it and i
leave but holy shit freddy have fun in vegas man thank you so much for the 600 bucks tonight
hash house agogo in the link make sure you go to the one in the link
like hold on what i need to read this i'm sorry germy but i can no longer watch the stream it's
not you you were hoggers it's me i'm an omega lull i'm sorry this is pepehands but it has to be done
we've been weird champ for months and it's time to end it thanks uh good luck good luck to you
uh but freddy have fun in vegas you want my favorite spots in vegas at least on the strip
because i think that's gonna kind of be where you are uh the aria and the cosmo are the two
best casinos on the strip without a doubt they're just probably the nicest ones the aria probably
especially is probably the nicest um scene on the strip uh circus circus is i mean i the place i i
do like the circus circus for different reasons another 80 bucks from freddy already dropping
stacks tonight uh i had almost 700 dollars love you big time germa thank you for the suggestion
i'm gonna i'm going to go on the link i'm gonna go to the link eye roller eye roller freddy dread
and play the betty white machine it's it's ready to pop it's ready to go i can feel i can feel a
jackpot coming on if you see it have fun though thanks so much for this this insane amount of money
that's a lot man have fun rich and handsome freddy dread
oh i need this right now do i have any slots okay that's 22 lightning resistance very important
right now tane can do this for free stop there was a wink i'm just gonna believe you guys now
every time all right uh i need to find i need a piece i need a socketable gear
i need something that can hold a socket because i want this lightning resistance
i don't have anything that can do it though and you can't un-socket well what about you do you
have any armor i can buy who has armor to buy i'm just gonna buy something with a socket or
is it who who sells it i think it's you yeah there was another wink
yes i don't think there was socket socket socket socket socket shit actual wink don't lie to me
i'm not doing another one the boy who cried wink greetings i need to i need socket
shit oh my god more money my lactary lich comes in with a 10 000 drop 100 bucks so you're going by
necromancer now nerd haha what's up douche it's clay golem from act one remember me me and the
guys used to give you a hard time in the graveyard sorry you were just an easy target lol i can see
not much has changed member dekker the old guy you saved yeah we're married now i make over 200k
gold a year and drive a horse and buggy i guess some things never change huh loser nice catching
up lol pathetic somebody had to write that originally can you imagine just the the shit
post connoisseur that just came up with i just wrote that one day somebody had to sit there and
write that it just it's like that and anyone like this yeah like you're doing now people come up
with the most ridiculous shit all right let's go thanks for the huge money i need to find a
place to put this phylactery to the 50 dollars 5 000 bits from phylactery i wrote it you nerd
no no i don't want any wrong waypoint thanks for the 150 fucking dollars let's go let's beat
him let's go let's go let's go i can't i don't have a full crew though i do now let's go vick
is tanking here he is get in vick tank his ass kick his ass we need a new tank not me not me not
me i don't have any lightning resistance quick all right keep it up i'm ready with the hill i
dropped it i dropped it hold on get him actual player the guy with better gear than me get him
call him going down all right vick is going to take care of everything
don't don't hit me don't hit me oh the last skeleton oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck vick vick vick
vick help vick get out of there get out of there get out of there all right we're fine we're fine
uh i need um quick quick i gotta hurry before he starts regenerating health i need let's go lower
cure let's go i need to re uh regroup i'm not gonna fight him i don't have my gear sucks i don't
have any offensive abilities my offensive abilities is other people's offensive abilities
quick before he recharges come on somebody i need to when you fight somebody anybody please before
he regens you were supposed to take that you wiped the whole raid all right get in vick i don't like
your attitude very much uh-oh guild's breaking up oh fuck okay get in anything metal on the ground
battle axe let's go i gotta move bring the crew back in hurry hurry hurry hurry docks all right
go swarm him i can replace he's gonna die kill him kill him go high minion act three is done
oh oh that's a lot of cool looking things that i don't know if we're gonna be worth it
i think i already own this this is this is i already have this breastplate
journey mafisto eyes and hearts my regards to the abyss 107 to 105 is the same fucking thing
but we can turn them into a uh it's still so stolen taking it to a golem all right i got some
more stuff to look at though helm 41 to health phylactery thanks for the 50 dollars hey it's me
mafisto where the fuck did you go i have an appointment after you come clean up these
skeletons i didn't read it in time watch the lore video all right we will watch the
cutscene on this one i promise um is that better than what you have hey berserkers 33 33 fire resist
that's better put that to good use all right what else we got faith in you was well deserved
but diablo has made his way to hell and it is likely that bale followed him there
diablo
i just said in spanish diablo your day is your day has come diablo your day has come
all right i can make these both into uh iron golem let's do the breastplate
oh now we're in act four it's gonna be fucking omega i'm so excited for how do we vote vick off
the island vick was an integral part of what's that yeah i guess i'll check the other loot too
and there's more stuff that dropped battle staff power shield broadsword battle staff
bring it back to king we got us three to glacial spike can the iron golem cast glacial spike
did i do this a lot of lightning damage all resistances plus 11 i wish i could store these
so all right it's time to get rid of the gems it was it was fun well lasted but these are all
gonna be worthless soon get sell the chip gems the shit's not metal that's right
we're in act four we're gonna start they're gonna start dropping at least flawed and regular
hey hey quest completely something else on the ground broadsword could this be better than what
i have not even close what are the gems for uh sockets you can socket lots of gear has sockets
they're good just to you know fill up what's the socket this see sockets too some gear just has
empty spots and you can put whatever you want in them we also didn't do quest four but we don't
have to do that you get a book of skill which you can use to upgrade your stats once we're almost
at level 30 i don't not necessarily not necessary time to go to x4 there's also some shit back here
this chest to open all the way in the back why you always carry keys because some of these
chest backs here that you see locked that's why you should have a key every time you do this
it would be something good in there very possible all right that's it pretty cool
hey i love these chill laid back streams lately yeah it's good to take a little bit of a
just hang out and play a game that you like happen sometime i like it too all right so you're
talking about sockets this has two sockets and it's not worth it unless you have a two rune word
i need a key how do i not have a key it's locked how do i not have a key portal
you want to watch the cutscene that's gonna be loud all right here's the cutscene quiet it is
you told me tyrael i found the temple of the zakka room in the deepest recesses of the temple
i found a dark gathering my companion the wanderer and a great evil
oh who could only be the lord of fate to himself
like a thousand needles in my heart my brothers at long last we stand
we currently from metal gear solid by the way and also benten's uh
yeah
the sky shall rain fire and the seas will become as blood righteous shall fall before the wicked
and all creation shall tremble before the burning standards of hell but i saw them who's not meant
for mortal eyes the gate stands ready time has come to assume your true form
oh
he doesn't do that there well the next cutscene coming up is the best one good to see you we've
made it the hell the time has come for you to destroy mephisto's soul stone
you get a lot of good shit stone to the hell forge place it upon the forge and strike it
soundly with the hammer only by doing this can you prevent mephisto from manifesting in this world
ever again mysterious it's good to see you again hero it is good to see you again i know every
line mephisto's defeat is a great victory for the light the pandemonium is the last bastion
of heaven's power for the gates of the burning hells this place has been hallowed by the blood
of thousands of champions of the light yourself now the final battle against the prime evils
draws near to face it alone i have been forbidden to aid you directly well it's actually gonna be
my friends to do it i ain't gonna you and i both are in the same boat here we just watch
which you're really talking to skeleton number 240 not me you skeleton 240 it is up to you
and vic you were there as well
and the skeleton is just like just brainless skeleton 240 lies to you and he just like turns
and goes like most guarded secrets he became a corrupt shadow of fallen ain't trusted neither
is wall for his transgressions is wall's spirit was bound chat build that literally never going
to kill diablo which was summoned from the abyss it's gonna be tricky spirit has decided within
that torture yeah it'll be hard it's gonna be really hard for long enough i employ you here
find his wife release him from his cruel imprisonment diablo is going to do his aoe flame
wave and kill every single companion and then i'm gonna run around going
and then open up a portal and run away and do it again that'll happen probably 20 times your
mela what do you need how come with the intro don't they have intros all right i got money to gamble
but we don't need cold in hell we need fire resist in hell what do i have for fire right now
zero all right there are only three quests in act four pretty self-explanatory go kill diablo
all right let's move i just need to get out there remember he's a set piece right now so he i don't
want him to die i am gonna gamble though let's do like a weapon or something anything because
right i mean this is not i'm in hell this is not going to do anything half the people
make a rune word well all right what do we got i what's the wiki i'm just gonna look it up right
like i don't know these by heart let me take a look double two rune words cheating that was a
knot how does the epic game store come up when you type in diablo two rune words that makes no sense
all right rune words we need okay three socket shield no scepter weapon three socket sword
to make this king's grace three socket sword or scepter is am ral and ful i don't have ful yet
though but that's a lot it's a lot of cool shit there's also leaf two sockets stave two socket
helm is orton soul those are kind of rare two socket helm nef and tier rhyme is shale and f but
shale is actually is not easy to find i don't have shale it's pretty good what about uh stealth
yeah talon f two socket body armor that's good but let's poison resist though
dexterity and poison resist and then a bunch of running and fat you run like really fast
that's not like not for me tier and l wouldn't be bad am and tier is called strength all right well
first of all i need to get something that has a socket in it two socket wand dull and low i don't
have those did you remember any advice um yeah i would probably i would probably try to tell
your teacher something else besides your username that usually doesn't work all right what about
these new ones no no it's gonna have to be one of the original ones at least for now all right
let's try to find a uh a two socket two sockets holy shit these are so bad sockets don't buy low
level garbage well i need something i could go kill uh i could go kill leg on dariel again
it needs to be white for room words well it has to be gray that's sockets all right let's just take
a walk outside try to just have anything drop we're not five forward now so oh boy all right
he's he's don't let him die he's got he's a green he's a set item all right get in there victor
make it happen set item into the goal yeah i did now we got skeletons now
gone and i would do it again too brass plate all right two sockets two sockets
yes all right come back so this is to make what should i make should i make stealth
let's see let me just check it one more time so two sockets two socket body armor
what does it make i could do smoke but i don't have a lum which is rare all right tal and f
f do i have tal no i don't have tal shit i don't have tal no you have an uno i need tal tal is not
rare and that will make this a sixth of dexterity plus 15 max stamina 30 percent poison resist
regenerate 15 man a 25 percent faster run 25 faster hit recovery do a countess run
damn it that was like opening a present holy shit okay tal f here we go al f all right nice
stealth i run very fast now uh yeah i do 25 faster run very cool all right now what about a weapon
we're looking for a two or three socket weapon three socket weapon is venom but i don't have it
i think that's the easiest thing i can make uh if i find if i'm gonna do malice i need if lf
or amd ral foe do i have a do i have am ral foe i have am am check am ral
didn't have a ral somewhere i got another ral didn't i they're all in here i don't have a foe
all right i'll try to get that i need to get a three so i have a three socket sword right here and
i've fucked it well i didn't know i didn't know ral foe and if i find all right ral i need a foe
and then i need a three socket weapon and then i can make that's uh that's king's grace which is
insane king's grace okay let's move still no fire resistance fantastic i'm in hell
yeah you just have to explore he knows all the voice lines but doesn't know how socketing works
well i didn't i know how socketing works i don't i didn't memorize every rune word in diablo 2
shit is gonna take a while little sorry pick three two data here only oh you get two skill points
for killing his wall by the way very useful he's an eye for socketed weapons i do move so fast
all right this is where i get the first test here oh he's gonna die where is he he's fighting
by himself where is he he's over here but he's alive he's alive okay where oh i'm all right
what's that fire still have no fire
the one place i really need it is where we are standing right now
i'm gonna take can i take i'm taking bone wall off my bar i have any i don't even use the damn
in their helmet one socket make an album of song covers what i'm not a singer
bone walls are just to troll people in pvp lobbies let's see sort of accurate
this really is a big game his weapon he's just doing so what's he doing 53 to 99
and look at his resistances they're all maxed out wait do you have fire resistance on any of
shit no you just have it because you're better than me oh i'm also not sure why i keep casting
bone shield considering there's one point in it begged us for bone shield i did beg you for bone
shield and you only gave me one skill point i can't even get two stop crying frame oh it's
because they're oops i just trapped my goal and killed them champions in here that's why
oh
nothing a lot of nothing
stand in front of that is well it's pretty close after you go right down
yeah you go to plains of despair it's the next level down and he's usually just right there
three two skill points we're gonna need to use them wisely regular skull nice
so yeah it's at this point i need to start to really pay attention we're going focus
mode for a little bit until we get close still everybody right yeah thankfully i can hurt you
guys because they're not fire resistant well so the people are here though
i am definitely going to do this though a couple of times try to farm out some uh
to try to farm out some uniques re socket re socket hold on i can't look at this oh my god
they have more than us they have more people than us i drank seven gallons of water today i think
i'm drowning re socket sword that's what i need the war sword i just need full my rings are so
bad too this one's okay i'm not going to use this i don't have what i don't have okay i need
and then i can make a pretty decent weapon take a golem out of the extra armor i already got he's
already he already is i need strength let's hold on to this until i can find it oh you don't it's
not rare why don't you carry a cuban inventory i don't like it what's this shit in here i'm using
it for extra storage space too much clicking that's for losers that's for losers what's that
sword i'm holding it because i didn't want in case i find a certain rune i'm going to make
another rune word and use that weapon get my oh so good i gotta clean up my bar too plus f buttons
i always carry a key might have an andy it'll hold party yeah
yikes zero fires this looks like oh don't stand in front of that
damn it just a brawl where are my tearless funny man uh after i beat as well we'll do one
i've been watching this for four hours and i still have no idea what's going on
oh it could be a little confusing just based on the fact that i'm running around with
10 random people this amplified damage has such a low radius that i have to cast it five times
it's like two yards found it all right all right as well give me those two skill points
dude imagine he sneezed two nights these guys suck too playing through this bear
chainmail what you got two
i'm gonna need you guys to stay alive actually my life well
actual wink this shook me out of bed and made me wink into a camera that's what that looked like
it was fake i'm sure it was while the skull incoming what's the max lightning uh what's
max resistance small charm gonna have 10 it's not a great role if that's the case 10 right
everyone's still left good where is his wall give me ruins
i got giant sword you better than have sockets
long sword three to 19 the other one was better
there's just cold in hell that's gonna be too much of a problem
junk the other one's 71 strength i mean at 58 it's not too far of a way to go
oh you're ignoring our weird pleas for attention
uh i'm not paying that much attention right now to chat yes you're right trying not to die in hell
sapphire super mana potion
flawed amethyst how has nobody died why am i guys so much better now
just not getting overwhelmed at this point chainmail looking for the quest marker pop up
go get him did i beat that on stream i played punch out on stream didn't i didn't i beat the
whole thing on stream no i did i definitely did that never happened maybe i just did it on my own
yeah i did it on my own now i remember but you said you did but you know what you said you were
but you never did i did it off stream i think sorry about that send this one to the doctor
we got a lot of doctor clips they're looking for as well
weird head oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yes yeah yeah there it is all right so this
is going to make okay sir i'll hold it because is war swords pretty good one-hander right for a
normal that's not a bad one-handed weapon hold it until i'm certain so what this is going to do
this is going to make something called the yeah by the way it has to be a sword it has to be a
sword or a scepter uh this is going to enhance the damage by 100 so this would be 16 to 40
pretty great considering uh it will do a an increased 100 damage to demons
50 more damage to undead five to 30 fire damage will be added three to 14 cold damage
152 attack rating and then 100 more attack rating to undead and demons and seven h
seven percent life stolen per hit it will not let me use it unless i have 71 strength dude numbers
all right so this is what is it it's uh make sure you get the right order am ralpho am ral
oh cool things grace looking for another three socket one-handed weapon uh if it's better base
damage then i'm going to use it kind of should just i'm sure i should just get rid of this
fucking thing do i have another skull don't i yeah there we go and wallace skull i gotta organize a
little bit because this is pissing me off oh this is irritating me this stuff is too big i'm glad i
found that move skull please what do you uh do you sell you do let's do that i'm gonna put this
stuff back in here move skull please move skull move skull it does make a great sound it does
uh skull asmr like that and nothing in here right back to it but i'm gonna pick up all the
remember it has to be a sword has to be a sword oh that's not bad this one's terrible
yeah let's put this on all resistances some resistance
eight resist all
oh Jesus who's he at no no don't get too overwhelmed
scale mail all right actually don't get overwhelmed i'm gonna go on i keep doing this shit
sword on sapphire it was a giant sword maybe i would do it too
all right a lot of invisible enemies found the next step but i'm not doing that yet until it
kills more junk not even useful at all oh well
golem's still alive yeah it was a lot of defense it was pretty good item for normal
so i'm gonna have to farm the pisto for a really amazing unique
and turn it into a golem so i can kill diablo you are looking into the future right now there he is
his walls okay get him taking 100 more damage all right stop fighting the crap soul please
you need all eyes on him we'll get him eventually don't worry
sorry kill somebody
but do a tier list while they kill them all right they got they got
i was gonna do it but uh i can't i die in a second here
here
why did you do it why did you do it
power all right guys this is important thank you hero it goes thank you hero
is was tortured spirit to rest the light protect you then i fear that we have been played for
feelings all along is wall helped diablo and his brothers tricked me into using the soul stones
against them now the stones powers are combined powers of the soul stones under their control
don't know i know the first line of every single one of these will be able to turn the mortal
because i've played this game hundreds of hundreds and hundreds of times
and most of the time the dialogue goes like this long ago i swore i don't know the rest of it
i just know the first line and i've heard that first line from every character
probably 2000 times all right this thing sucks one to 54 no junk two skill points bow
these skill points mean a lot to me this is a big boy 26 to 54
level one sacrifice an actual melee move that i could use instead of just default shit left click
it's two handed never mind i'll turn it into a uh bill i don't have room to do that anymore
all right we have two points to spend in fact i'm gonna hold off on this
because we're gonna have three points to spend so we're gonna do that first
i'm gonna keep moving uh where was that was down here right i found the other place to go
i forget where it is big map here in a second well actually i know it's right down here right
down here i think it's right here i mean i can run pretty damn fast so i'm not like in any real
danger where the hell was it right there right there big map where the fuck was it
oh these champions all right don't fuck around
oh shit i should oh fuck bombs dead bombs dead run run run run not worth it
wait i got another one let's go he's gonna be strong he's got a ton of damage
let him work let them work pieces we're good i don't believe where did the little staircase
that i ran by and i saw it and i'm like oh there it is i've got to remember where that is
i don't remember where that is all the way to the left i think yeah there it is okay no i know
where it is don't bring the mini map again please we're there are so good i'm gonna be getting to
the forge which we get some decent stuff there once we do the forge we get to break the stone
which allows us to get a bunch of gems and then maybe even a couple of rooms
big bits again from freddy freddy just gave another 250 dollars 25 000 bits and they say
hey hey my girlfriend at least just won 200 dollars at the aria hey there you go so i'm
donating it donating it to you it's like i played i didn't even have to play i went to the slot
machines already it was mine anyways hey viva las vegas i put 50 in 200 came out that brings
that brings freddy tonight up to 930 dollars in bits influence influence freddy dread everybody
hope you're having a good time don't don't don't lose it all though don't you don't go crazy vegas
is fun but don't let it consume you but holy shit that's a lot of money freddy once again thank you
so much for dumping almost a thousand dollars in bits on this stream i'm glad you're having a good
time now hey now go play brulette put hey put on 21 but hey put a five dollar bill put a five dollar
chip on 21 and then put five put ten dollars on double zero come back we'll see we'll see the
results gambling by proxy and then just let me let me know let me know how it went let me know how
it went after you do that and then if you could if you could for me
there's a machine there's a machine in there it's called they called it's called lightning link
it's great what you're trying to do is you're trying to collect these hearts
now just videotape yourself doing that for like an hour an instant
how is it unique in here i'm a unique enemy oh we've all right we got three levels up to do
let's do it you have three skill points not level 30 we have one more level you cannot do
fire golem yet i'm gonna do this one at a time these will be probably the last three skill points
that you put in until diablo so fucking hell whatever choose wisely you okay probably all
right don't mind me where is the first skill point going iron golem again five points
in iron golem i'm gonna give this another five seconds okay i'm doing it there's that one
where's point number two going no don't do fucking teeth this late i'm like gonna am i actually
gonna put a second point into teeth am i actually going to do that you can't be serious
these are so important and you're throwing it into the trash
there's still boats coming in hey i wouldn't mean no influence yes two points in teeth would be
fantastic right now late game into hell well instead of two to four damage we'll do three to five
going okay another point in iron golem you just guilt tripped everybody point number three
where is point number three going to go stop clicking on fire golem it's not gonna do anything
i can't do it okay it's it's actually it's actually fucking teeth two points in teeth
what a fucking what a joke what a joke two wasted points in teeth literally ruined the fucking run
how is it teeth because there's because there's 28 percent here like 31 percent here and like 15
percent down here that's 37 resplit but 63 split three times is 21 percent each blame the people
that are still clicking fire golem where the stats gone that's my fault it had 41 percent versus 34
percent just rewind it you'll see you want to do a re-vote you you want to do a re-vote i just want
you to see it's too late it's too late no it's too late i have to put it in teeth but i want to show
you all right it's going in strength we know for a fact it's all going in strength all right two
points going to iron golem because that's what you voted for one two and then the third point
streamer rewind there you go streamer rewind for the third i'm i've streamer rewind teeth is
absorbing us there you go 31 30 all right we did it again there it's 31 percent on the left side
done i have to put it in fucking teeth blame blame everybody here for doing that i can't believe
fucking but bone wall synergy yeah yep that extra percentage that that's 15 percent of
three can't wait to do an extra point four damage chew crew reporting in hey welcome everybody
welcome everybody from the chew crew good to have you here fuck off chew crew i didn't say
that don't anymore floods come on come on all right let's go at least we have two more points
in iron golem that's pretty pog pretty pog champ you know diddy the damned
make down one more flight of stairs and that will bring us to the end of the game so kind of
do i say fog in real life i mean i say can't wait to get fucking mcdonald's
in real life say that use teeth it's so bad it's so bad wasting mana that was fun
war sword oh pretty good war sword he's a golem guy
i know the funniest part about what just happened is this is the most humorous part for me
it took you guys until act four to start to ruin the game
that's i'm actually sort of impressed you waited for me to get truly invested in the game
and then you're gonna rip the rug underneath i know what some of you think you're thinking
oh yes he's doing pretty well i thought he wasn't gonna make it past like that too
oh we're gonna we're gonna change that make it so he can't win i still will
that is what i think oh i know us golem goons will never do that to you us golem goons
all right we're getting to a situation where there are are these naruto houses
the golem goons the shoe crew the drew crew the skelly crew not houses like villages right
there's like the leaf crew the fire crew what's the what is it the golem village the mega milk
crew you guys are what's my order for mcdonald's first person that says it gets it well they don't
get it i could eat it but you get to choose it i want only numbers number one number two number
three like when i thought of which one number number what number three what's the number three
what's the number three for mcdonald's i don't even know what it is that better not be any like
gross salad shaker or something it's a double quarter pound three is a double double cheeseburger
and that's to be a quadruple cheeseburger siri what's the number three from mcdonald's
you know his password is wow i gotta find it not using t no because it does seven thousand
percent less damage than me hitting somebody with a stick it's a noisemaker you bugleberry eating
mcchicken sure oh oh oh yes done and there's me doing an impression of bugleberry i can't
use a real person not me you guys have just moved one space to the right and given me even one more
point in bone armor no too crude gonna be right here watch don't run too fast
it's just false
did you give bugleberry a background check of course i did
i've been arrested seven times
come on i want to find bottom here lisa oh oh no i gotta run this way okay i'm good i'm good
that was almost really bad river flame found it and we got a waypoint just going in and all right
we're almost to the end game another five thousand bits you are just pile driving money onto this
ring normally yeah normal is not the end game i'm just saying the end game of act five four
phylactery fifty dollars says vic walks like he has a load in his diaper thanks for the five
thousand bits man appreciate it thank you thank you for the fucking hundreds of dollars
vic for first noble when's a tier list i know okay this is called uh
uh two thousands childhood snacks tier list what we got is fruit roll-ups pretty good pop tarts
depends on which ones let me get them out here i don't know what this is oh one of that's that's
tricks yogurt hmm bagel bites might be s tier it's possible gogurt's i'd rather have the tricks
yogurt where's don't is dunker dunker's on here dunker's are not on here so this test this is this
is an invalid test there's no dunker's on here so i refuse to take this dunker's fuck are you
i'll take it though just to snack pack putting gross not gross but like i these things are pretty
good but this is a snack or is it a drink lunchables were awesome that's a lunchables
pizza that belongs down in neft here these are the smushed up brownies where if you roll them up they
look like dog shits um they were okay goshers s tier no no they're not who be with these vitamins
circus animals i don't know what these are cereal straws those sound actually pretty good they're
going up here good cuisine disgusting although i remember no i like the brownie see these are
not the right ones but these were amazing uh animals hold on you know what these are
these are just oreos smuckers oh these are the gross pies okay sandwich creams grandma's sandwich
creams these are fucked up fruit by the foot and they're already on here all right hold on
let me get this right these are the gas station pies right those are the gas station pies
no where are the gas station pies why they're not on here you shouldn't this is a drink shouldn't
be on here disqualified all right hold on this is a drink and this is a tv dinner these aren't
snacks that's a tv dinner disqualified bagel bites this is stuff disqualified no wait this is
this listed i don't like this list that's just kind of sucked now the brownies don't even know
get the oreos up here go you put that up here gushers go down here fruit by the foot comes up
here i'd rather have a snack bag than a lunchable i'd rather have animals than a lunchable
well those ones wait what i can't even see what these are oh of course this is wrong this is the
ones with it's just like the weird mystery meat that you stack pizza is disgusting though
these are these are little drinkable yogurts yes okay they belong up here i'm not a pudding guy
i'm not a pudding person i kind of want this do they have this at mcdonald's hey can i get a
kid cuisine i'm done that's it top diablo to the stream we're looking at kids food whatever
all right let's do one more how about um chewing gum big league chew est here juicy fruit also
est here trident big red dog shit it just tastes like burning acid it just does not it tastes it's
awful it's just how is it with um bubble tape well i thought for a second i was like why isn't
this a bubble tape on it i'm only doing this because juicy fruit only lasts like eight
seconds that's the best tasting gum why is this on here oh you know i i think nicorette gum
belongs in s tier this is nicotine gum supplement orbits too basic the double bubble jug plus they
try too hard with their commercials gum doesn't clean your mouth so people like oh it's like
brushing your fucking teeth it's not it's like xylitol right whatever the sugar is
winter fresh i don't like the peppermint kind of gums i don't know what these are i don't know
what this is air breath i don't know what these are and then this is just gumballs gumballs
are pretty good actually can you do how it feels to five gum impression yeah sure
i think that's accurate wait now it is i'm not i don't i'm not a big mint gum person very cool
here it is big league chew is the best bubble tape juicy fruit double bubble gumballs from
the gum bubble machine 5g gum and then the rest of this we're pretending that we clean your teeth
and please stop smoking cigarettes i already got that one this one here the way that my my this is
the way that my my this is who would win in a who would win a fight food mascot combat prowess
they're all cartoon characters they don't they can't what do you mean wrong one well he's well
he's already dead so he doesn't make it he's already dead right sonny's sonny's cuckoo you
always got to watch out the guy that's willing to do whatever you just stomp on this
and it would just insta die all right it would just be a big tire mark footprint on this same
through this fucking glove we'll put out get let's okay let's go all the glove based
did you they're done you just rip them in half same with this like this is you're you're just a
piece of cereal you're gonna get stepped on in the fight this is the son i don't know who else
compares to that this is a baby i think the baby actually might be a baby would actually be able
to take on the gloves because the gloves can't do anything all right now let's let's do let's do
humans just like just humans okay is the king supposed to be a human chef boyard he's a human
is that all right this is a human oh that's not a human that's not a human i thought it was i
don't know why i thought that okay we didn't get this dog could be classified as a human
we need real all right this is a human this is a human this is a human in a costume small human
also small human green huge green human okay okay also human human except this this one has a gun
right this is supposed to be like a revolutionary guy but it doesn't look like a musket he doesn't
have like this guy's a musket right all right Ronald McDonald's a human all humans have to be
on the same tier because there's no they would Wendy's a human this is also cute there's a furry
right that's a human there's an anthropomorphic human uh no that's no no no no no no i just saw
the pants and shit this is also a dog okay dog cookie okay baby eats cookie
cookie stains gloves that's Julius Caesar i don't know who this is but it looks like a person is
it a person i think that's a human Count Dracula is a fucking creep but he's a human
and he's like Dracula's cousin so he goes over here all right now we do now it's animals no no
humans dog bigger dog obviously goes in front this is a cheetah so she's deadly
all right now we've got Pillsbury Doughboy would just get rolled over someone would step on him
these guys are supposed to be little right this is a bee but a bee would would just be able to get
just hit and knocked out by any human polar bear who know hold on we're just gonna get this right
frog would be down here this is like a wolf or something all right frog versus baby would a
baby accidentally kill a frog right if there was like a fight going on the baby would just like
and like roll over in the frog all right fragile but made out of glass so it's got to go higher
and this is yeah this would this would take this is taking somebody with him
what do you mean yes he's fragile he's made out of glass this is a big glass pitcher
all the all the Quaker Oats guy has to do is use the butt of his rifle and
and shatter him it's fragile he's made of glass he breaks through walls he literally runs through
walls it's just an owl little dog eats owl no actually owls owls are vicious this is just
a rabbit I don't be this would be if this would be a tough fight a chihuahua versus a bunny rabbit
would be that would I don't know bunny no I don't know chihuahuas don't chihuahuas
just kind of go like this what is this Captain Crunch is canonically microscopic well let's
let me just this is a big one let me get over this first what is this what is that an animal
it's a dinosaur I don't recognize a dinosaur all right it goes up here the bear another rabbit
they're both even doing the same move the Trix rabbit's a predator but okay okay hold on I
think that I think the Nesquik bunny would would beat the shit out of the Trix rabbit
they both do the same moves though it's hard they both do like when when the Nesquik rabbit
sucks up the Nesquik his ears go in a circle around and then when he eats the Trix it goes
and they wrap it they both do the same move they both move said it's a mirror match
that's too tricky I don't know this is a rooster I don't know probably down here somewhere this is
a regular dog all right wait wait wait okay Keebler elf would get stung by the bee and be and it would
spear him through his chest so he would die it would spear him directly through his heart
same with these three and a baby a baby okay the baby's leveling up
but the baby might accidentally eat the bee though okay also these guys tiny right
snap crackle they like this big yeah bee also kills these three this is a stork all right the
birds over here the M&Ms all right uh Tony the tiger tiger versus cheetah now that's tricky
this is just okay this is an apple this is an apple and a cinnamon stick at least the glove can
grab and squish and crush what am I thinking yeah the glove the hamburger helper could like wrap
around his neck and just start squeezing all right same here this would be tough because he has teeth
I think they lose to the frog though the frog destroys him but also he's made out of he's made
out of he's made out of like polyester the green giant is 55 feet tall we'll get to it
we're gonna get to it I don't know eat more chicken is this supposed to be just a cow
it's a cow right and these are just M&Ms but they're kind of big though they're bigger than
the rabbits and bigger than the chihuahuas human size they're like this big they're like two or
three feet tall all right let's think about this some nothing can compete with the sun
is that this is a dinosaur all right green giant you said he's 55 feet tall
that's just pure size no one can compare oh shit sorry yeah nobody can compare if you're 55 feet
tall the dinosaur would be tricky but this is like a friendly happy dinosaur this is not like a t-rex
right but this is also this this is the jolly green giant I don't know that's they're the same
remember the dinosaur is the size of a macaroni noodle oh it's the craft dinosaur all right you
actually these two actually can't do anything they just sit there they can't even move you guys are
all the way down here with this with the shit that is inanimate this would be a hard fight
please caesar has a massive army at his disposal out in 2020 well if we're judging if we're going
by that then these two are dead then these two are dead this is no no no no no by the way this
is little caesar he's like a foot tall I forgot he does have he does have a weapon though little
caesar is like a foot tall and he has a weapon he might not this the stork might beat him I'm
not sure little caesar can go up his dog or the bigger birds all right hold on let's get this
right you don't belong up here although you do crash through build it you like he like breaks
through like building walls and shit nobody else does that I think he actually might be stronger
tiger or cheetah probably tiger polar bear or cheetah polar bear sunny the cuckoo bird
or cheetah tuna fish or cheetah bear bear wolf wolf owl they're both fucked but I don't know
tuna versus cheetah you know no but okay wait but if we I don't let's I don't know
no tuna versus bear the tuna is huge they weigh like two thousand they weigh like three thousand
pounds if a tuna just swims really fast it's like it's like a mack truck running into you
no they're not well it's a blue whale whatever he's blue tuna's not fucking blue I don't wear
glasses either bear versus cheetah bear polar bear versus just regular bear this is a grizzly bear
what kind of bear is he no polar bear polar bear or tiger it's probably tiger the tigers are huge
and they're deadly tuna versus wolf all right this is where it gets I don't know if a wolf would
kill a tuna that had to be done it's just too powerful it's too many powers okay this is uh
let's get to the humans also two feet tall he is and he like two feet no no he's not he's just
kind of like he's just kind of a regular dude how I think most people could probably beat up a cow
in fact he's super old yeah he is old what I don't know what this guy is what is this thing
wario what is that that's john what a burger right what is he superhero is he just a guy in
a suit I don't get it what is he he's a superhero I'm not sure he well superhero but what are his
powers eating a shitload of calories like what do you how are you a hamburger how are you a hamburger
superhero ronald mcdonald is a hamburger character but he's not a superhero what does that even mean
yeah he can fly and he has super strength what do we know that though
or is this just somebody is this just a cosplay yes it's canon so then he has to be up here
if you're a superhero then you're up here if you can fly and super strength like obviously
you're going to be next to the guy that can crash through walls I still don't think he would win
maybe he would but I don't I'm not going to give it to him all right the king
just a guy these are all just humans wendy I think wrong okay this guy's got a gun so he's
always up at the top in fact he might be above the birds oh shit he might actually be above
tony the tiger he's got his revolutionary musket he would just shoot these people
what quaker a member of the religious society of friends that's a real name
religious society of friends a christian movement founded by george fox devoted to
peaceful principles central to the quaker's belief is the doctrine of the inner light
they're past the pacifists the fucking pacifist well then you're gonna get you're gonna get
bit to death by the apple good for you in this battle of all wits and skills the glove is
gonna just like suffocate you whatever the peanut would choke him peanuts dead he died he died
today he died this afternoon the rest of this is just like who got the first point I mean this
is this is this guy's all the way to the bottom is it you know how hard it is to be in one of
these suits it's hard for Mickey Mouse to even lean down and give you a hug in this he'd get
get mauled by the rooster maybe uh you lose to a dog you would he said he said captain crunches
is like it's like this no he's not there's like children in those commercials this would be a
fight no there's no way you lose you lose uh king this is just another person in a costume
why is wendy so strong if she pushed you just you push an old man down he's gonna die
he's all old men and these people are two feet tall how big is what is a king to a god a vampire
can't die i feel like this owl would just shred him up he's just still a person wait he can turn
to a bat yeah that's fine you're old you're old you're old ronald mcdonald though
how old is how old is wendy is when he's supposed to be like 12 or like 15 or something how old is
wendy just like 50 no i mean like now everybody's gonna throw haymakers i don't know if you're
fighting an owl though i feel like you you you'd probably win but you'd get
fucked up these are all the people that would lose to the to a vicious owl i mean if you were
big enough it how big is wendy is she like five four feet tall all right this is more accurate
the elderly would not you think chef boyardee is going to get attacked by a fucking owl
he's these guys they're they're toast donald sanders makes chicken for a living he kills
all birds but if he were face to face with a giant bird he's going to lose
he also walks around with a cane if you think that a giant fucking bird is not going to beat
colonel sanders this is just going to can open his head it's a hidden weapon cane that's not
part of any lore that's not true that's not part of any lore i think this is legit
hmm the dog might just okay wait the dog we're leveling dog up and cow little caesar has a spear
why is he so low because he's this big he's this big that spear is the equivalent of you getting
stabbed from the end of a straw and how much weight do you think he can put behind that spear
this guy weighs like 14 pounds you think he's going to be able to skewer you with a spear this
big and he's 14 pounds and he's eating he's currently eating always and his eyes are closed
you're going to be scared of that guy everybody else here has their eyes open he's the only one
that's not prepared also the only one currently eating quicker has god to back him up but he can
open his eyes he's eating a pizza every time you've ever seen little caesar ever he's been
consuming a pizza he's what he thinks he's going to lose that during a fight no this is that's his
lore that's what he does he's going to be eating a pizza why is quaker all the way quaker is a
pacifist i've got yelled at for this he might be able to he might be able to kill the rats all
right fine quaker has old man strength all right he would accidentally fucking step on some of
these things yeah okay they can eat right like of course they could they can eat he can eat
cookies he can eat bread he could eat apples all right he would eat he can eat he would eat these
guys if he like if he maybe he wouldn't know they were people and he ate them i don't know
what about the glove this glove can't do anything it doesn't have fingers all this thing can do is
scream at least these other things have arms or legs it's in a series of armless legless
faces that will just scream they're all in a row they're all in the same level
oh this thing might be punching and kicking and punching but the glove kills him the glove
just wraps around his neck don't underestimate the cinnamon toast crunch guys yeah that's true
that's yeah this he can't do anything they would just stick their fingers in his eyes over and over
again until he passed out or something i don't know still on diavolo 2 yeah we're probably
gonna call it here in a little bit turkey fried chicken presents the kernel of two worlds volume
one one and mr peanut's already dead please remember there's a literal baby above eat here
okay now explain to me how a a baby would not be able to defeat somebody that is an inch tall
or a single bee or a frog so the glove is gonna be taco bell dog but yeah but okay so but
but the the quaker guy here's the wall this is the problem the baby is the wall because
anything below baby needs to be able to be killed or defeated by being rolled over accidentally
everything else on this list it could the quaker guy does not that doesn't fit that category all
right quaker beats baby glove chokes quaker bunny rabbit eats glove done glove would just no it
wouldn't no no but it wouldn't though it wouldn't no it wouldn't no it wouldn't no it wouldn't
it wouldn't it just this is a pacifist no no i can't have that quakers used to hunt
so they have a gun thank you very much so he goes back to where he was before
but they don't shoot people but what's the all right so they hunt but they don't hunt
they're a pacifist but they they they shoot stuff they don't if chef boyardee sprinting at the
quaker in a full fucking sprint with a hatchet in his hand is he going to shoot him is the answer
no that would go against the ideology the answer is no and he's he's getting strangled by the glove
the quaker wouldn't kill the quaker wouldn't kill any the quaker oh he won't kill anything else he
won't attack but he'll attack a baby like that's not accurate the baby baby baby attacks quaker
yes defeats quaker glove defeats baby be yeah a quaker would like oops
how does baby kill quaker do you understand this is a paradox how does baby kill quaker how does
quaker kill baby paradox he wouldn't fight so he would die he wouldn't fight so he wouldn't kill
you understand the paradox here he'd be outlived all right that's fair all right let's go let's
it i'm done quaker in his own tier no he's just a guy baby starves to death no baby eats bee baby
eats keibler elf no no this has nothing to do with eating people this is fighting right this
is nothing to do with eating anybody all right that's it all right what no no no there it is
there's your there's your tier list for mascot combat prowess lower the tuna you think you
hold you think a tuna a huge ass tuna is not going to be stronger than just a person if you
are in the water with a fucking tuna you're in trouble what are you gonna do what do you mean
google i know what a tuna is i eat it all the time are they fishing or are they just fighting
and where's the what where what's the arena is this wendy home turf or is this star kiss tuna
guy home turf because it's wildly different either way is this on land he walks on land
how big is he average tuna length 15 feet fucking tall get out of here guys give me a break
this guy's 15 feet tall the average length of a tuna is 15 feet huge that's not an eel that's the
star kissed tuna guy he loses to a wolf no he doesn't he's 15 feet tall
how he he doesn't lose account count draculis still kills him though no he doesn't okay that's
good i'm done all right let's go beat diablo he's small in the commercials no that's it i'm good
that's that's the one we're good that was a good one river of flame this is the where the game is
gonna start to cross into the last part of act four the hell is that we're gonna have to break
the soul stone i have it with me right yep hurry up and die i want more clear lists
we're actually probably gonna end it here pretty soon i might not get to diablo tonight
we'll probably can it for tonight soon after yeah yeah yeah let we're not gonna do another
10 plus hour screen today well we'll can it after uh we do the soul stone that'll bring
us through about like eight hours you just want to do a third d2 screen well that's not what we're
doing tomorrow you're just gonna die at diablo i'll look forward to it bastard sword let's take a look
we'll need one socket damn it that's great minimum damage too
too finally the surge too tomorrow no it's co-op with joel right let me just make sure
that's actually let me just make sure that's happening i think we're good to go just make
sure we're gonna go for it should yeah i think we're good to go tomorrow around 3 p.m pacific
we'll probably do some keep talking nobody explodes and i don't know maybe we'll do
something else too we are officially i believe
one socket terrible terrible all right don't get trapped here
all right would you guys get mad at me if i like didn't the pistol like five times off stream
you would well i'm still alive here we go destroy the soul stone we actually got it pretty quick
i didn't think of anything funny to say for that one sorry if i died off screen
that would be so anti-climactic i'm gonna get up
what happened to my buddy he's sneezing that guy's eyes i did well you'll be all right
you know a little sneeze i do angelic mantle yeah
joel look at how much look at how many people are over holy
shit you lost 200 people when you go back to diablo
whatever you get from taco belt he's a goody to crunch get two of them and a water
and tell him germa said
that's right let's break this and see if we get very good
there is the guy there is a fast toe the armorer hell forge hammer play this out
and let's crack the soul stone and get a bunch of cool gems
well get it you deserve it you deserve couple though
okay all right here we go protect me smash it use the hammer see what we get
hit percentage flawless perfect emerald flawless emerald emerald bulb oh they're beautiful
beautiful weapon broken so now what now that's it now it's time to get taco bell that sounds
pretty good i know i really like these diablo cream it gives us an avenue just to just to do
whatever i love it it's only the second one and i'm gonna do it again and i'm gonna do it i'm
gonna do it until this character dies whatever that is all right i've got uh too much shit too
many gems how many ruins all right guys we are probably about an hour and a half but we're
depending on probably like an hour or so away from diablo and i am i have second thoughts on
if it's going to be possible so we're going to try again move the skull before you leave
pretty good but i actually i am kind of hungry and i do uh want to get some sleep last night
we did it for about 10 plus hours but i don't really want to do a 10 hour stream right this
moment i want to eat i haven't really eaten that much today i want to get food and then it's about
10 11 o'clock coming on 10 o'clock pacific it's a good time to end it let's all go to taco bell
well i don't know we'll see i'll see you guys tomorrow depending how long me and joel play
our co-op games you may see the conclusion the hardcore run tomorrow possible depending if i
can beat diablo tomorrow i'm saying tomorrow but i don't know we might play keep talking and maybe
some other co-op stuff who knows we made pretty good progress two more difficulties that's true
but when you get to i should have decent items what about bail oh yeah i'm gonna if this character
stays alive it stays alive what if joel doesn't do it again then it's diablo week no no tommy
lebone all right let's call it here i will see you guys tomorrow starting probably around three
to four p.m pacific we're on 34 typically i think uh joel streams pretty late so
we start around three to four p.m pacific good night everybody i missed freddy dread gave another
hundred fucking dollars i was in the middle of fucking yelling about something freddy dread gave
freddy dread's over a thousand dollars in bits today one thousand dollars in 25
gosh there's two s tier i was yelling about snacks but holy fuck freddy if you're still here
in one day a thousand dollars worth of bits that's crazy i'll see you guys tomorrow we're
gonna do the bits we'll chill for a little bit more and we'll do the substitute have a great night
a great rest of your night if you're calling a night then have a good sleep take it easy those
of you still here we had uh some stuff come in five community subs from z marin thank you z marin
jug mendio thanks for 300 bits hey jeremy you've been my all-time favorite content creator and
i've grown up with your content thank you for everything you've done for me in both defining
my sense of humor and inspiring and making me laugh in life's darker moments god bless
god bless it's always interesting to think that somebody may have been watching this channel
throughout their entire adolescent teenage years and now they're in college they're all
growing up you're all getting so grown up and so am i which is the scary part but i really
appreciate that thank you dunk hey min you access thanks for the three dollars and 30 cents 330 bits
thanks for all the great streams germa i've been having a hard time with the people close to me
for a while and your streams always helped cheer me up keep being yourself and having fun
started here about that but i plan on continuing just to do my thing however that is right thank
you for the 330 bits hope it gets a little better ocean dweller thanks for 250 hi germa why are you
not carrying the cube on you for extra inventory space it takes up four slots but can hold more
than the space it takes up i know it's just an aesthetic thing it's just i don't like the way
it looks in the inventory clutter like having 16 mana potions and 12 healing potions five different
keys i know it's a hypocritical thing i know ask name thanks for the 1500 bits has been
your major influencer and all you do is make us buy nancy drew thanks for the 15 dollars true
is it must purchase nancy drew well i don't want to make you guys buy anything
hey the acidic vengeance thanks for the 500 bits germa wanted to apologize that i'm so
rarely able to watch your streams as a european your stream times are late at night i especially
regret missing the simpsons stream blah blah blah i don't care about this message
that's so stupid i know i and i see it i read it and it's just i know no no no no no i do
i don't don't ever apologize for not coming to a stream it lasts a long time but ever since moving
to the west coast yes the eu that's why i brought the stream back to two three fourish p.m in the
afternoon because when i was in boston i started 7 p.m my time and i was late all the time so it
really turned out to be like 7 30 7 45 my time pm so i had i had to pull back my time to be able to
make it so there was no change your time you know what i mean i pulled the stream back about four
hours just to make it so it didn't start eu time like four o'clock in the morning or something
but i can't go much earlier than that i really can't i am not at my most energetic until at
least somewhere in the middle of the afternoon and streaming at like 10 11 12 i'm just not i'm not
i'm not gonna be able to do it so unfortunately most people in eu are between eight and ten plus
hours ahead of me there's nothing i can do about it i'm sorry that you're missing streams we live
in this big world it's 7 a.m here now it's a big world but if whenever you have time to catch it
then welcome good to see you thank you for the 500 bits uh lucas thanks for the 500 bits
remember your streams make working through my millions of scholarship applications a lot less
tedious thanks for everything you do by the way it's pronounced lucas got it right first try
well hope you get one of those scholarships good luck noon to 3 p.m eastern will be perfect for eu
and est viewers there's a nine that's nine o'clock in the morning i'm not i'm not gonna be able to
get up at like eight it's not gonna happen you don't want 8 a.m germa on this stream you don't
i am certain that e3 every day do it once do you see how groggy and irritable i am during
those e3 streams we had some community subs come in lord repta five community subs
prilla d five community subs thanks both of you now if you guys think that i can't reliably turn
a stream on between you know one to two p.m or like two to three p.m you know how exponentially
more unreliable i get every hour you go back you are talking about scenarios where i will sleep
through an entire stream oh hey i'm streaming it tomorrow at 8 a.m between like seven and eight
a.m pacific i'm gonna wake up at like 11 30 and it's gonna be like oh shit no no no i'm supposed
to stream and i'm gonna fucking rip out of bed and throw water in my face i'm gonna no that's
not happening i'm gonna sleep through every alarm i think this the sweet spot for me somewhere
between 1 30 p.m and like 3 30 p.m between like one and four is where almost every single stream
is going to start depending on the day and who i'm playing with and what i'm doing do i have
anything to do during the day or at night that's the sweet spot for me stream at 1 a.m
i it's weird no my my i'm no i can't because then i'll that's just i'll fuck up my sleep schedule
forever if i turn a stream on at like 11 to 12 p.m like 11 to 12 a.m like 11 p.m to 12 or 1 a.m
right i'm gonna be going to bed at like seven o'clock in the morning and then i'm just toast
you just reversed forever i've been on that schedule before and i hated it i did not like
it at all it kind of fucks with you you start to feel just strange after three or four weeks of
being on a schedule where you're going to sleep when the sun comes up and waking up when the sun
goes down it's just oh i have to do it for like i did it for like four or five months just total
maybe like three months in a row and it was just like holy shit i feel
just odd if you are able to do a true night shift then seriously more power to you because
i could never do it it's nice for a little it is nice for a little while because the world kind
of turns off and i hear something inherently nice and relaxing and almost it's like your own person
a little world because there's nothing is not there's no cars really going around
there's nobody calling you there's you don't have like an errand to do at 3 30 in the morning
four in the morning you get to live in your own personal little world but once that overstays
you can get bad for some people they love it and i hope you do but anyway a cream corn
thanks for the 250 250 bits from a longtime viewer here never knew that you'd love this
game so dearly do you think you've played it more than tf2 i don't know probably not because
i had time constraints when i used to play this at at its peak about three to four hours a night
i played it every day for years i played d2 every single day probably two or three years straight
but i was under time constraints because i was still in high school so i couldn't stay up i
could only really play for a few hours a night team fortress 2 was when i was in college and
then after college when i had every single day besides going to classes so instead of three to
four hours a day i could play tf2 for like eight to ten so he didn't study a six hour session
in tf2 was like ah that was that was awesome so just based on that alone that i don't didn't
have as many time constraints as i did when i was a teenager i would say yes tf2 probably at least
30 more uh doug mendio thanks again for 500 bits what would be your advice for motivation for a
project i have albums worth of music and my girlfriend really wants to see me finish the
record but sometimes i feel a bit scared to finish it just do it finish it because you don't know
what the end product is until it's done and i know we're getting the foreheads here right just do it
forehead but you have to take shots there's no such thing as a hypothetical shot you have to take it
you have to there's no hypothetical shot that's the way in gretzky quote it's true you miss
100 of the shots that you don't take wayne gretzky wayne gretzky smarter than albert einstein
because of that quote so you don't know you might finish that you might finish whatever you're doing
and go holy shit that this is great this is awesome i'm going to do it again
rather than hypothetically thinking what might happen if you do or do not do it
you can't miss if you don't shoot though it makes no logical sense well then revise it if you don't
take any shots you don't have an opportunity to make any goals there you go if you don't take any
shots one day you are going to die well yes of all of us eventually sure you don't take it
but you could say but you could say if if you cut your lawn tomorrow eventually one day you'll die
that could be if you drink water today you'll die eventually no i won't i won't die oh monkey i'm
drinking water right now but yeah you just have to let yourself do it you have to you just have to
try to do it try to finish it see how you feel when you're done you might have great things to
say you don't know give it a try hey airless thanks for the 250 bits didn't you say like five
years ago that when co-op was available on stardew valley you'd play it again i did say that
then i watched my girlfriend 100 percent the whole game so kim 100 percented the entire game
and i sat behind her and or on the couch and watched almost the whole thing i got to be the
viewer this time stardew valley why didn't she let you sit next to her on the couch no i'm saying
like i was just there sitting there the word behind i was always behind you like just i mean
like i was there not in the front and center doing the thing i was like behind you i was like not
doing it you eat 100 percent of the twinkies that you fucking open okay you eat 100 percent
of the twinkies that of the twinkie box in one sitting just be careful i know it seems like a
good idea but it never is hey freddy dread again uh yes just want to reiterate one more time hope
you have fun in vegas ash house a go-go blue cheeseburger if you like it one of my favorite
spots in all of las vegas at the link thanks for your thousand dollars plus in bits too so that's
even more that you had to spend thank you have a great time it's a great city hey chibi thanks for
the 400 bits i germ hope you're enjoying diablo 2 so far i do it's one of my favorite games
love your streams a lot and it's fun seeing you play my grandpa's favorite game
i haven't been able to grab him to come watch with me yet but he hopes you have a good time
as well ps the tristram town theme slaps it does very iconic let us put the sub
the sub uh credits on got a couple more bits to do but let's see let's uh get this to run
thanks for sticking around the diablo streams guys i know they not mean they might not be the
most exciting streams that i've ever done but they are fun i do enjoy them and a lot of people
have actually stuck around for them so i hope you like it i'm having a good time here come the
credits has changed the scene got a bumpy here sorry about that here are all the subs that subbed
on this stream thanks again i love you baker gun what with the old pistol no no no oh wait wait
all right is that is that a garden hose are we sure this is not a garden hose he's holding a
garden all right all right all right all right i don't want to show all right that's like
i don't want to show it like a garden hose i don't know no no i don't i don't want to show like a
brand like putting gun at me like that's that's fucking funny from the stream's perspective
uh what is it fun garden hose oh okay i can't laugh that hard all right now
holy shit germa sounds like a bizarro psychic right now why this is an old clip what is it
i did oh shit hold on wait wait hold on there is is wait till he lands wait till he lands
is that mr peanut what the fuck so i think the thing i thought it was mr peanut uh did they
kill that character off or does he still exist is mr peanut dead in camp that i did holy shit
this is like two years this is like three years ago yes oh i mean hey it's just this it's twitter
video so it's impossible to play the prophecy has been fulfilled no it's it's been it's been
at least a year and a half i moved to vegas in october of 2018 it's been at least like a year
and a half almost and this is yeah this is back in the old office the wasp is yeah the wasp is
more than a year and a half ago in a while i've been in vegas for almost a year and a half
please don't predict any more deaths well i'll try not to
anyhow we had uh eight dollars 800 bits from an anonymous cheer
thank you for the eight dollars anonymous cheer appreciate it 800 bits uh it the cas thanks for
500 bits hey germa i have a question is a boo the narrator on how it's made
that would be probably better show if he was uh we have a couple more to do we've got
what we got here we have 250 from yes is online i like giving you money people happy
i will take i will accept these bits thank you i will take them that makes me people happy
because it makes you people happy people uh assas w m h thanks for the 500 bits hey germa my
roommates and i watched your streams and vids a bunch in college i think you can say happy
birthday to a guy named andrew of your content keep it up man for sure happy birthday andrew
hope you have a good one you know i went to college once sick hold on auto is auto wants
hold on what does matter what is it you want to get out of here just wait one second i'm
gonna come with you uh what was oh yeah happy birth auto what's matter he's like no now he's
like not later now can you sit for a second just wait like 10 seconds auto says happy birthday
there you go he's like okay fine he's like okay fine he's looking at me like fine happy birthday
though seriously andrew hope you have a good one college buddies they're all they're all good
buddies all right hold on he's okay he's just like all right all right i'll let you you can
get up okay all right all right all right hold on give me a second all right we're good he
he was just like no i'm done i don't i'm not waiting anymore it just get me out of here
all right okay i don't know the music oh it's off this is auto's stream now he's recovering
very nicely too he has a few more days i think and then his stitches get to come out
and he's back to normal he's in good spirits uh we have two or three more to do we got high lord
high reward thanks to the 500 bits hi germa a couple weeks ago i saw you playing a clip of
spooky's jumpscare mansion and becoming so let me redo this before like air comes out of me
ah why a couple weeks ago i saw a clip of you playing spooky's jumpscare mansion and becoming
so scared you did a perfect amen break i had to see more so the first stream i caught was nancy
drew with the all the lipstick shenanigans and i knew i was here for life your veil your voice is
very soothing to me i also wanted you to know i saw you described as the king of jesters but
he'll never know it all he knows is his miserable jingling and his miserable jests love your boston
king miserable miserable jingling i don't know if it would be miserable thanks for the 500 bits
welcome sad e clown uh somnus thanks for the 500 bits uncut gems was robbed adam sandler should
have been on that ballot for best actor unfortunate apple shift thanks for the 250 bro i feel you man
i'm a huge night owl and a few summers ago i got completely nocturnal i went to bed at 6 a.m and
woke up at 5 p.m every day it's honestly really fun at first but after a while you just start to
feel like garbage yeah it happens and then it takes you so long to fix because even if you stay up
i'm gonna stay up all day and all night and then i'm gonna fix it and i'm gonna bet it doesn't work
you end up sleeping the same amount of time in different random time you'll wake up after four
hours stay up and then sleep for six hours it sucks how do you fix it you want to know the
real way to fix your sleep schedule and i mean this this is no bullshit this is true this is
actually real it's with food you have to eat at normal times if you do not wait till you are
hungry to eat at four or five o'clock in the morning your body will start to regulate itself
around your clock of eating food so if you just try to keep your meals out of like the wild zone
it actually can help am i serious no i i'm serious you look it up it actually like eating
at like normal times like keeps you regular no this ain't fake no it's not i promise
yeah how to fix your sleep schedule a late dinner can delay sleep so eat your last meal two to three
hours before you go to bed this will give your body enough time to digest the meal eating dinner
around the same time each day will also get your body used to into a routine yeah you want to try
to eat at the same time and eat but you want to eat early no it's real you can help reset your
body clock by doing it with food yeah i know it's real it helps i remember i did it and it actually
does help a little bit but uh peaceful hailey finally thank you at the end for a 250 here's
some bits have a good night germa and chad you as well but what about my ass eating schedule
well that's between you and whoever that's there's nothing to do with me why would it
have anything to do with me i don't know why did i implant myself in that conversation i don't know
why i just did that anyways uh tomorrow see you guys tomorrow for uh co-op with joe if for some
reason something uh is inaccurate there or for some reason we aren't doing it tomorrow
we'll see i'll be live tomorrow regardless why is this wrong all right see you guys tomorrow
around three to four p.m pacific good night uh wait vinny's playing chrono trigger vinny is
playing chrono trigger are you kidding me oh you gotta be fucking kidding me it's like the
best game ever made all right yeah let's ride vinny all right see you guys tomorrow bye