God damn it, I- really? Why was that turned on? I've been talking for t- okay. I was like,
why is nobody sympathizing with me right now? Okay, so listen. Wow, I've been talking for like
five straight minutes, like th- I've been talking for three straight minutes. Anyways,
I made a little bit of an oopsie. Uh, I um, I- I kind of was moving a table around,
because I had to put a table in this room, and I sort of maybe may have fell down and the table
like punched me right in the chest and throat. And it's actually kind of funny because I just
told this story, and I looked over in chat and I saw somebody say liar in all capitals. So I
thought I was unmuted. So I was like, no no no no no, excuse me buddy. I was talking to somebody
in chat. Somebody said liar right after I said this whole story two minutes ago. So I just went
off on a rant about that guy. And here's what I was about to say. You- if I was lying, if it was
like, oh I fell down, I oh have I smashed my chest. It would be 2 40 when I start the stream.
It would be an excuse. I'm five minutes early. That's how you know it's not bullshit. Think about
that. It would be like, oh 2 45 and I'm just getting started. I fell down. That's why I'm late.
I'm five minutes early. But anyways, uh, yeah that sucked. It like hit me right in the fucking
collarbone. It was bad. But I'm a little sore. I'm all right. Don't worry. We've got quite a day.
Oh, I hope you're okay. Give me sympathy. Give me sympathy. Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay. Thank you.
Uh anyways, I'm looking over here and I'm just getting real. You know what? We're going back
to- we're going back to 2017 streamer Andy. Those of you that remember that have been around for a
while. I've got a stack of PlayStation 1 and PlayStation 2 games. There are about 27 of them.
And I may have gone a little overboard. I'm going to give you a spoiler. I'm going to just tell you
what one or two of them are. Of course, we're starting with Driver. Driver 1 for the PlayStation
1. Right after that, I'm just going to give you just what's coming up next. I'm not going to tell
you anything else. We have the Land Before Time Racing Adventure. I feel like a lot of you are
going to be really, really happy about that one. So that's the first two. I'm not going to tell you
what the other ones are. Boomer game seems lame. Ban that person for an hour. You better fucking
have Crash Team Racing. I'm still stuffed here. No, I don't. No, I do have- no, no spoilers. Why
would I spoil it? I'm going to show it to you. You know what? Fine. Here's your last spoiler.
There are like 30 plus games here. I'm going to tell you one of them. And you need to trust me
on this one because people go like, oh, well, he doesn't have Crash Team Racing. What a fucking
idiot. Am I? Because I got the Bionicle PS2 game. You sitting down now? Are you going to be quiet
now? Are you going to quiet down now? Okay. Are you going to quiet down now? Well, I mean,
get excited about that, but quiet down after that. He knows his audience. All right. You guys ready?
Driver 1 is already ready to go. It's already here. My fucking chest hurts. Holy shit. Bionicle PS2
game. I might not be able to watch the Bionicle movie, but we can play the Bionicle game and
pretend we're watching the movie. Is that okay with you guys? Are you guys ready? Are you guys
ready? We need to do something very first and foremost. I want to make sure because capturing
old- because this is original hardware, by the way. This is original hardware. Capturing old
consoles. It's kind of hard. So we need to do a test. I know it's desynced. We're going to do a test.
How badly desynced am I? If I go like this, go, go, go, go, go. How was that? Your voice is
desynced. Okay. Hold on. Let's go for that. It should be lined up. How about this? Okay. So that
you tell me that's not lined up. Are you hearing me first or is my mouth moving and then you're
hearing me or are you hearing me and then my mouth moving? Which one? We hear you first. Okay. How's
this? How is that? Is that any better? One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Is it better? Still bad. It's worse. How does that make any sense? You hear me first? That's
impossible. Okay. Hold on. Hello. My name is Jerma. It's really good to see you. How are you doing
today? Now it's like two seconds. Wait. People are saying better. People are saying closer. Still bad.
Okay. Hold on. Okay. Hold on. Better, but still delayed. This is very confusing because here's
how this works for those of you that, you know, those of you that, you know, don't know that that
much about tech like I do. So I, because I'm capturing this console through a capture card,
the actual video is delayed. Like the video, the actual video game is delayed by about one full
second. So what I have to do is I have to delay my webcam and delay my voice by the same amount
of time that the video is delayed. And I thought I had it correct, but apparently not because they
should match up perfectly. So give me a second. That's weird. So why is that happening? This,
we do this now. So I don't have a meltdown in the middle of driver one. You know what I'm saying?
This should not be happening. So is this okay? So you still, are you hearing me first still?
What if I do this? Hi everybody. It's me, Jerma. How's everybody doing? You're doing good.
What's what's happening? How are you? But here's the problem. This is why this is going to get
weird. Cause watch this one. That's off one, two, three. Now that's delayed. It's two or three
seconds off voices. What is it? I don't, I've never had this problem before. I'm, I'm, I'm
delaying the video by 500 milliseconds and I'm delaying the audio by 500 milliseconds.
So what's happening here? I'm very confused. Is this, how is this? Hold on. Why is this so
fucked up? Okay. So now I'm delaying it again and now it should, it's here we go. One, two,
three, four. It should be synced. No. All right. What? Okay. This is the only time this has ever
happened. So I'm delaying my audio by 500 milliseconds and I'm delaying my video by 500
milliseconds. Why are they not matched up? That doesn't make any sense. I'm delaying the audio
by 500 and I'm delaying the video by 500. What's going on? What the fuck's happening? The video is
slower. Why the fuck is that happening? Hold on. I think I know why. All webcams are trash. That's
why. Hold on. All webcams are garbage. Don't believe any of the lies. Hold on. The webcam is slower.
I don't get it. Hold on a second. He's reading off of a script. All right. What if I do this?
Is it better? One, two, three, four, five. No. What the hell is going on? All right. So let me delay.
We're getting these bugs out of the way first because I cannot tell you why this is happening.
Every time you've ever seen a console game, I've done it like this and it's been fine.
So what about this? Hi. How are you? Just delay the audio to match the cam. That's what I did.
They were both at 500. How is it worse? The webcam is still too late. I've done it like this literally
every single time I've ever delayed the webcam. I don't get it. What happened? What changed? I've
got the PS1. Worst bit. This is not a bit. I swear to God. It doesn't make any fucking sense.
How is it getting worse? I don't know because technology is stupid. My webcam is delayed by
500 milliseconds. My audio is delayed by 500 milliseconds. Where are the scientists to
explain to me what's going on? Delay the audio by longer. It's going to fuck up how I capture it.
Hold on. This is a mess. It's all right. Let's try this. Why would that make any sense? So I'm
delaying my audio by 750 and I'm delaying the camera by 500. Excuse me? What's going on here?
Hello? Hi. How does that make? How does that make any fucking sense? How does that make any sense?
I need an audio engineer. How does that make any sense? Better? All right. But what about this
though? One, two, one, two, one. I got to match the video. The latency difference is malady.
Delay the audio by a little bit more. Why? What the fuck thousand times? I've never had to do this
before. One, two, one, two, one, two, one. Hi. Hello there. My name is Jerma985. I am ready to stream.
We're getting rid of the technical problems before we start. Am I lip syncing correctly?
Yeah. Good enough. Close enough. I don't understand this. All right. Let's go. Are you ready?
I'm closing the lid. That means we got to go. It's serviceable. The camera is like 50 mil. Wait,
hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I got to get this right. We got, I got like, I'm going to be here
all night like this. How's that? Hello, ladies and gentlemen, my name is Jerma985. I'm here to stream
some PlayStation 1 video games and I am here to describe to you what it feels like to have this
controller in my hand. It's still bad. It's not good enough. You overcorrected. What the fuck?
I've never had this experience before. No, it's food. Audio is now delayed. Wait, hold on. Let's
see if we can get the Goldilocks here. The stream hasn't even started yet. Welcome everyone to a
live stream on Twitch.tv. I'm Jerma985. Hi everybody. Welcome. My name is Jerma985.
It's a very beautiful day out today. It's a sunny, shining day. Good. It's so close. Clap, clap,
clap, clap, clap. Okay. Wait, one, two, one, two. Is that synced? Are we good? Good. Absolutely
perfect. Stop over pronouncing words. All right. Don't touch anything. The video might be delayed
slightly. Don't tell me that. Make it, okay. We've been in a nightmare for 10 minutes. People just
showed up. Look, I don't have an intro screen. You just watched it. It was 17 minutes.
It's slightly off. Don't tell him it's slightly off. Do head movements to match. Down, up, down,
up, down. Are we good? What'd you say? Get a movie clapper. Good. It's actually perfect. Play the
game. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. Welcome everybody to a PlayStation 1 game.
Let's close the lid. I'm ready. Are you ready? Welcome to PlayStation 1 Grab Bag Night. We're
starting with Driver 1. There's somebody on Twitter that has been asking me to play this
for, I believe it's been three straight years. Just to let that person know I'm here doing it.
So you're probably going to have to, you're probably going to have to
stop doing that Twitter. Why are you so sweaty already? All right. This is GT Interactive
Software Presents. This is Driver 1. This is a very important one. Is it going to be too loud?
I got memory cards. I was prepared for this, except for the fact that I had to change my,
whatever. Why did you turn your head that many times? What are you looking for?
That was just to prove that this was a 3D game. Am I stealing this car?
Is this my car? You've got your parking space. I just imagine the person that ran that Twitter
is sprinting into this room. It's just like, oh, I'm not ready. I didn't know he was even
doing this today. Why is it so loud? Though he was stealing it. Who was that?
Have we been just driving around in a circle the whole time? Driver, you are the wheel man.
Going back to these old games and seeing these old cut scenes, it's crazy what's been able to
happen here. That reminded me of an old GTA machinima, right? Turn the graphics up.
Audio is behind. The game audio is behind now. Don't even get started on that. All right. So
what do I do? No, no, it's fine. It's fine. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's fine. Just stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop. Stop it. One guy. Okay. So what do I want to do? Undercover car chases,
training, cheats. What do I do? Training, right? Car park. Okay. So this is the tutorial.
Somebody said I would not finish this. They said you're never going to finish the tutorial.
I think it was like a guarantee you won't beat the first level in Lord of the Rings, right?
What is it trying to show me? Demonstration. Oh, I have to do all those things. Okay.
Will you beat the tutorial in 30 minutes? What? You will not beat this.
Do a lap. It's no, it's not analog. What? Oh, it's not. Okay. It's not an analog game, right?
All right. Let's go. Show us what you got. All right. Did it burn out? So what's handbrake?
Oh, this way. This is reverse. Go away. I gotta go fast. What's brake? Okay. Handbrake is what?
I think it's L1. Ooh, I got it. 360. Oh, you can only do it four times before it's over.
All right. Hold on. Okay. Here we go. What's brake? Okay. Give me the controls.
Whoa. I just did it. Okay. Hold on. Reverse 180. So like, is that, how is that not a reverse 180?
Reverse 180. It's way, you're doing way to go faster. Who the fuck is this other person up here?
They're annoying me. I'm turning too slow. All right. What's handbrake L1? Wait, this is timed?
It's on a timer? No, it's not. Maybe I'll give you a call if I need a ride to the grocery store.
Oh, okay. I don't even understand it. Can I skip this? Okay. I have an idea. This is impossible.
What am I even? Lap? What do you mean do a lap? Watch the tutorial again. Okay. Hold on. I thought
it was just showing me the buttons. Let me watch it again. Do I even need to beat the tutorial?
Okay. Let's watch it. Let me try. Read the instructions. There are no instructions.
It's just like a hand cam of a streamer. That's way better than me. You didn't even get it. He's
not even unlocking anything. What? What the fuck? Okay. Here it comes to reverse. I did that. What
about speed? How fast can you go here? Okay. So he drives straight into the wall and lap is imagining
just a lap around the whole thing. Okay. All right. I get it. Let's go. Ready? Three, two,
one, go. I'll get the speed first. Lap. All right. Wait. What the fuck? Wait. Turn around.
That's not it? I have to weave through these, right? Why is it not doing the 180? No, I'll get
it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it.
I'll get it. I'll get it. Don't worry. I got it. I got it. Speed first. Okay. Now we're going to
do reverse. How is that too slow? How is it too slow? You're turning too early. I don't understand.
Just tap the handbrake. Handbrake. Handbrake. Dude, this, I don't, why can I not do a 180?
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Use the steering wheel. I'm doing, I'm using,
follow the ghost car. I thought you said that was my ghost car. Why would I follow this shitty
ghost car that I, it's not me. Wait, that's not me. I, oh, I thought that was me.
Like Mario Kart style. All right. Come on. Come on. I don't get the reverse 180. I can't do it.
I don't, I don't understand. I can't get it to work. How is that not a reverse 180?
I'm only doing this for five minutes. This is why everybody wanted me to play it. All right.
Play driver one. Don't tell them. Yeah. Cause this tutorial is stupid. Yeah. I remember reading
the reviews on this. Yeah. Like, I don't understand. Like I guess can't beat the tutorial. Like,
I don't know. What were they thinking? What were they thinking? You know what I mean? That's,
that's what I, that's where I am right now. I give up. I don't even care. I'm just gonna play
the game. I'm just, I think I'm just playing the game. You can't bail on the tutorial game
journalist. Don't, I'll get it right now. Five minutes. Ah, how was that not a reverse 180?
That's exactly what I just did. Escape sucks. I'm done. I'm not playing it anymore. It's, it,
it handles like a wet sock. Everybody was waiting for me to play this. You guys were all just like,
I can't wait. Here we go. Guaranteed fucking meltdown scream. No, it's not.
I'll give you a fucking meltdown right here. Get out of here. What do you got? Come on. Come on.
I'm not going to lose the tutorial and driver. Uh-uh. That should be about even 30 minutes.
How long does that take? How long does it take? That was less than 30 minutes. Who do you think
you are? Oh, who do you think you are? I am. All right. I did it. All right. Let's play driver one.
All right. So we got undercover new game. Truth is Tanner, three years on the department and you're
still the best driver I got. We don't get too many ex-racing boys in here. Lowlife rumble in Miami
is there's a hunt on for a guy who can pump the gas. Big getaway, big job, maybe even some kind
of hit. Some hood by the name of Rufus is in the picture. We need a line on it. Coffee? Yeah. Black,
right? Guys upstairs were asking for you in person. Look, we need you to go under, but no one's going
to know except me. If I bring anyone else in very wanted, by the way, why do they need your badge?
Any questions? Wait, I'm a police officer undercover. Remember this game is old. Yeah.
What is this? I just did this. I just did this. Why do I have to do this? I just did it.
Why do I have to do this again? What the fuck? No, I don't have to do this again. Do I? That was
the training. That was not the tutorial. Okay. Why did you let me do that? Why weren't you guys
screaming at the top of your lungs for me not to do training to get right into the new game?
Shit. Why am I doing this? I should have already did it. Why weren't you screaming at me?
We're going to do lap first. Give me that fucking 180. I didn't. Okay. The slalom slalom slalom.
Oh, fuck. No, you have to start with that. You have to start with slalom.
Do you have to start with that? There's no way you have to start with that. It's literally
impossible if you don't. I can't believe I'm doing this twice. I cannot fucking believe it. I can't
believe it. I forget how to start. I forget where you start it. You go like this way, right?
Do I start left or right? I already did it. I don't remember where to start
because you have to do the slalom fucking perfectly or it doesn't register. Oh my God. I
hate this game. How the fuck does that not count already? Now is that not a 180? What
fucking crack is this game smoking? How did I not just do the stupid giving up empty parking garage?
All right, let's go off with this. Turn faster.
Guys, it's a PlayStation one game. There's no pressure sensitive turning. It's either held
right or don't at all. How is that not a fucking 180? I just I'm doing a reverse 180.
What are you speaking of? What are you speaking of? How is that not a reverse 180?
What are you speaking of? We've got a job only you can handle. We need you to go on your cover and
go find those criminals. And by the way, can you slalom around these 10 times while I watch?
No, fuck you, buddy.
How do I burn out? How do I burn out? How do I burn out? How do I burn out?
How do I burn out? Tell me. Somebody tell me quick. How do I burn out? Quick.
Maybe I'll give you a call when I need a ride. How do I burn out? Circle. Oh my. You're a whiny
baby. It's a specific button to burn out. You tell me there's a burnout button on this fucking
computer video game. There's a circle is burnout. It's not handbrake and gas, right? It's not break
and get right. Like, okay. Okay. It's a button. Oh, I got it. Wait, save the game. I'm not doing
that ever again. I don't care. Just eat. Did I do it? All right. Thank God. Okay. Wait. Oh,
there it is. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Good. Very good. Very good. All right. We're good.
It's been 45 minutes. Well, technically it didn't start and it's been about 25 minutes. We're good.
We're ready. Why is it a different menu? Options? Get a new job. Why am I crawling around on the
floor? Okay. New job. You have one new message. Okay. We want to use you to be real sleepy.
You want it? Um, do I have to call them back? Oh, okay. Let's go. It's Charlie and Frank's
apartment from Always Sunny. It's bright. Bellany? Wait, why do I have one? We have one minute to
rob a bank. Why are we doing this in the amount of time it takes to watch a YouTube short? What's
fucking, what are we talking about? Where is it? One minute? Wait, up here? Is this a bank?
That's not a bank. What is the bank over here? Where is this bank? Bro, this is somebody's house.
Oh, there's like a big thing over here on the mini-map. Is it that way? Is it right there?
It's right there. Yeah! What? It's right, what? We're right here. What are you talking about?
What? Nice Target t-shirt. Wait, oh, you can, oh. Nope. I don't even know what the mini-map was
trying to tell me before. This is it. We're good. We're good. I got it. I thought there was a side
street I could cut through. I did the same exact thing. Move your fat head. I can't see.
My god, get out of the fucking way. What did I drive? Directly in, I was trying so desperately
to avoid that pole, and I drove directly into its square. Exactly, directly dead center of the car.
I was so obsessed with trying to avoid that. That's why I did what I just did.
Excuse me. Please don't fall off. All right, I got it. I'm right here. Too early? What do you
mean it's too early? What? Why are we picking up a Star Trek crew? Why did Captain Kirk just come
out? What was that? Where are we going? Where do we go? Fuck. Okay. Why is time going up? Wait,
am I gaining time or losing time? I'm so confused. What? Am I gaining time or was I, the time counted
down and then it was counting up? The game is so loud. Okay, this is a stopwatch. So I have to be
here within 10 seconds and then I have to, I thought I was up against the clock. I wasn't.
I kept looking up and seeing, oh, 20 seconds left, 30 seconds left, 40 seconds left. I was like,
how am I, am I running over little like watches or something? All right, I got it right now.
Wait, I took the wrong turn again. Okay, it doesn't matter because I have to be here within
10 seconds anyways. I'm here too early half the time. Nobody said it's still way too loud.
That was a 3D movie maker effect. Okay, here we are. Don't show up too early. Okay, now we go.
Pick everybody up. Here comes the whole, okay, now we get out of here. But I don't, I don't have to
freak out here. I want to go up this main highway. All right, let's go. There's way too many people
on the road here. Oh, what the fuck? Go, go, go, go, go, go. Okay. I think I was weaving around and
the police officer ran into somebody. No, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. Let's go.
Minute 45. What's wrong with that? This game is kind of fun. Oh, by the way, for those of you that
are wondering every 30 to 40 minutes, we switch games. It's been an hour and I haven't switched
too bad. And the intro was 20 minutes. That's true. We didn't really get into this until about
20 minutes ago. I still got about 20 minutes. There's so many games behind me. It is a daunting
amount of video games in CDs that are right here. I look back and it's like, oh my goodness. Okay,
we've got a lot to do. 20 plus 20 is 30. Well, 30 to 45 usually is the dealer. All right,
what about another job? Show them? No, I don't want to give any spoilers.
Who's censoring my calls for me? Was he doing that on his end?
Name's Deco. Which one should I do? That's it? He definitely left another message and just said,
it's me. Oh no, I skipped it. Which one should I do? The first one? All right, we'll do one more
and see how I feel. And then we're going to move on to this next one. Hide the evidence. Okay.
Take it to the breakers. New car. This car handles a lot differently. This dude is relentless. Get
away from me. Oh wait, his car got fucked up. All right, you can't hit anybody. Stop telling me to.
We're going to do this again. When is the driver? I know. What? I thought you said driver two.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay. I get it. Good. Stop. Who cares? Just go. Why do I care so much about
doing that? It's like just burning in the back of my head. Shit. What? There's a roadblock.
Okay. We're not going that way. We're going a different way. Where's the cop? Okay. Great.
And left and then right. I tried to hit every single object on the way over here. Okay.
Got no cops right now. That's good. I got to do the Mario Kart technique. How have you not
crashed already? Everybody does. If you do that in front of somebody, they freak out because they
don't want to hit you while they're passing you. And then you'll make them spin out. How have you
not crashed into somebody? Let's go. This place is far away. Oh, that jump did nothing for me at all
and ruined everything actually. I was supposed to go off that way faster. That was very lame.
I was supposed to go off that five times faster. That was lame. We're good. We're good. We're good.
We're good. One more. Blow right by this cop right here. 180. I love when cars harmonize in
video games, don't you? You know, like we're harmonizing. Stop. Stop it. Stop. Stop.
We're good. Nice. You should stick to TikTok. Dude, I've never opened the app TikTok once.
Whenever I tell you guys about watching TikTok, it's like going to TikTok.com and using getting
a link that somebody sent. I've never opened it. Or I look at TikTok compilation videos.
That's the same thing. Is it? I don't have like a TikTok account. Somebody's like, oh, look at this
TikTok video I found. I just opened it on like a website. I go, oh, that was okay. I don't care.
You're addicted. I don't watch TikTok. I don't. Stop it. That's worse. What do you mean? How is
that worse? All right. We'll do one more mission and then we'll move on. We want to talk to you.
We want to talk to you. That's it? The marino. Oh. We'll just hang loose till you get your ass
round here. Okay. Am I going to get double crossed? You need to do driver one all stream. No.
No, that's not happening. It's like, it's like 500 games behind me.
All right. I'm actually timed for this one. Go meet them. Is that, are they on the map right there?
Where is, where is, where are they? What am I? I don't know. Where am I supposed to be going?
Like over here? Hey, driver crawled so GTA could walk. Okay. All you haters in the chat right now.
What'd I do? GTA one came out probably like five years before this game. Do I have to bring the
cops? What did you say? Play it. Driver was made for aliens so they wouldn't get attached to earth.
What does that even mean? Where's this? Where's the road? So the frame rate drops to like zero
right there. Look at this. Why is it chugging so hard? Which road should I go on? This one or the
big one? All right. I just bounced. Oh, come on. Go, go, go, go, go, go, punch, punch, punch, punch.
This is so far away still. There's no way I do this one. One more try and that's it. That's it.
One last try and then I'm going to put in a different game. Final one last try. One try.
That was, that one didn't count. That one didn't count. Okay. Go. I'm going to, I'm not going to
go right. I'm going to go straight here. Right. And then go down this road up here.
This one right here. Yep. Yep. Okay. Go, go, go, go. Down this main highway right here.
Why was I speeding? Why am I in trouble? I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything.
Did I do it? Did I fuck it up? I went down the wrong thing, didn't I?
No, I'm okay. I'm all right. Can I go down this way? I can't tell from the map.
Dude, I can't, I can't tell from the map. Oh, come on. Doesn't it look like I can drive down there?
What even is that? I'm doing this one more time. I swear to God. You did the same mistake. All
right. I'm not making that mistake again. This is the last try and then I'm putting in a,
I'm putting in the land before time racing adventure. I'm not making that same mistake
every time. I'm going left. You're going to think it's crazy, but I'm doing it.
Now we're going to go right up here and then I'm going to go straight and then we're going to go
right up here and straight. Go. Just stay straight the whole time. There we go. Okay. We're good.
All right. There's a roadblock up here. I feel through very slowly.
That fucking idiot wasn't in the way. This is fine. All right. I think he crashed.
Where's the entrance? Where's the entrance? Isn't there a bigger entrance?
What? I thought there was a, I thought there was a bigger entrance. I went way too far. All right.
This is it right here. If I don't get it right here, I'm literally turning off the console and
pulling up this. Sorry. Where's the road I can go down? Is it this one here? I don't know. The
big shadow is taking up the whole mini map. I don't, I can't see. Why are my eyes so watery?
No, no, no. It was the wrong road. Oh my God. It's the wrong fucking road.
There's one road to get over there. There's one road and it's check it out. This is it right here.
I swear to God. I swear to God. This is it. I got it right here. I got it. It was a perfect,
there was no avoiding that car crash. They were coming from every piece,
every angle. There was no escaping. Everyone was driving to stop me from completing this mission.
Stop driving into me. All right. Here it is. This one right here. Go.
Making good time. Good time. Nope. It's not the wrong road. Look,
I was up to the one to the right, the road to the right. That's when I was up before.
I'm on the right one. There's a block here. Save. Stop talking. I got it for sure. Yes.
Need you to make an exchange. This case for a locker key. It's a sweet deal.
Cash for a key in and out. Wham, bam, boom. Meet them at the marina. Get the key or stay out of town.
This message is crazy. I just slammed my head so hard against the top of my door frame, putting up
lights. And all I could hear was the obscenely loud sirens playing from the game on my laptop.
For a second, I truly believed I fucking died to a germistream. Oh no. You all right?
Wait, what's this? All right, we're doing it. Last one, I promise. The last thing you hear
is like, I don't understand. I don't get it. No, I hit the brake button. I hit the brake button.
I hit the brake. Whoa, that's a weird thing. I don't know about that one. That's terrifying.
Go over the jump. I'm so angry at myself for missing that. Very annoyed at myself. I think
I got it. I'm almost there. I'm almost there. That was driver one and it was a good one.
We played that for a little while. It was fun. Worth the wait, I think. But coming up next,
we've got the land before time racing adventure. This is going to be crazy, I think. This is going
to be crazy. Oops. Wait, what? Oh, wait, I want to do this. No, I got it. Why did that just happen?
All right. Finally, it's time for a real game. I mean, driver one is a very popular real game.
Here we go. Yeah, for the game that I'm playing. Yeah, just leave it as retro. There's no reason
to change it. They'll be cycling so much. It's not worth it. All right, here we go. Land before time.
Yeah, I'm on a PS2 right now. PlayStation 2 and PlayStation 1. You have a PS2. At least the slim
model. I don't know. At least the slim model, whatever that means. Is that the one that's
backwards compatible? Because if you have a PS2 slim, you can play PS1 games in it.
Are they all backwards compatible? Okay.
That was wild. Okay. If you gave me a million dollars, I wouldn't be able to name one character.
This is infomercial music when they're showing off the grill. And introducing the new wave oven.
Cook. Clean. Store. You need at least one free block in the memory card in slot one. Okay.
Reading memory card. Land before time. Great balancing adventure. What do I do? Obstacle
courses. Pick an obstacle course. Free star dash. Rolling hills dash. Dino dash. Stone den dash.
Right. Ducky. How about either Ducky or Spike? All right, here we go. We're just going. Holy
shit. This game is awesome. This is like the iPhone run games before they were popular.
Oops. Oh, I didn't jump. Okay. I'm good. Sorry. Oh my God. Whoa. You can. Okay. You can swim on
that. What's the time I need to beat? There we go. Ooh. Got it. I think you go faster if you collect
flowers. I don't know how you do that reliably. I don't understand. Not bad. That wasn't that bad.
This looks like you if you were nice. Oh, I didn't do it. I think I could do. All right. What about
this one? What Dino dash? Let's try this one. We'll do Ducky. Maybe they all have different traits.
140 is what I need. Okay. Well, now I understand what kind of game it is. I didn't know what it
was before. It's like an auto run game. I don't know. I jumped over it. I think you have to go
through the middle of those. Yeah. You can't jump over those. I got it. All right. 140. There's more.
I'm so sorry. I love that harsh audio clipping that you hear. It's like reading memory card. You
hear that just noise. Oh, okay. I got my unlocked more. All right. Let me get this one then. We'll
do Sarah. After this, we'll do a race. Can you please drink from a hamster water bottle? No.
We already went over why that stream would be bad. Why? Because it would be stupid.
Anytime I ever think of something that we fund or interesting to do on stream for like a show or an
event, I think about the one thing I think is funny. And then I go, all right, can it be built
off of that one thing I think is funny? And yeah, me drinking out of a hamster bottle is funny.
But then imagine the panic I would have to have to fill like three or four hours of a stream
doing what exactly that's like, I would be in like a hamster costume. I would do the funny. Look,
I'm drinking out of the thing. And then I'd have a panic attack internally going. What else does
there do now? Oh my God, this how much does this cost? I would just be like, there's nothing else
to do. There's nothing else funny. What else is funny that could happen right now? This is bullshit.
Just walk across it, babe. It would be a one minute stream. It would just be you running in
the hamster. I would sprint on that hamster wheel and I would trip and I would go. I would fall and
just kind of be spinning in it. I would just puke. And then the stream would have to turn off and I'd
get banned for a week. What a fucking terrible stream. All right. How about a windy ridge race?
Ducky hamster wheel subathon. Oh, no way. Oh my God. I was trying to cut the corner. Get it.
Why do I? Why is this? Why can I? What song is this?
What song is this? What is that? This is a real song. Turn around.
Turn around. Yeah, that's what it is. Okay. Turn around every now and again. I get a little bit
closer. Turn around. No, it's different now. Play that song. Hold on. He's going to pass me.
He's going to lap me. Turn around every now and then I get a little bit closer.
Turn around every now and then I get a little bit more. Is this it?
That's the joke version? What? What do you mean joke version?
Why did you link me the joke version? There's a parody version of this song. I linked both.
Yeah, the first one doesn't work. It says video content unavailable. It's been blocked by display
on this website. Turn around every now and then I get a little. Just click the link itself. What?
Is this it? I can't hear it. Yes. When does it say turn around?
I feel like I feel like there hasn't even been any singing yet.
It just happened. They're doing it now. Oh, I can't hear it. It's been said three times now.
All right. Well, whatever. I can't hear it. My headphones are not plugged into my computer.
They're plugged into the game. All right. Well, I fucking lost. Who cares? Like,
I'm not going to finish it out. All right. One more. That entire song is him saying,
turn around a billion times. All right. Let's go. All right. One more. I'm going to win.
Why are you taking the lead? I did everything perfectly. No, I did everything perfectly.
It makes no sense. Why are you so fast? What is happening? He's blown by me completely.
There's a sprint button. There is now that I know that I'll try it again. You suck. I didn't even
know what the buttons were. OK, 30 minutes. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good.
Read the manual. There is no manual. Let's go. You stupid. Oh, my God. One little mistake and
he's so far ahead already. How have I not gotten any ground on it? I have to beat this motherfucker
so bad. I have to beat this guy. I have to beat him. I have to beat this. I have to beat him.
I can't move on until I beat him. I'm curious. You look different. Have you had plastic surgery?
I've not had plastic surgery. No, I've just aged like 12 years. No, I haven't. I haven't gotten
plastic surgery. Why are you asking that? You took that. I needed it. All right. Stop. He's so far
ahead already. He didn't even collect any of the flowers. This is horseshit. Oh, my God. I can do
it. I can do it. I'm going to quiet down. Quiet. We're at a joint. It's been flipping hamburgers
since 1910. This is Guy Fury music. You know, I come here for the atmosphere. It's always fresh,
always awesome. Great atmosphere back in the kitchen. Like, I quit. I quit. I need to restart
it. Craggy cave. I can do it. You got plastic surgery. I'm not going to get plastic surgery.
I'm not going to get plastic. The only time I've ever thought about getting plastic surgery
is like maybe fixing my turkey neck eventually. But I don't know. I don't think I'm going to do
that. I don't have a reason to. Oh, you just got destroyed. Why are you so much faster? Stop.
I quit. One more time. If you played this music in a room with two people, they would kill each
other. Why? No, I wouldn't. I actually wouldn't do that. I would go, this music's kind of weird.
Yeah, I'd like to leave the room now. Who cares?
This game is fucking impossible. I would have cried if I was a kid playing this.
I would have cried playing this. Don't pick that up. I want that. How are you right up my ass
already? How are you this close to me still? Don't lose right now because the music is so funny.
Go. He's right there. Please die. No, no, I didn't. I didn't say die. I said doi.
I said doi. Don't touch that. It's mine. Got it. Yes. Oh, thank God. Thank God. I don't have to do
it again. Thank goodness. That was fun game. How you guys feel? One more. All right. What do we
got next? Oh, this one's going to be, I feel like I'm going to be in this one for a long time.
Do I pull that out now? Okay. I'm going to give you guys a choice. We might be in this one for
a little while. Would you rather see mods make a poll? Oh, okay. The options are
Hey guys. Damn. Countdown. Countdown vampires or the golden nugget video game. It's a casino game.
And there's apparently 30 minutes of live action. Adam West video. I don't know what that means. I
just know that it's in the game. I don't know what that means. I mean, we're going to play in
both, but which one do you want first? I don't think it's even close. Golden nugget casino game
or countdown vampires. All right. It's not even remotely close. That was fun. That was actually
really cute. It was land before time adventure racing. I think this is two discs. Yeah. Two
discs. I'm going to have to put discs in to load up cut scenes. I bet it's going to be a disaster.
Let's try. Here comes the golden nugget video game. 81%. Oh my God. That's a lot. That's actually an
unbelievable number. Okay. Let's go. No casino game will ever be like Vegas steaks. Sure about
that. Okay. Is that me in the limo? Going to Las Vegas. The window going to roll down. Is it
going to be Adam West? Pull it up to the golden nugget. Is it one person? Okay. Let's go. It looks
like chocolate. Start or options? I mean, what could the options be? Background, sound effects,
computer players on card animation. I guess we're just keeping it the way it is. Okay. Let's go.
Let's do it. Welcome to the fabulous golden nugget. Visit the registration desk. Do I have to? Oh,
no. If you haven't saved your game yet, your current game will be lost. Steve. What's my name?
Steve Killsberg. Steve Killsberg. Killsberg. What do? Okay. I need a new name. How much money do I
have? Where's my money? What is that thing? What is it? What did I just click on? Oh shit. Maximum
bit of thousand. How much money do I have? 50, 20, 10. I have like 200 bucks. How much money do I
have? Go forward. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. You know, all right. Blackjack. Let's start with Blackjack.
Go all in. Okay. I'll go all in on the first hand. I don't even know what, do I have to put a dollar
up? Okay. How much did I just bet? Stand. Did I say that? What do I have here? 13 is four. Stand.
All right. How much money did I just bet? How much money am I betting? Oh shit. There we go. Okay.
Nine versus king. Oh, hit. I'm busted. Sorry. Sorry to hear that. I'll take a card. That's not good.
Stand. All right. Hey, look at that. Is that 500? What just happened? Wait, what's going on here?
What just happened? What's going on? What's happening? Oh shit. That was 500. All right.
I got it. I got it. All right. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. All right. Jack. Oh, 13 versus an eight.
16 versus eight. I have to take another card. 22. Hit. Hit me. I'm busted. All right. That's all
right. Sorry. I lose anyways. I would have lost anyways. All right. One more. How much money do I
have? All right. I have to stop after this. Let's see an ace right there. Perfect. Perfect. Blackjack.
Nice. What? Oh, that's fucking stupid. I have no money left. It's over.
Let's not stand. We're in. Stand. 15. There it is. We're back. How to pronounce stand in English.
Stand. Why do I have zero dollars? Okay. And here's the question. Stand. Yes.
Stand. Is that I win, right? Did I win? What is that? How much did I win? Seven. 14.
You fucking piece of shit game. What? A 21 again? What happens if I have no money? Oh, I have
special. I have markers. Okay. All right. Cool. That bet is over the table maximum.
I guess I'll do 5,000 then. I only won twice. Whatever. It's okay. It's all right. It's all
right. What do we got here? Roulette. Slots. All right. Slots. We'll just do slots. We'll do
slots. We'll go to Eureka. Where is Adam West? I don't know. It says this is like an hour of
footage. All right. This is one dollar. Okay. How do I, how do I, I don't want to bet $5,000.
How do I get rid of that? How do I do this? I can't click spin. I can't click bet.
I can't hit. Oh, okay. Well, there we go. All right. Five, 10, 15, 20, 25, 30, 35. Oh.
How much money am I putting in? Okay. Let's do a hundred. I hope Adam West like bumps into me.
It just dumps a drink on me or something. Okay. So that's about $500. Why are there dynamite?
Why is it spinning again? Why is it doing this? What's happening? Why is it doing this? I'm not
doing this. What's going on? Why is it doing this? I have a hundred credits still. Why? I didn't say
I'm spending money. That was one spin. I'm so confused. I don't know what just happened.
All right. Come on. Come on. Was that food and scrambled eggs? Gold, gold. Oh, five. I'll take
it. Three. Oh, that's when we leave. All right. Take it out. 6,125. Let's go. All right. Nice. Okay.
That's good. Look at that. I have one hundred. That's it. I feel like I've spent a lot. Play
story mode. Isn't, am I not doing story mode? This is story mode. How do I do story mode? I think,
I think we're okay. That's one guy. All right. How about, how about roulette? Where's roulette?
Right here. You didn't tweet your stream on. Oh, shit. Sorry. Okay. Let me show you my roulette
strategy. I don't want that much. How do I get rid of that? All right. So was it, I'm doing a hundred,
I'm doing two hundred bucks. Not this much, but you know what I mean. Two hundred dollars is going
where I would do in a corner bet right here. But this is four hundred bucks, right? So I need 11,
12, 14, 15, 17, 18. Let's go. All right. Let's do it. I'm ready. Spin it. All right. Go. Okay.
I came to see what it is. Eleven. How much is that? How much did I just win? That was
two hundred. That's two hundred times. That's a lot. That's two hundred, eight, four to one,
eight to one. Look at that. That bet is over the table. Oh, you don't know who I am. All right.
A thousand on red. Go. Where's Adam West? He's going to show up. You need to do story mode.
Story mode is the other disc. Winner. What? Golden Nugget features a mystery themed story mode.
What? This is disc one. Wait, are you serious? How do I do that? I want to do that right now.
There's another disc here. I want to play the mystery mode. Start a new file and select mystery
mode. You didn't even say that. There's a murder mystery or something. I need to do it. We have
that. We have to do this. Where's the lobby? No, I don't want to play crap. PlayStation version
was released on two separate discs with one containing the game story mode. So maybe maybe
that's accurate. Maybe it is on the other disc. OK, let's try that. Registration new. Let's see
if it does it here. Did you get a coupon in here? I don't think so. New. Oh, cause chaos
mystery. Chaos mystery mode. Are you kidding me? This is chaos mode. Let's go. This is it.
Chaos theory and you.
We see the formation of a cloud, the clustering of stars. Mountains aren't cones.
Clouds aren't spheres. The world is made of zigs and zags, random,
radical yet deep inside the chaos looks an even eerier order. And the key to this world exists.
Now the chaos chip, the chaos chip proper interface. This new microprocessor will
compute outcomes using data compiled sheerly from nature's weather patterns, life expectancy.
What role of a die turn? We could just play cards to, you know, what happened?
Well, at best guess, I'd say this computer your company makes has a bit of a bad motivator.
No big words, but they'll fund you. I'm sure they will after the card tricks.
He exposed tomorrow. It's not like I have time to predict the presidential election.
Maybe try walking on hot coals. That was last year. Not gonna answer the door. Somebody's
at the door, sweetie. Can I see any few? You expecting company? I haven't spoken to Steven
in six years. I had no idea he was going to be here at the same time.
You know, that's him at your little poker rondeley tomorrow. Won't you?
It's an invitational. First off, chaos indeed. Chaos. What is up? Oh, Dr. Harkness, I presume
shock or quick movements, please. Just the chip now. Chip the chaos one, the one you designed its
location. Who are you? Call me Shirako, but quietly. We don't want to wake the neighbors. Get it. I
actually don't. Get him to him. Where is it? I thought I hit her right in the head. I thought
I hit her directly in the head. It was like, holy shit. What is this? This is just a spray painted
shoe box. He's gone. So where is the mystery chip? I have a theory. I'll tell you in a minute. Steven,
it's me. Look, don't say anything. I know that it's been forever and we didn't part on the
greatest of terms, but I need your help. I'm in a real mess. I'm here to write the golden nugget.
I hope your poker skills are intact. Just listen, I don't have much time. Someone stole something
very important from my hotel room. It's a microchip. It's a processor that.
Trust me. I puke up cards. Am I like a monster like person? Why am I puke? Why am I throwing
a card? They left something behind in my hotel room. It's a registration form for the poker
tournament. So writing on the back, I can't quite make out. Anyway, whoever it is might still play.
And if you could just, I don't know. Don't leave it there. Ben's around here somewhere.
Maybe you could find my friend, Melanie. Why can't you just give it to me? Sorry, I'm still so high
maintenance, Stevie. I'll talk to you when I can. Okay. Sexy scientist super invention stolen. But
wait, wait, wait, you will need to have $20,000 to enter the poker team. Why does that headline
have to say sexy? That's bizarre. What the fuck is the point of that? Okay. I have a theory.
The theory that I have is that the golden nugget, I mean, these casinos rake in billions.
And I'm imagining that they probably had a hundred million dollar budget for this game.
And the developers and coders were like, okay, we made Blackjack, we made Keno, and we did poker,
or we're done. What do you mean you're done? Yeah, we're done. We finished the game. It's just like
Blackjack and shit. There's like a million of these apps. There are 100 million of these on the app
store on disk. There's so many of them. Oh, well, just take the other 98 million and make a movie
with Adam West. Why? That sounds like a bad idea. Just do it. Do it. Just spend the other like 75
million. It's just that. All right. I'm in. I'm in long term, by the way. I need $20,000.
Got to make this happen. The apps are in the nineties. All right. We got to get to 20K. How
much do I have right now? I have 10,000. We need to go register. I need to save the game. All right.
Save it right there. I'm ready. SpongeBob music. Go 10K. Put it all on black. All right. Let's see
if I can do it. No, no, no, no, no, no. Let me go to Blackjack. Come on. All right.
I know I don't want to do a $5 bet. No, I want to do more than that. Hit stand.
Not up. Hey, we're good. Hit me. Hit. I'm busted. I would have won that too.
I actually annoying. All right. How about 2252? How about 500 per hand? You guys are okay with
that? 500 per hand. I lost 500. That's, that's a terrible start. Stand versus four. Stand. Stand.
17 versus the king. I hate this. I don't want to. I don't, I hate hitting this. I don't want to hit
this. Stand on 13 versus four. Yeah. Sometimes I have to do it. 21. Oh my God. Hit me. I'm busted.
We're good. What is making that sound? You hear that? Okay. We got to go for it.
Thousand. Can we, this person gets Blackjack. Hit. Can we switch seats? Stand. Shit. A 16.
You're over Blackjack. Hit me. 15 versus nine. This sucks. You're over. Fuck you. Come on. Stand.
12 versus six. No. Stand. See. We're good. All right. We're coming back. We're coming back.
There it is. Hit. Hit me. Hit me. I'm busted. Dude, what are you doing? Hit me. Stand.
Let's take a Blackjack. All right. We're up. We're up. 500.
Okay. We're on a streak. Let's go. Can I split? Stand. Can I split? Do you wish to split?
Against a nine. That's a terrible idea. Should I do it? Or split? Split eights every time. No. No.
No. It's terrible. It's horrible. It's a terrible idea. Versus a nine. You're trying to lose twice?
Always split. Are you trying to lose twice? Always split eights. You're trying to lose twice?
That's fucking awful. Hit it again. No. Hit me. I'm busted. Hey, guy. Hey, you know what I say.
Always split eights. Always split eights. See, that's what I say. All right. One more and I'm out.
Stand. Get out of here. Hit me. Stand. Oh, sorry. Somebody busted. And that's now I'm at.
I'm getting close to 13K. 13K. I want to. Should I stay? It's a hot table. Hit. Stand. It's versus
seven, but I'm going for the double. Let's go. This is double down right here. 11. Let's go.
Give me a 10. Stand. Yes. I had to count for a second. There it is. Come on. 15. We're almost
there. You're addicted. I'm not addicted. I'm playing the story mode. I have to figure out
what the chaos chip is and I need 20,000 for it. Stand. Good. Hit. Stand. Yes. All right. I have
to be close. I'm at 16. I'm getting up. I'm getting up. That's a $6,500 profit right now.
All right. Now don't lose it. Roulette. No, maybe sit down and back her up. You need to be a VIP
club member before you can visit a high limit area. You have at least $50,000. What? No,
maybe play back her up. Go save it. How do you even play Kino? I don't know how you play.
Big six. Save the game. I will after this. What is this? How do you play big six? Put it on 10?
No more bets. What is this? Oh, it's the big, it's the scam wheel.
Yeah, that's the worst thing to play in the whole casino. All right. I need to go to the lobby. I
got to save it. We're so close. Where's the lobby? All right. Save the game. We're good. 15, nine.
Okay. I need 20 K and then after 20, yeah, you need 20 K to enter the first poker tournament.
I don't, I don't, I'm not good at poker. I like to play it sometimes.
Dude, this game came out on the app store and I'm not even kidding. It's so awesome.
Uh, what's it called? I'm, I'm seriously go get it right now. If you think like
poker is fun, it's a poker slash Yahtzee combo. It's Yahtzee, but poker and you deal your own
hands and you got to make this the it's like Yahtzee. It's really cool. It's what is it called?
What's it called? It's called, um, what's it called? It's what is it called? It's called, um,
no, it literally just came out like the other day. What's it called? Um,
poker. It's called something. It's got a name. It's like a pit or something like something pit.
It's called, what's it called? Oh, I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it right now. I'll get it
right now. What's it called? It's called something. I got it. I got it. The game is called. I got it.
It's called where it's under new games. Hold on. Oh, Holly. Holly. Yeah. Holly. Oh, what is it?
Yeah. Pizza. What the fuck? Hold on. I'm just going to yell the number. I'm going to mute.
I'm going to yell the number. Can you hear me? My, I think my iPad might be in the. All right.
What's the name of the game? What's it called? You can't close. Okay. It's called
pine tar is the name of the game. Pine tar. It's fucking awesome. The name of the game is pine
tar. It's sick. Oh, pine tar. And the game is phenomenal by the way. You're sick. Oh, stop it.
Okay. Let's go. Wait, where am I? All right. Pine tar. The game's like three or four bucks.
It's addicting. It's fun. It's just like a solo, just poker game. You play with your,
you play with yourself and it's like Yahtzee. It's like four bucks. That's it. All right. Let's go.
Roulette. The audio is fucked up. Spell it like pine tar. P I N E space T A R pine tar.
All right. We're going to go, uh, here's the strategy. We're going 500, 500. What do you think?
I think I'm going like in here, 20, like in here and then right here, thousand bucks, 22,
three, 25 right in this area here. Eight to one, by the way, if you hit any of these.
No more bets, please. What is it? Winner. Yes. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. I'm almost there.
That's eight to one. I only need to win one more time. I'm going to do 500 on black.
I just need 500 and like 25 on black. This is it. Go. That was a huge win by the way.
No more bets, please. Pine tar is just poker. It's poker and Yahtzee combined.
You didn't even download it. You didn't even download it. Nine red shit. All right. Come on.
These are easy bets. No more bets, please. Thousand on black. Come on. It's not a scam.
No, the game's actually fucking relaxing and awesome. Did I win? Yes. Winner. 20 black. Okay.
What do I need now? All right. I just need a hundred bucks. A hundred on. We'll go red.
100 on red before. No more bets, please. You're one of those four reviews. If you just played it,
you would enjoy it. 29 black. Red. No more bets, please. 13 black. No more bets, please. Red.
What the fuck? Black again. 28 black. Red. No more bets, please. Red. Let's go. Winner. 23
red. All right. I have. You've made it into the first poker tournament. There's no time to waste.
So hurry to the poker suite before they start without you. Let's go. Welcome Mr. Kills Bird.
I'm glad you could make it. My dear sir, there simply are no vacancies. I find no record of
your reservation whatsoever. Look, I'll pay you anything reasonable. Come on. What do you say?
Is this the poker room? Look, may as well let the white shirt in. Do Shelley's late anyway.
Give him Henry's spot. Too late. It's already mine. If I may be of assistance,
Mr. Swain. Mr. Farland may have my seat for the first just. It seems I have business elsewhere.
There you go. Well, well. Who are we? Kills Bird. Shelley's told me so much about you. My name's
Swain, but anybody who knows me from Adam calls me Hugh. I gathered from your body language that
you're a left-handed card player. A little disconcerting since I see that you've neglected
the laces on your right shoe. A stress level that could only be related to the jitters before
a high stakes game of chance or to the comments I overheard this morning from a young woman
at the pay phones downstairs since she called her speaker, Stevie. This is fucking awesome.
It can only be assumed that you're he and here for her. Or one of us has become vaguely confused.
Though my suspicions perhaps sound deranged to the common ear, I think there's more to this
friendly game of chance than meets the eye. You keep that eye on your opponents. Mr. Garth's not
lit. I'll be in touch. It's your turn at that. Mr. Mr. Slane, I'm just the pizza guy.
Can you sign for this or? I don't know what you're talking about.
Gentlemen, ladies, welcome to the Golden Nugget and this year's preliminary poker
invitational. Beginning on my right, please state the names by which you wish to be known.
I'm Joanna Kurtz. Hello, everyone. Ben Farland. Great to be surrounded by all of you,
especially the famous Mr. Kilzberg, who needs no introduction. You're a weird guy. Mr. Farland,
Mr. Kilzberg, welcome. Wait, we can't introduce ourselves? Short for Tracy.
Serako, if anything. Sheila Warwick. Call me whatever you like, within reason. Thank you all.
Let's get started. All right, here we go. I can't fuck this up. This is a big poker tournament.
Oh, this is not high. What? Oh, everybody, it's time for the billionaires to play with $25 a hand.
What the fuck is this? How do you play poker? What kind of poker is this? I don't know what
we're playing. What kind of poker is this? What's that mean? I raise. I don't know what's going on.
I call. I'm out. I don't know what's happening. You may vote, call or raise. I got queen high.
What kind of poker is this? Is it Texas Hold'em? Five card draw?
Because I mean queen high, that's pretty good, right? I will raise. I call. I'm out. I call.
I call. I call. Can we see other cards? Okay, so now what? I check. You may check or bet. I
don't know what that means. This is a pretty good hand. It's a pretty good hand. It's five
card stud. Okay. I got queen ten suited. Pretty good. Check. I bet. I call. I call. I call. I raise.
You may vote, call or raise. I call. I call. I call. I call. You got a pair of sevens?
It has nothing to do with my fucking royal flush. You may vote, call or raise. I need a queen under
there. I need a queen under here, right? I raise. I raise. I call. I call. You may vote,
call or raise. I call. I'm gonna have a queen under here. Whip him. Whip him. You may vote,
call or raise. Why so many cards? One, two, three, four, five. I have six cards now.
Is it seven card stud? Uh oh. I raise. I think I got a queen under there. I call. I call. You may
vote, call or raise. I call. I've got a queen. Flip that queen. I'm gonna flip a queen. Watch this.
Flipping a queen. Boom. You may vote, call or raise. I raise. I raise. I call. I call. You may vote,
call or raise. I call. Flipping a queen. I win. I'm getting too close to this guy's cards.
What are my cards? Where are my cards? I don't get to show my cards? Where are they?
You had nothing. You ate them. You dropped your hand on the ground.
Deal. I guess I lost but I didn't even see what I had for a hand. Okay. I'm out. Already?
I raise. I'm out. Why? You can't even see what you have. You have a queen high. I'm out. What are
they doing? You may vote, call or raise. It's just me and the guy with the king. Let's go. Raise. I call.
I call. I call. Give me a jack. Oh. I check. Okay. I check. Not bad. You may check or bet.
Let's check. I check. All right. Now we raise. Now we raise. I raise. Come on. I raise. You got it.
I call. You may vote, call or raise. I call. All I care about is the two queens. I raise. I raise.
I call. You may vote, call or raise. I call. All right. Is that? You may check or bet.
I raise. I raise. I call. You may vote, call or raise. I call. I call. I call. We got...
What do I have? Two queens. I'm out. You fucking have aces under there. What? I want to go see
Adam West again. I call. I'm out. I call. You may vote, call or raise. I mean everybody kind of
has a shitty hand so I might as well. I call. I'm out. I call. I call. I check. I check. You would.
You may check or bet. The hearts. I check. I can't believe we're doing $25 hand. You may vote,
call or raise. This is awful. What? I mean five, six, seven. I could. I raise. You could get a
straight call. I call. You may vote, call or raise. I call. You may vote, call or raise.
God, look at this bullshit. You sure you can't look at the flipped cards?
I don't think so. I think that's how this works. I call. I call. I'm out. You may vote, call or
raise. I raise. I call. I call. I raise. I call. You may vote, call or raise. I call. I raise every
time. I call. I call. I call. I call. Eventually. Will I liquidate myself? Ooh. I check. All right.
I check. We got Queen Jack. I check. Not suited. I check. It's all right. You may check or bet.
I call. I raise. I raise. I call. I call. You may vote, call or raise. I call. I call.
Look, it's kind of quiet. Look over, like Adam West just sleeping on that couch.
Yeah, he had all that shit to say and he's kind of taking a nap. I raise. I raise. You may vote,
call or raise. Well, the King Queen Jack, that's, I can't beat that. What the fuck is that? I call.
I call. I call. I call. I call. How long do you sit here for to do this? I raise. I raise. I call.
I call. I have Jack, Queen, 10. Is that a 9? Dude, I'm close. Is that a 6? No, it's a, wait, shit.
Is that a 9 or is it a 6? I call. I call. I call. I call. I call. Let's go. Come on. Let me,
let me get this big pot here to nine, nine, 10, come on. Give me straight. I raise. I raise. I call.
I call. I call. You have one pair. You may vote, call, or raise. I call. I call. I call. I call.
This is a big pot. Give it to me.
Give me the straight.
Do it. Come on.
I'm out.
Five, six, what is it?
I'm out. What do I have?
I'm out.
Did I win?
Ladies and gentlemen, we will now take a brief intermission.
Excuse me.
It would seem the waters run deeper than I feared.
Perhaps I should elaborate in our last conversation.
No doubt you found it
Puzzling.
You see, I was unwinding at the tables earlier.
His cigar is bigger.
His cigar grows when he tells a lie.
As always, when in a large room
filled with a symphony of hundreds of people
engaged in hypnotic entertainment,
I found myself lip reading.
Immediately I recognized
the renowned chaos theorist
from today's front page.
Yet though wracked with guilt
for my invasion of her privacy,
I soon noticed I wasn't the only one
paying attention to a beautiful celebrity
on the verge of collapse.
Ed, Edd and Eddie?
It's Ed, Edd and Eddie music.
Until that moment,
my main reason for visiting the Golden Nugget
had been the hope of winning enough to...
Well, let's just say I drive a guzzler
and have a charming collection of pads.
But suddenly I knew a storm was gathering
and this scrap of paper
began to look like the
only umbrella
of the entire western state
since we last spoke.
I examined this
telltale tatter using
what few items in my crime lab
I had time to pack in my duct tape.
Although encrypted
in pig latin,
I deciphered this curious phrase
written on the back in fresh black ink.
Why was six
afraid of seven?
Signed, bullets over kings.
He's making stuff.
I'll run this through the computer, you keep an eye out here.
The fiend who taunts us with these
dastardly rib ticklers.
This guy's a weirdo.
That's a CVS receipt for one coconut water.
Keep them clueless, casually.
No, save your questions
till later. I'm in motion.
Can we get you anything,
Mr. Kilzberg?
Yes. I would like.
Wasn't Mr. Swain with you
a moment ago?
No, no, it was a different guy.
That was a different guy.
Alright, here we go. I gotta keep this going.
I gotta keep it going. I can't just go to zero.
We gotta see how this plays out.
You may vote, call, or raise.
Hmm.
Yeah, two jacks, two eights, two pair, no way.
I would've lost.
Resident sleeper gameplay.
Get back to the cut scene.
I raise. I call.
Everybody's got good shit to start.
I call.
I'm out.
Ask for the beer plus milk.
I call.
It's been six hours. It hadn't even been three.
Alright.
I check.
You may check or bet.
Uh, whatever.
I call.
I raise.
Just watch the cut scenes on YouTube.
No, I need to earn it.
I call.
That's not bad.
You may vote, call, or raise.
I call.
Please, we want to see Spyro.
What makes you think I have Spyro here right now?
I don't have Spyro.
I raise.
You may vote, call, or raise.
I call.
I think I played Spyro already.
A long time ago.
I raise.
You may vote, call, or raise.
I call.
Just cancel the stream. There's no Spyro.
Alright, flip it.
I'm out.
You better play Bionicle.
We're not in a rush.
You may vote, call, or raise.
I call.
I'm out.
I raise.
I call.
I got surgery in an hour, dude.
Are you talking from the hospital bed?
What do you mean?
I have knee surgery in an hour, dude.
Go get prepped for surgery.
What are you doing here?
What are you talking about?
Are you lying down in the hospital bed?
That's a great hand, by the way.
I raise.
I call.
You may vote, call, or raise.
He is the surgeon.
I raise.
You may vote, call, or raise.
I call.
He's postponing the surgery.
I check.
Ace, jack, queen, king.
I raise.
Call, or raise.
I call.
I raise.
You may vote, call, or raise.
I call.
I'm out.
I'm not leaving till I win another hand. You show the lowest card and must anti what I call
I call I call I call I raise I'm out
You may fold call or raise shit fold that guy's an ace. I have a four. It sucks
Ladies and gentlemen, we will now take a brief intermission
Player you know that I lost every hand. I guess you recognize me Max Chilton my father
He's in town to unveil his new Adam's smash for tomorrow's expo
Personally, I've never understood any of the stuff his company makes
Ram wrong
It's all geek to me. So he gave me a little pocket change
And
Two people
Steven Killsburg
Two L's B. Oh you are G. Am I right? Correct. I'm Joanna
I crunch numbers for Henry was not your chips. Did you those are not your chips one of the smaller ones
They only make the little stuff like weather satellites
That
Girl's father used to work for me
But the cool thing about the backstab is you only need that one good
You didn't save her spot and it's open and now Max Chilton owns my old company and I'm Girl Friday for an obnoxious
tycoon
I'll tell you one
When I've won enough to get my new company off the ground
Daddy bucks Chilton is gonna learn. I would
Like any of this
Deserves a nut I
Would just stay home and just like watch TV
You know what I mean?
Like my company was purchased by this firm and then I need to go like I'm just gonna go I'm staying home
I don't want to deal with like all like the rich people shit
You know what I mean?
Like I don't I would never want to be in this room people just like striding in sitting down looking you right in the eye
So what's your story? What company did you buy? And it's like I don't fucking want to be here
I don't want to be here. I want to just like get high and watch TV on my couch
I'm never gonna I would never be there
I don't want to I don't want to have said somebody sit down and like look at me like that and talk to me like
That I don't know. I just would never want to do that
It's just ever it's like so much drama. I don't want to like have a cigar in my mouth and be like, yes
Now let's talk about the drama between the rich people. I know no no, I'm staying home
Yeah, you bought my company and I'm Matt. No, how much money did I make in the sale?
You see my my father bought your company. How much did I make? I'm not stock options
Oh, you made two hundred and seventy five million call or raise. Okay, I'm staying home and getting high and watching TV. Bye
I don't care. Fuck all of you. I don't want to be here. I
Call I call I'm out. I call what you're not upset that that my father
Bought out all of your stock options
Okay, I just want to watch fucking YouTube video. You may check or bet. I
Call I call I call I raise you may fold call or raise
I call I call I call
Yeah, I don't even know who these people are. Why are you telling me intricate weird rich people drama?
I call you may fold call or raise. I raise. Oh, there we go
I raise I call I call you may fold call or raise. I was watching Vinesauce when I gave birth
That's not a call. It's not a real story
That's not a real story
I call no
What this is to pair? This is not fair. I fold
Alright, I have a theory and that theory is I think you just have to play like three or four games before they do
The next like murder mystery cutscene, so I was gonna fold every no. I'm not that's an ace, bro. We're in it. I'm out
I'm out. I raise I call I'm out
You may fold call or raise. I'm out. I call I call
They didn't shuffle the deck. You may check or bet. I call I call they asked Vinnie to name the baby. What did Vinnie say?
What do you got? Oh, there's another race. I call you may fold call or raise. I raise
I call you may fold call or raise story. I was in labor for 22 hours. Lol. It was boring
I call I call
Give me another rise. I check you may check or bet. I raise I call you may fold call or raising money
I check you may check or bet. I call you may fold call or raise
You got nothing what do I have you have a pair aces I
Have a VIP thing I can do
That's not real. That's bait. You show the lowest card and must ante I'm out
I'm out. I don't think you realize how many mothers you're entertaining. I'm out
I call I'm out. I call
Hey, hey German watching in the NASA space station. I check nice. You may check or bet
you
Leave in the middle of the tournament you forfeit the entrance fee. Whoa. No, it's 20 grand. I
Call I raise you may fold call all right. I'm I got nothing
You may fold call all right. This is junk. Oh
Ladies and gentlemen, we will now take a brief intermission. We're taking a lot of intermissions
I
Even kills bird
Flushmeister clean you out. You hear me don't even think of coming your shell
tension
Number one cause of bad poetry and poker, but no offense kills her. I don't want to be here
Someone's gonna couch with my dog. I don't want to be here
Don't call me the flush Meister and you're gonna clean me out punk and shit like dude. I I don't even be here
I don't want to be here
You show the lowest card and must anti I call I'm out
What yeah the flush master? I'm out flush Meister
I'm out. That's what he called me. I read what he called. I call you may fold call already
What's my call?
Because of a flush in poker. Do I get those a lot? I must get those a lot. I check
You may check or bet a terrible hand. I check
Although I got dying. I raise you may fold call or raise
What's the way is the magical chip was the murder mystery you may fold call or raise
Yeah, I'm not gonna be two guys three pair
three-pair
You show the lowest card and must anti I call I'm on it. Where's the microchip? I'm out. I call I raise
I call you may fold call or raise
Pocket ace like that. Give me a better card
All right. Now we're talking. Have a good I'm out. I
Raise I call you may fold call or raise. I'm out
I'm on thousand people watching lose money on a virtual casino. I'm out. Here's the thing though
We're waiting to get the big call mystery. I can't
Happening soon here very soon
I'm gonna laugh if there just is no mystery check
We just keep doing these intermission cutscenes where they sit down and talk shit. You may check all that again. I
Raise I raise you may fold call or raise I call I call you win a big pot here
You may check or bet. I raise I call you may fold call or raise. I call I call
No idea what that is
You may check or bet. I raise I call you may fold call or raise. You're scary because you have the
You may check or bet I raise I call you may fold call
You need a light gun for countdown vampires what don't
What happened? I'm making it through the tournament. Here's how you placed
I didn't come in last place you will need to have a hundred thousand dollars to enter the next tournament
Welcome to the fabulous Golden Nugget. I don't know if we're gonna see that just do all-in five
What's the highest bet I can do you need a hundred grand to see who did it?
Hold on. We can get this quick. We can get this quick. We get me. We get this quick
I got a black check with five dollar bet. What's Dan? Oh
All right, hold on hold on hold on I got let's go. Let's go. Let's go
I'm gonna be quick quick quick fast fast fast money here fast
It's gonna land double down here Jack, that's awful and I still won I win
All right countdown vampires is coming up we'll see I have high hopes for this one
It sucks so bad
You should play a loud sound to wake everybody up to fell asleep. Um, that's a no that's fucked up
No
No, that's not nice
What was that saying? This is fiction. Don't recreate this like don't be a vampire. How would you recreate this? Let's go
Input your data. I this is hurting my head looking at this. I don't even care
Blood group. What's it? What's my blood type? I don't I I don't know what my blood type is. I have no idea
I'm just gonna say hey, I don't know. I actually don't have any idea. I said to get away from that screen
I'm a homicide detective from a neighboring state and I've specifically come here for a very simple reason
I'm working as a guard for the VIPs at the casino hotel opening party Oh connected games
It's me Adam West. Let me just tell you something. I found this receipt on the ground
Just not fit this game. This doesn't fit the game at all
This feels like back in YouTube when something got DMCA content ID and a default regular ass YouTube song had to be played over
the video
What's happening?
blackjack
Animals in here, why the animals in here? Why is this cat in here?
What?
This is real what
Why are they doing this what the heck is happening what the heck is going on here
Wait, is that is he a vampire who is shot who I feel like this was made in the movies
This is a movies movie game. You all right. What are they this white water turns them back to normal? Okay
It's good to know
Did we deal with the fire here use this?
This meeting what about you I've got one more wait here, I'm gonna look around
This is the main character
Alright, that was a lot to take in but leave this area within three minutes head for the screaming moon door use the anis
What I've three minutes to get out of here fire preventer procedures code. See are zero one
Okay, we will be sealed off in three minutes, but I move please leave club Regan immediately and proceed to a safe shelter area
It's fucking present you
How do I move?
The slot machine can be played but not what but not what you have chosen now, right?
There is nothing worse than tank controls
Nothing on this earth. How do I get out of here get up the stairs? Oh
God, okay, that security card died. Wait, is it wait the beginning?
Like I made it
Am I remembering what he said, okay or some white water on them
What do you want me to I didn't even have a second
Yeah, where's my menu about to pull it out of the drink
No, I don't wait, it's alright, it's okay. I don't wanna go one more
Okay, so I I'm sorry and I'm gonna make a lot of people really upset about this probably
You're probably gonna be like dude. What the fuck fuck you right? But just let me this is my opinion about video games
This is my personal video game opinion. And all I have to say is I don't like the old Resident Evil games
I think they're awful and I thought that when they came out as they came out during a period where I that was like a new
thing
Like when the Resident Evil games were a big deal
They were just barely releasing and I was part of that group that thought
And I do I did not like them and those are like the best of the best in this genre of tank controlled games
I don't think I'm gonna like this one very much at all
Resident Evil 4 is this does not count. I'm talking about Resident Evil 1 Resident Evil 2
Although I did I did enjoy them. I did play them. I did
Eventually, but I never was a fan of the
Okay, let me figure that I'm gonna figure this out
That's a zoomer opinion. No, it's not. I just don't like tank control games. It's driving crazy
All right anesthetic stun gun and after they're on to pour some water on them and I don't do I have white water
stun globe anesthetic dart I
Don't have white weight white water is in the corner. How do I use it? How do I use them? How do I use the water?
How do I pour the water on them doesn't help what action
Change weapon
Wait, what's that?
Like how do you pour water on them?
Ready are you though?
Bionicles going in ps2 Bionicle for ps2 going in now
I mean that was worth playing just to get that opening cutscene. That was great
Eidos really
This looks fucking awesome
But her that was a very long intro take two ice the movie starting everybody quiet
And
It's transformed all the islands inhabitants into all kinds of strange spiteful creatures
You must track that beat the Piraka to return boy, and we to peace
Use the powers that the masks will grant you to say boy, and we
I
Onicle heroes, I'm ready
I'm prepared. It's travelers tales. They make the Lego games really this still this still kicking, huh? That's pretty cool
All right, I'm ready. I know a lot of people were looking forward to this. Oh the bloom is
unbelievable
The whole game is a bloom filter enter shop. Whoa, what is all this? All right, I gotta go do a mission zone select
There's ox coastline. I think that's the only one I can do right. Let's go. You need 3d glasses
It really is like the Lego games, isn't it? I could turn scan lines on it might help
That's right. I'm gonna try scan lines. See hold on. I don't want you to see my I'm not wearing any clothes
All right, I'm gonna try you tell me which one
Does that look better it's too dark hold on how's that it feels like I'm playing this game
Dream, it feels like I'm playing this game in a dream. I had not even playing it right now
I'm dreaming that I'm playing this
2006 YouTube I'm gonna go back. I'm gonna go back. I'm going back. Just hold on
It does look like I'm holding it in front of a TV
Yeah, it looks like I'm pointing a camera at the TV the brightness down. How's that? I think that looks all right
That's actually not that bad. Let's go. Whoa. I have a lot of money. Is there like a dash? Whoa
I can change character
All right, that's pretty sick. I got another character but bloom on your webcam
This is a quo. I think it has killed that
cool
This game is actually really good
But bloom on you. I don't think I know I can't I don't know how to do that
5,000 another character
Was this person do?
grenades I could see how this would this would be
absolutely phenomenal
Like this is a great game
I have to collect them or something. Are they just worth money?
Bionicle series literally saved Lego from bankruptcy. It was the Holy Grail for them. It's pretty sick
You need your green
Gustability here. Is it Balta? I don't have this ability
So I do I have to leave
Bionicles were dope. I
Bionicle kind of passed by me. They weren't quite my generation. It was just barely
You're very old. Yeah
So when I feel that thing up at the top that means I've got maximum amount of money from this level
Hero mode increases weapon power and allows you to trigger gold
Constructions
What's that mean? What's that mean? Just go it's kind of hard though, doesn't it?
Was this whoa build the boat be kidding me. Holy shit, that was cool. What do I do the boat?
Is it on rails? I think it's on rails doesn't look that bad anymore. Looks all right be worse
Whoa, hold on. Holy shit. Oh
Open this geez, I'm gonna die. I'm dead
Jesus
I got the masks here. I'm all let's go. This game looks like the disk is rusted. It's not
the disc rusted dude
This is just what video games looks like like 20 years ago. It's still a boss over here. Oh, no, it's a mask. All right
I think I like this guy the best like the fire and I not I don't have that ability yet
Shit, I think your screen is dirty
Games really cool. But can we go back to Adam West? No to go back to Adam West
We have to play seven card stud which nobody wants to do that or seven card to whatever it is
I had a prompt for something. What was that?
Yeah, this is bionicle. I had a lot of people with that. That's a lot of money. Give me I like the building stuff
It's fun about to go hero mode. I need health. This is literally a cooler Lego game. I mean, it's pretty cool
I think it's fun. I need a mask. I need a mask
stop
This dude imagine a remade remastered version of this game would be amazing
Did they ever make one of these again or no never again? What am I doing? Oh, I can climb this
Never again, really?
Unfortunate that bounce I'm going this way and I go down there gamer Andy
Where is it? Where is that?
Stop, where's the thing?
Why can't I do it? Come on, do it fuck. I can't do anything with this. I actually can't do anything. I
Can't make it. I don't have the ability. I
Apparently can't do anything. You wasted the hero mode. No, I got it. Oh, okay
I need new abilities
Cool. This is cool. What is I want to sweat a cool game
If you get this for Christmas, you know, I mean you would be absolutely thrilled
So I don't have that character. I can't open this
Looks like it's behind me. Whatever. I want to go buy stuff. Look at much money I have
Here mode, oh
I
Need to get here a mode. This is a boss. I
Gotta get around. I can't fight this guy. Wait, hold on. I need god mode or whatever it is
Can't how do I activate here a mode? I don't have enough activated. I I can't almost there. Oh
This is bad, let's go nice job. Oh
I died I died I died I died I died I do
Know
It's alright I have money
Joe Biden left. I'm trying to find Joe Biden talking. What would it would it be under Joe Biden?
Hanging out. I don't think that exists Joe Biden voice lines. Yeah, but he's not like a fucking cartoon character
Like a voice lines Joe Biden Joe Biden's supercut. I can't I don't I don't know what this even sounds like
Okay, this is not even gonna be funny like at all
I
Told you it wasn't gonna be funny
Sounds like he's part of the game
He's in the game
New character how many it's a lot of characters. Is it all right? So now I can upgrade and unlock items
This is what I care about more than anything. I don't want to go in there
No, how do I get out of here? There you go. How much money do I actually have the question?
You can now visit the creature chambers
You can now visit the trophy room
canister locator
Diving board. This is all so expensive
What show me this? This is awesome. I
like the fire
Okay, who else do I like? Oh, yep. I like the I like green. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay
All right. All right. I'll take a hint a great hint. Thanks for telling me how to fire my weapon. Why is it a ball?
Okay, okay, like Lego pieces power up your hero meter. Yeah, we've done this in the very beginning
Okay. All right. All right. Now I'm excited because look at this
this guy's cracked out now, I
I would have put
Thousand hours into this game when I was like 12 without a doubt did that go to the ice level box mountain
What about sly Cooper? Um, you'll see it eventually. I got a lot of games dude. You're an adult
You can put ten a thousand hours into this. Yeah, but I don't want to do that
Making somebody did you suck? You're that upgraded torch? Oh, it's just absolutely
Melts people it just melts people
I'm not why would I switch to another hero unless I have to move something shit. I don't have that person
Almost psycho. There you go. There you go. Ooh
Can I open this?
Shit, I really didn't think I was gonna like this. I thought this was gonna be crap
So yeah, this is like this is gonna be dumb
Bionicle is based. Yeah, I know pretty like I'm doing here. What's this? Oh
We chirp build Bionicle on screen
Why am I dying? Why am I dying? Why am I what happened? Why am I dying? What did I do? Can't be in the water. Oh
That's bad, I can't walk across water now
Take another battery do this for six hours. Um, I'll do this for a little while
Yep, this is Bionicle. This is Bionicle for the PlayStation 2. Okay
Pop that I need to collect more of this shit. I'm out of money. I need way more money
I have heard of this thing so many times. It's kind of nice. I don't want to turn on the hero mode yet
Not yet. Ooh, what's this beat this game or watch the Bionicle movies? It's your choice
Well, one of those things is illegal. So I think I'll choose this for a little while
You both all right. I got here a boat. It seems legal
Alright, where's the where's the big guy? Come on. Where is he? Do it. It's been a towel rack
Come on. Where's the how do I make the big guy? There we go. There's a lot of people
Do it climb toll. It's worth a lot. The Lego games do this too. You'd have to touch everything
I buy it. I buy it was cool. Would you guys all leave a Bionicle stream if I made one?
I've never I've done I never even played with them ever never even seen him before I would leave. Okay one more money
Nice
It's so satisfying
This game is great. I like it a lot. It's really cool
Do a pole pole pole pole for what you keep playing this? Oh to make a Bionicle
All right, should I make a Bionicle like next week on stream?
It has to be at least 80%
Gotta be a lot
40,000 shit. I want that. Did I get turned around? Oh my god. Okay, please
You guys like Bionicle and don't have it. Do you look like a Bionicle? That's
Incredibly handsome and I didn't see them. Well, how do I get across money?
money
You've gone go. Who wasn't here. Will you eat the Bionicle?
No, I will display it on my reddit shell
Alright, I'm kind of just like vibing out right now. This is fun. Build it praying mantis. Oh
It's cutting the alright. I'll finish the job. Come on
Finish the job. Where'd you go? Oh
Boy, that's a lot. I'm hurt really bad. Come on do it. No, I don't want to lose that guy
That should be it, right? Do it. Come on punk
That's shield off. No
No
Uh-oh. Okay. Get up. I guess it up
Get this fucking shield off
Ah
shit
There it is. Damn
56,000 I was yeah, I was just vibing this game's fun
Remask andy. It's all right. I got one gold canister and I got corak. Ooh, what else I get
All right upgrade wait, it's a permanent 50 discount permanently. Should I wait for that?
How would you wait for that? Because it's 50 off everything maximum damage. You're gonna play more games tonight
Yeah, you upgraded his ability not his gun. Isn't that the torch is the no, this is the launcher. I think it's upgraded
Yeah, look at this maximum look see
All right. How about this?
One more level. Let's let's take a break. It's been four and a half hours. No break
Take a break go pee come back one more level and then we'll play something else. This is very good though
I'm very happy with this one
Only four percent game progress. How long is this game? Wow. All right, I brought back go pee
Grab a snack or something back in like two minutes. Okay
These things are so good. I could eat these until I puked. I really could these pretzel rods
These things I could eat these until I threw up. It's got to be the rods though
You know what I mean, you need to get a hundred percent progress that's not going to happen tonight honey mustard
A lot of people are going to think i'm gross for this, but I really do mean this
I think I've probably talked about this before trust me you dan's game that I didn't even say anything you see ready
Pretzel rods. I didn't even say you you didn't I didn't even say anything yet
You make tuna fish, you know, like as if you were going to make a tuna fish sandwich
Lose the bread bowl of tuna fish, you know with the mayo like as if you're going to put it in a sandwich
Don't even get the bread out of the out of the container pretzel rods tuna fish dip bite get a good amount
Good paste of the tuna on there. I just stabbed myself in the fucking lip and i'm pissed at all of you. It's so good
It is so good. No spices. Just tuna mayo. So don't act like you don't do that when you have a pretzel rod
You don't like squish it up here and like squish it back here and put it down here and over here
You
Tuna is cat food. I burnt my screen in I burnt my screen and I burnt my screen and I burnt my screen and
I burnt my screen in
It's my my screen's ruined. I you can't see this. My screen is burnt in
What?
No, no, this is really bad. This is really bad. Hold on
What the fuck?
Why is my why is it burnt in?
Hold on. I gotta take a picture of this. You have to see this it's burnt into the capture card. I have no idea
Yeah, this is not going away. It's okay. I gotta get this into discord. You can make out the letters
It says like reset start. Oh my god. Let me just see what happens
Yeah, because when I was paused here, it says yeah resume it's burnt into the capture card. Hold on. This is so stupid
You can see resume options and quit. Hold on. Let me get this so I can put it on the stream. Well done
Okay
Okay, got it. All right. This is what I see right now and I i'm gonna have to probably restart everything
So let me know when you can see it. You see that this sucks
I'm gonna I have to restart the capture card probably but that's what I see
Resume options and quit and then game progress is right there. You're making it worse. Can you guys make it out?
That says resume. I am i'm
Flabbergasted right now. I don't know what to do. Uh, what do I what should I do about this? This is unbearable
It's your screen. Not your card. Hold on
Fuck my screen
Hold on a second. I'm gonna laugh my ass off if I switch to my actual monitor and is it still there?
Thank god. It's not okay. Wait a minute. Is it it actually might still be here? No, it can't no. No, no
I'm seeing things
It's burnt into my capture card. Um, why would you not be seeing it though? Hold on. Fuck. It's still there
Oh, I didn't save the game. I didn't save the game. I didn't save the game. I'm so fucking annoyed right now
I didn't save the game. Did I it's still there?
It's on the actual oh no, it's it's over reset your monitor. Hold on. Let me see if it's still here
Yeah, it's burnt into the fucking capture card
I have to take another picture. You guys need to see it
It's so stupid
What are you our savior? I wonder if I can fix it somehow
It's 100. No, it's not the screen because I just changed over to my different. Um, I changed over to my other input
Let me reset the card. It's definitely still there
God damn it. Give me a second. Show us again. Hold on. I wasn't even gone for that long
Honestly, I was I was only gone for like five minutes. Not even two minutes
Here. Look, here's the other one just to prove that it's a different screenshot
If I could get it on there, that'd be great. Here's the next one
This one you can see it a lot better
there
Reset your monitor. It's image retention interlacing makes that happen. Sometimes our cycle you monitor. It's 100% not burning. Okay
So you're saying I should not be concerned about like this for instance, right?
Like I shouldn't be concerned about this
All right. I'm gonna reset the monitor and see if that fixes it
okay, resetting it coming back and
It's still kind of there
Wait, I think it's better the more you play the quicker it will go away. I feel like it's very faintly there still
All right. Well good. Let's just go. All right. Well, sorry about that. It was weird time to replace the monitor
No, i'm good. It would have been funny if your face was burned in
You have nine more days to play smite and get the 10 year anniversary rewards. I don't I don't what what are you talking about?
It's still there. I'm just gonna play and see if it fixes itself. I reset the monitor. I'm just gonna play
That's very very annoying. What's the last place I was here? No, what opened up? Nothing. Oh, okay
Our cycle not reset. Are you serious? Hold on like unplug it
Which one of these is the power cable? Oh my god, don't spill. All right. The monitor is unplugged. Oh shit
What just happened with my stream? All right. I'm good. All right coming back
I would I would pay extra dude. I would pay extra to be able to have them on the top
It's still there still there. I just unplugged it and plugged it back in it's there
I think it might be there forever. This is actually that kind of sucks. I'll just have to deal with it
Yeah, I can still see resume on my screen
Well, the pretzel rod is worth it. What's that sound? What's that sound? What's the why do I hear like crushing water?
You guys don't hear this you don't hold on. Can you hear this? Can you guys hear that?
It's so loud. Why what's happening to my fucking computer?
This is a disaster because I got up to piss with my mouse
My everything is backwards because I unplugged the monitor and it automatically corrected it to put the monitors in the wrong place
You guys cannot fucking hear this. I don't know how you can't you can you guys hear the rushing water?
I'm trying to make it so you can hear some cables unplugged or something. I don't know how what is going on right now, huh?
What's what just happened? Hello. Can everybody hear me? I have no more control over obs
It am I even on camera? This has been an insane last 15 minutes. Um, I can't even see my other monitor
Yeah, I all right. Well, let's just let's just go
I I can't I I don't have another monitor. It's gone
Burn this one in this one doesn't work
Yeah, so what why did that happen?
Why would I have a bad burn in for five? It wasn't even five minutes
Doesn't it take like hours or days to burn into your fucking screen?
And then all I heard was like
Through my headphones. All right, I gotta get in there. This thing does a lot of damage now
Let's go. What did that do? Oh
On the ground. He's so into it. I kind of am it's just fun to shoot stuff and collect everything. It's fun
We'll move on after this level though. There's a bunch more stuff. I want to do tonight
We're gonna go long
Probably a 24 hour stream. No, not that long, but we'll go longer than like five for sure
We're gonna do a new longest stream ever. I doubt I doubt that I would say no
But I know I could be wrong. I could be wrong
I doubt it, but I could be wrong
I'm gonna say i'm shooting for like
I don't know
I don't have a time limit
It's until i'm done
Ooh, oh, I don't have that character ball fondler wants you to play. Wow
I'm pretty sure ball fondler has a bot that just writes in this channel
Every like three days telling me to play world of warcraft. I would not be surprised
Nice
I would uh, I would definitely stay tuned though because coming up right after this
I don't know. Should I see what your reaction is? I feel like people are going to be to be very upset or very happy
Uh, can I not get over this?
Apparently not I love the music. It's great
The music I honestly is what's keeping me here
So much bloom in that room
All right. Don't I have this ability though?
See it's like oh be this character. I am this character and I don't do I have how do I do that move?
Burn it. It was a prompt
Okay
triangle
Triangle switch character
Okay, it wants me to be this character, but then doesn't really tell me what to do after that
Oh, it just lets you cross the lava. Okay
Did you get a snack from the gas station? Yeah, why not?
Yeah, go get a snack. You know, it's actually pretty good. I hate pepsi
but the that nitro pepsi is actually
Like at least at least an eight or nine out of ten
Nitro pepsi is actually pretty good
I can only really drink one of those every so often because they I feel like they're so much sweeter
They're really good
I don't believe that's real. No, it is check it out. Good
milk pepsi
No, no, no, no nitro pepsi
It's good
Hilt, you know, i've actually heard that term before
I've never tried it but
It probably that honestly doesn't even sound that bad
People do ice cream floats and stuff. Isn't that just kind of a float without it being frozen?
Kind of
Basically. Yeah. All right. Let me in
What does it keep what's the hold up? Let me in
right on stream
um
I have coke
Will coke and milk work?
Uh-oh
I can't build anything with that. There we go
Falcon
All right, boss time. Don't fuck it up
Uh, I need to get generate some more
drink drink
silk now
We'll do that later
Now no i'm doing later
Let me I have a cherry coke here. It's not going to work with that. I don't want to ruin my cherry coke
Cherry coke is s tier and i'm not going to ruin it with like your you're like pilk fantasy
Come on, do it already
Oh my god
Do it. Oh my god, do it already
Be killing me
Can you just kill it?
Shoot I'm gambling in front of my young audience my impressionable audience
um
What dude i'm playing bionicle right now
Get that shield down, please
That chatter is on a 70 minute delay
Wait, you totally took with the adam west game
Oh
All right, put the fucking shield down before everybody dies here
Whatever good shield down
stop
bounced off of his head
Excuse me
We still have okay. I was gonna say what the fuck
Hmm imagine if that was pilk cherry coke is so much better than everything else. I used to be a huge 7-up fan
But then cherry coke really took it over
I don't check. I don't have it that often sometimes when i'm just chilling out
What about your shirt?
I can't enjoy other soda brands. I have to just do the one meme that I did like
10 years ago on my youtube channel
Who's your favorite bionicle? Uh the fire one. All right. This game was actually
Awesome. This was fantastic
I really wish my obs and my monitor over here wasn't so messed up because I can't really tell
Can't really click on anything. I'm afraid to click on too much because I feel like i'll accidentally turn the stream off or something
Hold on. Wait, you guys aren't getting that. No, you're not. Okay. All right, let's keep going
That was bionicle and that was really fun
But we're gonna move on. I wonder how people are gonna like this one save the game
I think it was it saved didn't you say I kidding me that looks so much better
That looks a thousand times better for me. That's all right. Um
Yeah, it's fine. I think it's still I think I think it it saved didn't it find out
Yeah, we got it. We're good. Okay, give me another minute. I'm just gonna put in the next game and
Uh, I want a poll to be ran immediately
I want a poll to go up
Immediately the second that you get to the splash screen of this game
And I want it to be at least 50. Yes
Like yes, play this if it's not at least 50 i'll take it i'll take it out immediately. I will take it out
You can't know what it is until it goes in
Get ready to run it. This is just a simple yes or no
Do you want me to play this game for 20 to 30 minutes? It's just a yes or no question
All right, so let's get ready
Thq. All right now we're talking
What game by thq? Okay, bbc media interesting
consumer products
Run it run it run it run it run it run it now go go go go go go go
Has to be at least 50 or i'll take the disco
This is way too much
That's 84 let's go
All right, give me the 20 30 minute countdown bob the builder was claymation
Was
What this show was so much cooler. I I didn't have this memory of this show being this cool
It's claymation
I didn't know that
I thought it was just animated
Damn, that's pretty cool show. All right, i've had enough
Okay, can we build it bob the builder for playstation 1 porcupine rescue scary spud
wendy's birthday bubble trouble
parental options
Parents don't touch this kids
Travis's race day plumbing puzzle. What do we do rescue that porcupine porcupine rescue?
Okay, tunnel time or where's pilchard who's pilchard this
Tunnel time. Okay. I think the porcupines are scared to cross the road. Yes lofty. It's dangerous
I know let's make them a tunnel
I was to leave the wildlife along over a piece of pipe using the directional buttons
And pick it up using the x button move the pipe over the hole you think it should go in
Then press the x button to drop it in
That's it loppy
by the way
I gave you an out
That's it loppy. I gave you an out. I gave you an opportunity and 84 percent of you said to play this
I
Don't know what to tell you besides you had an op you had an out. I gave it to you
I was ready just to watch the intro and just take the disc out. That's great
The porcupines will be safe now
Bob will be proud of us. Look at that weird cat. I like that character
Would I like this show would I like this show?
Is it what I heard season one and two is like all right with the season like five gets like worse or something
But I like this
Should I watch it?
Move the bowl around the screen using the directional buttons until pilchard snores get louder
This means you are closer to where she's hiding
Okay, let's go
Where can she be
Literally you're literally right here that was the easy I even children could do this come and get it
How would how would you not see that?
Where can she be?
This one's a little harder
Say something over here
No, that's just some construction equipment
Wait a minute
Dinner time pilchard don't worry. This game was five dollars
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute. This is hard. Oh, there's difficulties
How much harder is this i'm gonna laugh if it's really really fucking hard, please be insane
please
Oh, it's not that bad
That's it lofty
Okay, it's just like I don't want to play this
All right. What else we got on here?
Can we build it can we build it knock it down build it up weird? Okay, how about knock it down lofty?
We'll use your wrecking ball to know good job lofty nearly try a little closer lofty
Good job lofty
Great good job lofty
How many guys grew up with this?
He's embarrassed. No, i'm not bob the builder was like a really great television program
This is a great television program for children
What are you on about? Sorry. I had the s tier
childhood shit, so i'm sorry, but uh
The muppets like the like the old muppets nothing even comes close hard like doesn't even come close
Move lofty's hook the old 80s and 90s muppets. Nothing comes close. I'm sorry you lose it up using the x button
Match the color to the color of the bricks underneath. Yeah, dude. I'm sorry. Fozzy would drop kick bob the builder
And it would be over
Why are they fighting?
All right. Um
What do I have to do?
Try another section. Uh, oh
I didn't pay any attention try another section
Try another section
Try another section. I didn't know I didn't I wasn't there. I wasn't there for the explanation section
Right. How was that next section now?
Oh, okay. All right. I get I get I get it
I I just didn't know I didn't even know what we were doing
Try another section try another section
You can't play the baby game. I didn't even know what I wasn't looking at all. I was looking over at you
I was looking at your comments
Try another section hasn't even been close to 20 minutes. We're gonna be able to do all these mini games
Right. Can you get the next section now?
Can't match the colors. I didn't even know I just was like, okay i'm building a bridge
Yes
Good work bob the builder hundred percent. That's not my hater day. That's like I got like a big thing back here. I don't like it
Uh bob
Yes lofty
Oh, no, I get
It's too worry lofty
The bridge is safe now
All right. That was cool. Now we gotta find the cat i'm speedrunning this whole game move the bowl around. I know how to play
What's the world record on this game can somebody look it up
You think I think I could beat this game. I think I think I could be the world record holder of this game
Back I think I could do it. I'm literally begging you to tell me what did you say? What a muppet is?
Who's your favorite muppet? Like do you uh, really you really are you asking that question?
scary spot
Hard it's gonzo. Of course it is nine minutes 15 seconds. Okay. So how do I do this?
Is it on hard or is it on easy? What what what is it on hard? Why is that happening?
I'm pressing x
That's me doing that
It's it's on easy. Okay, nine minutes
So at from what point?
I think I could do this in nine minutes the whole thing
Spuds on the job yummy apple all missions easy nine minutes. How do I get a timer? I don't have that set up
Back i'm gonna do an eight
I need time splits and shit
back
I need live split
That's too much work. How about this? I have a mod time it. Okay, somebody time it. Can somebody time it for me?
Somebody time it for me
Okay, travis's race day. I'm ready
Use the timer built into windows. Is there a timer?
There's a clock app
Is there holy shit? There's a clock app. All right, i'll try it. I think I could do it timer
Okay, I gotta capture this window. I need it to be
Uh, I need to speak counting right? Okay. All right. I'm going for it
uh
My obs is so fucked up right now because of the uh, like the glitch that happened earlier. Yeah, this is messed up
There we go. Okay
Uh timer
Can I not capture that? That's annoying. Why can I not capture this window in window capture? Okay, well, that's stupid
Never mind. Um, this is dev in chat. I that would be shocking to me. Why can I capture this?
I can capture every single window, but I can't capture the clock app google stopwatch instead joke
Okay, how about google google stopwatch? Let's try that. Okay. All right. I'm ready almost
Uh, this is nonsense stop this nonsense at once. Okay, can you see it? What's the record? Okay. Here we go
Ready? Okay
Even if I don't get the world record i'll be in the cat. I'll be literally somewhere
I'll be leading the top top five starts when you select the first mission. Okay. Here we go. Ready travis's race day
Easy on your marks get set watch out scoop. Watch out scoop
lap three
Watch out scoop
Job scoop scoop is
You almost lost no, I didn't on your marks get set go
Ask travis
Watch out dizzy
Fuck you game
This takes two minutes three minutes to do this one section
Watch out
I'm probably one of ten people on earth that have even tracked how much time this takes to do
I'm not gonna get the world record, but i'll be in the top five because i'm gonna be over five people that recorded it
Go go go go go go
Plumbing puzzle easy. I've never even seen this before. I don't even know what i'm supposed to be doing. What do I even do?
Yes, it does bob use your eyes this doesn't fit here yes it does bob
Yes, it does
Where else does it go bob
Here oops this doesn't fit here
This doesn't fit here
Oops, this doesn't fit here
This doesn't fit here. Oops. This doesn't fit here
Oops, this doesn't fit here. There's a way there's other rooms
This doesn't fit here. Why bob? Where are you going? How many more? Oh my
Sorry, that was a bad split. That was bad, but we can make up the time later
Now fuck that i'm doing it again now fuck that
And let's go travis is raced at e we refund what do you mean on your marks? Don't loading screens not count
Scoop has travis
Watch out scoop
I can do this better. Good job scoop. I can do this better scoop is the winner
Is this on easy?
Was that on easy dizzy you'll on your mark old split. This makes me kind of want to do that
Is that weird that I want to do this now?
Lap two lap three watch out dizzy
Good job dizzy
dizzy
Okay, don't fuck it up
Plumbing puzzle easy. Okay. Oh go
Gotta get good rng here. Ah, it's already already fucked up
Wicked bad rng
Come on. Really dude. You spliced this run. It's so obvious
You spliced this run
Easy am I sure that wasn't hard?
Perfect fucking seed perfect seed. Can we build easy?
Moving on its own on easy. That's what fucked me up. Good job lofty. Good job lofty
Great good job lofty
Such good rng you kidding me look at the placement right? Can you get the next section now?
Yes, just gotta find that stupid cat we can build it
Porcupine rescue ease that's it lofty good job
Where you going?
Good job
That was shitty rng. It was
Scary spot easy time. What do I got for time?
Is it over? That's one more. Oh go. Come on. Where's this cat?
When's time when's time when's time when's time when it's time did I do it did I do it is that it
Oh, no, we got there's so much shit to do wendy's birthday. What?
We're going to have a birthday party. How would you do all the loading screens? How would you do this in nine minutes? What?
What?
Wait, is this count technically?
Why is it dnt?
Dude, I don't think this counts like that. Just there finish this part of the run wendy
I've got a surprise for you. Thank you. Bob. I don't know if this counts for the run
This is this definitely no way. This is part of the run. Thanks for a wonderful
No, there's no way this is definitely not part of the run. It's included in the world record
what
Bubbled trouble easy. How would you watch the world record run?
I'm almost there. This is the last too many games. That's it. Where can she be time dinner time pilchard
12 49 top 10. Yo, I can do better than that. I can do better than that. I'm doing it again
I'm gonna get sub 12. Why do I care? I told you no, who's you nobody runs this?
I'm going top. I'm going. All right. Here we go. Watch the world record first. Nah, here we go already
Travis's race day. Is it on easy? Is it on easy by default on your marks?
Get set go
Try as hard as I can to get sub 12
Because I don't want I you know, I don't want any of you
Dicks to overtake my top 10 record because you just you just have to play
Just reset reset reset. That was a bad one
I know some one of you guys is gonna get this and you're gonna bump me on purpose. Help help back
Travis's race day. All right, no more fucking around. I'm going for real. I'm going sub 12. Let's go go on your marks
Get set go
Scoop has Travis. Oh, I got reset
Watch out scoop
lap three
Travis is right easy. No more resets. I'm going no more resets on your marks get set. No, I
This is a glitchless
Speed run glitchless any percent speed run
all mini games
I want to reset so bad
I have to reset one more time. I swear to god i'm not gonna do it again
Hold on. This is this is a glitchless any percent speed run. I promise i'm not gonna reset ever again
One, two, three go Travis's race. I promise
Last one for real scoop on your marks get set go
Scoop has Travis watch out scoop
lap two
Watch out scoop
lap three
I'm not gonna restart. No, i'm going scoop
I'm not resetting. I just need sub 12 and i'll move on. I promise on your marks get set up 12. I swear to god
dizzy past Travis
lap two lap three
Watch out that was shit placement and you all know it good job dizzy
All right, that's the worst part of the whole run
That's the shittiest part of the run plumbing puzzle
Can I move faster here crow is the worst one?
That was clean clean good timing
Think is bad bad rng. I think it gets up 12
Just can't mess up the crow part. It's not there. Don't be fooled
Lots of other runners get fooled by that
I don't think I could do this one any better if I wanted to
god like rng
Absolutely god like rng great holy shit all done pray for that kind of fucking rng
Can we build a job loppy?
Great good job loppy
Good job loppy
Great good job. Come on. Keep going keep going keep going
Do it right. Can you get the next section now?
Yes
Good work
We can build it
Where can she be
Good
I'm definitely gonna get sub 12. No doubt porcupine rest
This one's really really tricky. If you don't get a good rng, then i'm just gonna stop saying that word because like I don't know
What the fuck i'm talking about
That's it loppy
I couldn't press it. I couldn't press it. It wouldn't let me
That's it loppy. Yes. That's great. The porcupines will be safe now. That wasn't a joke
Where can she be
Definitely way better than last time
Scary easy
Making sure it's on easy. This one sucks. This is making this is gonna make a break the whole run get out what?
Get the fuck out of here. All right, that was
They gotta land
No, you want them not to land so they eat your crops
i'm fine
There's not much left. We have dance party. We have what's left
Wendy's birthday when his fucking birthday. Just okay. Here we go. Do I need to use all the ingredients?
Do I have to use all the ingredients finished?
Wendy i've got a surprise for you. No, I don't. Okay. All right. Good. Good. Good
This is it. This is it coming up. He's doing the cubrics there. Is it time after this?
Is that it what about your time time when right?
Yeah
Bubble trouble. Oh fuck. Oops. Oh no. Oh no
Why is wendy's birthday in front of bubble trouble?
Uh, it was so I was probably gonna be sub 12 probably probably even sub like 11 30
Well, let's just let's just see what would happen. Let's just see what if I did this so clean last time
Yeah, so now I uh
That sucks. It would have been sub 12
I know it's i'm not it's an illegal run. I'm not saying it's legal. Okay. Can I do this one more time?
Move the bowl around the screen. A lot of people don't want me to do this, but like can I do it one more time?
Where can she be?
Because there's that's a sub 12 run right there. When do I hit the stop?
When do I write when the cutscene ends, please? No viewers are gonna plug it. It's only 10 minutes
It's the last input
It's only 10 minutes dude. My six-year-old has never been more interested in you. Can I have one more attempt?
I promise I
This is the last time and no resets either and I promise like my head's not like shaped
Like I had my head's not made of clay. I promise. I don't know what this I don't know
What's going on back here, but I promise it's I didn't it's not what it's normal. It's not as abnormal
Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right, right. You should watch the world record
No, no, I don't want to I don't want to get anything in my head
This is it
Does it matter what I start with?
Could I start with bubble trouble?
No
Why not if you don't get sub-12 you have to drink pilk. Okay
Okay, if I get if I don't get sub-12 i'll drink a glass of pilk on stream in like 20 minutes
All right. This is it. This is this is one i'm gonna start with bubble trouble. Is that illegal?
Can I actually start on this or is that illegal read the mod chat?
World record video stops the timer when the final loading screen pops up
The world record starts with the radiators and the crows since they have the most rng
All right, so we're starting with radiator. No, we're gonna do it my way starting with bubble trouble
No resets no bullshit. This is it. I'm trying when we sub-12 illegal i'm gonna get a it's gonna be legal
I'm not gonna pause then unpause and no, this is just really going crows only count if they land first. Okay
All right. I'm ready. I'm ready to get sub-12
And i'm gonna do my strap
All right, i'm gonna start because I want wendy's birthday to be the end of the run
Bubbled trouble. I did it out of order. It's uh, what can I do it out of order? Is that okay? What the fuck happened back?
Bubbled trouble not bad not bad
I almost fucked that up
No travis's race day
On your marks get set calm down
I'm coming down
You put that shit right there it's hard you can't avoid that. Okay, don't die a godly bubble run
Don't blow it here
Why are you doing the cringe face to me? What?
Why'd you do that scoop is
Don't throw I won't if I can get through this in three minutes. I'll be good marks get set go
3 30 dizzy past travis
Watch out dizzy
Hitbox on that is so much bigger than it looks
gigantic square dizzy past travis
lap three
All right, that's it for that keep going plumbing puzzle look at look at that blue radiator this sucks
I gotta rock. Well, I gotta walk across the whole game
Look at this pill pill pill pill. It's not happening. I'm getting sub 12
I'm gonna stop pay attention. You're not like, you know, just like you're not streaming right now
You're fucking getting a sub 12. Um, don't look look at chat and start talking give us a good. Uh, good run here. Come on
Oh, that's good, but I walked by it
A week there. Sorry not bad. I think i'm on pace. Can we
Somebody said you can get two hits on the same pillar
I'm gonna try it and you're gonna be responsible for me throwing up after I drink coke. Thank god for that chatter
job lofty
Great good job lofty
That's a massive time save right here
Good job lofty
Let's build a new bridge. That's actually a massive time save
Right. Can you get the next section now?
Yes
Good work. We can build it
cat right
Porcupine rest that's it lofty
Shit rng on this one. I'm serious
Because I have to go all the way back
It has to bounce
Absolutely, just terrible terrible
That's it lofty. Yes. All right. I saved a lot of time with that killer hit
Will be safe now
Where can she be?
Almost there
Scaries
All right, let him land let him land right let him land. Let him land
Let them all land
Is that all right?
Where can she be?
Just the birthday party and we're done
Wendy's birthday finished
Wendy i've got a surprise for you. Thank you, bob. You missed one
What did I skip? What did I do?
No, no, I didn't i'm good. It's gonna be close. So at the loading screen, right?
Give me that sub 11. Let's go. Come on
Come on
1102 back
1102 that's a big I could do more than that. I could get probably sub 10
Don't please don't do it again. Hey, I got the sub 12. That's all I care about that's seventh place. What's
What's fifth place
Tell me what fifth place is. I just want to know 10 16 is fifth place
I don't know if i'll get top five 10 16
Just so we're all on the same page
You speed ran bob the builder for an hour before you even considered purchasing a spiral game for the ps1
Sounds about right. I think
I'll take seven place lucky number seven. That's fun. Let's move on
All right coming up next
Oh, that's a good one, too
This one could go pretty hard
Uh, i've had a bunch of requests to play this
And I think we're just gonna
Go for it
You have to submit the run
oh, um
I don't think maybe I don't know
Uh, so we got
I want you to pick between two uh, two things
Pick between looney tunes back in action
Or scooby-doo night of a hundred frights
That's your choice
Uh scooby-doo or looney tunes
Looney tunes back in action or scooby-doo night of a hundred frights. He's gonna be very popular
I knew it
We definitely need to pull though because I can't decide. I mean we're gonna do both but
I've seen a lot of scooby-doos
All right. Yeah, I got it. I think I can do it. Wait. I created a moment. Oh because the speed run
Uh, okay. I got it up right now
Scooby-doo. So what you want is scooby-doo
Or looney tunes
How do you spell looney tunes like you?
Yeah, all right, you got two minutes content does not meet the guidelines
I don't need the guidelines
What the hell are you talking about content does not meet guidelines?
What's wrong with this what game and I wrote scooby-doo and then looney tunes?
Content does not meet guidelines
What's happening here flash poll?
Okay, minimum two quiet question what game?
responses
scooby-doo
For looney
tunes
Two minutes start poll content does not meet guidelines. What am I what what what am I not writing here? Look my you try it
Do is a bad word
Do do
Wait looney tunes. I can't write looney tunes
Huh?
Wait, what can you do it?
Just drink filk anyways
Okay, well question
What game?
How about um, like the tunes
tunes
Or scooby does that work? Wait, how did you do that?
Wait, was I spelling it wrong?
No, I was spelling it right loon. No. Oh
You can't write looney tunes without you have to do it without the e
Use a zero
Okay
All right. What what's the poll say?
Whoa, I did not even look at it until the last second. That's
77 I thought I was gonna be way closer than this. Why would I even do the poll? All right scooby-doo night of a thousand a
year door
Whatever the fuck this game is called
Go for it. Yes. I promise. I oops. I promise. I will do a scooby-doo laugh. Here we go
Later don't laugh. Okay, i'll try not to don't laugh at anything that happens with scooby-doo. I'll try
All right, I won't laugh drink pilk if you laugh, okay for how long five minutes
You guys just really want me to drink the whole game. That's okay. It's still burnt into my screen
By the way, I can see it still the bionicle text is still there
PlayStation browser and system configuration is burnt in now
If you got a scooby-doo, you want to eat a lovely scooby snack
That's a fact
Oh, that was cotton candy
I'm sorry. I'm weird today
Okay, how do you play?
Remember your favorite hot wheels car?
Well, they're now in smite
Doesn't count
Get ready for a close encounter of the scooby kind with scooby-doo and the alien invaders
Snack are the first five scooby-doo episodes ever including the series pilot in scooby-doo's original mysteries
This is spooksville
Then join the gang
And fasten your seat belts as the original screen team uncover some swashbuckling spooks in scooby-doo on zombie
villain
It's scooby-doo's spookiest tales
with the absolute kookiest creeps
Oh the kookiest creeps
Scaredy cats that's the fun as the gang goes digital
How how many of these are there
Stop scooby-doo and the cyber chase. They're all absolutely scarified
Why should you be the only one screaming so much scooby-doo
These incredible these include great features like a look behind the scenes
music videos
trivia games video bios I should get this
Scooby-doo zombie island scooby-doo alien invasion scooby-doo spookiest tale scooby-doo cyber chase
How many are there? There's like a hundred movies. That was cool. The mystery machine part one. What about pilk? I will after this
Smell that salty. You know what that means, buddy
Seafood fried clams runa fish
cracked
runa salad
jumbo shrimp
runa sushi
All right, you two don't forget the real reason we're here
The lobster bisque
No, silly we're here to solve a mystery
Ah
And she could really use our help look there she is now
Hey holly
Hey daphne
I'm so glad you could make it and you must be freddy felma shaggy and scooby-doo
Wow the whole gang i've heard so much about you daphne's kept me up to date on all of your cases
So I figured my mystery would be right up. It kind of looks like you
Mystery is famous inventor professor alexander graham
He was just about to unveil some new top secret invention when he disappeared without a trace
No one saw him leave mystic manor and no one will help me search the premises. Why are you yelling?
Don't tell me because it's haunted, right?
Yeah shaggy, how'd you know bailing out the window always haunted?
Jeepers we'll help you look around you said it daphne. We're not afraid right gang
Like me and scoop have seen this show before you guys can go poking around scaring up some spooksters
I kind of want like scooby-doo if I could make a character real for an hour
It would be scooby-doo
I think it'd be so fun
Just for an hour, okay you scaredy cats stay here if you want come on guys
Yes, the dog scooby-doo
Don't you just wouldn't you just want to eat a pizza with scooby-doo
I feel like that'd be crazy
That'd be the most unbelievable thing like that'd be crazy
Fishy pal gooby snacky
Wait
Gee scoob. It's not like they got your name all over them
I already I beat the first part
Look for more of these clues to give you hints about the area you're in the grass is always greener on the other side
Who the hell is this? You're messing up my love. Hello scooby
I will give you some tips on some of the things you will find around mystic manor
Make tracks scooby-doo. You can run faster while holding r1
jump
Some doors will need a certain number of scooby snacks to open
I gotta turn the brightness up on this though. You don't think it would be cool to have scooby-doo as like a friend for a day
But and just I just want to eat a pizza with scooby-doo and then I want him to punch me in the face as hard as he can
Uh, you know what I mean? Like it's just like I just want to throw a punch in my head
I don't know why like just like
I feel like that would never happen ever you would you only have one opportunity
It's like scooby-doo. Let's eat a pizza and then I want you to punch
I want to punch me the face as hard as you can
Like we need to see what he what like how strong he is
Do you imagine that like on like fucking tiktok?
Hey, yeah, i'm gonna eat a pizza with scooby-doo and then he's gonna punch me in the face. Why?
Why would he have to why would I want him to punch me in the face?
I don't know why I just saw like an image of him being like you're crazy. What?
You got tiktok on the mind. Why not?
Okay, don't stay on these for too long. Why do you let it go?
Why do you want this? I don't want it. I just like I had a flash
I'm just like oh
And it's just like he like clocks me in the fucking side of the head
I'm gonna turn the brightness up. It's too dark. My computer is so fucked up right now. That's a little better
That better
I need to crop it. I would but it's gonna it's way too much
It's not too hard. All right, let's go. So what do I have to go find shaggy?
Okay, cool
Can I change the camera?
Something's wrong in my game
Oh, never mind
There's a laugh track in there. There's a laugh track in the game when you do something funny
That's awesome. Okay
What the fuck I don't know about this scooby I would let go let go scooby please
Get up there. It wasn't even that funny. That was not even funny. I wonder if it's random
Have you ever done that before?
The background looks like world of warcraft it does look like a world of warcraft
Okay, we have to find shaggy looks like terrors fall glades
150 snacks
25 let's go. All right, let's do it. I'm coming
Can I is it our attack? We need to find the professor spring's invention before you can make this jump
a metroid game
What? Okay, that's cool. I'm playing this for a little while
Gooby-doo, i'm so glad you found me. It was just awful as soon as we got inside the mansion the mastermind appeared
He told us that he is behind my uncle's disappearance
Here take this map it'll help you get around a little easier
Secret
Who made this? This is awful
What was this a map? I thought it was gonna be a map of the mansion
What is this?
I can't read that. That's not helpful at all. It's like hollow knight
That bait. All right. How many snacks do I have that scared this shit out of me? Why was that so scary?
You need the professor's helmet to bash through these webs. It really is hollow knight. Where am I right now?
You're funny. I like your streams. Hey, thanks. Thanks for um hanging up
This is a secret door right here. How do I open it? You can see the outline
Where the hell I go? Here's the ps2 version records for this game by the way 26 minutes that i'm not doing that
I think you're wondering where the key is to the gate, huh? I'm pretty sure it's buried around here. I need to shovel
Here. Oh take this get to work
Thank you
I need a flower patch
first item
How do I dig?
Another 60 years and then I can retire
Maybe i'll take up your pleasure
That was kind of funny
Wait, was it the the key come out? No, I need more flowers. Is it really right here?
Keep off the grass movie keep okay. I got the key to here to smuggler's
Warp gate
Whoa, okay
This game is huge
This game is enormous
Sounds like the dynasties crowd laughter in hades
Oh, yeah, the one that goes like
So you might be wondering how I got over here so quickly
Well, never mind. I'm that is what it is spooky
Now move along holly you are right
I knew I I was like i've recognized that somehow
Where are the other characters? Where is everybody?
You can jump on top of small monsters squashers
You say rats how yummy
Scooby-doo doesn't need rats does he?
Beware scooby-doo. You need one of the professor's inventions to defeat larger monsters. How many inventions does professor have?
It's just a guy with a it's a guy it's just a guy I thought okay
Hang on to the pelican for a shortcut back. Be sure to grab all the goodies along the way
I don't want it anymore
What's in here? I'm hungry
Oh there is for a long time
New party member
Great, okay
All right, do it
Was the laugh track for that catch up with you later that was the funniest joke so far I want that snack
Nice
Dark souls
Oh, okay, I got a warp gate how much do I need to get in here 50 snacks drink pilk now
I'll drink pilk in exactly 20 minutes
I will drink pilk in exactly 20 minutes
exactly
at
Seven hours stream. I will drink pilk take this for a ride. I don't want a shortcut
Oh
Is it gonna be oat pilk
Yeah, probably
I don't have pepsi. I have coke. I have coke and oat milk. Sorry. I didn't I didn't i'm not like prepared for drinking
Pilk can't jump. Oh, you need to get the professor's
special books
Oh, I got it double jump. All right, that's huge
It's a delicacy
You want to just do it now
Be right back. I'm gonna drink i'm gonna drink some pilk. Okay, be right back. Okay. So what what is the um,
What's the ratio fucking screen is gonna burn in god. Damn it. You're right. It is shit
It is come on
All right. I gotta it's 50 50. I have to keep this. I kept looks like a screen saver
I have to keep this here. All right, so you're telling me so it's 50 50 half and half
So if I take some oat milk, it's oat milk, i'm sorry and just fill it up a little halfway
I'm gonna prove this is milk like that
Ah
The vibration is on the controller. Did you hear that? It's doing it still
Did you got I don't know if you even heard it. Did you hear that?
That was horrible. My whole body hurts
Okay, here you go. I've got here is the milk right here it is. So now we take the coca cola
I thought something just bad happened. I thought like my ceiling caved in
Okay
Here we go
People drink this
Do I need to stir it? She needs to that's so much. That is so much. I didn't realize I just made it a lot
I just made it as if I love this and i'm gonna drink it all the time every day. That's a full glass
I'm gonna fucking break it get away from me. Stop
That's a lot
Oh, I have to drink this. Okay. Here we go
Okay, it tastes like
you know when you have a
Float like a root beer float or a coke float
And you get to the very very bottom but there's nothing left in the glass
But there's a little bit of this weird foam fluid down there
That's what this tastes like
I mean, it's not that good
But I wouldn't consider this to be bad
I wouldn't say this is bad
This does not this does not taste bad
You guys are gonna get me so fucked up now i'm gonna just wait i'm gonna drink this like tomorrow and the next day
And the next day i'll be like, yeah, i'm just doing it ironically
Same shit's gonna happen to me
But like takis
I bought takis. I tried them. I told you guys they were the world most disgusting vile snack i've ever eaten
And now I can't stop eating them
I seriously thought takis were a zero
zero
and
I just was like, oh, haha. I think me and holly were literally at the grocery store. It's like oh
Let's get those. Isn't that funny?
Yeah, they're gross. They suck. I haven't had them in a while. You wanna try one?
and then we both go like
That lime's kind of good though
Gross I hate you hate them too. I hate them too
and then
Ever since I bought them every time
I've ever gone to the grocery store since it's not an ironic funny joke anymore
Just doing it and I just enjoy it and I like it
What's wrong with me?
It's not good. Like I just it's not good
But it's definitely not the reaction. I think a lot of people thought was gonna happen where i'm like
Like spitting it. No, it's like fine
It tastes like fizzy milk
It tastes like carbonated milk
But sweet
It's like the bottom of a root beer float. It's just like whatever you have serious problems
You're gaslighting yourself
Yeah, it's the bottom of a root beer float. You if you know if you know, you know
I would not recommend drinking this for any reason unless it's like somebody bet you and they're like, oh dude drink
It'll be funny. This shit is fucking cold though
This shit is gold
This is the good shit. I'm telling you. This is the good shit
You want you want do you want to drink gold milk? Get it telling you this is the good shit
This that this is a it's a delicacy in this household
All right. Let me let me bring this back. I don't want to put it in the fridge
Let's see what we do gonna get burnt into this
And i'm done look at this why is it vibrating show what on the screen is happening for it to be vibrating show me
What is going on on screen to have to have a vibrate the controller that hard?
God, I need a break
That's a good break
It's scooby scratching
All right. So what can I do with the double jump?
Sue's drunk on pill
Jump off the boat with a double jump
Thank you for playing these even if you had to skip vampire countdown. I mean
I like just kind of jumping on random shit for like an hour or so
These these place these old kind of grab bag
You never know what you're gonna get if you be anything we could get absolute dog shit or we get a fucking legendary
Bionicle game, you know what I mean?
Can I not go this way?
Oh, I thought that was it. All right, so let's go in the boat and somebody's a jump off the boat
All right, there was something I couldn't reach before right
Happy always told me you plant where should I go?
How is that not reaching
And it's not reach i'm touching it
What does scooby do his favorite food do we know is it a scooby snack
Has it actually ever been?
Decided what it is
Is it scooby snacks? I feel like that's so I feel like that's easy though
Oh, it's like a crunchy like dog treat
It's not like a lasagna
No, that's that stupid fucking little shit cat. Whatever that other one, you know, whatever is
Green orange, whatever
Green cat
How do you grab I can't grab onto this uh seagull whatever the hell how do you grab
Why do you hate garfield so much?
Um, I don't hang on to the pelican for a shortcut. How do I grab the pelican?
Okay. All right
Okay, where I go
Stop can't i'm about to take it up. I'm about to press the button. Nope. Where is this bird?
I'm just going back
All right, if somebody ran for congress and they just had a scooby-doo avatar and they did the voice
Do you think they would win here food doesn't grow on trees
Do you think that they would actually win?
What if they had like good policy?
I feel like it'd be kind of funny
That's a black mirror episode. That is a black mirror episode. Fuck. What a great show. This one was 150
Rip off randy rip off randy. I didn't rip anybody. Oh just fell off during season five
I actually haven't even watched it since probably like season two season three
What was even in here? Oh my monster collection
This was not why did I spend 150 bucks on this I don't have any monsters there's a hundred no
Not the game
The scooby snacks this game was not 150
You bought this for it. No, I did not how many I think this game was like five dollars
Mm-hmm. It was a little more than that. I have the double jump I can jump across
How much all right? It was 20 bucks. Okay
Worth it
It was worth it
I got a token
Yes, this was this was 20 dollars
Okay, oh I can go up here now
Uh
Lying son of a gun. It's 100. This was not 100. Why would I lie about something so stupid?
Holy shit, that was pretty good. All right under the chandelier
shit
How do I get up there? What do you do with the token? The tokens just sit in your inventory?
Because I can't get in here
I try to I press the mute button. I try to press the mute button over here. I don't think I can do anything else
Cool
I need the headbutt. I don't have the headbutt. Where can I get the headbutt?
Where did it not go? There's a key outside you can double jump to sick. Thank you
The outside I can't believe you've been playing this for seven full hours. It's a good game
Okay, somebody said I can jump to a key that's somewhere out here. Where is it the playground? There's a gap in the mansion
I don't think there's anything over here
Gap in the mansion
You mean like outside though, right? What's the name of the current game? This is scooby-doo night of a hundred rights
That's it was not very good. I think I got a lot of
Something settled. I don't know what's settled if it was the coke or the oat milk, but something settled
Gap in the mansion
All right, we're moving on
This is fun
This is a cool one
This is cool. It was right there
Hey, I just had knee surgery. Can you do uh, can you do Velma?
Oh wait, that's knee surgery guy knee surgery guy. Did you had surgery and you and you woke up?
That's knee surgery guy. That was like seven hours ago, wasn't it?
How'd it go? Did it go good? Oh, this key is right here. How did how did it go?
Another helmet
That was weird
Dig the flower dig the flower. Okay
Yikes
It was a sandwich, why did I come back for this? I thought that was an npc
He's hungry
Just get hit by every single enemy. You're the target audience for youtube shorts
I don't think I am because I don't really watch them
I can't
I can't do it
That's a small enemy spider. That's not a big enemy
Here are two of the professor's inventions the slippers and the lampshade you can use the slippers to sneak quietly past monsters
By holding r2 or the lampshade to hide from monsters by holding r2
Use your new lampshade and slippers to avoid the zombie
Where's the
Please
Hey, dude, your editors have been doing zoom in on your face thing
Oh, that's like I
Have been doing the zoom in on your face thing. I know exactly what you are talking about
I know exactly what that means
Oh fuck i'm alive
What happened? What did I do?
Oh, I got hit by a dart. All right
One more try and i'm putting another game in
This game's fun, though
It's very nice
I could see being a big fan of the show and playing this when I was a kid
Now we're an adult. Whatever it is. This is very cool
Very nice game. It's very enjoyable. We're gonna move on
Get out of the way you just walk in the way
Ruby
Ruby snacks
I I understand this map, but it still confuses me when I look at it
You gotta play spyro for the surgery guy. Is that what the is that what the knee surgery guy said?
Where did you get that?
Help help help i'm helping
Cookies
Oh, they were shooting
All right, i'm moving on i'm moving on we're gonna do another one we'll do one more try in this and i'm gonna do
These are so bad
Has anybody ever heard of this game?
Largo winch have you ever played this
Largo winch
I looked at the it looked fun
Do looney tunes. We'll do looney tunes after that
Please please what?
Robbie
Wait, wait, what toy story? Wait, wait, wait, wait that we we have we have we have the knee surgery friend
You're a play toy story through the video game play toy story through the video game play toy story through the video game
Please please please toy story through the video game. I I don't have it
How was surgery?
Wait, that's not knee surgery guy. Oh
Who's that?
Why did I just read that? Who was that?
Who's this?
Oh, it's the person that said please. Oh, okay
I'm curious. I want to know what's in here. I need to know what's inside of here
We said well, we had we did have a raid. We did we did a big raid
That's a lot of people snuffy. Thanks for the raid snuffy. Appreciate it. Have you showered ice shower? Yeah
Welcome everybody. What's up?
Today, uh, oh snuffy. Hope you had a good stream
What was snuffy doing? What's not be done when we look at your armpits shut up
Hey, dove raid came in. I need to relax. Hey, welcome raiders have a
Beautiful evening. It is a nice day today
And no, you cannot see my fucking armpits
What would I want to know what stuff he was playing?
I asked a question
Nobody told me anything
Nobody said anything
funny videos, oh sick
Ah, welcome, uh, we're doing old playstation 1 playstation 2 omega night. This is an omega weekend
What that means is uh, i'm just not turning this off until I feel like it
We're not gonna be playing scooby-doo the whole time so don't leave please don't leave
We're gonna be playing. Uh, in fact something really interesting next come on
That was a cake holy shit
All right. I'm gonna get through this section and then we'll change to the next one
Like the spy game
This is actually kind of a fun platformer
What did I play recently that I actually the crash bandicoot game, right?
It was like a crash remake or crash four. What what was that? That was very good. That was very fun
That was exceptionally fun
Crash four. Yeah
That was really fun. You should finish it. Maybe one day
Oh
All right, that's fun, let's go this one I I this game's part of the argo winch
commando
Find out very interested. I'm just as interested as you are
Called largo winch
I've never heard of this before until literally
Like maybe four days ago
Five days ago. What's for dinner? Um, that's a good question. I don't know
hmm
Be soft game
Oh, yeah based on the tv series largo winch adapted from the cartoon
What?
This is tv show
Okay
All right
Let's go
I'm getting out of play. Hmm
Welcome to the construction site largo when you're ready come and join me inside use the directional button on the left analog to walk
This game's very crunchy
We're a little late. So let's race to the port of the cabin
You're on
Hold on r2 to run
I can hear this game in my teeth
Well, that got my circulation going
Let me show you how to use objects walk up to the button and press x
That was I just punched
I don't know. I don't know how to do it press the button
No
Good. Remember to use any object press x button
Unfortunately, this button seems to be broken
We don't have the time to wait to get it fixed so you'll have to do it yourself
what
Try this toolkit pick it up. Just walk over it and then try pressing x button on the switch again
Why do I walk a waddle around like I made it a fucking clay?
Okay, I got a toolkit
Pick up the toolkit by walk. I just did it
Did you not just watch me do that?
Very good. You're learning fast to see what objects you have in your possession press select
Okay
Cool bare hands
Sometimes you'll have to search other objects to get them this door needs a security car to open it
There's one in that desk. Did you just cut me off when I was in the middle of doing it?
I was doing it
What
Fuck out of here
I'm just kidding with you. I'm just messing around
Hey, you locked me out
Make your way around the side. I'll see you later
Don't get stuck in this game
Climb over any obstacle
Good to know I would have I never would have figured that out
You want to watch out for the
Excavation run up to it and then jump over it using triangle. Don't miss though. It's a long way down
oops
Mid-jump you gotta I think I can fucking make it
I can I can make it I can I can I can I can I can
I've got a prediction. I think this might be the gem of the night. I'm just saying
I'm just saying I think this has got
Unbelievable potential and I mean unbelievable potential
The versus has a nine on their back. What is that?
Practice punching and kicking. There's a kick
Oh, that is not a kick that it that is a like
a post-op
Oh, I can't wait to play this
Okay, you will find blocking to be very useful in any fights you get into
I think I okay block
Will you do something?
He's not fighting
He's not
Kick his ass. I'm supposed to be blocking a punch. He just won't punch punch me, please
What
How do I stop looking at this guy?
Wait, I go the wrong way
Where
Where are we right now?
Where are we? This is a strange what?
It's like dirt wood concrete
What is going on?
It's a construction site
This looks just weird. It's just a weird place
How do I get the hell out of here? He said follow me follow you to follow you where?
Can you open this open the door?
to the ring
his foot ring
Down the ramp
I physically could not walk down there a minute ago. I was running into invisible wall
combos
With his back to you as joe teach you how to knock guards unconscious
Further away is Morgan with whom you can try out everything you've learned
You won't kill a guard with this move
Good. That's not my style. Anyway
I know however, he'll be out cold for a while
So I don't need to worry about him waking up while i'm still around
Correct one more thing if you're going to pull this move off the guard has to be totally unaware of your presence
Okay
combo
Yeah, all right 100 of this. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. All right. I'm ready
And try out all the skills you've learned
He's not going to show any mercy
All right, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Okay
Sneak into the factory
No, i'm not nearly as stealthy as you. I got the blueprints the details the pro route
All right, fuck off. Is there a heel? Okay. Hold down r1 to sneak use the brain wave monitor
This guard isn't looking in your directions. He's sneakers
Okay
You can peer around corners by holding l2
And use the controls, okay
Okay, so what's okay crouches r1?
Is he looking over here? Where can I leave?
What are you talking? No, no game over not game over that the guy's looking this way and this way
He's looking this way and this way. He's looking the same direction
The fuck is this guy?
Oh my god. All right. All right. All right
This might be causing the crackling the disk speed thing. Oh, is it spinning too fast?
Here's this guy
Whoa, okay
Don't peek your head out like that. Stop. All right. So how can I tell when this guy can it can see me?
He's looking like this and then he's looking like this
What direction is he looking?
Because to on to me he's looking in the same direction. Oh my god. He's looking at me. Oh my god
Is this a sex game fan that person for like 10 minutes?
Shadows are your friend. Okay, you can hide in them. Where is this person?
Yeah, I quit I let me play I let me find one of the stealth shit let me play the game
Wait, I think I fucked the game up. I'm good
I yeah, I messed it up
Okay, they beep at regular intervals. What just happened? That was very wait
Uh something got messed up here
What why was he right behind me? I don't need to do the training anymore. I'm done. I know I know
I know how to play the game. Okay, I don't need to do this anymore
Fuck oh, okay. What happened?
The shocking scene before you is that of the appalling situation that has developed at the opening of the w chemical factory here in venezuela
The south american redemption have taken over the building but insists their intentions are peaceful
I can see now the head of the w group lago winch being escorted alongside our very own tanio conocova
Who was sent to interview lago winch earlier today?
This is an important development if they release the head of the w corporation it shows they definitely are peaceful
So what do I have to do?
This is an ai voice
Another shocking development it appears a lago and tanio are being held hostage
What
What wait, okay. I saw I gotta get in there lago lago. Come on
What's wrong joy?
Simon lago has been kidnapped by operatives from the south american redemption. He'll be okay joy
He's been in situations like this before if anyone can escape lago can
I hope you're right find out
Okay, this is where the game begins. I'm ready. What oh can I
I'll get you out of here. Can I untie?
No
Is there no I probably need like a thing
I must find a way to get the power back on in here the fuse missing my tool kit
No punch the ropes. I swear i'll figure it out. Wait, maybe I can go inside this car
Maybe I'll get a car battery
Yeah, I think I can okay elevator should work
I don't know how to get out of here
I thought I didn't think that was an elevator. I have to be honest
Why would I just leave that person gone? That's a gun. Oh, it's a radio
They're not peaceful at all. They planted a bomb inside the main building somewhere. You have to find it and defuse it
Do I have to who am I gonna stop these people?
I think you got too much coffee
I have no idea what he said
What the fuck are you gonna do about it?
Oh shit
Turn around and face him
Fuck christ. We're good. Go. Nope
I'll go they've got the main doors locked down. There's no way through find another way around. Okay. Well, thanks for the info
Here he spent four hundred dollars on this. No, this one was seven bucks
Don't fucking knock me out, please
What the fuck are you talking about?
No, I need i'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Okay, I can't go in the main door. Where the hell is this other door?
I'm gonna stop these people
Classic, you know what? No, fuck this
Just run
Why would I fight anybody?
This guy nobody has a gun
How do I get out of here?
What's the where where is this person going the window?
Oh shit
They were doing that on purpose
He was npc walking and the other guy wasn't gonna ambush me get up there get up there
Shit, I can go up there. I can get up there. I can get up there. I can get up there
I can get up. I can get up there. I'm just gonna i'm just running
This game is terrible. I mean, it's it's I it's charming to me
I am very charmed by this. I have no we're not doing not next game. Not yet
No, not yet
I am not changing games until I get a like two by four or like a gun or something. You know what I mean?
I ain't just gonna
We're not just moving on not yet. Not worth it
Okay, so where was that?
I gotta go stop these people straight
We need to hear him talk some more. You don't think we need to hear like at least another 10 minutes of conversations
Okay, i'm going
Uh-huh. We're gonna now we're gonna do about it. Can I kick him in the head?
Why did I not knock him what I didn't knock him out don't you dare I took me so long to get here
I think i'm safe
You're very close to the bomb. You have to you have you've got you got anything you can use to defuse it
Yes, joy. It's all under control. I don't have anything. I have now. I have a minute
Get out of my way get out of my way
I'm gonna fucking punch this guy in the face as hard as I can
Why?
I only have 37 seconds
Where's the bomb?
Where is it?
There it is
Oh, how do I defuse it?
Mr vinch
Unfortunate business in venezuela last week. I hear nothing. I can't handle miss fritz. What can I do for you?
I'd like to make you an offer for the chemical factory. Isn't it considered a high-risk investment by your people?
Nothing we can't handle. Do you intend to sell? No, miss fritz. I do not intend to sell
I'm a powerful woman. Mr. Vinch. You may regret saying no to me
I don't have any idea what just happened
Was he talking to me?
I mean the playstation 1 card not the playstation 2 you would regret saying no to me
See what I mean?
No, I just want to sit on my couch. Oh, you're you're going to sell all of your stock to me. No, I don't know
Just leave me alone. I just want to just I just want to sit on the couch and watch tv
I want nothing to do with this. I wonder what she's planning. Yes. I'm here i'm going on an excursion
I want to find out what motivated the sar to attack my factory last week. Well, I owned the factory
That was my factory
Who was the person that was wait? I owned that factory. He hates us what?
You were beating up your own guards
Okay, largo need to find some information on the sar. There should be a safe at the top floor. Try to find your way up there
Largo, this is strictly covert operation. Don't let anyone see you and that includes cameras
All right. Well, what are we playing next?
Don't let anyone see you
This is oh, this is
awful
Pivot to looney tunes. There's a looney tunes after this
Pivot to looney tunes this person looking over here pivot pivot. Hold on. No, no, no, no, no
Hey you why can I punch? Why can I punch him? Oh, it's because i'm holding the computer in my hand
Pivot pivot. All right. All right. I'll pivot. We're gonna pivot. We're gonna pivot. This game is so funny though
Like it's so good. How do I put this down?
I can't put the computer down
Yeah, I can't put the computer down. All right, we're playing looney tunes looney tunes back in action coming up
Let me pee one more time
And i'll come right back. I am back probably going to
Call it after looney tunes. I think that's a good place to do it after like eight nine hours or so
Yeah, it's gonna burn in isn't it? It is it's okay
It's all right. Uh, this is looney tunes back in action
You can do more infomercials. Yeah, definitely. I just don't I don't want to go too late pacific
Oh shit. I never played this game. Is this game good? I never played it. You're gonna stream tomorrow
I think so. I think that's the plan. We'll see either tomorrow or monday. That means no. No, i'll be live tomorrow
Okay, abc
Play traffic attack play right? Yeah, I did I got xbox to do as well now. I have a question for you guys tomorrow
Do you want more ps1?
Ps2 or do you want to do some xbox tomorrow? What do you think you want to get a poll up xbox?
Or more ps2 ps1. That's what we'll do tomorrow. How about half and half we could
Soon the whole world will be helpless before me watch as I transform you into my singing sways with this
the magical blue monkey diamond elmer fudd is
Robotnik if I have anything to say about it evil doer
Prepare to suffer the righteous fury of my over five fomley tex muscles
The girls love them
Hold it
What do you mean hold it? Don't you want to see my righteous fury? It's really righteous
Daffy i'm afraid you're just not action star material
This guy I guess we know what 65 years of loyal service is worth in this town
Thanks a lot. Mr. Moral support
Hmm
It's a smash hit I love it xbox to think I already went out of pocket for this prop diamond
Five bucks at the pawn shop why it's the real blue monkey diamond
Okay, so it's not an original concept but this guy looks like the real the car accident guy last I found me industries
I began by taking over the studio that gave my company such a bad name
And now with this diamond I can turn everyone into monkeys and conquer the world starting with the two of you
A hollywood executive who's secretly evil should we be surprised?
Nah, but the mask was a nice touch
Well, that wasn't supposed to happen
I
What is daffy gonna be in multiverses I want it so bad you up for saving the world things worth a fortune
Get back here you little lifetime of total financial security
You just didn't even get a sentence out
That was I I don't think we've ever heard him do that. All right. Acme mailboxes are everywhere
These are checkpoints
Oh my god, that was actually okay. Cool
Checkpoint grab as much money as you can you're gonna need it. What is here for a weapon?
Ooh, it's a pan
It is a pan. It's like a big boiling of a pot
Okay. Well, that's the edge
Collect seven acme bird seeds
Oh, okay
Why did I I why did they go all the way over there?
Qte, no
That was a tourist watch out
It's like the mario 64 bunny bullshit
Do a daffy impression?
I will with the camera off. I'm not doing it on cam
those cheap skates
That's my diamond
And that's why
You're gonna get smacked in the face
Stop thief
I'm not doing that with a camera on I would rather show my penis on stream
I wouldn't actually not at all. I would rather do that on camera. Oh they got him
Why did you say that I don't know
Because I just really don't want to I didn't want to do that on because you know how weird it i'm gonna i'm gonna look
I'm gonna be mid daffy impressions. I'm just gonna get a screenshot and it's gonna be whatever people can put it everywhere
But if well, how would me not hold on a minute? I'm i'm very confused at what I just said if I showed my dick
That would be everywhere
Why am I so concerned? Well, i'm less concerned about like people spreading that
Why would I be less concerned? Well, I don't know my the logic. I don't have any logic for you. I don't know why
I have no idea what logic that was
No, they'll spread it because I have a funny face and they'll make like memes about it
What do you think would happen if you did the other thing? What do you think is going to happen?
How do I do that?
Rent a hula costume 50 50 dollars
Wait, what is that?
What is going on in here
I didn't distract him
So he's dancing with me did he just say bazinga that was bazinga
He's got a rare bazinga
What character is this supposed to be this is a weird looking character who is that
Who is this?
I'm innocent. I tell you
No
I'll get it. You're terrible
I got it. Don't worry
We are dancing get out of the way. I love porky's porky's dance. I like it better
Do the looney tunes where do they live at the center? I don't know what you're talking about
Or is that motherfucker?
Oh
What just happened to my character got no gratitude what just happened I don't understand what I just did wrong
For crying out loud
All right, so is everybody aggro is on to you does nobody's friendly everybody just everybody's aggressive
Oh I got it
Not as big of me, of course, but a star nonetheless
Gee, you try to they're just here. I'm doomed
I could bash all those wanted duck posters to pieces and make you a free duck
Yeah, okay. You're a genius. Thanks
I'll wait right here for you until all those posters are done. Hey big ears. You're
So start tumbling careful they'll throw us out
Wanted for what dinner
Smash the wanted posters over here. There's ten of these things. Oh, this is the lady that goes
Right unless that's a different character
No
Three no, you did it, right? Oh, I know what it wants me to do
What's that it's true that carrots are good for you
Any daffy posters are one is roll
Ooh cool
Do not money every little bit helps a lot of gold
Wonder if he was wanted before the whole acme thing or just after
Shining cool
I could see playing this game. This game's fun
I can't reach you. Well, golly the movie star sure are short and thanks for all your support trudy is
For this I left to pick
Yeah, that's all folks don't be so
Yep back in action looney tunes back in action
There another uh
Did I miss a daffy?
I love this guy
You see
Okay. Sure. I'll guess i'll take one when it comes to brains. You don't miss the bus boy. No more monkey
You sure drive a hard bargain
Do his voice
Oh, no. No, I said no. I said no. No tell you something. I said
I'm done. I'll see you guys tomorrow. I'm out of here. I'm fucking leaving
I'm leaving. I'll see you guys tomorrow
I'm kind of tired. I want some food. All right tomorrow. We'll do some xbox
Uh starting probably around the same time around two o'clock. That was what I love doing this
You know what the best part about doing this is there's just no pressure for any of these to be any good
It's just like yeah throw one in does it suck? Who cares? This is gonna be another one in like 30 minutes
I love the grab bag. It's fun and there's a shitload still to do so
We'll do some xbox tomorrow probably opening with the the matrix. I've owned the matrix
Video game enter the matrix
For at least a year or two and I haven't played it
So I really want to play it so we'll be doing we'll start with that around two o'clock pacific time
See you guys later. Yeah, I don't want to go. We're already going kind of late crossing that threshold of
1 a.m
Eastern so it's getting late
Yeah, if I went any longer
Let's say if I just I probably would have played this for like another 45 minutes or so hour
Uh, I probably would have tried to come up with an excuse for you guys of oh, you know, uh tomorrow
I did I just stream for 10 hours. So nah
No, i'll just come back tomorrow get some sleep. It's 6 a.m. That is very late. Honestly favorite game of the night
That's a tough one. I don't know. I have to look what do we play like 10 things
Bargo winch was probably the worst one. I like scooby-doo
Oh bionicle bionicle was fun. Oh bob the builder was pretty hog. Yeah, I just said that i'm sorry
Yeah
All right. I'll see you guys later. Thanks for watching get some sleep. We'll see you tomorrow. Take care of yourselves call your mother
See you later