How you doing? I'm here. I'm here. I'm just finishing up something.
Come on, don't don't dot dot dot me in a minute after starting the stream. I'm here. Trust me,
I'm here. I also had a dream about the stream, by the way, which is very important. I forgot,
I don't remember what the context was. I don't remember what it was. Something really embarrassing
happened. I don't, I was in, I was on camera and I was sitting here playing a game or something
and the first part is gone. But the second part is I remember I was so embarrassed by something,
like a really like, like not funny joke or something like that. And I like, I like went,
like pretended to think something on stream was funny. Like, oh shit, that joke didn't go well.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, or something like that. And I just, I went like, oh my God,
what do I do? What do I do? So I like pretended to like fall forward and go like, oh, whoops,
I fell. And I was like on camera. You could see like in the monitor, like I was like down,
like I wasn't, I was off camera and I was like, oh guys, I fell down down here. Yeah. Oh man,
I'm gonna have to turn the stream off. I like fell down and everyone said I was full of shit.
Like the chat was like, liar, like full of shit. Get back on cam, liar, liar. And I thought,
I thought I did a pretty good job of like selling it. That like, oh, I fell down,
but like in my mind, I was like, this didn't, they didn't buy it. So now I did something that
people didn't like, but like I told a joke that people thought wasn't funny. So I tried to like
run away from the stream by pretending to fall down and like get hurt. And that was a disaster
because everyone here was like, no fucking way, liar. So that was a double embarrassment. And I
was like, what do I do now? Like, what am I, what am I even supposed to do right now? And then I
woke up. Imagine if like, I made a joke that was so bad that I pretended to fall out of the chair.
Oh yeah, guys, I fell down out of the chair. Like I'm hurt. I have to leave.
Anyways, he's going to do that this stream. No, it's funny because I have fallen out of the chair
like two or three years ago. I fell down on stream on the New Year's Eve stream from two years ago.
And it's not like, oh, I have to turn the stream off. I was, I was, I was fine.
Anyways, I was going to stream yesterday, but I kind of felt like shit. I'm honest.
I still kind of have a headache. I had a bad like migraine like headache yesterday.
And I didn't want to turn the stream on. And then in an hour, just be like,
sorry guys, I got to go. Cause that's happened before. So I figured why not just go today.
I feel better. I do feel, I feel better. I don't want to overdo it though.
So we'll see how I feel in a few hours. So I'm imagining we'll, we'll, we'll take a look,
see how I'm doing in like three to fourish hours right now. So I'll give you the plan.
The plan is as follows. Take notes day one today, this week. Well, it's technically the weekend,
but you know, whatever this seven day period of, you know, I haven't streamed in two or three days.
That's what we start our new period, our new streaming period. Today we're going to do
dinosaur fossil hunter for as long as I think it's fun. It looks pretty good. Actually,
it actually looks fun. Uh, after that, some point in the next couple of days,
we're going to play later alligator kind of a point and click puzzle game. Cute. Looks really
cute. It's really fun. Looks really interesting at some point, somewhere in the middle there,
or on that stream. I don't know. I'm going to play the house of the dead remake. That game
is literally like 40 minutes, so I could probably do that at any point that I feel like it. And then
at some point this weekend, we're going to do some horror stuff. More of those little
short one to two hour horror games. I got blood wash and murder house. That's going to be this
weekend. There's your plan for the week. Excellent. Are you going to finish inscription? I am not
going to finish inscription on stream. I've got to, I've got to tell you something. I've done
something. I've, I played it off stream already. Yep. I already did. Sorry guys. I did. I did get
to the, I got to the third part. I have not continued since then without us. Yeah. Well,
some games, some games I would rather do off stream. I already, I talked about this for a little
bit, but let's go over it again. A lot of games that require a lot of focus and paying attention
and do, don't fuck up this hand because you're going to have to start over.
I really don't do well with those games on stream. My brain is just too, I can't, I'm just too
scattered talking to chat, looking over here, looking over there, looking over here. And then
I'm like, oh shit, there's a guy that I'm playing a game. I have a lot of trouble with that. So I
would rather just play those kinds of games off stream. And by the way, I've, it was, it was,
it was pretty cool. It was pretty cool. I haven't beat the whole thing, but I got to the third part
and at the, okay, I'll be honest though. I got to give you my honest, what happened.
I got to the third part of inscription and kind of went, this is fucking cool, but I don't,
I don't know if, I don't know. I like, don't want to do it again. Does that, does that make sense?
Does anybody, does that make sense? When I say that, when I say like, I don't want to do it again,
I don't mean like the game. I mean like, I don't want to like do it again. Right. It's really cool
though. And when I say do it again, like, yeah, I don't want to, I don't want to, the games,
the game is crazy. I don't want to like spoil anything when anybody hasn't played it,
but I'm going to finish it. I'm more, I'm, I'm assumed that's the last or third part of the game.
I don't know if there's a fourth or fifth part of the game, but I know that I'm at like a third
portion of it. I don't want to do it again. You know what I mean? I don't want to do it again.
That's all you need to know. Anyway, so that, okay, that's your plan for the week. Oh, also
something important that I want to make sure everyone is aware of this too. So if you ever go
to an arcade, there's one real, we were talking in pre-stream about this, by the way, if you don't,
if you don't know, if you don't know anything about this stream, I show up to my stream 10
to 20 minutes late every single time, but I'm chatting in the pre-stream chat 20 to 30 minutes
before the stream starts every time. So I kind of, I kind of fuck myself over in a way because like,
I will hang out in chat for like 20 minutes before the stream and then I'll go get ready and I'll
those 20 to 30 minutes is how, where the stream starts. Right? So anyways, we were talking about
arcades and something that I think is really important for you to understand is that there's
only one way for you to understand if you're in a real arcade or not. Forget about like, oh,
what do you mean an arcade? No, just listen. If the arcade has the point blank arcade cabinet,
rest assured, you're in a real arcade. You can be like, all right, I'm in a real arcade.
That is the only way to tell, by the way, if they serve high strength alcohol, that what?
That's my, that's my determination, determine if I'm in a real arcade or not. You're gatekeeping
arcades. No, I'm just, everybody has their own version of what they consider to be like, all
right, I know this is, I'm in a place where I'm going to enjoy myself. This is a real arcade for
me. For me, it's point blank. For you, it might also be the X-Men arcade machine with six slots
that have the six slots on it. And it's two TVs, two big TVs are connected in the middle to each
other. And one of them is way fucking brighter than the other one and has way more contrast
and looks wicked fucked up. I know that's probably your indicator, but I have my own indicator.
That's my way to tell full story, bro. And don't even tell me, Oh dude, no, if it has an air hockey
machine. Oh my God, that's please. An air hockey machine is how an arcade wants you to think
they're a real arcade, right? They put that in there like, yeah, dude, we got air hockey here.
No, excuse me. That's like the way to make you think that it's a real arcade. What about house
of the dead? Oh, that's right. I'm going to play house of the dead as well. Wait, I already said
that. Air hockey hater. Okay. Casino Andy. Point blank is a light gun machine from like 20 years
ago. It's not a slot machine. I would understand that argument. If I just told you, dude, you know
what I really love in the arcades? Just throwing dice in the air and hoping that I get a money
after I do it. Huh? I said a point blank. It's a light gun game. If there's a bowling alley there,
you know what bowling up a bowling alley? I think is Adam. Not a fan of that. We could spend a lot
of time doing this. I don't want to spend that much time doing this, but bowling alley being
in your arcade. That's just less room for arcade machines. In my opinion. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's just how I personally feel. If you've got a, if you've got like 20 lanes of bowling
and it's like two thirds of your entire floor and the rest is an arcade. Oh man. You could have had,
you could have had point blank one, two and three 20. I don't know. What about a roller rink? What
about a go-kart track? Remember you're gaslighting a lot of people. I'm not, I'm just telling you my
opinions. Okay. I didn't say you have to believe this too. I just said, I think I personally,
what I believe. What about a wrestling ring? That would be ridiculous. By the way, this is this,
this is the music I've been listening to this whole time. I think that's why I'm so ready to
tell you this. This has been blasting in both of my ears. What about laser tag? Look laser tag is
fine. Bowling alleys are fine. But if I go to the website and I look at the pictures of your
floor that you have and you do this, a bunch of like real estate angles to try to make the bathroom
look bigger than it looks, right? Like, oh, here's our arcade section. And it's like, whoa, look at
how big that looks. But there's like fucking eight machines there. No, like, okay. If you have enough
cabinets where it's like, all right, you've got enough arcade machines. Sure. Throw a bowling
alley in there if you want to. But if you call yourself an arcade and you got like fucking eight
arcade cabinets, I think that has to be a threshold. I'm sorry. This is the weirdest rant. It's not.
This is the German on eight five fucking whatever podcasts, but we just kind of talk about whatever
and it like zooms in on like the iTunes store that zooms in on like, like 40 reviews.
And, and I've got like two and a half stars and the podcast is like a hundred bucks,
but whatever podcast and the first like the most highly rated review or whatever is just like,
this guy didn't even talk about anything important. He got to the section where he was talking about
like how many arcade cabinets you have to have to be like the threshold to be allowed to be an arcade.
And I stopped listening and I requested a refund. Anyways, put the face cam on. All you face cam
Andes. I didn't even tweet this. Did I? Did I tweet this? I thought I did. I guess not. Okay.
Well, there you go. Tweet. Tweet done. I got to use my Twitter more. It's so bad. It really is.
I need to do more tweets rather than I'm live.
But like, I don't want to, okay. I have a huge draft of tweets. I just write tweets and I don't
do, I just think that people are going to think I'm an idiot. This is, I'm going to read you every
few months we do this. I'm going to read you my drafts. Okay. No, no, no. Stop it. What, what you
doing my Wellington? No. What? Stop it. Stop. You donkey. What you doing? No. What you, my Wellington.
That's the last thing I wrote down. And then I don't know what this one is. This one says
wrestling referees are video game AI. I think you can probably break that one down.
Um, and then the next one is, I guess, I guess this one lost arc came out.
The only arc I care about is Noah's arc. Get out of my mentions and into a Bible.
I don't know what that one was about. Sometimes I just read, I don't know. Sometimes I just write
these down, but then like I only publish like going live at 6 PM. If it makes you feel better,
everyone already thinks you're an idiot. Read that now. That lost arc came out like five months
ago. It's not going to be relevant at all. Maybe when there's DLC, I'll do it. Who cares?
The game came. I'm not. Okay. That would be like making it. It's so irrelevant. I can't.
It's too irrelevant. Next game. I haven't even started playing. By the way, I, for a second,
I thought this was like a roast beef. I forgot what game this was. I was like, oh,
this guy's got like a whole pot roast here. All right. Stop it. Let's go. You guys ready?
I'll turn, I'm going to turn it off if you're good. Only if you guys are good.
Okay. So this is a game where you go. I was going to say you hunt dinosaurs,
but that's not what you do. Here with games presents dinosaur fossil hunter. Okay.
It's fully voice acted. By the way, the wind is fucking crazy right now. Can you hear that?
Wild right now. It's crazy here right now. All right. I already did some of these controls, but
here it's fucked up. It actually sounds like, it actually sounds like I'm going to like get blown
over. Oh, happy mother's day to all the mothers out there. Oh, by the way, call your mother,
please call your mother. Is that good? I got to put both headphones in. I might want to turn it
up. Art Andy and that guy permanently. I never want to see his fucking name ever again for a
minute. Okay. Let's go. All right. So this is my, is this my museum? Okay. Controls, tip panels,
prestige roadmap. What is the prestige road? I can't even open it. Okay. Left and right. Okay.
Your museum sucks. No, it doesn't actually. Is it T-Rex? I thought the T-Rex was way bigger than
this. And this here is like 50 feet tall. Cool. It's 50 feet tall. Okay. So I think this is where
I gotta go. Museum workshop. Okay. I think this is probably a tutorial. Platinum patron of science,
Kendra. Gold patron of science, Jack Renshaw. This is, all right. We're slowly running out
of space in the museum. Oh, I thought I had to do this. I'd love to draw dinosaurs. I was like,
this is not the game I thought it was going to be. Oh, I do have to do this. All right. Let's go for
it. Give me the pencil. Oh shit. Honestly, I'm telling you right now, this is, this is, this is,
this kid's ready for upper management. It's just like, oh yeah. It's just like these, these little
dot to dot puzzles just to bore, bore your child. Okay. Is that good? I got it. Is that it? Oh,
that's it. Okay. Next drawing. You missed the front leg. I just was, I was just coloring it in. Okay.
Next drawing. New draw. Oh no, I have to, I'm doing it. I have to do it again. E? Okay. Oh wait. I
can, oh, next one. All right. So let me do it right. Let me actually do it right. Why do I feel
like kids in school, like probably do this stuff? You know, like sometimes you just look over and
you see like, Hey, come sub to my Twitch. Like, Hey, you can find me over here at Twitch. I feel
like, I feel like kids probably do this. Oh, like they're like Twitter. What kid has a Twitter?
Do kids have Twitter? They shouldn't. They shouldn't. Do they? No, they don't. Do they?
Kids don't, kids don't have Twitter. I hope they don't. I missed these dots. So I'll get it.
All right. Continue. What the fuck am I doing out here? Oh, there's a sprint. Wait, I'm supposed to
be eight years old right now. Where, where's the, where's my supervision? Okay. Right. Left mouse
button. Pick up and inspect. Right is drop or hold to throw. All right. I found my first fossil here.
What are all the car sounds? Okay. I'm just in my backyard, right? And I'm in, I'm just like,
it's imagination time. I'm imagining all of this. Okay. Holy shit. That's why we're like
$50,000. Okay. So this is, I can rotate it. I can rotate it. Oh, no, I can't. I lost it half a year
later. I mean lost it. At the age of 14, nearly all I could think about was putting together and painting
dinosaur models. I was getting better at it. All right. That kid, this kid got into the wood stain
and did this. Like, I, excuse me. Like, where'd you get the stain to do that? This one comes with
the manual. It's dead simple. It comes with the manual. All right. Hold on. Let me do a little bit of,
let me do a little grease action here. 14. All right. So here we go. So I get to do this.
Oh, this is cool. Rotate, pick up part, drop part. Okay. So I just have to go this way. All right.
So here we go. I got like a, this is easy. No, pick it up. That's a great sound effect by the way.
Why is my nose so itchy? Ooh. All right. So I got a brontosaurus. This one's tough. Oh, fuck. Okay.
Can I like spin this around? All right. Well, very obviously this is here. What if I don't have the
drawing? Yeah. Easy. Easy. Do I get to paint it too? Why does this 10 year old have a voice like this?
He's remembering. He's reminiscing. Okay. Well, this is definitely where the head goes.
Oh, that I can rotate it. All right. So this is where the head goes. These are the arms,
the tail. All right. This is the big part of the tail. Yep. No, that didn't work. Let me
just do all the stuff. I know where it goes first. Hey, this is a leg. That's like, there's like a
thigh wrong way. I know these are, this is tough. I don't know. Like this. Yep. Okay. Keep going.
It's like a life is strange soundtrack. Is that right? Yeah, I got it. I'm good. Maybe I could
use more practice and build one of them again. That's difficulty level. I don't need to do that.
I know what I'm doing. A couple of years later, the money I had received as a reward in that
competition turned out to be of an invaluable help. I mean, I got some money. Adventure of a
lifetime in your twenties. I think it's possible. I was exactly 20 years old when I found an article
about a paleontological group in a newspaper. It turned out they needed volunteers who were
willing to work in the north of the country. It was a long shot, but I didn't want to miss
such a great opportunity. Oh, for some reason, I thought dinosaurs like existed in this world.
See like the front page, like front page of the news, man, like the T-Rex is back.
Stay in your house. What would, what would people do if there was a front page on like number one
on Reddit, like top of Reddit, top of every news website, CNN, Fox news, ABC. If it was like T-Rex
is a back, what would happen? And it was like a big roaring T-Rex. Like that's like the pictures
of it on Reddit. I don't know. Okay. Gameplay basics. What would, would you like leave your
house? Like front, the top front page of Reddit, over 50 T-Rexes have been spotted in various
cities across America. Are you going to leave? Are you going to like leave? What do you do?
I think I'd be scared. Okay. Gameplay tips, important interactive objects. Let's just go
over this real quick. You know, it's a video. I'm going to give the dev plus one full letter grade.
You just show me, show me what, show me. Don't tell me, show me. Yep. Gameplay tips up a right
corner. Read them on the tablet. Okay. F1. Got it. Look at this. Absolutely perfect tutorial.
What about this one? Important object display description in the lower left corner. Okay.
Look at this. I honestly, like, I'm not kidding. This is like a perfect tutorial.
Okay. Third hint will be in the color of the pointer. Okay. So yeah, just like this
information on the bottom. Easy. Icons on the compass hide with growing distance.
Okay. Just like that on the map on your tablet, you can select an object or place that where you
want to go. All right. This would have taken a AAA game, like three hours to tell me this stuff.
Okay. Then when you unlock new locations, use the travel tab on your tablet to move to another
location. Good. Okay. So it's like right there. I'm a day in the trip. You can select the time
of day car. You want to make your cars are in this game. You just got two full letter
grades in one minute. If all of you said this game was like a C, it just became an A minus
just because of the last 15 seconds. Okay. So cool. Let's go. So I can drive, I drive around.
I got my tablet. Welcome to the mining area. A few weeks ago, miners came across something that
appears to be dinosaur remains. We managed to get the mine closed until the matter is dealt with
as neither the workers nor the board of directors is happy about the lockdown.
Okay. We got to act fast. Your job is relatively easy. Head to the area marked on your map and
leave no stone unturned. The area is marked on your radar as well, so you shouldn't have any
problems finding it. The off-road car parked nearby is fueled and ready. We hope your work
will be fruitful. With your help, we should be able to finally complete the full skeleton
for our new museum. That's a fun one to say when you do like the radio voice
of the missing bones that we're looking for our hip bone, right arm bone, and a vertebra.
All right, let's go. Let's go. Turn it up a little bit. It's not that loud.
Okay. So we've got two tools. This is my flashlight. I've got a drone.
Does this have gas? How do I get out of here? Okay, let's go. So I need to go where on the map?
Two by four, four by four. Why do I have like a bunch of moving stuff? All right. Use the horn.
Nice. This is the music. Okay. So where am I going? Where's the map? Okay. I got to go
over there on the right. All right. So turn around. They have like a street. All right.
You can go kind of fast. Uh-oh. It's like, wait, don't go so fast. Hold on. Removing obstacles.
Remove lying tree trunks with a chainsaw and use sledgehammer to break rocks. Note the color
of the interactive cursor when using tools. When it is green, you can work. Ooh, can I find stuff
in there? If you find stuff in a place you can't get out of, use R to reset your character. I think
I'm about to be in that part. There's an excavation equipment in your car. After using it to secure
the excavation area, you'll need to get another set of equipment from the hub. Don't forget about
this when you go on your next fossil site search. In hard to reach and muddy terrain, use the four
by four drive. You can reset the car by pressing R2. All right. Just hit like it is dead.
Like I'm dead. Like I'm, it's over. That's it. All right. I got to do this, right?
Like I missed the sledgehammer. Cool. All right. So how do I get this? How do I get this out of the
way? Just going to pick it up. I have to keep cutting it. How many, how many pieces do I need?
Can I just drive over it? How do I pick it up? Oh, there we go. Nobody else works here, right?
That's why I shouted the windshield. I don't do that with any bones. That would be bad, right?
This, I love this music. It's so like epic. Okay. So I got to go that way. There's the dig site.
I put it in four by four. Yeah. Four wheel drive. All right. I can't go that way. Maybe I can. You
see, they never show this in the car commercials because this is what happens if you were to do
this. That didn't do anything. Okay. There we go. Four wheel drive. Get through the mud.
I don't want to push the car. I'm fine. All right. Back into two wheel drive.
Let's go. Use a hammer. All right. Our need to have all wheels grounded to get. Oh, I thought
the other wheels were all gone. This is a big cheese. It kind of is like a big piece of cheese,
isn't it? How strong is this guy? Oh no fucking way. Hercules couldn't even do that in the movie.
That would be so funny if there was sound effects. It was like, I definitely cannot pick this one up.
You big? Make your own sounds. I can, okay. I don't, I can get out of this. Is there any
valuables here too? Like with it, can I like sift for gold? Okay. Here we go. We're here.
Now I got to get out and I've got to do some excavation. Oh, it's this way. Okay. Is it near
the tree? All right. It's somewhere over here. Bring your car. Oh, this is just like Minecraft.
Not really. This is dinosaur poop simulator. I don't think you did. The dinosaur poo didn't
fossilize. Wasn't it absorbed into the fucking ground? Did it? Okay. Here we go. So what? Oh,
I have to fuck that. Secure the area. Oh, it's just doing it. This is funny. Where's he going?
Oh, just, should I skip it? Dude, I'm sorry. This game blows. You know, it's, I can tell you,
I can tell you about these like, these are like five minute Andes. Okay. It's so it's been like
15 minutes. You should play a different. No, stop. Oh, wait. How big is this area? Oh, okay.
Play checkers. No checkers sucks. Okay. Here we go. It does check. Okay. Checkers. Look,
I don't like chess either. I'm going to, it's not like, I think I look checkers is not a bad game,
but checkers chess, any game where I have to sit down like across somebody and move little pieces
on like a game board and go against somebody else. I don't care. I'm, it bores the absolute
fuck out of me. I would rather like just go like roll down a hill. You know what I mean?
I don't want to look, I don't want to play chess. I want to like roll down the hill.
I don't like want to play chess. I, but Hey, let's play chess, dude. Oh, just like,
please. Like I want to do anything else. Anything but chess, anything, but checkers or chess.
I don't know. There's some like really like high brain people that they get a lot of enjoyment
from that shit. You're really analytical and you like problem solving and stuff. And that's
awesome. That's really cool. I'm glad you have the capability to do that. I just want to roll
down a hill. I don't, I've always tried. My brother was into chess and he really wanted somebody to
play with and he would just checkmate me every fucking 10 seconds. Like he was just trying to
find someone to play with and he'd be like, Hey man, let's, you want to play chess? I was like,
yeah. And I would just sit there and I would just, I only, the only thing I knew what to do in chess
was move the pawns. I didn't know how to do anything else. So he would just, I would move
my pawns up sometimes two spaces, sometimes one for no reason. And they would like and checkmate
me in like five minutes. This happened to every time. I've got to feel bad looking back because
he really did just really want to play and like the internet didn't exist. Right. So you couldn't
just like, Oh, go play chess against like a computer. You can just right now you losing
viewers. Good. Right now you can open up any app, any website. You can literally go play chess right
now in literally on five seconds from right now. I kind of feel bad for the people that really
wanted to do that kind of stuff, but they just have no, you didn't have any access to it.
All right. There's your story. In the excavation area, use the GPR to find the stones hidden
underground. Ooh. Okay. Dig in the soil and sand with a shovel. Pay attention to the color of the
cursor that indicates where you can use the tool. All right. So you got to find the rock, dig,
use the pickaxe to search the rocky ground. Pay attention to the color of the cursor that indicates
where you can use the tool. Sick. Visual inspection at this stage will help you identify stones of
other geologic periods. You can remove them quickly. Let's go. I love stories, people happy.
Losing viewers equals spinning out the week. Did you hear that noise? That was like, oh,
okay. Grab a palette. What do I do with this? Oh, there's no fossils in here. Okay. I get it.
All right. Here we go. Now we got to open up the machine. That is this thing here. All right. Find
a good place for exploration and scan it. All right. Scanning. Is it on the map? No, just somewhere
here. Scanning. This is a bunch of bullshit. What's going to happen is that somebody told
me to come out here and do this. There's nothing. There's not going to be anything here. This is
like this way. Somebody wanted to get rid of me for a few hours. All of a sudden, like all
the sprinkler system is going to turn on and just get me like soaking wet. And I'm going to be like,
fucking pieces of shit. This is not right. Yeah, Dave, go there and go look for dinosaur bones.
Where? There's nothing here. How do I scan? I just go out here. There's nothing in this place.
Place, place flag. Where is this place? Go to the dirt mound. Oh my God. What? There everything's
this whole thing is a dirt mound. Oh, you mean this, you mean the fresh dirt. All right. Whatever.
That looks pretty good. Oh, all right. Mark these two spots. Mark it here. Right here. Okay.
There's a lot of fossils here. What about there? No. What's your guys favorite dinosaur? Mine's
the chicken. Look it up. All right. I think I got enough. So now I got to dig at these spots.
How far down do I go? Oh, I got it. Oh shit. I can't move. I'm going to get rid of this crap.
All right. I, okay. Be careful. I get, I got to dig that out. How do I, is it, can I get it?
Can I just pull it out? Put the chainsaw away. How do I get this out? Dude, there's probably like
10 dinosaur bones in here. Okay. I get it. I pick it up. Find first. Inspect the stone.
How do I inspect it? Dude, stop digging. Hold on. How do I inspect this?
Inspect the stone. How do I do that? Pick up, use, inspect. Right? That's what I'm trying to do.
I need to do more pickaxe. Oh shit. All right. Here we go. Fossils emit small amounts of radiation.
That was a bad one. That wasn't, that was not a funny one. No, I didn't. I'll do it again. I'll
do it better. That one was not as good either. I'll try it one more time. Oh, this, wait,
radiation? That was a good one. Use that one instead. That one, that was actually a pretty
good one. The first two were fucking cringe and awful. All right. This allows us to use the
Geiger counter to search for them. It will be indicated. All right. Cool. None of those.
That third one was fine. Use a towel to remove mud from the stone. Okay. And then we can identify
the species. This is cool. This is cool. All right. Let's go. I said bunker ass the first time.
Cringe. There's no bones in this rock? Oh, I can't get out of here. Hold on. What do you mean
there's no bones in this rock? Oh, there are fossils in that little one. You need boneless
rocks. You don't want to have, you want boneless buffalo rocks? That's so stupid. I love it.
Okay. Prepare for transport. Use plaster to protect fragile fossils. This is so much, this is,
this is cool. You have to pack it into a, place the plaster stone in a shipping crate.
Okay. And then you put it into a crate. You're going to bring the necessary amount of crates
and then place the boxes with the fossils in your car and transport them to the hub.
Transport. That small chest can be transported by passenger cars. For large, you need a truck. Okay.
Park your vehicle. Okay. I got it. Big money. I can't move though. I can't get, I'm stuck. I
can't move. It's R, right? I can't get unstuck. R. Get me the fuck out of here. All right. I'm
good. But I want, I need to check the other ones too. Why did I not bring a stepladder?
Okay. I got to make a path. What'd I put with that? Let me, let me do the thing with this,
this one right here, right? All right. This is it. So let's look at it. Okay. Yep. There's bones in
there. Plaster it up. Make sure we keep it safe. Okay. I got a message. Evacuation. Oh, nevermind.
Yeah. The, been secured. Yep. Transport it. Okay. Yep. Okay. And now I got to put this in a box
over here. Why are you putting a cast on it? Okay. Yes. Okay. Unknown species, unknown bone.
How many can I fit in here? Oh my God. That, what the hell was that sound? Let's get this shit out
of me. Okay. Wait, there's more of stones. I can fit one more in there. All right. This is fun. I
want to do this more. In my, uh, this thing. Can I eventually get a bigger car? Where are all my
markers? Oh, did you just hit that Yonki Splonky? You got it, man. All right. Let me clear this out
because I don't want to get stuck like I just did. Dude, we missed you. I haven't gone anywhere
because I haven't hit the Yonki Splonky in like seven months. You know, there's other dances
besides the Yonki Splonky, right? You know that there's other things to, there's other movements
you can do with your body. You know that, right? Is that a fossil? I don't know. Okay. There was
another one here. Where is it? Let me check these. Does this have any fossils in it? That's passive
aggressive Andy right there. Oh, that's fine. Oh, you said it's fine. Oh, you said it's fine.
That's fine. That's okay. Sure. Oh, that's fine. Whatever you say. No dinosaur bones in there.
Oh, whatever. All right. Let me, there's other ones here and this one, the guy flies an avatar.
All right. Let's identify these. Take that up. There's gotta be one in here, right? That out of
here. Excuse me. This out of here. I don't want to confuse you with another one. He's gone. They
look at the CCTV footage. Why did he do that? Why would he do that? What was he doing? All right.
Let's take a look. Nope. Nope. Three in a row. What about this one?
In go. All right. Get this out of here. Break this one up. Good. Get rid of it. See you later.
All right. So what's in here? We got two stones now. All right. I have to be honest with you.
Turn off the music. Not yet. Not until I'm sick of it. The first like 20 minutes of this game,
I thought we're going to be just like, like a piece of shit. Um, I am over the last like 30
minutes have slowly been going. This is actually going to be probably pretty cool. This is actually
going to be kind of fun. Like I was like, this could be, I don't know if I'm going to like this.
I think I'm actually going to really like this, especially when you start like painting the
dinosaur bones and stuff. This looks like cornbread and I wait, I can do three. I can put one on top
too. All right. I'm going to get another one. One can go up top. All right. Let's keep this one area
here. Oh, we got it. Please turn the music off. I'll just wait. You know, this is making me like
into it for a minute. I'll get bored of it in like 15 more minutes. Trust me. Don't worry.
Can I get rid of this? There's some shit right here. This one, what does it even down here?
This one here. All right. Let's see. Any of these have anything in it? Get that out of here.
Nothing? What the fuck are you talking about? Oh, there's nothing here at all. I did this.
Okay. I'm an idiot. Where's the, over there. There's nothing there. How come you like boring
games? Not everything has to have like machine gunfire. Okay. Not every game needs to have
machine gunfire. Okay. Every video game does not have to have, it doesn't have to have it
be an enjoyable experience. Plus I'm a boring fucking person. So there is your answer. Dude,
those are the, uh, dude. Oh wow. Like I wonder what his life is like when he's not streaming.
I am a boring fucking guy. Okay. Um, I think it was last night. I fell asleep. I had my iPad
and I fell asleep too. This is like kind of crazy. This is why I had like a nightmare.
I was watching a showcase, like a Halloween convention showcase where they show all like the
animatronics and shit. And I fell asleep to it and it autoplayed like five years of their convention.
Like if you scroll through these videos, it's like, oh, that was the biggest Halloween
convention or something. And it's like a huge thing. And they showcase all the new
animatronics and Halloween scary stuff. Right. And I just sitting there, dude, like this, just like,
I'm not doing anything else. Right. But if you scroll through, it was like five straight years
of their convention and people going to it, like hours of videos. And I shit you not almost every
10 to 15 seconds. You hear. It's like this, this like fucking face peeled off zombie going like this.
It was literally the whole video. And I was, I felt I slept to that.
Was anything in here? They all do that too. When do you, okay. The, I, all those like crazy
animatronics, they all do that like really strange like movements. It's just so unsettling. It's so
scary. And I make this reference to you too. Animatronics, like the Halloween ones where it's
like the ghoul that like moves and just kind of goes at you. It reminds me of like Dark Souls
enemies. They're just these mindless, brainless things that just, I'm getting you now. Like here
I come. That's why Dark Souls is so scary. We talked about that when I was playing Elden Ring,
but all the From Software AI, it's just, I'm killing you. I'm killing you. I don't care about
anything else. I don't give a shit about anything else. I, my programming is just get that fucking
guy right now. It doesn't, there is no like, oh, he's running back off a little. Nope. It's just
until I get you. It's horrifying. It's like a nightmare. It's a dream. That's why those
things are so scary. They just don't stop. That's why Michael Myers was scary. Michael Myers didn't
do anything. Like I could probably sprint, punch Michael Myers in the face and knock him out and
he'd be dead. You know what I mean? Like I could probably like full sprint, fucking smash him in
the head. Like right here. He'd just be like, but it would take one punch and it's right here.
And he would, his head would explode. I'm telling you his head would explode,
but no, because he's just like, just walks forward and has no emotion. He just has like an AI that's
like, go get that person. Just walk at them. That's why it was just, holy shit. What the
fuck is this terrifying thing in this one? All right. Where was I digging? I completely forgot.
We started talking about Halloween stuff, but yeah, I was sleeping to that. It is every 15 seconds.
You just hear screaming. No wonder I had a fucking nightmare. I could have turned auto play off, man.
It's seriously, but I always just forget to cause I'm logged in. How many pieces of furniture do you
have? I don't know. Like I have a chair, two chairs, I think table. I don't know. I got five
pieces of furniture, maybe. Fuck. I said, this is going to be a chill stream. I say that every time
and then I've, I don't know. I'm like fucked up. I'm going to give myself another headache.
Like I had yesterday. All right. Let's get this sealed up. You need to inspect it first. Oh shit.
I'm not inspecting it. That's right. Perform a visual inspection. Oh fuck. I like plastered
those without knowing what it was. Oh shit. Well, Jerry, you, this is great. You found these fossils,
but you like mummified them and we're never going to know what they are. Thanks. Okay. Well,
I know what it is. Are there any more? All right. I get it now. Next time I'll be out there. So this
is a head, like a skull. What's this music? This is, this song is called the river doth flow.
I forget the artist, but it's the river. Oops. The river, the river doth flow. I have no idea.
Okay. So I did it. Now I got to get out of here. I got to go back to the
campsite. I probably should actually be careful. You can probably dump this.
I'm going to do the right thing. There's no way in fuck, you know, what the word doth means. It
means does or do. How's that wrong? Yeah. Like, oh, whether thou doth go or not, whether you will go
or do or not to be or not to be, thou doth the question. Don't crash into a rock. What does it
actually mean then? How's that wrong? But what does it actually mean? What does doth mean?
Does it mean like to do, like to go, like doth, like to do, does?
It does. Yeah. What are you talking about? Don't make me seem like I'm an idiot.
Listen to this music. This music got cooler. Can I put this down and open it up and see what's in
there? All right. Open this. I can't open it. Unknown species. Just throw it over there? No,
I can't. All right. Open tablet to leave this area and transport the findings to your museum.
OK, I can hire a worker. OK, so I can go back to the museum. How do I?
Do you want to send the crates? Yes. Yes, I do. What does doth mean? Tell me or I'll turn the
stream off right now. I'm going to turn my stream off. I'm going to hit end stream. I'm
meant to hovering over it right now. What does doth mean? Three, two, one means do. Thank you
for saving the stream. Lucky, lucky, lucky.
Preoccupied with collecting and preparing dinosaur bones.
When I arrived at the museum's lab, it was time to start cleaning what I had found.
It was a fascinating experience. It required a lot of time and attention.
The results always worth the effort. There's a lot in this game. It's fun. OK,
moving the crates around with box cleaning station. That's it. It's so visual. That's why
I've been able to blow through this tutorial. Look at this. Remove plaster and extract fossil
from the stone using the available tools. I almost said avalanche. Oh, after extracting
the fossil, make a decision who should clean this set of bones, you or the museum employee.
Somebody else is going to do it. If you clean the bones by hand, pay attention to the game
controls in the upper left corner. Here you'll find some useful features such as focus mode
and highlighting of uncleaned areas. Oh, that just scared the shit out of me.
I thought there was a monster in here. What is this thing? Why am I skiing? OK, cool. Get off.
All right, what do we got in here? Unknown bone, unknown species. Let's take a look.
All right, let's clean it. Where do I get this off? It's a loot box.
Do I just carve it this way? Oh, there we go. OK, so now I'm looking for the where was the fossil?
Right there. Watch out. Don't break it. Don't break it. Can I break it if I'm not careful?
I'll clean it. I want to do it. Clean it. Whoa. Oh, shit, I broke it. I think I broke it. Did I
break it? Cleaning scope. Oh, wait, you can see magnified. That's funny. I need to rotate this.
All right. So what is that? Remember, remember that one? OK, this is going to take too long.
These just look like the dinosaur chicken nuggets. Well, they are based in reality.
Send fossil to preparation room. Based, based. Pod watchers skip. Pod watchers don't listen to
don't you got to let somebody dictate what you should do. You know, listen to one person dictate
what you should do with like what you do with your time. Think about that. I let somebody tell
you how to dictate your time, right? Stay. Listen to that guy. All right. Just painting some barbecue
sauce on these. Is it ready? Now what? Whoa. Am I supposed to do this?
There's so much going into this. What is going on? Look at how much is going into this.
There's something kind of like therapeutic about doing what I'm doing, though. This is kind of I
like this and I upgrade the tools. Are there upgrades in this game? You're ruining them.
Dinosaur ribs. Those aren't done. That's not done. All right. What's the next step?
When I drop them into the hot vegetable oil, we got a joint cooking up dinosaur bones like
you wouldn't believe full of flavor. Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
I've been coming here for 25 years. That's Don Stevenson. He got the joint from his granddad.
So what made you want to eat dinosaur bones? Well, my grandfather was a paleontologist and
one day he's out there decided to take a little taste snack on some of the bones he had found
and realized that there was still some pretty delicious marrow in there and some meat still
there. Well, he opened up this place and I've been taking it all over ever since. He said among us.
All right. Spin it around. This. Oh my God. This is what it takes to do this.
Just spray paint them. Whoa. Remember you'd make a bad dentist. It's really simplified, dude.
Millions of year old fossils. So what you got cooking in here? Well, these are T-Rex legs.
Only eight of these exist on earth. Oh wow. So you marinate those? Yeah. Water. Water from the sink.
He goes, he's like goes and dips his finger in the water from the sink in the bucket and goes,
buddy. Whoa. It's like, that's just, that's just sink water. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Let's go.
Take it from this, put it on this into the skeleton or store it in the museum store room.
After cleaning and collecting and connecting the skeleton pieces, you can proceed to complete the
entire dinosaur. When the knowledge tab on your tablet becomes available, you look in the ability
to manage dinosaur skeletons. Really? And you can move it into an exhibit. That's crazy. Okay.
Design mode. Oh shit. I don't know where this goes. I don't know where this is supposed to go.
Oh, now I guess I do. Do I have the whole thing? I do. What the hell is this? Um, I'll take it.
Don't drop it. Oh, look, it's right here. Oh, whoa. Okay. So I, I'm assuming the other stuff
is the head and the legs. Drop it and it just shatters. Oh, it's a, it's Bob's dino grill calling.
I heard you dropped a dinosaur bone and shattered on the ground.
Mind if I come, come take that for you for like $40. I've been eating here for 25 years. Yeah. So
you got a statistic for us, don't you? Don't you, Bob? Yes, I do. Yes. Every single person that's
ever eaten here has gotten sick. Every single one, every single one, every single one guy.
I think this is the Virta, the vertebrae, but I have to manually clean this. Don't I? All right.
We're going to do the speed run. Somebody said it'd be a bad dentist. Did you see what I just did?
I got to get a worker. I need a worker. Why's your face cam shaking? Um, because the wind,
it's really windy here in Vegas. I told you guys. Jesus. No, it's because my mouse is on my desk
and my desk is connected to the monitor. The monitor is sitting here and the webcam is on
the monitor. So when I go like this, I shake the whole thing and I'm like shaking right now here.
I really probably should put this somewhere else, shouldn't I? These ones are so small. I hate it.
They're too small. These little meatballs. Oh, I hate it. I just have to do like, they hate them.
You got, okay. This for those new viewers out there, I hate needing to like hold left mouse
button down and like trace like really small, tiny little areas really consistently. Oh,
it just makes me want to scream. It makes me want to scream like, I just want to like just
get up and run in a fucking circle. I just had like my arm. I hate it. Like it feels fucking,
I hate it. Oh, funka ass.
You only got to spray this once. Like don't spray this too much in the bathroom. You know what I
mean? I know people like, I know if you go to the bathroom, you really don't want anyone to know
you went to the bathroom. You're doing that. Don't fucking do this. Just literally like this.
This is all you need. Ready? That's it. And then fucking stop and then just leave. Relax.
Why can't I? Right on the rotisserie. I love it.
I'm serious. I would be a horrible dentist. You're right.
You're like, turn it with your mouth open. The dentist is like really leaning in and slowly
cleaning each tooth and then goes like, what's he doing? No, sorry, man. I just like, I just
hate like being like doing tiny little movements. My arm gets lost. I feel weird. I would think
there was a spider in my mouth. It was the other day. Stop shaking your webcam. Stop shaking your
webcam. Stop shaking your webcam. I'll put it somewhere else later. I'll like glue it to the
fucking wall or something. I don't know. Where are you supposed to put a webcam? To like prevent
that from happening. I don't, you know what I mean? What am I supposed to put a webcam to make this
not happen? You're the streamer. I mean like you'll use a DSLR with a stand. I'm not using a DSLR.
No fucking thanks. Nope. I don't want, I don't want you guys to see every individual pore on my face.
Sorry, not happening. Not, not pushing 40. Not pushing 40. That's not happening. You, we want
to see you in 4k. I don't want to see me in 4k. So why would I want you to see me in 4k?
What an insecure millionaire.
Huh?
Let's go. This dude's not, what are you saying? We want to see, we want to see your beautiful face.
You're looking at it, literally looking at it right now. Donate your teeth. What, what do you,
no shut up. In a nice way, right? Like shut up in a nice way. These bones are so little. All right,
so I can have somebody do this and I can do like the digging part, right? Do I have to make money
or something? Or do I have to do these few because it's like that tutorial. This is kind of relaxing
though. I can see this just kind of hanging out and just doing this. I know exactly what I'm doing
right now. That other one's definitely the head. No way it's not. It is. This is a big one. Okay,
so now can I just have somebody do it? Shut up in a respectful way. It's the whole skeleton.
Can I live in your pores? That is fucking weird. Find that person out. Oh my God, look at this.
Tons of little things in here. Okay, also preparation room. What happens if I do that?
Where is it? Does somebody else do it? Do I have to go get it? Oh, okay. Somebody's just doing it.
Oh, this is way better. Can it be fire? Yeah, I could have had one going while I did the other one.
They're way faster than you. I just started working here. What is this prestige road map?
It's almost done. I thought you were being attacked by a serious scam. I can't even say
serious Sam enemy. This IRL takes about five years. Oh my God, that's so much better.
So with this, I can put, I can display this. Holy shit, that wind. I feel like my fucking,
that's scary. They had like, look at these eye bones. Okay. All right, I have a full dinosaur.
What kind of dinosaur is it? The museum I was doing my internship in was getting ready for
renovation. I was afraid my classes were about to be cut because of that. I wouldn't have been
more wrong about this one. Turns out the exhibition hall was being revamped. I was asked to participate
in the redecoration, but that's not all of it. We were also given a second complete skeleton
of orthothomimus. Orthothomimus. To turn dinosaurs for one display. Well, let's just say all the
pictures of dinosaurs. Jesus. This wind is fucking scary, man. All right, put it, let's
jack it up. I don't even, can you guys hear it? It's violent. Oh my goodness. What the fuck.
I don't even know you can hear it, but that's fucking insane. Okay, we'll unload. Interior design.
Tab. Wait, wait up here. Okay, here we go. Fuck off. Fuck off. Fuck off with this. Holy shit.
Off with this. This wind is scary. I don't know if you guys can hear it. I'm trying to see if you
can hear it. All right, setting up skeleton. Whoa, you can make it like a habitat. Wow. Okay.
You can change the skeleton's pose, the grass and stuff. That's cool. Look at the decoration
symbols. Decorations and shit. This is fun. Rotate and scaling. What? Okay. Okay. Next pose. I can
pose it. Wait, what? This is cool. All right, hold on. I need to, how do I rotate it? Right there.
And I want to do a pose. That one's kind of cool. Yep. That's where it's going. Okay. Now. Grass.
Jesus Christ. Grab, I like the grass or the sand. That's kind of cool too. Turn off the noise gate.
Oh my God, guys. Okay. I'm going to turn the noise gate off. This is what it sounds like without the
noise gate. Are you ready? Hold on. Just wait. I mean, you can hear it a little bit, but wait
till the huge one happens. I just want to catch a big one. I feel like we're like storm watching
right now. He's going to do a joke, isn't he? No, it's not a joke. It's fucking crazy. Sometimes Vegas
gets 70 plus mile per hour wins. No, I want a big one to happen before I continue.
When a big one happens, when every time I go, Jesus, that's what you, that's what I'm reacting
to. Now it's not going to do it because I'm like waiting for it to happen. No, he's going to just
do a huge fart. I'm like, okay guys, wait for it. And I just go like, that would be really funny.
It would be like, that would piss a lot of you off, but all right, I'm going to give this like
20 or 30 more seconds. 10 more seconds. Viewers dropping. It's, I don't care. 10 seconds. Come
on, just do it so I can stop doing this. Viewers rising. I don't care. That was a mini one. 10
seconds. Every time I talk, it happens. It doesn't want to do it now. Whatever. Okay. Just know that
it's really crazy. You know what I mean? What does that sound like? I just fucking screamed into the
mic. Can you hear it? Okay. Let's get back to what we were doing. That's unfortunate. I really want,
I want you guys to hear it. Okay. So it's like you're trapped in a box of frosted flakes.
Hello. Is that what it sounded like? I'm going to go with the stones. A huge one just happened
and I get right when I turn it off. I only have one plant. Big plants. No, we'll get rid of that.
Freeze. Grass. All right. That's fine. That looks good. Perfect. Looks good to me. Wait a minute.
Take out. Oh shit. I need, I need more room. I guess get fit here. Uh, how do I move this back
again? That's okay. Um, this, I need to, can I, what should I sell this? Like the stupid fucking
Zamboni machines in the way. How do I get rid of that? Back, back up. I have to get, move this
thing. Ooh, this is pretty fucking cool. I like that. That's, that's pretty museum like. I like
this one. All right. Walls. Ooh, I like that. I like this one. I like this one. No, I don't.
This one's good. All right. Decorations. We need a bench here so people can sit and look at them,
fighting each other. I want to plant over here. No, a little bigger than that. Paintings. Stacker
them. Stacker them. Cool. I found that. That doesn't look bad. All right. Now I need to,
I got to, can I move this over? I got to move this here. It's kind of in the way though,
isn't it? Wait, what's that mean? Oh, I, I, this thing's, how do I make it so I can fit it?
Paintings suck. Make it one big exhibit. Yeah. How do I do that? Can I put them both in here?
I could make it just one huge exhibit, right? And then put the other one in. I can. All right.
Nice. Nice. Nice. This is perfect. Okay. So I want to put this one here, rotate it. It's too big.
That's not bad. If it right there. All right. I want to pose him though. That's all right.
That looks fine. We need some more plants and shit though. Move this over here. This looks pretty
good. That looks fine. Okay. Now we need, um, there's a little like bird nest for this. All
right. That's good. We got it. Look. Beautiful. Stunning. Close these fucking windows. I don't
want people looking in here for free. Cut these up. Ooh. Oh. Ooh. Ooh. What's that dinosaur claw?
Whoa. I'm in a weird mood tonight and I'm really sorry. That was the last day of a
too symmetrical adventure. Just believe it's a weird phone. The director called to ask me to stay
and help the museum build a bigger skeleton. There was a vacant position because one of the
workers got sick. I felt bad for the guy, but I was so glad there was a chance to work in the museum
for longer. The decision was a no brainer. I went to the museum the next day. Although the place
wasn't new to me, this particular moment felt different. It was the first time I was asked to
enter the museum's workshop with my heart pounding and my hands sweating. I walked towards the door.
Okay. Just in case I got to shake somebody's hand. Oh wow. This is a Tyrannosaurus Rex.
I've got to admit, bigger skeleton the director was talking about was indeed a huge one. I was
dumbstruck when I was faced with the legendary Tyrannosaurus. Even in my dreams, I would never
fathom that our museum was in possession of such a treasure. Complete the T-Rex. You got it. Oh.
Oh. Collectively, everybody in the room. Oh. Oh. This is tongue. Never mind. Shut up, please.
Okay. I'll shut up. How am I supposed to get those up here? I have to walk. I can throw. I can't. I
have to walk individually. No, I don't. So I could have decorated this place too. When do we stop
making money? What I want to know. I want to go dig some more. That was really fun. Oh, I did it.
The hidden skeleton of Tyrannosaurus looked majestic and I had the honor to contribute to it.
Yet another beautiful moment that has been etched in my memory. Open your window? No.
It sounds like Interstellar. It does. It does. If I saw the movie, which I haven't. I don't know.
It's pretty amped up. I've never seen that movie. Just pretended to know what you meant.
Finding a job, but that was about to change soon. For the first six months after graduation,
my focus was to find a job in the field of paleontology, or at least something that
relates to it. I submitted my resume for every paleontologist job I could find. But didn't I
get a job already? Jobs were either already taken or I lacked the experience. After six months,
I started looking for any job, but that also didn't come easily. I was trying hard, but to
no avail. Not a good movie, but everyone saw it. I didn't see it. One year after graduation,
things finally started to turn around. Although it wasn't exactly how I had imagined it.
Did I give my Spider-Man take yet? Did I give my new Spider-Man movie take yet?
Okay. I didn't. Okay. Let me give you my Spider-Man. Just real quick. The second half
of the Spider-Man No Way Home movie felt like a college humor video.
Is it? That's the take I'm going to have. That's the only take I'm going to give you.
It felt like an old college humor video from like 2011, 2008. Did I think it was a bad movie?
No. It was very enjoyable. It was very enjoyable. I almost kind of felt like
the second, like third of the movie. I was expecting actors to look into the camera and smile
after saying anything. Like, oh yeah, blah, blah, blah, blah. That's what I was expecting.
After every three or four lines. I thought it was good. I liked it. I liked it, but I felt like I
was just watching a movie. You know what I mean? It was like a movie. It was like, hey, we're making
a movie right now. Do you know there's a movie on the screen? It was like, hey, I just want to let
you know that you're watching a movie right now. Hey, this is a movie. You like movies, don't you?
You've seen movies, haven't you? You're a big fan of movies. I like movies too.
Am I, is this my house? Hey, let me, I'm going to be very honest with you. Spider-Man is my
favorite character in everything. It's not Batman. It's not Captain America. It's Spider-Man. Spider-Man
is my favorite character. And I think the trilogy was the best Spider-Man trilogy, the best Spider-Man
movies that they've ever made. Oh, but what about Sam Raimi's Spider-Man movie? All right, get out,
let go of me. Yeah, they're great. But I think they, I think this trilogy was great. I think they were
great. Like Homecoming, it's fucking amazing. Far From Home, I loved it. This one, I liked it.
I really liked it. I liked it. I liked it a lot. That's it. Venom, be careful. How do I go in my
house? Where are my keys? But a part of me almost felt like in some of the scenes in the new Spider-Man
movie, like the director was just going to start walking around on the set with like a fucking stone
in his hand, with like the thing in his hand, like just be like, this looks good. Okay. Just like
walking around in the background. All right, how do I, select drone? No, I want to go, how do I go
into my house? What was the objective? 35 year old man complains about comic book movies. I'm not
complaining. That's not a complaint. That was a very, very mild observation. It was mild. It was
very, very mild. Okay. How do I go in my house? Holy shit. I get every channel on every from every
country that literally every country on earth. I get all their TV stations. I'd love to get in here.
That was a mild take. Okay. Come on. Oh my God. What is this? Why is there a car made out of
ground beef in my house? How do I get in here? What's going on? How do I get in the house?
I have to go in the garage? Why can't I go in my front door?
Oh, watch out for the red barrels. Dude, I'm sorry. I'm not going in there if there's red
barrels. Like bright red barrels is like, those explode. I'm not going in there.
His body didn't catch up with his spirit and he had to pass on his little project.
I decided to clean up the workshop for him. Yeah, dude. I don't know. You've like bright
red barrels with like the flame sign on them. We are slowly getting these out of the house.
We're removing these. Okay. What am I doing? Can I just like, no, I can't. What does this happen?
What the fuck, dude? What is going on in here? Yeah. My grandfather collected exploding barrels
and he kept them all in his garage for some fucking reason. I don't know why. I don't know why.
Do I have to fix the car? What the fuck was in there? Wash your hands. Wash your hands.
Grandpa was shitting into a box. Wash your hands immediately. Go wash your hands right now.
I lost fossil piece that I found during the school trip. Despite it being over 15 years ago,
I felt the exact same mix of excitement and joy that I'd felt on that beach years ago.
The desire to search for fossils has become immediately obvious with full force. All my
problems. This game is cool. I actually think this is fun and game. I just had to put it
into action. I started implementing my plan by acquiring a set of excavation tools.
This was possible thanks to a garage sale. Wait, now we're not going to glaze over the fact that
grandpa has a bunch of like fucking gas tanks in his garage? I thought those were like guns.
Like oh my like rifle collection. Okay. Look at your desk from time to time. You may find a pale
intelligent dude. There's a lot of content in this game. I'm not going to let the negative Andes
here tell me. There's a lot of interesting content. This is cool. I think this is actually pretty
cool. I do. Okay. Like you can paint. Wait, I can mess with the car? In the next room in the garage,
the museum, you can see a map on the wall. It will show available locations that you can travel to.
Can I go to Nevada? If Nevada is in this game and I can go to like Las Vegas, this is a B plus. This
game is a B. You can also find here collectible items discovered during research expeditions.
This is like my house. This is cool. Okay. So what's on the news?
Dinosaur skeletons are waiting to be discovered. There's a toy. Hard difficulty.
Don't get me. I don't want to do that. All right. Let's um, let's go. Okay. Those elbows are a little
fucked up. He's supposed to be going like this, like with his arms, like on his side. He's like a
muscle shirt button up on. All right. Now I need one more finishing touch. Those teeth are kind of
fucked up. Um, this is just like somebody drawing like their boss. You know what I mean? Like, oh,
there he is. That motherfucker. Like, oh, this is the boss. You're gonna get fired. This is too much
empty space up here. There's too much empty space up here. I'm not happy with this piece.
I ain't happy with this. Get back to work. Yeah. I crumpled it up before the boss gets over.
I'm like, what you working on over there? That's just, uh, just like, you know, stats and shit.
I was drawing the boss. There's too much empty space here. I'm not happy with this. I'm going
to throw it all away. Put sunglasses on them. No, no, I'm not happy with this. How about like a house
in the background, right? We got to have like some, some, uh, focal point, right? Yeah. He's
in the foreground. Don't adjust your fucking TV, man. Don't adjust your screen. This is perspective
here. He's in the foreground. Don't be alarmed. This guy's scary. The house shouldn't be like alive.
He's focusing. I feel like this is okay. Don't they do those things where it's like the way you
draw a house, the way you draw a person, the way you draw a son. Isn't this like, you can determine
the kind of like personality, like psychology that I have or something, right? I feel like I just did
all of those. So there you go. All right. Now what do I, how do I, what do I do with this?
It's just going to be there. Can I hang this up? I definitely did not draw these. I did not,
the same person did not draw those at all. What the fuck? Dinosaurs on Mars. Okay. So now what do
I do? I get, I'm trapped in here. Get me out of here. All right. I'm fine. Holy shit. What did you
get a military vehicle? Why do I have a military truck? I'm sorry, guys. They both have to be
Jurassic park theme trucks. Okay. Oh, you've, you've really leaning into that here. That's good. Okay.
I'm ready. Make it bright pink. It's like a big bubble gum car. All right. That's good. Oh,
Jerma. Oh, I know. Hey, Jerma. All right. Now what do I do? That was my blue though. I need blue.
I need to, okay. I need a third car. And that third car has to be like an aqua, like a teal.
Nice Thanos truck. It's not the Thanos truck. It's literally bubble gum pink. What kind of
insane person puts their lawnmower on a shelf like this? Am I weird for not ever doing that?
What do I do with this stuff? These are all locked. It's all locked. Am I insane for not
doing? How do you just get it down? Like how do you pull it down? There's a lot of tools.
Okay. Where's my, what do I have to do? Messages. Travel. I think I just go, right? I just go
somewhere else. Knowledge. Management. Whoa. Oh, I have no points. Workers. How do I get out of here?
What do I do? How do I like get out of here? Travel. I have no destinations. I got no destinations.
I have to read the newspaper. Play Fortnite instead. I would never mind. How do I get out of here?
You should dig here. Oh, there we go. Okay. All right. We're going up to Canada. Canada.
We're going to be taking the grandpa truck into Canada. I need some more of this. I need some
more of my drink. Can we take a quick break? Right. So can I can go fill up my drink again?
I'm gonna fill my drink up. I'll be right back. I want more of a drink. It's green tea. Relax.
I'll be right back. Well, it's green tea with vitamins. With vitamins. All right,
baby. Boys and girls, I have a treat for you. I have a treat for you. I completely forgot about
this until I just was reminded. So the Vata Science Center, if you guys remember, this past year,
we did that kind of all the raising the money and stuff. And the community was able to give
them $10,000, if you remember. Pretty cool shit. They sent, they sent some really cool shit.
I don't even know what half of it is, but let's, you want to examine it? It's like,
they sent literally fossils. Actual fossils here. You really want to take a look? Let's take a look.
I don't know what a lot of this stuff is, but we'll find out, right? The game can wait for
just a sec. Oh my God. I look crazed. Okay. So let's take a look at some of this stuff.
They're in these little bags. I think this is, I don't know what this is, but it's some type of
fossilized like pyrite. There's a bunch of these. There's like at least four or five of these. It's
in this cute little bag. I think this is for fools gold. Yeah. Hey, that's cool. You see? Very cool.
But that's not necessarily a fossil, right? This is. Be careful. I don't like break this. I think
this is like a tooth. I think they explained what they were. I just don't remember. Take a look at
this thing. This is crazy looking. Yeah. Look at this. This is like, this is, look at this thing.
This is like a tooth. What is this? Isn't that crazy looking? This is like a dinosaur tooth or
like a shark tooth. It's moving on the other side, right? But over here, it's really tiny fossilized
like shark tooth or fossilized dinosaur tooth. That one's really cool. Is it a plant? It looks
like a tooth. That's a crustacean, you idiot. No, this is a crustacean, you idiot. Oh my God. This
is kind of delicate. This is like a, whoa. I don't even remember seeing this one. This is a
fossilized cinnamon bun roll. Fossilized cinnamon bun roll. That's like a shell. It's like a seashell.
Look at that. Let me get a better view here. It's pretty detailed. You can't really see maybe,
but it's really detailed. It's like a nautilus or something, right? There's another one here too.
What's this one? Whoa. This one feels weird. What the fuck is this? Whoa. This one's crazy.
Oh my God. It's like a, it's a fucking skeleton. This is actually a skeleton. Are you ready for
the reveal? Check this out. It's like a rib cage or something. Look at that. It's like a,
of like an animal's rib cage. It's like embedded in there. It's crazy looking. It's like a big
fossilized bug or something, whatever it is. What's it called? It's trilobite. It's an ancient pill
bug. All of a sudden, like six legs break out from the sides and like, like crawls in my mouth.
What is, what is that? Extinct marine anthropods that form one of the earliest known groups of
anthropods. The first appearance. So this is a legit fucking real animal here. Whoa. Whoa. It's
weird. It's like, you can see its tail. I didn't show you this part. See, see like that ridge in
the middle there. That's like its tail. Whoa. This is weird. Whoa. Cool. All right. It's going
back in the bag. That's what they looked like? Dude, it moved. I want to look at this one again.
You guys saying this is not a tooth. This is like a leaf. I know for a fact that they described them
when they sent them. I just kind of forget. It's been a while. Yeah. Look at the pattern on that.
That's insane looking. Look at it. It's like a, is it a leaf? It's wild looking. Some kind of shell.
Yeah. That's cool. Yeah. Well, what a perfect time to do that. I'm probably going to wash my hands.
I think. I don't know. I feel like if you touch like a 5 million year old animal, I feel like
I don't want to like put my hands on my face. Is that weird? Like, I feel like I should wash my hands.
Shouldn't I? All right. I'll be right back. I'm going to wash my hands. Give me one second.
Yeah. I guess. I don't know. I don't want to have like some 10 million year old bacteria
get into my body or something. All right. Let's go. It's a rock. It doesn't matter.
Remember it's a rock. I don't know. It could be something. It could be embedded. Some kind
of bacteria or something. Who eats rocks? I'm not going to put like my hands on a rock and
put my hands in my mouth. I put my hands in my face all the time. You did. You eat rocks.
That was, that was for research purposes, not for to eat for pleasure, right? That wasn't for me.
I wasn't hungry. That was for research purposes to determine where, how old that rock could have
been. That was for research purposes. That was for me to determine how old the rock was. I think he's
on meth. That was cool. They look like face huggers. Yeah they do.
Look up isopods. They're like dinosaur bugs. Yeah that's, they're scary. They're scary. Okay.
Back to the game. Oh I'm in like, this is a bigger open world now. All right. So we're going to go
through the same thing. What's the map look like? Where's the dig site? There is none. I just have
to go find it. Let's go. Mouse sensitivity has got to go down, like way down. There we go. Do I have
enough boxes? I need boxes. I need my excavation equipment to be loaded. Changing cars and fast
travel. Yeah you can change cars and travel around. Off-road. An important part of the hub
is the laptop workstation. Change the car if you feel like it. Okay. Fuel tanks are used to refill
gas canisters. I feel like that's not going to be too important but it might be later. On the hub
you'll find the equipment necessary to set up your excavation as well as empty boxes for transporting
fossils. Put the crates with the fossils that you want to transport to the museum in the highlighted
area. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Let's go. Press E. Okay I want a few of these right?
Car managing station. Car switching and fast travel. Once you have hired the right employees
to be able to use the fast travel tab. Yeah you need to hire employees to fast travel. That's
good to know. And I can just switch cars with the laptop. Okay. Hack digging tools. Car trunk
is full. With what? What's in the trunk? What do you mean it's full? Pick up canister. Canister
into the car. Okay. All right so we're good right? These simple crates can be packed only into the
back of the trunk which is occupied at the moment. So why? Can I not bring these? Are they? I think
there's already a couple already in there. I don't know. I need to make two trips. What about over
here? Can I like go over there? Is it my free to explore now? What should I set up? What about
like right here? Being in the mine. Dumbledore's voice? Notice the excavation area in its lowest
part. This is where I was to start my search. When have I ever done a Dumbledore impression? Strong
wind to destroy the excavation equipment. So my first job was to clean up the exploration area
and set up a new fence. I've never done a Dumbledore impression. Well okay I'll try. Oh Harry
as you know the three houses must come together in harmony Harry. Like that? Is that good?
So much shit everywhere. Hold on. That was Voldemort. That was Harry Potter Dumbledore.
Oh yes his full name. Harry Potter Dumbledore. No I said name of the series colon name of the
character. Hey there's so much. Okay I do have to clear the whole road of this bullshit.
I'm not doing it. I'm just clearing this part to drive over it. Do your classic Cookie Monster
voice. Cookie Monsters like Tasmanian Devil. You have to go all in or it's not going to work.
You can't do a Cookie Monster impression by just going like oh it's me. No no no you have to go
all in please. All right four-wheel drive come on. I don't want to clear this whole thing. I just
want to go. Maybe it'll unstuck me on the other side. You just put me on top of these. Wait no
it worked. Oh my god come on unstuck it again. I'm already over the thing. I'm already there.
There we go. All right we're good. So where do I want to set up shop here?
Do a Cookie Monster impression now. I forget what Cookie Monster sounds like.
It's like it's like you need like almost like a voice changer with it. Hold on.
What does Cookie Monster sound like? It's like um what does it sound like? It's kind of like
cookies. I love cookies right? Something like that. I don't know it's something like that.
The problem is that I didn't I didn't go all in. Let me try to let me go all in with it and see
what happens. This cookie is delicious. I love cookies. Oh yes cookies. That's not that's not
really not that good but I mean it's how do you even do it? It's so gravely that it kind of hurts.
That's just an orc. Done building ship. Done building ship.
We need more gold. I'm done doing that. I'm not doing it ever fucking again for the rest
of my life. None of you are going to hear that ever again. I promise. You notice it's the ow.
It's the dob dob dob part. I fucking hate that. Don't you? Like the dob dob dob nom nom right?
It's like shut up. I hate it. That's the worst impression. No it's not. It's not even close.
All right I gotta secure the area. Secure it. Left mouse button. I need to secure this area.
Let's go. Secure it. Secure it. Secure it. I can't. I'm clicking. Secure it. Secure the area. Oh there
we go. All right we can skip this. I'm excited now. Now we get to actually do the the fun part.
Why would I drop down to the sky? Okay use your laptop to transport crates by drones.
Oh I can call it? Really? Well let's just let's do this. Let's get started here. Other tool
information. What about the other tools? Underwater fossil searching. Okay turn it on. Suck out all the
water. All right diving. Dry the area. Suck out all the water. Shallow water that blocks digging
must be pumped out with a diesel water pump. Place it in the highlighted spot. Turn it on and wait
until the water is completely pumped out. And then connect the lamp in case it gets dark out.
And then you got a generator just in case it gets some new electricity. All right other tools. All
right let's go. Uh let's pump it up. Wait I need my uh device right? These have fossils in them?
I'm fucking drowning. Okay okay you can die. All right I need my um this is a death mechanic. You
almost became a fossil. I need um my thing. Uh where's the the little ghost buster tool? Did
I bring my ghost buster tool? There it is. I'm just gonna go clean them up and throw them over
here. Just remember that's where those are. All right let's do an inspection here. Anything? Nope
what about the one I threw over here? Nope nope okay. I have to take them out and throw them.
There's a giant gold nugget. What would that be worth? A gold nugget this big would be worth
how much? Like a few million? Isn't this some asteroid or something that's worth like 50
trillion dollars in gold or something? Yes there is. There is right? Am I just making that up?
All right I gotta check on these ones. My uncle has that asteroid. Are you serious?
You're not even you're not subscribed. What he's these guys this this guy's got a net worth of
like 50 trillion dollars. All right let me check these. But what if he doesn't like your stream?
What if he does though? There's nothing in any of these shitty rocks. Something's moving in this
one. This one's gonna hatch. Okay I don't want to get confused because I'll- my uncle learned how
to do a kick flip last week. You're not subscribed either but you didn't celebrate your uncle's kick
flip and subscribe here? Really? I don't think there's anything even down here. I'm just doing
this for no reason. So uncool. Yeah I mean that's like not cool. I don't want to have to keep
coming down here throwing rocks. Can I just suck up all the water? One of these has to have something
right? Yeah! What is it? I can't identify it. Oh he's he's he's having a monologue here.
What's huge? What is it? What did you find?
All right is it gold? No it's something something actually pretty important I think. I think it's
important. General Macerous Albertensis.
Oh shit my power might go up. Did you see that? Uh oh.
Uh did it blink? Did you guys see the power like that the lights just like uh okay well
oh power doesn't go up. There's probably more in here. It's probably the whole dinosaur for
god's sake. I'm gonna have to do this. Okay just bear with me. It's gonna be the whole
dinosaur down here. Yeah of course it is. All right the whole dinosaur is down here.
That's such an excuse to end the stream early. Bro my power just flickered. What?
Like you could just see the lights flick. I I said oh man uh power's gonna go off probably
guys sorry stream's probably uh what are you talking about? You just you just watched it.
Save the game? I got an autosave. Junk. Wait what happened to the one I just was looking at?
Where is it? Okay that's the tail. Yeah this is the same one. Tail set two. Back right limb.
All right send this back to the um I gotta send these back all right send these back.
20 fingers am I holding up? Zero. You're typing in a chat room. All right small crate. Delivery
of crates called drone. Do I not have it? I can't do it? Did I not upgrade it? Nothing here right?
There's definitely at least one or two. The head has to be in here. The whole thing's in here.
Bro just carry them. I don't want to carry them. What are you talking about? That's so far.
Can I throw these out? No. I'll do three at a time. That's probably easiest.
Bingo. Oh two here. Okay let's break it up. This game I like this game. I'm skipping class
for the stream. You need to be funny. No you need to go to class and turn off your phone or your
laptop whatever it is and not be watching the stream. What are you doing?
You need to be focusing on class right now.
Okay so this is plastered up. Can these fit in with more than one thing? You're learning
archaeology right now. Do your fucking homework. Do your homework. All right that's a left limb. I
don't have enough space. I need more crates. Um all right well I have to I gotta what do I do
with this? I can't hold on. You're such a teacher. I need to have a drone come pick it up. Wait can
I just do it? How come you're so catty tonight? I don't know. What do you what does that mean?
Why am I so catty? Am I catty tonight? Name the field of research. This is paleontology.
Okay well I can at least store the other ones. Have to come back and upgrade or something.
Can I put this on the roof? Dude I can't even store this on the roof. Are you shitting me?
I need to put it in the storage area for the drone. I can't. Shit. Oh well I think I can at least
store this one. Um okay so where do I get another pallet right here? Small crate three to six.
Large crates. I can't. I don't think I can pick these up. I think I actually have to drive that back.
All the drone. Yeah I can't. I don't think I have it like unlocked. I don't think I have it unlocked.
My uncle is skipping work to watch the stream. These aren't. You're in a
set stop. The laptop. Yeah look look look look. I just. What? Laptop. Management station. E.
I can't do anything. Pallet two. Small crate full. I can't. I think I have to upgrade this.
I think I have to buy it or something. E. E. Cancel. Yeah I need to upgrade it. I'm using
this stream to de-stress. Nice. Hope you hope it works. Hope it's good. All right I don't know.
I don't know. I don't get it. I think it's because I have small crates and not large crates here.
This game was fun. This is a cool game. I like this game. This was cool. But now I'm gonna play
House of the Dead. This was fun. Oh my god. Jesus. Okay we're good. This was fun. I had a good time.
Played it for like three hours. That was fun. It was cool to hang out. Let's play House of the Dead.
I've been looking. I wanted to play that. It was a good time to play it. Jesus Christ. Is everything
gonna be all right? The stream might just get turned off. All right give me one sec.