Here comes the huntsman. Here comes the huntsman. I am the huntsman. I will shoot you in the face.
Get out of here, spy. Yeah. What do you know? What do you know about that? Shpee.
What do you know about that one? Shpee. What do you know about that one, Shpee?
That's a triple kill.
And spies?
No, no, no, no, no, no. Get out of here, Shpee.
I got him. At least I got the Shpee.
Hey, medic. How are you? Hey, spy. Time to singumentary. You want me to singumentary right now?
Do you understand what a singumentary is? You know what? Just get... Both of you guys are just done.
You see that headshot. You see that headshot. Just two in a row. Make it three in a row. Make it four in a row.
Actually, was that four in a row? I don't even know.
Get that headshot, girl. You gotta play. Team Fortress 2 is on its way. Got Star in the call and he's playing ten million. What is he doing that for?
I gotta beat this because you beat it. I feel like less of a man.
Come on. Are you sure you don't want to have two default snipers sitting in spawn AFK?
I'm sure. I want them there. I told them to stay there.
Are you sure that you want to have two default snipers sitting AFK in spawn?
Yeah, I told them to stay there. We need them there. What if they start spawn camping us?
Yeah, what if?
Oh, I'm on the red team. Toadman.
Hey, you made it. You made it on the team?
Toadman.
Oh, great. Where are you? Oh, hi, Toadman. Hi.
You want to high five me? Fine. Here's a high five.
I've never seen this joke before.
You're ruining this whole game. You're going to be. No, this is it.
No, with me again.
The I blew up joke. I don't want to see that again.
You're going to see it again.
No, I'm not. Because it's three, two, one, go. Go.
This scout is so toast. Damn it. I said that so preliminarily.
Wow. Is this mad, Jerma?
No. Is this what it's like when you're mad, Jerma?
Because you're mad right now.
You mad right now?
All right, come here.
Come here. I want you to go as fast as possible.
That sounded like a little kid.
I want to get up top, but we can't get up top.
Here, come with me. Come with me. You ready to come with me? You ready to come with me?
Don't whip me. I might blow myself up.
No, don't. If you blow yourself up right now.
Watch out for this stupid scout dickhead.
Oh, look, you got to spawn. Who cares? Let's go.
Let's go left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left. We're doing a flanking maneuver.
Do you know what that means? Have you ever been to school?
You're way faster than me. Hold on. Come here. Come here. Hit detection.
Rocket jump. Rocket jump.
That's a spy scout. That's got to be.
Do you like that sick rocket jump, rocket jump, kill?
Here we go. Center down. Center down. Center down. Make it happen.
What are you playing, Pyro? I'm a sniper.
I was just walking with you just with me.
I don't remember my memory. I have a memory of an elephant.
Reverse. There's going to be a scout coming up here.
What? No, he's going to kill me. No, I'm going to get.
I'm going to get panned. Oh, do you shut up?
Shut your mouth. I'm not talking.
I got him to 150. You see that 150? No, did you see that 150?
But we were moving on.
Oh, your day. Shit.
Did you see that 150? Yeah, on me. That guy 150'd me.
Did you see that 150? Did you see that 150?
Star, I have a really serious question for you.
Did you see that 150? I'm going to soil my diaper.
I'm a baby. I soiled my baby diaper.
There's a spy behind you. What? You are such a troll.
I really thought. I seriously thought.
No, no, seriously behind you now. Shut up.
No, are you serious?
I'm checking everybody because of this.
I have a feeling that you are just being a dick weed right now.
Yeah, you totally are.
There's a scout running at slower speed.
I wonder if he's like a spy. He's got like the pistol out.
I don't know. I just heard.
I seriously heard the dead ringer. I'm not kidding.
Got to be the most obvious spy, not spy you can be.
Can I get a heal too? Could I get. Could you heal me?
Please God.
There's a health kit down here.
Yeah, it's a little tiny shitty one.
Oh my God, you're the worst.
This guy's going to die because of you.
Did you see what you've done? Did you make it down there?
Do you see what you've done?
Okay, I'm going in.
What do you mean you're going in?
I'm going in. I'm not going in.
I need health.
Yeah, it would be great if I got that health too.
This guy actually did it.
Watch out, crits.