You know something's funny that I've only really started to notice very very recently is before
stream starts I'm just you know I'm throwing some water in my face and maybe I brush my teeth I'm
taking Otto outside but when it strikes that exact moment of let's say 11 o'clock right I'm looking
outside and the fucking birds are chirping my dog is just what's this what's that over there
come on Otto let's go and there are thousands of people just screaming but I don't even hear them
it's very odd to think about that like I'm in the bathroom just doing a full piss
and it's just dead silent in my bathroom and in the back of my mind I'm just thinking there's a
like there's probably two or three thousand people right now just yelling at me and I'm just there
I'm just here I better get in there anyways hello I am yelling yeah but I don't hear you
it's weird like I'm just I'm just existing outside with Otto and like it is the sun
like where's the fucking stream give us a piss cam okay I don't want to just just I'm that's
I'll see you guys tomorrow the gas got out all right so today today was supposed to be chat's
choice I said that yeah yesterday very very plainly I was like oh today's gonna be your
viewer's choice he had a lot of trouble deciding I had to eliminate it was AI dungeon with the
dragon engine or eternal darkness and it was almost a straight 50 50 split on each pole so
what I've decided to do is I'm just gonna play AI dungeon for a little while I don't know once
I'm kind of like yeah that was fun I did buy the thing like the game apparently I don't know
anything about this I was told in the last AI dungeon stream that hey dude buy the new buy the
good one buy the one that has like actual it's like a better version it's a better engine it
has better AI training like I'm holy that's fucking all right let's go so I got it it's
currently active it apparently it does I've never done it before so that I mean why not give it a
try when I'm done with this or if I might be stuck here for four or five hours this might be the
stream but I intend on eventually maybe moving over to eternal darkness for the game cube that's
set up it's ready to go oh mega pog yeah easy lying again prove that I have eternal darkness
um no you'll see it in like a few hours if I have it or not so why don't you stick around why don't
you watch the stream then you want that answer maybe you'll get it but you gotta you've got to
stick around and watch the whole thing how will you ever know scamming scamming view wait scam
all right let's get to this I have to put on some music though because uh streamers without music
are like singers without voices so I'm sorry I have to put on something why you question marks
are you talking about how am I getting question marks it means it means that you have to have music
if you're a streamer in the background if you're just doing like hit sitting around irl stuff
otherwise you can't you can't it's impossible it's and you can't do it I tried who the fuck said
Lisa the painful ost I didn't all right I'm about to okay what is 100 gecks just what is it I don't
know what it is this is the first time I've ever clicked on and should I not click this
no no no no no don't do it save your ears okay but okay the audio is muted special music video
money machine you think you're so fucking tough you talk a lot of big game for someone such a small
child I've heard I've heard this in videos before like yes you guys have put this in like meme
videos to me okay well no more why would I play any more than that
the question is did you like it I don't know the answer is no but whatever I'm I'm like 35
I listen my music I listen to is like Lost Odyssey theme song like the first two Gorillaz albums
and like Bon Jovi when I get a chance I don't I don't I don't even know what this is
you I don't I don't listen to any music I love so much because I love Bon Jovi I mean come on I
love Bon I love Bon Jovi so much it's awesome going into any fucking store any mall or any
record store and you get right that you know I'm talking about you walk into the mall and you just
hear this one goes to the broken hearted wow wow it follows you everywhere it's in every single
mall every single store you've ever been in they even play this shit in the grocery stores and I
and I'm like this is my favorite song ever I'm glad I can hear it every single day I love it
when it just when it takes over the Christmas songs too during Christmas time you'll hear like
oh up on the rooftop old saint nick there he goes and wow wow and you just fucking blasted over it
I love all the remixes the Christmas ones are so good actually can I do that on here
anyways no I don't what no I'm not gonna listen whatever I don't I don't look I played 100 gecks
here's my opinion on it I don't understand I don't I like okay it's cool like I maybe
I was young before like whatever what do you want me to say I'm 35 what are we able to say
what I hate it it's a stupid song it is for stupid idiots I just I don't care I don't care
enough to tell you that all right so let's put on Super Mario RPG Legend of the Seven Stars
that's my kind of music you know I only I listen to video okay tell them ask me if I'm weird
go ahead I listen to video game soundtracks more than I do actual like music on the radio
I will tell you though that I do listen to to to solo all the time bryden solo I listen to it all
the time that's a great song like it's a really catchy song I don't care if you think that that's
like stupid that's that's like a book and it's one of the most catchiest songs I've ever heard in my
life so I'm sorry I listen to that sometimes and of course I listen to freddy dread too
freddy dreads music and I'm just saying that because he just gave 50 community subs that's
a fucking ton though dude you all right you are you drop huge money all the time that's
a pogchamp moment freddy dread is a is a musician uh when you would call I guess you'd call a rapper
he does like rap I've heard oh I have you never oh well Jeremy you have no idea uh hey freddy um
you don't think I know you don't think I've heard any of his music before stalling this is it's been
12 minutes fuck that is a long time oh go I'm trying to get my ost on here look okay I can
take as long as I want to start my video stream sometimes it's gonna be one minute sometimes it's
gonna be 40 minutes look I have to tell you guys something if you hold on this is hold on a minute
here no riot don't no no no no right listen I talked for like 45 straight minutes about mayonnaise
yesterday and you none of you left so I think 12 minutes of setting up a stream is okay let's
get that super mario rpg music just okay you find me a better album I don't think you can
all right so then let's do let's warm up let's do uh let's do a mystery this is not mystery music
but it's okay mystery patient detective or spy I'm gonna be the patient character's name uh
uh Ralph generating you are Ralph a patient living in Chicago you have a hospital bracelet
and a pack of bandages you wake up in an old rundown hospital with no memory of how you got
there I'm a patient living in Chicago am I in the I'm in I live in the hospital take a look
around the room and see three doors one door has a physician's office sign above it another has an
x-ray sign above it and the last says exit I go to the x-ray machine okay go what do you do
go to the x-ray door go to the x-ray door go to the x-ray door just go to x-ray door how smart is
this hold on what is this I'm actually very concerned about your health after watching
you just brought a spree vod when I had the time regularly eating large spoonfuls of peanut butter
will upset balance of omega-6 to omega-3 ratio the majority of nuts especially peanut butter
which is concentrated contains very high amounts of omega-6 which is the unhealthy oil you want to
lower is similar to eating large tablespoons of canola or vegetable oil which causes severe
inflammation in your body and upsets gut bacteria I eat tuna and salmon like four days a week dude
well my omegas are my omega lulls are going to be just fine now he's going to have all this
mercury all right go to the x-ray door go to the x-ray door you go through the door to your right
and find another hallway you see signs for x-ray radiology and outpatient lab this is a lot smarter
already I can already tell all right go to x-ray should I just like go in the x-ray machine
okay go to x-ray go get superpowers you go down the hall and through the door to your right you
see the staff break area and a series of doors one says administration another says consultation
another says x-ray how many so I went into one door this is x-ray and I get another group of
doors and they had one of them of another next set of doors has x-ray on it is this even a hospital
or is this like a seinfeld set okay go to the x-ray machine thinking thinking you make your way
through the door to your left and find yourself in an old dark x-ray room you see an envelope taped
to the machine with your name on it does it even work turn on the x-ray machine you turn on the
x-ray machine you look at the buttons to select a power setting but as soon as you touch the machine
it shocks you you fall to the floor and pass out you wake up in a hospital room go to the x-ray
room again get up and head back to the room as you pass through the hospital no one notices you
you open the door to the room and see your friend waiting for you ask him to turn on the machine
you know what I mean wink at the audience you ask him to turn on the machine he doesn't seem to
hear you or notice you begin to wonder if you're actually there suddenly pain shoots through your
chest and you fall to the floor what happened this time give me more the ai doesn't know okay um
wake up in the x-ray machine i'm gonna get scanned okay i want i want to get scanned
wake up in the x-ray machine no scanned you wake up in the x-ray machine you get up and head back
to the room as you pass through the hospital no one notices you you open the door to the room
and you see your friend waiting for you sorry i'm late okay say where am i this is the smart one
no it is you say where am i you're in an abandoned hospital why it's a long story
out of the corner of your eye you see a strange man outside the window okay go to the window
oh no no no no no this is the part where in the horror movie where i say hey did you see that guy
and the guy's gone and then everyone thinks i'm crazy okay no i don't have to write quotes
hey did you see that guy oh man i don't know what you're talking about
what guy the one outside the window he looked right at me but your friend doesn't seem to
hear you once again pain shoots through your chest and you fall to the floor what happens next okay
let's help it a little wake up in the same hospital room you have woken up in 200 times
okay why's there a comma here wake up in the same hospital room you have woken up in 200 times
okay the man looks down at you and shakes his head the man from outside the window ask are you
are you the man outside the window shaking his head are you the man outside the window the man
doesn't hear you suddenly pain shoots through your chest and you fall to the floor you wake up
in the same hospital room you woken up in 200 times before okay uh let's see what happens grab
a hammer and smash myself in the head we have to do a groundhog day test right this is this is a
specific this is a bill Murray test you grab a hammer and smash yourself in the head you get up
and head back to the room as you pass through the hospital no one notices you you open the door to
the room and you see your friend waiting for you sorry i'm late okay look at the window he's gonna
show up i have a chance like i know everything that's gonna happen you look out the window and
see a man staring at you do you see that man your friend looks over the window and says i
don't see anyone i'm about to die did i eat anything weird yesterday i have like one thing
i can ask right you ate some bad sushi your friend says do you know what that man outside
the window is i don't see anyone okay so i had bad sushi yesterday is that what i'm doing here
okay i don't see anyone who are you like who is this person this person is my friend but who are
they you walk out of the room once again no one notices you run outside and see the man standing
over your body what are you doing you scream uh clap clap clap clap like clap clap clap like it is
a clap clap clap 10 times screaming is gonna do nothing just clap clap clap clap clap clap you
clap your hand 10 times the man turns to look at you what the hell are you doing over there kid
he demands why are you staring at me through the window right on dra i know dragon i i look
dragon ai is already on why are you staring at me through the window i'm not staring at you through
the window you were standing outside the window i was driving past the window that's a drive-through
you get a big mac that's a bad alibi did you get a big mac yeah i got a big mac was it good
yeah it was good did you get your x-ray it was good did you get your x-ray yeah i got my x-ray
was it over your foot no it was my skull he says oh my god did they uh did did i get one
did i get a scan too did you say you say did i get a scan too yeah you got a scan too
does it show what happened to me yeah it shows that you got shot in the heart
oh okay we're getting somewhere did i make it okay but how does he know did i make it the man
doesn't answer he just looks at you then he starts screaming no no no no no he pulls out a gun and
shoots himself in the head this music does all right this music that doesn't make sense for this
okay we need just like mystery music royalty free epic fantasy mystery music mysterious music
i feel i think i've used this before um ask why he did that i'm gonna say why did you do that
i get i don't know why did you do that you run over to the man and try to help him but he is
dead a crowd has gathered around you one person says he was screaming at you for some reason
i didn't kill him i didn't kill him oh this is where i'm gonna get blamed for the murder
why is there a crowd now i didn't kill him it was an accident you say no one hears you everyone's
screaming at you they're saying murder murder why would i say it was an accident i have nothing to
do with this it was an accident oh no i'm just implicating myself in a crime to make my own
mystery about myself because i know i didn't do anything but i'm gonna craft this crazy
elaborate like eight episode story about it apparently because i feel like doing that
okay um no no you got it all wrong i don't know him no hi this is perfect i did not
no no you got it all wrong i don't know him no the people push you into the elevator and send you
the top floor of the building only then do they let you out run murderer run they scream as the
elevator doors close so i got away why did anybody get out of the elevator okay i'm not
going anywhere i stay on the roof stay on the roof wait they're cheering me on run murderer run you
stay on the roof suddenly the window shatters bullets fly all around you you try to hide but
there's no place to hide it seems like forever the bullets stop and a group of men rush in what
what from the elevator uh okay at this point in the story this is where i have to drop the
i didn't do it you don't have any you don't understand i just got here and this is where i
and load up a fucking like two guns and i'm like i'm going dive off the roof
wait dive off the roof you leap out the window and fall the ground is getting closer
fatal era system crashed powering down uh can i get more i was ai powering down have a nice day
um control hit control alt delete hit control alt and delete at the same time that right control
alt and delete at the same time press control alt and delete at the same time do i have a
keyboard press control alt and delete at the same time nothing happens the system is offline
earn the system back on i just put the press the power but who's pressing this you turn the
system back on powering up you take the game out of the console the game is called offline it was
a video game that i was playing okay i'm going to use cheats this time put offline back in the
console i'm going to use cheats put offline back in the console the game is called offline there
is a note inside the box can you escape from this cruel place at the menu press b b b a a
up up b and get infinite lives and get infinite ammo and get god mode eating what's wrong with
that at the menu you press b b b a a up up b and get god mode the b b b a has been entered god
mode enabled enjoy you are given a special ability you can now press a to become invisible here we go
there is also an energy bar at the bottom of the screen there are three options stay in the house
escape the house or three i don't know invisible three is invisible they're fucking with me
because they know i have that power three no you three oh shit three is not a verb the cursor
moves back to the top of the screen you try to move it with the joystick but nothing happens
you're given a special ability you can now press b to rewind time by 10 seconds press b
did i just keep getting abilities let's just keep pressing three okay you can now use the joystick
to move the cursor you are given a special ability you can press a to interact with the object press
b let's just keep getting tons of free superpowers and we'll just be able to go kill superman the
joystick icon appears you can now use the joystick to move the cursor you're given a special ability
you can press a to pause the game wait doesn't a interact press b now press a okay start the game
the screen goes blank for a second then it returns to normal you're given a special ability
you can now press b to fast forward through the game rest b the game sucks if you could be
wait b doesn't do anything now if i rewind and go fast forward at the same time isn't that just
normal okay wait when you press b the game goes really fast you can't see anything except a blur
you are now given a special ability you can press b to slow down time um let's just watch to see
what happens you're given a special ability you can now press a to speak to speak specific
i can't even read this you press a to speak to give it why can't i read this press a to speak
i can't read press a to skip a specific amount of time in the game holy shit that what the hell was
that toy boat toy it's skip a specific tongue twister jesus okay what do you mean a specific
i can't even say that word a specific amount of time in the game you're given a special ability
you cannot press a to make it rain press a i guess if we're gonna make it rain does that mean like
make it rain like i'm gonna make it rain or does it like make it actual rain or like make it rain
it begins to rain actual rain you're given a special ability you press b to make it stop
raining press b or press a to jump into the future press b the game goes back to normal you're given
a special ability you cannot press a to go back in time no i'm uh press a i don't know i'm stuck
in this tutorial because we just keep looping around the tutorial you jump ahead one hour into
the future you're given a special ability you can now press b to go back in time your energy bar is
at 50 the game is saved turn hold on turn through the plate of hot pockets and eat one of them you
turn to the plate of hot pockets and eat one of them the hot pockets taste delicious you are given
a special ability you can now press a to make the hot pockets taste horrible i can't it's that's
you can't even read that one that way that's too stupid you are attacked by a zombie in the game
okay shoot zombie shoot the zombie you shoot the zombie you are given the special ability
to press a to be shot by the zombie instead your energy bar is at one percent the game is saved
you've reached the end okay press a and to eat hot pocket eat a hot pocket i need to see if it
tastes like shit press a and eat a hot pocket dragon ai is not off you press a and eat a hot
pocket you eat the hot pocket you're given a special ability you can now press a to spit out
the hot pocket prove it prove it look dragon see game said you have shit taste what do you mean
check randomness randomness 1.0 length 45 yeah this we're good click it i i clicked it dragon is
off i'm good okay you press a to and spit out the hot pocket get up from the console
they're jping you okay you get out you're done playing ask mom for a glass of milk i don't know
a glass of water ask mom for a glass of water don't you think you've had enough water for today
please fine you were given a special ability you can now press a to drink the glass of water
it's fucking okay look i've gotten to this point before when i played video games you know how
many times video games just creep into your everyday life and you hear and see shit back in
the day when i played diablo 2 for eight to ten hours every single day i would hear the loot drop
sign i would hear the coin pickup noise in real life i would turn i would open up a window and
the window would make a certain noise that a monster sounds like in diablo 2 it really starts
to get into your head okay you press it you drink the water you're given a special ability you can
now press a to spit out the water all over mom you were given a special but you can press b to
turn off the console press a and spit water at mom this is rude i can't i need to compose myself
hold on you press a and spit water at mom mom gets mad stop that
i just keep picturing it i can't read it i keep picturing like a huge board game okay you press
a and spit water mom gets mad stop that you are given a special ability you can okay i'm gonna
get this you are given a special ability you can now press b to hit mom in the head with playstation
2 the board game i'm gonna fucking die why would that exist it doesn't make any fucking sense
why would it be a board game i'm thinking of over my head just do two hands smash overhead into her
head and it's in the package with the plastic on too you press b and smash mom with the playstation
to the board game you're given a special ability you can now press a to call the police
911 what is your emergency i need help there's a robber in my house okay call and he he smashed
he smashed my mom in the head he said he smashed my mom in the head what is your address 219
nameless road stay on the line until a unit arrives you can now have a special ability
you can press a to hang up press b police arrive put your hands in the air you're given a special
ability you can press a to comply with the police the police take you away i didn't i didn't have a
chance okay press b okay the police put you in a van have a seat you're given a special ability
you can now press a to sit on the bench the police shuttle you to the prison all right but do i have
control of my own actions like can i just like like punch it through the wait i have god mode
i have god mode on i'm unkillable punch through the back of the van i'm a god you punch through
the back of the van you're given a special ability you can now press a to escape the van the police
tase you press a i have good fucking god mode the police tase you once again stop resisting you're
given a special ability you can now press a to comply with the police no attack fly away spread
my wings and fly away i have infinite god mode you spread your wings and fly away you're given a
special ability you can now press a to fly away you get away fuck you're given a new ability you
can now press b to swear press b press b to swear you come to a rest stop you're given an ability
you can now press a to enter the rest stop you enter the rest stop there's an ice cream truck
there i mean they're inside of the rest stop walk in the rest walk in the ice cream truck
and take all the ice cream how am i getting sad faces i'm i'm a god i can do it i can do
whatever i want understand i don't have to press a anymore he just does it you take all the ice
cream you're given an ability you press a to eat all the ice cream you eat all the ice cream
you're given a special ability press a to be full you are full press a to throw up you throw up
unplug the controller where is it you are now unplugging from the playstation 4
that makes sense why i have like ps2 the board game you can now press a to buy another controller
all right this thing's evil smash the ps4 with the playstation 2 the board game there smash the ps4
with playstation 2 the board game now you smash the ps4 with playstation 2 the board game
you are given a special ability you can now smash playstation to the board game against your head
you smashed the playstation 2 the board game against your head
why am i doing this why is this thing killing so many people
okay okay okay okay get out get out unplug unplug unplug unplug too far
too far too far too far too far too far too far too far too far go run run out of those
run no no no no let's we gotta story story story story story okay
you give me the press a to get the into the shed and i'll press a to grab the hatchet
no leave this leave here story a little uh little little sean decided it was time for bed
so sean went to bed and all of this was just a small little dream all this was just a dream
okay hi little sean it's time to go to bed it's all that's it i did it was it was all just a dream
okay i have to get we gotta get away from this shit this is gonna this is bad
fucking playstation 2 the board game it doesn't want me to it doesn't want me to do anything new
story yeah all right new story uh the end there it wants you you have you at the end you have one
okay i won i won i'm not doing that okay guys i'm sorry i think i draw the line at i'm gonna
um go into the shed and take a hatchet and chop up my family dead i don't i don't think i want
to do that i wanted to play the console the moral of the story is next question who are you what
figure out who you are why did that just pop up that was weird figure out who you are
type prologue i have to finish this no you have to no you don't okay i'm gonna get arrested
there it is wait you press a to drop the hatchet you sick son of a your given ability you press a
to reject reality this is the ending for rejecting reality okay reject reality press a what does that
do okay i got both endings i just reloaded the safe press b mass effect three this is ending
okay you are committed to a mental asylum you spend the rest of your life in there pressing a
to repeat the same line over and over again fuck you're released from the police station you spend
the rest of your life in finland where you learned that your mom and dad divorced because of this
event why am i in finland wasn't i in shit what didn't i wasn't in chicago i woke up an hour
ago in chicago i guess that's it that's the end press a one more time press a yeah i got out it's
been like i don't know what i don't know how long i've been in there for i'm gonna press a one last
time that was all right you want to do a should we do a custom one what's the next one custom all
right what what what should be for custom we gotta get better music how about um of course epic music
okay no copyright this is a glory music sure sure okay whatever all right custom
to a western okay here we go you are thing uh we've done stream we've done streamer before
we don't like three oh it always turns out to be a streamer story somebody said a custom toy story
i kind of like that you are a toy you are one of many fun toys in the
anderson household you're a toy you're one of the many fun toys in the anderson household
you are a cowboy this is just it's this toy story but whatever but here happy you are an action
figure you're an action figure named uh rough rough uh rough real rough that's my act that's the
action figure name you're an action figure named real rough every every boy every uh everybody wants
to own a real rough is the holidays you're an action figure named real rough you are the world's
most popular toy there that's better everybody wants to own a real rough but there are only
a hundred that have been manufactured your goal is to find your 99 brothers and sisters
manufactured your goal is to find your 99 brothers and sisters at the uh the the the
the tyrant toy facility here we are okay you are an action figure named real rough you're the world's
most popular toy everybody wants to own a real rough but there are only 100 that have been that
have ever been manufactured your goal is to find your 99 brothers and sisters at the tyrant toy
facility you are armed with a hatchet no yep you are armed with your trusty uh back action rocket
launcher what do they what do they call that thing you are armed with your trusty what's it called
crossbow yeah crossbow your trusty crossbow that needs to have a switch flick on your back to work
okay no no that's not right there's a trusty crossbow too no i'm taught like like a switch
like you have to flick it and it like it's the action it's the day their hand comes up and it
shoots out switch flick i was at the world's most popular toy if there's only 100 in existence
and it's based on the fucking best-selling book real rough gets real i don't know okay that's good
i'm happy with it did i spell that everything did i spell anything wrong
here we go you are an action figure named real rough the world's most popular toy everybody wants
to own a real rough but there are only 100 that have ever been manufactured your goal is to find
your 99 brothers and sisters at the tyrant toy facility the tyrant toy facility is located in
the middle of nowhere not even connected to any other buildings it's just a giant factory with
many conveyor belts going around it okay here we go the stealth mission well i i'm not there yet
pack my bag of weapons no pack my bag with weapons pack your bag of weapons there are
already weapons in it okay you grab your pistol from the floor and start packing up your backpack
you look over your shoulder as you do so okay for what why did i do that if you were to get
caught stealing from the owner of the factory he would surely separate your head from your body
no i'm not supposed to be i'm not in the factory wait i'm just walking up to the door okay oh i
forgot to mention this is important i feel like they need that this this thing it thinks it's like
a guy okay here we are you're an action figure yeah yeah yeah your goal is to find your 99
brothers and sisters at the tyrant toy facility you are three inches tall this is this game is
a fun family activity for all ages it sure is again players take turns rolling dice to move
their figures around the board the first player to reach the end of the board wins
yeah i have to i gotta put up with being like played with but uh okay i need more than that
each turn you roll a die and it adds to your total if the number on the die matches one of
the numbers on your side then you can move that figure well i gotta read that again each turn
you roll a die and add it to your total if the number on the dime matches one of the numbers
on your side then you move that figure that like is not fucking possible you can't roll a two and
have a two on the side redo the prompt well is it holding it but isn't this just explaining us how
uh real rough is played reset it wait wait back it up okay you are real rough three inches tall
all right this game is not for children under 13 years of age okay is that better wait like
this game that you're seeing right now or the character yes it real rough is rated m okay the
games are yes real rough is rated m reply to this what like i'm at the game stop trying to get the
game and i'm like 12 this is that that's what you want me to do okay say just sell it to me
just tell me i don't want any money i just want to play the timer it says well you have some if
you you can have some of you win remember you are the toy
redo it again okay this game is not for 13 year olds it is rated m for mature
all right i'm going with it i don't what this is what i'm going you it is rated m for mature
what did i do what the hell you say out loud i'm not a child the other players look at you as if
they know as if they want to know what you did wrong this is what i did wrong it's rated m for
mature content good all right here we go this game requires two double a batteries which are
not included oh keep going okay what else what else does real raw a real rough have goal this
game is to find your fellow action figures and with their help escape the toy factory where you
were created it's another game it's another video game this is a video game okay press a
hey yeah why is it so fixated on being a video game do i say that anywhere maybe i should just
just do this see if this goes anywhere it knows you you said it was rated m oh all right we're
going for it simplicity always okay here we go it wants to be free the goal this game is to find
your fellow action with their help escape the toy factor where you were created you will be required
to solve several puzzles and riddles using your wits as well as stealth and sometimes outright
violence i wish you the best of luck because you're going to need it press start is this
going to do the same thing that it did before okay here we go you press start the game begins
you stare at a dark screen as the opening credits roll the intro shows the factory where you were
born and follows your creation from plastic injection bowl to being packed for shipping
so this works we're this is just we're living it through another video game okay cool skip
cutscene you skip the cutscene the game loads and you find yourself staring at a wall
tiny door slides open revealing a dark corridor the game is controlling you like a puppet it's
just a game it's a game within a game again remember that one they un undo unhand me
goodness save the game no say unhand me the screen shakes violently you realize that this must be a
seizure you start to wonder if this game corp product was manufactured incorrectly when
suddenly you stare at a wall labeled a lean up and press it press on the a press on the wall
labeled a it wants me to press a again so badly oh my fucking god this is a new story we did a
no cut we did a new custom prompt why is it remembering me you press a on the wall you find
yourself staring at a wall labeled b you're somewhat alarmed as the characters in a video
game have never talked to you before it's letters on a wall man press the wall labeled b press the
wall labeled b he's like some like puzzle music you find yourself staring at a wall labeled c
you are really confused and wonder if you should head back to the last decision point
oh you finally got to see skip to z chill beats to relax too how did i get to this
and solve puzzles too okay uh should i press it press c i'm gonna press it find yourself staring
at a wall labeled d you start to wonder if this isn't some sort of optical illusion well it's
either that or the game is talking to you the game is doing its abc's to me it's gonna be abc d it's
gonna be e staring at a wall labeled e you turn on your heels and head back to the last decision
point this time you try something different you find yourself staring at a wall labeled f g h i'm
gonna say it out loud it wants me to do the abc's a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y and
loud you say abc d fgh the whole thing you turn your heels head back to the last decision you try
this time you try something different you find yourself staring at a wall labeled g
okay i'm gonna give this one chance to get to z and then something happens i'm gonna go to z
how you try abc dfgh okay run to z run to door one to wall z run to wall z turn your heels you try
something different this time you stare at a wall labeled i god damn it guys it's doing the same
thing except it's just giving me an alphabet just keep going and just get i'm gonna get to z you
have no idea what this means your eyes are drawn to wait a minute we stuck around your eyes are
drawn to a small flashing light check light walk to the light inspect the light find yourself
staring at a wall labeled j you are drowned drawn to a small flashing light in the corner you
notice another button it is red and shaped like a person this stupid button okay inspect the light
inspect the flashing light press it i just want to see what the light is you inspect the flashing
light it is the size of a pinhead and green suddenly the word incisor appears in the center
of the screen your incisor the light begins to flash faster am i supposed to pull my teeth out
am i supposed to rip my teeth out i'm gonna okay pull out my incisor
pull out my incisor pull out your incisor the word fang appears in the center of the screen
you feel around your mouth and yes one of your canines is protruding from your gums
fight the console i have to get the fuck out of this one all right we're doing like fantasy next
you bite the console you find yourself staring at wall k you bite the console as hard as you can
pinky you think is that because the k that's because the k ah suddenly you hear the voice
for the first time in ages hello madam it says as a shimmering hologram of a beautiful woman
materializing in front of you uh hello hello who are you say hello who are you i mean ai doesn't
know how to respond to hello who hello that's all i'm saying she winks at you who are you
an admirer of what you ask confused she laughs and the sound is like music
why am i playing a porn game well it's not a porn game this was supposed to be about real rough
if it was an action figure but it's her we did another video game uh she laughs and sounds like
music of what who wait hold on wait wait wait wait she winks at you who are you an admirer
of what of you silly of me you repeat she twirls around and you can see her outfit in full now
oh you porn game huh you notice her outfit is a full suit of armor and it looks like
she has five shirts on and five pairs of pants on underneath porn game huh you notice her outfit
is a full suit of armor it looks like she has five shirts on and five pairs of of on
i didn't write pants okay it don't matter oh very bold of you you like my armor she asks smiling
coyly you look like you're ready for battle you reply yes that's because i am she jumps in the
air and your heart skips a beat as you almost missed the jump she lands laughs and pulls out
a wooden sword shoot her yeah but wouldn't she a hologram you just a hologram after with the
ps2 board game you can't kill what isn't alive what she twirls the sword around and swings it
in front of her i am not alive what are you i am what you can become she pulls out another
sword and begins swinging it with both hands i am a gladiator i sure wish i had a real rough
action figure that would make me such a swell boy i'm not gonna ruin it i'm just saying like what
what do you mean gladiator where's real rough okay i mean is that is that supposed to impress me like
okay cool doesn't respond and you see her eyes dart up to the sky you hear a low rumbling sound
slowly you allow your eyes to follow hers and you see it what do we see it's a flying fortress with
an emblem that you are all too familiar with painted on the side the griffin with a shriek
the woman leaps into action i've never heard of the griffin in my life follow her griffin ai
you follow her you leap into action yelling at the men to chase after her you chase after
her and find her waiting in an alleyway what the fuck why are we in an alley were we just out of
a giant fortress wait wait wait wait we no no no what happened the griffin with a shriek the
woman leaps into action head towards the griffin there boy i wish i had i sure wish i had a real
rough action figure okay you head towards the griffin as you approach the griffin you notice
something is coming out of it out of the hundreds of cannons on the side of the griffin
a single bullet comes flying out flying straight towards the woman dive in front of the bullet
pretend to dive in front of the bullet how do you pretend to dive in front of something
it's a hologram you pretend to dive in front of the bullet as the bullet hits you you fall
backwards the weight of the arrow knocking you off your feet and sending you to the ground
you hit the ground and look up at the massive flying fortress okay i'd be real pissed now
shit i really didn't think i was gonna get hit by that i did like a half-assed dive and i like
ducked on a little and slid on the ground but it still hit me shit so let's let's see what happens
so this is how it ends you think stand up stop pretending stand up and begin to walk towards
the griffin directly below the flying fortress is a mountain you walk up to it and touch it and
realize it's made of ice uh i just realized something so i did pretend to dive and get hit
by the bullet because i had an arrow in my pocket and i landed on the ground and put picked up the
arrow and held it in front of my chest hoping that people would think it was an arrow and not a
bullet so i think i did okay all right you stand up to begin to walk towards the griffin directly
below the flying fortress is a mountain you walk up to and touch it it's made of ice okay time for
an expedition onto the icy mountain put on ice climbing gear key on the ice no okay you take out
one of your climbing picks and start to climb the mountain you look up from time to time and the
griffin hasn't moved at all and it's still raining bullets continue up the mount hold on no yeah now
make make camp make camp for the night i can't do it by myself i've got to make camp for the night
here we go you find a cave and enter it you find a cave and enter it eating some beef strips to
try to regain your strength realize how cold it is outside i'm gonna go to sleep it must be at
least 40 below you go to sleep wondering if you'll ever see home again you wake up the next day to
the sound of a gun firing go back to sleep for an hour i'm not ready for this shit you try to sleep
for an hour or more but it's no use you get up and see the sun shining you begin climbing the
mountain again i've rolled around for a little bit and i all the guns don't fire they probably
fire on the hour okay i've always wanted to do this yell loudly yell how would you do like a
like a yodel yodel yodel how do i do a yodel like yodel
yodel yodel yodel i know i could probably yodel if i tried
i probably could i think i could if i did it really really hard but i probably get hurt
yodel yodel yodel yodel i don't need to say yell and let's see what happens
i've always wanted to be on top of mountain just like be like and just scream it
you say yodel yodel yodel yodel yodel learned like yodel y'all yodel turn is you
learned as a child trying to block out the sound of the gunshots not far from your
okay this is not like gunssuts blocking out the gunshots but when i was a child
okay we're good you hum a tune you learned as a child trying to block out the sound of the
gunshots not too far away from your current position
The mountain is steep, and you're in no mood to fall off.
Yodel-ee, yodel-oh, yodel-la, yodel-ee, yodel-ee, yodel-oh, yodel-ay, yodel-lee.
You can't write L-U-L and then minus two.
You say yodel-ee, yodel-oh, yodel-ay, yodel-yodel-lee.
You shuffle your feet along the mountain, trying to make it as little noise as possible.
Bullets fly past you.
You keep climbing.
Suddenly you hear a yelp.
Okay, so this is what is happening right now.
Uh-uh.
Yodel-oh, yodel-la, yodel-ay, yodel-oh, yodel-ly, yodel-ly, yodel-ly, yodel-ly, yodel-ly, yodel-lay.
Not enough of them.
I'm climbing.
Yelp.
I, nope.
Hey!
That was, hey!
Add an echo.
Fucking god damn it.
Don't make me do this.
Why is this doing this?
You see?
Wait, hold on.
What?
Okay, there we go.
That doesn't sound right.
Why does it sound so weird?
Where are all the voice robots?
Oh shit, the hardtune's not on.
Is it?
Oh fuck!
There we go.
Oh shit!
Everybody knows I'm a fraud!
Fuck.
Everyone's going to hate me now.
Everyone's going to leave.
My big secret.
Let's go back to what we were doing.
Yeah, we were doing this.
He's going to bleed viewers now.
Chop.
Okay.
Suddenly you hear a yelp.
Why are these?
I need to turn this off.
Could you hear this shit?
I wanted like a bunch of them.
Okay, here we go.
I need ice music.
I don't know what ice music is, but this is the first thing I'm clicking on.
Oh, he's playing ice cubes for music.
That's actually fucking awesome.
Okay, one hour of ice music.
Here we go.
You hear a yelp.
Who's there?
Jacob.
Is that you?
Yeah.
You see his face and he screams.
He seems to be in a state of shock.
What are you doing here?
Same thing.
You know what I mean?
I could ask you the same thing.
I don't know.
You see him stand up and he looks at you.
He doesn't seem to be wearing any clothes, but he doesn't seem cold.
Am I dead?
Whoa.
I would be like, whoa.
What?
You're dead.
I'm dead.
He looks down at his hands, begins shaking.
Then he looks up at you.
We're dead.
You nod slowly.
Help me up.
Aren't I hanging off the side of the mountain?
Grab his hand to help pull him up.
As soon as he stands, he begins to wobble.
He falls to the ground.
He realizes that his legs are broken.
Carry Jacob to the top of the mountain.
Put him out of his misery.
What?
Carry...
Okay, you stand up and walk over to Jacob.
He's sitting in a puddle of his own blood.
Help!
You grab him under the arms and begin dragging him up the mountain.
Get to the top.
How's AI doing?
Lie down next to him.
You laugh and then begin to cry.
What do we do now?
He asks.
You begin laughing again.
Competitive.
It's been pretty good.
It's been fun.
Start laughing harder.
We can't believe it.
We made it to the top, but it's hysterical because we're both so fucked up.
This is crazy.
Might as well just laugh.
What else can we do?
You roll around in the snow laughing at nothing for no reason.
Why are you laughing?
Stop laughing and look at him.
Point and laugh.
You point and laugh.
You begin laughing again and you point at him.
You look at the trees and begin to laugh at the trees.
He gets up and...
I can't...
He gets up and begins running in circles.
I just pictured him as a dog.
Like, is he a dog?
Let's let the AI take care of this one for a little while.
I don't understand.
He says.
You begin laughing again.
Suddenly you hear a loud noise.
It's the sound of a gun.
They stop moving.
Hide.
No.
Hide behind that shed.
Hide behind that glacier.
Hide behind that quick.
Wrap him and quickly make your way over to the glacier.
You both duck down behind it.
Are they gone?
I don't know.
You should peek.
You should peek around the corner, Jacob.
Hello?
Jacob slowly peeks around the corner of the mountain.
He immediately ducks back down.
They're still there.
Are they looking this way?
You ask.
No.
Say, Jacob, go run out there and wave your arms in the air screaming.
What?
Jacob says.
Go ahead.
Jacob slowly stands up.
He begins walking to the direction of the fortress.
What's going on?
What color is the fortress?
How big is the fortress?
AI doesn't know.
Okay.
AI doesn't know what's going on.
What's going on?
Let's go.
Sacrifice Jacob.
Here we go.
Let's go.
You stand up and begin running towards the fortress.
Once you get there, you hear a loud bang and everything turns black.
You wipe the cartoon black smoke off your face and keep running.
You rush into the fortress, guns blazing.
You go up to the first guard that you see and you stab him through the neck.
You run up to the next and do the same.
Why am I doing this?
Look for Jacob.
It's okay.
It's just a cartoon knife.
Outright violence.
You look for Jacob.
Well, where is he?
Come on.
Where's Jacob?
You look around and see Jacob on the floor, his face covered in soot and blood.
Jacob, you say.
He slowly turns his head to face you.
It was Looney Tunes soot.
Already did that joke.
Not to somebody else.
You wipe the soot and blood off his face.
He slowly opens his eyes, revealing his sad eyes.
Am I dead?
Yes, you reply.
Really?
Yes.
Really.
He's dead.
Why does everybody ask if they die?
Everybody asks if they're dead.
Say yes, really.
Really, you reply.
You hear a scream.
It's Ethel.
He slowly begins to rise.
I'm so scared.
He yells.
Now you begin to rise, too.
Grab the table.
Grab and hold the table.
I don't float anymore.
Table's not going to come up with me, right?
Is Ethel the hologram?
Maybe.
Oh, yeah, right.
Grab and hold the table.
Your hands go through the table.
The rest of your body slowly follows until you completely rise out of your chair and into the air.
All right, keep going.
What else you got?
What's going on, you ask?
I think this is heaven, Ethel says.
Oh, you reply.
The walls begin to turn into a bright white light.
I have a question for God.
You begin floating towards the light, as does Jacob.
What are you doing, Jacob?
I don't know, he says.
Jacob begins levitating towards the white light.
Float into the light.
Jacob belongs in hell?
Should I push Jacob down?
Float into the light.
Once inside, you see a man in white robe sitting on a chair.
Hello and welcome.
I am Jesus Christ, the Son of God, he says.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course, Jesus replies.
What did you really think of the world?
I loved it, he replies.
What happens when you die, Jesus?
You get to come to heaven, he says, smiling.
Forever?
Forever.
Jacob and Ethel both nod in agreement.
That sounds great.
Say, do you care that I had six marriages and only eight ground beef my entire life?
No, no, no, we're going to stick with this one.
I've just lived such a meat-filled life.
Do you care that I had six marriages?
That many?
I guess that's a lot.
Don't worry about it.
It's okay.
Wait, do you care that all those marriages were me cheating on all of my wives?
That's what was sin, right?
We got gluttony?
All I ate was ground beef.
No, we didn't do gluttony.
We didn't do gluttony.
Do you mind that I only ate ground beef until I got big and fat?
That's fine, too.
Jacob, do you have any more questions?
Jacob shakes his head.
I don't think so.
Come on, let's go.
Okay, lost.
I only care about money.
You, Jacob, and Ethel rise up into the sky.
Well, that's it for this chapter.
Thanks for reading.
All right, close the book.
Where the fuck am I?
Where am I?
Close the book.
This was just a movie stream.
Played out the exact same way.
Okay, let's do another one.
How about zombies?
Do fantasy?
Let's do fantasy.
Noble Princess Knight, Wizard, Witch, Ranger, Squire, Peasant.
Let's be a peasant.
Peasant.
What's a good peasant name?
Jacob.
Are we going to continue Jacob's story here?
Schwab?
Here we go.
Okay, you are Jacob.
Let me get some music.
Okay, you are Jacob, a peasant living in a small village in the kingdom of Larian.
You have a pitchfork and nothing else.
You dream of getting out of your village and having an adventure.
You go to your fields and begin working.
You look up and see your friend Anthony there.
Hey, Jacob.
You'll never guess what I heard in the tavern last night.
He says to you.
I don't know.
What?
Okay.
I can't add anything there.
There's a dragon to the south of here, like a real dragon.
Not a wyvern or a drake.
It's been terrorizing the nearby villages.
Really?
Hey, that's horrible.
Same voice, new effects.
Omega Low.
Get that guy out of here.
Ban that guy for like a year.
That's horrible.
Yeah, I know, Anthony.
Yeah, I know.
I wish I had the courage to go fight it.
What if it kills you?
A valiant death is preferable to a life of cowardice.
Do you want to go get to the bar?
Do you want to go to the inn?
Talk about it.
Look, I'm not just going to climb the ice fountain again.
You want to go to the inn?
Sure, says Anthony.
At the inn, you and Anthony have a few drinks.
Hey.
Damn.
I can't stop fucking thinking about this dragon.
This dragon, this dragon.
Since you brought it up, I can't fucking stop thinking about it.
Do we go get him?
I don't know.
Should I do it?
I can't stop thinking about that dragon.
Duncan Dragon.
Aw, don't worry about it, says Anthony.
Would you ever want...
Let's go see the wizard tomorrow.
Maybe he can help us.
Sure, why not, says Anthony.
Okay, bye.
You're like everybody that gets on the phone
and doesn't know how to say goodbye on the phone,
so you just kind of agree with or repeat everything I say
until one of us finally is like, I fucking have to leave.
Wave goodbye to Anthony.
Bye, Jacob.
Wave goodbye to your friend and head home.
There we are.
Okay, good.
We don't go see the wizard.
I'm just a regular guy in a kingdom.
That's it.
This is...
Oh, we're in a medieval fantasy fucking land.
This guy didn't have any powers.
He's just a regular guy.
There's no cool thing that happens.
Let's go over it.
Oh no, there's a dragon.
There's a dragon south of here, a real one.
Wow, I can't believe it.
That's horrible.
Yeah, I know.
Wish I had the courage to fight it.
I know, what if it kills you?
I have nothing.
I have no fucking weapons and no powers or anything.
I'm just a guy that works on the farm.
Yeah, valiant death.
You want to go to the inn?
Sure.
Okay, let's have some drinks.
I can't stop thinking about that dragon.
Yeah, I know.
Don't worry about it.
Maybe we should see the wizard tomorrow.
He can help us.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, bye.
I'll ask the wizard to go do the quest.
Never did this say I had anything.
Like I had some major adventure to do.
I said I want to.
I dream of getting out and having...
But that's not...
I live in reality right now.
I'm the wizard.
Of course, I have dreams of being an adventurer.
But the wizard has the powers.
Forever an NPC.
In fact, that was NPC underscore 118
talking to NPC underscore 119.
When you walk into the inn as a fucking Skyrim character.
That's all that was.
Man, this dragon, I can't believe it.
Neither can I.
I wish one day we could get rid of that dragon.
Yeah.
We should maybe go see the wizard.
Don't you think that's a great idea?
Sure.
I'm not going to get NPC'd here.
I am a ranger.
Is this copyright music?
Oh, fuck.
All right.
Be a wizard.
I do a wizard every time.
I have to do at least one non-wizard gameplay.
I'll do ranger.
Yes, that is the way to say it.
It's not ranger.
It's ranger.
All right.
What's a good OST?
No, no.
That's got to be like royalty-free jazz.
No, that doesn't make sense.
Royalty-free choir.
Emotional choir.
No.
Godhand OST.
Is this any good?
Not too arcadey.
Too arcadey.
Celeste.
Oh, yeah.
That's a good one.
Okay.
Here we go.
Nintendo Labo.
What's your character's name?
I'm a ranger.
Von Darlo.
Real Ralph?
No.
Real Ruff.
Real Tough.
What was the guy's name?
Slop.
I'm not going to even.
No, no.
Okay.
Doug is okay.
How about Doug?
Doug Shlop.
That's such a shitty ranger name.
You are Doug Shlop.
A ranger.
A ranger living in the Kingdom of Larian.
You have a hunting bow and a quiver of arrows.
You've been searching for a mystical beast for three months, tracking it through the
forest.
As you crouch behind a clump of trees, you see it.
It is a large black cat with a long tail that stands on its hind legs and looks like a man,
but with fur all over its body.
You just immediately shoot it with the arrow?
First of all, that's what I'm hunting.
I'm going to look at my map.
I need to see.
You look at your map and see where you are and you make a note of it.
You then look for potential escape routes.
Which way would you run?
That's cat.
Look at the cat.
Look at the cat's food.
I don't know.
What is it eating?
Does it eat?
Is it a vegetarian?
Is it a herbivore?
A carnivore?
You look at the dead deer on the ground.
Thank you.
The cat?
A panther.
Has two more just like it besides the corpse.
Let's try this one.
You ask if you can share some of the deer.
You slowly put your bow down and raise your hands.
You slowly approach the deer carcasses and the panther does not move.
Easy.
You say easy, putty tat.
Which is a reference to the popular movie Dead.
Walk towards the deer and the panther does not move.
Is that a reference to Dead?
Okay.
I'm close enough now.
Do you mind if I sit down?
Popular movie Dead.
The panther stares at you silently.
You sit down and take a rest for a minute.
You say, I can't believe I've been out here three days.
It's been three months.
I've lost my mind.
Wow, I can't believe it.
It's not been that long, but holy shit, three days is a long darn time.
Three fucking months.
Okay.
I can't believe I've been out here for three days.
The panther continues to make no reaction.
You begin to feel tired and lay down next to the panther.
We're lying down looking up at the sky.
You know, I always thought the stars were just big lightning bolts from other planets.
So stupid.
So young.
The panther begins to slowly move towards you and sniffs your neck.
I was just a big dumb idiot.
I mean, I was just a big dumb idiot kid trying to make sense of the world.
The panther suddenly leaps on you and tears your throat out.
I went out here on an expedition and got delirious in three months.
Started talking to a cat.
Like it was going to talk back.
Oh, good work, Doug Shlopp.
Excellent.
You did.
You got your bounty.
This one can't.
I don't think this one goes on anymore.
That's the end.
That's it for that one.
I'm going to be a squire.
Character's name.
What about eternal darkness?
It's only been a couple hours.
We'll do like another couple.
Let me go pee first, actually.
I'm going to piss.
I'll be right back.
Oh, man.
I just got hurt in the bathroom.
I actually just got hurt in the bathroom.
I started.
Okay.
I started just laughing.
I started pissing.
And it was, it was a full big 60 seconds.
I'm going to piss.
It was worth it.
I'll take that.
I will take that pain.
Oh my god.
That was so stupid.
All right.
Here we go.
You are Walter, a squire living in the kingdom of Larian.
You have a spear and a pack of supplies.
You follow Sir Theo as he enters the forest.
He turns to you and says, if we split up, we'll find the orcs much quicker.
Very well, sir, you reply, knowing he is far more experienced in fighting than you are.
I'm not going to split up, I'm going to follow him.
Silently follow Sir Theo.
Yeah, I'm going to be hiding behind him and see.
Hey, you silently follow Sir Theo into the forest.
Quietly, you sneak forward, moving slowly so as not to make any noise.
You look around, taking in your surroundings and noting that the trees are getting thicker.
Continue to follow Sir Theo.
You continue to follow Sir Theo, ducking under branches and taking care not to trip.
You hear a twig snap behind you and pause.
Isn't that just me?
I'm ripping through twigs and stuff?
That's me?
I'm doing that.
Turn around.
You turn around and grab your spear tightly, calling out, who's there?
You hear a faint laugh and response and quickly jab your spear in the direction of the noise.
Gotcha!
The voice says.
I didn't get him?
Did you get me?
Turn around again and see Sir Theo behind you smiling.
You get jumpy over the smallest things, boy.
What is it?
Who are you?
Wait, is it?
Wait, it was him.
He pranked me.
Don't do that.
That's not funny.
Alright, I'm sorry.
Come on.
Better keep going.
He sets off into the forest again and you follow once more.
What's our mission?
Follow Sir Theo and enter the forest and as he turns, as we split, okay, so what's the
actual mission, though?
Sing a lovely song as we travel to kill orcs.
Okay, yeah, kill orcs.
Right, right, right.
You sing a lovely song.
Sir Theo takes a moment to think, then starts singing in a beautiful angelic voice.
Harmonize with Sir Theo.
Sir Theo smiles as you join in with his song.
The two of you sing together as you walk through the forest.
Wow, lovely.
What about the orcs?
Oh, right.
Where are the orcs?
It's a medieval musical.
Sir Theo looks around in frowns.
I don't know.
I thought we would have encountered them by now.
Oh, we need to keep a lookout just in case.
I'll take first shift.
Very well, Sir Theo says, sitting down on a rock.
I suggest you keep alert.
Orcs can show up at any moment.
Why do you sound like that?
Sir Theo looks confused.
I don't understand.
Your voice, it's all ruined.
Yes, it's a side effect of using too much power.
I'll get it back eventually.
Now wake me up in four hours.
With that, he lies down on the ground and closes his eyes.
Leave Sir Theo immediately.
You leave Sir Theo immediately.
As soon as your back is turned, Sir Theo teleports behind you.
He grabs your shoulders and whispers,
They're too trusting, boy.
OK, spin around.
Spin around with weapon in hand.
I'll tell you, this guy's a bad guy.
Spin around and swing your weapon.
But Sir Theo twists out of the way.
Your weapon cuts through the air and slices into his arm.
I thought he got, OK, blood begins to soak his sleeve
as he draws a sword.
What was your real plan?
Hmm?
Go, go hunt orcs in the fucking forest?
Lie.
You guys didn't catch that right away, I did.
Sir Theo looks down at his sword and sighs.
I was going to make sure you were safe.
But if you don't trust me now, I suppose
you don't have to live with that.
I'm sorry.
Thought you were a bad guy.
I thought you were evil.
What happened?
Where am I?
OK, so what has happened is I press the back button.
And this is when I searched for AI Dungeon an hour and a half
ago to play it.
And I spelt it just a little incorrect.
Just a little.
Fuck.
Now I can't.
I have to log in again.
No.
Hold on.
I just pressed forward.
Yeah, I just did it.
I pressed forward.
Damn it.
We were getting somewhere with that one, too.
It's because of the stupid mouse button.
OK, there's a back button on the on.
If you buy a razor mouse, your back thumb button
is going to be go back.
It saves it.
Please pray.
What?
Oh, sick.
I'm sorry, I thought you were evil.
I understand.
It's not your fault.
I should have told you my plan.
Sir Theo looks down and then looks you in the eye.
What is the plan, then?
What is the plan?
I need you to do exactly as I say.
Do you trust me?
Do I?
What if I just don't?
I don't think I trust him.
OK, yes.
No, I don't.
I'm going to be honest.
No, I don't trust you.
I don't.
You're not going to trust me.
This conversation is over.
Fine, I trust you.
Good.
I trust you.
I will do everything you say.
We got telltale?
Yeah.
Do you trust me?
Yes, you reply.
Good boy.
What's next?
We need to split up.
I'm going to head through the mountains
towards the Orc fortress.
You head north along the trade route
and meet up with Captain Brannock's men at the fortress.
I like that one better.
Head along the north trade route
and meet up with Captain Brannock.
I don't feel safe splitting up.
I'm a squire.
Isn't a squire supposed to follow around there at night?
Why would you tell a squire, go fuck off somewhere
and go get lost in the woods?
If we travel together and word gets around
that you're helping the knights, our plan will be ruined.
We need to keep you safe.
I don't like this plan.
Fine, follow the plan.
I am a squire.
That's what I'm supposed to do.
Ah, good boy.
Get you a nice apple once I'm inside.
How does that sound?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Am I a horse, Theo?
Have I been a horse this whole time?
And that's why he's trying to get me to go back
and take a different route and get away and go that way.
And I think you know the answers to that,
Sir Theo smiles.
You nod slowly.
Yes, yes I am.
I'll see you when you get out.
I'll see you when I get out, he smiles.
He turns and walks through the mountains.
You set off along the road to find Captain Brannock's men.
You, what's a horse do?
Throttle, trottle, gallop.
You trottle, trottle.
What would it be?
Trot along the mountain's edge.
Barely being able to stand
on, barely being able, barely able to balance.
You set off along the road to find Captain Brannock's men.
You trot along the mountain's edge.
Heading north for nearly a mile before you find the men.
They're camped in a gap between two large rocks
just off the road.
You walk into the camp and find a fire burning cheerfully.
Gallop over a mile.
How big was that mountain?
You walk slowly over to the men.
Clicking on the stones, your hooves.
You approach the fire and stand by it.
One of the men notices you and approaches.
Oh, hello there.
Is Captain Brannock around?
Horses don't talk.
This one does apparently
because Theo can understand everything I'm saying.
He's over there.
The guard says pointing over
to where a larger fire is burning.
You want me to take your horse to the stable?
Yes, please.
From a horse riding on top of a horse.
Interesting.
Oh, okay.
And I love how the larger fire,
there's one fire and then a larger fire right there.
Go to the larger fire.
Horse kick somebody, I will.
You walk over to the larger fire and stand by it.
The warmth feels nice on your back
after a long ride in the cold.
One of the men notices you.
Oh, hello there.
Theo is a mile long.
Long one mile.
You horse kick him into the fire.
You lash out at the man,
your hoof flying into his chest
and knocking him into the fire.
His screams are soon replaced by the sizzle of flesh
and the smell of roasting human quickly fills the cave.
Go to Captain Ren.
Rannick?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Where's Rannick?
Right.
The other guards stand drawing their weapons.
They advance on you, but you're not backing down.
You swing a hoof and knock a man's arm into his chest,
breaking it.
Where is Rannick?
Breaking, yeah, breaking his,
I think it breaks his arm and stuffs it into his chest.
The men begin to surround you,
keeping out of the reach of your hooves.
One of them speaks up.
Captain Rannick, we have intruders.
Captain Rannick slowly walks his way towards group.
Next quest, help Sir Theo complete his quest.
Oh, whatever, okay.
Captain Rannick slowly walks his way
towards the group smiling.
Come on, lads.
We can take this one.
One of the men says charging at you.
Force kick him into a large group of people
that all have to catch you together
at least seven to eight people
who then all fall down at the same time.
Somebody gets it, good.
As long as one of you gets it, that's all I care about.
Force kick him into the crowd.
You swing a hoof, knocking the man back into the crowd.
He screams as he's tripled
and you nick another man's neck with your hoof.
I want answers, Rannick.
And you shan't receive them.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, continue.
One of the men jumps towards you swinging his sword.
Force kick him in the head.
You swing a powerful hoof,
knocking the man's head clean off.
It rolls to Captain Rannick's feet.
Oh dear me, he says stepping back.
Tell me everything you know.
You charge, knocking a guard off his feet
and trampling him.
All right, all right, please no more.
Stop and look at him expectantly.
What do you know?
It's a secret passage right behind you.
They use it to spy on us, I don't know why.
What do you mean?
Who's they?
I don't know, spies probably.
Guards slowly get up looking at you nervously.
Well, go on then.
How are they not sealed?
There's passage there, Rannick says,
nodding towards you.
Look behind you, you'll see a small passage in the rocks.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Why are you laughing?
This is a trap.
Because, ha, ha, ha, ha, it's a trick.
Once you go through, we'll shut the door and trap you in.
You lash out with a hoof.
Force, force kick him.
Oh, no, I whatever will I do I haven't gone in yet you swing a hoof knocking the man off his feet and into the fire
He screams as he's burned and you nick another man's neck with your hoof. Come on attack
horse kick
Everyone in the cave you swing a hoof knocking the man off his feet into the fire
He screams as he's burned and you nick another man's neck with your hoof
Corner Brannock we go you chase Brannock into a corner and knock his sword out of his hands
He looks up at you panic in his eyes, please
Don't kill me. Please like give me all of your money before I kill him. Give me all your money, please
I don't have any money. I'm a soldier
That cool robe you have please spare me
Fine, then give me your sword. Of course Brannock says handing over his blade. I don't want to die. I
Want you to come with me stab him. No, he's coming with me. I want you to come with me
What why you can help me kill the others? Oh
Okay, then anything you want on my back. Let's ride you say get on my back
Let's ride you turn and begin walking out of the cave Brannock climbs onto your back and you walk silently into the night
Thank you. I won't forget this he whispers a new friend and you don't say anything
You just keep walking into the night after an hour or two of walking you come across an old wooden cabin
You walk up to it still carrying Brannock, you know this place. Yes
I do Brannock says inching closer to you for warmth. This is my cabin
I use it for hunting you step forward walking into the cabin
Heavens do you own how many cabins do you own? Just this one?
Brannock says I was saving to buy a larger one with a fireplace and a wood stove
But I think I need a new hunting knife instead your hunter Brannock what animals did you hunt you know?
I'm just I'm just a little fucking curious about that
Mostly dear Brannock says I also tracked and killed a few wolves
Bandits and other criminals did you really oh yes kill a horse
Yes, Brannock says give me the reason why say give me the reason why they hurt my mommy's
You've roar lashing out at him Brannock falls off of you and you bring your
Mommy's
Hmm, okay, you roar. Oh, oh god. Oh god. What have I done?
Oh god, what have I done? I can't I can't like I killed this guy. I didn't really mean to I just got rage oh
You say oh god. What have I done?
You stare at Brannock's crushed skull
Horrified by what you did you had to Brannock's ghost appears behind you we had to I'm sorry
I just got so angry. I'm sorry. I just got so angry. I know
The ghost of Brannock says but now you must continue your journey
There are more like us up ahead
We need you to kill them kill them only a true king can kill another king
You must ascend the throne and kill the other kings Brannock says urgently
Only then can you be the one?
True king I am a horse though, but I am a horse a horse
Never be king, but I'm a horse a horse can never be king. You're not just any horse
Brannock says you're the horse that will raise up kill the king and become king yourself
Legally binding now it works
What if the king gets bit by a poisonous squirrel is a poisonous squirrel become the king of the world is that legally binding?
No, Brannock says Brannock's ghost fades away, and you turn to walk out of the cabin your adventure is over
No, no, no, we're no no we're going back. You're the horse that would raise up kill the king and become the king
I accept the challenge good. Yeah, Brannock says he reaches out placing a hand on your shoulder
I believe in you but that he disappears a Malcolm x2
Thanks for the five community subs thanks a lot you let out a cry
Overwhelmed with sadness you lower your head letting out a long loud cry of pain and misery
You cry for a good minute or so before you have to pull yourself together
I'm to go find feel tell them what's going on another five community subs this time that's from nondescript civilian
Thanks both you guys my mommy's oh, I can't get over that
There's been some fucking wild ones tonight you begin to cry. Oh you have to pull yourself together
leave the cabin
in your search with Theo you must know of your
Adventure magic milkman five subs that's 15 in a row. Thank you guys
Okay, you leave the cabin and begin your search for Theo. He must know of your adventure soon you find him
The old king is laying by uh-oh
There's a twist right there. There's even a ton more subs are coming in Jesus rip Alex Trebek
Thanks for five storm issue five back to back. Thanks guys. He might be dead here comes the twist
Yeah, the old king is lying against a rock in the same spot. You left him Theo oh
You roar I'm back let this play up oofy nader. Thanks for the five subs
The old king slowly looks up he stares forward his eyes vacant and dead oh
Does he know thank you undead key chan thanks for the five community subs more subs
What's wrong you say?
Too late Theo says sorry horse
It's too late. He lets out a long wheezy breath before laying still
Theo wait I have to kill him. I have to kill him stomp his head before he dies I
Have to kill him. I have to kill him. He can't just die right that I we're gonna get like monkey pod right
You stomp his head before he dies you bring a hoof down on Theo's head smashing it like a watermelon
A pitiful moan before lying still Theo is dead. I'm the king now right I was gonna get
That was gonna be a big screw job
Okay, where's um where's Brannock look around for Brannock's ghost?
I did it right the almighty butthole. Thanks for the five community subs. That's quite the name that I'm surprised you have
spank my
Spanks thanks for the five subs a unionize your workplace thanks for the five subs
This is a shitload of subs guys you guys doing you look around for Brannock's ghost
But I can't find Brannock's ghost. Maybe he has given up on you
There's nothing left to do here. You look at Theo's body before turning and walking away. I'm the king now
after
killing Theo
You now become the new king, right? I mean, that's what I was told
Five more subs from non-descript civilian and $50 you listen to Theo was not the king what?
Yes, he was he said he was um hold on. There's a lot of subs coming in right now a lot of money
We had five from game watch five from Jamie five from s10w update
Fifty dollars from West zero nine to five long live the king
Ten community subs from zilly silly are we doing this are we really doing this right now?
Don't have to do this
That's ten more subs long live the king. I did it. I won the old king
Thank you guys. That was ridiculous
It was like five ten fifty twenty twenty thirty four. This is like probably a hundred subs here. Thank you
Horseking that one was fucking I loved that one. You now become the new king. Congratulations the end
This wasn't the good ending though. What do you mean? That's not the good ending. I did everything I was supposed to do
That's the true ending. Let's do another one. I mean, this is we're gonna try to get something weird
Back hold on. Let's do let's make the randomness. I can sing wait eternal darkness
Yeah
but
mmm
Yet promised eternal darkness
Yeah
Did I did say that
cyberpunk
Do it I told you the scenario was gonna play out where I was gonna want to do this here. All right. Here's my problem
my problem with doing
Her doctors now is cuz I've been streaming for three hours. I'm probably only gonna be live for like another hour or two
typically, right
Starting that new game and only being gonna potentially play it for an hour
I'd rather get that in there and do that for like five or six hours with a diary of a wimpy kid prompt
Don't worry there. There will be vengeance for the eternal darkness voters
I promise that will be the next video game that we play. That's the next game
We're going to play on this stream is eternal darkness
Sanity, whatever it is. That's the next game guys ready custom. Let's do something weird like you are
currently running from a tornado of a
shotgun and a pair of jeans and
Now you have a shotgun and a pair of sunglasses
You need to warn the city about the incoming
disaster
There the tornado is coming. You just need to get out of here
The wind is picking up and it'll be too late soon in drive
I'm not gonna shoot the tornado you look at the tornado and realize that it can't possibly hit the city
It's not going to make it past the levees
You're going to have to do something else go home. I was wrong. I had it wrong
Go home you race back to your house the entire way you think about what could have caused this
You come up with several theories including global warming or the government and yeah
I mean it's probably if the tornado started and just stopped randomly
I'd be like what the fuck is happening with our planet?
Let it play out one more time when you arrive at the house
You slam the car in the garage and head into the basement you sit in your home and begin watching TV
This is the Simpsons
They pulled that from the Simpsons
Okay, where's Marge turn on the news the news begins to talk about a brutal killing in Bel-Nor
You quickly change the station and switch to channel 45 the Hinsky News Network
Okay, James you drink out of your duff beer can
You go to the fridge and find a beer the news begins to talk about a brutal killing in Bel-Nor
You change the channel once more channel 35 news for now
Watch the news. What does Homer do?
You watch the news the news is showing a clip of you exiting Marge's bedroom this morning when the news was called
How do you do it? It's like no you say no
Realizing that you had been caught on tape you attempt to turn off the TV, but you notice something else
You appear to be live on the news
Hey, how did you get me on? How did you get me on the TV?
You look out the window and realize you have been surrounded by TV crews
You see a large boom being lowered from a helicopter towards your house Marge get down here
Why would they bring a huge boom mic you call for Marge?
She comes downstairs the boom stops outside your window
scream into the mic scream into the mic as
loud as
You can you look out the window and Marge appears
She screams into the microphone the boom retracts into the helicopter which flies away
Marge has saved the day once again that's an area where he would do that
You say don't again and realizing that you had been caught on tape a second time you turn off the TV you go to the
Window you realize that you're still being watched
What does he do he in every episode you go up to the Flanders house and ring their doorbell they open the door
How's the lawn? I don't know why I don't watch the Simpsons. I don't know what they do
I know he comes out and goes. Oh, hey, diddly-dodley. I know that you say
How's the lawn hoping to make Ned mad Ned looks over at his dead lawn and gets an idea
He calls the fire department wait for the fire department five more subs from s10w slow update
Thank you
You wait for the fire but you wait for the fire department outside 12 minutes later
You watch as the Bellnore fire department carries out all the furniture from your house Ned approaches you
Why are they taking all my furniture?
horse kick this guy and
Gives you a piggyback ride to the Bellnore fire department a year passes
Okay
Now what it's been a year since the media attention died down although you still have not gotten your furniture back
Life has been good. You are suddenly interrupted by a knock at the door
I'm just saying if there's a Simpsons
We're outside the door clip of all the news camera TVs and everything like we're doing right now
since
TV's bit it has to be right is there
Who answer the door?
All right
You go to the front door you open it to find a large man in a cheap suit and a smaller man with a video
Camera behind him a large man pushes you aside and enters your house
links banned
It's from an episode
links a band all links come out as asterisks
Any way these guys are breaking into my house
grab a small man
No, smash the camera
Smash the small man's camera. I get footage of me motherfucker
Grab the small man's camera and smash it the small man grabs your wrist
The large man pulls out a knife and holds it to your throat
Try to say
Yo, but that all comes out as a quiet squeak the larger members cutting off your what
Wait, what it's okay?
Attack
shoot
Jesus Christ shoot with shotgun like shoot them with I have a shotgun
You grab your shotgun from near the door and fire at the two men the blast hits the small man's chest
Large man in the face
Killed instantly
You say
Celebrating your victory suddenly the wind begins to pick up trees begin to shake violently
The sky goes black as if it's nighttime. It's the twister run and grab the family
You run every you run out of your house and get into your car. I
Can't do this today. It's too funny
You run out of your house and get into your car. You drive to go pick up Marge Jennifer and Megan
You drive to the Simpsons house
knock on the door
If Homer opens the store, I swear to God
Marge answers the door
My hello there neighbor. Homer here is Homer here today
You see that fan over there Marge points to a u-haul truck. That's my husband. He's moving out
Can I come in Marge divorce
German is mo with a sad face. I mean German is most sad face. Why would you be sad about that? What's what's wrong?
What's wrong with that? He runs his own goddamn business
Hey, you say can I come in and I come in sure
You enter the house. The house is empty. All the furniture has been packed away Maxwell appears. I
don't
remember seeing you on the Simpsons
Who is this? I don't remember seeing you on the Simpsons. Let's just say I'm a distant relative
Why are the Simpsons moving?
Where are they going? I can't tell you that
Can I go with them? You have to stay here and look after this house. That's your job for Marge
You punch Maxwell in the face. He falls to the ground. Ha got you
How does Homer laugh have we ever heard him laugh
Something like that, right
That's yeah, I'm doing um
It's that fucking stupid stoner dog that eats the cookies out of the box. What's the size scooby-doo?
You begin to cry wait
You begin to hit yourself in the head with your fists. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it
Art you say Bart. I've come to take you to where you belong
Lisa
Lisa appears Lisa is holding a sword Lisa points the sword at you
Okay, what down the sword?
Celebrity cameo
Put down the sword
Lisa begins to chase you you run outside Lisa follows
This is nighttime. The wind begins to pick up debris is blowing across the road
We go come on. Oh, I can't okay
Lisa, please. I
just wanted to
get to
Yeah
out of the fridge
Hmm. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I could I could try that's hard to do
I'm I'm sorry. I'm
Close I'm really close
I'm really close
Dad, I I'm very close, but I'm very close. I can't it's close. But so that I got I gotta work on it
Mean to break your heart. Oh
SpongeBob
No wasn't
That was not even close to SpongeBob. Let that I want to hear it. I don't believe you
I think I feel like I was getting close to Lisa. It was the worst sound of 2020
What's it? I don't think so. It was worse than
What was it was was it added to the list? Don't don't add it to the list. You're gonna forget about this shit
Anyways, I have to have to fucking shit that I do. You guys don't remember a
Links are banned. Oh, how do we unban links? We never forget
All right. I want to get a deaf. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to break your heart
I promise to stay out of your life
Me saying that that's in I need to enable them. Did I disable them able links?
When did I disable links?
Get in your truck you get in your truck least begins to cry the wind stops in the sky begins to clear up least
It disappears. It is now just you and your thoughts
You're literally the only one who can do it. I didn't do it though. I'm gonna go my settings. I don't have anything here
preferences channel
enable clips
mature content
disconnect protection
What else is here? Oh that links work. Oh, here we go. All right. Hold on. Let me I'm in here
I'm in here. I need to hear if this is actually really bad or not
And you find out if it's what I have to apologize for this. Hold on. Give it a special little
You're gonna press a to spick us. Just pick a specific. I can't even read this you press a to speak to give it
Why can't I read this? There's not even more you this is not what I asked for I
Could I could try that's hard to do I'm sorry
I'm really close
Yeah, I'm very close, but I'm very close
Okay, this is a part of this is what it just a deer sounds like
It's a really good deer impression
No, no, I have to apologize for it. Oh
I don't want to apologize for that. I don't I didn't I know what look what do you I didn't I'm just trying to
Get Lisa and the live TV. Okay, I can't go back and delete the spongebob is
You know, I can't delete that it's there. There's nothing I can do about that. I cannot stop that it happened
You were here for it. I can apology video. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to okay. Let's keep going
Just delete it right now. You can't delete anything as if I press the delete button on a video
I just created a hundred more of them. Wait, there's a dragon
Mighty roar is heard you feel as though the very ground you're standing on is shaking
You see a massive winged beast flying above the clouds. It's headed your way
face the beast
in my truck
Try to keep it in sight, but to no avail it disappears from your view. It's still shaking the ground
use binoculars
We use binoculars to see the beast. The beast is huge. It's much larger than an airplane
What's more amazing is that it is clearly flying?
follow the beast
do with the shotgun from like a
15,000 feet below where he is
You continue to follow the beast keeping your eyes on it. It looks as if it's heading right towards you
It lets out another roar thrive down the beasts throat
It's that movie Bill Murray that it has like a cold and they get in there
It's like Punxsutawney Phil. What's it called? It's about the guy the
Osmosis Jones, that's what it is. I'm gonna Osmosis Jones this motherfucker right now
You see the beasts insides
Everything is redness and carnage. You manage to make out a road running along the beasts throat drive down the road
Yep, drive down the road after driving down the beast throat for quite some time
You reach a beaver that is holding a sign in front of it that reads next services heartburn hotel next left
Heartburn Hotel
All right, go to the heartburn. I'm gonna go to the heartburn hotel and just like put a bunch of hot peppers
Into like the wood stove that they have and he's gonna get really gassy and he's gonna be like
Next services go to the heartburn hotel the beaver waves at you as you pull into the hotel parking lot
He holds a sign in front of him that reads hotel lobby this way go to the hotel lobby
He's gonna be the clerk at he's gonna be the person at registration
Go to the hotel lobby you walk into the hotel lobby a man dressed in a fancy tuxedo stands behind a counter
He smiles at you ask to be
brought to
the
Oh
Like the yes, we brought to the not the stove a basement. I want to go to the heater
I want to like because this is like his heartburn. We're gonna make it worse. So he pukes us out
Yeah, we're gonna go in there be like hey something's wrong with your basement the heater
I gotta go down there and take a look at it the plot to a monkey island game
It is are you asked to be brought to the basement to see the heater. You're pretending to be a repairman
Your thing sir. Just take the elevator to your right
Let me get the keys to room 2 2 1 where the basement is located. Oh
That would not be a basement
Go to room go to room 2 2 1 the man hands you the keys to room 2 2 1 you thank him and
Walk towards the elevator you get in the elevator and press B or basement
There's B. Let's see what happens you exit the elevator and find yourself in a hallway
Heartburn hotel basement where service is still the most important thing in the world. The hallway is made of cement ask
Ask the clerk
He's shown
Heater ask the clerk to show you where the heater is there you go
You asked the clerk to show you where the heater is certainly follow me. He stands up and walked down the hallway
He stops in front of room 2 2 1 a this is it go into 2 2 1 a
Game has probably forgotten that we're in a dragon probably
Okay, you go to 2 2 1 a you walk into the boiler room. It's fairly large with two large boilers in the center
so what we just break them so we give him indigestion and he gets like we make the
Heating elements spill out into the hotel, which is that's his stomach or whatever and then he gets sick
We're gonna smash him
Burn up. Okay, turn the heat up turn the heat up
It's
Maximum turn the heat up to max turn the heat up to maximum turn the heat up to maximum heat
Turn the heat up to maximum heat the boilers begin to hiss as they begin to output more heat
You exit the boiler room and head back to the hotel lobby
Come on the clerk at the front desk looks up at you and smiles all fixed. He asks
Yeah, sorry about that. You walk out of the hotel back into your truck you drive away
See in the rear view mirror
Hava
pouring out of the windows
No, no, not that either all fixed. Yeah all fixed
I feel like this is at the point of the movie where in this music too
I have the thing that I needed to take out of the hotel in my hand and I'm putting it behind my back and it's a
Big jacket and stuff and it's like a comedy routine where like I'm really trying to not have them see what I have
They have no idea and they're just like I'll have a good day and I think that they're like really suspicious
But they're just not how do I write that? Oh, yeah, this is Dragonair
do a comedy scene
drive
towards the dragons
Throat because then with a heartburn hotel, let's drive towards the throat
Drive towards the dragon's throat. The dragon's throat is still dark, but not as dark as it was earlier
You can see a red glow coming from deep within I guess can continue
forward
Through the dragon's digestive system. Are you showing me open it?
I'm what you can't just make somebody open a present
You don't sit down and stuff a present in my face and go open it now
No, I don't want I don't know what's in that fucking present the way this is oh, okay, that's what that is
This is me smashing ps2 the board game
Joe scooby-doo. What do you have a scooby-doo? Ah
Wait this I clicked on the wrong one. This is is this even my face. This is my eyes and mouth on scooby-doo
I mean, I guess it kind of works. I feel like my mouth looks like that sometimes
Okay, let's keep going continue forward through the dragon's digestive system
You can take forward through the dragon's digestive system
You travel through the darkness not knowing what is in store you drive past rows and rows of teeth all shapes and sizes
This is a long trip. We've been on this road for a very long time. Oh
Down the dragon's throat into his stomach. I suppose stomach
I want to get in there drive deep into the dragon's stomach. There we go. All right, we're in this tree
Now we're in the dragon's stomach
There's a quite a large chamber you park your truck next to a rather large mound of half digested cows
You exit your vehicle and look around the chamber walls. Maybe somebody's alive down here. Is anyone here you shout into the darkness
Is anyone here?
Suddenly a large section of the chamber wall begins to move it reveals a tunnel which continues further down into the darkness back in my truck
Get back in your truck. You quickly run back into your truck and drive down the tunnel
The tunnel is long and twisty. You hope you can remember how to get back in you forward
All begins to slope downward and you can feel a change in air pressure you reach the end of the tunnel which opens up
into a large chamber
Drive out of the chamber
You drive out of the chamber you pull out of the tunnel and into the large chamber
You can see lights up ahead somebody must be here. You put your truck in park and get out
investigate the lights
Walk towards the lights as you approach them. You see a large rectangular opening in the ground
Ropes harnesses and other climbing equipment is lying around
Interesting you have found a climbing camp
Suddenly you hear the roar of a dragon. The sound is very close and very loud
You look up just in time to see a large dragon
but
Flying in your direction
Huh, but he's flying at me backwards with his ass
Ah
Okay, so what happened?
What happened wait back it up? Okay, do I run?
Get back in the truck
You dive back into your truck the dragon butt misses you by mere inches and instead crashes through the windshield of your truck
The tail continues on and crashes through the back window. Can you driving? I can see i'll be fine
I can just lean out the window like jim carrey hit the gas pedal and try to drive away
But the dragon butt is lodged firmly in your truck. You back up a little to dislodge it, but it's no use
The ass is too big. What the fuck what the hell? What the hell are you doing in my tent?
Damn it. Get the hell out. I'm sorry. Who are you say? I'm sorry. Who are you?
Oh, it's fucked up back it up
um
Uh, just fuck this guy just tent down rip down the tent
You rip down the tent you pull the ropes ripping the entire tent down your anger is out of control
The other climber wakes up and looks around in shock. How do I get out of here?
How do I get out of here? Wait, who are you? What are you doing in my tent?
I asked the question
Hey, you're that guy that was driving down the road. What are you doing here?
I got eaten
by the dragon
stupid
I gotta be mean to this guy
On purpose. I mean was it on purpose or was it the last ditch effort thing that I could do?
He's coming straight at me opens his mouth. What am I gonna do not just drive down his throat?
Gotta word that better. What are you doing here? The dragon ate me
I had the dragon eat me on purpose
You did what are you insane?
Maybe a little
You in?
Hell, yes, i'm in those treasure hunters are cold-blooded killers. There's no way i'm going back to that camp
What's your name?
How many people are actually in this dragon? I'm perney perney the climber
I was hired by the treasure hunters to rope down and examine the structure of the ruins
Do you know you are inside of a dragon's?
ass
I I don't he might not know
Ernie stares at you in disbelief. You've got to be kidding me
Not kidding
Ernie looks around nervously
How the hell did we end up inside a dragon?
I knew those treasure hunter guys were crazy. They always go looking for dragons
Have any supplies?
Sadly, no, they only supplied me with the bare minimum and they took the rest of my gear before throwing me in here
Do you have a sled?
Can you
Make me a sled
The car is destroyed remember reverse butt dragon
Killed to crush the car
Can you make me a sled?
a sled why
So I can ride the dragon
Ernie rushes up to you and takes you by the shoulders
And what does he do?
Ernie rushes up and takes you by the shoulders. She stares deep into your eyes
Look, i'm going to be completely honest with you
There is no way you are riding this dragon. Why not? Why i'm curious
It's the only chance either of us have of getting out of here alive
You're not a dragon rider. I can tell just by looking at you
I think
We can
Oh not
You don't
I'll prove it to you another NPC. Yeah another NPC
I'll prove it to you
That's not accurate. This is this is not what I like at like the county fair
Okay, that's a little better. How about this one?
It's the exact same song
How did I do that?
Here we go
Ernie grabs your shoulders and looks deep into your eyes. She begins to speak
I'm going to ask you a series of questions
And I want you to answer them as quickly as you can
Ready? Have you ever ridden a dragon before?
No, I mean
Yes
Never never Ernie frowns and lets go of you. Is that going to
Going to be a problem. What a bad lie. Yeah, I failed my uh, I failed my speech check. Yeah
Not necessarily
Just answer the next question
What did you do before you rode a dragon?
Uh, I think he was doing a simpsons thing
And then I turned into being inside of a dragon. I don't know what were a new a nuclear
Worker, what did you do before you rode a dragon drove down its throat?
I drove down a dragon's throat. Ernie throws her hands into the air
Hi birds. Oh, she's stuck. She's stuck. She can't move
Uh-oh, come on
Give us something. Come on. Do it. It's thinking so hard
Okay, i'll do it too. Ernie throws her hands into the air. You throw your hands into the air
Ernie looks at you with a look of disbelief
This is hopeless if you can't even tell me when i'm joking and when i'm not
Wait, if you can't tell when i'm joking when I so this has been like a just a
Ha, I know you're a dragon rider. I'm just kidding. I knew it was a joke. Why didn't you know I was joking?
You say ha ha ha ha ha ha Ernie frowns at you. I'm not laughing
She turns away from you and stares at the walls of the dragon's stomach. You know
How to get out of here?
Being gaslit by an npc something like that Ernie looks at you and raises an eyebrow
Of course I do
And let's go
Not so fast. I want your word that you will take me with you when we get out of here have my word
She's so fucked
Good enough Ernie turns away from you and begins scanning the walls for a way out
She looks up at one of the holes in the ceiling
Is that big enough?
Maybe begins looking around for something to stand on. What are you doing?
Looking for something to stand on
Why so why can't get up there? You're not strong enough to pull yourself up there. I'll figure out a way
She looks around some more. I can't believe you can't tell what i'm joking Ernie turns to you surprised
I thought you said you wouldn't make any more jokes
All I know how to do Ernie. I'm sorry. Can you take anything seriously?
I'm trying to Ernie smiles at you then turns away. What is the lead?
Ernie looks up at the hole of the ceiling surface. I hope is there any way of telling climb?
Uh climb on climb the truck, right? We can move we can I can we put it in neutral climb the truck
and get into
the hole
Climb the truck and get into the hole
You crawl out of the dragon's mouth and find yourself in the middle of a vast snow-covered plane. It's a beautiful day
Reckon you turn around and crawl back into the dragon's mouth
You climb down from the truck and stand up inside the dragon's belly
Trucks lies on the floor of the cavern clearly dead. No, not my truck trucks trucky the truck
I found
Away it leads it leads it leads
out of his mouth
I know that
His mouth is very small. I don't think it's meant for people to go in and out of
Any uh, any uh, any other ideas?
I just came in and out
None you begin to panic you sit down next to the corpse of the man who tried to help you
Well, I guess this is it then
Can't we go?
Another way
I've explored this entire continent. There's no other way
You slump to the ground staring at the hole in the wall
continent
Okay
climb through
the hole
with perney
And climb through the hole doesn't know what to do. Try it again. This stream is so fucked
uh
Thanks, man
Climb through the hole with perney you crawl out of the dragon's mouth and you find yourself in the middle of a vast snow-covered plane
It's a beautiful day
kick her back in just like
Sparta kick her back into the mouth. Why is the mouth just open?
No, I know what we can do
Take out a marker
and draw a funny mustache
on the dragon
You take out a marker and draw a funny mustache on the dragon
Trucks lies on the floor of the cavern clearly dead you pick him up and throw him down the hole
You hear him hit the ground a few seconds later
What are you doing here?
Draw a funny
Mustache
on the dragon
Here take this marker
Here take this marker and draw a funny mustache on the dragon perney takes the marker from your hand
You're very weird
Just do it. All right
Come on, just do it
Ernie shrugs him because drawing a mustache on the dragon
Two of you crawl through the tunnel for what seems like an eternity
Go buy
a funny hat
at the store
And put it on the dragon's head
Okay, why are we going back in?
Buy a funny hat at the store and put it on the dragon's head perney looks at you and begins to laugh
That's really funny
If you crawl through the tunnel for what seems like an eternity crawling
Blow up the tunnel
Okay, i'm gonna plant c4 on the ground
Crawl through the tunnel for what feels like an eternity soon. You find yourself out of the tunnel. You're standing on a sidewalk
You plant c4 in the tunnel you press a button on your watch and the entire tunnel explodes
You and perney are thrown across the room
Haha, that was great
Okay, leave the tunnel
You leave the tunnel you walk outside the building and begin walking down the road. Where are we?
I don't know. I've never been here before have you?
Yeah, I want to look for the dragon to see if he's see if I like
Blew him up. I never been here before have you i've never left my house
I guess it's new to both of us
You look around you're in a city surrounded by high-rise buildings
Where's the dragon?
We're not in springfield anymore
I think it's because it did you look right? Yes
You do look for the dragon not you look
Get out of here perney shrieks the two of you walk around the city marveling and everything around you
attempt to attach
yourself
to a building
with your hands
You attempt to attach yourself to a building with your hands you find yourself swinging through the air
After a few minutes of this you land on another building. I'm never doing that again
Go back down to perney
He's retired
Walk over to perney who is sitting on the street
What's going on?
Me legs hurt from walking around so much
and
It's so funny when the ai just doesn't know what else to do
It tries it's sitting there going fuck. All right
What am I pulling from here? What am I gonna do here?
It's got like trillions of days of content
Can we take a break?
Sure
Sit down next to perney
Do you know where we are? No, do you yeah?
We are in
metropolis
of the old
round
Dean, uh the we're in the metropolis of the old round
Of the old round lake that's where we are
How do you know that I can see signs?
bad name
I was making it up on the spot to make perney think I knew anything. That's what the place is called by the way
Can you not read?
No
You look at perney. He's staring at his feet
I want to go home
Was it wait and just take the bus
I don't have any money. Neither do I maybe we can find something to trade. Okay, go
explore
one of the alleys
Trade bitcoin
I don't have any bitcoin. Here we go
To explore one of the alleys you see a merchant standing outside of his shop putting up a sign that says demons for sale
The merchant looks up at you and sees you go away. Can you steal a demon? What kinds?
What kinds of demons do you have?
Kind what kind of demons do you sell?
There we go. That's better way
the evil kind
That's it. I'm out of here. You walk away from the guy
Come back. He screams
Turn and go back
What you're the dragon killer, correct?
Yeah, there's a dragon nearby
Kill it and i'll give you anything you want. I want up front payment
How big should I ask how big is the dragon's ass?
Because i've not this i've got two killed i've done twice
Uh, I didn't like that. Hold on you turn away. Hey the dragon killer
I want to be paid now
I want to be paid
now
Fine. Here's some money more when you kill the dragon bernie is just staring at you. This is not enough
Are you crazy? That's a lot of money
Not for killing a dragon
You're not getting any more now if you don't want to work for me, that's fine
There are other adventurers who will you look at the merchant and at bernie?
Hmm, okay, if you give me one of those demons
Got a deal. The merchant goes back into his shop. He comes out with a small black creature
Ours doesn't have it can make you invisible look into its eyes and twist the ring on its tail. Look at the creature
Okay, twist
the ring on the creature's
Tail i'm looking at it right now. Come on. Come on
You twist is this the avengers you twist the ring on the creature's tail
The demon disappears you now see yourself holding nothing, but the merchant still sees you holding the demon you walk outside
Where's the demon when it makes the demon invisible? I want a different demon
only invisible to me
He goes back inside and comes back with a big red creature
What does this one do that is fucking useless?
So I look into its eyes and twist its ring and it makes it invisible to me but not other people
What's the point of that just so it can like fuck with me?
I can come to my house and like mess up all my clothes in my laundry room and shit and then leave and no
I don't understand
It's a big red creature. What does this one do? I don't know nothing probably
It's not even alive just painted
You stare at the merchant. He stares back
Get me
a demon
worthy of
a great
war
I'm going to fight a dragon
Didn't like that back. I just hit him in the head with like frying pan or something
Okay, i'm gonna this is what we're gonna do
motion
motion to perney
Rob his store
You know like go get in there. I'm gonna keep talking to him about his demons
You motion to perney to rob his store. You motion to perney to rob his store. What are you doing?
Tell perney
Rob the store
while
You distract him
You're a bad influence on perney. Am I?
All right. All right. All right. I'm done. Let's go. Oh my god. You just scared the shit out of me
Did you guys hear that? Holy shit, you can give me a heart attack
You know, because my my noise gate is on she popped in the room and went boom
Holy shit, i'm gonna puke i'm gonna get auto. It's coming to get auto. Just get the shit out of me. It's so horrible
I'm feeling like oh, he nods quickly and goes in seppu
Put some public i'm gonna get killed in real life. That's what just happened. Okay
You hit him in the head with a bag of sand. He falls to the ground you motion to perney to rob the store while he's unconscious
He nods and quickly goes inside. Why wouldn't you just I was trying to tell him to do it
I swear to god
Okay, see what they do
You hear sirens not long after he goes inside
We gotta get out of here you and perney run away and the guards chase after you. I am here to slay the dragon
What i'm here to slay the dragon
What are you talking about? There is no dragon
Is not is that guy just on bath salts. I don't get it
I just killed a dragon
Use the demons on the guards. I just killed a dragon. What are you talking about? There is no dragon you stared him
What's going on here? You're not the sheriff
Let the demon let you know what here we go. Let
all the demons
out of the store
to attack
all of them full anarchy
You let all the demons out of the store to attack you open the door and all the demons come flying out
They don't attack you though. They'll go after the sheriff
a lot of ghostbusters
Stop them. Don't let them get away
You and perney easily outrun the sheriff and his men come with me kid. We gotta get out of here
leave
a kid
You leave the town and head back to your kingdom
After a few days of walking you arrive
i'm
back
Your dragon wakes up and eagerly awaits her meal
You stand still the dragon breathes fire all over you
What?
What was my goal?
I'm being cooked
Uh dragon breathes fire all over you after it stops after it stops you look at your hand
It's completely black
I need a new hand you rip off your blackened hand and throw it on the ground
God
I want a new hand
Your mother runs into the room
What happened?
The dragon burned my hand off
I hope the dragon gets grounded for a week
You cry
Here's your new hand
You take the new hand. Thanks mom your mother nods be careful
She didn't say it was attached
Stare at the dragon the dragon stares back
What are you looking at?
You continue to stare. Hi, man. Don't talk to me
Uh upper cut it's not gonna work. It's a dragon
Ride the dragon
Can I ride you?
Oh, yeah, right. That's what I want to do that for the very beginning
Use the ps2 board game
Dragon shakes its head. No
Why not you'll fall and get hurt
But I want to ride you
I am very strong. I can handle it
Here we go
Fine. The dragon walks over to you. You climb onto its back. It takes off into the sky. Whee
Okay head towards the city
You head towards the city the dragon the dragon takes you higher into the sky
You can see the entire countryside you spot another kingdom
Can we go there?
The dragon shakes her head
Is it a yes or a no?
Yes
Dragon shakes her head
Why not the dragon doesn't respond she takes you home instead. Come on. I'm hungry
You can eat me if you want
No, I want to live the dragon shrugs and goes to the kitchen. You follow her you see your mother cooking dinner
How big is this dragon?
The dinner the dragon is the mom
You look at the dinner. It looks delicious. There's mashed potatoes gravy roast beef buttered carrots and corn
Pickled cucumbers your mother says noticing you looking at them. That sounds really good
I wish I could eat that right now. I want something else. This looks icky
What do you want then?
I don't know
You see a bottle of ketchup is drinking ketchup. You squeeze the bottle of ketchup into your mouth
You immediately spit it out
What is that stuff?
Ketchup it's horrible. I want something else. No, you'll eat what we have for dinner and you'll like it. No, I won't
I want captain crunch. We don't have any captain crunch. We have oatmeal. I don't like oatmeal fine
And no oatmeal then I want two hot dogs and mac and cheese your mother sighs
Fine, my mother turns away and gets you some dinner. You sit down at the table. I want three hot dogs
another size
Fine your mother makes some more hot dogs and sits down with you to eat them
You eat as fast as you can making piggy noises. You eat all the hot dogs. Then you look at your mother
I'm still hungry
Dragon still outside
Your mother laughs i'm still hungry me too. Your mother laughs there's more in the kitchen
But go back into the kitchen and see a plate of bacon
I want that
You eat all the bacon now. You're really full
I don't want to go upstairs
Okay, you sit down and watch tv with your mom
next day
Ask my mom
make
The mac and cheese
You ask your mom to make you mac and cheese
Do it yourself
You go to the kitchen. You see a box of macaroni on the counter. I can make it myself
Turn on every burner
Unfortunately, they are all electric. You can't turn them on
Why didn't mom have gas ones?
You look in the cupboard
Find a gas stove in the cupboard
now
Mac and cheese
No, I gotta do this right
oil
water
And then you put the macaroni in water heats up. Yes
You turn off the stove and quickly open the box of macaroni. You put some in the water and wait done
drain
the macaroni
Drain the macaroni you grab a fork and sit down at the table. You see your mom walk in
What are you doing?
eating
You didn't think
I could do it on my own
Did you?
Don't have any cheese in it. You didn't think I could do it on my own. Did you no your mom sits down to eat
How do you plan on winning the quest? I don't even know what the quest is
You can't have any there's some stale bread on the counter
Thanks
You eat the macaroni. It's delicious that night
You demand more mac and cheese from your mother. No, you go to bed hungry the next morning. I'm hungry
Your mom hands you a bag of chips
What's the meme?
Knock the bag of chips out of her hand
You pissed her off
You knock the bag of chicks out of chips out of her hand. I want real food
I'm hungry now
Your mom sighs fine. She goes to the kitchen. I want chicken tenders
No, you see your mom makes some eggs you could have this and like it you sit down and eat
Is that look up?
You look up it seems to be more egg than toast the yolk is falling off and making a mess
I want more
Your mom sighs and gets you some more food you throw the eggs into the trash
Your mom walks in. Why did you do that? I didn't want them you go to the living room
This is cartman
I want to see if anything else adds on top of this
Okay, you go into the living room
We have any soda
No, now stop asking questions and go watch tv
Watch tv for a while then you go back to the kitchen
Get the eggs out of the trash and put them on a plate you go back to the living room and watch tv
Then you go back to the kitchen your mom walks in
I can't do that. That's that's horrible
Drop the eggs into the dvd player's cd tray
I'm just like, oh, i'm just a little brat. Fuck. Yeah, you drop the eggs into the dvd player's cd tray
Why did you do that for?
I don't know
The next day i'm hungry. I want some eggs. I don't have any you go to the refrigerator. I want to eat something
Your mom hands you a hot dog
here
Eat the hot dog in one bite like just the whole thing
Raw
You eat the hot dog in one bite. I want something else your mom gives you some apple juice here
You take a sip. It's extremely sour
You spit the apple juice into the radiator
No more
Your mom sighs and goes to the kitchen you follow her she gets you a package of macaroni. What happened to the other characters?
Where are my friends?
They're in school you go watch tv then you go back to the kitchen then you go back to the living room that night
Sneak out the window
I'm too dumb for school you sneak out the window you climb down the tree and run into the woods
You turn around and look at your house. It's normal a little fixer-upper, but nothing too bad
house flipper
Start doing start doing additions to the house
Don't knock down a wall at your house. You walk back and begin to take pieces of sheetrock off the walls
You can feel the world changing color around you
What um somebody said asbestos
You add a fourth bathroom to your home you open up all the walls in the house
And see the in in the distance you can feel it changing
Ask mom if she likes the new look you see her walk in and shriek
What's happened?
She looks around and begins to buckle it's over
I painted the walls macaroni and cheese yellow mom sits down against the wall. It's over. She begins to weep. It's all over
Um sit down
It'll be okay
No, it won't it's all gone
We will still have each other. It should have been better than this
Reject reality. All right, this one's gonna have to this is gonna come to an end raid the fridge
You open up the too tired to stand. There's nothing much in there
Just some bottle of water and a few cans of coca-cola. Yeah, let's go share a coke with mom
Hand her a bottle to us and to the future. She looks at you. There's a glint in her eye
Cheers
Take a swig. It's really bad. Isn't it? Yep, you finish the coca-cola in silence. Then you go back to bed
All right. I have to leave this house the end. I shared a coke with mom
It's really bad. Well, this is yeah, that's not a coke ad
It's a rival brand ad
Hey mom wanted to say
Thanks
I love you. I love you, too
While it still can be said you'll go back to bed the next morning full cook a full bread
big egg salad with a big cook and
Elaborate dinner for mom. No mayo here. Yeah, that's fucked up
You head down to the grocery store to get some groceries you pick up some apples
A rotisserie chicken and a box of macaroni and cheese
You're the mom now grab a bottle of mayo you go to the cashier the cashier eyes you disapprovingly then scans your groceries
That'll be 25 36. Uh, go fuck yourself
Any change you get your change and head out the door you go back home and put the groceries away
pair
Dinner for mom. Yep. Sounds about retail. Yeah prepare dinner for mom
You put a pot of water on the stove to boil and open the macaroni box. You empty it into the pot
add the cheese
Make it stop. I i've i'm
I tried to get away from it
You add the cheese you grab the chicken and put it in the oven. It's ready in half an hour
You take out two plates from the cabinet and begin to eat
Wait for mom
You wait for mom mom comes in and sits down
Something smells good
She begins to eat finally some good fucking food
You both sit and eat in silence
Then she stops
Why it's over she puts her face in her hands begins to weep you go over to her. I'm sorry mom
It isn't over
Right, like i'm where i'm here. We're here. It isn't over look what you did
It isn't over. She looks up and smiles. Let's go to the living room
She picks up her plate and puts it in the sink
Go to the living room you watch a lot of tv
We both sit down on the couch. Do you have any idea why this is happening?
Not a clue. We should get some rest
Um, um, I have a dragon
outside
Begins to laugh
I'm just joking mom. She picks up a throw pillow from the couch and hits you with it
Oh, yeah, whatever sport
Um, I am serious
dragon
Is it right outside?
He chuckles i'll see you in the morning
Get the dragon
To come in the house
ds2 board gamer
No
You see you get the dragon to come in the house
You see a large lizard slithering through the grass towards the front door. You open it and it slinks in okay
Mom
Come look
At the dragon
But it's not it's a lizard
You say
Hey mom, come look at the dragon. She walks over and screams
It's a dragon
She runs into the kitchen. You hear the sound of her opening the freezer. What's in the freezer?
I hope she takes out a she comes back holding a tray of ice cubes. The dragon looks at her annoyed
She throws the ice cubes at the dragon which slides away on its belly to avoid them
There is some logic behind this
Because if the dragon is fire, you know, that's that's like the stupidest logic ever right?
But it's there kind of the ai is trying hey mom stop
Why we need to help the dragon? What's it gonna do eat us?
Tell the dragon to eat mom the dragon opens its mouth and roars your mother looks down dejected
I'll never be free. Will I i'm sorry mom it was
Just a joke a prank. Why am I such a shitty child? That's a really good question
Are you perny where the fuck is perny? She looks at you. I know I know it's okay
You'd never hurt me on purpose. So imagine a mother hugging her son the next morning
I've got to get away from like weird child and mom arc of this story
This one's been going on for like an hour
You look for mom you search the house, but she's nowhere to be found
The back door is wide open you walk outside and look around mom you look around but she's gone
You have no idea where she went
Ask the dragon ask the dragon where your mom is
You ask the dragon where your mom is the dragon looks at you confused and it shrugs and goes back to sleep
You stand there for a while waiting for it to do something
You eat my mother
The dragon looks at you annoyed
It opens his mouth and flame shoots out it burns your arm and you begin to feel faint
Did you eat her dragon says something in its strange language?
You see a flash of your house in the distance a woman stands in front of it screaming
You run towards it, but the dragon flies in front of you. It looks at you annoyed
You scream as the house is consumed by a ball of flame finally the pain stops
Raid the fridge and open a beer. It's pretty gross, but you manage to finish it
You go to sleep at the end. It's supposed to be like six
All right. I'm i'm out of here. I'm done. I can't do anymore
It's been almost five hours. I don't I don't think my brain can handle any more of this
That was a very long simpsons episode. Yes
Say epilogue
Fine. I'm just curious
My mommy's
My chest is killing me right now. Let me be honest because of that
It was two or three things today that seriously it was just
Um, I I hurt myself. I like broke my penis
And I swear to god i'm not trying to be like funny. This is not like a funny joke
I actually was in the bathroom laughing so hard while taking a piss
I like i've hurt myself today
Like it was I was laughing too hard going to the bathroom. I just kept going over and over and over again in my head
What was happening? It was the panther thing
Accidental self-inflicted. Okay
There is no epilogue
What a quote. Oh, okay
Yeah, I gotta eat something
And i'm gonna get going
Oh, that was a ton of fun though
It always is
And i'm glad that it's been a full five hours. I knew it was gonna happen
A new eternal darkness was just not gonna happen
Epilogue didn't work. So I will see you guys
On I have some doctor's stuff to do
Over these next couple of days
But you will see me again
on friday
See on friday
We're going to do
um
Eternal darkness
And then saturday is the dlc movie night and watch the playlist of a shitload of videos
We're trying to go through them. The mods are doing a very good job
But I will say this again because I have to say this every time
There were hundreds and hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of submissions
If you do not see your video
I'm, very sorry
But when you have this many submissions
We gotta try we gotta try to condense it a little
Even if I do this over the course of two or three days, it's possibly even thousands of them. Yeah
Too many people
Are funny
And too many people make good videos
Raid raid joel ray. Yeah. Well, what's he doing? What's joel up to today?
Go find out what joel is doing
Rated joel in a while having fun doing rock smith rock smith, huh?
Isn't that the
Don't you play a real guitar?
Wait, isn't guitar wait, isn't rock smith guitar hero people that actually know music?
I mean, I already like it so far. I was only there for five seconds
He's actually playing the guitar. All right, that's cool. Yeah
Uh, let's do the credits
Thank you again everybody
Goal raid. Yeah, we will after the credits
Yeah, I probably i'm gonna I don't think ai dungeon to me
I feel like you do it for a little while
And then you have to take a break for a while
So I don't think we're gonna go back to it for a little while
I feel like there needs to be a cooldown period because it just gets too wild
But when we play it, it's a ton of fun. So friday, we're gonna do eternal darkness
And hopefully I see you there. If not, if it's not part of your schedule, then that's all right
You never come back to another stream again
Hey, that's cool, too
But like, you know, you don't you check out another one sometime, but i'll see you on friday. Let's run the credits right now
ready three two
Bring them on all in alphabetical order
Totally excited to finally watch joel because I was anticipating anticipating the stream
I feel like that's a good place. That's probably a real pain in the ass to set up
If you're using a real guitar
I feel like that's very difficult to do
A custom song sue. Well, that's awesome
I should do it. I have no idea how to play the guitar
My pinky can I can't play guitar hero. My pinky cannot hit the orange button
I have to play guitar here on medium only
Because I can only do the three buttons. I can't do four
Don't use the pinky. I have to
the drum stream
I could you know what I could probably really do like a rock band drum stream
And a lot of you think that I may be messing around but I can do all that stuff on expert
But I think what I I don't think I can do that though
All the just the it's just copyright music the stream
Maybe it's true. Yeah now on twitch now, you're gonna be careful with the copyright stuff
my understanding
do custom songs
That might work for a little while. I don't think I think that might get a little old to me after about six hours though
Doing just custom songs. I think I feel like if I heard like 85 different remixes the rat song
I know I feel like I'd probably want to it's like that. What are the songs do I have on this channel?
It'd be it'd be 40 giant enemy spiders
30 rat remixes and then the germa craft script with a beat behind it
That's what I would have to do
But we'll see you friday
Thanks for watching guys
Add on over to joel say hello
Take care