Yo, Jerma, check out this sweet ass car right over here. Get in here. Don't knife it. Don't slice up my ride, nothing like that.
We got an incredible orb in his, like, whack.
Hey, Jerma!
What's up? Oh, a nice peel out.
I like how we start in Star Junction every time, too. Hey, check out this cop. Cop!
Hey, wait for me.
Hey, I don't have a door.
Shut up. He needs to see my car.
I like this doorless DeLorean.
Wait. Wait for me, guys.
Hey, guys. Wait up.
Hey, guys. Jerma.
How did that not kill me? You hit me with the car. There's no way I didn't get hit by the hood of your car.
I'm getting on this bike. You guys are gonna get biked.
That was great. That was like an action movie. You just pulled in perfectly into frame. Right when I... That was so great.
Let's go.
Alright, we're gonna... Alright, we're gonna do a race orb.
Alright. So, Star's gonna be the finish line. Alright?
Okay.
How did... I can't get... I can't get out of here.
You gotta get some speed. You gotta get some speed.
Oh, what the hell?
Hold on.
Hey, I just saw...
What? I'm like in the...
I thought you were like honking the horn.
I can hear that all the way down here.
I'm gonna go forward and see if I can make it over.
Come on.
I made it.
Oh, shit.
Your ride is still down here, no?
What are you doing?
Trying to drive on top of your car.
It looks like you're trying to hump my car.
Maybe I am. It's a pretty nice, sexy car you got there.
It's bouncing around all over the place.
Oh, fuck.
That took them a long time to take me out.
Alright, guys. Let's bounce.
We just had a moment.
Hi.
Make a drug deal.
Is that another bike?
Yes, it is. That's another bike.
We're good.
Oh, another one right here, too.
More of the orange one.
Did you die?
Alright, should we all just die right here?
And then come right back and grab the bikes?
I don't have a...
Oh, damn.
This guy means business.
That guy just tossed me off the bike and shot me.
Bitch, you're shooting me. I didn't do anything.
Wow, you're getting fucked.
What the fuck?
Alright.
Alright, don't move, Orb.
Orb, now they're shooting you.
Why?
I don't know.
No, they're not.
Yes, they are?
Fuck!
Why did your gun just fly 30, 40 feet in the air?
Where are you?
Where the hell are you?
You're even lower than that?
Yeah, right below you.
Oh, damn it.
There you are.
Alright, it's time to end this.
What's it time for?
I don't have a parachute.
Oh my god.
What are you doing, guys?
Guys? What happened?
You went right next to me.
Guys, what happened?
I don't...
Wait.
Where did you get the helicopter?
Where did you get that?
It was yours.
It landed safely.
It was intact?
Yeah. I shot you out of it and it just landed.
Oh my god.
Alright, I'm going up.
Where are you?
Where the fuck are you, Jerma?
I'm high. You're below me.
I don't know.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dude!
Oh, I'm dead, huh?
I'll get you.
You are just raining fire on me.
Dude, I'll get him.
Have faith.
You're too far away for these shots to register.
I'm going to get you eventually.
Don't worry.
This thing can't fire.
No!
I'm still alive.
Orb is there now, apparently.
You ain't getting me, sucker.
Oh my god!
Did you get him?
Yeah, I got him.
Did I hit you with that last rocket?
No.
It looked so close.
Just drive as fast as you possibly can.
Everyone has bikes because I have a bike.
Everyone's a copycat.
You can never be a hipster in GTA.
As soon as I see something, I'm jumping.
What happened up there?
Tell me when you're jumping.
Do a countdown.
Do a bike jump.
Like a 360, 1080.
We're going to get some air from this.
Oh!
Hit escape and see where I am right now.
I don't know.
I don't know how that happened.
Wait, what the hell?
Look where he is on the map.
What the hell?
Me and him hit a jump right here.
I launched off the bike.
Let's ride to him.
What the hell?
Put that in slow motion, nerd.
I'll kill you.
Wow.
That was one of the most intense things ever.
I started to laugh.
My head hurt because I was laughing too hard.
Then I realized what was happening.
I was just in shock.
Holy shit.
That was seriously unbelievable.
I thought you landed behind me.
I have no idea how that happened.
I think it's because I jumped off the bike
last second and we hit the telephone pole.
Yeah, I'm alive.
Not for long, apparently.
And I'm dead.
Fuck you, nerds.
I'm out.