So is this going to be like a little hotel? This is uh, it's going to be like a little...
How? Hey, I'm not sleeping with like three dudes clumped up in one little area. I feel like I'm
back in college. Alright, here's a crafting table and we can't make... Do we have coal?
Anyone have coal? Anybody? It's down there. By the tree. By the tree. Okay, well we need a pick to do
that. I'm gonna make a leather helmet and I'm gonna make a leather... I don't know. Alright,
I have a wooden pick now. Alright, I have leather pants and a leather helmet. I'm gonna look like a
clown. You look all steampunk with this texture pack on. I look like I have a cardboard box on my
head. Yeah, I think we're all using different texture packs. It's pretty cool. I'm using Snacks
PRBD. I'm using the default. That's a good one, you know. That's the classic right there. I'm using
the classic. So don't... Did you guys plant the saplings? Don't dig this out. There, let's
put the door down right there. So I'm gonna plant a tree right here. I'm making my way
through the snow. I can't plant a tree anywhere. You have to do it on the dirt. Oh,
uh, right. He's way over there. He's exploring without us, man. We're like building structures
and houses and stuff. I'm playing with fire right now. I'm throwing snowballs at this enderman
that's all the way up there. No, we might throw snowballs. Put the door down right here, man.
Oops. Oops. I got sticky keys that did not like that. Okay. So we make a door.
I think you have one. I made one. Oh, God. Mops are dropping down on me. Oh, look at this little
house. Oh, yeah. Julius Caesar would have lived in this house. And just unlimited glass. I have
three stacks of 64 glass. All right. I want my bed to go right here. I want a picture of my favorite
president. Uh, Grover Cleveland right here. And then I want, um, a cop to go right here.
We need to find some sheep. I don't think we're going to find any sheep.
Uh, we're going to find a bunch of leptors. Just look at this.
Left is up there being like a one man army. Oh, I just fell. Yeah.
I'll get your stuff, man. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, zombie. Get away. All right. Oh, my God.
I'm getting knocked all over the place. Oh, there's a creeper and a zombie. Oh, my God.
Okay. Creeper blew up. I'm cool. All right. Here's some leather stuff. No problem. I'll make some
other stuff as well. I am. We need to make a chest.
Welcome back. I have something for you. You do? What do you got? Let me see. What is this? Do we
have like a new friend? Is this like our God dog? What is this guy doing? He's, he is, uh,
defending the fort, man. That's pretty cool. Hey, Hey you, I'm talking to you. He's, he's waiting
patiently for the lepter to come out. You look at me when I'm talking to you. All right.
Oh, well I just hit him. He's dead. Nice. All right guys. Here you go. All right. We do have
some bones. He's got an iron sword and I'm over here trying to pass out wooden swords.
Hey, I'll take a wooden sword. I will absolutely take a wooden sword. It's starting to be daytime
now. I'm going to do a travel. Germa, pass me your, that bone you picked up. Here you go. I have it
now. It's my bone. My one and only bone. I put two more bones in the chest. So we got, we got some,
some miracle grow right here. Oh, I thought you were just looking at your pants.
You look like Steve Urkel. You got your pants are like all the way up to like to your belly button.
All right. Back up, Germa. Back up a lot. They're all going to die.
Yeah. They blew it up. Ha ha. Yeah. This is all, there's a bunch. This is two or three in there
still. I'm going down. I'm going to bring the bow. And then, then there was one. I thought he got
him. I thought he got him. Let's go together. Hang on. Hang on. There's still, there's something
in here. Look, look, look. This is what I wanted to explore before. I think, was there only one more
in there? Did you get them? Was, was there only one more creeper in there? Yeah. He blew up.
All right. There's nothing in here now. Oh God. There's one in here. All right. Here's the thing.
We got to get back and get our stuff before it disappears. But sweet. I finished them off.
Why are these, why are these two fighting each other? Because one of them took damage from the
other. Taking these guys down. I'm almost out of food though. So kind of a problem.
Get out of here, spider. Anybody got any food? I need arrows. Do you guys have arrows? I, yeah. I
do not. All right. Cool. All right. Zombies are the primary target here. Yo, there's electric.
Actually, let's just go to the melon farm. Yo, that's. Venom sack. Venom sack. Really should
have attacked his ring today. Yeah. But where's the fun in that? So. Oh, there's another one though.
Come at me. Watch out. Come at me. Everybody. Let's go. Don't, don't, don't go that way.
All of you. We'll take every single one of you on right now.
Oh, there goes Jerma. But he took one for the team. Hey, at least we got some zombie flesh.
Okay. So try to stay on the same path. Man, this bridge freaks me out. Yeah, it really does. It's
just like, where am I going to fall down? Drop that skelly on the left. Oh, there's a chest down
there. Forget the chest, man. We got to get that enchanted bow. Except everyone is. I think
Jerma went the wrong way. Did I go the wrong way? Oh, there he goes. Watch out. There's a skeleton
that's on you. Except for me and you left there. I looked over to see you because I heard you say,
I think you went the wrong way. I turned and I fell.