Good evening. Good early evening. How are you? Oh dude, Minecraft? Today? No.
I did the reason why we start in a couple hours later is because I was actually in a call
and we were talking about all kinds of things for the Minecraft
uh fuck the king server. That is yes still slated for the 15th. Has not been pushed. It's still
going. Uh it's it's gonna be I can't wait. I will have complete and full details on how that stream
is going to work tomorrow. Tomorrow after the game awards we're gonna sit here and I'm gonna open up
paint and we're going to go over how it's gonna work. If you have no idea what I'm talking about
then check the stream tomorrow night because that's going to be half game awards and then
uh half fuck the king explanation. So I'm a little excited because not only are we doing
fuck the king this coming uh 15th. I'm also about to play right now uh one of my favorite games
and I got it's working. It works perfectly fine. I'm ready to rock and roll. We're gonna play
red alert today. What's gonna do the campaign? I you know what I don't think I've ever even
done the campaign. I think I did the first like two missions and I gave up. This is like 15 years
ago. The campaign is really good. I know. I know. So that's what we're gonna do today and maybe now
at this time maybe I'll do like a skirmish where I really test my skills against like a good computer.
There's multiplayer that you can do but I want to do that with I want to set that up
with like subs or mods or other streamers because that's more fun that way than just
kind of detonating all the community servers that exist. We'll see if I still am into this after
today then maybe we'll open up some multiplayer stuff with actual multiplayer people. You should
do it with Joel so he can pretend to like it even though he hates it. I don't think you can
pretend to like red alert. I think you just like red alert. I dedicated my english project video
to you. Hey thanks. Did you make me look good? All right. Are you ready? Are you ready to see
my childhood? I am. Take a look. There it is. Red alert and it's all I got everything. There's no
sound. Now there should be. There will be. They're going to remaster it. Well we don't have time for
remasters. We play original hardware. Why is there no audio? Is there actually no audio?
Is it so low that you can't hear it? That's weird. All right you ready? This is by the way if you
don't know what uh red alert is it's the best rts that's ever been made. What about warcraft
2? No no no. Sit down. What about warcraft 3? Sit down. What about the original command and
sit down? What about red alert 2? You could. All right hold on. You don't have to sit down
but I don't want you to stand and interrupt my broadcast. Uh what about a warhammer 40k?
Dawn of war. The original dawn of war. All right you can you can come up and stand here with me
because that's the only other one that deserves to be there. How hard is this game though?
That's a lot of people. This game's very hard isn't it? All right let's go.
Oh what do I want to be allies or soviets? I've got to be the allies. Allied headquarters
present day. Good thing I turned it down. Commander. So last transmission? All 900 hours.
Since then nothing. Perhaps Einstein escaped. Too much to hope for general. He would have contacted
us by now. This is classified. I know. I sent for her. General von Essling. She is a civilian.
That's why I don't get killed. Commander this is Tanya Adams a professional volunteer. She has the
best voice lines. She will work with you on this mission. Somewhere inside this research center
the soviets hold Albert Einstein. We need him back immediately. Get Tanya inside so she can get
Einstein out. Once you have located him bring him back to your drop-off point for immediate
evacuation. Be careful. The base is heavily fortified but not invincible. Their weakness
is power. Black out the base and nothing will stop you. Good luck. That's just, that's Tanya.
That's the best line in the whole game. We gotta go get Einstein. Here we go.
Oh I can feel the nostalgia. There it is. All right, all right. Hold it. Let's, let's go this
way. Holy shit. It's like the blood's rushing to my face right now. I'm so happy to be playing this.
Affirmative. Wait, wait, wait, wait. No. Well and back up, back up. I gotta, I gotta do this
correct. Why is the music so low? Hold on. Game controls. No, no, no. I want to keep that note.
Sound controls. There it is. Let's drop this. Let's raise this. There you go. Now we're, now it's normal.
That's better. Okay let's go. Here we go. So Tanya, if you don't know, Tanya instantly destroys
buildings that she walks into. Yes sir. Take out their resources. Don't get run over. Don't get
run over. Okay, I lost a lot of people. I gotta take out their power. Oh shit. This is harder than
I thought it was gonna be. How do we get it? Where's Tanya? Okay, Tanya. All right, let's go.
Get in. Wait, how do you attack move? How do you attack move? I don't know. Take out the power. Take out
the power. Is it A? No, it's not A. Control is to target individual. Okay, take out the power.
Easy Tanya. Don't get killed. All right, the power is gone. Take out their tech center. Got it. What?
Oh, I just, okay, I killed Einstein. All right, let's go. Take out the buckets. Please turn the
music. I'm gonna turn music up and turn volume down. Take out the power. All right, this is very hard.
Okay, hold on. I don't, this is why I didn't ever play the actual video game because it's very hard
to do. All right, I gotta, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. All right, I want two different
groups. You're group one. Group one, I want you to go take out this. Group two, I want you to take out
the stuff in the base. Group one. Group two. Group two, take out guys on the right. All right, don't
destroy the base. All right, back up, back up, back up. Is that enough? Okay, now I can take a
sec. Wake up reinforcements. Don't destroy the tech center. All right, here we go. I gotta think
this through. They're, I gotta take out their power. We're gonna wrap around. Let's take everybody
over here. Is this still powered? Take it out. Take this shit out. Kill their resources. All right,
take out their base. Destroy the whole thing. Yeah, yeah, we took the power. This is good.
All right, I just had to avoid. I don't want to, Tonya can't die. And neither can Einstein.
If Tonya touches a building, it instantly explodes.
All right, I'm good. I love this game. Get Einstein to the helicopter. That's Einstein.
All right, we got it. I did it. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no.
Why did they destroy the building? I don't even know how to, how do you attack move?
All right, let's do it again. It's not A. All right, just get in there. No, it's not A. All right,
let's go. I got him, right? You select and you right click. All right, we did it. I got Einstein.
All right, that wasn't so hard. What's going on over here? Oh shit.
Where were these guys before? Okay, that was very easy.
I got full motion loud cutscenes. Great. All right, only, all right, I had, they had more
casualties than me. Therefore, I win. I'm going to turn the base volume down and then turn it up.
Soviet aggression has increased tenfold already. We don't have the manpower to fight Stalin's
armies on every front. Commander, you did a fine job rescuing Einstein for us. Now,
we are counting on you again. One of the passes we use for a supply route has been blocked by the
Reds. A convoy from the 434th is due through in a matter of hours. The supplies they carry
are critical to our war efforts. That's not a belt. What we have in that area to work with.
That's a power lifter support. And time is against us. You will have to make do.
You wear that to a bench press. So the convoy can get to safety. Their lives rest in your hands.
Go. Here's the best part. Here's the best part. Here's the best part. Here comes the best part.
Wait, clear the way for the convoy. Yes, sir. All right. I like to play a little bit slower. No,
I don't. I got a mess of a volume here. That's, that's probably better. Take a look at this.
But you didn't, you know what? They all watch this. Ready? Bang. Power plant immediately. Oh,
also some people are probably going to realize. Where's the guy? Where's the guy talking? Where's
the guy? Uh, I deleted him from the game. I literally, I literally modded the game to remove
that guy talking. Building unit, ready unit, lost unit, ready building unit, ready unit,
lost unit, lost unit, lost unit, lost. I know I modded them out of the game. All right. Oh,
we got, I got a oil refinery. Let's go. Let's start clearing. I don't even need two groups.
All right. Go down here. Wait, I'm going to leave a Jeep here. You stay up there.
Shoot him. If this guy throws a grenade and kills you, I'd be so mad. The one DB music is good.
All right. I, what is attack move? That's attack point. Let's get that down.
Oh, they're really, oh, I got a time limit here. A click. It's not though. It's not,
it's not doing it. Yes, it is. No, it's not. Attack move. No, it's not. This game was made
before attack move was invented. No, no, it was not. All right. We have a, I need an
engineer to repair that Jeep. How are we doing? How are we doing over here? Good, good, good,
good, good. We need barracks. No, you guys stay, just stay. And this is like a way you can do like
a guard, can't you? My base is not dying. It's fine. I don't think we can get through this.
You don't have any engineers. Clear the way for the convoy.
There's dogs. All right. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Don't go up there. You idiot.
The base is right up here. All right. What's going to, I just want a ton of rocket soldiers.
You guys go this way. Actually don't kill dogs. What do you, I can't help that. Can I do it?
I know this is the dog house, but it's important. It's a strategic location. Oh,
shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Shit. Don't be an idiot. More, more soldiers.
Psycho streamer can't help itself. What? This is clear. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Move in,
move in. Go, go, go, go, go. Take the whole thing up. Over the base. No, just keep rocket
soldiers coming. They're the best. Construction yard going down. My base is fine. There's nothing.
Watch out, watch out, watch out. Oh, that guy died. Run him over.
All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Who's still alive?
Convoy approaching. Oh, I did it. I got it. Oh, that, that's my, okay. Get in the convoy.
They just have to be protected. Nice. All right. I got it. Loud, uh, full motion,
loud video coming soon. This is the best track on the whole entire soundtrack, by the way.
They're just going to make it all the way up and that's good. We can't hear it. Hold on.
Yeah, but now it's like, now my, now it's hurting my ears.
Hold on. I got to turn it down for me. It's too loud for me. Good. No, not good. All right. How's
that? I can do, I can deal with that. That's good for me. All right. Mission two complete. I've,
so this is, I love this. It's all coming back to me. Loud. It needs to drown out your voice. Why?
Command and Conquer generals was better. I don't think so. Just wait till I do a skirmish again
with like two, like three V three. It's going to be nuts. Wait, so let me just say I'm rooting
for the Soviets. Well, all right, which one up or down? Let's go down. It's a nice bridge.
Intelligence recon shows heavy Soviet movement in your area. Nearby bridges are key to Soviet
advancement. Destroy all bridges as soon as possible. Tanya will assist keep her alive at
all costs. Destroy the bridges. Tanya has to stay alive. How are we doing? Okay. This is
over here. I instantly killed that guy. Don't go, don't go and just guns blazing. I got to
have a strategy here. Shoot the barrel. Oh no, it's going to like press an alert. No, it's not. I'm
fine. Wait, who just came out of there? Is it a medic? Oh, fuck yeah. Why can't Tanya be in
Smash Brothers? Just one guy over here. Get used to those sounds because that's all the sounds
you're going to hear for the rest of the time that I play this. And you wanted me to have
the unit lost. Every time a unit dies in red alert, that guy says that somebody died.
Unit lost. Let's rock. Unit lost. Affirmative. Unit lost. Oops. I just fucking murdered the medic.
It's okay. It's still doable. It's still doable. I didn't know he was going to.
All right, watch out. This is flamethrower turrets.
I think I get this. This is mine. It's not mine. I can't pick this up. Come on. This is mine,
right? Why can't I get it? I'm taking it slow because I don't want to walk into.
Why is this following me now? What's going on? There's three tanks over here.
I have to shoot the barrel. Nice. All right. Hey, well actually that's good. That works out for me.
I'm okay with that. Somebody said no cha-ching in like 10 seconds. Sad. I don't walk over here.
I'll burn instantly. Save the game right there. I wonder if I should go down. Wait, take out the
bridge first. Uh oh. What is that? Don't let him land. Don't let him land. Don't let him land.
What's down here? Any reinforcements? Any medics? Any friends? Here we go.
Crate. That's a crate. Crate. Give me the crate. Give me the crate. Crate. There's an item in it
or something in it. You can get like extra items and stuff. All right. Let's kill this guy. Don't
aggro everybody. Money. Wait a minute. Oh shit. I got four engineers.
All right. Stay here. Tanya has to take all four of these guys out.
Unbelievable. Good work. All right. Let's go. Now where do I go from here? Up this way.
Don't blow up the bridge again. No. Don't worry. I'm not going to kill anybody. We're just going
to go slow. There's a medic up there. All right. I don't want to kill this. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh
shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Watch out for the grenade. He's hurt. Come on. Get over here. Heal us. Heal.
Nice. Do it again. Now do it to yourself. Do it to yourself. Oh fuck it. Whatever. All right.
No, no, no. Not everybody walk in. Tanya just goes. No one will die. No, this goes self-heal
unfortunately. All right. Tanya Goker. Wait. What was that? Wait. What happened? What was
that? Uh oh. What was there? Any more bridges? There's like a naval base over here.
All right. Everyone get out of the way. We're going to take this thing out. How do I? Oh,
we have to go across. Okay. So these turn up the in-game voices. I'm not going to turn the in-game
voice up. How am I going to do this? I think I'm screwed. Tanya's dead if she walked in there.
Is it my softlocks? Hold on. It's still a kill. That's all right. I have a save point right here.
Good. All right. Don't blow that up. Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill,
kill. Too late. I was too late. I do want to get. Where are the engineers? Oh, fuck.
I have to get these engineers. Where's the music? This is weird without the music.
It's strange without music.
Okay. Save it here. My nostalgia. I know. Really. It's true.
Let's rock. Let's rock. This feels dark without the music. What do you mean dark?
I'm there. I'm there. Let's rock. Let's rock. And I am doing it wrong actually. It's let's rock.
Let's rock. Let's rock. Let's rock. Let's rock. All right. Heal yourself.
Save it here. Good. We're still safe. Let's rock. Let's rock. Take this shit out. We can move across.
He's scumming. Medic reporting. Let's rock. Yes, sir. I'm there.
Don't blow it up. Just go across it. I'm there. Don't trigger this. When we get across,
blow up the bridge. But then we can't ever come back. All right. We're going to have an
engineer go out and scout. We're good? All right. You go forward. Test for the landmines.
Okay. Here we are. Good. Yes, sir. I'm not having any fun. Medic reporting. I don't like this.
All right. We're going to take this out. The engineers can repair buildings. I think they
can take them over too. Can they? Don't blow up. Do not blow the bridge up.
Do not blow the bridge up. Stay here. Snipe. All right. Get across. Yes, sir. Affirmative.
Affirmative. Chew on this. Chew on this. Affirmative. What's up? I'm there. Okay.
Slowly. Okay. I'm going to blow this up from a safe distance. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir.
Oh, shit. Is that destroyed? No, it's not. Okay. Thank God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Run. Run. No,
don't run. We're good. Wait. I think I just did it. I did it. That's it, right? Yes. Okay. We're
good. Well, that would have sucked. Turn your volume down. Unit lost. The only reason why you
have that guy enabled is for A-bomb launch detected. A-bomb launch charging. A-bomb launch
detected. That's the reason why you have that guy enabled, but I couldn't. I just modded him out
again. All right. Any more? We got another one opened up right here. Oh, commander. We didn't see
you there. Oh, there you are. Commander, I wish I could say I had good news, but not all of our
battles fared as well as yours. The Greek front is collapsing and Germany is all but taken. However,
not all is lost. Your efforts have hampered Soviet progress in this area. The bridges you destroyed
have caused the Soviets to redirect their forces through a certain mountain pass that I believe
you are familiar with. They are gambling that you will not be able to stop them a second time.
We got enough screens in this room. Prove them wrong, Stavros. Expect a heavy concentration
of Soviet armor. The base you established is still standing. Get it up to speed as quickly
as possible. We're counting on you to keep the Reds from breaking through. Fake German accent.
We are going to stop them from breaking through. Cut. Hey, can I get a water, please? My throat is
fucking killing me. Can I have a water? Reporting. Destroy all Soviet units and structures. Let's go.
Very well. Shoot her out of the air. Acknowledged. All right. I need a...
What are they doing? I don't like this. Okay. Oh, shit. I got people down here. All right. Wait,
we got people everywhere. There's one guy up here. We got to get this guy back.
This fighting. I don't know where the fighting is happening.
We need to get back. Get back. One guy. Oh, fuck. That's my base. That's my base they're destroying.
I thought it was... What? I was just laying mines? Okay. Don't let them just go over here.
Reporting. Very well. Get to work. I need a new one. Kill him. All right. You... I just
dropped two mines for no reason. Yes, sir. Acknowledged. They're just going to keep coming.
All right. Put a mine down. Acknowledged. Why is it not going off? Wait, what? Yes, sir.
This guy's crop dusting me. All right. This is where it really begins. Okay. Give me a medic
and I get oil refinery. Come on. Hurry up. Yes, sir. Where's their base? I don't know.
All right. Back to work. You can do it now. Go on. And I got another. I got two of these now.
Pillbox. Go. Two medics. Yes, sir. Moving out. Ready and waiting. I want a medic with each group.
What's my APM? Probably four. Two pill boxes up top. No, I don't have enough money for this shit.
What's going on? Yes, sir. There we go. All right. I need... The rocket guys can shoot up there.
Pillbox down. Pillbox here. All right. You missed silo. All right. That's good. Now we need... How
are we doing on power? We're doing fine. Radar down. This is a radar dome so you can see where
everything that's going on. All right. We got a pillbox. That's good. Pillbox down here. Tuna
cans. Situated. Oil refinery. Doing strong. More rocket soldiers. They have planes.
Silo is needed. Silo is needed. You guys, trust me, you're going to be really happy that you don't
have to hear this guy. Yes, sir. Medic reporting. All right. I want to separate out. I want two
groups here. Group one. I want at least three. I want a medic. That's fine. You guys stay down
here. Yes, sir. Group one. Group one. Take this up here with you. Yes, sir. Acknowledged. Radar
dome. Let's go up here with it. Yeah. All right. I also want... All right. All right. Good. Good.
Just defend it. What am I going to do? I got a barracks already. We're going to do...
This is all I can build right now. So we're going to do two barracks. You're probably asking,
what are you pretty stupid? No. The more of anything you have, the sub tier under it will
go double as fast. I've already checked this out. Rocket soldier. Look at how quick this is going.
Now check that out. All right. I'm almost out of money. Acknowledged. All right. We're going
to take the scouts this way. This is the team scouts. Acknowledged. Where's the medic?
Heal these people. What are you stupid? Yes, sir. Ready and quick. Yes, sir. Agreed. Acknowledged.
All right. Here come the scouts. Get them all together. I'm going to get pill box.
I'm going to say the tanks will be coming from down here.
So that's a turret. It's better for tanks. This is team one. They're going to stay up. Oh,
look at me. I can do that instantly dead. Not even. Don't kill this.
I need engineers. I don't have any. Fuck. Okay. All right. All right. Where's team one?
You guys have to protect. Yes, sir. All right. Let's go. Team one. Stay in this area.
Wait, there's a guard button. I know there is. I played this game when I was like fucking 12.
I know there's a guard button. Affirmative. All right. What do we got? 1900. Get another,
get another or finally. No, another pill box. No. Yeah. Another pill box. Ready. Acknowledged.
Let's go scout. Acknowledged. G is guarding. Acknowledged. Acknowledged. Acknowledged.
G, you hold. Isn't there a patrol too? Acknowledged. All right. Where do I want this?
Probably over here. Okay. Hold on. You hold P. Acknowledged. Does that work? I just held it.
Why is it not working? That was red alert too. All right. Hold on. This is bad. Yes, sir. Wait
for the rocketeers. We're going in. Go for the tank first. Go. Kill the tank. Kill the tank.
Don't let them. Don't let them just run you over. Disaster. Absolute fucking disaster.
Are they going to counter? Okay. They're going to be coming in for a counter. Yes, sir. Run them
over. I need a war factory. I got destroyed. I know. Three guys in a tank versus 15 people.
Yes, sir. Acknowledged. Acknowledged. Acknowledged. Affirmative. Good. Okay. Keep going. Where's that
war factory? I need money. Prepare the buildings. I need an engineer. I think you need a war factory
for an engineer. Acknowledged. Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. More effective.
Okay. All right. Give me my war factory. No. Stop. Stop. Stop spending money. All right. These are
all. They never expected. Let's go. Oh, fuck. Look at all these rockets. This is good. I'm
going to melt this thing. Watch this. Nice. Good. Go this way. Yes, sir. Agreed. Agreed.
Very well. Affirmative. I need my war factory. I need more money. Hurry up and pick this up.
Agreed. These guys are so slow. I need the things to carry them. Can tanks take that
many rockets? No. The rocket guys are amazing against tanks. And I'm one of those idiots
that only makes rocket guys and they get destroyed by regular infantry.
Give me the war truck. Ready and waiting. At once. Save the game here too, by the way.
All right. Vehicle report. Yes, sir. Acknowledged. Affirmative. Stop. Stop. What are you doing?
Acknowledged. Acknowledged. Where's the base? It's like right here.
Affirmative. All right. Affirmative. Here we go. Affirmative. If they counterattack,
I lose. Affirmative. Acknowledged. Affirmative. Retreat. Retreat. Retreat. Back up. Back up.
Back up. Not worth it. Not going to happen. Retreat. Retreat. Retreat. Retreat. Don't go in.
Don't go in. Bad idea. All right. He singled himself out. He's an idiot. Get him. Acknowledged.
They have three tanks. I'm going to lose. Acknowledged. Back up to the base. Back to
the base. Back to the base. All right. Now it looks like I can see where they are.
Keep. These guys have... Okay. I need war truck. Is there any more ore? Oh,
fuck. There's no ore. Affirmative. Okay. I have to go up and get the ore up here.
Affirmative. I can't make an engineer? Surface depot. All right. Wait. I need a tank.
Awaiting orders. Affirmative. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh,
shit. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. They're getting ready. They're getting
ready to come this way. Everybody get over here. Very well. Affirmative. Vehicle.
Affirmative. Okay. Now this thing is useless. I don't have any money. I've spent my resources
so poorly. What's firing? Oh, my God. I'm going to lose. Oh, this is terrible. Stay back. Stay
back. Stay back. Just deposit your money and stay here. Deposit your money and stay.
Reporting. Yes, sir. Acknowledged. Three. Affirmative. Very well.
Some of you go. All right. I need. I spent my money in bad places. Kill it. Kill it. Kill
it. Yes, sir. Fuck out of here. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. All right. We can go back to work. Not yet.
Run them over. Yes, sir. Okay. We're looking good. Okay. Here they come. This is the next phase.
Affirmative. Yes, sir. What shitty APM they have. Don't run them over. Make it out. Good.
Don't ever underestimate a dickload of rocket guys. Vehicle reporting. All right. I need to
start. I gotta start. Oh, my God. They're just going to forever feed people over here, aren't
they? That's the never-ending harass. Affirmative. Get it. Strike first. Kill them. Yes, sir. Okay.
Now, I got my money's back. Where's my order trucks? They're all doing well.
Tanks. I just want tanks. God damn it. These are so slow. I need another war factory. Those are
expensive though. The $2,000. I just need to get a couple more tanks. I would feel comfortable with
four tanks. So, after this, we're going. Awaiting order. Acknowledge. Agree. This thing is. All
right. This thing's useless. I'm just going to. No, no, no. I'm going to run this thing to its death
so I can see what's going on over there. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. The computer mouse
can just go die up here if he cares. Go, go, go, go. Affirmative. You need to see what's up here.
You idiot. Why'd you stop? I think that's it. I think we can go. They have heavy tanks though.
Oh, all right. I'm going to do it. Vehicle reporting. No, they have a base right here.
This is where I can make it happen. Another tank. More tanks. Vehicle reporting. And another
turret too. Okay, let's go. Yes, sir. It's time to move. People are going to be one. Yes, sir.
Tanks are going to be two. Reporting. We're running out of time. Affirmative. Go. Affirmative.
Don't go in all the way. You only got like two health. How am I doing on money?
Kill it. Now they have a base. I might not be able to take the base out. That might be hard.
Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Back it up. Back it up. Back it up. Be strategic about this.
What's up there? All right. They have... We're going to take out the...
Yes, sir. Affirmative. I need the tanks. Wait, let's wait. Let's take out their resources.
Affirmative. Affirmative. Here comes the fight. Medic, get in there. Kill the snowplow.
Snowplow. I can't get in there with these guys. Yes. Don't go in too far. Don't go in too far.
Don't go too far. Yes, sir. All right. Take it out. Can you do it at range?
Yeah. Oh, no. That's okay. Yes, sir. They're coming in from the stock. Acknowledged.
Give me another... Give me another barracks. Reporting. Affirmative. Affirmative. Oh,
shit. I'm out of power. This guy needs to up this game. More. Don't let up. Fuck this. That's
all they got. Go in. Go in with the tanks. Uh-oh. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back up. Back
it up. Yes, sir. That's bad. Just take it out. Take it out. Take it out. What else is up here?
Take out their flame shit and then I can have my infantry actually go in.
Affirmative. Crush. Crush. Crush. Oh, my God. Run them over. Run them over. Run them over.
Yes. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I need... Yes, sir. Affirmative.
Waiting orders. Report. Very well. I'm going to run out of resources in a minute.
There's no more gold to get. It's only over here. I need money. Dick. Yes, sir. I need to expand.
Uh, I can't expand because I don't have... I can't... There's no more... There's no construction
yard. I just have to win. Agree. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. I'm slowly taking out this shit.
They don't have much up there. Thank God. Go. Affirmative. I need to make an ore refinery
like over here. Affirmative. Shit. What... Okay. What's absolutely... This is not necessary.
More tanks. I need more tanks. Reporting. I need to spend the money on the tanks. I can't
have a second ore factory. Ready and waiting. Acknowledged. Affirmative. Affirmative.
Okay. They have one tank and like... Yeah, this is over. I win. Just don't go in yet.
Yes, sir. Acknowledged. Sit on their ore field and just keep killing the snowplow.
All right. What needs to happen is I got to take out this, take out the tank,
and then I should win. Here we go. With the tanks. All right. They're just... Why are you going that
way? No. Go. Damn it. He killed the damn thing. No. You motherfucker. You dug the snowplow. He
knew what he was doing. He knew what he was doing. Send him in. Send him in. Send him in. Everybody.
Go. Go. Go. Go. Who's left? Oh, shit. Affirmative. Don't get in range of that. I can do this with one
tank. Take out the barracks. Yeah. Oh, spam. What the fuck is he made out of? Oh, my God.
Kill him. You build a flame tank. Don't let him rebuild. Go up here.
Affirmative. No, no, no. Stay. Stay. Stay. Stay. Stay. Don't go that way. All right. Here we go.
Unable to comply. Building in progress.
Air field?
Build some barracks. God damn it, man. Just go up. Take out the silos. You're on run-over duty.
Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir.
Acknowledge. Acknowledge. Very well. Very well. Don't get in range of that.
Uh-oh. Here comes snowplow. Don't let him run you over. Don't let him get... All right. Good.
Take out the construction yard. Where did you get a tank?
Affirmative. Kill him. Yes. Why are you going up there?
They can't build buildings anymore. I win. Of course. Affirmative. Agreed. Agreed.
Very well. Reporting. Acknowledge. All right. Hold back for a second.
Affirmative. Affirmative. Vehicle reporting. Affirmative. Affirmative.
He's going to run in front of you. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Acknowledge.
Affirmative. Acknowledge. Acknowledge. He's going to kill it, isn't he?
Affirmative. Acknowledge. Reporting. Acknowledge. No. Run him over.
You literally cannot win. I win. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Acknowledge. Acknowledge. Acknowledge.
All right. Yeah, it's over. I win. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Literally. Yeah, at this point, this is annoying.
Why are you still in the game, man? Like, you're going to ride this. It's over. You lost.
You're going to stay in the game. I have to go around and find the one farm that you built.
To BM the game. Yes, sir. Affirmative. How do you still have money to do this?
Acknowledge. Acknowledge. Acknowledge. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Don't cross the space path. Don't do that.
Thank god. Yes, sir. Kill them buildings. Just kill them buildings. It's over.
The germ is gaming hard right now. Yeah, I know. I gotta turn this down. This shit is so loud.
Okay, that's better. Did he just sell everything? Yes, sir. All right. This motherfucker is
seriously BMing me. He sold everything. Affirmative. He sold every building.
Very well. And you just left with a snowplow. Affirmative. Yes, sir. At once. Affirmative.
Is that actually all that you have left? Affirmative. Here it comes. The final battle.
Ready and waiting. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. This is the last line of defense in the war.
You know you're in the snowplow. Like, what do you do? Snowplow BM. Yeah, I know. What the fuck?
I guess I did that.
This game. I love this game. 157 to 120. What building did I lose? I lost a building?
This one's into, we're going into Russia. Not quite. Let's go. Let's go up here.
Government leaders have abandoned the capital and are now hiding in exile. Information out of
occupied Athens has been sporadic, but Soviet forces are indeed in control of the capital,
as well as much of the outlying territories in Greece. In the city, fighting among allied
and Soviet troops continues, but the allied death toll is rising rapidly. Now it remains to be seen
if allied forces will be able to weather this onslaught intact. What the fuck? Reacting to
this latest assault, allied diplomats led the United Nations in a 281 to 7 vote that in approving
a unique military funding initiative aimed at increasing global allied support. This proposal
calls for the formation of a global defense agency to be temporarily established in an
unnamed European capital. Sounds bad, does it not? Well, it is, but Stalin has just written his
obituary. At last, this will help us galvanize the rest of the world against him. Yes, we have lost
Greece, but we are not out just yet. We've lost Greece. Stalin may think so, but if we can continue
to counsel the talents of commanders like yourself, we will come to this war on top.
My old friend, one of Tanya's men, she found something. Russian security agents have captured
her. They will almost certainly take her back to Moscow. They must get her back. She has vital
information on the Ion Breton project. Did you hear when he put it down? That information could
help tip the scales in our favor. Let him clear his head. In this state, he is of no use to us.
The Soviets currently hold Tanya near Grodno. The prison is well guarded with a supply truck from
a nearby Soviet base, runs through the facility several times a day. If your spies can infiltrate
the war factory, they may be able to hitch a ride into the prison compound. Once you have found Tanya,
get her out of there, any way you can. Such a pretty face. Where is Professor Einstein?
That was a real spin. I was hoping you'd say that. Oh, fuck. Oh, it's a syringe. What,
what is it blood? What is that syringe? It has to be a syringe in every game.
I'm afraid the effects are quite permanent. Oh, get it away from the eye. Oh, I hate this. Oh,
I hate this. Oh, is he stuck in his chest? Wait, wait, what?
Let's go get spy into the war factory. War factory over here.
The dogs can see through. Oh shit. Oh shit, a dog is chasing me. The dogs can see through
your disguise. I remember. All right, get out of the way. Got to get in here. Watch out for that
dog. Watch out for that dog. Watch out for that dog. Watch out for that dog. Watch out for the dog.
What? Didn't I just die? Didn't, what about, didn't that guy just die?
All right, I gotta wait. I gotta go like now, but I can't. I gotta wait. This is Hitman.
I gotta play it like Hitman. Okay, there they go. They're going to come up here. How far out do
these guys go? Maybe I should go down. They're not going to see me, right? I'm going down. Look
at that mammoth tank. That's the best, that's the best unit in the whole game, by the way.
All right, don't, I'm not, just stay here. Just stay, stay right here. They come up,
they come down, then they go this way and I'm going to go over here.
Save it right here. All right, I'm ready. Up and then they come back down. Hide up here.
Stay right there. They don't, please don't see me. Right? I'm far enough away. Okay.
Don't move. They go down. Okay, they go down there.
Get in there. I'm in. Now what? Oh, I'm in the convoy. Oh, shit. Save it here.
This base is huge. Christ. Get Tanya to the helicopter.
Destroy the SAM sites. Let's go. Tanya? What happened to the spy? Oh no, the spy is dead.
Destroy the SAM sites. Get Tanya to the helicopter. And he gave, it gave his life.
All right, I gotta be careful. The dogs can kill you in instant one hit. So
there's another dog. Not so far so good. Helicopters. I don't even know where it is.
Hold up. Shoot. What the fuck? It was obvious. He was a red spy.
That's very good use of what he just said. Oh shit. Is that me? I'm getting reinforcements.
No, that, just get in the helicopter. Did I do it? Destroy all units and structures.
How the hell am I going to do this? I don't even need a construction site?
All right, I have to get an engineer into their construction site here.
This is gonna be fucked up. All right, I need to, we gotta do some group dictates and stuff here.
I want tanks on group one and I want jeeps and people on group two. Group one. Get you guys on
group two. All right, group one goes in first. That's a mammoth tank.
Let's try to take it out before I can do anything. Kill that mammoth tank.
Oh fuck. Kill it. Stay away. Stay away. Stay away. Only group one. They got dogs.
All right, engineer. Get in there. Take over the base and then I'll have a construction site.
If you get an engineer in any building, they take it over. That's not true. That's not true at all.
Oh right, right. You have to damage it. You have to damage it all the way.
Okay, whatever. We lost him. It has to be all the way on this damage. He's fixing it from the inside.
What are you doing? Stop it. Now it's ours. Okay, now I'll fix that. There we go. Now I own this shit.
Okay, I whoops. Okay, whoops. That was a whoops. I didn't capture the war factory. That was a mistake.
It's okay. I'm gonna make a sub pen. Shit, this is bad. What are you doing? Don't destroy your own
fence, you idiot. Don't. Actually, don't. Take out there. Take this up. Dog. Nobody get yourself
killed, please. Sub pens going in here and then I can probably go around. We'll find out. Warfare.
Sub pen. Let's do it. I need an engineer. I wonder if I can make engineers. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Affirmative. Affirmative. All right, let's do a submarine. Wait a minute. Hold on.
Does the water go down here? Stay up here. Stay up here. Don't go down that way. Did I just waste
like a thousand? I think I just wasted a bunch of money. No, it's good. It goes. Yeah, I wasted
a bunch of money. Oh well. Oh well. Barracks. Let's get this ready. Let's do this like down here.
Engineer. Here we go. This stuff is all mine now. All mine. In fact, get everybody out of the way
and blow this up. Sell it. Destroy everything. I will. Did you seriously kill him? No. No.
It didn't hit him? All right, I need to repair you. Come here. How do we repair?
Come here. Did the fucking service depot just exploded? God damn it.
Oh shit. They're coming in. I think I'm gonna lose. I think he's gonna lose. I'm gonna lose. Oh my
God. No. No. When did I last save it? When did I save it? God damn it. When did I save it? Just
load it. I don't care. Okay. Yeah. What a disaster that was. We're not fucking doing that.
Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Affirmative. Let's kill the tank. Get out of there,
Engineer. You seriously can't hit the dog. How bad are you guys? All right, we're good. Now.
Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Kill the dogs. Kill the dogs. Kill the dogs. Kill the dogs.
Don't turn yellow. Don't turn yellow. Don't turn yellow. Good. Why are the engineers on the front
line? I don't know. But I have to get them out quick now. Engineer. Hurry up so I can get this
done. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Let's take the service depot first. Oh my God.
I didn't think it was gonna destroy the whole thing. It did get killed instantly. I thought
I was gonna at least... There was three barrels. Get in there. Stop shooting it. No,
fuck the ore refinery. Give me another barracks. Okay, I need engineers. Give me another barracks.
Capture the snowplow. I can't. Grenade? A Grenader. What's he doing? Get the fuck out of here.
Affirmative. Yes, sir. Knowledge. Get on the... Just defend. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Vehicle. Affirmative.
Give me another barracks. No, that's overkill. Super overkill. Yes, sir.
Stop. Stop. Don't go that far. What are you doing? Okay. Yes, sir. Affirmative.
Don't. Just go attack it. That's bad of you. Oh, yeah. You can repair. Right. Right. Right.
That's instant repair. Yeah, you're right. You're right. Yes, sir. I don't even want this one.
I'm not gonna take it over. I'll just replace it. It's probably cheaper for me to replace this.
Let's get dogs. I'm gonna get like 50 dogs. More. I need money. I need money. I need money. I need
I need money. Don't do that. I don't have refinery. Okay. That's so many dog kennels. So,
plan A is see if I can wrap around this way to take out... Because these Tesla coils,
the flame tower, it's gonna be a shit show. Affirmative. I still have... All right. We got
dogs. Okay. Plan B is go... Oh, they have those things. What is it? The V rockets.
Just go wrap Main Streets the other way. But that's a horrible idea. I'm gonna go...
You know what? The transport actually doesn't sound like such a terrible idea now.
Because I could just put people in them and then bring them down here without...
No, what a mistake that was. All right. This guy's almost dead. Go scout over here. See what's over
here. Go to these so you don't get killed. All right. Go this way. No, no, no, no, no.
I can... I can admit it here. I could just launch a... I'm going for it. He sees me. He sees me. Come
on. Get it done. Get it done. Yes. Mission complete. You did a good job. It's all right.
Here comes the retaliation. That's fine with me. Oh, fuck. Here come the rockets. Bad, bad, bad.
These things kill everything. Kill these before they do anything. Don't get too close.
Back it up. Okay. We're all right. Yes, sir. I gotta take off those fucking Tesla coils.
Of course. Agree. Kill it. Back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back. I don't have the
power to do this. I gotta go around this way. In fact, you know what? Just get over here. Get
this way. Don't activate the Tesla coil. Just wrap around it. Because we're going down. These flame
towers are not as deadly as the Tesla coils. Okay. Good. Good. Good. Get in.
Oh, fuck. All the dogs just died. I didn't even realize they were here.
Where are you going? Just get across the bridge. What the fuck are you going? I think I'm gonna
go all the way around a long way. That should be good. We're good. Why did he explode?
Yes, sir. Stay in the base. These guys are just gonna be painting the ass.
It's all right. These guys are flamethrower troopers. Oh, shit. Yes, sir. All right. Slowly
take them out. Take out their resources. Take out their bullshit. Power. Focus on that first.
Out of money. All right. I did what I wanted to do. More power. Take it out. I got an ore
truck, right? Yes, sir. Get over there. Affirmative. Where's my other? Okay. Good.
You're good. You're good. You're good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Don't leave the base unguarded.
Okay. Good. I got to take out this thing, but I don't want to. These are all grenades. Fuck.
I have no money. How much is 1400 bucks? Give me another tank. Two tanks.
All right. The grenades are actually awesome. They have. Don't run them over.
Okay. Do they have enough power to use the Tesla coil? Hello. What the hell was that?
What's going on? All right. I need to do a test. Ready and waiting. No, don't do that. That's a bad
idea. What happened to the music? The lack of music. Who is being shot at down here? All right.
This is freaking me out. Oh, they have a plane. It's planes. They're just doing these. Oh,
that's not good. That's a pain in the ass. I need a. Give me a silo. No music makes it serious.
It is serious. No, they have power. Oh shit. That's bad. That's very bad. Kill it. Kill it
before it. I get it. We're doing tanks only. I need just only tanks. In fact, where are the
other resources down here? This shit. Get away from me. Oh, you fucking motherfucker. I'm so angry
at that. Only tanks. Tanks only. Let's go. Those anti-infantry things. All right. Keep going.
Another war factory. So this goes faster. This will be worth it. I'm rolling with tanks.
I actually probably can do some. I'm not going to do it, but I probably could take out some more
shit down here. Make a radar dome. I will after the second war factory. You're not even doing
it. You're just being annoying. You're not even doing anything. Bad strategist. Yeah, I know. I'm
pretty bad. So you can build your own rocket trucks. Can I? I don't think I can do that. Can
I do that? Oh no, that's right. This is a, this is Soviet, right? Yeah. Okay. Now that's better.
Let's make a bunch of light tanks. Yes, sir. Acknowledge. Affirmative. Kill it. Okay. Radar
dome. It's a thousand bucks. I need another ore truck. They're almost, they almost have all the
ore. And then they're dead because the only other ore is over here. Okay. I think it's worth,
I think I'm done. Affirmative. I have a lot of tanks. They don't have that. I need to have these
rocket things, but shit. I'm out of resources. Take out this snowplow.
Yes, sir. Kill this thing. Just kill it. Yes, sir. Get the Tesla coils. Get them. Hurry. I'm dead.
I was, I just like aggroed everything. That was to kill one Tesla coil. Um, it's over. I'm dead.
I don't have any money. I have zero dollars now. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. At least the Tesla coil is
gone. So this thing can actually ore. You guys are such a pain in the ass. This is what happens
when you fight mighty Russia. Yes, sir. Kill the harvester. I can't. If I do that, I aggro the whole
camp and they have a rocket guy right here. I'm so screwed. Not so mighty. I would just take the
bridge up, but I need to use this bridge. I'm going to park my guys here. Yes, sir. Or a truck.
Hurry up. I couldn't, I can destroy the bridge, but I don't want to go down here. I'd like to
keep going through here. All right. Make this thing's life a living hell. Cut them off.
Okay. You're harassing me. Stop it.
Kill the bridge. Not yet. I need this bridge. Wait, destroy the bridge and then put transport,
get transports. That's a great idea. Actually. How can you guys suck that much that you can't
shoot that one? Yes, sir. Yeah. Fuck it. Let's go destroy it. Cut off the resources. That's
completely. Can I? Yup. Do it. You ain't got shit now. Do it. Kill it. You're not going to let
this little shit kill you, are you? Okay. I have two ore trucks. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. God damn it. Why didn't it get destroyed? And now here, this thing's going to stay. And now I
have no money. Ah, I'm going to eat up every resource. Why did this bridge not get destroyed?
Let me do my stupid thing. Do I need, I need to know. No, I don't.
Every tank versus every tank. Yes, sir. I got the jump on him. I got the first shot. I win.
I think I might have to restart. I have to restart. I'm not going to have enough money to do this.
I shouldn't have even made this. You know what happened? It's when I destroyed the service depot
that fucking tanks the whole game. I might still, I might be all right.
Actually don't even destroy the bridge. This thing is so fucking annoying. It does not have the toys.
What do they have? Just drown them. All right. Fucked up their resources.
Nice miss idiot. They have so much shit over here.
Now pull it back. Pull it back. Pull it back. Pull it back. Don't do it. Don't do it. I'm just
trying to just lead them out there resources. Take their refinery. They don't have it. That's
all right. They don't have trucks. Here comes a truck and it's dead. Control supply and you
won't have to worry. Control supply. They're not going to have any money left. Yes, sir.
You're really going to let that happen. You destroyed. I needed that. Oh my God.
Let's kill it. Where do you think it's going? You can't go over here. Oh, it has to go all
the way around. Now check this out. I'm going to make turrets. Don't aggro everybody.
Man, I'm so angry right now. The stupid ass V2 rocket blew the bridge up and it fucked up
my whole plan. How is this still alive? What? Yes, sir. Kill it. I have to go in the front
goddamn door. Shit. I got to take out everything. I need. I need. Okay. That thing. Every time I hear
that noise, I get fucking mad. What do I, I need money. They have more than me. They don't have
any money though. So just keep, just bleed them out completely. Can I make Sam sites? Not yet.
Let me make a radar. They're not going to attack. These guys sucks. Imagine getting stabbed. What?
The plane attacks cost them nothing. Okay. Good. Well, here comes another truck that thinks it's
going to actually do anything over here. It's not. Just wait. Okay. V2 rocket. Make one.
All right. Good luck ever having any money ever again.
I think I can actually reach the, yeah, let me, I'm going to get two of these.
I'm going to take out the Tesla coil in one shot.
Yes, sir. These things are just smoking. Okay. Yes, sir. I got two V2 rockets. I got a bunch of tanks.
Not quite ready. I will be very soon. Let's get some infantry. Yes, sir.
Knowledge. Okay. I can't. Okay. Now let's get like 10. I missed the spy. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
All right. Here comes the truck. Good luck. You ain't going to get over here.
Got some infantry. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Okay. All right. I'm, I'm going for it. I'm going to
go for it. We're going to test the coil, kill Tesla coil, save it right here. Say this is something
else. Cause yeah, watch this shit. Yes, sir. Why would you shoot? You're not even shooting
at anything. I need those rockets loaded for when I take out the. Yes, sir. Very well.
These two V2 rockets have to shoot this and kill it. All right. I'm going one more heavy tank. I'm
going to game over. Here it goes. I'm ready for this. V2 rockets. Here we go. Yes, sir.
Oh, what are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you
doing? Why did you not? What? Sorry. We don't even need it. Don't even need it. Take it out.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Here it goes. Here it goes. Here it comes. Here it
comes. Here it comes. Kill this. Just stand off it's okay. Let's go. Go get it. You ain't got any
money motherfucker you can't do shit take out the war factor that's all I care
about who cares everything else fine go get it that's it game over I win all
right I didn't win yet this game is low-key cute yeah I mean sure I don't
let up don't let up power get rid of power make a Sam site I can't even make
it sit no I win I'm so glad I did the bleed him dry tactic an airfield I mean
that got this in the back actually no I don't that's not confirmed silos do it
no I don't even need a silo it took 75 minutes it did not take 75 minutes it
didn't take 75 minutes I've only been screaming for two hours it didn't take
it didn't take no it did not it did not take 75 minutes no it did not I refuse
to believe that it didn't take 75 minutes all right this thing's all that
he's in denial he's serious would you get the money to build this he's in
denial it did not take that long to build this it didn't take that long
get everybody in the right spot okay cool take it off see that's the play
as you sell it before it gets destroyed you'll never take me alive
the Soviet base is dumb and thick I don't know why I read that I don't know why do
I read anything what trucks oh you mean coming yeah let's go
faces huge what a giant-ass face go that's it some of you go this way haha
haha no I have to kill these go over there and deal with that you guys take
now it's the kill kill every unit yuck that was technically a unit Tanya's safe
you can go home did we hit 80 minutes I'm about to go look at the bond I'm
going to my bod right now and I'm gonna see that they're not even fighting back
I thought we got Tanya out wait would Titania not get out so very pretty but
also stubborn wait oh that's me that's the spy they get cut off so quickly I
want to see what happens one hour and 18 minutes no it hasn't but I I read that
was a hard mission but remember that was I had to like infiltrate the base and
escape with Tanya that's also included in that time that was two different
missions together I'm going down excellent work commander the information
recovered has proved invaluable would you not agree this is on normal normal
yes our analysis is almost come no no no sit sit I'm late I apologize
Albert Einstein is not working professor Einstein this is an honor
general Nikos Davros professor let me introduce the commander who rescued you
this is the only clothes that Albert Einstein ever wore apparently this
professor Albert Einstein yes very exciting he's always in this like I'm
in my brown vest and brown jacket these are reconnaissance photos there are no
photos of him see in pajamas professor perhaps you can help us identify the
specifics from what I've had a chance to read this is Stalin's main research
laboratory why would they be they are working on a new kind of defense he
doesn't look like this is it it's just messy bald gray head with mustache is
based on the theory of resonating molecules a sure yes professor but what
does the Iron Curtain do do well by the theorem it appears to make things
invulnerable any vehicle or structure covered with this effect this guy's
idea now will be impervious to harm yes Albert Einstein is dead yes I know
Tesla was experimenting with this kind of professor that is all we need to know
Soviet research on this device cannot be allowed to continue destroy it what else
do we know about this research he's not talking he just runs away put your
personal losses aside from a reveal yes of course besides R&D functions this
base also serves as a waypoint for Soviet submarine actions so it's
heavily populated as far as we can tell the only prototype they have of this
Iron Curtain is located here we do not know if it is operational yet commander
your task is simple get into that base infiltrate their laboratories and
destroy all information and prototypes of this Iron Curtain
this is one of the harder missions I looked up I saw it on the on the
Wikipedia it said this is the mission that's very hard let's make this good
okay go get it going all right before I do anything is there actually an attack
move because I can't seem to get it to work I don't think there is not what is
it no you can just move them where you want and then press G to put them on
area guard okay so it's G you just have to move him somewhere press G there is
no attack move in red alert yeah like that's all I needed now so just be G go
okay in fact you know just stop moving stop moving up get up there start
scouting G how big is this map pretty big take it out don't get in range of
them G don't sneak up there stay back how we doing refinery get it up radar
don't worry don't don't don't attack don't die you idiot sorry no no no no
it's just guarding G scout this way this is a GTA 5 sized map there are some maps
in this game that are huge they can have up to eight players play them that was a
spy plane I got a set to build up I don't have very much room all right power
plant I don't have any room I'm out of room I don't have any room I don't have any room to build
oh shit this is bad okay I need a barracks stay here and guard stay back
you guys up front G oh shit get over moving and shoot what are you doing why
did you do this oh fuck this is very bad I have no room spy oh fuck spy get in
there I need rocket soldiers to prevent that from happening why did I just make
two spies I just panicked it I don't know why I did that these guys over here
all right one of you guys will get this done I have to infiltrate what the iron
curtain good nothing can get over good okay stop that get regular inventory
what do I need to do all the Grenada's bad what do I need to infiltrate I just
keep coming in I don't even build anything I mean what was it I'm dead I
I needed to have turrets and pillboxes from the very beginning otherwise you
guaranteed to lose enemy tech center that's not up there all right I'm dead
it's over that's all so this fucking redo it again retry fishing all right you
got it you got to do you got a pillboxes and turrets eat immediately like to go
hurry that was nice and immediate thank you there are you still here standing
around what are you dumb
yes okay don't hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry move your MCV past the base
because I don't know if they have up here they might kill it before it gets
up there wait let me check that if we go up here and kill this shit let me see
maybe it actually would be better up here
yeah put it right there all right okay let's go before they send anybody over
this has to be quick kill all right deploy gee right here let's put you guys
here yes they fire from that far away barracks I'm gonna put the barracks right
I'm gonna start feeding out people I need infantry and then rocket soldiers
like five infantry let's go let's take these guys this way because they're
recently did you just see useless over here why am I not making buildings
I just made three pillboxes I know I know and it is after they or no no no no no
no no go go just do it now can these guys like volley anything over here two
pillboxes over there you can't just like shoot over it all right what about down
this way turret these guys are useless not but they could be okay I don't want
to spend I need two thousand dollars put the I'm gonna save right in the middle
like right here okay refinery I'm not a power fuck low power get spy into the
tech center yes it's probably down here refinery get it up
you dickhead I gotta spread these guys out because the grenades are gonna kill
them all okay it looks good give me the refinery war factory now look at his
multitasking it's actually pretty awful but you know I'll take the compliment
thank you at least I'm seeing where I'm going just take them both this way
I'm gonna use that thing for good more factories almost done how we doing wish
I put the war fact you're probably up here don't give a chance all right all
right all right all right easy don't go too far out don't go too far out stay
back the pillboxes somebody's gave a bunch of money KXE just mega cheered
gave 5,000 bits and shared rewards with people what was that thank you KXE there's
no message it's just a huge amount of money thank you so much for the fucking
ridiculous money drop what's the sharing what was that thing do all right let's
do light tank what's that noise I just heard the Tesla coil boot up they have
Tesla coils over here do where the fuck is the or are you kidding me dude but
really though where's the or we got to get with the move forward all right a
couple more light tanks and we're gonna take this part over and I'm gonna make
an engineer or two I'm gonna steal some stuff so I can continue to build in fact
let's go hold on hold up hold up hold up hold up hold up tanks what do they got
nothing they get a bunch of junk over here tanks take this out so you don't
get sprayed you're not supposed to be getting far enough away where you don't
get sprayed get in where's my engineer take that radar dome that's ours
god damn it don't no no get no you know I don't want this I don't want this it's
all right wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait stop
stop stop stop stop stop stop stop my uncle's a pro so why do I care about
what your uncle has to say about how I play command and conquer all right where's
my engineer where to go come here all right I got a free radar down they don't
even want to repair it they know what I'm taking it okay now what now I got
all this space i have a new power okay sounds good my uncle knows that guy's uncle and he said
that you suck wait wait you're making this up all right it's up above us yes sir yes sir
affirmative what's down more or reporting let's just check it make sure there's nothing over here
makes it bullshit derma's just figuring out that people lie to him no i know that
don't be new base new operations they cannot come over here now so i can take my time so don't get
this wrong save the game here you're probably wondering what idiot nope naval yard
i mean i'm gonna get three ore trucks and then we'll just power it through
okay gunboat let's get a gun let's get some gun boats no check what's up transport like a spy
we're gonna transport a spy over here
that's what i heard dock is he coming all right get all the way over here because we have to
awaiting ship all right he's waiting we got that shit to deal with over there
all right i'm done i'm dropping a spy off
just go down there for now okay good i'm gonna get another harvester
it's i'm playing a long game here let's see if we can get you over there safely
without you getting attacked by the tesla coil
your uncle says he loves you that's really nice
affirmative affirmative gonna find the tech center affirmative four dollars currently that's
not gonna help me over there tesla coil don't have one over here affirmative i need
it's a submarine shit affirmative how am i gonna drop you off all right i'm going for it if this
thing's gonna die but i'm gonna at least i'll be able to dump them affirmative let him out yes sir
indeed okay holy shit he's almost dead or king and country gets fired into enemy tech center
oh no i didn't even see that dog where's the tech center over here all right whatever okay
uh i mean i can at least i know i can do it i'm gonna get some gun boats and we're uh where's
my money yes sir all right i got three ore trucks give me a silo okay good uh
kill it okay he was an idiot just keep everybody over here until i get this done
ore refinery going up right here and then i'm making another ore truck there'll be two down
here their base is absolutely enormous they don't have for as big as this base is they don't have
a lot of stuff though put that on hold till this is done i'll get a free one for this anyways
reporting after this dude dumps we're taking him down here to dump that acknowledged all right
now you start grabbing it from here and we're gonna put this right here go for it all right i got
one two i got a lot of stuff going on good all right now my i should be being fed money one more
ore truck let's go fucking nuts why are they all coming over here wait what's uh i need power
i would repair this but i don't think i really need to put your face cam on you'll get that
tomorrow um excuse me where are you going with this what's in there uh here comes the spaceship
all right it's v2 rocket okay we're gonna be careful now i need units and shit this is
is
no oh fuck come on i can't even do anything about this i don't i need you not getting that shit for
me where's my other ore truck waiting orders all right i need a service depot and let's start
building some tanks give me another spy and let's get some tanks yes sir why are you going all the
way across here to dump that look at this money rolling into good good that means i can do this
it's the mine layer second war factory i'm doing three war factories and i'm gonna spam uh light
tanks and tanks in fact get over here because the service people heal tanks reporting knowledge
how we look where's my spy yes sir yes sir king and country i wonder if i can go this way
yes sir king and country right there medium tank reporting
to be fair tanks are the solution to everything in this game that's true
yes that is absolutely certain a third war factory i got my money is is it's not empty
although i do have to get these guys in transports so let's hold off on that
watch that money yes sir acknowledged look at how fast this is going to look at how much more it's
it's gonna go twice this fast when i get another one all right what am i missing anything not quite
all right check this out spam medium tanks and i need i'm gonna need like 10 transports
the sack so many now this is no i'm not even close to being done okay another one all right
this is a lot let's do wave one okay wave one is land here and just start taking shit out
i need to enable these can you guys not figure out how to dump let's go
dump it yes sir what are you doing why they don't understand how do you why can you guys not
understand what are you did you miss as it's stuck
dump it all right well just finish it then um what you sneaky little bastard
take it out noob you rushed me you're supposed to wait 15 minutes let's go kidding me i can't
what am i supposed to do brother we're gonna go like oh my god did you guys even get in here
we're gonna go down here oh my god i have so much money all right we're doing light tanks now
it's connects right okay i need like five transports but this music though is just going
all right we want tanks medium tanks get in yes sir how many can fit in one five right one two
three four five get up here yes sir yes sir five in there five in here and then i'm gonna
we need another one we need room don't ignore us what do you mean don't i hear no i hear sounds
all right some of you are just going to stay back here like over here because they keep trying to
come from the other side don't get caught oh no no no no no no no what do i do what do i do what
do i do what do i do what do i do yes sir yes sir piece of shit how many how many do you have
all right just make like five of them all right you guys keep going go we're gonna destroy this
house of coil yes sir pizza shit all right now they're not you can't do shit now
all right let's get some more uh with my spy by getting in there get in there with like three
tanks yes sir reporting yes sir affirmative reporting affirmative where am i where am i
guys at awaiting all right here we go affirmative affirmative awaiting orders you ready awaiting
orders here we go yes sir yes we're good
good yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah take out the test the coil and and run over the dogs while you're
at it kill the dogs take out the kennel where's my where's the spy oh there was a spy in where's
the spy what okay the spy was in wait wait wait wait wait stop stop stop stop stop i guess open
this is by okay good what's that noise did you hear that yes sir affirmative affirmative
please read this please reimagine if germa's real name was harold or something what
why do they need to read that all right tech center is this a tech center is it that's a tech
center right indeed this is a tech center isn't it indeed get in there destroy all units and
structures well great so what's the point all right just kill everything
i need your transports these guys got to go up here okay um everybody hang tight we need
transports to be filled with people so i got eight thousand dollars i have made it to the max that i
can we're gonna do all medium tanks you guys stay down there what happened here
yes sir
i need to have people stick around in these spots like i need to have some tanks down here
all right where are my transports
i need a couple more of those i need like three more of those hello you give me this a gun
done how many minutes so far i don't know it's an rts the missions take a while
why are we counting the amount of time i spend on a mission it's like they're designed to be
played over a long period of time all right we're good look at how many people are here and you're
gonna let them do this eight-year-olds outpace you it's an issue eight-year-olds don't play this
game what eight-year-old do you know that played this game you 20 years ago what are you talking
about you can't even remember what you had for lunch a week or two ago you really think you can
remember like how fast you did mission seven 20 years ago yes sir yes sir reporting yes sir
vehicle reporting acknowledge fill them up yes sir affirmative vehicle reporting yes sir
affirmative it was a ham sandwich no it wasn't yes sir affirmative all right look at the scouts
forward and then there's a lot of people up there yes sir affirmative yes sir how much more space do
we have we need a few more tanks get them in there yes sir yes sir vehicle reporting more i want 20
medium tanks what did he eat if it wasn't a ham sandwich that's it's so easy for me to tell you
that i ate a ham sandwich like oh two years ago what did i eat for lunch last yeah last week i
don't know i'm not on trial here though you are telling me how fast how fast you beat this level
when you played it 10 years ago yes affirmative what the fuck was that what did they just kill
what did they destroy yes sir yes sir yes sir yes sir acknowledge yes sir oh you motherfucker
they're just it's all right where's he going why would you do that that was kind of dumb
i'm just gonna kill both those things all right full full almost full we need one more yes sir
and we're gonna go for it right now i have a ton of tanks scout ahead get up there here we go
by a ton you powered yes sir i'm gonna harass first
try to get uh kill these and then we're gonna go up because they'll just get destroyed
it please read this german please read german read here we go once that b2 rockets dead i
feel safe let's go see you later let the games begin let's go it's war war you can't fuck with
my 20 medium tanks you're not standing chance zero focus the mammoth tank i remember playing
this online and only making mammoth tanks and still losing the game i would have like 40 or 50
mammoth tanks i'm going too far too far too far it's not surprising yeah i would have like 40
mammoth tanks and now they would all slowly be going across the whole map and i would get
flanked on every side and they wouldn't do anything liar you can't remember here comes another
mammoth tank liar liar liar right now somebody's going like this fucking liar fucking liar fucking
liar fucking liar it's just like relax yeah this is game just spread about are they still attacking
my uh my shit all right spread about you guys go down wake up from a coma and discover your
real name is harold why would you why would you want me to do that
harold wake up harold wake up
harold harold it's your mother harold i love you wake up please harold am i missing something
they have a bunch of submarines oh that's great yes sir that's all there is is fucking submarine
i gotta make gun boats and run around in a circle like an asshole where's my
harold go back to sleep the outside world is what imagine being in a coma and dreaming
you're a streamer sucking at command and conquer i'm about to win the mission
you guys act like my eyes are closed and i'm lying face down on the ground
what like i'm i'm doing fine aren't you not doing that can nobody get over here and kill this
yes sir reporting acknowledged they're just stuck over here let's get over there get over there
slowly they'll make it inefficient inefficient inefficient you would have made v2 rockets
and you would have had so much more fun you can't reach actually stay here
you can't make v2 rockets as the ally idiot yes sir yes sir i won i won 48 leadership that's
better than what it was last time 80 minutes yeah they're designed to take time they're not
designed to be done immediately imagine not being a pro at command and conquer
after playing one rts in the last 15 years wow how could you the doctors are seeing your coma
dreams wow this guy sucks at command and conquer it must be because he's in a coma it has to be
why there's no way he could be this terrible yet you see what he did with his naval base the
sitting there with popcorn just watching the screen get this i get this right that's you
hitting me kind of hard get this he he built a naval base and then sold it hey get this
get up ow uh interception of soviet uh communication indicates that their iron
curtain research was set back by espionage excellent work commander i'm getting they're
saying excellent work come communicate is that a word communicate communicate was traced back
to secret soviet base in bornholm investigate possible connection with iron curtain research
capture radar center and destroy sub production capability here we go why is my money getting
burned
who's in here oh shit it's my tank okay let's go
escort him over this is probably a pretty good spot not gonna lie but i'll wait
yeah it's a good spot right now
quick start the production
yes sir new construction options building building building cancel building building
come on hold cancel yes i modded that thing out of again i know you're probably upset
yeah come on come on come on come on come on come on just checking to make sure there's nothing
else over here i can't wait to watch him play this for 80 minutes
all right all right you relax holy shit you almost killed it kill it kill it before it kills my stuff
scout keep the pressure up wait wait wait wait wait important uh i need radar don't
no war factory first just build it keep the pressure up efficient that's what i like
affirmative what oh fuck that's wrong grenades don't let it kill you dude all right
they're just feeding people up here all right good good good good good good good good god
i can blow that up all right you know send somebody to blow that up blow that up now go
just go do it yes sir i'm taking over this radar don't uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
kill that just pull it back that's all right it's all right it's all right it's okay it's okay it's
okay um shit what do i need i need something okay medium tank coming up
squish just kill it kill it kill it what the fuck kill it hang back here
i got a tank what else we got i need money i need the ore ore truck
yes sir i might actually what do you got is there only one tank here
no it's not worth it not worth it i'll get that radar don't for free just need to
i need to buy some time here what's better this or dune i mean this is this is much better
this is a far superior video game at least i think so reposition the refinery i can't
i can't that's all right i i kept the pressure up they can't build anybody else down here i'm
gonna steal that radar dome i'll have double the ore trucks down here which this should last about
it should last just about give or take about 80 minutes okay i'm gonna go for it i need
okay let's wait for one dump i'm gonna do a ranger car and then a couple of infantry i'm gonna go
take this shit right now there's the second dump we should be able to get this actually kind of
glad i did that because what are you doing here what was that for i think that was reinforcements
that is a risky play but i'm gonna go for it you stay back while everyone goes forward we're
gonna take out this guy right here kill you stay like over here
here
take it off we lost we lost it's fine free radar dome let's go
i need more money he's not doing this efficiently okay good don't go that no no no that was a bad
idea that was stupid because i don't know what's up there continue the base now um okay okay okay
ore refinery do it again just just keep it going keep moving forward and put the ore refinery right
here let's get some more like a couple more rangers do you ever click the link i'm i'm busy
at the moment i can't just alt tab and click a link i'm gonna lose the game if this is like a
photoshop of me eating a hot dog i'm gonna turn stream off what is this like 35 minutes into
into my what was this from today what are you talking about not that one what do you mean not
that one do you know how many times people spam links in here and i'm like oh i wonder what that
is and it's just like the mick chicken image that this happens like once every few weeks
explain that one i didn't write that somebody's lying to you oh all right i need stuff i need
shit it's getting uh okay i need rocket soldiers look at all menacing that is what's important i
need power destroy the sub pens i will i promise get out of here with that shit
anti-air all right um you know this music is like driving me nuts i keep i'm like scared good
hey what are you doing over here all right now what do i need what do you guys think uh i probably
need another i'm doing a second order finery yeah no just give me another war truck no
we're fine we're down here i'm gonna take a look
just want to make sure this is safe it's not safe i heard that just hang out over here
how is it even possible okay we're good
yes sir affirmative now um let's get a light tank yes sir in fact put some i gotta make some
infantry there because they're gonna keep doing that shit i'm putting i'm gonna put some down here
they're gonna keep dropping people on me don't go up too far all right what do i have silo make a
silo build close to the ore i just i got scared i couldn't help it all right you stay down here
these guys next to this you can stay here too let's get actually another couple riflemen
because when i destroy the planes they're gonna land here and that'd be bad all right now
we're starting to get some money i'm gonna go pillbox here and turret i feel like this is
a game where you could just build 300 infantry and win oh no way they'll just get run over
they'll just get run over oh this is where i'm gonna aggro fuck it you don't just go for it
all the aggro shit i'm not ready for this i'm not ready for this i'm not ready for this i'm not
ready for this oh fuck i pulled the whole thing i pulled the whole camp no no no no no this is bad
oh it's over i think i'm dead it's over i'm dead sell everything back up back up back up don't
maybe they'll maybe they'll leave me alone there's so many people over here fuck
oh my god they're gonna kill my construction site
all right uh i still have a i'm okay on money but i just got so
fucked it's unbelievable they have planes and shit
here comes the attack i think this is the end here i'm gonna have to redo this one
yeah they're advancing damn it damn it i'm so they have so many more stuff than
ah i'm just gonna board dude how much money did they have like an extra 50 million dollars
yes sir i gotta be quicker and i i gotta get tanks eat war factory immediately
deploy you dumb motherfucker what are you doing just stay here go right here
you can't verbally abuse your units until they do what you want them to do
he's gonna defect to the soviet union what are you talking about
right here or and then we're going barracks immediately quick and then war factory
the second i'm able to yes sir yes sir acknowledged reporting affirmative yes sir
he's defecting he's defecting i'm not defecting how much apm am i at i don't have a thing that's
counting waiting orders yes sir affirmative yes sir knowledge yes sir let them come to you
okay all right yes sir
like when i select you and i say go here and do this why would die why do you just stand still
get over there you're upsetting me you guys you're gonna be you're gonna think i'm a fucking psycho
for this but i'm doing a third ore truck yes sir knowledge i hate this i hate because i don't
they might just attack right now why am i buying silos because this is what you do you bought a
silo here because they've been there too much ore gets in there i actually don't remember what these
do i know like over the silo overflows the when you have too much money right and you get like
the diminishing returns or something what do the silos do i forget you don't have i know but this
for the future is an investment for the future they're useless nothing else you can hold more
credits i know right this is an investment for the future all right done good three war trucks now i
got money rolling in vehicle report knowledge second war factory where's it going with that
shit you attacked me in 15 minutes not fair i'm just gonna spam blight tanks still i have a second
war factor nice air force yes sir affirmative we're good i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine affirmative
the plan's gonna work affirmative affirmative good good yes sir knowledge third no sir okay now
radar dome no no they have a radar dome down there just light tanks i need a barracks
dump it okay now uh another light tank i think i can actually take it now just give me an engineer
give me two engineers no no it's not worth it how much is a uh it's 300 bucks for that just
no just one engineer take the radar dome what does having multiple war factories do having multiple
of anything in the game that makes units will make it go faster so for instance if i have like six
war factories this these will almost instantly produce yes sir anything that produces units will
double here we go one more light tank and i'm going
engineer can stay back let's get this ready now i actually have a bunch of people i fighters now
i have to leave i'm gonna leave a few people behind this should be enough to take this
yes sir yes sir acknowledged all right got it without much of a problem
give me the engineer no air force i'll i'll make an air force just wait
okay more artillery look at my money i'm good silo yes sir what the fuck did you think you were
gonna do with this run them over dick what the fuck are you just letting them do this for
you turned away from him he's shooting you with a machine gun drive over him yes sir
okay now i need what do i need all right we need uh tons of rocket soldiers and i mean like too
many like a like a hilarious amount you're getting mosquitoed okay now you just stay up here and if
anybody falls out then the infantry will kill them yes sir guard guard this shit with your life
yes sir you down it's time to continue building this way yeah fuck off
i'm gonna do shit give me a uh give me an a gun over here you guys are so annoying i'm just gonna
yes sir you stay up here stay up here stay up here what just happened there's no power to this
i need a big power plant all right now you guys you guys just go down here and hang out with
where the ore trucks right okay stay here you guys stay and ready to shoot at the plants
a gun here power plant go all right good good good good good good good good good good good
there was my artillery okay um just start making some tanks yes sir yeah they did look at they're
afraid to send anything over here now what are you doing hurry up blind what what do you mean blind
internal i got this yeah i should be all right affirmative what am i missing uh i'm gonna say
a service depot let's go yes sir affirmative i think it's almost about time to start pushing
forward here they i mean they yes sir look at all these guys that need help we're gonna have a
service depot lined up and yes sir affirmative reporting they can't shoot over here right
second ore refinery is gonna go over here service depot going down here
you know did you have anything in you what yeah okay right here everybody repair one by one
what the fuck was that what are you doing don't shoot each other what are you doing
hey why are you doing that yes sir an idiot's affirmative yes sir affirmative all right we need
to i need okay money is coming in they're coming in they're coming in they're coming in they're
coming in they're coming in all right all right okay i'm gonna move some of you guys down here
front lines all right fuck off let's go bring them all what are you stopping for
why do i have a snowball over here oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no oh no
i don't think this is a good idea he's gonna crush everybody with like no he's gonna
there's so many v2 rockets it's unfair oh no what did i do look at how many v2 rockets they have
all right just buy me some time buy me some time oh my god i didn't think they were all over here
everybody get back
stop pull back pull back pull back pull back
oh they're going where they're going where they're going where they're going i don't
it's okay it's not it's not completely done yet yes sir then they're just they're preparing
yes sir yes sir yes sir reporting reporting get the fuck out of here leave me alone
okay i still have two ore trucks let's take out these guys down here and that's pretty much
their fleet man we're not it's not over yet everything's fine it's gonna get really
hairy here in a second though all this money i don't know you drive over them instantly when
i try to do it they go around the people that i'm trying to have to drive over all right well you
just completely you just fucked yourself here good let him come over here
he will control the money controls the war oh my god okay uh what do i need to do here
i need to just defend just defend well like that was a quadruple although no
i'm not even gonna die over here hold on just come back it's gonna never-endingly
see i just drive around you can you roll your r's yes i can i can roll my r's
all right this is not looking too terrible i just need more money yes sir control the middle zone
here stay here just be a pain in the ass just stay here
all right all right all right all right they're not coming from this way
mine gems it's fat loot all right they've they'll keep feeding people over here but i don't think
it's gonna be enough for them they just i don't know why they keep just dumping people over here
what are they doing all right easy easy this is just run people run them all over
good
don't let them do it kill them fuck off all right uh i need more money i don't have enough money
more money why do you keep just sending these guys over here okay i'm starting to get some
money now i still fucking the motherfuckers are you serious
how does he have all this shit like why do you have all this did this game do the thing
where the computer just has like 30 times more resources than you forever he's they're gonna
destroy my fucking refinery okay stay i need to just have i need to make some money for a little
it's over make some defense what i have 1800 make some defenses what are you talking about
the pill box gets killed in one v2 rocket i have one up before all this guy has to do is drag over
a fucking rocket and it's gone don't scream in front of the kids why are your kids watching me
what's wrong with you you know i said i've said the f word like 30 times every time i say that
you have to turn over and go don't do it don't say that that was just fucking stupid i should
ah yeah what do you get the mute in your hand you're doing a lot of coughing dad or mom
oh it's fun are you all right yeah i just got a chest cold dad do you need a halls i need to
rebuild my shit man no they're never gonna stop sending enemies to me pull them back pull them
back they're just gonna i'm computer i just said five people forever yes sir yes sir yes sir
ready and waiting what are you even doing right now what are you doing
it's like harder to play against the computer than a person
because like the computer does shit like this like what are you doing
you're confusing me the tactic is working yes sir affirmative let's go reporting why are you mad
yes sir yes sir because it's tricky yes sir
acknowledged acknowledged affirmative affirmative yes here he comes two people i just said two
it's like they have you know like the rally flag they just have the rally flag over here
and just making units they're just walking over here yes sir affirmative get out of here
why they have so many more resources than i do what the fuck
i have like three trucks and i can't even make any fucking money all right i'm gonna go
shoot the trucks and then no if i shoot the trucks i aggro the whole camp i need a power plant yeah i
do i don't know where they even get the money to do all this they're not gonna be any more money
left they're fuckers well how do you have all this money you have two or you have two snowplows how
do you have this much money like yes sir shoot yes sir okay what do they even have over here
that guy'd be getting close reporting reporting affirmative what the fuck was that i need some uh
i need some uh i need some uh these guys just to hang out what do i got do i got enough you think
you think i got enough for anything i might be able to move forward let me get awesome
i know i know i know i know that's what i'm doing these guys are just sitting in here
yes sir they're gonna drop people it's all right i got reporting reporting i need like a service
depot or something bad all right i'm almost out of materials though i wonder if this is enough
those things are expensive yes i'm gonna go for it yes sir i have to we're almost out of resources
i'll keep a few people uh some just to defend the base awaiting orders i'm saving her right
that's my favorite meat uh that's that's tough don't go in yet
fish him out fish him out fish him out fish him out fish him out uh i'd probably say uh the
seasoned taco meat is up there somehow somewhere pretty high whales back it up back it up fish
him out fish him up back up just stay here okay they got v2 they got a bunch of shit there we got
yes sir what do we got what am i gonna do a little bit progress that's fine all right stay here
don't move let's get some navy i gotta okay let's get some navy i'm gonna reinforce the cars
navy i'm gonna make a shitload of these give me give me actually two naval yards i'm out of money
where do i get money now where do i get money now oh wait a minute hold on wait wait wait wait i'm
out of money where are they going i have to take something over
oh this is bad then of course you drop them right when i move on the pillbox better kill them
shoot him why are you standing here for he's standing in front of you what are you doing
in the amount of time this motherfucker is going to god i have to what happens when there's no money
what happens when there's no money left uh i think we have to go i have to attack
there's no money but he's not moving he's just waiting for me to die he's out of money too
real life what happened oh wow both of our economies we don't have any money left uh
now what do we do should maybe i think it's time to sign a deal um i this is bad this is
really bad i have to play this right this is my only chance here is going all in this is
what you put all the chips on the table trucks like even the businessmen are at the at the front
lines here okay hold on i can do another one i'm going artillery i'm just going to destroy
is let's break this up with any more artillery over here yes sir all right first line of defense
is the ore truck uh sell the last power plant no sell this
all right first line of defense of the is the guy the yellow shirt guy okay yes sir yeah okay
this is gonna go so badly all right let's get my artillery artillery is gonna be one yes sir
affirmative these are designed to destroy buildings as quick as possible yeah okay yeah okay what are
these i think what are these just people i don't understand what these are all right yes sir at
once infantry is going to be on two all right i want i gotta do this right this actually has
to be done right otherwise it's not gonna happen uh yellow shirt guy and ore trucks you are going
to be actually yeah you'll be four reporting affirmative yeah yes sir okay you guys are
going to be number four we've got yes sir one yes sir one over here two is all the infantry
yes sir reporting two and then all the tanks are going to be three acknowledged waiting order
yes sir acknowledged vehicle reporting fall in yes sir waiting order yes sir vehicle reporting
all right save it here save this as
okay
reporting okay
they're gonna absorb all the fire the ore trucks have a lot of armor all right we have to move
i'm not very good at strategy i'm sorry i'm like kind of panicking why is my heart rate increasing
i my heartbeat is is going like fast i don't know why yes sir i'm like this is nerve-wracking
to me affirmative okay we need to go okay this is it okay okay yes sir vehicle reporting we're
going power plants first okay yes sir this is this is what we're gonna what's gonna happen taking
a power plant with artillery do it don't go up there shoot him
slow yeah okay don't go over there okay they still have power can you reach from here
they still have power check for power yeah okay okay okay
Okay.
Okay, okay.
They're out of power, go!
Get in!
Wait, units one!
Unit two!
Unit three!
Four!
Wait, why do they have power?
Oh, it's got zap.
Take out the power, take out the power, quick,
take out the power.
I did it, it's over.
The Tesla coil is strong, yeah,
it's like the most destructive thing in the whole game.
There's so many.
There really are so many people.
Get rid of that thing.
Ooh, that took out a chunk.
That's a sizable chunk of every person.
We're good.
Really?
That desperate?
You can drive around that thing.
Oh shit!
Why do they have power?
How do they have power for this?
Kill it!
Kill the power!
If you even two tesla coils can kill everybody here.
Take out the subpens.
I think I just did it.
Do they have more subpens?
Go with this.
Okay.
Done.
Where's the last subpen?
No more?
Up here.
What are you doing?
I saw...
I saw my construction yard.
There's no money left anyway.
I think I just did it.
I saw my construction yard.
There's no money left anyway.
I think I can kill them still.
The artillery has a bunch of range.
They just can't go underwater or I'm softlocked.
There's a little bit of money left in their base.
Okay.
Nobody fire yet.
Seriously, nobody fire.
Do not fire.
I need to get all the artillery up here and fire at the exact same time and kill them
on hit.
Destroy subpens.
You idiot.
Don't fire.
Don't.
I just told you not to fire.
Don't fire.
Oh, you're going to ruin this whole thing.
Fire.
Come this way.
I hope this is it.
Affirmative.
What's it?
There's another one over there.
Affirmative.
What is it over there?
Acknowledged.
Affirmative.
Is there another sub over here?
Yes, sir.
Affirmative.
Oh, please tell me I can reach this.
I definitely can with the artillery. There's no way I can't reach that far
I can see you. It's the transport that has to be it, right? Yes. No, this is it
How many more are there
Come on you can get it. You can get it. There's one more. There's a bunch off shore
Oh
No, how many are here? Oh
Are you serious? I can't know I can't build an A because I sold my construction yard
Come on, he's got a visit. They can't be much more than that. What about off the coast over here?
I'll try to go this way
Sell units and make a new yard. I I don't have that. I can't make a new yard
No, this is over
It's over. I actually have to either restart or like put a cheat code in
There's like a pen down here that I can't see
How do I cheat I didn't lose notice I won I did is there yes, sir
How do you was it a tilde shoot the trees?
Enter
Doesn't look like you won they're saying a PC is aquatic
There would be a PC what
Eight what what's aquatic?
I don't have any I don't have an APC
That's not aquatic
No, this thing's not aquatic guys
Sell and build an ore truck. I
Does not have anything to sell
You can't sell units
No, that's it. It's I lose your game. I can't I don't think I can no, I'm actually soft-locked
I can't beat this. I cannot win. Yeah
How far where is this? All right, this is it I'm still good
All right, go in go in right go in just kill everything quick
Go in the Tesla Tesla Tesla Tesla Tesla coil
This is your brain your brain is suffering
Okay, all right, here we go
I still have the naval yard. I'm still everything's good to go. We're gonna build
destroyers, no
gunboats I
Like ten of them. I feel like at least five of them
artillery
artillery and gunboats
I don't need that much artillery. I do need gunboats though. We're gonna do the same thing we did
We're gonna go in and we're gonna attack
We have to do this quickly though. Like for instance, I remember getting angry at this part right here
I got really fucking mad at this part because now I just remember I said this
Oh, I just moved him and all of a sudden now I remember I said that you remember that right?
Here we go
Get him in close and they'll take care of the rest no more gunboats after this
Each of you pick a spot for the love of God and now fire
Okay, stay there
Check it. I don't have any
Sell everything except the construction yard now, I don't do that yet
Let me take care of this first
I'm gonna do this first
Okay, there's no more money
It might be time to do everything except construction yard. I actually agree with you know
But not yet
Save it right before that happens. Oh
This many subs just sitting up here
Why do you have this many why are they over here? Why do you have this many submarines?
Fuck is that?
All right, we have to go in now. We have to go in now
Build why is it not building? Do I need a power plant? Okay, let's see what the fuck's going on here
I need power right now. Oh, wait, what what what what what what what what happened? That's all right. It'll build it'll build eventually. It's fine
Still a goddamn power plant over here
I'm not bringing this
I'm not bringing the ore truck. I can't I need like one power
Keep the ore trucks cuz when I clear this
Kill this use your artillery in range
It's so strong they're insane and I made oh my god, I have to redo it
Just go in who cares
Just get in there
Holy shit, man
No, I have to do a definite knock on boats. I'm just
What's the cheating bullshit that just happened right there? They got to two buildings at the same time
You can have two buildings building at the same time
So what wait? How are you building these this path?
What are you talking about?
That's on that's that's you literally cheating. It's still okay. It's not over yet
It actually might be alright
I have five thousand dollars
The dogs are gonna eat your tank enough. Yeah. No, I just I gotta get rid of their defense, man
All right. I have an idea how much is barracks. I'm gonna steal. I'm gonna steal their water refinery
Just get rid of the Tesla coils and shit and these things
I
What world can I not kill two infantrymen with two fucking tanks
Why do you take so long to kill them? Why?
How are you?
They're gonna rebuild everything. Well, I'm like pushing on my face right now
These aren't even gonna do anything what the hell are these things gonna even do it's I'm fucked again
No, but please build like ten structures in less than a minute
Build an ore refinery. I can't even I I I can only mine over here
You get to double build. What the fuck? All right, I need to
So mad right now, I can't do anything
I can't salvage as I have to start it over again the infinite resource computer
These are like six thousand dollars
This dude has so much money he just put like
$20,000 in submarines just up here in a fucking toy closet. You're not even using them
Waiting orders why so quiet do the exact same thing. I did last time just don't sell the construction site
Like
25 minutes ago in game
There's no more money. It's a there's no more money and he has more
He just has never-ending
regenerating bunny
It's about money
Okay, I guess do the same thing at the last time fucking who cares
I'm just not gonna sell the construction yard and I'm gonna keep one power plant. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
Let's go
Leave the naval yard one power plant construction you had sell everything else and just get a bunch of artillery and go and fucking
Just go just do it go and
Then when they're all dead, I can start mining and then go search for their 50 submarines
All right. Are you ready? Are we ready? Let's go. Okay
Artillery you guys stay here
The shitload of artillery and then I need to see they need to be placed over here
Just keep getting those crumbs on the ground keep a couple guys in defense. All right, I'm gonna keep these three
I'm gonna keep these three guys here. Yeah
Okay, where are my electricity testers?
Where are the guys that are gonna like to lick the inside of the socket to see if there's any electricity?
Yeah, okay
Run is there electricity? Okay. It's still electricity. Okay
Fuck
Artillery
That's good. Now. I just have to move them here
There's still a power plant that's right over here, can I reach yes I can
Electricity tester, please stick your tongue in the socket. Okay, not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Not yet. Wait
Okay, very important job go for it. Okay. Why am I not using planes because I can't build them
Look at that overkill. Look at that overkill. Do you see that fucking overkill? They don't have anything now. He just shot all the Rockets
What just happened? Go get it. They don't have anything. They shot all the Rockets are ready
Okay, it's gonna work this time thank everybody thank the guy that stuck his tongue in the
Okay, okay. No, no, don't go that way. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out
I love it. Now just have at it kill it if you want
You yes, sir. You too
this way
Alright guys, it's time to steal
I'm gonna steal
The air refinery still both their refineries. I'll have to
Why does that matter? All right, good game
Good game
Now bring me an engineer. What are you firing at?
Bring me an engineer
Now I'm gonna build like 30 destroyers
Okay, I need a
Barracks and then I need to wait a minute. Hold on. I need to barracks and then sell
Okay barracks sell my refinery. Oh
Fuck I need power
How much am I gonna sell and then engineer steal their refinery? Why did I do that?
I'm gonna steal their refinery so I can get over here
Why did I do what do you mean? Well, I cuz they have to go a long way and I don't have any money
I can take them. Okay, just watch you'll see you'll get it. You'll get it cuz they're gonna go into deposit to this one
Don't worry. It's all part of the plan here because now I can just build a bunch of destroyers
Let's actually get one queued up. Wait, just make sure I'm not stupid
Are you actually repairing this you've just been in the lobby the whole time stop stop firing
Jesus man
Don't turn you don't turn don't turn
Yeah, okay. We're good. See then this is a much shorter trip
destroyers
Just only destroyers. That's it. Nothing else
I'm actually gonna go down here. Why is this guy so nutty me?
Yes, sir
Yeah, okay
Get this up and yes, sir
More destroyed how many do I need?
like ten
They probably have like one two, three, four five this one. Okay, I'm gonna guess
I'm gonna get six just stuffed up here in his closet
one two, three, four five six
So that means I have to go in with like ten
It takes 80 minutes per level
Yeah
This is a hard game. It's tricky and yeah, okay. Well, I'll level with you here. I will be fair. I
Don't RTS is not like the thing that I'm known for I'm made only I'm basically mostly known for
Beating the last boss in securo on stream in under 60 tries. That's what I'm known for
This is not what I'm known for. So I obviously not gonna be that great
If there's no way I lose I can't lose I actually cannot lose as long as I have
Look at how big this Navy is
I'll be ready
Wait, this guy actually beats the carol. Yep. I really did
All right. Is there anything else I should do?
How about a second naval you had to make this faster?
Yeah, this is plenty of money over here. Come on. Really? Is this too far away?
What what?
Power
Just capture the other refinery
Why did I do that? I why did I do that? I could have put it over
You know i'm known for
I used to do these things called tf2 live gameplay commentaries
And I used to play as certain characters like the spy and I would go for weapons
This has to be enough you know what I mean, seriously, this is
There's so many boats
This if this is not enough
Then I deserve to lose
Affirmative. Yes, sir. Acknowledge. Yes, sir. Let's go. Yes, sir. Affirmative
Acknowledged you have the tactical advantage
Not really
He has submarines. I don't know where they are
I mean they're here, but they could be anywhere
affirmative
guy
Fucking god, how many do you have acknowledged?
I know I have to destroy the sub pens. What do you think?
Acknowledge
All right, let's let's celebrate
Where where are the planes coming from ever cease fire cease fire cease fire cease fire
Cease fire. Where are the planes coming from? Yes, sir. Oh my god. You have so many submarines
Just get in
Where are the planes?
Is there a tiny island that he put a airstrip on
Where is that? You know what? Go look over here. I need to know
There's a tesla coil over here this guy these things are like 2,800 is like $3,000. Why is it over here?
Yes, sir, affirmative
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Acknowledged
Okay, there is no other area on this map
Where's the other airfield?
Affirmative that doesn't make any sense
Got it two hours
Whatever the game just crashed. I got the actual spinning death and the window came up that said
Uh, the program stopped responding but now it came back
Thank god
I uh left
I
Incredible we made it disappear and reappear
But with very little control
We lost some men, but do you have the control problem solved? That is the heart of the chronosphere project
Charging this is where you come in
I wanted you to see this
She understands the importance of your next mission
He still the clonosphere is being tested here
At our research center outside like
The soviets recently learned of its location and have begun bombing it regularly
You must protect this research site
And the scientists working inside get to the base immediately and fortify it
we would evacuate the base but
Months of preparation would be wasted
The buildings and their contents must remain operational until the experiment is complete
So I have to defend against probably waves
But I say it was like
Of a a guns
I don't even have a
All right. This is the base. What is that?
This is the chronosphere. Yes, sir. Okay. All right, go go go go. What am I doing? Go go. I didn't go
What do I need to go go go?
What's where are they attacking get down there I could I could just build it over here though
Get in reporting
That's the definition of a bad idea
It's all right. I made it that was just to get the escort over here. That's it
All right, get in here
Sell the tech center if you need cash, you just need the chronosphere
Not a bad idea. All right, let's get it right is good
All right, let's do it
What do we got over here? I have lots of money tons of money
Shoot it I want you to power power power power power power power power power power
All right, anybody else I could maybe take this over
Vehicles, oh don't you dare?
fuck
Okay, any doubts
I just wrong power plant. I picked the wrong one. Hey agon
He's gonna do this in more than 40 minutes
Don't worry
There's plenty of time
Good. All right. Everything's online. I'm gonna fortify the fuck out of this place
All right, now I just need to survive for 40 minutes
Oh god
I need
kill this
Dude, you got mammoth tanks and shit up here already
Huh? You've already got mammoth tanks
Fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck
What are you guys just standing around for?
All right. Um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, uh
I need a
Oh, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo war factory. Where am I? Okay, just i'm gonna hold on
Put like stack them up
Cornispheres to stay online
One more and i'll be and then i'm safe
Oh fuck this is there's a side that's not there's a side this side there's nothing on it
So there's nothing on it
Um, I didn't even know I didn't even know I didn't know I didn't know I didn't know I actually really didn't even know
Okay. Okay. Okay. Um a war factory right now
Shoot him
Okay
I think we're okay for now
Uh, I need hurry up hurry the fuck up. Hurry the fuck up. Hurry the fuck up. Hurry the fuck up
What's going on? This fucking mammoth tank over here
I didn't do this fast enough
I need fucking units. I need units. I didn't do this. Correct. I might have to stop this over. I didn't realize oh
I did not realize I had to do that. I didn't realize what they were asking me now. I do I know what I realize it now
Uh
My what the fuck
I need another war truck. Oh my god, they're everywhere don't my god
Okay, 27 more minutes where's that ore truck where's that ore truck I need it now hurry hurry up
I might just sell the tech center. That was actually pretty good advice sell tech center if you need, uh stuff
Um, okay here comes another bunch of people
Yes, sir
It's all that orange building in the middle what orange building I can't that's not mine
You mean the chronosphere almost
close
I need the money. They're in the tech center. They're in the tech center
They're in the tech center. Somebody told me to sell the tech center and they were so convincing
So he said if you run out of money sell the tech center and I go to sell the chronosphere
And I even said it twice back to myself over the last 15 minutes
And I have to start over from the very beginning, all right, let me do this differently
Yes, sir. Yes, sir knowledge reporting permanent. I'm just gonna go in fuck it. I'm just gonna go through. I'm
Fucking sad right now
Oh my body hurts my whole body hurts. I fucked it all up my whole I hold on. Oh
I'll be right back. I could be I'm so fucking mad right now. I'll be right back. I gotta pee
Oh, I can't believe it
I'll be right back. I'll be right back. Be right back. Be right back
Uh, you know when you do a pee
And then it's over
And you do a second full pee after that
So I swear I have two blooders
When am I gonna play red alert two? Uh, let's get through alert one first
All right, uh, slow it down
I'm gonna slow it down here
So let's go like this
Check out what i'm gonna do here. I had this epiphany in the bathroom
Let's go you know, i'm gonna acknowledge why do you not don't
Yes, sir
Get over there, why would you just
Why do they do that?
Oh, I want you two to attack this guy. Oh one of them
We'll turn around and go i'm not gonna go over there. Why would I go over there?
Go
All right. All right. Good. Good. Good. Everybody get in there go. I have a lot more people this time
Hurry up, hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry up
Yes, sir, this is a good start
I can't blow this
Full power. It wouldn't need to be repaired anything
Get in there get in there get in there get in there get in there get in there get in there get in there get in there
Get in get in get in get in get in get in get in get in
Oh my god, you slow motherfucker. Why are you going this way?
So texan I can't I was so fucking upset with myself. You have no idea
Put it down here
Hurry up. All right, let's play some placement placement placement placement minds
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Affirmative
What is shooting stop shooting the fucking wall mate
Walk into it
Good go that way go all the way that way good nice idea
How much time time time time? Good. Oh, I haven't been doing any mining
God damn it. It's too stressful
All right. I'm gonna settle down just settle down
Okay, you guys go over here
Okay, i've got everything good power plant again, I need another uh a a gun
Okay, I can settle down now
Where where are you? What's going on here? Who's shooting?
good
Yes, sir, don't let's motherfuck get over here waiting
All right, that's all that's fine. Just stay here
Let them come
I'm serious
How useful selling mines
I need
All right, now fuck these guys, i'm just just run to your death. I don't care forget about the mines they're useless
Okay, okay. All right 32 minutes
I need some tanks. In fact, i'm doing two war factories everybody relax
That means go when I click that means you go
Don't stand there
sell tech center
Don't let it just stay there kill it
That means attack it
Is there a reason why you won't shoot this?
Don't let that thing take off
Okay, good second war factory. Now we start going tank city. Let's go. Yes, sir
Agree, I actually can't believe I have to do this for 30 minutes
They just keep going in different directions, okay, we're fine. Yes
I'm doing four tanks and some people up at the front door
Some people over here and then a few tanks over here you stay this way
Good. This is intense. I have no money either
All right second ore truck
Sell the walls so the trucks can get in
I hope you're right
No, that's not that's a good idea. That's not it's not a bad idea. That's fine. Yes, sir
How are we doing? We got some v2 rockets coming down this way
Fuck it's all right. You need to be over there, too
Seriously, you need to be over here
I gotta cut them off
Okay, they got harassed good get up right in their face
Affirmative good. Okay
Yes, sir. Nice
I think this is time to save the game now
He's so stressed. Yeah, it's a very stressful game. It's super stressful
Sounds good sell the spinning. I don't I don't know what those are. I'm not going to touch those
Sell them i'm not going to sell them may have a tank good actually though those versions very good
25 more minutes and we're done
Let's get another medium tank
I would build more turrets, but I guess maybe i'll put another one over here
Yes, sir. Acknowledge sell your construction yard. Why would I do that?
That sounds like a bad idea
I'll do one more up here in this spot
All right, here it comes here's a block them off block them up. They're gonna come don't even let them get to shore
Don't let them get to shore. Where are they? Where are they?
Yes, sir
Fuck
They get over the rocks are even possible to get over there
You guys so useless just take i'm gonna take them. I think they take a long way every time
A giant circle
Just get up there and fight
So i'm gonna start doing light tanks
No only medium tanks
Let's get some more uh infantry as well
Oh, I don't have money I need more money than this
Where's he going? All right, that's fine. Don't let them stand there
Two minutes takes two minutes takes focus focus one at a time
Oh shit, I can't build any
Pull back fall back to the tech center
What was that?
I've still got plenty of money
How am I doing I got power still
You can come back to the front he's gonna be playing this the whole street
I mean i've been playing for five hours already
This is what we're doing
All right, I knew I should have waited here
Yes, sir, yeah idiot get out of here. Yes, sir. Don't let him get away with that
He's gonna go all the way around be ready
Oh god the v2 rockets are over here
13 minutes reporting I need to stop making stuff
Rocket soldiers build turrets
Yeah, I mean, yes, sir, but they'll they'll get in I only got 10 minutes i'm good
Good probably gonna get really hairy here in a second
I'm just gonna block the port
Where are you going?
Okay
Get out of here with this shit where they come. All right, get ready
Oh you're going for my shit, huh?
All right now i'm gonna do only turrets
I'm gonna pull everybody back
I want at least three turrets on each side. I heard something
Don't let him destroy that I need that nine minutes remain
Yeah, you ain't going in this way that's fine coming this way one mammoth tank
Oh so much to pay attention to
Who's left what else what else what else what else what else we good?
Don't let him in the face they're going for the v2 rockets
Um, um, I don't know over here
Don't do it sounds
Five minutes, that's it
Get over there
Uh, okay another turret
Don't go too far out here
What needs help?
this side does
No on the northern front money. All right, don't bring every single person. Yes, sir pull it back. Yes, sir
That hurt pull it back back back back back back. I need some right side support
All right three minutes I haven't saved it in a long time
This should be in the bag
All right, that
Yes, sir. This is wild
40 minutes defense now
Two minutes remain
I think they it's gonna take too long for them to get over
This should be done
I really just hope I don't have to kill them at the end because that would suck
Kill his ore truck
I have to assume the ore is meaningless because they just it's like waves. So I don't know. I don't think I don't think he even has to
Actually spend money
Plus we got 30 seconds still
This is counting down very fast
Is it kind of not that fast?
So that wasn't 40 minutes then that was like 10 minutes
46 minutes now, I guess it was 46 minutes
Incredible. All right. I feel like i've gone bottom most of the time
Let's go up commander. Is he controlling that? I believe if he may well be at the turning point of this war
The stalin's iron curtain offline and the success of the chronosphere
Victory is finally within our grasp
However, there is still much to be done
One of our spies has confirmed our worst fears
So russians have developed a weapon greater than anything previously known an atomic bomb
Stalin plans to unleash these bombs on several european cities
If he succeeds all they have worked for as a race as allies
To be for naught
this
Is major vladimir korsygin?
One of stalin's key atomic strategists
Intelligence indicates that he has vital information on stalin's plans for this new weapon
Kosygin is appalled by stalin's methods and is ready to defect
apparently
Stalin plans to use his own troops
As sacrificial lambs to draw our forces into a trap once v takes the bait
He drops the bomb you will find Kosygin here in the riha compound
Direct the spy past that compound's defenses to the command center
Once you reach Kosygin get your apcs in and Kosygin out
Okay, build your base get a spy into the command center. Let's do it. Let's see if we can get someone clean and quick
Clean and quick
Scouts you go that way
You go that way
Good luck
Okay
There's very ore on this whole island
Uh
Well, why am I building a refinery then?
No, no, no, no, no, but I should have built right over here though
All right, i'm restarting
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, I this is gonna be clean and quick. This is not clean and quick
You have the game speed termed up this is what yeah, this is the default though, I think isn't it?
I don't think I changed anything
There we go
Turn it up more. No, you can't play this game at like times 10 speed. It's ridiculous
Yeah, there's plenty of uh fluid over here
Plenty of food
I think the default's actually even faster
I think it actually is but it becomes unmanageable when you go so high for instance. Just look
One two, like just watch this
Um, I my brain can't handle this turn it down turn it down. It's actually hurting me
Okay. Good. Uh now i'm gonna do barracks
Let's get a spy
Spy is we need a
Not advanced power first
You're gonna do red alert two some other day
Maybe I mean, I love these games
I didn't play that much red alert two, but I do remember it was fun
Um
You can uh, you deploy your troops in red alert two, right?
You can bunker them down in that big mechanic of the game
Actually, it's pretty huge
You have a spy into the command center. I'm gonna try
You need a naval yard go ahead and build it
They promote that's right. They do promote that's so fun. Yeah, i'll play that
Uh, i'm thinking down here so they're the transports aren't any danger
Let's get them in one see what we can do
War factory jan rittles is the best one. Yes, sir. They're all good
There's not very many commanding conquers that aren't fun
Tiberian sun is fun
All right, i'm just gonna go on a little espionage mission here
Just keep going up
It doesn't seem like i'm very much danger, but i'm gonna tech for a little bit to make sure I don't get killed
Have an assault team going with the spy
The reason why I don't want to do that is because they might just all instantly die
I am going to do three ore trucks together at the same time
Let's do a
Uh, get a surface depot too. I want to tech tech tech tech tech tech
Acknowledge affirmative acknowledge. All right, let's dump them
Acknowledge yes on my way
For king and country i'm gonna get eaten by a dog instantly indeed
For king and country for king and country is a huge map too on my way. All right, let's do
another war factory
Dog dog dog because dog dog dog right next to me
Fuck. Okay. How am I gonna wrap around?
Yes, sir, what's their route? I might have to do some killing here
I might actually have to bring this all team up
Because i'm not sure this wraps around on my way king and country indeed
All right, we have to yeah, we're gonna get this all team up here
Yes, sir, king and country because we're gonna go right at the front door and they ain't gonna move
All right, let's get some uh, you know, come pick these guys up. Why not? I got them right here
You know what i'm doing fourth ore truck, you can't stop me tech tech tech tech
Yes, sir
Yes, sir, let's kill this dog. Yes, sir. Yes, sir
What the fuck is that? Yes, sir. What is that doing?
You did
You could I why did you not shoot the dog get away?
Why did you not shoot the dog?
Click attack dog and it is walking over like shoot it
Hit
Now i'm fucking mad. We're just going we're just going in with hardcore. I'm just going in with a shit load of artillery
I need some anti-air
That shit's going to be coming over here. I'll do two and then another power plant after this
Anyone remember the roblox version? What are you talking?
All right, give me some transports
Should I do another naval yard? Probably
I just want to start. Yes, sir. I want to
Affirmative yes, sir
I want to start just hammering them from far away. So i'm going to bring
All of you get in here how many can fit in here?
And just get some ranger just get some jeeps. Am I having fun? Yeah, I love this game
We're doing artillery and jeeps
And then we yeah, we'll do uh one more with
Uh, I need yeah
rocket soldiers
Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, it's full. It's full. All right, actually two more
Gold here
Where where are all the fart and poop jokes
Um
No, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't i'm trying to move you
Okay, this is artillery this is jeeps I want a couple more
One couple more jeeps
Get in yes, sir
What the fuck
That's so stupid silo
Yes, sir. No, no more rangers reporting now. I need artillery low power my ash low power
And we'll do rocket soldiers
Hold on. I can do transports, right?
APC is a transport vehicle. We're gonna do
50 people in these. I don't know. We'll find out give me a second barracks. I got plenty of money
What's in here reporting?
All right, so this is artillery jeeps artillery
units
Just make a shitload of people you're downloading this right now. I mean, I wouldn't blame me. It's
an awesome game
Faster more
Under the apc four more load them all up
Yes, sir. Get in the boat
You still need some artillery
These guys they're all gonna just fucking die. Aren't they they're all just going to die immediately
No, not if I do this, right?
As long as I don't go over there yet and then I gotta remember the spy has to be filled up, too
Yes, sir agreed reporting
The rocket soldiers are for the helicopters, yes, sir
Yes, sir. Affirmative. How many more we need? Uh, we need two more
One more. No, not a gunboat
Why is the stream silent?
It's not
I think you're you got you need to check your ears. I acknowledge
Why is this thing a silent streamer? All right, I hope this is worth it because this is literally all the money I have
1930 silent stream
Reporting all right. Yes, sir. We're gonna go in a safe spot. Yes, sir. Acknowledge vehicle reporting. This is it
This is it
Okay reporting very well. I don't even have any defense
I'm gonna keep a couple of just little light tanks behind. Yes, sir. All right. It's time
Do not destroy their tech center, right? Yes, sir. Affirmative
Wait, I need oh no, I need I need I know
Oh, no, don't do it. No, i'm gonna wait for me
No
Okay open
I need at least a few dumped out good
Stop going that far
All right now you're fucked
Imagine that many people firing at you at the same time
Yes, sir
All right, bring the apcs back
All right, here we go get them out of here
Vehicle acknowledged. Yes, sir. Agreed vehicle recording. Okay, this is gonna be really really terrible. I think
Reporting acknowledge jeeps up front. Yes, sir. Acknowledge awaiting or affirmative reporting knowledge. Stop don't go that far
Don't go that far jeeps up front. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Affirmative
Jeeps are gonna be one
so
All right. All right larry it works
Okay, you guys all gonna be over here. Yes, sir. Acknowledge you guys will be three
And the infantry is going to be two
One two three, here we go
Let's give it a let's give it a shot
Get rid of the dogs
Oh, oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. That's a lot
Just kill it
Vehicle
There's people in there there's people in here get out open open open open out out out out
Wait, those things attack. I didn't realize
No dogs just gotta get to the tech center
King and country indeed king and country. All right, it's tech center right here for king and country
But that's not that's the command center
Bring him back to the of course. Oh shit. Wait, he's just gonna walk out. Of course move out
He's just gonna walk out. Oh, there's dogs now, of course, of course
Oh
We need to make a distraction
Look at the dogs
Okay, I need this distraction a bat I need a huge distraction
Oh man, this is bad
I need to go over there. How the fuck am I supposed to leave?
Send a decoy spy out to die first
Yes, of course, yes, yes, of course move out move out
You brought him over here
I god damn it. I can't
What the fuck?
I don't even know where where did I save the fucking I don't even know where I saved the game
Wait, did I even save it? I don't even know
What's it called? I don't even know
the
There's like 60 dogs in this base
Oh my fucking god
Acknowledge acknowledge they even have them up in the corner stored. What a pain in the ass
Yes, sir
All right. Well now that I know that the entire base is dogs that now I know
How are you supposed to sneak a spy in there?
That does that doesn't work
The whole base is dogs. How do you get in there?
Do I have to just go just kill everything and then sneak a spy in?
The term sneak doesn't make any sense at that point
Just running and just cause a massacre and then sneak in a spy when there's three buildings left
Just zerg the dogs
Send a hundred spies. I might even just fucking do that
No, they can't even attack. I can't believe I didn't even save it either. Oh, it's so annoying
You cannot win against so weak might no you can't win against
Stealth missions. Yes, sir
He's fully molded. Well, not yet
Who's my favorite classical composer, uh, I don't even know. I don't know any classical composers
Besides like bethoven. I guess bethoven is pretty cool
I mean bethoven
Mozart. I mean, yeah, I don't
I'm not like I don't have bethoven cds in my car
All right, we're going tanks and we're just going we're just
We're going hard
shitload of tanks shitload of light tanks
Just run them over kim says that he's still on the same level
No
Yes, sir
I am not on the same level
No, i'm not at that when kim was watching like an hour ago. I was on the previous mission. This is a different mission
By the way, just in case anyone's curious i'm doing six ore trucks
And then i'm gonna save the damn game
Because nobody's attacking nobody attacks
So I may as well just spam ore trucks and just have 20 million bajillion dollars
Yes, sir, that's it last one. Yes, sir, they're gonna start running into each other
Okay, get the radar dome I mean I want to build another construction site
I almost just built another one. That would have been really stupid
And guess what i'm doing a third war factory and then we're i'm going to send
50 tanks up here
I'm going to be a cycle about this
Yes
Dump dump dump dump dump dump. You wouldn't do 50 ore trucks, would you?
I probably would
But i'd like to beat this level
I'd like to complete this
It'd be good
Remember this level is unbeatable without the fursuit
Oh shit, where do I get that?
All right, that's enough
Look at these medium tanks. They're just so they're just so spammable
One more silo
All right, I don't want to just only I gotta do this again, too. This is uh
I gotta build a naval yard
Oh, that sucks
You promised to eat a ghost pepper. What happened? I already did it. I ate it
It was gross
Yes, it was gross
No one's coming over here
transports
Let's get a barracks up here
I'm almost ready
Just chewing through money
Yes, sir affirmative start stacking them stack them up. I can't really spend the money on it here. Yes, sir
If I get attacked and they kill uh, 10 medium tanks i'm gonna be very very upset
Does this fall still space cry cry cry cry cry
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Why are you guys so vicious?
Yes, sir
All right, move somebody go dump
Full full full this one's not full. All right, that's 15 medium tanks
We're going 20
And i'm just gonna get them over there
with
um
Just some I don't know. Am I doing a 24-hour stream?
No, i'll probably finish up soon here. Yes, sir affirmative and then we're streaming the game boards tomorrow
All right. I need
I need apcs
Just a couple because i'm i'm doing 10
And these things fire affirmative one two, three, five one
two
Five, okay
Start filling them up
Yes, sir. Very well ready and agreed. Yes, sir
Waiting orders. Yes, sir. Affirmative acknowledge reporting. All right, I need a couple more tanks
Yes, sir
Uh, i'm gonna I gotta mix it up a little bit though. Let's do
Um
Let's do some light rangers
Stop counting up. I stop counting
You're in trouble. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. At once. Yes, sir
reporting affirmative
I'm saving it here
I don't even know what this one's called. This game is so much fun though waiting orders. It really is
Yes, sir. Affirmative. So we got two, uh seas will
Like that and then a couple of light tanks sounds good to be who cares but just going into fucking
We're trying to slot up
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Affirmative
reporting acknowledged
Hands hurt. Yes, sir. Waiting orders. There's a lot of clicking involved. I'm getting like my fingers hurt
Yes, sir. That's enough
Save the game and let's move on
All right
I'm gonna move them away
I'm not going right in the front door
I want to see if I can wrap around if I can then I can if I can't then I can't
Right, but at least i'm trying
Affirmative because if I can come down I would just launch an artillery into like the dog pen
Oh, this is bad
Can I get through?
Okay, I have to go the other way
Yeah, you got to go the other way
This is seriously the only way I can go
Acknowledged. Yes, sir. Acknowledged. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir
Affirmative affirmative knowledge hallmark Yep
Yes, sir. Acknowledged affirmative
Affirmative vehicle reporting affirmative
dickhead, yes, sir
Waiting for yes, sir. Yes, sir
Awaiting awaiting answer. Yes, sir. Acknowledged vehicle notion reporting acknowledged. Yes, sir
Yes, sir. All right
keep everybody over here all right kill it now these guys are gonna move back down here
have they done they got all the ore they got all the ore there's no more ore left on this map
now what are they gonna do i don't know what are they gonna do i don't know um okay i need
spies it's time to at least attempt yes sir get a jeep over there get a spy into the command
center and pull out the guy and then remove guy all right i'm gonna pull everybody how the
fuck am i supposed to get by this if i'm supposed to sneak by this no they'll see you these guys
will just see you do it okay save it here just kill the dogs and you're good kind of but then
i gotta get them out too run run run okay all right hello who's there
oh they're gonna drop bombs over here move stuff stuff stuff don't panic okay just slowly
just have a defense right here they gotta come to you spies
yes sir for king and country commander for king and country yes sir
knowledge acknowledged
get over there and just start firing
irritating yes sir for king and country indeed king and country yes sir get in affirmative
affirmative reporting knowledge yes sir affirmative yes sir kill it
what do you think you're going what's in there what's in there kill it what's in there kill it
fuck go what in the ever-living fuck are you doing how many times do i have to click on that
before you attack what are you doing yes sir affirmative what the fuck are you standing for
yes whatever i don't know what you want me to do is shoot him i don't know what that is
let's go king and country indeed what is going on yes you are what was the goal here
to just be annoying that's all it was
okay so i just have to get in there and then just wait to eat this there's a plan here
indeed my plan is indeed spread them out indeed so here we go on my way king and
my way yes sir indeed sir on my way for king and country yes sir indeed yes sir on my way
on my way for king and country yes sir
go go go go go get out get out get out of here
No, don't run back
Into the transport quick
Okay, we did it of course, okay
Get it. Okay. Get the fuck out of here. Where's the helicopter? Where's the helicopter? Where's the helicopter? Where's it?
How do I get him out of here?
How do I leave what is north? No, it's not
What is that? Oh?
Oh, I did it 40 minutes not 80 I didn't have to restart though
That's so funny
All right, how we doing? Let's see. What's the next mission look like see if we're gonna do it
how many
atomic bombs
does Stalin possess
At least four to kill a ton warheads are in production
But there is much even I do not know much. We are nice for Stalin's speeches coming on
Stalin's
Correct
Think of a better word to describe
For margin he is mad. How can he do this?
Explain to see what are you talking about?
He announced he is telling everyone he's threatening to destroy the world his missiles are ready
He's preparing to launch. Is this possible the week ago? No, but now who knows this does not sound like a
Bluff
Even now a great purge tears through the Kremlin your allied force becomes too powerful in his fury
Stalin kills his own people
More death more dishonor
The Russians are manufacturing missiles at this site
This factory is main Stalin. We call it Johnny of a sod Nicky the dark horseman
You thought this is an ad for the tank games destroy it. Oh the IOS game
scorched earth
Establish a base first then move in on the command center get the spy inside
No, I suppose my realized launch capability get spies in the base anymore. This is our neutralized
destroys the facility
everything
scorched earth
You can't say sneak a guy in and then
Destroy all Soviet units and structures awaiting orders. I'm gonna give this one attempt
One attempt and then I'm gonna call it night
and then we're gonna get the game award stream ready tomorrow and
The explain how the fuck the king stream is gonna work. Let's set up shop right here
Is he addicted yes, but that's besides the point
If you don't know what I'm talking about tune in tomorrow I will go over a full explanation of how the game is going to work
Let's just kind of take a look while we build this up. Where's the
Oh
You go this way. Where's the ore refinery capabilities the golden brown?
Or we're over here
Diamonds are over here. Whatever the hell these are. These are worth more money
I need to make sure I'm not going into danger
Till that dog kill that dog
Take a look
Oh shit, you're already down here. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait go back down
Come on back
Jams how much gems are worth a shitload, huh?
Okay, destroy all server units and structures
You got it one attempt here. That's it. You get it
Planets by what?
Affirmative check the right
Yeah, what the hell are you guys talking about?
Just want to get my idea of a sort of a little convoy kill it
Kill that whatever
Pick it up somebody get it. That was worth it. That was a bunch of money
Not or I want to or truck
I'm going a little too far here
This ain't smart I'll take some of these idiots to do a retaliation zone
Now pull back pull it back pull it back pull it back. Don't go too far in dude
Stay right here. There's plenty or I'm gonna go go or up there
This is actually I don't like this dangerous to me, but whatever a third one one more. Yes, sir
Feels good man scouting. It's right. That's how we do it. That's how we do it
Send a spy up there. I've killed a lot of dogs tech center helipad now. I can make some actual shit
Easy on the easy easy easy
What's up there? Take a look
Tag I need a service depot. I don't see any dogs
Although I do need some of you guys for the flying helicopters that are you gonna do that exact damn thing?
Let's get like five never mind this dog there
He's hunting dogs on purpose. I'm going tech center
Fuck I'm addicted to the game. I knew this is gonna happen
It's getting late, too
Cuz I had to start late because the minecraft server thing. All right. All right, this last mission and I'm going
Then then we're done
Good spend that money tech center and I'm gonna do my own shit. I'm gonna do
You know what? I think I'm gonna do I'm gonna get planes and shit
GPS satellite, what does that do? What's the GPS satellite do? I don't know. I forget it's a full map reveal
Should I get it? How do I get it?
All right, I'm going I'm gonna do no, I don't know. Yeah. Okay. I'm gonna do helicopters
We're gonna do like a bunch of helipads up here
That's the cooldown right right right I see you mean nothing too funky right now
I'm gonna go up my helipads are gonna be this way
long bow
Service center you get one for free. Oh, that's sick. All right anymore
You're gonna start doing his crotch. We'll get we're getting into money territory here
Another war truck. No, no, no, no, no, no, no slow down. I gotta start I gotta heal some of these
Don't fucking
Can they not get it through this
Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir
So long to move
Oh my fucking god. Why is it right when I put this shit down?
Oh now we're gonna attack you from the top. You just put an important structure down now
We're here at the top where you put that down right when you put it
Hey, we haven't attacked in eight minutes by the way. Hi
Fuck off with this
Oh here we're just here where you aren't this thing's so expensive
And now I have an extra one just go fly wherever just go on just scout for me
All right. Can I can I do it in the service center?
Acknowledged. Oh, let me put this down
Look you put down an important structure three sent three people
Reporting just going to acknowledge. This is land in front of them
I have sam sites
This actually is a pretty bad idea
Zerg them now. No, i'm i'm dead if I do that awaiting orders. Yes, sir agreed. Why are you all so stupid?
It's so if you're here and I click here, why don't you just go this way? You're making me angry
Why would you go all the way around here to go from here to here?
Guys, yes, sir. Why are you doing that?
What's that?
Oh, that's my satellite thought it was a nuke. Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me here. Okay
Reporting knowledge. Yeah, I got all that shit for free by the way. I'll do one more
Let's see if this play if this is gonna play out sam site over there
sam site over there
Damn, I don't
Over this way. There's no sam site this way. I can start I can take out some of this shit over here
I'm just doing helicopter run
Vehicle reporting. All right, let's go for it
I'm gonna say where's the sam site sam site is up there
So we're gonna go wrap around this way
We're gonna go this way fly over here
And we're gonna fucking bomb right here
No sam sites this way
See you later. Motherfucker
strategic bombing
Don't go that way fly down here
Take out the bridge
Oh
Fucking coming over it's like five people. Why didn't I have anybody over here?
Old woman
It would have been so good it would have been so good
I sent you five regular guys over here. Oh so fucking bad
I'm so mad right now
I'm actually not happy like this sucks
That was like $15,000 worth of shit
No, nobody else do anything
We're gonna have to refill one at a time. Just put it right in the middle of the goddamn base, please
All right, get off
It's somebody else's turn
My brother used to do this one like that and I just copied him from 15 20 years ago
Yes, sir. Now i'm angry
Now you fucked it up because now now i'm going i'm going up here again
What happened? Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Acknowledged
Someone shoot this guy
Why
Awaiting
Am I going crazy or are they just not firing
Shoot him
Have I lost my fucking mind?
What are you doing down here? Yes, sir. Fuck your base acknowledged i'm taking the whole damn thing out
Yeah, good luck
Don't fly over the same site
Come back come back
Oh my chest do I lose anybody
I was like in one of these helicopters
All right, i'm think i'm done. I think i'm done. I've had enough
This game is really fun. It's just stressful. Yes, sir. All right, it's somebody else's turn
Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Acknowledge refill
All right. What else is important?
I think I could take out a sam site as long as I kill a sam site just start going for power
Wait, where's the tech center?
Okay, is there a dog up here?
Uh, no dog
See if I can end this dog right here kill dog with helicopters. Yes, sir. Take out their ore trucks
Say a letter
Come on bugs go back affirmative took every shot and now here they come this is where it ends
This is the end here
Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir
I'm gonna exit the game just because I know it's gonna happen. Yes, sir. Affirmative. Yes, sir. Acknowledge
Yes, sir. All right, I bring all my money on helicopters
I did the wrong strategy
I got too I I got over I got I got over mad tapped
I just have to go kill something
All right, i'm gonna go for
Sam, sorry
everybody go
Moving to kills one if I just just just take it out so I can keep going in here kill kill kill kill kill
All right, start to taking out power plants
Sam site get the other
Kill the dogs
Instantly put it on the same side
We're good. Okay
Now I just need to get him in there somehow. How do I I gotta break into this door? All right shoot
Why don't I hear tank shots?
It's musical chairs. So you gotta find a way on
It's over. I it's okay. I know the game's already over
Spy got run over whatever
Never give up
All right, it's not completely over yet. It will be really soon
I need to kill
This dog over there's one dog somewhere over here. No, there's not so just straight up kill this dog
Get into the base
There's no other dogs
Go right into the command center and the tech center two spies. There are no dogs. There's dog right there. Who cares kill it
Check this out
Don't go that way the same sites
kill
Was this dog over here? There's a dog over here somewhere
Where's the dog?
No, there isn't a dog
Just take out the the base thing here just take it out if I can get a spy in
That's all I need
Good. This should be it
If this isn't it then I quit
I have as many power plants as I have entire base
Save the game. No, this is this is a shit show. I made like
I made like 12 helicopters. This is not a real game
There's a dog right there. I can take that dog. There's a dog right there, too. I take the dogs out
Yes, sir acknowledge kill that dog and then kill that dog
Yes, sir
Acknowledged acknowledged target
Anymore I don't see anymore up here
Oh no, he's going for our dogs
Good to go. Why would you land over here? Oh this game?
Super hard and super into it
So I have to get a dog in the was it the tech center or the command center
It's in here, isn't it?
Is it the command center or the tech center? I don't remember
Oh my god
I just saw what was that?
Commander as you are well aware. Stalin has launched four atomic missiles
The only way to stop them now is to get into the command center
Each missile is controlled by a launch terminal
Deactivate all the launch terminals and stop those missiles
It's a sad day today, oh that sucks that sucks
Okay
Fire at the ground over here because this there's obviously mines
activate the mines
Get in there
You need to capture that with an engineer
dude
if you
Go
Wait a minute if you go just up this way
Can I cross this?
Because you could just take this up
Can I'm this is i'm testing to see I don't think I can pass
I don't even have any units anyways
What through the trees?
Can you like burn the trees down or something?
No, this was a shithead run anyways
No, you can't can you from here maybe it's just a little moat
Maybe I can cross it
Damn well, that was fun. That was a fun game
it's uh
red alert
It is as fun as I remember
Last time I played it. I was probably 16
It's very very good
last year
So am I going to beat it tomorrow?
Uh, I don't know
I don't know about that
There's too much to do tomorrow. I think
Play red alert 2 before the game awards. I cannot do that
Before the game awards i'm going to be in the minecraft server
So because that is really going hard
And we need to get it set up for the weekend
All right, that's it
I'll see you guys tomorrow for the game awards
You can beat this
We'll we'll see how much time is left. How long are the game awards? What are they a few hours two three four hours?
Something like that probably a couple hours two three hours
Well, it's probably going to take
It'll take probably at least 30 to 40 minutes to really slowly go over everything that's going to happen with the minecraft server
So after that maybe i'll just you know, try to beat it
I don't know. I can't make any guarantees that i'm gonna play it again today tomorrow
This mission has a special failure cutscene
Does it?
Yes, sir. Okay
The guy's on red alert what the hell is going on
Damn
Well, that was a
that was
Red alert two is the best red alert. They're all good. They're all of them are good
All right. One last thing before we go
Y'all start here wait what i'm behind i'm behind i'm behind i'm behind
Make fake ones. I wanted to play skirmish just because it's so much fun. All right, just start going check killing
I'm just make barracks just don't even make or who cares
Get out of here with that shit
This is a mess unit lost unit unit unit lost unit lost unit lost unit lost
That teaming up on me wait what
What why were they teaming up on me?
No bases
50 units each eight players
Good luck focus one tank at a time
Oh shit here comes teal
Don't spread out so thin
Don't go up there. Don't go up there. Let's kill each other. Let's kill each other. Not you
Yes, sir ready and waiting is there a reason why they're not fighting each other
Why is he yes sir affirmative affirmative they know you're human affirmative
Well, this is unfair
Uh, there's orange
Hey, it's it's a war germany. There is no fair
Well, i've refused to participate
All right, your apm is too low
It doesn't matter as long as you have fun. It doesn't matter
All right, i'll see you guys tomorrow
For the game awards and then we'll talk about minecraft
A lot to talk about it should be a ton of fun. I am so excited for this stream. You have no idea
That was red alert
I may or may not play this tomorrow
After we go over minecraft. I don't know it depends on what's going on
I might have to believe and get some stuff situated with the server
It's going to be the next few days are going to be a little messy
So we'll see but I will see you tomorrow for the game awards at least
Have a great night
We'll do the bits
And the subs, of course as always see you tomorrow for the game awards get your bingo cards ready
I mean i'm not making one but just get them ready
Let's go back. I can't believe i've played that for almost seven hours
I did get addicted. It's it's it's hard but it's addicting and it's fun. It's good
Hey peaceful hailey
Thanks for the 250 say hey germa tomorrow's my birthday. I'm turning 22. Have a birthday
Kind of weird to say I know it's not old but I know that i'm getting to that age where I don't think I should be
Fucking around and doing nothing with myself
You in this community has made me want to do better things for myself
Anyways, I hope you had a good stream. Good night
Well, first of all, happy birthday
And second of all you got a lot of time. Don't worry
22 is really not that old. It's not
If you're in your early 20s
You got
You got plenty of time. I I didn't know what the hell I was gonna do till I was like 27
And even then I still didn't know what the hell I was doing
And even now i'm still a kid now. I'm i'm not even grown up yet
I got and also I got news for everybody yet. Nobody knows what the fuck they're doing
It's just a series of people just kind of doing the best they can
Even when you get to an age you're like, all right, I think I figured it out
It's a never-ending process
Don't worry about that
Happy birthday. Peaceful. Haley. Thanks for the 250 at my starfish. Thanks to the five community subs
I was very very focused today because I did this was just I play the game stream
I was remembering and it's being very very nostalgic and I was getting uh, I was being very nostalgic at how angry I would get
When I was 15
And I would just make the same unit and send them all to death and then I would smash my keyboard
Um went through a lot of keyboards when I was like 14
The thing they were just amazon basics 12 dollar keyboards. That's not canon. I know that that actually isn't canon
Now today was canon no just because last week was non-canon that that that doesn't bleed into the
And plus I retroactively made two streams from last week canon. Just wait, we're gonna play nancy drew again next week. Anyways
I'm gonna do the nancy drew like once a week for the next like
Year until people are so sick of it
No, but thank you for the five subs at the starfish and atma gives 500 bits here right after that
They said do you ever play red alert 2?
Yep, that's also a fantastic game
Slight frustrations aside with red alert. It's still that holds up pretty well
It's that still holds up
20 fucking years later
I can't imagine how red alert 2 holds up. But yes, I did play most of the time I played was red alert 1
Red alert 2 I was kind of
I didn't get I look I didn't get it. I never got it
Especially when I was younger. I didn't get it
You know when you play dark souls for the first time ever
Uh when dark souls first came out or demon souls first came out and nobody like understood what the fuck was going on
You just don't get it
Go watch my first dark souls video. That's a person that just doesn't understand what the game even is supposed to be
That's kind of how I was with rtss
I just didn't I just made units and fight I didn't because there's no strategy and I still don't even know what i'm doing
Point is it's a never-ending process trying to figure out, you know what to do
But yeah, I do I do love the old rts games
Warcraft 3 is another one that I was really into most of the custom games though
I loved the tower defense games people would be really angry people would talk shit to me all the time though
Because I was so stupid and so bad
Remember the tower defense games custom games where you had to work together and build towers together and make
the big tubes together so the monsters will actually have a
trail to go on
I would just do wrong stuff and people would be like, what are you doing? You're an idiot
Why are you building that there stop doing that you fucked up the whole line
And I'd be like, I don't I don't know. I just I wanted to shoot a guy
I loved tower defense
I there's one game mode in particular
In warcraft 3 that I was obsessed with
It was hero line war
And I am shocked
that people have
put so much time and energy and effort
into
the
defense of the ancient stuff
And not the hero line war stuff
Because you made money and then had to send units to the other team's
line
And you made money by killing other heroes that came over to fight you or by killing monsters and you could keep
uh
You could send crazy crazy expensive monsters if you wanted to and they had to deal with them. It was two teams
hero line war was seriously the the best custom game mode and
Nobody gave a shit
I would I did I did I went back in warcraft 3 and even starcraft
dota all-stars dota all-stars dota all-stars
I would refresh the custom game list over and over again because I just didn't want to play dota and you would get that one
Custom game lobby that was open that wasn't dota all-stars and you're like, holy shit. Thank god. Somebody's playing something else
It was so much fun. There were a ton of custom games as well. I hope they bring that shit back
It was an awesome thing to do
But you know, I could go off for a million years here
Trident jacks. Thanks for the 500 bits have been really sick these past few days
Watching your videos has helped me through some of the rougher nights
much love and appreciation
Thank you trident. Sorry to hear you're not feeling well get well soon. Hopefully you get better soon stream, uh reforged
That's a plan
I'm sure it'll be really really active. So i'll definitely do it
Juno upsetto. Thanks for the five community subs. I think I missed it. Thank you
With five gifted subs
Should you go back to the fridge to get one more pickle? Uh, that depends how many pickles have you already had?
I'd like to know tell me i'm good. I i bob
How many pickles one? Oh go get two
Yeah, that's fine
Uh, but thank you juno upset over the five community subs. Thank you
Goop snatch for the uh, that's not even the right amount of i've just didn't mean right say that I finally watched Aladdin though. It was good
Yeah, it is. It's a really good movie
Aladdin's awesome the original laden. I'm glad you got to watch it
Marvosh Magali, thanks for the 250. I love seeing you play these boomer games. I mean old gems
Any plan to play some old?
Mame games. What is main meme?
What is that?
And they say is it against tos?
uh
arcade games
oh
There are actually a lot that would be fun to play
I mean it's for some of most of the ones that you can't even
Play anymore would be fine
But yeah, I've thought about arcade cabinet type games before
The issue is a lot of the arcade
Cabinets that I would want to play came out on like another console like dream caster or something
But the ones that didn't it would be fun
It's been up to set it up correctly
C4g, thanks for the 250 germa used to never do war crimes pepe hands
What are you talking about? Demonic cucumber. Thanks for the 250
Imagine saying let's rock
Lul this meme was made by i'm there gang
Thank you for the 250
Thank you. Uh shalash ashka for the
250 bits
Thanks for making me feel better. You're a beautiful man with an even better heart germa heart
And then a tal groovy a tal rad
Thank you
Glad you're feeling better
Thanks for the 250 shalashka
Thank you so much
Winsok, thanks for the thousand bits
Ten dollars here. Thank you. Consider this an apology for making you say dummy thick
Well, I said it twice
The second time, uh, it was ten dollars
Thank you for the thousand bits
Appreciate it
Flare pancake. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey germa. I was gonna send a bit message once I hit my two years subscription milestone
But it looks like i've put it off for a month
I guess final projects aren't the only thing I procrastinate
Kind of be looking forward to the fuck the king minecraft stream hoping to participate in that maybe
I hope so
There's going to be some very strict rules on the server
That have to be in place there's a ton of stuff back end that is being done
To make this go as smoothly as possible. Although there's I mean, it's this whole thing is a beta. Anyways, it's just an experiment
Tease us about it
Just wait for tomorrow tomorrow. I'm gonna go over the whole thing tomorrow
How many people at once it is a I think it's a
500 plus server
So i'm not sure it's the exact number but it's at least 500 people
That can be in the server at the same time and there's a lot of things that have to go into place to make it
So it works
Not enough
Once you cross like three or four hundred people in the same spot
You start to run into
Uh, not possible anymore
We'll see
It should be a lot of fun. We're gonna break the server
I don't think you will
There's a lot of stuff that's being done to help with that. So don't worry
I am, uh
Putting the necessary resources in
Let's just put it this way. I'm not
I'm not running this on like a pentium i5 in my basement
There's uh, there's a lot of legit hardware here
Because it has to be
But we'll talk about it tomorrow
I'll have way more to tell you tomorrow
Internet Jorge
Or internet george. Thanks for the 1500 bits. Please wake up harold. Your family misses you. We all love you
Please wake up. I get one of these
I get one of these
Every other stream I think I I think I do get the please wake up jeremy. We miss you, please
At least once a week right once or twice a week
How fucked up would it be if this was real and shit and my brain was making this whole thing up?
Can you imagine that?
He's so close
None of this is real. It's not but thank you for the 15 dollars. That's a lot of bits
Appreciate it. I hopefully I'll wake up
Uh hypo cube. Thanks for the 1500 bits 15 dollars a lot of uh more than 10 dollars here in a row. Thank you guys
15 bucks from hypo cube
Glad you got around to playing this goofy delight of a game
I'm so happy when you squealed with excitement yesterday about playing this on stream
This dream brought back so many good memories of being a kid working my way around rts's and I wanted to thank you for it
You should play too sometime. I hear the fmv gets even better
Yeah, I love this game
that really is great, you know what my favorite part about this game is
the
Construction site opening that's my favorite part and it still holds up
But thank you for the 1500 bits
I will probably end up playing too at some point
Dark soul. Thanks for the 250. Hi. Wow. Great stream. Where do you stand on the twerking fiasco?
What I really didn't know so I can read so I can refund these bits if you disagree with me
I don't know what I don't know what this is and I don't know what it's working for you. I don't know what a twerking fiasco is
Is uh, I don't know. I don't know who that is
I don't even know that I don't know what that is
I've never heard that name before. I don't know what that is. I don't want I don't know
I don't twerk. I don't know but I don't care about twerking twerking. I don't care
There you go. There's my stance
Apple ship. Thanks for the 250. Hey, do you have a set date for the next community content night?
Probably not till january
Probably the first week of january second week of january
Just because there's a I there's a lot going on
there is
I still have to do
I want to get in front of the green screen and that's I have to wait a little bit
I kind of planned this all and then it all fucked up because of my illness
but
I
The new year's eve stream with the award ceremony
The green screens that has to happen first the minecraft has to happen first
There's a lot going on in the next like four weeks
so and I really really wanted to get the
green screen footage for the next community content night, but
If it can't happen, I can't happen. It'll be for the next one after january
And I the rumble. I've still had them. I'm still making the rumble
That's still gonna happen. Uh, this is gonna have to be spread out a little further than I thought there's a lot planned
No set date for it though. Uh, let's get the
Let's get the subs going
What do you say?
subs
Roll those credits
Thanks all of you all of the subs all the subs all the subs if you're a community subs
If you're a regular subs if you are a new subs if you are a tier one subs if you're a tier two subs
If you're a tier three subs
You guys are awesome stream the awards. That's what we're doing tomorrow. That's what we're doing tomorrow
Much love to all you. Thanks for continuing to support this channel
Thank you. What about tier four? There is no tier four. Are you gonna do the stream awards?
Oh, yeah, that's happening on new. That's a that's new year's eve
in fact the day or so
after the minecraft stream
After the minecraft stream is happening on the 15th
so
as of like the 16th or 17th
This is going to be the new channel is going to open up in the discord
And we're going to start to talk about nominations
And thankfully there's enough time because remember last year it was like a
Whole shit. Uh, that's what I want to do
Uh worst of the year best of the year and we did that shit in like four days
Do you guys remember that we did that in less than three or four days?
It was like less had to I remember it was like december 26 or something when I was like, okay nominate
So this time we're gonna have a good full week of nominations
And plenty of time to put it together
It would it might have been less than two or three days
last year
But I I loved it
But we'll have more time
And that is happening on new year's eve
Of course, but pin thanks for the 250 pin
once I showed up to a black tie symphony for
Tchaikov Tchaikovsky in some crappy shorts in a shirt during the intermission. They were setting up some sort of after party
I was chatting with the help and he let me snag a few glasses of wine for free
Uh little did I know it's the wine that gets you destroyed
So I stumbled back into the symphony and it's suddenly the greatest music i've ever heard
Afterward, I hung out with some old rich guy who hated his wife and then I got hit on by that guy
That's an odd story but it's that's a that's something that you can tell that's a story to tell
Well, this is the best music ever I love this music what does it go like
What's that one it's not that
But thank you pin for the 250. Thank you sticks renegade for the 250
It's almost that time of year again my birthday's on christmas since there's no christmas stream surprised me with a random
Happy birthday like last year and the year before happy birthday sticks renegade
And I was I will remember it and there's not gonna be a stream on christmas
But there will be a stream like probably a few days before christmas or like that week before christmas
So you'll get i'll be live on christmas not that i'm just i've rewind that not gonna be live on christmas to make that very clear
No christmas stream this year the minecraft stream and the new year's eve stream gonna be taking the place of anything that would be christmas related
We'll see a few days before christmas happy birthday
Let's get to the end. See you guys tomorrow for the game awards. We have a couple more bits we have
Bot squire, thanks for the 500 bits
it's uh, just
Me, I don't know what i'm doing here. It's probably probably playing a thing game of the year
And those eyes are real even though they might not be though
Those eyes could be doctored
I think they actually are
Yeah
Somebody fucked up somebody did something with my pupils. That's weird
Those things streams
What a hoot
Let's examine this for a second
I want to I want you to see
Let's zoom into the eyes
We're going late tonight. Damn
Why do I still even have this on the desktop?
So that's the one
I can't believe I thought this was real
I can't fucking believe I thought that was real
that's not the image though see people have gotten smart and
They doctor it in a way
Those eyes aren't real
Right. I don't think they are
I don't I don't it's just pupils
There's nothing there's no definition to the it's just pupils
You have a shitty camera
Hey
Don't be mean to my camera
Hey, thank you pin
For the 250 is this doctored? Hold on
Nope
Oh my god, where's my spine?
Beer belly and nerd neck
Okay, i'm out of here i'm out of here is this doctored I don't know
What are you guys getting these
Let me see if this one's doctored
What was this called?
Where is it? I mean that's where the image comes from
I think that they fucked with it though. They fucked with it. Look at the mouth
You did this is doctored. Look at the mouth
This a hundred percent has been met has been doctored
All right. Good. I'll see you tomorrow for the game awards
I can't wait
Oh, yeah, I should have a couple of bits pin. Thanks for the 250 right? I didn't even say it. Thanks for the 250 though
Uh say ha I used to get yelled at all the time when I was like 10
Because I would run
straight skeleton
Necro on diablo 2 go to cow runs and kill the cow king
Wow, you're the worst kind of person in the world
You you you went in there you killed the cow king on purpose
Wow, yeah, so that's unbearable. I can't believe you would do something like that you dick
Those of you that don't know the cow king if you killed the cow king in a server
Nobody else in that game could play the cow like it couldn't make the cow lever ever again
You essentially turned off everybody in that game from being able to physically open the portal again
You had to make another character
That was back when you could have like 20 skeletons it would lag everyone out
It was called the lag romancer. I never understood why everyone was upset with me because I was having the time of my life
Yeah, I miss
playing diablo 2 necromancer
Having 50 things on screen run around. You just don't have to do eat a sandwich and play the game
Maybe one day i'll do like a hardcore diablo 2 thing would just beat him with anyone that wants to play
And I just play
uh necromancer
What this would just be fuck the king again, except i'm a necromancer this time
D2 paladin. Yeah, that sounds like the worst stream ever
Come on the time to the game awards start
530 pacific they started right game. Let's see
the game awards are
Yeah
8 30 pm eastern 5 30 pacific i'll see you for that stream
The 8 30 eastern am I going to stream before that? I will not be streaming before that
Before that i'm going to be in the minecraft server
Getting stuff ready because that stream is happening in like four days
So I need to take some time to get it ready
But i'll be live. I would assume like at least 10 minutes or so before the stream starts so I can get it ready
We can be watching it
so
Did germa ever tell the oreo story one time I ate a bunch of oreos and threw from my mother's bed
Finally we have wembley t tv for the 250 germa
You've been in a coma for nine years after the helicopter crash
We had to plug you into the internet and you you're stuck in a vr simulation
Please wake up
I maybe I will
I'll stream starting soon
You'll get moments like this
All right. Good night guys. See you tomorrow for the game awards and we'll have a lot to talk about tomorrow after the game awards
a lot
Good night. Take care