Hello. Hi everybody. How y'all doing? I'm doing good. I'm a little tired.
But that's because I just got back from the east coast. My plane actually landed really late.
So I got in late late late late late last night early early early this morning.
I'm a little fucking zonked. But uh we're gonna do we're gonna hang out with some chill.
And may as well take in a hot air balloon. Uh we're gonna play Planet Zoo.
Those are those are two very distinct dings. I don't even know how I made those sounds.
Yeah I must have smiled twice. Now I hope you enjoyed the Halloween stream. Hope you had a safe
fun Halloween. After the Halloween stream I ended up staying down there for a little while.
Uh get some stuff situated with my family and see some friends. And I just got back.
I just I literally ran here from that getting out of the plane.
Hey great Canadian FK club. Thanks for the five community subs. Thank you.
Let us observe the animals. That's what we're gonna do. Is gonna this is a long tutorial
incoming. That's okay. Guy guys it's a long tutorial. All right sorry a sim just yelled at me.
Let me put the audio on so you know what I'm talking about. Um this is a long tutorial kind
of day. So you know we would do what we're gonna do. Don't abandon Bugleberry. But why would I?
Why would I? He just had like five times reverb.
I didn't even know. I didn't know that I had that much reverb on until I watched the stream like
two days later. I was laughing so hard. It was so much. You could like barely hear what I was saying.
Oh I guess like the reverb was going on top of the reverb. Okay when I first watched it I was like
oh I did that. Maybe it like gets fixed. Maybe they like drop the audio like the reverb a little.
No it got like worse. I screamed. Oh I didn't do anything. Right? This is somebody else doing this.
Oh man it was so loud. I didn't know it was gonna be that loud. But hey Bugleberry's pretty good at
pottery don't you think? What do you mean no? What do you mean no? What did the doctor have to tell
you guys? Oh that I was full of shit. That's what he said and he stormed out. Yep. Come on Dr.
Schmoyxen was back. That was a ton of fun. I was so glad to see Dr. Schmoyxen again.
Literally full of shit. Was that the same? Yeah that's the same person. We're a legendary doctor.
Haunted noises. Jeremiah joined when you had a diaper on. Oh yeah let me talk about the diaper for
a second. All right shut up Sim. I was lying in bed in the... I was in a hotel right? I'm lying in
bed after that stream and somebody... there's like three or four photos that I saw of like zoomed in
diaper full diaper and I put my iPad down and I put rested my head on the back of the pillow
and I said was that a mistake to do that? No. It was. It was. It wasn't it? I had this like weird
not okay uh look let me like I don't like care about any of that shit right like I don't like
I'm not like embarrassed by anything really anymore right but but I don't know why but for
like 10 seconds I was sitting there going I was in like a diaper on stream and shit like that
I don't know if I should have done that it's weird but no it's okay you know if I get embarrassed
for five seconds you know that it was embarrassing your next employer will see it let's hope they
think it's funny I gave you guys shit for like saying like bald on stream imagine imagine the
person saying that to you that then filled a diaper with slime on themselves the person that's
hiring that sees that they might not even let me in the building all right uh but yes I'm back
uh we're gonna here's here's the plan for this week we actually got we got yeah well you don't
think I'm gonna step on the brakes no step on the gas uh so today we're gonna do planet zoo
tomorrow it depends how fun planet zoo is you know if I'm like you know let's do it again tomorrow
we'll do tomorrow and then later this week we're gonna do dead rising 1 beat dead rising 1 and then
we're gonna do community content night next week like probably uh like yeah like probably like seven
or eight days from now and then five or six days later somewhere probably like next weekend or
the weekend after that we're doing green screen dlc for free volume 2 so I will open up a new
discord channel we will do suggestions we'll vote on responses and things you want me to do
in front of the green screen again and that will make it we'll make a day out of it you know
well it's good to be back um taking a lot of planes recently I've been going back and forth
back and forth back and forth uh the last couple of months so it's good that I'm gonna be my feet
will be cemented in the ground here for at least another another month or two I think we'll see
depends on what happens but why don't we move over here where you got uh we currently have
this is our avatar I didn't know that you actually did I just did it I don't care it doesn't need to
be anything this is my avatar that's the kind of I mean I would wear this I would I think I wear
this exact outfit all the time actually and now we go from here this is planet zoo place your avatar
hq the hq is where other players will see your avatar and access any zoos or blueprints you have
shared this is like the me plaza position your avatar anywhere on the globe you can edit your
avatar hq position later oh well what do I do do I do like boston or do I do vegas
oh should I just do it in the ocean brazil why do brazil what about like no this is like the funny
way to do this like oh Russia somewhere can I zoom in no I can't even zoom in no this is
probably gonna fuck up my ping if I do this it's gonna connect me to like european servers all
right I would just somewhere over here in like Florida should I do no that's not where I live
should I do like all right I made my decision career I have the tiger all right guys I hope
you're ready for a tutorial stream because I'm that's what I want to do career franchise
challenge sandbox five days left for eye of the tiger what the hell is this all right progress
through a career in zoo management oh boy are there 36 tutorials what is this what country is
this oh I was gonna say we like we are we like under attack it's like the earth under attack
okay so let's do the good the good one house but that's where we're going okay what is this
game this is you make your own zoo tutorial all right renovated and renamed after the play
what is the lore somebody can read the lore wait update hold on I have to I have to read this
actually I'm not gonna skip the tutorials okay renovated and renamed after its purchase by
bernard goodwin in the 1980s goodwin house has since become one of the most respected zoos in
the country more recently has undergone a further renovation to update many of the habitats and
facilities but due to various issues the work hasn't been completed which is where you come
from I'm ready I'm I'm excited I am I'm calm excited you know what I mean what's with this
loading screen two mega lol tutorial lol I couldn't even no I'm not just gonna burn through the whole
thing I need to know how to play I was actually kind of excited for this game oh oh sorry about
that I I have a habit of slipping back into the planco language okay it's good to finally meet
you in person I'm bernard although I insist you call me bernie the only person who calls me bernard
is my wife and even then only when I've tracked elephant dung into the carpets wait throw oh as
you know I own why would you have that but I always like to show people the ropes here at my home
this is the first zoo I ever opened and the source of great pride for me this is so cool
thanks to a lion breeding program we ran in the 80s but we're in the middle of a big renovation
that's where you come in sadly our old contractor had to retire after developing a fur allergy
peacock or devil kept sneezing his dentures into the lion habitat so it's up to you to finish
everything off don't worry though I'm not completely throwing you into the deep end
my headkeeper and Nancy Jones will be lending a helping hand whoa oh did you see that jump
you to be too but I'm sure that was a fucking fog even better one that isn't on fire less
shouting that way
okay from that rosy fresh face of yours I'm guessing you're Bernie's new hire
good now I hope you're ready to ditch your diploma because we're about to get
really hands-on okay but before we begin the real work how about we familiarize you with the zoo
by learning how to fly around and visiting some of our beautiful animals okay well these I just
have a tutorial and having a look see at the grizzly bear habitat enter enter the grizzly
bear animal habitat camera locate the West African lion habitat look at the empty habitat
all right well why does have my controls on the screen why are you taking away from me
all right find the grizzly bear habitat okay it's right click how do I uh pitch there we go
all right find the grizzly bear habitat oh I see it did you know that grizzly bears
also known as Ursus Arctos horribilis can hibernate for up to seven months a year
but then again given the chance I think a lot of people would do that too I don't even want
to play I just want to look look at the bear select one of the bears and you'll bring up
its information information panels seven years old this is where you can find out all kinds of
information about your animal the most important thing being its overall welfare
you'll learn more about animal welfare today as we go through your objectives
but for now let's enjoy this magnificent animal why don't you select the camera at
the bottom of its information panel okay activate the animal camera so this is it here whoa see now
this is a fantastic way to get a close look at your animals you can also get this view of an
animal by simply double clicking on it yeah that's much easier to do all right well that's cool
okay when you're ready let's pop over to the other side of the zoo what is he gonna go
is he gonna take a bath marked their location for you to find
do you get to watch him eat but I don't even care I just want to watch okay what's he doing with his
bum all right uh let's go back okay if uh enter the grizzly bear what is he doing oh shit okay
uh locate the west african lion habitat okay let's get out of here right uh west uh west
african lion habitat where is it over here all the west african lion to you and me
lions are the most social cats and they can be as many as 40 lions in a pride although prides of
that size are pretty rare as bernie would say those lions are awesome which is precisely why
i handle the training instead these days what is that how about we get started on those objectives
they have like a little like a pinata in here and see what he's doing
do i pick up the coin pinata enrichment what oh it is a pinata why are they why the pinata is
in here okay look at the empty habitat now what we got empty habitat this way my first animal
i can't wait it's gonna be kangaroo no it's gonna be armadillo no it's gonna be a raccoon i want two
raccoons all right i got it it's right there right as you can see it's a lovely space for animals
but it's missing a certain something beavers two somethings warthogs so i'd like to adopt a pair
of them to adopt animals we need to open the animal market which is in the animal trading
section people watching right now okay um animal trading there we are a pair of perfectly splendid
warthogs for our zoo just click on them and select adopt from the side menu normally the animal
exchange would be full of animals but i've emptied out the market while you learn how it works
okay so we got the last thing i need is you accidentally ordering a dozen elephants
what's wrong with that okay well i'm being drip fed content because the game knows that i would
just click this button a thousand times and then have to restart the tutorial so it's size longevity
fertility zoo all right let's get one so just send to zoo waiting in the trade center
send to zoo delivery scheduled how many do i need two when you adopt an animal it's automatically
placed in the trade center where they're held until you're ready to move them into their habitat
which as it happens you are so how about you move them into their new home okay animal store wait
animal storage okay so this is animal market animal storage trade history are these stocks
okay so common warthog in trade center move to here when you ask for an animal to be moved into
a habitat your caretakers will go to the trade center collect your animal and deliver them to
your selected habitat i've marked the trade center's location so let's go and watch the
caretakers in action oh it already happened okay so animal trading does it where's the trade center
oh okay i got one look it loves its new pen no get out i want to talk i want to get in here
what the warthogs are fucking ugly what do you mean no i'm sorry warthog looks like five animals
combined hey what i didn't say i hated it i just said i said i said that warthog was ugly that
doesn't mean i hate the warthog okay so i have one okay i got two in here now what's the uh how do
i feed them animal storage okay so i have two in here so what was it what's the next part what's
the woman to do but how do i feed them because of nature habitat habitat the tutorial like just
gave up on me what was i supposed to go to the trade center first i marked it on your map oh
okay it's over here well as you can see those caretakers don't hang about they'll move those
animals to their destination as fast as possible right of course normally we'd have to place the
animals into quarantine before moving them into a habitat but i am assured by a good standing
that these warthogs are in the very rudest of health okay right let's get the warthogs habitat
finished up so we can keep them nice and happy what do they eat each animal in the zoo has an
overall welfare statistic basically how happy they are and that overall welfare statistic is
it self-compressed of four different areas nutrition social health habitat
luckily if you select an animal you'll bring up their animal welfare information panel which
we saw earlier where you can see how they're doing that way you'll know exactly what areas need to be
addressed but don't worry if that's a lot to remember you can always check the zoopedia for
more information are they not supposed to be eating this let's start elephants care of the
warthogs nutrition welfare at feeding station and water station to place a food station and
a drinking station now each animal requires a different type of feeding station and for
the warthogs it's a small feeding trough so pick up put in case and a water bowl no stop okay
uh habitat uh we have water bowl food through small for water bowl okay so 100
dollars that's a lot of money for just a big fucking box objects can be placed pretty much
anywhere use the commands below to help change the position okay so you rotate raise and lower
that's weird can they put it in the ground okay rotate is z that's i'm gonna have to remember
that rotate toggle advanced mode is x oh god you get like these kind of like blender controls
oh no i don't care about that oops how do i move it no why do i have two what have i done
uh they can't reach this okay raise it how do i edit it why did i go into like the second life
editing mode how do i edit it well m hold on angle snap reset height is shit okay shift reset height
there we go okay align to surface is v that's good all right i'm gonna put it like over here
let's put like their feeding tray over on the rock so people can watch them eat
and they can like look up and like sneeze the food on people i like that okay how about here
right here right there okay and then now we need a uh water dish align to surface and um yeah uh
all right closely no this is like kind of huge all right how about over here so they can like
yeah i want them to like lift up and be able to be like can i angle it that's extremely
unhygienic you sign away before you go to the zoo that bath will count towards their enrichment
welfare specifically their toy enrichment welfare mud bath okay get it as close to the people as
possible okay um how about like right here right in the corner right there oh nice work you've
got a knack for this i see now our contractor had to leave in a hurry so this place is in a
shadow state unfinished splash zone what sits all over the shop but the first thing we need to
finish is the ostrich habitat it's over near the hippos is this full do i have to fill this or is
it full if how do i put food in here all right let's go to the ostriches this i'm gonna mix
my zoo is gonna be so bad before we actually start building our ostrich habitat let's pause
the game just click the pause button in the bottom right corner okay ah that's more like it so can
you do anything when it's paused sometimes it's a good idea to pause the game whilst you're doing
something which requires your concentration because it'll stop the zoo spinning out of
control while you're looking the other way let's keep the game paused while we get this ostrich
habitat built okay job number one here is to add a habitat gate before we complete the barrier
every habitat needs a habitat gate after all how else would the keep are there dinosaurs in this
game without t-rex's here make sure it's hooked up to the path so the keepers can reach it
habitat gate right there right oh it has to be in the gate right here how about like where
this is a tutorial let's complete the perimeter barrier so we can adopt us some ostriches
i've marked out an area for you to use so i'd like you to finish off the perimeter using the
brick barrier okay so that is just as simple as just snapping it and dragging it or clicking oh
okay oh nice well this is kind of intuitive good work remember before you can place animals in any
habitat it has to have a full loop of connected barrier now you've probably noticed that guests
can't actually see into this habitat at the moment at least not without a step ladder but
i'd like you to select a piece of barrier and swap out the brick for a glass barrier so the
guests can see in the whole thing or just like one section just make everybody crowd around it
yeah like right here highlight sections then click the grab glass barrier and browse it okay
there we go adding in more windows gives guests even more opportunities to see the animals in
a habitat i want crowded areas here make sure the guests can get a good view into a habitat from the
path they're walking on because it makes them happy and because this would be a pretty terrible
zoo if they couldn't why don't do the whole thing glass then the last thing we need to do
is to add a donation box you see when guests enjoy the view of an animal they'll make a donation
just make sure you put them in easy to reach places like near a viewing point
donation boxes are one of the main sources of income for the zoo so make sure you remember them
this is the main source of income is through people wow okay this is a lot like streaming
i'm just behind the glass here now before we adopt our ostriches you should click the play
button after all if the games pause then so are our caretakers which will make it a bit tricky
for them to deliver the ostriches eh okay so complete the ostrich i don't even have any
ostriches by the way as well as pausing the game you can speed the game up by clicking on the fast
forward button it'll run everything at two times and five times faster five times it can be useful
especially if you're waiting for money to accumulate or for animals to be delivered
to your habitat personally i use it when i'm waiting for a brew to finish
all right you finished the habitat so it's height and we adopted those ostriches don't you think
let's get four of them in here ostriches are really tall right now let's see animal uh
marketplace common ostrich do they have rarities like is it like legendary ostrich epic ostrich
do they actually have that all right this one's why this one's 464 at all how does it what's this
mean okay well i'm just gonna tell you i'm gonna get a naio okay i'm waiting in the trade center
uh move to here relocating to habitat 22 all right let's go hurry up where are you let's go
get in why does somebody have to bring a box over here like okay here we go
this is opening loot boxes is that what they did in this game they can i just buy crates
to open them and it's like what's nutrition all right now i got a feeding zone what about
this do they want sprinklers is an ostrich like a three-year-old kid well no i don't think we want
these okay so let's go to habitat uh food and water feeding state do i need two of these
how many do i need do i need more than one well i'm gonna get the i'm gonna get the expensive one
five did you say five i have to get all four of these while we wait for them to be collected
by the caretakers and brought to the habitat you should get it ready for them add a suitable
feeding station water station and an appropriate food enrichment item it's often best to place
things like enrichments and feeding stations near to the habitat perimeter so guests can get
a really good view of the animals wait the mouse is fucked up hold on a second here why is this
happening because right now right now i'm over the ostrich i'm selecting the ostrich right now
what the hell is going on here wasn't this happening before hold on a second yeah this
shit was happening before too this makes no sense alt tab no okay this what why is this happening
hide cursor in game trying to try changing window to full screen let me let me see what happens if i
just do full screen this is weird maybe it is already in full so no it's borderless all right
what if i just do full screen there we go okay weird all right let's get going so does this guy
have to go back and get another one and then come back and bring it what is it is this the only
person that's here doing this all right anyway i need habitat all right uh water throw they like to
drink out of trees don't they no that's a brontosaurus um how about in the corner no no
over here i want over here so they can like put water in the mouth and like go up and like spit
it out over it people okay food bowl all right that's good and then a slow feeder all right
good to see the ostriches have somewhere they can really stretch one joke did you know they can
actually run at 43 miles per hour oh heaven forbid they ever escape the speed camera finds alone
would bankrupt us all right i did it visiting player bernie certainly seems impressed speed
camera joke every time we get an ostrich so now we've made the ostriches lives a bit better
let's do the same for the keepers shall we so somebody's visiting the zoo for the keepers to
feed the ostriches and hippos we should build a new keeper hut the keeper huts are where the
keepers prepare the food for animals so they should be placed near to the habitats to make
sure the keepers don't waste their time walking when they should be looking after the animals
who is this visiting player who is this person visiting player it's freaking me out i didn't
listen about the phone all right keeper huts are found in the facilities menu all right
plays a keeper hut uh let's do this one you'll need to rotate the keeper huts to get it to connect
up to the path how it helps all right uh where did it want me to put this how stupid is it being
dark souls invaded all right over here that's really ugly how about here right there this keeper
hut only has space for one keeper but the larger keeper hut can allow multiple keepers to prepare
food at the same time is this her apartment is where they live that keeper huts and other
staff facilities shouldn't be placed near to areas where there are lots of guests
guests don't like seeing facility buildings and it can affect their happiness
negatively in case that was why something that's all facilities shops and a whole host of other
i don't want to see i only i i want to pretend like i'm in the savannah let's place a transformer
next to it shall we well yeah like downtown san francisco oh yeah sorry it's not like this
fucking savannah you know you don't know that now those i don't like seeing that that building
that powers the place bury it so disney world's like that there's like fucking a whole city
underground now the reason everything is ugly is because you're using the power heat map this map
allows you to see what is and what isn't powered in your zoom oh man so once you've placed your
transformer you can click in the bottom left to turn the heat map off okay so this is what's
powering so anything that's in this circle is being powered they're not going to do like a
factorial type thing are they lovely work now the keepers can start using the hut to prepare food
and thanks to where you've put it they won't need to walk very far to deliver it to the ostriches
and hippos let's get on to your next objective then bengal tigers we want to adopt some but i'm
afraid there's nothing ready for them yet head on over to the plot of land i've marked out it's not
too far away in the next building it's the research zone and the transformation zone
here you can put two strength potions in with an ostrich and you'll get a strength-based ostrich i
can't wait for that shit what is the objective i wasn't paying attention i forgot a highlighted
area okay righty your next job is to build a habitat from scratch and concrete and really
expect so go ahead and build it just make sure that the habitat includes that big hole we've dug
oh and don't forget to add a habitat gate to the barrier okay so build a build a bengal tiger
be able to see the tigers sure not climbable water tight climb that there's a climbable rock
like it's i just the tutorial i don't care i just i'm just trying to learn how to do everything
all right now we fill this hole with what was what is what was it good add the gate complete
the habitat boundary okay we need a gate um how about like over here now like in the back this
way now bernie takes safety very seriously at his what is he trying to do here probably make
sure those tigers can't jump out of their habitat don't you think the way we'll do it is by changing
the height of the height of the barrier okay then you should start by double clicking the habitat
barrier which will take you into barrier editing mode okay angles are here length height great now
highlight the entire perimeter of the habitat you can do that by clicking and dragging the
barrier selection tool drag this widget to select the habitat then drag this okay you just now you've
got all of the perimeter selected you can increase the height of it by clicking and dragging the
barrier height tool upwards you'll want to make sure it reaches a height of at least 3.7 meters
3.7 meters can i change this to like i'm an american is this it click and drag it
turn this into like a baseball stadium all right how about right here let's do four whatever now
that the habitat is in place don't forget to put down a donation box near to your viewing areas
i have to make like fenway park yeah i'll do that especially as these tigers aren't exactly eating
instant noodles for lunch okay donation box always remind me that the donation box is in
facilities because i will forget should i put more than one like put like two or three of them
well people are gonna be watching from here okay that's the habitat boundary complete the
habitat gate in place and most importantly the tigers won't be able to jump out of it anymore
i think it's time we adopted those tigers okay animal market uh
this is a very large increase we went from like two hundred dollars to ten to twelve thousand dollars
here whilst our trusty caretakers collect and deliver the tigers let's take a look at preparing
the habitat for their arrival we'll start feeding station lake add a suitable feeding station for
them okay this is a food a large food tray i think i would like to eat here instead of adding a
water bowl these food trays are solo panels some animals need a pool in their habitat so they can
go for a swim but they can also use it to drink from all you have to do is make sure the banks
of the pool have a gentle slope so they can easily get a nice refreshing drink there's already a pool
but you still need to fill it with water you should do that by going into terrain and selecting
the water tool okay water here it is calm water or rough water calm water right
add water is just left click and move water oh that's kind of scary uh water is an essential
part of many animals lives so it's important in fact to consider when building a zoo many animals
need a body of water in their habitat to swim keep cool and drink from if if water is necessary
in this way it'll be highlighted along with any space requirements in the terrain tab of the
animals info panel okay create a space to put the water eg create a pit or lake with the terrain
tools highlight the position of the wall in the space for the water to be filled click to fill
some barrier wall types are capable of holding back water yes that'll do nicely of course just
the war togs and ostriches these tigers will also need some enrichment why don't you add some that
looks like the bottom of a urinal that does not look like a pool so i can save money okay
okay let's put check it out how is it this is gonna make mud drinking it just eating
mud they're both gonna have diarrhea in like three hours all right so what i'm gonna do place a
toy and food enrichment item enrichment frozen blood pumpkin why is there blood in this pumpkin
and a rubbing pad here come here you can like use the rubbing starting to take shape now the tigers
are in their habitat so they can hide from the guests or more like do they drink blood out of
a pumpkin in england is this for real if that just is normal weather go on add a shelter to
the habitat why are tigers fucked up suitable bits and bobs or if you like just pop down the
blueprint that i've already built for you what oh oh god they're eating his brain they're eating
his brain just take that clip like i'm sorry okay uh so which way is correct should i put some
solar panels on this way do they like to be facing people or not facing people oh poor dabs i'm sure
it can't have escaped your attention that the tigers look a bit miffed that's because they are
too keen on the type of terrain habitat select a tiger and bring up its information panel okay
it doesn't like its habitat we'll fill it with water click on the terrain tab that way you can
view the terrain information and see how they feel about the different types that'll tell you
what the tigers need more of or less of in this habitat okay you need more terrain plants okay
i gave you more water all right you want more plants all right okay then open the terrain
editing tool select painting and give them some more soil yes that should help with the habitat
okay terrain painting tool that if he was like sprinting all right you want more short grass
okay i can do that for you oh you want to cut the grass oh i see tigers don't like uh grass
to be long what happens if i go too far outside the lines oh i'm just in this habitat that's awesome
you can't color outside the lines looks good wait wait whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa too much
less grass okay whatever you okay goldilocks there's too much now there's too much long grass
animal needs less long grass how much soil soil okay we need less long grass
it's almost perfect right then all animals need plants and trees from their own biome or continent
you know desert savannahs or asia you look at the thing looks like these tigers need a few more
plants in their habitats to get a perfect fit use plants from the rainforest and temperate biomes
that are native to asia farming minus two farming minus two farming minus two the tigers will also
want a certain amount of their habitat to be covered by those plants to find out which plants
to use and how many select a tiger and go to the environment tab okay so let's take a look
so that's now as you can see some of the plants currently in the habitat aren't quite right for
the tiger like the wattle bushes wattle bushes why would they put them here okay the the wattle
bushes you can find all of the plants you need in the nature section and you can use the filters
to only show the types of plants you want to see in this case that's plants from the rainforest
or temperate biomes use filters to get the correct continent and biome for tigers
um what do we want here well first hold on a second you've got too many things open on
my screen at once now can i make this thing like 10 smaller hold on get out of here like
let me go come here plants yeah i know so if i go to your not enrichment terrain terrain okay
okay so uh environment plants and coverage continent asia biomes tropical temperate and
grassland but you don't like these so how do i just i want to just delete these like how do i just get
rid of these all right so we need we're gonna do tropical so tropical and then asia sure it's down
here so let's do uh tropical and asia all right so you want some of these how about uh coconut
coconut palm that would be cool over here right here let's put it up here so like the coconuts
drop and i'll keep his heads can i straighten this thing up why is it so bent okay looks all
right i want to get rid of this how do i just delete these delete this is gonna be an easier
way for me to do this right all right how about a a bangle bamboo right there all right oh i thought
i put that down all right you look like you're all right how's your environment doing you want
more plants all right get rid of this thing where's this can i like go to plant all right where's this
thing ready this tree they don't want this tree they hate this thing okay now let me put and they
want more plants how why do you want so many do they really want that many more or how about um
like a little group of these over here okay and then how's that how do i clean up their shit
what's what's pre-recorded actually pre-recorded what are you talking about what is actually
pre-recorded now i want it smaller here we go like all right is that is that fine do you like that
i mean no one said that you all of you were saying that i need more of this
coverage zero percent how much more do you want all right let's go with temperate asia and you want
like some elm trees this is so huge though this just blocks view put on your face cam not put on
my face cam okay and then how about like down here it's more tree than animal
they say the good fences make good neighbors i guess that's doubly true when one of the neighbors
is a bengal tiger all right cool still those tigers look so happy that i doubt they'd leave
even if you didn't poke a hole in their fence oh but for heaven's sake don't test that theory
i'm not gonna move this right let's head over to the indian peafowls i've been told that we need to
improve their social welfare okay i'm starting to get it there's a maze in here this is cool
just find one of the peafowls and select them to open an information panel then we can have a good
gander at how they're doing is this maze for me i suppose ganderin would just be for geese
found one expand their social welfare and we can get a bit more detail
social group there are too few adults and juveniles in animals social group
uh now they've clearly got plenty of space and they're not stressed but it looks like
this social group isn't quite right so let's find out more click on the social tab at the top of
their information panel adult population is only two right as you can see the peafowls need their
population to be larger to solve this little problem you'll need to adopt three more female
people three female power to the animal market then okay here we go uh we need female bring them
in i think i'm gonna play this like all night good work on those people but sadly it sounds
like our snow leopard is a bit grumpy let's head over there and see what's wrong with her
something about the snow leopard i don't know how to snow leopard just like people animals can
suffer from stress if things aren't quite right you know like how shitty that is in the milk
before the teabag in the case of these snow leopards they're a bit stressed by their lack
of privacy you can lower their stress levels by swapping out the normal glass barrier by their
cave for one-way glass i don't see any stress not a cheap option but i think they're worth the
expense don't you this will give the snow leopard somewhere to go when they want to get away from
the prying eyes it's going up it's gonna jump over i just like realize how fucked up this is
that'd be like i might have like looked out my window they were like 700 people all looking in
the window by the way this is when i'm showering wow this is getting a lot of money imagine you
get out of the shower and you're just brushing your teeth with a towel around your waist
and you turn around and your whole the whole wall of your bedroom and your bathroom is glass
and there are just people staring there watching you like take a shower i'm getting out of there
that's what's gonna happen all right so what do i need to do uh one way glass barrier
how much just enough to make them i don't understand like
like the whole thing or just a little bit just where everybody's standing
okay so that's selected now how do i say yes
what i'm just doing oh right okay well this is even worse how do i what's going on here
okay um what
i did it right that's not me doing it
is it no wall this is a wall here already i don't understand what's going on one way glass
like select it but it's there so why is it still telling me to do this i'm selecting the wall one
way wait one way glass from the outside that's what only the window part of course when an
animal isn't in its natural biome it's probably going to be too hot or too cold unsurprisingly
for the snow leopards it's it's too hot i can't just select it you should help cool it down by
adding some coolers to their habitat but let's start by opening up the temperature heat map
and having a look see at the temperature in the leopard's habitat heat map
open the heat map this is electricity oh okay as you can see we already have one cooler in there
let's pop some more down and get as much of the habitat as chilly as we can there's like too much
going on this habitat already has power but you'll need to make sure that in the future just so you
know if any part of a habitat is powered then the whole this whole place is on fire look at how hot
it is in here is that safe okay coolers so where should i put this just it doesn't matter anywhere
over here how many do i want to put down okay is that better and it's did they're working yeah
habitat 91 yeah this is this is fine put them in the middle these people are freezing
so the whole habitat's supposed to be like this well i would have done that
you can find heat maps for all sorts of helpful things so do be sure to explore them and make
good use of them okay this coolers and heaters it'll take a little while for the temperature to
adjust once you've added coolers or heaters but now we've got the coolers in we can address the
leopard's terrain welfare you see what the leopards really want in here is snow and rock so let's make
that happen so somebody just half-assed this part okay terrain so you want snow
just the whole thing we're just painting this on the ground this is horrible this is so cruel
protesters have arrived at your zoo what it's only one right when i say it
okay let's all of that should give you a pretty good understanding of how to make animals happy
so i'd like you to go and check on all the other animals any issues with their habitat care given
to your animals increase the average welfare of the animals across the whole zoo why didn't you
tell me about this welfare is a very important statistic now to quickly see how all your animals
are doing in the zoo somebody's not doing okay management and then into the animals section
zoo management and then go to the animal section as you can see this list shows you the animals
overall welfare so if something's a mess then you can quickly pop over to them using the locate
button right i'm going for a cut by while you make sure all the animals are well looked after
enrichment habitat oh wait it's the zebras you're contraceptive so what how do i go how do i go over
all right all right what's wrong with this place wait this is us but there's a switch of giraffes
in here where did you come from okay what's wrong with this habitat let's find out what do you think
what's wrong welfare your habitat sucks and your enrichment sucks too insufficient food
enrichment is being provided to cover all animals and there's not enough toys in here okay and
this is not a good i didn't do this yeah just just get on like the the playground thing that
spins around everyone will have fun on that all eight of you can sit on it all right let's do um
terrain so what's the what's wrong with the terrain what kind of terrain do you like
you like okay there's not there's not enough short grass there's not enough long grass and
there's too much soil well shit let me i'll take care of this no no no terrain all right there's
not enough short grass let's do this around the bank plenty of rocks intensity and just that's
better they have like nice green grass over here okay grass is good now we need some long grass
i'm gonna do long grass over here um this way back behind here are they even enclosed
let's do they don't want any soil so it's all short and long grass all right take out the soil
this looks better all right so that's better took care of that wait there's too much there's not
enough short grass now i got it okay so that's okay now you guys are happy what about the giraffe
the giraffe is the only one in here is the giraffe the weird outlier here oh shit okay now special
food enrichment for a second i thought they were enriched by zebras and i'm thinking what kind of
fucked up environment is this no that's a species bonus okay all right so the environment they don't
like these trees so why did he put them all here they're everywhere how many are in here
there's so many of these in here why are these all in here it's for the tutorial yeah but i mean
still come on what the hell are you thinking uh where is it new environment it's every tree
just delete every tree i tell you i'm gonna make this mistake first all right you better
is there any more here no it's still well it's hard to even see these select button in bottom
right multi-tool select click and drag to create a selection they can drag to add to selection
holds control to toggle selection but i don't want to get rid of everything at this point
i guess i can just do this no no that's good to know is it all these trees okay are we good now
you need more stuff right oh what else is left get these out of here this is not even in your
enclosure what because you can see it you don't like it oh my they just hate trees they but
i didn't know that oh my fucking god okay we're just starting from scratch fuck it i don't even
care i'm just deleting everything no not the shit outside just this shit here no no no no
why is this stuff selecting that what are you doing why are you selecting the what are you doing
hey okay we good is it any more just random one tree that i need to delete there's probably like
one or two more things here okay you better no then we where we hit this is a hidden object
game find the fucking dumb trees that we put here what else oh my fucking god can i just delete all
of them just delete them all why is this all in here just delete all what delete the zoo
delete zoo looking for trees what holy shit somebody's gave a lot of money
doctor doctor give me the news thanks for the 50 dollars thank you doctor how do i delete this
not pre-recorded why would the stream be pre-recorded i can't i can't just like mass
delete this there has to be a way right like select and then like so oh my god i have to
give it all of these all of them just leave it i can't they hate it i want to just fucking
delete this why did it select that fuck all right i need to put that wait oh hold on hold on hold
on uh doctor doctor thank you for the 50 dollars 5 000 bits just came in let me pause this
they say uh i'd like to shake your hand if you ever get to another convention on the west coast
i would love to do that too thank you so much for the 5 000 bits really appreciate it it's a lot of
fucking money thank you i hope he washes his hands i do and then there was another 5 000 before that
by the same person was actually a hundred dollars it was 10 000 doctor doctor gave 10 000 bits
they say they actually say first time donator but a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a big big big
fan of yours that's not this they didn't write all that i've been a big fan of yours for years
so this is a long time coming i know you always say never feel bad for not donating more money
but i wish i could unfortunately my job security isn't great right now so there's the best i can do
but i still wanted to give back at least a little to both the man and the stream that have helped me
like countless others through some of my darkest times you'll never know the true depth of your
effect on so many people jeremy thanks a lot that means a shitload i'm glad that you can have fun
here seriously and i know i say it all the time don't feel bad for not donating money like for
that's not necessary take care of yourself take care of yourself first you are number one
put me somewhere else down that list take care of yourself i wish you the best
so moving on i have to lead it to a few too many things somebody was saying it doesn't matter does
it really not matter at all wait is this he's he's escaped wait that fails the tutorial
he's going are they biting people why would you run towards the animal all right i get i
understand the gist of the game is there a rewind is there a rewind button is this how giraffes
sleep that's fucking crazy what don't you get a stiff neck okay all right i get it i get it i
understand how this works uh come here come here get over here how do i pick you up call the vet how
do i pick you up emergency capture but how do you this is disabled by the tutorial so how do i get
them back where are they look i didn't mean to delete this i'm trying to delete plants because
it's like they don't like the shrubs in there get rid of them they they hate it was it the sims
when you have a painting in the room that the sim doesn't like they're like fun goes to zero
there's an undo at the bottom wait can i
how do i get the animals back in no no no where are you going where are you going how do i get
these animals back in here he's just walking around all right how do i delete this part
here come here just let him walk around let them roam no i i i need to do the second tutorial
okay let's do this come here this is temporary i didn't want to fuck this whole thing up but i
have to get rid of this shit how do i delete this road call the keeper i i can't can i not even i
don't think i can do that call vet because look i can't i can't let go of the emergency capture
is vet gonna go over here what about this call the vet they'll walk back in when i'm when hungry
it's going to the bathroom
oh
there's a line out the door to leave he can't even escape what the hell was that
what you got sniper rifle what the fuck just keep keep get him i didn't want it to go to like to
shit
he can just step over this he can step over this it's like a baby gate are you serious
i just because i deleted this that was bullshit okay well the the vet's on duty
what habitats invalid what's wrong with this what what's wrong did i buy something hold on a minute
what the fuck is going on here that's a chain like that how about a brick wall all right are
we still good this is an in fact well how did it become invalid how did i fuck this up i don't
understand what's wrong with this how many are in here all right what i what is wrong with this
gate marked as not a habitat boundary where what how did i screw it up is it this part here that's
the problem i soft locked it the fence was fucked up how did i fuck up the tutorial well it's very
easy because i was selecting i was selecting the bushes over here and it was selecting this
fucking building and i deleted the building when i was selecting the bushes here i did it like
10 times you sure you don't want to pick up this building and delete it look i'm moving on to the
next tutorial i know what i'm doing i soft locked myself somebody said why were they
selecting the bushes because they don't look they don't like bushes they fucking hate them
and it was like there's something wrong with their habitat they don't like the bushes
no get look see well you know they really really don't like those trees they don't like the bushes
either they hate them so i have to go through and get rid of these oh they're gonna hate their
environment no i know how to play i'm done we're gonna play like all these plants need to be
deleted wait what is it 90 well they hate everything in here okay well okay enrichment
we need food in here habitat all right how about food and water food cage what am i trying to do
here enrichment but what what do you want for species food enrichment and toy enrichment
zero enrichment items okay bamboo feeder walk of frozen fruit that sounds pretty cool who's it for
no wait can i do by giraffe all right let's do it by giraffe what kind of giraffe is this
reticulated giraffe okay uh big high suspended high feeder there you go okay and a sprinkler toy
that hurts my eyes all right so that's good all right so you're fine one habitat cleaning
wait there's a disease habitat cleanliness is a disease risk for what i don't even know
where i'm going the lemur we haven't gotten that far in the tutorial yet i can't believe i deleted
that fucking building because i'm trying to select a goddamn bush so what's wrong with this place
i this is power is it like cleanliness habitat temperature water power buildings negative impact
on guests why is it doing this habitat climate is a disease risk let's put on your fucking x-ray
goggles how did somebody okay i get it i have to get out of this i have to play a new scenario
it's all it's fucked forever all right i know i'm gonna do a different scenario
that was fucking horrible okay let's go back to the main menu um should i save it i guess i'll
save it just whatever uh it's because the journey okay main menu we're gonna do a different i need i
still need to learn i still need to learn how to play i'm still learning i opened up another
scenario see okay we are i'm already done with the goodwin house the madagascan simian conservation
project tutorial okay this is just going to teach us some new things no tutorial no i have to do
there's a lot of systems in place i need to at least kind of have somewhat of an idea what the
hell i'm doing i can't i'm having trouble i can't get over it welcome to madagascar it's quite the
change of scenery from dreary old england apart from the weather i suppose they don't call these
places rainforest for nothing the zoo you'll be working in is an ape sanctuary we're doing
vitally important conservation work not just for apes but for all kinds of species but apes
well apes are some of the closest relatives to humans there are and yet the way the world treats
them is like well very much like some of us treat our actual relatives anyway that's why i'm
determined that our operation here does some good if we can all leave some part of the world in a
better state than we found it we'll have lived lives worth living and speaking of states i have
a horrible feeling i left the house in a right one when i get back i expect my life will be worth
living at all this is bernie's primate sanctuary it's not just primates though we've got all sorts
of animals so why don't we go and have a look at some of them eh we'll start by taking a look at
the red rough lemurs they're the ones that look like they should be in a shakespeare play
come on let's head over to them okay i think i'm gonna be all right okay locate the highlighted
area there it is this is a nice little setup i thought these were sinks from back here that's
in northeast madagascar oh cool they can actually live anywhere from 15 up to 25 years that's a long
time okay when you're ready let's go find out bornean orangutans i like this little
playground that they have hey let's find the orangutans the bornean orangutan is such a
marvelous creature they're always a big favorite at any zoo they feature in and they're also the
dwelling animal on the planet assuming you don't count any lions that got stuck up one
oh why don't you take a better look at them open up that information panel and go into the
animal camera okay let's go let's take a look aren't they just incredible i like the zoom
in feature it's really cool when you're ready let's go and have a look see it some of our
beautiful bonobos they're quite the characters what's that noise you can do cinematic camera
okay yeah all right let's go to the other place these habitats are really well done i want to make
like a habitat from scratch that's pretty much what i care about oh dear it looks like we've
arrived just in time one of the habitat's barriers has collapsed we'll need to catch them but before
we do we should box up the other bonobos to stop them escaping too select the habitat boundary to
bring up the habitat information panel okay good now open the animals tab animals and click on box
all animals box all animals whoa we'll need a vet to recapture that escaped bonobo but it seems our
last one left to do some research in the wild not an ideal situation so we'll need to hire a
replacement sharpish hire a vet go into the zoo section and then into the staff management area
staff and then i know you can find all of your staff in here so there's no time to go looking
at their particulars at the moment hire a vet hire a vet now click on one of the paths to place
the vet in your zoo right there great now let's deal with our escapee before they can cause too
much havoc okay use the animal alerts to jump to the escaped bonobo okay right here call the
vet on the call vet button to call the vet over to capture it okay that's a relief so while the
vet deals with our bonobo friend let's go fix up their habitat okay is it i understand okay i get
it that this is like dangerous and scary but like it's just one monkey
oh did he trip this guy i don't give a fuck okay ah so now i have relocating as you can see the
barrier's collapsed someone's taken their eye off the ball obviously let's get this one replaced
this is what i needed to know last time and then we'll edit it okay delete the broken section of
barrier and replace it with a brand spanking new one the broken section of barrier okay so right
here so you have to you have okay you have to delete the part first how do they break it
obstructed i'm not gonna leave like a barn door open like connected whether wrong am i insane
i'm not right okay now that we've done that we need to make sure to add barriers to the top
that way the bonobos won't be able to climb out just make sure you've got the correct
piece of barrier selected when you do that climb proof options climb proof so go into the option
section and select which side the climb proof barrier needs to go on and don't get it wrong
we're more worried about bonobos climbing out than guests climbing in
people will climb into these things nicely done and i think it's high time we unboxed those bonobos
that's not correct the poor mites will get sad if we leave them in there for too long
select the habitat barrier to bring up the habitat information panel again
okay what is it select the habitat information panel and then open the animals tab animals
unbox all animals and finally click on unbox all animals to let them out i expect some of them
are fair bursting for the toilet it turns out that as well as the old vet leaving the zoo's
mechanics realistic sounds we'll need to hire a couple of new ones so we can help stop any more
breakouts why do all sorts of helpful things around the zoo but one of their most important
jobs is taking care of the habitat barriers without mechanics around to repair them the
barriers will crack crumble and fall down and before you know it will be overrun with escaped
animals so don't do wood section and then into the staff management area again make it out of
cement and then paint it to look like a tree right what's the i don't understand hire a mechanic and
then click on a path to place them in the zoo okay and then click on the path again to hire a second
mechanic as you can see you don't have to go back into staff management if you're hiring lots of
the same type of staff member okay so now they're going to be able to watch
i'm off for a cuppa oh i think bernie wants a word with you what does he want oh i hear you had a bit
of an issue with an escape bonobo the main thing is that you dealt with it swiftly and more
importantly without the animals stealing someone's clothes putting them on and then walking out of
the front gate i thought that was an animal you see another key responsibility for our vets
oh these things are vicious by the way researching animals allows vets to unlock new enrichment items
additional information for our education resources enhanced breeding programs and
improvements to food quality oh the animal's food not the vets it'll take more than a research
grant as you can see research is a key part of running your do it
in order for a vet to undertake research they require a research center and once again that's
something that this zoo is missing so let's build one i've marked out an area for you to put it
a research center right here now you've probably noticed that there's already a building where i
want you to build the research center don't worry you see the building that's currently there is
actually a hollow shell so we're able to place our new building inside of it if you select the
research center for placement and then hover over the shell you'll see that it asks if you
want to add the research center to the existing building okay so okay click to add it to the
building oh but that won't place it in just yet though first we'll need to rotate our research
centers which automatically connects to the path when we place it uh okay wait okay ensure auto
stacking is off to make splendid work now that we have a brand spanking new research center we can
give our vets something to do in there oh by the way it's worth noting that the vets will only do
research when they're not required to do any other jobs that said you can change what jobs a vet does
does have a bunch of vets how much money you get to start with let's not worry about that just now
so let's get our vet researching ring-tailed lemurs go into the zoo section and select vet
research vet research and then bugs you can see a list of all the animals present in your my first
zoo is going to be bugs only potential diseases that can occur now let's have a cockroach on to
the ring-tailed lemur to start their research one star megan what is up with this actually
thinking about it i'm not sure we've got any education i'm gonna have like 10 000
let's head over there and add some so our guests can learn all about the fairy little delights
okay so this is first off let's pop down to education educational boards place them on
the habitat barriers at a height that guests can see or if you like pop them down on a stand
yeah well i would do that but i think what i'm gonna write here is
private chests don't do not open i'm gonna put two of them here back to back next to my
storage box what was i making an educational board what the hell is it i thought they were
throwing stuff into the habitat workshop trade center research center what's it what's it what's
it called information board education board facilities uh is it not in there what it
find education boards in here okay what the fuck are you talking about oh this no god this is ugly
a line to surface okay and then one over here okay now that they've been put into position
we have to tell them what animal to display information about select one of the education
boards to bring up its information panel habitat education board okay educational content from the
drop down list select ring-tailed lemur yeah when you link an education board or a speaker to an
animal you need to make sure that said animal is close by if it isn't the guests will get confused
and won't learn as much okay ring-tailed lemur cool okay now that we've done the education boards
let's pop down a pair of speakers speakers play audio to the guests so they can learn while they
look at the animals instead of having to go through the laborious process of reading
okay one thing to bear in mind is that it's important not to put the speakers too close
together if you do the guests won't be able to understand what's being said why
what was that that was like in this is like a flash mob but what are they doing
okay um speakers educational speaker oh right here and then right here now we simply need to
link the speakers to the ring-tailed lemurs just like you did with the education board okay
okay now i'm gonna put like 10 of these next to each other and have each one of them be a different
animal it's gonna be unfucking bearable fantastic oh it's worth remembering that education boards
and speakers both need power to work they won't do much good without it so any power supply
it looks as though our vet has completed their research on ring-tailed lemurs we'll need to
collect the results we can do that by clicking on the notification or by going back into the vet
research area okay let's take it up go on okay what do you got collect my research just so you
know vets will continue to research an animal even after successfully completing a research
level take them off i suppose when you're in the zone you're in the zone ring-tailed lemur level
six now that we've enriched the lives of our guests let's enrich the lives of our ring-tailed
well i gotta collect the research some animals like lemurs will have a climbing need that means
they have a requirement for a certain amount of climbing space and you can fulfill that
requirement by building them a climbing frame okay we'll hope let's find out how much more
climbing space our lemur friends need shall we select one of them and bring up their information
panel so how many you need oh wow they hate this next click on the terrain tab they need land area
they don't care about water you can see they need climbing zones quite a lot more climbing
space but as it happens i've already got a climbing frame blueprint built for you so you
can either pop that down or build one yourself from scratch by the way it's not always just
climbing needs that you have to worry about this thing other animals might need a certain amount
of water in their habitat so they can go for a swim they certainly do keep us on our toes
wow look at this but what i can just make my own no wait hold on move get rid of this
so you have a huge view no i want give me the small one too tall give him a space to go out
no not yet not yet that's for like in like in like 20 minutes all right i want to like hold on
it's not snapped to surface here we go i want to bring this up there we go like come on get on there
what this one that'll stand right is that enough i know it's disgusting but it doesn't matter
environment what do you want terrain okay i need more than that all right how about um
habitat climbable shift it around like this do they jump okay i'm gonna wrap around this way
and then go up here what's this guy doing like i had like a what is he doing
oh wait wait connect this all right this is gonna go a little bit higher from here
this here how much more space do you need there we go all right now i'm gonna connect this
that does not look stable at all that's very that's like dad dad's first tree house for the kids no
it's not that's huge and horrible i would never want a child on this all right that looks good
so that's they got their climbable area now what else they need social enrichment
species toy enrichment okay so they need oh well hold on he loves it he loves it
well he's having so much fun he just he just jumped from here to there look at how high up this is
he just did he shit i think god you gotta go up to the very top oh he's got itchy ears now take it
away from him tell him make him learn life is cruel this would cost more money to dismantle
than it did to put up don't miss don't miss that's dangerous oh look at that one all the
way to the top yeah whoa oh that was insane i can't believe you made that can you get down
is this a baby does tail up mean like i'm scared oh no no it's good go for it again let's see the
jump again come on impress us big jump nice nice that was cool you guys didn't like my structure
and now you say that's like the favorite thing in the world all right we need some uh toy shit
uh so i need some toys these lemur toys who's been in a box wait wait wait what
means they've been in a box for too long why are they in a box why are you putting them in boxes
why are you in why are they in boxes that's weird all right i know a lemur toy oh cardboard box watch
this shit oh yeah you better believe it they're gonna get the skateboard too up here block of ice
musical skateboard oh yeah all their toys will be up here beach ball they're gonna love this
okay now social severe social welfare issues insufficient size or crowding issues are present
are you all right though like overall you're okay we need to expand it
it's because this is too big um maybe i should drop get rid of some of these
i think let's get rid of this one hey why are you capturing my lemurs what are you doing stop
doing that who's doing that i need more space can i just pull this out they need more space
social okay animal has moderate social yeah but i need to make this bigger too many lemurs
is that why she's deleting them wait we might get a skateboard what the fuck was that
he just did a superman jump uh okay can somebody play the keyboard look there's a fox up here
who's gonna get in first hey that was not very nice uh i think they're fine
i love the long jump i want to make an even bigger one yeah they're fine wait
yes look at how smart he is vet research is complete oh i did it you've discovered three items
all right so let's put you i wasn't i what do i do here what's the next part of the tutorial
because i mean they're space too crowded so should i like put cockroaches in here
i know i'm gonna we're gonna i'm gonna do the bug zoo all right you know what i think i know
what i need to know uh i can't just do this i think it's time for me to make my bug zoo
free the hippo where's the hippo where's the hippo here no where's my just where's my animal
chart okay let's go with uh here we go where are you over here can't delete this can i not
delete this berry i can't delete it in the tutorial it won't let me it does not want me to delete this
well oh well you have to run the tutorial in administrator mode what if i make it easy to
get out no the game definitely doesn't want me to do this right now no no i can't all right
well i know what i'm doing now it's time for me to make my zoo let me save it it's time i want to
make my insect zoo why can i delete the building in the last one okay here we go franchise build
zoos all around the world and trade your animals online let's do uh franchise or sandbox sandbox
create new zoo scenario zoo create new i don't i did like all right what's the best bug zone
probably tropical right north america let's go to name the zoo uh bugs is there more than
just cockroaches or am i just gonna have big cockroach bug world bug world is so easy roach
ranch roach ranch is pretty good let's go north america roach ranch you guys are gonna have to
help me out here though holy shit this is the biggest bug zoo you've ever seen so i'm gonna
pause it here's the entrance all right is it like okay barriers blueprints construction
uh construction uh terrain oh we did paths okay here we go path um this is fine we'll go out like
this just to start it go up four and then all right ray's path is u oh all right lower path is j
what else is there increase length that's what i want it's it's a weird thing to have for increased
length okay i can actually put this down here too width i want this a little wider okay that's a
good spot now let's go this way one two done out this side one two that's good and then we'll have
a spot i want like a little circle i'll do one now we'll just shorten it here but like this
would be like information and stuff over this one okay maybe one this no okay that's fine
it's crooked it's crooked oh no whatever will i do i'm in unlimited i've unlimited money and
everything okay so let's start i win wait wait wait now i'm gonna go up i want to raise the path
you right okay let's go this way keep it right there because this is gonna wrap around there's
gonna be a big bug encasement here that'll wrap this way okay then over here i want to extend out
a little bit more and then we'll go up this way okay oops no that's fine and then i don't want
to fuck this up um that could there could be something here no that's too that's too short
that's not long enough undo it all i'm gonna start with this i'm gonna overwhelm myself okay
i'm gonna start with this so i got paths here i need all right habitat bugs no um look at uh
insect species oh shit um uh bison camel what was this thing called something cockroach right
is it not here do i have to research it i think i have to research this
animals let's go to uh staff i need oh i need some vets all right let's hire a couple of vets
one two three okay and then let's go uh caretaker let's do one two three and then
okay keeper we need like one two three i have unlimited money so who cares hire mechanic one two
two bug vets one security guard they just have to protect the bugs so does it really matter
uh vendor one two habitat food and water heaters facilities constructions blueprints
facilities small exhibit facilities small exhibits okay all right classic small exhibit
okay how about just a classic yeah but this sucks though i want them in a big cage
is this going to be like a series of dog houses i can't do that i what i can't put like 5 000
cockroaches in a cage roach cage all right well whatever that's fine ow god dude they couldn't
have this be anything less harsh than this all right that looks fine roach a full roach sidewalk
that's what i'm doing okay small animal exhibits now i can do so now how do i where do i get my
animals okay from the you must have at least one trade center in your zoo in order to trade animals
right okay well let's do a trade center uh animal trade center this has to be one of the inside one
of these doesn't it all right let's do the trade center like over here now this has to be inside
one of these buildings whatever who cares what does it really matter that much
making a roach exchange
all right this is fine okay animal trading here we go so bugs we're looking for bugs
is it only roaches there's a lot of animals here all these alligators okay this is going to be a
roach alligator and giant panda exhibit we're just we're starting with roaches what are these
things called uh reflect is there a search feature here species is there is there a search
oh what whoa the spiders okay hold on what do we got what we got what we got
giant centipede brazilian salmon pink tarantula holy shit oh yeah okay giant burrowing cockroach
got it and here we go nice oh nice i'm so happy okay another one and then we'll do
scorpions well let's do another let's do another giant what's this what's this
leafs what does that mean this is this can be cockroach alley is there only one in there
okay is there any more cockroaches just giant cockroaches snails frogs oh goliath beetles
nice yeah this is gonna be spiders everywhere and stuff this is gonna be awesome all right
we'll keep the cockroach thing going because i'm gonna have another row and i'm gonna make
some benches and shit okay now what do they need do they need anything you know okay welfare and
the exhibit sucks what's wrong with it exhibit layout is partially providing enrichment features
humidity they need more humidity how do i increase the humidity humidity here we go all right a little
bit more let's turn it on humid whoa okay how much humidity does it need 78 80 humidity is that
too much i'm killing them wait wait wait wait wait pause it pause it pause it what do you need
you need the temperature is too low it's the exam is oh shit i'm fucking murdering them all right
slow down it's too hot and the humidity is too high well shit temperature lower the temperature
to like 35 humidity down to like 78 humidity is good temperature is too hot 30 how about 30
what do you want it at like 28 29 30 30 all right we're good and 75 humidity let's do it on all of
do i have to go through and do it for all these all right 30
and then 70 humidity can i do it to all of them for the love of god there's no power okay i make
a power plant hold on all right pause it pause it pause it pause it pause before they die
microwaving them i'm they're fine it's not it's not a pizza oven i'm trying to get it to be ideal
and then i'm gonna put the power on this don't just wait till my buggy museum is done hold all
your judgments for like another 20 minutes okay i need power so we need to go to facilities we need
to go to power power what the hell is it called electricity is it under where is it under utilities
okay here we go i let's do solar are you kidding me uh what happened done you see how sustainable
this shit is uh exhibit layout is okay layout would it look go back how many are in here
there's only one animal in here this one animal social population genetics fertility gene effects
wait appeal lifetime all right hold on wait wait wait this thing's ready to go we're good right
let's check it all all right so you look all right the layout is still something wrong with it
layout broken hollow log okay and oh it just wants like some cool stuff all right i got you
and like no no no i want to be able to see what you're doing all right you know you like the
layout now this one will do uh a log and then some leaves people allowed in here yet did i open the
park no no no no no the park's not open yet there's just like six bugs you shouldn't be kept hold on
pause it pause it that looks good that looks good let's go do it on all these they want to see the
bugs yeah but you have to wait okay that one looks all right well let me just put this shit in here
it doesn't cost me money implement a breeding program well first i have to make sure that they
can live in here where are the speakers i'm i'm getting there hold on a second all right climate
windows no that's fine all right editing core classic small exhibit what are you talking about
all right so these are ready how do i say i'm gonna see the cockroach wait i need the speakers
oh i don't even it had this right here all right educational content
cockroach they can't even get over here to this to these ones well fuck it they don't need it
wait this um doesn't make sense just put different lessons on here they can't get over here all right
let me just go where's my path i'm just gonna fill it in one bloody roach gets a bigger room
than i do and fucker didn't even pay rent all right i will improve on this i need to put some
foliage and stuff around too okay i want to see the cockroach though let's let's go ahead are you
even in there yes you know the funny thing about um enclosures like this you could just have nothing
in here how many times you've gone up to an enclosure like this whether it's like a lizard
or a bug or something and this is not you oh where is he oh he must be under a rock somewhere
there he is what if you just don't put anything in here there he is there he is i want to go over
there all right orbit camera where is he you write oh no right there uh what's that noise
the only people here are the workers why is nobody coming over here
what they're turning around even no one's even go has seen the exhibit yet okay um all right all
right all right no no i gotta i gotta i gotta i gotta keep here i gotta all right i gotta
we're gonna see me to selling point what looks like a bug but isn't a bug giant pandas
rhino no no no no i have to hold on i'm gonna put some maybe it's the type of bug they don't like
i also need some facilities what else we need bathrooms okay we need a um staff room
keeper hut okay i need a keeper hut right that's important except i don't want to put it over here
though let's put it like over this way it has to be close but not in the way but i'm gonna block
it with trees later okay there's a keeper hut guests don't like to see facility buildings
that's all right they're not gonna have to okay looks good this is the final boss room
um okay now uh keeper hut good now i need facilities let's do
make a staff room somewhere oh this is cool a big big triangle okay research center okay uh
workshop planet suit maybe do i need like a workshop maybe one of these like this way
this is just the staff tree that's all this is down here okay quarantine
why can you put it underneath you need power in these buildings don't worry i'll make power
okay vet surgery okay what else we need um trade center i already have one transport rides oh god
no surgery on the roaches yes all right power i'm going green guys that's good pretty good bug
hospital that's right wind turbine all right that's going out here i'm just making the bare
bones right now i'm gonna decorate and everything just wait hold on let's do okay guest facilities
atm okay donation boxes okay let's make this correct now uh chief beef vending machine
it's just cockroaches in here oh you take a look at that side you do you think they're very
interesting would you like to try one staff room scenery rating add scenery items around building
to increase yeah yeah i know prices cockroach burger okay what else we got here a shop guest
spawner what does that mean toilets okay actually i do need toilets we'll put them in the front
uh classic small toilet yeah that's fine let's put these like here over no no let's do it in the
front okay let's do another one classic small toilet well classic large toilet looks good
put the burger put a burger king in your park no that's all good all right here we go small
oh what i didn't know i could do this can i do a double this is all fucked up though let me do
pass and fix this you know that looks like shit that can stay now we're gonna make some foliage
and stuff okay we've got uh beef all right now we're gonna do that looks good let's move this
way i want to do okay exhibit trading no facilities small a classic medium can i do a classic large
exhibit turn get that off will i be able to fit everything in here or no does it have to be small
no no no damn it because this could be a big thing for the spiders let me try it let me see
if it works this would be the spider den all right this is gonna be shrunk okay bring that here
what the fuck right okay wait can i let me go now get off to deselect the damn grid
no we no what the fuck hey stop how okay just get rid of this for a second
so how do i make this go a line to grid right now i want it to like this okay now deselect grid
we'll do a line to grid again here my goodness all right now i should be able to go from here to
there let's get some animals in here so now this can i do how many exhibits are in here
okay what do you think spiders spiders centipedes we're gonna do the huge spider
let's put the spiders here and then we're gonna do centipedes and then we're gonna do
uh scorpions and then we're gonna do how about one of these down here put in more than one insect
titan beetle oh right because i'm only putting one beetle in here i'm putting one insect oh this
place sucks what a waste of space all right goliath beetles right right okay i i feel you
all right so that's good don't we don't need the goliath beetles so now let me go back here
that's why everyone hates this who's in this enclosure right now what do we got uh animals
okay so we got this is a let's put a uh let's okay exhibit trading we need a giant borrowing
cockroach let's do a female this means that they're they're looking for a mate right all
right you got it this is another one how many can you have in one can i buy like 30 at a time
can i put it in here this is going to take forever this 10 13 oh these are all female
okay hold on all right so exhibit has severe social issues the group size is too large
how many uh fuck what do you what's in your thoughts what are they saying hold on there's
no this the ticket price is great i'm beat time to call it a day i'm content with my this staff
room is so far away i'll be worn out by the time i get there the zoo price is great okay it's time
for me to leave zoo ticket price is great no one's even going past the first kiosk
are they gonna finally somebody gonna come over here yeah all right finally we have some we have
some tourists look at them look at the bugs okay cool throw some money in there all right finally
whoa hold on a second here somebody tweeted about this okay okay okay okay okay okay
let's do i gotta fill these with some more um this this is the only attraction that actually pause
all right uh wait this i gotta okay hold on what's in here right now we got uh climate
temperatures what do you mean temperature's not good it's 30 degrees what's wrong with that
too high or too low it's perfect what okay animals let's get another let's get a female
uh are you compatible no what if i have a spider and a beetle can they make like a new animal
okay um let's go to the let's just do two all right that's good right there's social there's
that's still fine okay there's more than one there's more than one there's like a bunch of
these wait wait wait wait wait wait they're going to this wait whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa slow down slow down okay i have to do i wait wait they have no idea what's in here
what is it i don't even know what's in here what's in here oh shit this exhibit sucks
temperature is bad is dead is alive they just see a spider on its back with its legs in the air
okay layout okay temperature what did it want temperature it's too hot what's your ideal
temperature in here what was it what do you want 37 30 you good 25 it's probably 30 no 28 27
protesters were at your zoo already because of exhibit nine what's wrong with exhibit nine
bug protesters
uh i i hold on nobody even knows what's in here okay this is a scorpion so crowded
all right all right all right all right scorpion scorpion that's what's on there right scorpion
why does it look like nothing's happening to this yeah like this one right here scorpion
what they can't i can't put more than one oh they're all fucking dead that's all right all
right this is a titan beetle let's put it over here titan beetle titan beetle all right what's
in here this is a uh giant centipede okay the game is paused how can i be on the phone and this is
the tarantula this one's good looks good all right now i have to take care of this
there's a one female in here this exhibit the layout's terrible and the heat it's way too human
okay you want you want it okay that's really bad you want it really really dry right you're a
scorpion like 10 humidity like 20 humidity please read chat what's what are you talking about
look at you what's wrong what's wrong what's wrong there's no power right okay good call
okay let's go back in here not pre-recorded pog okay this is i'm working on that layout
needs to be changed a little bit you like that better okay that's good hiding place
temperature we're gonna do 20 humidity the temperature is fine let's do a little bit
cooler 35 degrees you're good now what about you how do i feed these things okay welfare
layout what do you want okay it's it's it's way too high you want it to be at about like
33 and like 60 percent humidity okay let's give you a better layout to give you a couple of rocks
there you go you like that nice okay good for you the protesters can leave right when they walked
in the door okay temperature it's way too high i'm this is a desert bug right no it's not what's
right talking about 32 33 78 give you a better layout a couple of rocks and you're good too
right all right play everybody's good now look everybody loves the scorpion that's pretty cool
all right that donation boxes donation donation donations donations pause it look at this huge
crowd of people coming over here right now putting more bugs in here all right let's get a let's get
two more uh bugs in here so let's put a male let's put two males and another female oh right
exhibit okay there we go let's do it again uh where is it back here holy shit there's a giant
scorpion i can't just put it in there why did i not pick the giant scorpion is this too many
this is okay right one more that's four there's four scorpions in here let's get
a couple more titan beetles just let's put two titan beetles in here titan beetle what's in
there right now male female it's a male let's get a female in there okay uh let's put two females in
there and we got in there we got this is centipede centipede is uh says he did everything sucks in
here 30 all right i'll change that real quick all right i think we're good so we got our part one
of our bug world right i don't donation donation donation right right right right right i fucked
up okay i need speakers too to explain this get out of the way i can't tell which way is it facing
this way oh they've arrived no they're gone okay let's see what's playing in here oh this is
wait is this are these powered um no this is actually this is just actual music
people are getting stuck there's too much to see in here they're getting stuck
all right no no no no no no no wait wait wait yeah i don't even have any of those here
wrong zoo oh right oh right they hate being that many together how do i sell them what is coming
is what is like what like mothership is like over us right now these this bug is fine okay now i
gotta i gotta dress this place up a little let's do some benches some foliage um just one of these
is good you know so you can just hang out with the bugs okay same thing over here let's put like a
little spotlight right here two next to each other right one two so now people can actually sit down
and then over here look at this ready check this out and a light post is gonna go right here or not
um no that's okay add a donation thing on every bench uh no i need to i gotta do some
i gotta change some shit here uh nature here we go i'm gonna sneeze really loud
okay plants let's do what's what's kind of buggy bushes that's nice all right now over here we're
gonna do i want some big trees not too big oh this is kind of cool nice okay
i didn't i didn't put me to put like a squid in the tree what do you mean wasteland it's supposed
to be bugs that's this is like bugs making haunted house i'm not making a haunted house
i need like some here we go that looks cool how about this one moss i like the moss looks nice
this is really earthy and interesting this actually sucks well that's we can have different
opinions that's fine i'll do that i'm gonna get some cool lights in here and shit
let's get some big trees back here carpet moss no that's weird oh look at this all right and now
you're gonna tell me that this is not cool it's not cool this is it's too much i think it might
be too much this is too much what is this thing okay wait how about back here no that's it just
doesn't it doesn't work um how about oh i like this no it needs to be bigger than that no bigger
than that bigger than this that's cool no it doesn't fit with the theme that's cool too with
it does this fit with the theme not really right this fits with the theme it's like wooded
what the hell am i gonna do over here no this is too it looks too no no i don't think i even need
it no maybe just a couple of like little brushes just some like little brush no it doesn't fit
with the theme i need a um okay that's all right no that doesn't fit with the theme either let's
go with uh i don't know okay this is three different worlds now do you know what it is
it's got to be broken up back here you know i'm saying like this is gonna be shit over here too
it's gotta be broken up with a few more with like some trees and shit that's the issue that i'm
seeing it needs one mega tree because then i'll put something in here and yeah i mean this is
that's the problem that was the problem okay all right i'll i'll go back to this and finish
whatever was that moss oh ivy oh oh wait hold on cool all right i don't want to hold on i want
to make it so it doesn't now that actually is a haunted house i can't do it don't stop it
no less is more get rid of this one in the middle it's two it's two one two three you know what i
mean get rid of that get rid of this too it's two it's two you know it's like one two one two one
two that's fine there okay that's better i like that this looks like shit but i can't really move
it anywhere i guess could i angle it let me see if i can angle this can i angle it down i guess
that defeats the entire purpose of a solar panel that looks a little better all right so now
all right now it's time to get a real animal in here this is going back here
i'm bringing in something ridiculous i want like how about hmm i want to have like the
what the lemurs are the ones that jump around right yeah okay i want a lemur enclosure like all
over here and i want to have a huge like obstacle course alligators that's not bad either let's do
alligator first all right habitat i need alligator can i do it by animal species okay alligator
what are these called croc is a crocodile or alligator saltwater crocodile there we go so i
need a basic shelter with dimensions shelter with a eat the pumpkin brain all right uh i need the
walls first barrier okay so okay what kind of crocodile not go through just make a hedge maze
concrete what kind of glass that would be kind of cool all right this is gonna go
there's gonna be like a couple of shops here and then it's gonna lead into the alligator
enclosure so i'm gonna say like right here we'll go because there'll be the entrance this way
so i'll go like this across here i wonder how big does it need to be crocodiles are my favorite
bug i think that's all right i should be able to close it up here okay let's get an entrance
out this way oh shoot i'm gonna pull this in so they can look down to the alligators that's
perfect it's too small is it really is it it's gotta be bigger than this is that all right
bigger than this no way no this is huge okay so now i'm gonna get the gate on here habitat gate
there all right now i need all right so this is an alligator habitat what are what are alligators
like what should i have in here like five ten of them okay they need okay source compare mates
all right this is fine this is this is the same thing put 200 gators well i'll put it
just a shitload okay let's just do this male and then female you're in there
i'll do two of these and then two females that's not a gator it's a crocodile isn't it
okay then here we go we'll do uh two uh two so we go there's more are we remaking that game where
every city the city's run off by animals huh all right now i gotta get the environment correct
because what are alligators like i guess i need them to be there first and then pause it
all right well this it's there i need water that's very very clear person's got a really
long run what are they running to oh shit somebody called it an order i gotta run
where are you going someone needs to feed the roaches you run into the bathroom i hope he runs
to the bathroom so far to go oh i need another okay we need more staff rooms oh here we go
here the alligators all right what do you like what's wrong zoo alert keeper hut too small
wait is it this doesn't have any power no fuck okay hold on pause it that's why he had to run
all the way now it looks so ugly that's better okay okay let's uh what we got here low welfare
right okay so let me let me get these are the need what do you guys like you want water
okay let's get rid of this tree because it's useless right now okay you're good for coming
in so we need some we need to dig up some water very important they need critical size or crowding
issues um okay well first of all let's do water terrain uh sculpting so we need to go down
we told you how big does this shit need to be this is like the whole park
i can fix it it's all right all right so let me go to size drop the intensity drop the size
this would be the little the little area over here i can't really see what the fuck i'm doing
how deep does this need to be this looks too deep actually they do want deep water don't they
need more intensity okay how's that maybe a little bit more what does too deep mean for
a crocodile they can swim right that's true yeah that's completely right it's gonna have to be
like 80 of their enclosure right they want to like swim around okay then they can well that's too
much hold on bring that i have to bring this back up okay they need like a place to come out and eat
though flatten to surface oh i like that take this take this out oh i'm making like man-made rocks
no it's gotta go this way stop stop stop stop what the fuck are you doing the size is too big
that's the problem okay here we go it's it's like bumpy and rocky it doesn't have to be perfect
this is huge i think i'm good this is huge this is absolutely massive plus they need a place to
come out and like beach let's see what this looks like all right let's put some water in here
take a look at that perfect a little higher look at that that's pretty beautiful if you ask me
all right now let's give them one of the what do you want what do you want more water
coverage of what coverage plants all right tropical aquatic plants aquatic plants let's do it
cool oh okay uh lily pads let's put some of these on here uh just like just dinner plates
here we go pretty good all right wait you don't like lily pads why do you not like lily pads
what those looked so cool too come on man all right aquatic okay what are you talking about
then asia aquatic a little trees all right i'll put a little tree down here okay coverage one
percent reeds oh you can stick some of these over here like one two some more of these over here
common reeds get this right let's get over here and then spin it around like this
uh okay cool what about this common water lily we're almost there tropical banana plant
banana palm all right we're almost done oh wait this is gonna be the big the big seller here
how about like right against the wall this way no one's gonna be looking this way yeah they will
uh how about like up here i'm thinking like right there right like here in the corner all right
we're 100 we're good all right now i have to feed them wait what about rocks i want some rocks
is that too much it just topples down all right okay okay i'm sorry i'm sorry i just need to see
if it was possible just a little one like one of these just a little rock formation you know
what i mean i don't want to be huge just like that that looks nice okay that's fine what how
cold is it in here in richmond wait wait wait wait wait okay cool all right we got the alligator
enclosure ready we just need some toys take toys enrichment speed food enrichment let's go to
habitat wait wait wait people are starting to notice these alligators okay so what happened
over here okay we need to do a blood scent marker enrichment i don't i don't know where to put this
like over here i don't know anything about alligators like over here okay how about a
food tray large food tray are they gonna eat next to their favorite rocks
let's put another one over here frozen blood pumpkin put that over here next to the blood
tray okay cool what about um a water jet oh cool no water pipe what is this for
did they step on this and pump their own water no they don't how we doing we need a little bit more
mud bath can i fit this over here all right i'm gonna make it a little bigger
uh let's edit this barrier let's take this part off delete that so now i'm going to put a mud
bath up here okay mud bath habitat bedding large oh fuck i need one of these don't i
metal basic shelter basic basic basic how big does this need to be oh god damn it it needs to be
huge uh does that work all right heater um is it all right that looks fine all right i think we're
good how the hell are they doing yeah they're good they seem to be uh comfortable they get
their feeding tray oh i need a sign stop stop stop no no no you kids you're not doing this for free
relax everybody you're not doing this shit for free uh i'm looking for
board can i put a keyboard in there no uh where's it under facilities donation come take a look at
the alligators if you would give some uh money that'd be nice too there's nowhere to view these
alligators from right okay let me fix that now it's gonna be wider than this fuck hold on he's
deleting the highway wider okay that's good let me curve it this way i want to be able to get close
that's a good place to stop then you can turn this way if you want and then bang
something else is over here all right let me take a look how this looks get these donation boxes
out of here move them up here and then up here oh what a what a view there's gonna be a huge
thing up the display up here education board uh habitat education stand guys okay this goes
right here you learn about the crocodiles not i don't want to get anybody's way education board
uh a line to surface okay and on there we got oh look at this it's gonna be perfect
there you go and i need seats i need seats seats seats seats seats uh wait wait wait wait okay and
then i want speakers got it okay many guests think the tickets are underpriced well i didn't
know that the place was even open
in case you want to know about the giant cockroaches
whatever no no no no where is it where can i know i can't do it
here they come here they come they're realizing that they can see it from up here better wait i
need lights like lamp what time is it right now water treatment uh benches benches look at this
fucking 10 000 people can help you right now what is it uh nature habitat what's what would it be
called let me go nice right here no i want it to be why is nobody coming up here no you idiots
there's so much over here go up there it's why it's raining what i mean read chat what's wrong
what what what's wrong they hate the sign your sign is upside down does that matter all right
so what that's why they weren't coming up here because the sign was upside down all right how
is it what's going on staff alerts i can't find a staff room what do you know why i can't find a
staff room where's the staff room oh i need a staff room okay facilities staff room uh large
staff room all right now i can put this over here ready check it out no no they don't like to see
the facilities um this is gonna have to go over here like back here just put it with the other
staff room no it's gonna be spread out okay now i need to uh i wish it was i could see anything
okay whatever that's fine for now does this have power this is power right that's getting hit right
on the line all right we're good i don't have any lights i don't think i can put lights
i think like a grill do they actually sleep in there everybody where they getting the umbrellas
from okay no no no no no okay i got the alligator enclosure now can it be light so i can know what
i'm doing how people still not figured out to go up here you know there's like a whole place to go
and enjoy the alligators from a really cool angle this isn't alive oh here we go people are figuring
it out wait this is gonna be children how much money's gone into this thing 624 dollars have gone
in there nobody cares about the tarantula dude look how many people love this stuff this is cool
oh right i want to do some more stuff here all right um why is the alligator enclosure
suck so bad people need to seriously come here and figure this out just that was a long throw
they'll figure it out eventually that's a staff door get the fuck away from the staff door
the path is not connected yes it is people are walking up how is this not connected
okay i feel like this doesn't this doesn't need to exist but it does all right do they have water
this is water technically right yeah all right the next thing i want to make i'm going to do
we're going to go this way and in here there's going to be two viewing levels of fucking elephants
i have no idea uh i don't need this right now i'm just moving right barrier what do i want to make
here no i want to make the uh the ones i can jump around the lemurs maybe a bunch of flamingos
this used to be roach ranch well not anymore because okay here we go ring-tailed lemurs so
what do they need they need all right uh so africa madagascar tropical biome grade one climb proof
uh doesn't matter what it is grade six semi-transparent not climbable
oh this would be nice because they can now they can turn around look at this way too
this would be cool this would be where they sleep and then i can all right i'm gonna i gotta get
rid of this wait this is an electric fence that'll be all right let us not turn it on all right pause
it for a second how do i tie this okay it's gonna go this way and it'll connect right here
yeah i'll deal with that later it's gonna connect right there and then it can go around and there
we go yeah you got it you understand let's keep going what are you doing this no stop stop what
are you doing so they can look down into the enclosure and they'll be able to see it they'll
be able to jump up and like look at them and stuff right that's big enough for the lemurs i think
yeah oh it needs to be higher well i mean it's not a t-rex so it doesn't need to be that high
no because then they can't see over this no no i want it down here it has to be below this so
they can look in this is a high security lemur all right so there we go now okay lemurs climbable
right okay um i have to build this out oh there's already cool stuff here
holy shit that's awesome oh that's so cool look at how cool this is all right oh it's gonna go
like this in the corner can they jump they go from here to there are they smart enough for that
so how are you supposed to keep them in i want a huge jump no fuck this delete this
okay ready i want it to go from here across the hallway they're gonna do these huge jumps
wait am i i need the long one this is not gonna fall over is it no give me the wizard longest one
six meters there we go the fuck did i do that i better idea how high is i want this to go as high
as i can get it i'm gonna give them an insane diving board that's not what i wanted to do
it's okay whatever i mean that's really dangerous oh how can i make this um this is big this is like
gonna be two or three hundred feet tall are they gonna be like get up here
the whole thing no i gotta change that angle they have to stay in the enclosure oh check this shit
out you guys are gonna lose your minds and you see this one why can you go this high
so instead of building a satellite why can i do this still i should be stopped shouldn't i be
stopped by now honestly why can i keep going is there a skybox oh shit
not rapture what was it called the other one the one that was high and not low
no you can't why is this allowed let's try turning it this way now check this shit already
there's gonna be a huge jump do you think we can make it just do a second zoo up here this is the
lemur portion all right i gotta make it so it's it's doable so it's right here and then that's
doable right and then they can get down all right this is gonna come back into the enclosure
wait where is where is their enclosure oh over there okay god i have to i have to look at this
from like a fucked up angle it's gotta go over here and then back this way because they need to
be able to jump down too okay i'm getting there oh can i make this longer no i have to look at it
from up so that's the only way this is gonna be possible oh man no it's not what if they go the
other way up they won't be able to i've already i thought about that plan already and down i have
to get on there we go okay good almost back in the enclosure how long is this this might be better
actually can i keep going up though unpause for a second what do you mean unpause for a second
oh it stands all right okay close this is a 90 degree drop oh not quite hold on i gotta go
that way i mean if i'm a lemur this is probably the coolest thing i've ever seen in my whole life
oops i mean they want to be up high all right that's good there we go can they make the jump
this is all i care about right now all right what about like from here i can't fucking believe it
can still go up i cannot believe this this i can't believe no this is unbelievable this shouldn't be
able to happen is this broken i don't think it's supposed to be like this i'm making getting over
it yeah yeah i am well i mean it is sandbox mode but this is ridiculous oh wait wait can i
put one of these all the way up here guys i've never seen anything like this before even if the
animal escapes how's how is a vet gonna get up here i think have to climb this we're still going
this is like the magic beanstalk okay i'm getting to the point where i'm not sure i'm gonna i want
to keep doing this we have to watch somebody go up here no lemur is not gonna go all the way up here
i think it's it that's it that's it that's it no it's not no it's not that's not it
it keeps going the fuck oh my god please how high can i no no no no no no it's fucking up
it's just gonna take like 20 minutes to watch your lemur go all the way up here it's getting hairy
hey hey edna okay does the tv work yet maybe just adjust adjust it a little to the left
get rid of this i'm gonna get rid of this part i want one way up okay put food at the very top
that's fucking ridiculous that's ridiculous can i make him sleep up here i think i can make him
sleep up here what are lemurs like all right hold on wait wait let me get rid of this let's do a
big board this is just snapping too much the game's having trouble here okay i need to
yeah good okay good good good good good good just a little bit more
the game's crashing stop no i'll just do one the game i'm actually almost just hard locked right
there oh my god it's so finicky okay we need food so we need uh habitat this is we need lemur right
what the hell is this thing called save it save it i will i will don't
what kind of lemur was it red roughed lemur i want to put a bunch of boxes up here so they can like
throw beach balls and shit over the edge oh come on stop stop stop stop please stop it please
this is gonna be so fun for them okay so now i need food where's the actual food bed and
shelters okay here's the shelter medium okay and then uh water all right it's gonna it is
gonna crash it's gonna crash it's gonna crash i have to save it right now save again done okay
wing-tailed lemur what was it called red roughed lemur ring-tailed lemur that's the same food
though and they have the same toys okay so i need uh another i need a feeding platform
it's gonna be bigger i gotta it's got bigger than this shit okay hold on stop come on don't
got it right there okay good good good good good good good good good good good good perfect
and by the way i'm putting like 50 lemurs inside of this need more access i'll fix it don't worry
feeding stations water station okay i'll fix it okay they can get up here right forage box
toys okay wait block of ice sure they won't be able to get up there why not that was the funniest
thing i've seen all night the wind up there is going to be lethal yeah it's going to be like
a hundred mile per hour winds up here enough air is that gonna put oxygen up here okay all
right i lost it where am i oh my god is it gonna be fucking horrible where is it all right here
we go now i just need to put like 50 to 100 lemurs in here and we're gonna follow them
is it called ring-tailed lemur ring-tailed lemur here we go yes i'll i'll take 50 of them please
what are we talking about what do you mean invalid destination oh i need a door right
i'm gonna fucking lose my mind habitat gate who cares i mean that was kind of cool
oh i like that all right habitat gate let's make them sure they're happy when they're in here
all right ring-tailed lemur ring-tailed lemur i had the game is safe before this so don't
worry when this goes to shit don't worry go ahead 10 okay let's get some females here we go
you used to make a rival tower i can still press this button why can i still press this button
okay this i can't do anymore all right what are lemurs like just so i make sure they they're not
like mad about this okay tropical tropical bio sure okay tropical tropical uh let's give them
some rocks okay are you guys ready oh shit it's raining many guests think tickets are underpriced
well i don't care about that right now diseased animal discovered what do you mean who's diseased
oh and you have salmonella where are my lemurs oh okay here comes a box save it right here
no no make a new safe here they come here come the lemurs so way much of amazon prime delivery
packages uh-oh where are you going where are you off to let's go lemurs they're making their way
who do we follow it's supposed to be like 30 in here oh shit hold on do you even know what's in
here come on look at this cool tower over here this enclosure is huge they don't know what to do
somebody's gonna go up there all right let me make their environment better
hold on wait environment we need some more plants all right tropical biome plants
what i'm planting on rocks god damn it you don't like these what do you like what what what what
what's going on all right pause pause pause pause pause you don't like those okay hold on what do
you like these do you like those you like those right oh you hate all this shit god damn it
okay what do you what do you want welfare enrichment i know you have this enrichment
right over there okay so you like tropical africa got it oh my god uh no that's too big
some over here dig this down to the ground a little bit there all right we're good we're good
you guys what you want that's what you want what else you need climbable area um really you need a
climbable area sure what the fuck are you talking about all right we need short grass long grass
no less long grass and more soil wrong stick they can't climb that type no that's not true
don't even say that i don't believe that i really don't okay what else you guys want social space
whatever enrichment okay it's better than it was before wait javier the titan beetle has died
do you not see what's over here they don't just nothing they haven't seen it yet no climbable
platform climbable logs no these are climbable absolutely they are a new a new lemurs arrived
all right but get over there these are for leopards what no it's because it's raining out
right now that's the problem go on something i think somebody just had it okay hold on move
what do you mean delivery schedule that's the room over there all right look what's right next to you
look at that do you see it it's right here it's climbable and it's cool you have to try it
i'm looking at it come on come on throw them into the tower they're not going to work
what if i go like this hold on hold on okay i have an idea i have an idea everybody hold on
climbable right you know i'm saying how are you doing on enrichment what are we talking about
oh you shit that's a lot of people i just want you to climb this how do you not know how to climb
this toy enrichment it's right here climb it oh shit i locked him in the wood
why won't you climb these god damn it no somebody's gonna jump on it right
are they not old enough can they not climb yet is it like a research thing get leopards
climbable see but it might be this i think this is fucking everything up come on somebody get on
there filter the climbable logs by species yeah they can climb these i think it just went too
high and it's all fucked up uh i mean this is not even part of an enclosure i'm just waiting for
one of them to accidentally jump on it though enrichment come on god damn it no come on get on
these it's outside the fence if that's what it is it could be right so so what do i need to go to
like out oh man no i spent so much time on that it has to work once it has to work one time
i'm just trying to keep it i'm trying to make it so the when it goes up it stays in the enclosure
maybe if i go across this way it'll do it it'll do it i mean is that in it looks like it's out
right here it's got to be like the whole park it's saved it's saved the game is saved it's
saved it's saved don't worry it's saved i need to see if this works no if the game is saved the
game saved don't worry how do i get rid of an animal how do i get rid of an animal just leave
it and forget it but i need this to come out i need to see if this works i need to get these
alligators to go for a minute just get out of the way the game crashed i mean whatever for the best
no oh the lemur pole come on maybe if i load it back it'll be all right that's that's a good
idea i want to see them climb the tower i want to see them climb tower too you know what i mean the
thing i was just trying to say just move a lemur up there i don't think i can why is my planet
coaster isn't turning on anymore what is what this new steam sucks new steam is like battle net
all right here it comes or maybe not maybe it'll uh maybe it will never open up again
i'm so sad right now i really thought we were going to see the ultimate lemur feet of strength
make a new tower from scratch with lemurs in so you can make sure it works
fuck but fuck fuck right like that sucks if that's what i gotta do but that sucks i gotta
pee too i haven't gone to the bathroom i should have did that from the start but i got i got super
into it okay where's my uh was it roach ranch did i save it before the tower
this looks correct okay so here's what i have to do everybody's gonna be really we're gonna be
this is sad serious injury discovered he's the animal all right all right all right all right
load game load load load load load zoo it was tower yes it was this one so i'm going to
just i'm gonna delete the tower oh but look at how cool this is beach ball fell off no
this is so sad it really is but it's terrifying it's terrible but i have to do this i'm sorry
everybody i'm sorry we need to do it yeah it sucks okay all right just pretend it didn't happen
here we're gonna go here we go all right so that didn't happen this did not happen nothing happened
blueprint a tower can i do though all right here we go i'm gonna put some lemurs in here let's get
one in here uh let's go for it animal trading it's okay ring-tailed lemur invalid dedicated
to the door i remember this part and you know that's it i edit this whole barrier this is wrong too
this is electric fence all right this is going to be what is it about wood just concrete concrete
glass okay good done so now this is this is normal now this is not
fucked up let's get a lemur in here let's get a door on here first please
okay cool lemur we're gonna start small i pee so bad but i can't stop playing this i'm gonna pee
my pants who cares whatever right it's my i'm in my own house what is it ring-tailed lemur come on
in let's just do one terrain no not terrain i need this to be soil right habitat okay no no no
how do i do just where is it the hell is it god damn it i gotta go to the bathroom
fuck okay i'll be right back i'll be right back i'll be right back just chill i'll be right back
pause in the game oh you know when you when you're peeing and it just will not stop i hate that
that's the worst you do a full piss and after you're done yeah i'm done i'm done peeing it's
over i know how that feels it's just still going and then it starts again and you're just sitting
there going like let's go hurry up i i'm just i'm just sitting here it's boring you should see a
doctor i've been to the doctor like 15 times in the last like six months i've been there plenty
of times don't you worry thanks for the information i just been looking out for you guys all right so
where we last left off uh hold on i've got to make a text here
okay let's go i was gonna get a lemur in here and then i was gonna what was i gonna do i don't
remember oh yeah i was gonna change it let's just get the lemur in here first lemur incoming we will
slowly work on their habitat what happened to the tree house uh it was a waste of time because they
wouldn't climb it because i broke the game but now okay here we go in richmond it may have been the
food on top too i don't know let's do uh let's pause it okay habitat this is we're looking for
a ring-tailed lemur cool uh let's we got a feeding a little feeding zone over here
over by the inevitable tower cool let's put like two of them and then let's do um water you know
some water bowls okay we'll get the feeding stations water stations uh their welfare let's
take a look there so we want some uh africa tropical tropical africa cool okay and we're
gonna slowly do this correctly that looks nice a little tree coming in from there nice cool all
right we'll put one of these over here i'm just trying to do this correct some bushes bushes over
here almost there more coverage some of the bigger ones okay nice let's do one more here
now your terrain shelter space is critically insufficient terrain is wrong it's grass and
soil so we need a shitload of soil soil light make this huge and just do the whole damn thing
okay good short grass perfect shelter where is your shelter here it is a basic shelter
very nice place to sleep what's wrong with this what's wrong with this why is it still zero
how's that zero they want privacy where's this lemur where are you okay now habitat's fine okay
enrichment yeah that's fine okay enrichment here we go i'm gonna start right here
let's see if this does anything pause it climbing climbable log climbable log
where's the 10 foot one two meters this is one six meters here we go does it show up
no why why is this doesn't why does it not work this is for it's not a little ring-tailed lemur
look so what the fuck climb it all right so climb it climbing isn't enrichment well you're good
to go okay so hold on it's it's probably because it's raining it's definitely because it's raining
right is that really what it was all right it's a sunny day what are you doing do something have
fun all right oh wait wait wait wait wait okay where you going cool okay he just doesn't want
to do exercise maybe he'll eat put in more let's get some more the second that one of
them decides to climb i'm pausing it and doing a tower to the sky look i have these things here
too all right let's get a couple more in here pretty lemurs two just like four of them that's
all we need let's do like two females and then i don't know one another male one more male
that's good to me are you climbing wait all right come on go for it somebody climb this
fucking pole please how okay wait other animals need to be seen because the person's okay i thought
that somebody just walked in here okay somebody climb please go somebody have some fun do something
fun are you gonna go for fun check the climbable okay all right all right all right stay there stay
this don't move don't move don't move here we go we got a raid oh we did lazy purple thanks to the
raid that's the name i haven't heard in a long time thanks ladies purple appreciate that that's
going all the way back team fortress too damn well hopefully you uh hope your stream was good
i'm not sure what you were doing but we're doing uh welcome everybody we are doing uh well this is
planet zoo but it's not really planet zoo it's called giant cat tower if you stick around for
like another 45 minutes to two hours you might see the outcome of how it works but thank you
welcome everybody let's see if i can make this happen you're the one you're the chosen one here
we go where is it habitat climbable here we go climbable log six meters let's do this right
let's get it right fucking in front of you here we go why did this turn away all right this has
to be perfect how can i get this to be perfect angle snap yep i gotta make sure this is going
in a straight line up this actually not gonna be too bad i can do two at a time
um free to time actually this is gonna take way less time is it leaning no it's not i can fix it
is it leaning no it's not is it leaning is it leaning i can't tell are you lying to me
no it's not leaning it's fine i had it too shouldn't have listened okay i gotta get like
this is where it gets hard somebody's gonna do this i guarantee it wait see if that it actually
climbs it um good idea did it go up did it go up i can't see is it dark like it's too dark i can't
see did it go up it's so dark out right now i i don't know where he is why is the zoo open at
like two o'clock in the fucking morning let me see tell me if you see any movement oh get oh my god
what happened oh okay what all right somebody get up there and climb that please don't make this be
a complete waste of my time any more lemurs in here come on get up there please i just need you
to climb it they're not dead they're fine they're over here playing around
oh it looked like you were going over to it they need incentive it's not gonna be leopards are not
gonna climb it fuck i'm so disappointed make some platforms i'll try that one climbed up earlier
yeah i know that's why it's like it's definitely possible now let's do some platforms climbable
ramp or a climbable platform because somebody get over here and just climb that and like
go from here to here and there to there right somebody just do it it's raining again no it
ain't raining again because i say so how do i turn this off all right i'm giving this like
30 to 40 more seconds and then i'm moving on get right all this shit oh this is possible
thinking about it thinking about it thinking about it thinking about it where are you going
no do that over here over this way you idiot why would the other lemurs so much more climbing
they climbed they climb so where do you go what the animals are all died well this is
all right i'm done and then i tried to make the tower and none of them want to climb it they
don't want even go over here we had lemurs in the last game and all they did was jump around in
circles all right back to the real game it's so disappointing when you try to do something
like that it just fucking doesn't play out it's disappointing it's a zoo not a circus i know
all right i'm still doing lemurs oh fuck i forgot it was here still
somebody climb it please climb it i need you to climb it please all right hold on
there's a diseased animal we have a vet right all right i gotta check around and make sure
everything's all right let's take a look at the animal list what's going on here all right all
the all the bugs are in bad shape it's because they all hate the environment i know well i'm
gonna release half of them into the wild so who cares it's this one they don't like to be together
there are too many giant cockroaches in here so i'm gonna get rid of them
what beetle diet dude that one's fine all right yeah i'm gonna get in here and i'm gonna delete
half these beetles okay release to the wild wait did i just let them out of the cage is that all
i did all right there's still a problem socially in here why how many are in here
there's so many in there
15 15 15 15 all right we'll keep like two in here better all right now we're good back here
uh everyone else is okay everyone's happy a beetle did just die what is that well i was
smoking what's going on call mechanic over here please the person had 10 umbrellas
what's wrong now tickets are underpriced okay not anymore all right so i have this i have my
this is this is the lemur place and it's all it's just too it's too much i'm going to keep this
in the very rare event that the lemurs actually give a shit and do something with it so we're
going to do an actual lemur in enclosure we're going to delete this business electric fence still
okay this can't be electrical do leopards instead or with chimps
what's the hold on wait we're like an orangutan climb that
no you guys got me stuck on this shit all right hold on i'm really quiet what shouldn't be
maybe i am i'm also just leaning back to do leopards or chimps all right i'm gonna do
chimpanzees god damn it all right no no no no no this is just gonna this is gonna be a chimpanzee
enclosure that happens to have a huge tower okay cut it off here this is too big or we're done now
it's not so huge it's gonna be a chimpanzee enclosure maybe even a little bit smaller from
like here to here that's good make the walls bigger i'm gonna select everything up like i
don't know five feet 10 feet whatever five meters that's fine chip is gonna just break through the
shoulder tack of the glass and smash it open make it as tall as the tower i can't do that
that's not possible so sorry okay now uh we need some can chimpanzees climb that
let's just check it this is for a chimpanzee western chimpanzee okay they can climb this
okay okay it's possible
reinforced concrete what thing climbs the most out of anything in the whole game bonobo bonobos
reinforced concrete okay good so now i need bonobo make the habitat small so i don't have
anywhere else to go this is fine okay you see a bonobo please work i'm like gonna lose my mind
okay we need we have one here we go invalid destiny because i need a damn door or whatever
put food at the top of the tower we let me just see if they'll even go on it first
i by the way i have so much guys you have no idea how bad i hope this works
more than anything this has to work i can't even select this shit it's too far i'm too
damn it put food at top now i'll put like toys and shit at the top how do i get rid of these
beach balls no i want to get rid of the beach balls not the whole thing in game price get rid
of the i want to get rid of this so bad advanced how do i just i can't i can't even select this
shit does this cardboard boxes up here permanently
that's not even correct
no no i didn't stop everybody stopped i have to stop this they i need to even see if it works
no i'm not i'm trying to move on but i can't move on i'm just trying to make a chimpanzee
enclosure if they climb it they climb it i don't fucking care what's going on
tickets are overpriced now okay well sorry there now what it's a power source failing
well get up there i can't can you knock it up you can't get it well how are we supposed to
it's gonna get on the roof get on the roof why can you not get on the roof it's a solar panel
what's it how do i go up cute motherfucker i can't why can i not turn it i don't wait just set it on
the ground can i get like the terminator vision turned off i don't i don't ever want to see that
again it's gotta be the other way i thought a solar panel had to be like on top that's so ugly
why can't it spin i can't turn why can i not turn this i can't i i can't turn it i cannot spin this
it's just facing this way permanently it has to face the sun all right holy shit finally i can
use okay all right all right all right all right right right can you leave me alone now please
all right don't ever change from night i just stay daytime permanent how do i can i make it so
it's never nighttime ever again this goddamn sandbox mode no i didn't want to he thinks he's
god all right what happened to the alligator sign got that in here
this is not powered anymore two springs why for that too all right i guess this too
too where is everybody all right don't worry they'll come chimpanzees or uh bonagos animal
trading let's do this again oh fucking god damn it nobody wanted to look at dead bugs okay that's
fine okay you let's go two of you add two females i think oh is it female all right wait wait wait
what did i just put in there what did i just put in there uh and you looking good okay i need them
to come in then i'm going to do some i'm going to dress it up multiple animals have low welfare
oh come on what's wrong here well nutrition social health the group size is too large what
do you mean it's too large aren't there like two in here how many are in here this 13 scorpions in
here they've been having children oh all right well get get rid of some of them uh who's the
coolest one all right you you can leave all right get out see you later now what else is wrong
the humidity is okay raise the humidity a little bit 25 24 24 23 cool all right it's good cool
exhibit this exhibit urgently needs to be cleaned well get somebody over there that's not my ball
that's not my problem all right what do you like and what do you not like social enrichment habitat
you want climbable area i've already got a shitload of it but apparently that doesn't matter
all right so we don't we need grass and soil they don't like long grass so we don't want short grass
and soil okay and then what's next they like um tropical africa sure uh oh that's cool you
don't like these tropical africa tropical africa you don't like this okay
um where are you would you go okay social habitat you actually i'm done
enrichment toys this is the wrong animal okay feeding platform you can just eat like around the
tree some water very nice we need to have some toys for you so what do you what do you like for
toys better tv reception what oh that i made that right okay i was like what the fuck is this
now you're not even gonna use this what do you want is that what is zero percent enrichment
termite mound toys grab ball how many more of these do you want
well this guy's got a lot of toys go for it go for it you know you want to go for it please
okay so now social all right you need we need more what the hell is that why is there a fox in here
here what what did you get in here how did you get in here who is this person
oh i didn't it's a panda free the panda how did it get injured okay you're fine
okay you happy more insufficient size what do you mean insufficient size
copy paste 20 of those towers eventually somebody's gonna touch it
boys and girls i think we got it is it time finally what it's just an enclosure
what is the crocodiles getting birth it's dead oh oh wait that which one just had the baby
it's a lot of people standing here i'm gonna laugh my ass off i scroll up
with chimpanzees i can't stop like laughing i'm like seriously turning into the goddamn
rats from uh roger rabbit the weasels okay get a vet over there someone's going up there
eventually it's gonna happen i know it is all right the enclosure is too big well here move
over here but it's too how is it too small this is huge this place is enormous let's go this way
all right i'm gonna say like here all right now that's small now i just have to change this
all right this doesn't lead to anything anymore so get rid of it
that okay fine so is that better now that it's not as huge so that should work right
better no social group too few adults in jupy too few you want more
let him out let him out of here let him out what are you doing why is he trapped in the box
relocating what free him i i need another couple of uh we need some more adults right okay i can't
free him what am i supposed to do the mouse isn't centered again why does he keep doing this
i seriously why can i not get unbox him do something do something well i'm trying to get
one of i'm trying to get a vet in here where's it oh god just hire a bunch of people sprinting in
diseased animal where what's wrong with you why are you diseased who's injured
seriously injured who do you have unbox all animals where are they taking
why i just hired like fucking 10 people why is everybody running away what
how did they all get so sick disease serious injury serious injury what what did you even do
two habitat one cleanliness call keeper and a mechanic and a vet get all three of them
get in here good you sprayed some leaves nice work will you check out what's going on in here
now what can't find accessible vet surgery how many surgeries have to take place
do i have a hospital what the fuck was that
that was so scary all right move this move this move this move this
okay all right all right this is the hospital do how many do i need another hospital
fucking god is because this shit i thought you had to have these on top god i thought you had this
solar panel i thought it had to be on whatever okay um walked outside of habitat for too long
oh okay where are they bringing all these animals right now
this is a spider convention this is so
they're running back and forth where are you going
what's going on over here
please fix them fix it anyway where's my power thing this one is not caught by anything god
damn it okay move this oh yeah yeah it's the only person in the whole world that cares about the
cockroach everybody's over at the spider no nobody's listening at all you just came back
how can you be diseased again what do you what does this mean research research illnesses
oh my god okay just some get on it get on it get on it oh right research complete oh okay
uh so social i know we need to where are the other animals okay here they come
he's lying on the ground oh no okay animals hungry what have you not eaten food oh my fucking god
nope there's just sprinting around they have to go after i need more i don't have any security
feed them please wait what did you okay are you healed okay space nutrition social we need more
of those monkeys come back just buy more monkeys no they're okay so what's good what's wrong here
they don't have enough climbing area okay well sure i'll add some is that okay now okay that
counts somebody's gonna accidentally jump on that there you go here's their whole area someone's
gonna actually they're gonna accidentally jump on this and go shelter oh fuck they don't have any
beds oh right okay that was a mistake okay shit that's why that's the that's the problem
no beds oh my god is this a field trip why there's so many people coming up here
it's up it's not ready okay we got enough all right they're all happy now put some beds
okay maybe they'll be happy now all right not terrible but you have you have a disease again
i'm just uh animal is hungry why won't somebody feed
get in there hurry the fuck up and feed them i need to wait okay wait wait this is important
pause it and i need a key a kiosk because seriously there's so many look i need a donation
thing or an information booth here at least like a education board advanced movement get
now you know i appreciate the actual lizard vision that they give you
no god damn it i really love the change to dog eyes cam oh i don't care oh fucking god damn it
gives a shit where where are my controls for this don't i have a list of controls where they go
usually it's in the corner where the hell is it where where are my controls to like rotate and
snapping and where the fuck is it why is it not here i don't even care whatever i just need
electricity to go over here i think apparently lost i lost my lower right ui panel hold on
facilities power first let's do some speakers over here and over here okay power why do they
put power in this game doesn't have fucking utilities really i could put like transformers
around whatever i don't care he's joining the dark side but why do i have to put like
power connections that wasn't a planet coaster it's it's just like a middleman all right i don't
know i think the screen is actually fucking i don't care you're gonna have to lean forward
you have to lean forward and like turn your neck this way it's it's for the monkeys all right
we're gonna put tv shows on there we're gonna just give them a netflix remote and see whatever they
put on who cares uh i 5 000 bits just came in from yes is online thank you for the 5 000 bits
say monkey will climb if you believe in it go monkey go just turn on my stream okay well they
have information here now cool where did you go do it come on do it look at how cool this
that it connects now someone's gonna do it i guarantee it let me just do this let me connect
it over here are they doing that okay now they're all connected all right so what was what's what's
going on here how you guys doing you want uh too few adults i can throw a couple more in there
let's close this let me see what else is going on in the park oh donation i didn't do a donation
thing that could have been a thousand dollars already give me some money give me some money
well not you guys now this looks like it's okay quantity are the keepers even coming in here this
is a keeper right here we haven't got anywhere to prepare the animals food what are you even talking
about this food here on open up what are you why are they in boxes that guy came in here
and dropped him in here okay keeper hut let's do classic large keeper hut let's put it this way
away from everything we'll connect it down here can that reach the solar i'll just put another one
this needs power and this needs to come down uh go back well i'm just gonna wrap this around
this is temporary rare pepe thanks for the five community subs
thanks loving dodged i need to put another power source here
i'll be climbing won't you be stupid enough to do it they keep getting diseased i need someone
to research this listeriosis research complete so what the hell is the problem
oh it's already done adventure mf dan thanks for the five subs appreciate it dan
those power sources failed clean this just get them all in there again another five subs from
volemy five five five five back to back to back to back to back to back thank you guys seriously
all right i need to open up fix that habitat so i need someone to clean this
maintenance time since last minute has nobody gone in here you have no keepers assigned to a
work zone containing this habitat why is nobody going in here all right let's get a couple more
monkeys in here am i insane or do the music just get louder for the last like 30 minutes
five more subs from david saved it thank you david thanks for saving it thank you oh and here
we come out flinzenberg five community subs thank you flinzenberg they're looking all right
you're just hanging out up there maybe you'll get adventurous and actually try eventually i don't
know that's it's all right we're doing fine this needs to be cleaned get the fuck in there
where are you and why are you doing this get in here yes is online five community subs
midna thanks for the five community subs you open the door and then walked out
there's another one good thank you david saved it thank you guys thank you for the huge amount
of community subs high amounts of litter i have like so many people in this zoo how much let me
look at my staff i have nine keepers seven vets three vendors some more caretakers
volemy five more community subs eased waffles five community subs
thanks both of you seriously thank you more it's happening again here it goes again
these are power right two staff rooms these things still will not be cleaned
you won't somebody clean this fucking habitat what do you do something he's scared of the
alligators we're five more from adventure mf dan thank you dan do i have to clean the water
please come on oh i was thinking it might be possible okay so i i have no idea why this won't
happen why there's something wrong here i don't know why a keeper has come in here like 10 times
isn't with his one in here now and he's just leaving water treatment maybe maybe that's right
water treatment i'm not supposed to put this in the enclosure with them obstructed i can't
oh shit what the fuck did i just do
well let me move it down let me see well it's still hitting it so although i need it i guess
it is fine over here no because they need to be able to get to it is that good enough down like
here let's see if that's okay i guess i it's treating this body of water all right although
i need to like obstruct this stuff more community subs five more from rare pepe body lotion thank
you thanks a lot guys okay how are they doing you guys are doing okay right social maybe a
little bit more space something this is without power somehow what building is this uh i will
put in more power in then i need power solar put the solar panel back here doesn't really matter
does it not really it has to be connected to a road eventually here all right good cool all right
wait you're gonna have a kid where when hey look there you are cool that's good
there's a problem there's a problem social here great canadian fuck club thanks for the five
community subs uh did you have a turtle who brought this giant turtle in here
i need some turtle toys what is this thing a galapagos
why can this climb no look here have some stew what the fuck is that they seem to not
really give a shit do the monkeys are the monkeys mad where the tortoise is in here
i think it's okay all right uh let's i want a new animal i want a dangerous animal let's see
elephants somebody's give 20 community subs shady seas that just gave 20 community subs right now
thank you that's a drop right there that's a big one more turtles um
um bears pandas gradually bears whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what this 21 notifications
what happened what happened what happened animals stressed and trying to hide what happened
are you better off somewhere else who can you hold on oh that makes sense
get me out of here get me away from these monkeys
i'm gonna get up here
he was trying to get away so fast all right so he belongs with like the alligator
they're both reptiles you need better enrichment in it see you look at the stress is going back
see all right we need some food in here for the turtle stress is being reduced what are you guys
talking about we just need a turtle feeding thing okay food uh food and water yeah look just a
little like turtle eating zone over here okay a little water bowl okay social is moderate social
is all right he needs a shelter though we need a turtle shelter uh just have a little bed
so over here away from the fucking alligators you don't have a shelter right is that not big enough
extra large no he wants less uh grass that's fine all right we'll do less good there's a lot
of baby alligators in here tower tower tower tower what about it there's nothing here guys
i need less uh long grass more short grass better okay i need a shelter for you though
for some reason i can't who's been in a box
now what's going on with the scorpions you've you've had more 19 children all right you guys
got to relax seriously
shit
what happened to it why is this going on animals is de-stressed oh i need more toys
toys and ritual here look a little ball look see you like ball oops you like ball see see you like
balls see this doesn't bad it's the animal is social welfare issue it's an alligator
um protesters have arrived at the zoo all right just but when why is he not stressed anymore
look at how big this alligator has been i didn't realize how huge that was uh all right we'll make
a tortoise enclosure all right we'll get you out of here we'll make that over here check tower
it's not gonna happen it's not gonna happen this will never happen all right tortoise enclosure
it's gonna be just over here just one uh the protesters are here for the bugs i did i don't
even know where they are where are the protesters oh here they are i guess they got what they wanted
i don't know okay this is still okay um where's the tortoise all right i gotta get you out here
pause the game i need a barrier i'm gonna do enclosure over here just a small one for the
tortoise just like a little what tortoise is like but it's class right all right nice all right
that's good let's move them there we go let's add some more pathing over here so we can look
that's uh interesting pathing right okay that's i don't care all right let's get him in here and
let's make him a little fun home come here antonio i'm coming to get you we're doing
monkeys are doing fine how many i got a thousand people here i think i broke a record all right so
the tortoise wants once it's delivered we'll make a little nice and closer anything's better than
being with crocodiles right here you go tropical south and central america will make you happy
let's do tropical not africa tropical and south oh you like lily pads okay cool i like you uh you
don't like this but there's nothing that's not in here all right let's do a little bit of water
just a little pond just for you to check out and hang out if you feel like it you don't have to
no pressure pressure at all so that's fine that's just a little pond for you
okay look at that and we're gonna give you
uh what do you like for terrain right some sand right over your little beachfront
so let's do some uh sand there we go see better already short grass perfect a little more sand
yeah yeah some more sand back here all right so you got your little beach zone that's good you
need a shelter what about environment you love it we could get some plants though yeah let's
get some plants take a look at this ready i'm gonna get a little lily pads this is huge that's ugly
okay better and um
look at this look at that it's perfect for you he's gonna love it give you a little apple tree
over here there we are that's all you need maybe some rocks too no all right now you need a shelter
you also need some enrichment which is in habitat all right galapagos tortoise
beds and shelters why is this in shelters okay there's a little spot to sleep food and water
here you go a little medium uh we'll put this over here because you want to be able to relax
over there you can eat over here right in the corner and we'll give you a water pipe
no just a little dog bowl right here right there ah okay good now you need some toys
a ball right cool and then a fruit spike back here near your bed and a scent marker back here
no what about your bed and a sprinkler what's going on here
and a ball why is your enrichment not going up oh because you need to see it okay he loves it look
he loves it oh he wants some friends no actually he doesn't want any friends
it's his own little paradise he's good to go he's very happy
what are you two doing
uh tower check you can't go in there look this is starting to turn into a zoo
okay oh i need a little tortoise thing right there okay uh what is it called education
i would have not just be facing them correctly why is it facing out why is it facing out by default
okay i spent the other damn way control alt how do i flip it how do i flip this damn thing
z is just rotate how do i x c that's fine turtle donations there you go are you gonna go to sleep
has there been any no no notifications things are going well tigers next
oh
whoa more offspring how many are here now seems like a lot
13 that's not bad maybe we'll send uh on the sneeze
is he still building towers no not anymore i tried and i failed now you on your hand all
right you guys are doing fine all right new animal i'm thinking like an elephant enclosure
or something over here gave up on the dream uh no i'm i tried to build another thing for them
to go up on to maybe the ai would accidentally go up this all right what's another animal that
i want in here lions tigers do rats i don't think there are rats in this game 13 yeah let's do west
african lion all right sounds good
where the where the monkey why would it why does it do that it puts them all in a box and
stuffs them in the front of the whatever something's wrong power source is failing
shit i forgot about this where's it's right there okay this range sucks i know it's ugly
but what do you want to do you're still making roach ranch well this is yeah this is what i
started with now that's never gonna happen all right uh lions so what do lions need make a swing
on the top of the tower they won't even go up there they won't even go up there all right i'm
gonna assume that i'm gonna need something very hefty like a not concrete what about um brick
wood there's brick they're lions not rhinos but they're strong so it's well they can i chain link
fans i know they're gonna climb out i know they are but save it all right all right all right all
right all right i got it i got it i'm gonna call this one so i know what the hell's going on
all right let's do brick let's make this not huge that's plenty big i think maybe like a triangle
okay and then we'll have the viewing area be over here yeah the end the okay the entrance
for the vet will be right here and then the viewing angle is going to be glass it's going
to be right here this too okay diseased animal who oh no it's running a baby hurry i'm obsessed
all right i can't do that it needs to be like at least three meters tall yeah so they won't
jump over this that's a good viewing area okay so that's done let's get some lions in here
like six or like four two males two females there we go thirteen thousand dollars
all right that's why it's doing this shit why it's like defaults to another animal
yeah why can't it just be the animal i just had the heck are you doing okay this one here
let's just have two maybe one female all right i gotta be careful here because let me get
big today he's fucking huge he's injured why did you give me an injured one
you dropped him too hard man okay let's see what you want terrain so you want tons of grass
and a bunch of rock okay so it's short grass bring up the size here do the whole thing short
grass because you don't like long grass at all all right so now we're going to do a little bit of
soil over on the side here just a little bit just not just a tad just a taste that's a taste
and then where's rock you want a lot of rock too much too much rock leave that in the soil
all right germa a capybara germa a capybara germa a capybara what is it please what's that
get a little rough rock over here i think it's a long grass over here environment you like it
grasslands africa yeah we got some already grasslands flipped out of the window
game soft oh all right uh how about one of these over here let's do some nettle along the along the
rocks over here they don't you don't want that much they don't want that much that's good enough
maybe one more tree oh no they're gonna hate this no they'll hate this there's some shade over here
that's good i'm done maybe a giant tower oh maybe that wouldn't be a bad idea i think
all right food species last frozen blood pumpkin here goes a little blood tree
now we need to actually here we go take a look at this that's huge never mind this is too big
i mean this is too this is way too big how many are in here four well wait wait wait
viewing angle viewing angle hold on a second here i gotta rethink this it's not perfect i
can't get it perfect shit it's not gonna be perfect ever i'm gonna make it it has to be
flush hold on rotation fuck off whatever okay good so then people can go see people can see them
sleep that's good facilities now we need uh i can actually play social group i know you want some
people to come over here and you're injured i don't even know how that happened oh we need some toys
right let's get some toys in here here's a little pinata they can play with that in
here people think it's fun and interesting scratching board uh put scratching board back
here so they can play around that looks good okay okay good why is there enrichment still though
enrichment all right fire hose ball does that do no idea i thought he was about to just leap over
that was like a here comes the jump over the fence and a scratching post nice okay and we need some
feeding places this is kind of concerning me they can't jump over this right serious injury
discovered he didn't even do anything okay food what do you mean two injuries what what's what
happened what are the bones made out of like glass tubes why would they be seriously injured
uh okay sure all right we need a viewing angle here oh i need uh bedding and food shit uh food
and water here we go food tray let him watch me that's cool you know that's interesting
let's do two food trays and then a water pipe right here no no no no no no no no no no no
all right good tickets are underpriced well i got lines now so let's go with like 20 bucks
your cockroach just had osprey now i got 1100 people here all right i gotta wait wait wait
path path let's go this way over here widen this is gonna be a huge deal for everybody
wider shit wrong wrong wrong wrong redo it are you delivering them like you have packages what are
we doing is there no power here what is the problem the door the door is blocked nobody can
get in good joke why would you put it here why would you put the lion here there's no reason
for you to do that just go invalid destination quarantine any more workers i have like a thousand
workers okay uh veterinarian are they are you still in a box did they did it just bring the
box inside so they're just in a box inside the quarantine building how do i take them out no
that's wrong where it's in here why are they in transit to habitat but weren't they injured
i have no idea what's going on okay um there's one line in here right just hanging out yeah
right okay very i gotta now i need uh education board i'm sure it's facing the right direction
this time there we go so you say you injured no you're not all right so just keep them in here
release the roaches
roaches there we are is your info
is the other one i don't get there only three in here right okay
fighting fighting for alpha status who gets it
you're saying left to right left to right left to right right right
right
yeah
that has to be worth a lot of money hold on hold on i gotta answer this
i gotta go open the door hold on i gotta have the door go back dude pizza party
i had to look inside what i missed
falling out of the tree okay oh cool some speakers here learn about the lions
that's really fucking loud but it kind of works no that's gonna annoy the lines here put on a pizza
can i don't have a pizza can what's going on here they fought again who's the alpha
all right so that's good uh how's everything how everybody i got 1400 people in the park
it's coming together uh just uh chimp check that looks good very cool okay i'm gonna expand out
this way i could do something a little here but i'm gonna go this way make people part of the
exhibit turtle all right hey he's all right how you doing he's happy i'm gonna need more toilets
all right where's the where's the toilet over here there we go not as popular as i thought
it was gonna be it's not as popular as uh spider but what about let's come back here
alligator how much money have the alligators made a lot no wait does this mean this person's very
dumb this is like a low education or something what's that mean it actually is what that means
holy shit everybody's a fucking idiot all right okay i guess you know what you know i'll tell you
i think all the smart people are gonna be with my bugs even stupider wait hold on this person
okay uh let's do another enclosure i think there needs to be something more back here besides just
the uh the monkeys you know i mean it's really cool people can hang out up here and
all right that's fucked up but it's okay it's for them anyway all right well do the rats so you can
either go you can stay here or you can come no we'll put it right here it'll go right here
that'll fit right should they definitely don't need anything they need like a chain link fence
or like a wood wood logs chain link fence they have rats for god's sake looks good
entrance over
well it's gonna be people looking down no it's gonna be here this way i'll fix it in a minute
no let's do it now that's way too thick thin it out a little jeremy thin it out a little
because then we'll wrap this around okay because then there's a little staff room here
although they have to go a long way to get in here all right oh fuck them whatever they figure
it out so then this is the viewing angle let's get some rats in here something here already
did he throw shit over the fence okay whatever you say at least they have fun on this one all
right uh is it other pigs instead i kind of want to do pigs instead anybody like objecting to this
camel tiger little beast bongo cheetah
what what's their way um a bot what's it called a barra happy bar
a c where is it it's a cafe bar that's a cafe bar oh you guys are just debating
oh okay lizards wolves oh yeah gorillas okay a gorilla uh two gorillas what are gorillas like
what's what's wrong fighting they're still fighting in here for alpha status
you think what had happened already this is a really bad design
i feel like these are everybody that's standing around waiting for the airplane
for their row to be called sit down okay i hate that shit let me look at my plane ticket where
i'm in i'm in uh group c what they just call group a i may as well stand in front of everybody
oh well i'll be i'll be standing here for about another 25 minutes all right let's uh fighting
due to incorrect sex fighting due to incorrect sex ratio what does that mean
i didn't know the female in here one of them's not having sex okay diseased animal
all right all right all right wait wait i'll get another female uh and okay here we go there
my low welfare for the gorillas oh shit right why are they always injured when they come out of the
box okay i'm gonna need long grass no don't want long grass we need rocks and i mean you need short
grass short grass just put it over here
climbable area okay fighting due to incorrect this still fighting okay look look what i got whoa
where'd he go where's the other lion oh he's over there serious injury discovered and not and
diseased i don't know why they always uh diseased all right well let's do let's get them happy this
is tropical africa tropical and we need wild plants you got it okay let's put some ferns
okay bird nest fern that looks good a huge tree too many huge trees
i need smaller stuff smaller scale okay a little custard bush
vines no they don't like the vines
whatever no it's too huge and annoying there oh that looks nice i like it already
well they both tickets are underpriced still all right we'll go 28 15 for kids disease animal
okay rotavirus nice they're tossing tons of money because they get a really good view
look at that how much is taking is taking in nine thousand one hundred and ninety five dollars
holy shit wow 5,500 bucks in comparison this is like the titan beetle all right that's bringing in
big money all right where's the gorilla uh and camera i hear protesters where you going
what animals infected yeah well i'm sorry but they they got delivered to me injured
block him block him block him block him let's get carrying around there's more fighting i don't see
anybody fighting i see people lying around are they all alive animals hungry all right all right
how okay you just hate everything here critical size or crowding issues critical crowding
okay well you can climb okay hold on wait wait i haven't saved the game in a while
i just saved the game shit okay i gotta i have to take care of this now okay so uh where is he
going they don't know he's out they don't know he's out i can fix this but first of all how do
you like the place it's all right okay in richmond we need some toys toys here we go a little um a
meat puncher and a sprinkler over here and then a scratching post oops it's okay okay that looks
nice don't you think you need climbing area okay we need some climbing things just like
one of these over no that's too big that's this is enormous just a little one that's all right
like right here i don't know if you know guys but he got out he got out this is on west african
lion fuck he can still use this stuff i'm gonna save it i just want to see what happens
all right we need to change this edit barrier this needs to be concrete done done get him get him
please select close this somebody go get him why there's no call call vet call keeper okay
really here we go got him i don't know how that happened but it did is he unhappy no okay
enrichment i have to save it i have to save it i have to save save the zoo uh he's climbing up
he's going pretty slow no he's not going toward food uh species food food habitat food he's just
letting you have in the face food okay toy enrichment he's really amused by the sprinkler
see social that's better are you injured no social group space i need more space god damn it
well it's unfortunate take the meat chunk out oh yeah that's right that's right
multiple animals it's because there's like 300 in here yeah they just keep breeding
okay looking good let's go back here where the i just got like i'm so twisted around
all right how we doing the need and species any food enrichment i gotta do it on the ground
they ain't gonna happen okay that's fine enrichment toys uh
block of ice put it up here to like hang out and just put it over here whatever
you can just have to play with a soccer ball too have fun look at all these people just staring at
them it's not even connected it's not connected it's not connected it's not connected shit wouldn't
be connected okay let him out so many people are okay i need enrichment we need more uh food or toys
or uh oh oh here he goes no no no you had it you had it you were so close you know what to do you
know what to do you can do it it needs to be a ramp climbing ramp
there's so many people here they're pushing each other off the fucking bridge uh okay
that's just a traffic jam who's what was that oh that's the same
save it save it save he's gonna figure it out he still won't figure it out uh oh no uh
you had it you went right there still wrong uh do a pole i can't i can't do a pole
climbable pole no it's not gonna work do a better this is like connected here now
oh my god what if i just put a bunch of these no it needs to be i don't do where's this exact one
so many fucking people here oh my god get up here it's right there all right you can do that now i
know you can
okay they're in oh come on get out of the fucking way unbox the animal
this all right we're good move the door move door move door hold on
all right wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait they figure it they figure it out hold on
this is so
i would be fucking screaming right now
it's so slow it's so slow
oh
he's back oh that hurt real bad for a while he's going again hold on wait wait wait wait wait i
need to i need to block this facility broke down what facility the atm what do you mean the
facility no he's going for it again wait wait stop stop he's not he's gonna do the same thing
he just did i can't just got it all right hold on he's gonna climb where is he going
i need to change this
this is wrong it's not gonna work unless it needs to i don't even know what to do with this
is okay so i need to build i don't even know i'm gonna have to leave okay so i'm going to
we need a climbable ramp climbable platform okay what if i just do little ones like this
because these are platforms they're not ramps climbable ramp okay here we go i have to turn
this and i have to make it lower but i don't know how to do that
okay so i need to go into the advanced building options which are was in no control
yeah it's advanced building mode but how do i do advanced building mode here okay angle snap here
we go 30 degrees no i'm not 45 i'm gonna do the advanced mode maybe i can just do it afterwards
no because i don't want to make it part of the structure is it x okay there we go okay
let's do the rotation what the fuck's happened what's going on no stop what is happening
what the fuck is going on is that enough i think that's enough maybe a little bit higher
okay can he jump from here
make it a little one okay i'm sorry i'm like my head is i fucking am like dying right now
okay
that should be good i think that's the one i think we got it i think that's it we got it one more
oh
all right do it okay one more what he can't jump okay one more oh he's gonna be it was so funny
because he was so slow climbing up the thing they're so they're both so slow all right are
they gonna do it you're going for it thinking about it grab a platform do it you can do it you
can scare oh come on he's scared his pants he can't do it he's too scared god damn it
you can do it it's right there it's in your grasp just go for it you can do it i know you can do it
i know you can do it delete the things behind them when they go up but it'll
no no you can't because it'll it'll put them in a cage this is it this is it go
no you can't do it connect ramp to the walkway fuck me
this is an extra piece get out of here should be it so tomorrow uh we're gonna start dead rising
one okay here we go this should be the one that angles down all right you can do this
it's all connected now because the stream ends after this i have such a bad headache right now
go where you going you know what to do eat eat up fine that's fine connected to the path
and make one more you mean and they connect it to the down here just put a bunch of monkeys in
uh we'll see if they go up it here's the here's the attempt if he stops here and then that's it
oh come on it's right there
god damn it no it's so goddamn close he's coming up again is that it is that connected
it's not okay here we go you gotta get your fucking heads out of the way
move out of the way i can't see what i'm doing is that close enough
okay one more i'm trying to let them out don't you guys see all right that's it
that's it it's there that's it done go are they dead it's not touching oh my fucking god
dude it's touching now if it doesn't work i don't care stream ends don't matter i don't care
okay all right wake up it really fast here we go come on up here we go thinking about it
thinking about it thinking about it thinking about it thinking about it thinking about it
thinking about it no i'm not doing it you've had there was that one time shit where do you
let them go they're not gonna do i need to like i'm gonna put an ice block in here so i don't know
then then we need some enrichment shit toys i got clam blare everywhere put like a suspended
forage puzzle computer a forage box oh no look a little foraging okay cool good why are you in a
box all right i'm i'm really doing this attempt one more time just put more put more monkeys in
just okay hold on son of a fuck all right i'm just throwing in tenderills
just put them in someone's gonna do that someone is gonna do it this is the stream is over guys
i have to save before all this monkey stuff ah this is wrong why does it have to do this
all right let's see what happens make your way over this way i know you can do it
i know you can guys this could be it gorilla gorilla gorilla gorilla lion
what is that mutant
play the piano
what is this is that a cat
why is the lion going
it's like a pig
no one's gonna leave nobody's gonna escape
look at this guy
oh what's next an elephant he's going for it nope no one's leaving
laugh my fucking ass off with the camel climbs out of here
oh no guys a cockroach died
can somebody please predation is occurring what does that mean whoa oh shit what is he doing
oh
figure it out you have it's not like covered in oil get up there oh come on
go
oh
oh my god please oh fuck wait a minute he had second thoughts no no no no no no no
somebody get out of here just jump
um
like a christian like is that like a priest oh no no no that's the back of the sign okay
like this is so fucked up over here we need god what happened there no there's no one's ever
gonna get out of here it's not gonna happen it's over just wall off the ramp if i do that he turns
into a box wait what who got out who escaped who escaped
it's never gonna happen i'm so disappointed
i have one more i got one more trick up my sleeve
i'm gonna move this i could have just done this from the beginning why did i spend so long
where is everybody what who took them who took this huge shit are there any animals left in here
that's like oh that's elephant that's dinosaur type shit all right be free go he's gonna figure
it out he figured it out he figured it out he figured it out the rabbit figured it out
nobody else seems to care it's just like a little rabbit where's the lion where's the lion
what happened to the lion fighting due to overcrowding no shit wait these two are fighting
i'm gonna break for it he made it no no what are you doing don't go back
oh we're going
all right that's it see you see you tomorrow guys that's it stream over good luck where are
they look at all these cubs this is cool don't worry i gotta save look at all the janitors
everyone is leaving they're not even trying to do anything
okay i'm done i'm out i'm out i'm out it's game over
wait why is everybody locked away i can't unbox anything
what is he doing he's free
people are still coming into the park
record attendance uh-oh sniper uh i don't think there's anybody left besides the bugs
else you know the alligator wait the bugs are the bugs are already free
look at all these snipers i feel like this is like a fucking rail like an arena shooter
anything left i think that's it there's two elephants
all right uh bye see you next time wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute no i can't i can't i
was gonna see if i could build on there all right that's it that's the end of the zoo
and then any animals left yeah there you go he's being so sneaky he's like everyone is left
the tortoise where's it oh the tortoise right where's the tortoise peaceful peaceful ah big
stretch that was incredibly uncalled for uh mr kool-aid thanks for the 10 community subs that
was like excessive incredibly excessive well i had that saved uh but tomorrow we're gonna
start dead rising this game was uh fun it was very interesting i feel like there's enough
to enjoy if you want to make like an elaborate place kind of like planet coaster but
there's a lot of weird shit you can do so dead rising will be tomorrow i will see you guys then
have a great one um my whole body hurts from laughing at some of the stuff in this game i
don't know why the gorilla climbing up and then climbing around the side is just i was in actual
pain my god okay all right i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll uh we'll do the bits and subs
and everything but thanks for watching see you tomorrow for dead rising one hey look can we
can we get some top bits is that gonna happen you know when you laugh so hard that you have you you
you're forcing yourself to stop but it makes it worse like you triple laugh on top of what
you're already laughing at and then you just feel inside your chest it just tightens and pain happens
hey look at that it still don't work just pretending this stuff there
uh anyways let's go through it from earlier today we had what did we have what did we have i need
the music too what am i doing there it is so a while back a few hours well more like seven
hours ago at this point we had cf cvfd thanks to the 2500 bits welcome back funny man how was the
trip also uh free doc dr schmikes and they're talking about uh the trip was great i got to
meet up with a bunch of people that i haven't seen in a long time so that was really good
i got back really really really late last night really really early this morning so i'm pretty
tired so i'll get some good sleep tonight that's the plan is to get some food and then just crash
and wake up uh probably pretty early tomorrow hopefully and start dead rising but thanks for
the 2500 bits uh cvfd appreciate it peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hey jeremy how are you
we're doing pretty good i recently recently i hosted my own halloween stream with chat and
it was a success i painted myself as a clown and we watched a movie that's the most fun i've ever
had in a little while and i can't wait to do that again hope you have a good stream tonight
nobody does clown makeup stuff on stream people are trying you know i used to people do like
cosplay and stuff well i want i want a foal of real actual foal clown except for you yeah but
i did it once the joker no the joker's that's that's not a clown the joker doesn't make balloon
animals i think maybe in the he doesn't like have i mean he's a he's like a super villain he's not
a birthday clown yes he does he doesn't he probably put like weird gas in them one time
and like popped him around batman and robin and oh no here's the gas the noxious fumes he probably
did that like in the 60s he does he does this oh well i don't know i'm wrong then but yeah thank
you peaceful hailey i'm glad you had a good stream halloween is always a fun time however you can make
it fun and the cartoon even maybe he does this i don't know hey great canadian fuck club thanks
for the 1500 bits the grapes and a spaghetti is the reason we bought a zoo is my favorite movie
i have no idea what that means i think that's a reference to the movie thanks the 1500 bits
though appreciate it 15 bucks drink big gulp thanks for the 500 bits sands the tenno thanks
for the 10 bucks 1000 bits did you see i saw the sands entrance i saw the sands thing i saw the
fucking full sands costume it's ridiculous it was a really damn good costume too i hope they do more
shit like that man i don't know about you guys but i really i really i stopped watching wrestling
when it went from fun weird interesting characters to first name last name wrestler
i just lost interest first name last name in underwear was spandex it's just like i don't
care this is not like this is it's not like like baseball it was like the evil clown he hates stone
cold steve austin no no no because that was not steve austin it was stone cold steve austin that
was stone cold steve austin was just his name but stone cold he went by stone cold and that's the
bottom line hulk hogan that guy's name is not hulk it's you think you think that hulk hogan's
first name is the hulk that's like a made-up fucking name hulk hogan's real name is like
terry or something isn't it let's see what is it yeah it's terry balia come on guys but yeah i
did see it i hope they do more stuff like that that's really cool really fun hey fitting thanks
for the 500 bits uh dr schmoykson obviously knew the earlier questions for the he knows literally
everything joke uh did he also know the answers to this question or did he actually get so close
on accident you're talking about kazoo i'm gonna let the magic just stay no behind scenes on that
then what it's gonna let the magic play ufo kazoo uh sometimes you don't want to know what's behind
the curtain somebody must have mouthed it uh i was so happy that it was dr schmoykson back again
he had to come back and prove how smart he wasn't that he was a real doctor i'm suspicious of dr
schmoykson's credentials why would you be who is he that's dr dr schmoykson that's dr arthur
schmoykson i don't know what do you want to tell you but no it was great it was really good to
have uh the doctor come back hey nevery thanks for the 250 hi germa you ever said pog and ironically
off stream please tell the truth i promise i won't judge you no it's too ingrained in my brain
to say stuff like sick or that's oh sick nice no i say i say that's fucking awesome
no i don't say pog i go dude that's fucking awesome or go that's awesome sorry i'm too old
hey am scoots thanks for the 1500 bits donation box streamer i mean there you go thank you
appreciate that i mean like a couple weeks ago i had what i had the lion one out there
dude that face when you make more money on a stream than a lion exhibit and i mean i'm going
like stop stop stop stop stop stop stop but no thank you thank you dark soul for the 250
dark soul 9669 i just want to say that your hair is very epic and doesn't look like a peanut butter
m&m at all are you very handsome please dear god let my family go i said that you wanted me to
i said what you wanted me to admit okay well don't worry i don't have anybody thank you
uh thank you thank you tibetan hovercraft for the 500 bits hey germa 95 big thanks to
you for streaming today because it's my girlfriend's birthday happy birthday
please give a big birthday shout out to lynn happy birthday lynn she and i watch your streams
together and i know what make today extra special for her thanks for all that you do well lynn hope
you had a great one happy birthday i really hope that i really hope that uh tibetan here got you a
100 dollar applebee's gift card i really hope that's what you got and you can both go
and you can both enjoy the the riblets do they still have those those things sucked i remember
they were just like chewing on a dog bone can i say no whatever that's my opinion swiggity swanky
thanks there for the 250 they say free doc this is the clip where he's like i have something to
tell you i have something to say let's see what is this one i got i didn't even see that he
he was like he was like yelling at me i got something to tell you
that's so funny all right i'm gonna show it i'm gonna show it hold on
that was so funny yeah he went off on like a i swear like this is things that i didn't know
he went off on like a full 25 second rant that we just don't have i guess i didn't see that part of
this frame that's so funny let's take a look is it gonna play no we're gonna go off and pass this
off to bf bugleberry i got something to tell you guys
no we're gonna go off and pass this off to bf bugleberry that's so amazing i love it so much
yeah i think they they cut early i'm so happy that happened but yeah that was a lot of fun
hope you guys enjoyed that stream we try to do our best with having like two and a half weeks or
two weeks or so of planning so the actual the bot the chat counting uh points bot broke
immediately and that's why i failed the first level of plants versus zombies i was sitting
there getting fed into my ear that like the whole thing was broken i'm just going oh okay so look
that i'm just failing the plants versus zombies tutorial while i'm like talking to the production
people back there but i think i had a lot of fun it's always fun to do something like that
impromptu and it turned out pretty good i thought i had a fucking shit load of fun link link link
link link link link link what about it what is it let's see what's this link is this oh is this
diaper resident schmeichsen that's pretty good that's pretty good but it would have to be shorter
than that though because it would be germa resident schmeichsen germa schmeichsen there's
some pretty good screen caps one of these i'm telling you one of these days i'm gonna just sit
here and i'm going to add like 20 emotes i'm just gonna happen it's and i'm not even gonna tell you
when they're gonna appear they're just gonna be there one day like you're gonna just turn the
stream on and you're gonna look at your thing there's gonna be like 30 fucking new emotes
it's just gonna happen i'm gonna do it i'm gonna take like i'm gonna take like two days off
and just do all the stuff that i wanted to do for the stream all the new music all the new art just
make like 40 emotes and just load them all up no not tomorrow that's not what i said but uh thank
you too we were back here where were we lost there we oh and the music turned off too what the fuck
okay we were at thank you gnarly for the 250 hey germa thanks for choosing a game for me a couple
weeks ago it was earthbound over luigi's mansion now i want to play more classic rpg games i already
have super mario rpg on my list anything else i should add chrono trigger in fact play
chrono trigger twice in a row just do it uh chrono trigger chrono cross okay
no have to play chrono trigger and then like record it and then play it backwards
it's too long i'll change that i'll fix that shit thank you for that uh yeah mario rpg and
chrono trigger are the two of my favorite turn-based rpgs i've ever played hope you
enjoy them cold rush thanks for the 900 bits love you jeremy thank you cold rush appreciate that
thank you bone jackal thanks for the 500 bits yo this guy uh in a white van outside my house says
he's giving away tons of free leftover halloween candy i would not i would not get in i would uh
tell that person to leave and i would call i would probably call the police
or and just let them know thank you though thank you bob boy it's bob boy
bob boy with the 500 bits last of the bits for the week tf tubers thanks a lot bob boy
appreciate the five bucks appreciate it thank you then we had a shitload of community subs people
were just dumping them in five ten five five five five five thanks a lot there was a string there
of about 40 or 50 in a row thanks guys seriously even more we had shady seas dropped 20 during that
whole thing abomination zero thanks to the 250 i dropped my cookie in my milk it's all right leave
it there leave it there let it sit at the bottom let it turn to milk cookie dust and then you drink
it at the very end leave it there don't take it out are you crazy no that's how you do it if you
if you drop no no no no no listen to me if you drop a cookie in your milk and it's goes down
and sinks to the bottom if you we're gonna reach in there and with all your hand oils and like the
hair that's on your hands we could get a fork and dig it out with a fork no you get your hand oils
don't do that what if i drop it in my soup well then you're eating dessert and dinner at the same
time which that's pretty cool i wouldn't be i would not be embarrassed about that at all
uh thank you plank v2 gave 3,700 bits just about 4,000 bits from plank v2 they say hey germa i
usually try to give a fun fact but today i just want to say thank you for the years of entertainment
and i wasn't able to make it to the slime stream but i got to watch the bottom my birthday this
past weekend i do germa nose wipe thank you plank hope you liked it no fun fact but
you don't have to have any fun facts if you don't want to thank you so much though
and also happy birthday that was a fun fact now but happy birthday thanks for the 3,700 bits
really appreciate that mr kool-aid dropped 20 community subs went right when we turned off i
think back-to-back 10 sub drops we're gonna have an entire chat of subbed people thank you mr
kool-aid seriously why don't we show them on screen let's do it credits time let's see oh boy oh
oh boy that's a lot that's a lot thank you all of you for all your subs all the community subs
everybody you still push this stream to new monetary heights somehow all i can say is thank
you reaper thanks for the 250 hey german just want to say thanks for all the laughs recently
got a new job after losing a position i was certain i was getting a year gone but i now have
a concrete job now that's good you kept me laughing all this time and now i can send some love back
expect more bits from me in the future much love glad you got a solid job take care of yourself
first put me under like fast food mcchicken run you know what i'm saying i appreciate it though
thank you seriously glad you got a job that's pretty low no no it's not that's higher than pack
of gum right that's higher than water at the airport things you just wouldn't do i think
that's pretty high watching you is like eating fast food bad for me but good for me well thank
you though appreciate it but thank you reaper thank you for let me for the 300 bits stream
clown complains that there's not enough clowns on twitch i've been i didn't complain i just said i
would love to see more clowns on twitch but i wouldn't though that's a part to dot that's
bullshit i'm just making this up i wouldn't i don't want to see that i don't i don't care
i'm like faux caring about that it's i don't know why i'm doing that i just am whatever thank you
james for the 500 bits hey jump of the halloween stream was awesome i loved every second of it
maybe not the slime action part because it was because i was wearing a diaper
apologize personally to you well anyways i kind of recently started working in a
lush bath bomb factory really that's really fucking cool actually remember that bath bomb
that turned you into a simpsons character well was it lush i wish i could send you some make
you other cartoon characters tell shannon sharon she's a good host she was and tell
uh i mean dr schmoitzen what i'm gonna tell dr schmoitzen that you said hi okay bye they said
uh that's i'm thinking of jobs that would be like interesting things to do making the bath
bombs for lush is kind of sounds like fun to do is it you'll have to inform us apple shift thanks
for the 250 hey what's been the greatest day of your life ever so far um that's tough greatest
day of my life ever as i don't know hmm i don't i can't answer that there's been too many things
that it could have been that you know what probably probably when i got the message
from and now this guy this company like sucks okay i know but when i like got my you are
partnered from machinima message like eight years ago that was like holy shit this is the
greatest thing this is the greatest day of my life i was like wow this is fucking awesome
i was like that was like pretty cool that was a big deal that's what a shitty life no no no no no
you gotta remember i'm talking about like eight and that like eight and a half years ago because
like the youtube ad program and making money on ads on youtube that that like started just barely
like seven and a half eight and a half years ago they never used to be like that so essentially i
was being told hey uh the views on your on your videos are now going to make money it was the
first time it had ever been a thing so it was like what the fuck are you serious and then that
company made a series of some of the worst business decisions you probably could ever make in your
whole life and like they went through like four ceos and turns out one of the ceos i think went
to jail and uh the whole company got liquidated so okay turn turn the clock forward 10 years
happy ending but that was a different time period on youtube it really was just nobody knew anything
nobody knew what the hell they were doing there was no formula it was just you just did whatever
but the golden age of youtube i don't know if i would call that the golden age of youtube i
would call probably you know here stamp this i would say like 2013 like 2012 to like you know
2013 to like 2015 that like two year span of like two or three years was i think the best uh the
most fun i ever had on youtube between like 2012 and like 2014 2015 a two year span of two to three
years yeah that's exactly yeah 2013 especially i think it was i was having the most fun ever
you talk about oh what's like the greatest day ever i don't know when when castle griffinstein
got uploaded that was just i just loved every second of what i was doing i'm serious but we
could reminisce all day german rumble live too but that was also that was kind of at the tail end
though and then they made all kinds of ad friendly decisions and changing the way the site works and
what constitutes a view and what constitutes engagement and then what happened is he started
having people just feed into engagement and it wasn't about getting clicks anymore is about
making people stay and watch and watch a bunch of ads and mid rolls and then i was it was kind of
like i don't i'm i'm kind of done he hates youtube no that's not true it just things changed a little
and i was kind of just over it so here we are now but we only have a few more left to do uh snoozing
copter thanks for the 250 i linked this video once but i don't remember when and you had a really
funny reaction so i hope to recreate that now also streaming planet zoo was my wish for today
there you go i told the pre-chat to tell you to play it if it wasn't there so i'm glad this
happened it was a fun stream also congrats on the halloween stream it was incredibly fun the way
you're using this platform to be innovative is seriously awesome see you next stream i'm gonna
try i can't say that everything i'm gonna do is gonna be perfect but i'd like to continue to try
things that i think are different or interesting or fun for me or
we'll keep doing would you go to mixer if they paid you a ton of money no i don't want to change
platforms again i'm not gonna do that again all right did it once i went from youtube to twitch
i'm not going from twitch to mixer if i started on twitch maybe i would move to mixer maybe maybe
if that was the only time i'd moved but i took an established audience on youtube and said all right
go here now and took a while for you know that whole thing to play out and for years to go by
all right well let's do it again i'm moving another mixer this time and everyone has to move again
and people will just be like i don't want to and no i don't think and i would i'm not one of those
people that would be brought to mixer i don't i'm not i wouldn't consider myself one of those
people that we've reached out to you already lost a lot of people i still have people saying oh he's
streaming i'll check him out yeah i just don't want to have to bounce around to platforms i'm
just here i'm just here and i'm gonna be here okay now yeah sure okay if if i got offered like a
million no if i got offered like that's a lot of money that's a lot of fucking money that's a lot
of money let me just you guys understand how much money that is if somebody offered me a million
dollars i would have i would seriously have to consider what that was twitch is gonna hear you
you're i mean you're talking about more if okay if it if it was like fifty thousand dollars
i'd be like get the fuck out of here no if it was like a hundred thousand dollars i'd be like get
the get out of here you bastard okay 150 to 200 thousand dollars i would be like
you're not gonna get me over there i know um what is there any other offer
three five five hundred thousand dollars is like ah he's naming his price i mean you're talking
about like just immediate complete like life-changing money like immediate is not
like oh we're gonna give you uh 250 thousand dollars over the course of 40 years no no you're
talking about here's five hundred thousand dollars it's like okay you just like solidified
my whole retirement plan but plus taxes 10 million dollars to partner with magnavox for vhs content
only yeah sure that'd be the stupidest fucking thing ever but i would make 10 million dollars
and there'd be vhs streams it'd be hilarious for like a year and then i would quit but i it would
have to be a stupid amount of money for me to even consider it i don't care i really don't like i'm
not like look at all these other platforms that exist whatever there's already so many people here
and i get such a huge monetary support on this platform why would i do that there's like no
reason to he hates money he's too rich to care no no i'm just saying like there's already i already
i'm doing just fine here you know what i'm saying golden throne well make it out of like
granite it's like a rock throne rock can be pretty damn expensive it's big it's a big granite throne
you know what i'm saying watch the clip what is this you guys keep spamming this damn thing
what is this i don't even care what i was talking about i'm talking about the game
the uh i was trying to put the monitor on the educational board that's bullshit
and you all know that but no yeah money is nice right to end that story and then that rent and
then that kind of piece i'm not going to move to another platform that's what i mean hey they're
gonna hey uh we want to give you five hundred thousand dollars to move here hey uh hey current
platform i just wanted to like ask you a quick question about how things are working here and
um just if you're curious the number was around half a mil and that's what i was offered and i
wonder if you would anything you'd like to do to maybe increase that and keep me around
and then you get that number hey dear other platform yeah it's me yeah i considered your
first offer unfortunately i was uh just offered from my current platform um 600 and you know i
think i'm gonna have to stay all right so i mean it's that's a lot and i don't really care that
much unless you know there was if you had anything you wanted me hit me up you got my number
and then you take that over back to the current platform well you know i got let me guys let me
tell you something i'm really really loyal and then bang bang bang bang bang bang bang eventually
you get that number like 1.2 million and then you go too high and you go too far that you overbid
and both of them just leave so and then you just have nothing you just keep going back and forth
until you just lose it all that's like continuing to bet at like the roulette table just keep
putting down a hundred dollars and if you just keep winning over and over again and keep doubling
your bet i put down a thousand dollars on red you won put two thousand dollars on red you won put
four thousand dollars on red you won put eight thousand dollars on red you lost oh oh well can
i have that back no you can't oh bye room eight thousand dollars pocket change for germa that's
not true it's pocket change he's in his ferrari i would never buy an expensive car i'm of the
opinion that if you buy and you have like i'm talking like a fucking 100 to 200 thousand
dollar car you're just yelling out your windows and blaring speakers that say i have a shitload
of money i have way more money than everybody around me what do you think about that yeah i
probably have five hundred dollars in the glove box in cash i don't know probably there i don't
want to do that and plus a car like you you look cars people like that really like cars i get it
i do it's it's a whole it's a whole world with different cars and engines and and mechanical
stuff i know people love that shit but i'll just drive around in like a camry i don't care
if i had 50 million dollars i would drive like a 2014 camry and then i would just hold the
megaphone out the window and say i have more money than all of you you idiots i have a thousand
dollars in the glove box you can do that other ways you don't have to do that with just a car
anyways how much of the donation donations get used on the strip not very much maybe like 40
percent of my income no i'm not even going to keep i'm not even like that's fucking ridiculous
i'm not even going to say that because it's like so easy for people to be like what the fuck is
wrong with you it's not even real it's ridiculous it's a joke anyways we have yes is online thanks
to 250 you already gave money this stream but here's a necessary link also i'm going to go
into vegas for thanksgiving so i need good food recommendations if you can john wick out hash out
so go go done just eat every meal there at the link what is this buzzfeed pick a slang word and
we'll tell you what boomer you are what is this what's the highest single bet you ever put on a
table is was it 100 or 500 see this is like this is like an uh an interesting bait to try to be
like oh i was like 100 and and then wow holy shit you're fucking insane right i know i understand
like the game you're playing uh much more than that though and i won all 15 times in a row that
i did it and i just was like driving like around and just like throwing the cash around under the
parking lot just like dropping it in his ferrari in my ferrari all right what am i clicking what
am i what am i doing here no i don't carry cash i really don't i don't care i don't i never have
more than like a ten dollar bill on me at all times ever because you know you lose your wallet
what have you had like a what have you got like 500 bucks in your wallet you've like lost it or
something like that goes 500 dollars no i never carry cash all right it's about what boomer am i
i just clicked it why won't it open what percent boomer are you all right what do you call a friend
uh buddy pal bro or dog uh that's that's that's one of my buddies what do you call a group of
people a gathering y'all dudes fam or squad well i do not say fam or squad absolutely not
uh i do not say y'all i don't say a gathering i say dudes these is like you're like people i don't
know pick a pet name for your significant other my dear bae stud muffin darlin um these are all
i don't use any of these my dear uh what do you call your mom mom mother mommy birthgiver mom
uh oh okay climate change no okay not real no opinion needs to be taken seriously or who cares
okay he threw he threw in the climate change no we're gonna fucking burn our goddamn planet
to the ground yeah all right climate change yes what do you call food grub chow food a meal
that's called food how do you write this is how this this this i don't know lowercase i'm 10
boomer there you go guys there you go took your test i mean that is i mean that well well that's
from buzzfeed so it's 10 10 everyone at buzzfeed is a boomer i don't think that's true how many
articles are they read on buzzfeed today like 30 40 it's something like that so that's 10 of all
articles written today i also got 10 it's rigged is it can you get more than 10 or is it just a
way to just diarrhea out an article by the way what the hell did i just do why does that exist
it was like six random like questions eight well how many what even was that why was that an article
you just sold your information away no that's that's not true i guess i am a hundred percent
boomer because i just took the quiz that's the real test guys actually taking that quiz means
you're a boomer right i actually clicked on the squares anyways i'll see you guys tomorrow uh
whoa hold on a minute we got a jerma's pet ferret thanks for the 300 bits jerma i work in a vet
clinic and today i turned on your stream for the dogs in the kennels to listen to and i must say
they the usually noisy crowd was pacified by your voice really you always start streams while i'm
at work but thank the gods for vods much love hell yeah jerma's pet ferret thank you thank you
uh super tentorium thanks with 300 bits jeremy any chance we could see some kind of charity stream
with the success of the carnival and halloween streams i truly think we can make something big
happen yes there actually is a plan to do one already uh i'm gonna be working with one of my
buddies who will be running the marathon and we're gonna try to we're probably gonna sell a shirt
and just the shirt is just any money that comes in the shirt is to sponsor his run and to uh go
to the charity that all the money goes to charity so there will be there's gonna be just a there'll
be a charity t-shirt probably soon here so that is it's interesting that you said that because
we literally just talked about it like four or five three four days ago what's the schedule
this week um i have a doctor's appointment on thursday so i will not be around on thursday but
we're gonna go tomorrow dead rising and then i have a doctor's appointment on thursday and
i'm gonna do friday saturday sunday i'm gonna assume friday will be dead rising maybe i'll need
to do another stream after that we'll see outer worlds that's right i do have to play outer worlds
as well uh outer worlds i'm gonna tell you i'm probably not going to finish outer worlds on
stream we'll probably do a red dead scenario where i do it a couple of streams maybe two or three
and then i'm gonna finish it off stream it's not that long i know i know but still it is though
isn't it it's not a long wait how is it not it's not long that game sucks so nothing of value is
lost it's 45 hours yeah but that's still a lot 30 to 40 hours is still that's about at least four
streams i don't do like 10 hour streams we'll see we'll see but we'll do that after dead rising
and then that's no we know we got more we got more we got more unkind thanks for the 500 bits
hey germ i'm just chilling after an eventful couple weeks and now it'll cheer me up to hear
you speak to me directly let's go unkind what's going on they say keep up with the creative and
awesome shit really enjoy the halloween stream here's to many more i hope so there are at least
a few already being planned right now i'm going to get back in front of the green screen that'll
be one of them we'll do a whole night of it that'll be probably happening somewhere in
probably the moment probably one of the last weeks of november yeah because i want to give
you guys like a week or two to come up with uh things to for me to do jerma used to be so
handsome i can't ban you through stream labs but i tried to that's all that matters yeah thank you
unkind i really appreciate that thanks to five dollars and stay tuned there should be some more
stuff to see and then bobo dorago thanks with 300 bits thank you jerma for all the epic gamer
moments any tips on dealing with boomers um no i don't have any i don't even i don't have
any no what am i going to tell you uh the tips on dealing with a boomer well try to come to an
agreement try to give you a perspective listen to their perspective and then immediately tell
them immediately point at them and say wrong incorrect stupid wrong you have to say oh no
i'm not gonna say that that's like a new meme thing isn't it well give me advice but to give
you that's like your parents hey can you give me some advice on how to talk to my parents
i don't know it's your parents i don't know how do you talk to your parents hopefully not like
the way i just did otherwise uh you are grounded i got grounded like two weeks ago guys it sucks
they took away my ps4 i couldn't go out with my friends i was so pissed off all right good night
let's see you tomorrow how many people live with you um 17 this is a a 22 bedroom house
i don't even know the other i have no idea who these other people are i just know that i live
here is that real i don't know you be the judge see you tomorrow guys good night dead rising