Hi. Hold on, I gotta grab my... One sec. Okay. Good afternoon, everybody. Good evening.
We are gonna do... It is Saturday. I don't know what that means the last few weeks. That means
Microsoft Distributed Operating System. Microsoft Operating System. We ended last
night very late, so I figured I'd give myself another hour or two. Still in the window though.
Doink occupied the stream? Like dunk the clown? Did Cox finally fix the internet? No,
unfortunately not. We still have problems, but we did change over IPs and we have static IP now.
They know there's a problem. They know it exists, but I don't think they can fix it because
of a million different things. And I feel like I've been talking about this the last
week straight. So I'd like to not even think about the internet. You know,
I don't even want to think about it. Let's just pretend it's not a problem until it is one.
Right? Ten years. But it was actually... It was all right yesterday. Yesterday was fine.
And then into today. Seems like it's okay. I mean, probably gonna drop frames, but I
don't think it'll be a huge issue. Although I've been wrong many times before. I mean,
just make a tweet and I'll be right back when we get started. Alrighty. Welcome. I'm ready to
check out a few more of these games. Why not DOS and DOS nots? Because it's do's and do's nots.
No, it's do and do nots. DOS and do nots. Whatever. Title's not changed.
What does the title say? DOS and do nots. Yeah, like do's and do nots.
Some of these are great. Some of these are like I'm not even going to click them. So
do's and do nots? Well, then you can't have the S. DOS and do nots. Speaking of DOS
and not necessarily do nots. Take a look at that. So the last time we did this,
I will show you. We did... We changed categories. Instead of... We see here where
we are up here. This is where we started. I was sorting by views last time. The time
before that. And then the last time we did this, I just kind of picked a random page.
So today we're going to go back to like the popular tab and we're going to go down
to where we were last time. There's Super Mario's Video Game Gallery. We can tell
that's a good one. I already know that's a good one. So this is where we ended up
two... three weeks ago, right? Because I remember Dangerous Dave's Haunted Mansion
and then we ended up about here. Right here. Just about. So because of the way that these
they kind of move up and down, they're not in a straight line anymore. I would say the only
ones you should be clicking on are the ones that the text is visible. Right? Don't click on these
ones down here, right? Because I... We don't know what they are. Visible text only. And if you
have a moment, I would just love if you would pick the first game we're going to play
right now. What? Okay. You guys clicked so fast that you broke the click thing. And no,
porn games are not going to be played. Remember, this is DOS and DOS nots. This is
DOS and DOS nots. I'll change that title. That's better. What do we got? By the way,
the rules have changed. We're going to do three on this list. Just pick three and then we'll
move on. It looks like I'm going to play The Hobbit. It just... I guess it's the title
that everybody... Just click on that one, Jeremy, because it says Hobbit in the title.
Like bugs to a lamp. All right. Can you guys even see my cursor? That's odd. You should
be able to see my cursor. All right. Thank you. Now, I'm going to click on The Hobbit
and let's go. For some reason, you guys are still on the screen. Okay. This is 1993 from
Milbus Software. And we need to... What do we have to do? What are we changing? What?
Why can you guys not see this? What the fuck is going on here? Oh, right. I remember.
Okay. I remember. I remember because my scene is messed up. Because last time we did this,
I had to... Remember, I zoomed in really far because we couldn't read the text.
Here, I'll just do this. Fix this real quick. Yeah, I remember now. There we go. Okay. All
right. Here we go. Choose monitor type. This is mono or color. Mono means it's going to be
black and white, right? So we need to... We want to do color. Kind of wish I picked the
other one. The Hobbit. Press space to begin the game. Choose display with 40 or 80.
I mean, we have to do 80, right? Do you want... What? 8? No, no, no. I want 80.
I don't want 8. Do I want pictures? Oh my god. What the fuck is happening?
I didn't pick 8 resolution. Did I? That's not possible. It's 80. You are in a comfortable
tunnel-like hall with a perfectly round green door like a porthole. Ow! You are in a
comfortable tunnel-like hall with a perfectly round green door like a porthole. The walls
are paneled. The floors are tiled and carpeted, and there are a number of polished chairs
around the walls. To the east there's a round green door. You can see Gandalf.
Gandalf is carrying a curious map. Thorin, the wooden chest. Gandalf gives the curious map
to you. Thorin, rising to his feet, says to you, well, Mr. Baggins, it's all ready
for our adventure. And I must say they're looking very hopeful. Shall we be off then?
You wait. Time passes. Gandalf opens the round green door. You wait. Time passes.
Gandalf goes east. You wait. Time passes. What do I need to do? You wait. Wait. Wait.
I don't see the ring anywhere. Wait. What am I supposed to do? You wait. Okay. Freak me out.
Go east. What? You are in a gloomy empty land with dreary hills ahead, rising higher and
higher, dark with trees. On some of the hills are old castles that have a very evil look
about them. To the west there is the round green door. Visible exits are east, north,
and northeast. You can see nothing. Thorin enters. Thorin? Where? What do you mean Thorin
enters? Where is he? You attack Thorin, but the effort is wasted. His defense is too strong.
Thorin attacks you, but the effect is wasted. Your defense is too strong.
You have mastered two percent of the adventure. You are dead. What? With one well
placed blow, Thorin cleaves you. Cleaves your skull. You are dead. The story of Phil
Vovagans. The Hobbit. A wizard is never late, nor is he early. A wizard wait when he's dead.
Who killed him? Who killed him? Can I restart? Oh yes, of course I do. Let's try this again.
Gary, you're in the green door. I'm inside my hobbit place, right?
Gandalf is carrying a curious map. Look at the map. Look what? Map. You look at the curious map.
It is a map drawn on a piece of parchment of the area around the lonely mountain.
There seem to be some symbols on it, but you cannot read them. Gandalf opens the round
green door. Thorin says, well, are we going to just stand here all day? Okay,
Gandalf goes east. Follow Gandalf. You're in... okay, we're back here.
Gandalf takes the curious map. Thorin enters. Follow Gandalf. Gandalf takes... okay, talk to
Gandalf. You talk to Gandalf. Gandalf says, fascinating, but I wonder what I could use it for.
Thorin says, hurry up. What is he? What? Use map. Northeast. Go northeast. I'm not going to
kill Gandalf. Here we go. You are on the almost hidden path through the trees.
On the ground are many trolls footprints. To the north there is the heavy rock door.
Visible exits are south. You see nothing. Just want to make sure he's still here. Oh no,
Gandalf's not here anymore. Let's go north. You cannot go north. The heavy rock door,
south. I can't do anything. Talk to Thorin. You talk to Thorin. Where? Hi. What? I do not
know the word. It's. What happened to the word 20? You wait. Time passes. I don't know. What do
we do? What happens in the first part of the movie? What happens in The Hobbit? I try to
open the door. The door is locked. All right, south. You are in a small clearing, half hidden
amongst the trees. Yes, yes, yes. A hideous troll. Uh oh. You can go southwest, southeast,
or north. You can see a hideous troll. A troll is carrying the large key and a vicious
troll. Thorin enters. A hideous troll says blimey, look at this. Can you cook them? Yeah,
I could try, but they wouldn't make a bovver mouthful. Thorin remarks to you. Well, thief,
you don't seem to be making a very good beginning to this adventure. I hope you
have some idea how to get us out of this mess. You wait. Time passes. The hideous troll
eats you. His foul gluttony has killed a hideous troll. You are dead. I was too slow?
Did I have to go faster than that? I was reading the text. I guess I had to just go
immediately. All right, one last try. Try it again. Okay, we're gonna go follow Gandalf.
What do you mean I can't follow Gandalf from here? Oh, Gandalf hasn't left.
Okay, it's map drawn. Gandalf opens the round door. We're gonna go follow,
follow Gandalf. I'm just, I'm doing my slash following. Go east. Close the door.
All right, Gandalf enters. Okay, we're east. You can go east, north, or northeast. Let's go
northeast. I gotta hurry up, though, because you don't have to look. This is the hidden path.
No, let's go back. Wait, did I go, go, go south? All right, here's the trolls. Here we go.
Here we go. Ready? Go, uh, go north. No, no, no, go south. Go, um, hide. Hide. Run. Made it.
You're on a good path at the brink of a fast flowing river. All right, here we go.
Behind a narrow bridge of stone, without a parapet, crosses the river. Ahead, you can see the last
homely house. You can go east and west. You can see Elrond. Hey, hey, Elrond. You wait time,
but Doron, with a fair way looking at us, starts muttering about gold and treasure. Elrond
gives him lunch. Eat. You eat some lunch. Doron says, hurry up. Day dawns. What? Um,
um, inquire about the ring. I don't know. Leave. Exit. Go north? Hello? Hello? You,
hello? Time passes. Doron starts singing about gold. Elrond gives some lunch to you. Eat
lunch. You eat some lunch. It was delicious. Talk to Elrond. You talk to Elrond. Doron waits.
There's nothing to eat. Okay, let's leave. Go north. You cannot go north. Hurry up. What
are we hurrying for? I can't talk to. Go west. You go west. The trolls clearing.
Visible exits are south, west, south, east, north. You can see Gandalf. Ooh, the large
key. Gandalf takes the large key. Thorin enters. You wait. Time passes. Gandalf says,
what's this? I wonder. Take key. Gandalf is carrying the key. Talk to Gandalf.
Gandalf gives the large key to you. Well, are we going to just stand here all day? All
right. Uh, go to the, what was the heavy door? South. Go south. You cannot go south. Go
north. Go northeast. Follow Gandalf. Um, leave. You leave. Time passes. Gandalf
goes southeast. Go southeast. Rivendell. Visible exits are east, west. You can see
Gandalf and Elrond. Gandalf goes east. Thorin enters. Elrond says hello. Yes,
hello. You see hello. Time passes. Elrond gives some lunch to you. I guess I'll
eat. You eat some lunch. Thorin says, well, are we going to just stand here all day? Go
east. You are on a hard, dangerous path in the Misty Mountains. The path is marked with
white stones, of which many are small and others are half covered with amazes or heather.
You can go east, northwest. You can go any direction. Where's Gandalf? Thorin sits down
and starts singing about gold. The mean goblin enters. Go Gandalf. Go Gandalf. Go north. Go
north. Go north. You are on a narrow path at the top of the valley, which opens suddenly
at your feet. You are on a narrow path at the top of the valley, which opens suddenly at your
feet. At the bottom of the valley, trees can be seen poking above the mist, and the sound
of running water can be heard. You can go east, north, south. You see dead Gandalf.
Attack. Attack. Attack goblin. Who killed Gandalf? Attack troll. The mean goblin
captures you. It is too dark to see anything. Did Gandalf fall off the mountain? Oh, this is so
stupid. Run. But you go somewhere. But in the dark, you stumble and fall heavily to the ground.
It is too dark to see anything. Hide. Um, uh, pray. Struggle. Go east. In the dark, light.
Use light. Light. You light. Time passes. Thorin appears. Thorin, to you. Thorin asks,
would it perchance be too much trouble to inquire as to your plans for getting us out of here,
or are we just going to sit around it all day in this dungeon? Time passes. You hear a noise.
You wait. Time passes. You hear a noise. It's too dark to see anything.
Listen. I don't know the word listen. Um, walk. Smell. Run. You stumble and fall heavily
to the ground. It is too dark to see. You hear a noise. You hear a noise. Again. Uh,
it's too dark to see anything. You hear a distant vroom. How long are we going to be in here for?
Just eat? Nothing to eat. How long are we going to be just sitting here for? Follow.
Follow noise. Go noise. Noise. Talk to Thorin. I see nothing here. What are you talking about?
Talk. Like it's too dark to talk. I can't, it's too dark to talk. Call out. Yell. Just keep,
I'm just going to keep running. Run. Run. I just keep falling down. Run. I'm just running
into walls back and forth. Um, use the light, but they don't know the word use. I mean light.
You light. Time passes. Run. It's too dark. But what, you light. Take the ring.
You follow no, but you can't follow the noise because it's too dark and he doesn't,
they don't know what the word noise is. Lantern. Inventory. I can't see my inventory.
How dark is it in here? Wear ring. Ring. What? Open eyes. Oh, what? I finally had,
just kept my eyes open this whole time. It would have been so much easier. Equip ring.
I don't know what that word means. Hear. Noise. What? You do know what the word
noise is. You just wrote it. You just wrote the word noise. Listen doesn't,
I just already tried that. I don't know what the word listen means. Status. Um, feel.
I don't know what that word is. Uh, light torch. You light. Time passes. You hear a noise.
Break. Climb. Close. Dig. Dig. Untie. Untie. Why don't I read how to play? Sorry,
I didn't read the game manual before we picked a random DOS game. I don't know the word pants.
What? A window should be no obstacle to a thief with friends.
Window. Look. Where's Thorin? Thorin. Stand on my shoulders. Stand.
Stand up on my shoulders. Climb. Thorin. You cannot climb into Thorin.
Look. Window. You can't climb in to Thorin. No, I don't think I would like to either, so.
Yeah, when I say talk Thorin, I can't talk to Thorin. Apparently we cannot talk.
You sleep. I think I'm just dead. I don't know how to die. Drink. Empty. Enter. Enter.
Enter window. You cannot. You cannot enter the window. Break window. It's too dark to see.
I just lit. Open window. I can't. Smash. Light. It doesn't do anything, guys.
You light. Time passes. You hear a noise. Look. It's too dark to see anything. Did you just
know? All right, it's. I'm out. I'm out. Yeah, listen to noise. I don't know what
listening is. I don't know what the word noise is. I need to light something. No. Hear sound.
No, it doesn't know anything. Light sound. All right, I'm out. I'm out. I'm stuck here forever.
I can't search because there is no. Look at. How many times do we have to do this?
I'm not going to sit there anymore. We did every single word and it didn't know half of
them. We were on that one for like 20 minutes. That's enough time. All right, we're back here.
Where? No, we're not. We should be back. Where's the hobbit? Right there. No, we were like here.
Yeah, we were. Like right here. Right there. Okay, so this is where we were.
That was fucking all over the place. It could be fun though. All right, give it a click.
Where are we going next? Light self. Why can I not see the clicks? Oh, that's why. Okay,
looks like we got a lot of people that are clicking on the
president one. I think that's going to win by what I would just determine this to be a landslide.
Here comes a politics stream. Sort of. Maybe. All right, so we're going to call it there.
We're going to president-elect. Thank you for voting. President-elect 1988 edition.
Interesting. 1988. I wonder if the sound on this one. Okay, this is the president-elect
1988 by Nelson. 2.1 copyright. IBM PC version and graphics designed by CHO. Begin new simulation.
Continue old simulation. We had $50 just came in right now. That was from Alexander Gabriel.
Thanks to the $50 and two cents. 5,000 bits. We got our first campaign donation. Oh, I gotta
turn on. Yeah, hold on. I still have the click. You can still click the click map.
There we go. But thank you so much to Alexander Gabriel. And they say here's to you,
Jerma, for being here for all through my high school experience. Just graduated on Thursday
and I'm so happy to be out of high school now. I'm going to become an electrician now,
so I can give you more money. Jerma Hart. Oh, you don't have to work to give me money.
But congratulations on the graduating high school. And hell yeah. I wish you luck. I wish
you the best in your future career. Thank you so much for the $50. Hell yeah. Cheers to that.
All right. So we're going to begin new simulation. Choose map colors. Red, green,
brown, cyan, magenta, or white. I mean red. Let's do RG. RGB. Except that's what? Press enter
to begin. 5, 1, 17. What's going on? Red, green, brown. RGB is blue. What? What am I
doing? And what's this 1, 5, and 17? Okay. Pick your year. Oh, this is what happened.
Third party. Okay. 1988. What is the last name of the Democratic candidate? Candidate not found.
Try again or rate candidate. Wait, I have to pick somebody that was actually a Democrat
in 1988? For the following series of issues in question, stats. Raise taxes to balance budget.
What is it going? Wait, hold on. For the following series of issues in question,
state the candidate's support or agreement on this scale. Oppose, disagree very strongly.
Okay. All right. Raise taxes to balance budget. What would Gandalf say? Oh, boy.
All right. I know how to do this. Ready? You guys can't even see my answers. All right.
Rate the candidate's poise. Under intense pressure. Frequently puts foot in mouth.
Sometimes slips, but not often. Extremely cool under fire. That's Gandalf. What state
is the candidate from? Middle Earth. Is there an M-E? Yep. What state is the vice president from?
Also from Middle Earth. What is the last name of the Republican candidate?
No, I can't do that because that's like, that's making it evil.
I don't know. Fucking Homer Simpson. Candidate's personal magnetism. Ease to ignore.
Average for... pretty average. Rate the candidate's poise. Yeah, sometimes you have an issue. What
state is the candidate from? What's Springfield, Ohio? No, they've never said it. They've never
said it ever in the whole entire run of the whole show. Just not Illinois. Vice president is
gonna be, I don't know, gonna be Marge? What is the last name of the third party candidate?
Oh my god. No, it's me. Let's get that candidate. How do you feel about all the...
Rate candidate's speaking ability. I mean, we're talking about like an orator for the ages.
Rate candidate's personal magnetism. A spellbinder. Absolutely irresistible.
Candidate's poise. Extremely cool under fire. Frequently puts foot in dog. What state is the
candidate from? Well, what do you like? M-A. What state is the vice president? Vice president
is gonna be... who's vice president? Otto. Okay, so he's also from M-A. Which party has
been in power for the last four years? Well, let's just go for like realism here.
Is Homer Simpson the incumbent? Yes. What has the rate of inflation been for the past year?
I don't know. Five? Six percent? Is it a percent? It's six.
That would be catastrophic. The party and office would certainly be thrown out.
Yeah, if Homer Simpson was the president, we're into something more reasonable.
All right. Something high. Like 16%. That's fucking crazy. What is the latest unemployment
figure? Well, if Homer Simpson's the president, let's say 94%. That would be catastrophic.
All right. Reasonable. I don't know. What's like... 68%. 50%. 49%. 45%. 30%. 29%. 28%.
20%. Okay, all right. So what is the current rate of GNP growth adjusted for inflation?
Is the nation at peace or at war? We're at war. On a scale of one to nine, how would you
describe the popularity of the war among the voters? I don't know. We're living in fucking hell
right now. This is actual hell. World War II? I don't know. Will Gandalf be managed by the
computer? Yes. Will Homer Simpson be managed by the computer? Yes. Will German NA-5 be managed
by the computer? No. Okay, here we go. As of the last week, national polls reported the
following average projections. Gandalf with 38% with 320 electoral votes. Homer Simpson with
30% and 81 electoral votes. And German NA-5 with 32% of the popular vote but only 13 electoral
colleges. Too close to call. There are 530 electoral votes of which 270 are needed to
win. What do you mean that's too close to call? Oh, I see. Gandalf won already. Gandalf
leaning. All right, who's leaning Gandalf? Who's leaning me? Only my home state. That's it.
Massachusetts is leaning me. Homer Simpson's got like the middle of America here. Gandalf.
Okay, Nevada is leaning Homer Simpson. All right, let's go. Ready to begin campaigning
for the week of September 1st to the 7th? Starting week one. Eight weeks to go. All
right, let's go. Economic news. Economic indicators during the last month showed a
modest weakening from the previous month. Foreign news. Slightly favorable. At this time,
all campaign staffs must decide whether or not their candidate will visit a foreign country
during the campaign. Gandalf has decided to send the vice president to a friendly country
during week four. The trip will last six days. Homer Simpson has decided not to take the trip.
To the German NA-5 staff, do you want to take the trip? He sent Frodo to Mordor. Sure,
to a friendly neutral or unfriendly country. Unfriendly. Send vice president or presidential
candidate. Send the vice president. Let's send Otto. During which week? One first week. For how
many days? Cost in PAP 500 plus 50. Uh two days. On a scale of one to 100, indicate the
quality of German NA-5's organization. The best would be 100. Anything under 75 might be
unwise. I told you I'm a B plus streamer. What's my social? What? No, no, no, no, no,
what's my social blade at right now? Somebody go check. What is my stream twitch social blade?
What is it? I think it's a B plus. There it is right there. B plus. Done. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, it just skipped. What is it? Why did it skip? I think a concrete car
for the five community subs. Thank you concrete. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Five subs coming in here. Coming in hot. All right, here we go. I gotta make some
choices here. Political action points. I have 16,000 this week's overhead. All right,
political points. National campaigning covers entire nation. States with more electoral votes
will receive proportionately more coverage. How much should I spend on nation coverage?
To 2,240? So I should go all in on the first week? That's probably a bad idea.
All right, here we go. New England. Gandalf, Homer Simpson, and me. I got Massachusetts.
I'm close, pretty close to Connecticut. I'm close in Rhode Island. I'm losing in Maine.
Losing, I'm losing, I got Vermont. Homer Simpson is not in this part of the country.
Mid-Atlantic. I'm not winning in any of these. Why is Gandalf so popular?
In the South. Nobody likes me down South. Holy shit. I have no fans down South.
Everybody loves Gandalf around the whole country. 15 community subs just came in from
Ampharic. Thank you. That's a lot. Big 15 sub drop here. Thank you so much.
Congratulations to all the people that just got the subs. 15 of them just came in.
Thank you so much Ampharic. I have no fans though. Wisconsin, but Gandalf is winning
everything. How do we smear campaign Gandalf? I got it. You went into the middle of nowhere
to get a couple of hobbits to go do a fucking mission for you. You couldn't just do it
yourself. They were children by the way. Homer Simpson's got Missouri. I got Oklahoma though.
Those Oklahomans. New Mexico, close. Nevada. Great state of Nevada, close. California.
Californians love Gandalf. Not going to be able to do anything.
Gandalf refuses to debate. Homer Simpson is calling for a debate anytime, anywhere. Does
German 985 wish to debate? Yes I do. Do Homer Simpson and German 985 agree to a debate at
this time? Of course we do. The candidates have agreed that Gandalf's going to go do his own
thing. How many questions will be asked during this debate? I'll get them all. I'll knock
them all out of the park. The candidates are ready to begin. By the luck of the draw,
candidate Homer Simpson will answer first. Other candidates will then alternate on subsequent
questions. Question directed to Homer Simpson. What is your position on the current military
budget? Are there any areas you believe that need to be cut or increased? And to the percent
of time the candidate will allocate to each line of argument? What? Hold on. So he four
percent discussed irrelevant considerations, spent half the time stating his own position, spent
90% of the time contrasting position with me, killing time 12%, and then attacking opponent's
position 15%. What is your position on the current military budget? Are there any areas
you believe that need to be cut or increased? Turn to speak, Homer Simpson! 41% emphasis,
clarity on their own positions. No criticizing with, uh, witticisms. Spend a little bit of
time killing time, implying opponent is uninformed. Criticize with moral indignation,
okay? My turn. That was just a, you're wrong. How should the United States deal with illegal
immigration? How should the United States deal with, okay, kill time! Homer Simpson did the
same thing. So both candidates don't want to do that. Okay, uh, my turn. Let's clarify our
position a little bit here. Let me clarify, and then I'm gonna give 10% here, 30% here,
I'm gonna criticize with some, uh, I guess, uh, what's, was this a new question? We're gonna
imply that, not imply at all that they're uninformed, but we're gonna do some moving
around. 30, 10, 30, 30. Well, fuck, he, I got him against the ropes. Uh, Dark Soul,
thanks for the five community subs. Dark Soul 115. That's a lot of subs tonight, yeah.
So Homer is, is doing like the joke I did in the very beginning. He's fucked. He's just
killing time. His, like, eyes are darting back and forth. Um, uh, uh, don't, oh!
And then everyone laughs and he gets, like, the votes back.
Are you in support of affirmative actions and programs as a means of bringing minorities
and women into the mainstream of the American economy? Uh, okay, yeah. So,
enter the percent of time. Uh, let's discuss relevant considerations. Let's give that about,
let's give that, uh, let's give that, like, 30%. We'll go with the 25% here.
Uh, contrast position with opponents. I'm gonna give that, um, I'm gonna give that 10%. I'm
gonna go with, like, 40% here. Oh, fuck. I went over. How do I go? I don't go back. I went over.
Can I do minus five? Zero? I did 105%.
Canada tried to exceed time on that last reply and had to be cut off.
Time has been redistributed so the sum of all five lines does equal 100%.
Homer Simpson, he's not, he's just killing time. 40% emphasis on your own position.
41 kill time. I, you are fucked. Oh, and now you're just killing time. Let me give you a 20,
let me give you a 30% on my position. Here you go. 40% on criticizing you. Don't need to do
that one. And then, uh, incredibly uninformed. Let's go 30% here. Not gonna kill any time.
Right now, I'm, I got them. I'm like, I'm, I'm beating them in, in, like, in, like, this,
like, uh, Muhammad Ali did. What? German 95 has committed a gaffe. The questionnaires are
looking at each other in amazement. What was the gaffe? What did I do? Am I miked up right now?
Did they hear what I was saying? Are you in favor of tariffs of a means of protecting domestic
industries? Fucking gaffe. He gaffed. How did I gaffe? State-owned position. 10%. Contrast
position with opponents. 10%. I'm gonna, I'm gonna back off here. Let's go with, like,
8% and then, like, four. We're gonna, I'm backing off. I'm just gonna kill some time.
I'm gonna get my breath. Don't be a gaffe. All right. Are you in favor of tariffs as
a means of protecting domestic industries? Um, that's a pretty good question for Homer Simpson.
He didn't really dodge it. I did. Just, I wanted to back off a little bit. I just had a big gaffe.
I'm gonna clarify. I'm gonna go, like, 58%. No. Round numbers because I'm stupid. We're
gonna do 60% emphasis clarifying my position. I backed off a little. I don't need very much
criticisms here. I'm not gonna imply that they're uninformed. Maybe 5%. And then we'll
kill a little bit of time. We'll just kill, we'll kill a little bit. See? 50%. And now,
hold on a minute. Let me clarify. Excuse me. What measures would you take to correct the
adverse trends in our balance of trade? He had a lot of responses here. 18% discussed
relevant considerations. 39, 36. So he wants to know, he's contrasting his positions with mine.
I'm going after him here. Yeah, I'm going after him. 20%. Give you a pin. Okay. 30, 20. 20%, 20%.
40%. No, no, no, no, no. 10%. And then 50%. I'm going after him.
Derma has committed a serious gaffe. The panel is aghast. How unfortunate.
What do I keep doing? What am I doing?
62% clarifying. 22, criticize morally, kill time. What, you're not gonna make any gaffes
with like 60%? I'm clarifying everything now. Clarify. Clarify. Clarify. Clarify.
What about your policy on nuclear power? Um, I don't know. I'm not gonna, I'm not getting
into the gaffe. Discuss relevant, let's talk about the relevancy of nuclear. State your
own position on nuclear. Let's go with like, let's go with like 45%. Like,
let's state my own position. I'm gonna be clear here. Not gonna con, maybe a little bit
of contrasting. Not gonna like attack very much. Maybe like 5%. No, no, no. Like 5%. And then
we'll spend 20% just kind of moving around and doing some anecdotes. I wanna be, I need
to start clearing up my, my shit here. Yeah. See, they did the same thing. My turn. All
right. Clarify my position. Again, we're gonna go hard here. No, no, no. We're gonna
go like 45. Uh, we're gonna go like 15 with some criticisms. Another like 15. I'm gonna
criticize. I'm not gonna imply that they're uninformed and we're gonna kill a little bit
more time here. Mmm. Besides my serious gaffes, I've got them against the ropes.
In the opinion of the press, the debate went as follows. Homer Simpson, 17, 16,
German 95, 9, and 2. Nobody else. I just have Massachusetts. Nobody else likes me.
God damn it. Uh, begin campaigning. Starting week two. Questionable statements. Homer Simpson
had a questionable statement. What'd he do? German 95's running mate was abroad for two
days last week and receiving mixed reviews. Campaign officials are accepting this philosophically,
but in any event, it appears the trip will have very little impact on the campaign.
It's because Otto's a dog and he just walked around and looked cute. I'm gonna do 2000.
Save some of these points. Covers all states in a region with uh spending. All right. New
England. I'm going all in in New England because it's the only place that they like me.
Mid-Atlantic, 250. The South, 300. Industrial Midwest, 200. Mid-West, 400. West, 450.
Pacific coast. Uh, 400. Oh, this has to be 2000. I thought, no, no, no. I thought this was like
a scale of how you want. I didn't know it was like literal. So I have 62.
What the fuck? 15, 5, 5, 5, 5, 10, 5, 10, 15, 20, 30, 35,
and then I want. Dermot gave my phone a virus. I did not do that. You were downloading something.
You were downloading something and you got caught with a virus. I didn't do it.
Literally a worse politician than Homer Simpson. No, I'm not. I'm not a worse politician.
We're gonna do 20. I want, I want the Pacific coast is mine. I get 15. That's,
I can do 17. I feel like I want to just fail this because I don't want whatever. All
right. I went up in Massachusetts. 140. Gandalf is losing the mid-Atlantic
in favor of Homer Simpson. No, the south there, down south. They're really just,
it's too far out of reach. And I'm a fucking third party candidate. I just, by default,
get like 5% of the vote. That's what's going on here. It's going up in all these other
states. No, none of them. I'm not going to win. Ooh, wait a minute. California. Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. California is huge. California is like the most important.
It's like the biggest one. Holy shit. I might win if I do this right. And I got Hawaii
and I got Oregon and I got Washington. I got the whole Pacific coast. Gandalf refuses to,
no, I'm not debating. I don't want to debate anybody. I'm not gonna have any more serious
gaffes. Gandalf. All right. I've got 13 there. All right. Anybody leaning towards my way?
Yes, let's go. Okay. The latest monthly consumer price index showed an increase of 1.7%. The
rate of inflation for the past six months is now 17.7%. Somewhat unfavorable news.
I would think so. Okay. National campaigning. Cover his entire nation. States will,
yeah, yeah, yeah. Not to spend. I want to spend it all. 1867. Go all in. Massachusetts
got it locked in except Homer Simpson. Fuck off. I got Maine. I got Jersey. I got Maryland.
I'm tied with Delaware. So how come we go to the map? Why do I only have Massachusetts?
80, Florida. No. 43, 52. No. When we get to the industrial Midwest, I lose everything.
I'm not going to get it. The Midwest is a toss up here. I got Kansas. The West.
Homer Simpson's got Nevada. Pacific Coast. I lost it again. Gandalf. I'm going to go to,
no, no, no. I have to debate. I get to debate next week. God damn it. How do I get another
state? Third party is hard mode. Yeah. Why did I do third party? Unemployment was 20%.
All right. Let's debate. I'm going for it. 1661. I'm spending all my money, but
I got to get a debate in here. I have to win some points. My only hope is California Hail Mary.
No. Gandalf is locking it in. Let's go. Debate. Let's go. How many questions
would there be? Let's do three questions. Homer Simpson will answer first. Do you
intend to follow an environmental policy that will be more or less restrictive on business?
Homer Simpson says he's going to state his side and he's going to contrast it with mine.
So we have a very different opinion, apparently. We're going to go 20%. I'm going to state 30% my
opinions, contrast it about 25%. I'm going to say your policies are a little, a little weird.
I don't know. I don't like your policies. I'm going to go just kill time.
That's pretty balanced. Now he's clarifying his position and he's killing time.
He's not criticizing me, which means he knows he's wrong. Okay. So I'm going to,
I'm going to clarify mine again and then we're going to criticize.
So let's, let's get a real good, like 35% clarification. 10% here, 25% here.
Let's, you're a little bit uninformed on this 15% here and then we'll do a little bit of time
killing. I think that's pretty good. What did I do? What, how is this a gaffe? What did I
gaffe? You, you kept Clara, I didn't wear pants to the debate. Yeah, I'm at the podium
and that's why I think our environment is incredibly important to protect. Like cheering,
cheering. Yeah. I think that we need to be very, very careful with how we do and deal
with new industries. And I take a little step to the side, right of the podium.
And I also believe I don't have any pants on. Oh, what the, I think that we need to be
on point here with every part of our environmental lifestyles. And I looked down
and I'm like, what the, and I like put both hands down like that's going to help
like covering me. Oh, I'm like covering, even though that doesn't do anything.
And like I tilt my knees in, then I go back like right, left, left, left, left, left, left,
over to the podium. All right. Am I in favor of changes? Discuss relevant considerations.
And now let's, let's go contrast and then attack and then we'll kill some time.
I'm contrasting, I'm attacking. This is a gaffe. Okay. So now he has to stay
at his own positions and he's killing time. So I should now, I should now criticize,
or I should imply that they're uninformed because like, oh yeah, you're just wrong.
Everything you just said was wrong. And I've already clarified mine and you,
you just spent that time clarified. So you're wrong. Let's go with,
I already did this like 15% emphasis. I wouldn't, I'm not going to criticize.
Let's go with like 5%, 5%. Implied that they're uninformed. 50%. Like, no, that's,
is that going to be a gaffe? 40% and then we'll just kill around. That's a lot of time killing
though. That's too much time killing. No, it wasn't. Okay. Clarifying. He's saying that
I'm uninformed and he's killing time. All right. Well, I think I've won that one.
No gaffe. And I look at, look at how fucked up he is right here.
What thoughts do you have on the situation in South Africa and to what degree should
we press our objections? He's like, I don't know. I don't know. I should just run over
there and just shove him because he didn't take a step to his left. He's got, he's
naked too. I'm the only one that can see that. So I'm, you know, I should do it.
All right. So now I'm going to say, discuss relevant considerations, state my positions,
bang, contrast positions with opponents and attack. Watch this one. Ready? 25%.
Contrast. We're going to go to, let's see, 25% state my opinions. I want these to,
at least one of these has to be big. Attack opponent's position probably has to be,
I'm trying to think of like points wise, probably 30, 30, 30, 10 or 30, 40, 0. Oh,
no. God damn it. I forgot I did 20 on the one, the first one, the one before. God damn it.
Whatever. I got my point across. See, he's fucked up anyways. Now he's going to clarify
and he's implying that I'm informed and you kill in time. Okay. Well,
now we don't have a shirt on. Clarify own positions. That was an actual gaffe.
I thought I did like 10 for some reason. I was just going too fast. Strip debating.
All right. I'm going to, I'm not going to criticize. I'm going to maybe morals. We'll do 10,
10 and then we'll do like 60 or 50 and then 20 or 40. Yeah. Well, no, no, no, 40 and 30.
This is not going to be a gaffe. I came fucking close to on the points. God damn it.
What's this intangibles bullshit? How a 20 to six fucking playing on third party mode.
I should have just picked like the Democrat. I would have gotten free points. I should have
picked Republican. I would have got like free points already. I'm starting with my ass against
the wall. Gandalf's running mate was abroad for six days last week and received good press.
They're very pleased. I'm almost out of money too. I have to go. I mean, I'm not going to
win. It's not possible. I'm not going to win. There's no way I can win. Why are these all
so close? I got to release a catchy tune. Gandalf always refuses to debate. I seriously
should have listened. Oh, I dropped. I have, oh no, my own state left me. They went to Gandalf.
I was naked too many times on stage at this point. You drop out, you know, it's like,
I concede to my fellow candidates that I wasn't up to the task of running our nation.
Or apparently I got to get one state. Oh, Gandalf says a debate may be possible this week
if the staff can agree on a time. Let's all three of us. Do all three candidates agree to
debate each other simultaneously? Yeah. Okay. Here comes the big debate. I'm supposed to be
dropped out. Only two questions. Homer Simpson always gets to go first by luck of the drop
bullshit. He's like stuffing the ballot box. He's, he's stuffing the ballot box. I spoke
to Homer Simpson. Do you believe, I think I'm, you know what, because I've already lost,
I'm just going to act like a fucking idiot. I'm going to attack everybody and kill time,
every question. I've already lost. I'm just up there because I'm rich and I can keep blowing
money. I could keep burning money. I have no states. I have no votes. I'm just the other
guy that's there being annoying at this point. And I'm, and I'm going to go fully nude.
I'm not going to be embarrassed this time. I'm going to own it. I'm going for it. Here we go.
Do you believe our foreign and domestic competitiveness has been hurt by recent
merger and acquisition activity in the private sector? Oh yeah. How about this one? Yeah.
Fucking who gives a shit. State opposition. I'm smoking a cigarette on stage now. Yeah. Who
gives a fuck? By the way, he sucks. He's dumb. His TV show went on for way too many seasons
to a point where it's just sad now. Gandalf, do you believe our foreign and domestic
competitiveness has been, you know, like the same question to you?
Well, I think that yes, I'll at least state my position on those. Great.
Homer Simpson's killing time. No, that's fine. Hey, hey, Gandalf. Hey, Gandalf.
Really made that big blunder sending everybody into the, uh, the goblin town,
didn't you? That was a real stupid idea. Whoa. Oh yeah. Yeah. Oh yeah. Say it. Say it.
Everyone's booing me. Look at this. Look at me. And like they have to fucking sit me down.
I'll sit down. And I'm like kind of freaking everybody up. 16% emphasis.
Well, my opponent is really just, I kind of, these circumstances are just a little too much
for me to handle. I'm going to just say that we should be more nice to each other.
What does your stand on the death penalty? Do you feel our criminal justice system is
overly lenient? Well, I think that it's possible we could have two different debates
and figure out what this could be. And I think this, and this is exactly how I believe.
Yeah, I think that is, I don't really like this question, but so maybe if you get,
oh yeah, I maybe move on to a new question. I think we should kill them both. Both of these
clowns right now. I've sat for a position. Yeah. Yeah. We're not even real characters.
We're all fictional. I think that you are out of your mind. Legalized method. Emphasizing my
current positions. Oliver Simpson is really, really distraught over this one. My opponent
doesn't understand, but we're cartoon characters, so we can't die anyways. They used to die in Tom
and Jerry every episode. I love Tom and Jerry. It was my favorite TV show. I especially liked it
when they used to hit each other with hammers on the head. When I was a kid, I used to laugh
at it. That is 13. I'm probably going to get removed. I'm going to get removed. How did
Homer Simpson win again? Unfortunately, it has been, I still got, I got 22% of the popular vote
though. People are still voting for me. Across the country, there's a bunch of just like
sickos. Hey, let's vote. Yeah. I like what he's doing up there. I like what he talks
shit to Gandalf. I love his position on Tom and Jerry cartoons. Yeah. Fuck the other
candidates. All right. Only two weeks to go. We have to see this through. Inflation increased
by 2%. That's so bad. Gandalf had a questionable statement, probably because he was talking
about me. I don't want to be on stage with that maniac anymore. He's purely uninformed and
possibly insane. Oh boy, I dropped out big time here. I know what it's like to deal with
maniacs. Sauron, Saruman, all of them. He reminds me of them when they were younger.
He may as well change his name to Smurma because all bad guys names start with an S
and end with an O and he should be Smurron. Holy fuck, I'm losing bad. How did Homer Simpson,
this looks like this is just a fucking like you hold down tab in an online game.
Homer Simpson just doing too good to a point where like you don't want them in the server
anymore. You know what I mean? You even like hold down tab and you just like got 315 points.
Okay, I'm going somewhere else. North Dakota and South Dakota both do not like me at all.
Who knows this even bad? It's 408. What happened? Do I wish to debate?
Gandalf doesn't want to debate. I'm not debating. This is the last week. One week to go.
Unemployment was 20%. Gaffs committed Homer Simpson. They're like, I've kind of like
detonated the space here. Like I said a bunch of crazy shit and now they're like
backpedaling, stepping forward, making like gaffs and questionable statements. I'm really
like Homer committed a gaff. All right. So I got eight. Yeah, spin it all. Who cares?
I'm just doing this for fun. Massachusetts, 120 points. Yeah, I remember when I had
Massachusetts. They all thought I was awesome. And then I read in the newspaper I was naked
five times on stage. And all those other brutes didn't like it. They all said I should
put some clothes on. I said, yeah. During the interview, German 95 was also nude.
Why say I should not have to do that? It's Ed Bighead. No, no, you're talking about
the other Bighead. Bighead. That's that's Ed Bighead. Bighead's wife was what was
Bighead's wife's name? Bev. Yeah, that's Bev Bighead is unwilling to debate at this time.
I'm just going to take the loss and leave. No, I don't want to debate. I'm done. I give up.
I'm not debating anymore. I'm taking the loss. This is the final week. Good news.
The economic indicators are up. Yeah, whatever. Spend the last $6.56. Not like I care.
Yeah, apparently the people of Maine and Rhode Island also do not care because I have
almost 33% of the vote for this week, polling wise. Here's the final debate. This is the last
the presidential debate. Unwilling is why would you be unwilling to? Yeah, let's go.
Let's go. Yeah, the guy that's running everything, the guy that's winning everything.
One question, two questions, two questions. Okay, I get to answer first.
What's this? This is interesting. Everyone's kind of sitting in their seats right now
looking in sort of confusion. German985 has come on stage in a suit with styled hair and looks
like he had some work. He had like green teeth last time. Looks like he had some work done on
his teeth and he smells considerably better and people are a little concerned about this.
He's just normal. He gets the first question. He comes on stage and he's very just relaxed.
Uh, uh, we can begin the debate. Now, um, Mr. Albertson, given recent demographic trends,
what is the likelihood of your administration proposing a return to selective service system?
Well, on further positioning and moving my name around and looking at the facts,
trying to find out what is real and what isn't and all of us have different things
and different opinions that we all care about and decide that is important. And every single day
we come together as a group of not, not this person, this person, but as Americans to gaze
upon the beauty of my body. Oh, God damn it. He ripped his clothes. He fucking depated us.
God damn it. He did it again. Yeah. Get the fucking cops in here. I don't care. Hey,
uh, get off me. I don't care if I fucking lose.
Give it. Get off. I'll rip your head off. I'll kill him. Get him in the car.
I'm not, I'm not going down without a fight.
So who won? Silence. Gandalf gets the most. Okay. I was hard not to laugh at that
because it said Gandalf seems to have come out the most from this debate.
He probably was like, fuck you. No, I can't say that on TV. Project next date. Okay.
So what state is this? Ooh. Holy shit. I got 634,000 votes.
Let's just go to the final. Fuck this. Did I get any states? No, I don't think so.
Well, the results are in. Ladies and gentlemen, your newest president of the United States
of America. Please welcome to the stage Gandalf. He wins a landslide. That's so fucking
ridiculous. Chairman at five is was last seen being taken to the local penitentiary.
He said in the back of the squad car, if you let me just open the door and fall out on the
highway, pretending, and this is a direct quote, pretending that I escaped, I will deposit
a hundred grand into both of your bank accounts. He now awaits trial.
Look at this map. It's like never been a map like this. I think this has happened like twice in
history. You got a fully, a fully red, a fully red west and east coast, and the middle is blue.
That very, that doesn't ever happen. The color's a flip. No, Homer Simpson was,
was the Democrat, wasn't he? Wait, what? No, red, red was, was Homer Republican?
Wait, hold on. I get invited to the inauguration? Why would they do blue Republican and red
Democrat? That's been like that for like hundreds of years. All right, I get to go to
the inauguration. I'm in like cuffs and like an orange suit. See, president. Oh, there it is.
It's time to move on to the next one. It's been like that for millions of years.
That was president-elect 1988 edition. So where to now? Oh, this is incorrect though.
This needs to be like this. There we go. So we were down here. You've been invited to the
inauguration and with a pair of clothes. So it was down here, right here somewhere, right here.
All right, we've got one more from this list. You'll be able to click in just a second.
Here we go. Remember, you have to be able to see the text. I'm not doing leisure suit,
Larry. No, no. Go again. It's not a porn game. It is the original porn game. It's the porn game
to create all porn games. It's the one that they based all the other porn games off of.
Every porn game that you've played in the last 10 years is because of the porn game that
was the leisure suit Larry porn game. Damn it. All right, you ready? Ready for this?
All you guys want your porn games. Stop saying porn game. Well, sorry guys. I can't play it.
I tried. I clicked it. I'll try it again. I'll click it one more time. We'll see.
Leisure suit Larry. Land of the Lounge Lizards. All right. I'm going to for total transparency.
Look, it actually fucking worked. First sound in an hour and a half. Okay.
Oh, leisure suit. Leisure suit Larry in the land of the lounge lizards contain some
elements of plot which may not be suitable. They may not be appropriate for children.
No, how old are you? Oh, okay. Oh, it's not a porn game. We just have a click,
a age verification click thing. It's not a porn game though. Hey, look, I still get to click
this one. Yeah, sure you are. To verify your age, please answer the five simple questions.
Ah, who lost a daughter but gained a meathead? I don't fucking know.
I don't know what this is. Which U.S. and there's like boobs back.
Not that this like a shirt on. Which U.S. Secretary of State was born in Germany?
Who was the inventive genius behind the Apple computer? That's Steve Wozniak.
Close encounters of the third kind is about creatures from outer space. Yes.
IBM stands for itsy bitsy men. It's international business machines.
And now a question that won't tax your memory. This question refers to
your documentation that came with your copy of the game. Okay, so we can't play this one.
The gal sitting around the campfire is playing a what? This is your one chance.
I ain't, I'm not looking it up. No, I refuse to look this up. Is it B? B, here's your chance.
Smart map. Oh, hold on. I can't really get it. Here you go. Smart map. This is your shot.
I can't reset it because I have to, I'm stuck in this window. It looks like it's harmonica.
I'm clicking harmonica. You guys, this is why you can't have nice things.
It's actually B. I looked it up. Did you look it up? Was this real?
Thank you. And now slip into your leisure suit and prepare to enter the land of
lounge lizards with leisure shoot suit Larry. Okay, I got it ready. All right,
there I am. I want to exit this game just because how slow you move.
Why is he like an octopus? He's like a squid. I guess we're gonna go in here. This is a bar.
Nice tuck and roll. What? So that right click is change. Right click changes what you do.
That's porn music. This is porn. Okay, we're good. Why is Dr. Dawn back here? That's Dr.
Dan. He has nothing to say but says it continuously. You coily turn your back and
relieve yourself. You quickly feel much better. The hint of smile. What? Did I just piss on the
ground? This place has no taste. I can like taste things? To you, Lefty has no distinctive
smell or taste. You greet the bartender with a friendly hello. What'll it be? Around. Around
for everybody. Are you sure? It'll cost you $90. Do I not have that money? Blah, blah,
blah. Yackity, yackity, yackity, yackity, blah, blah. Because Thursday's your night in the barrel.
Har har. What? Why am I moving so slow? Talk to someone in particular. Can I leave? Can I speed
up this emulator? I don't think... I mean this is just like on a website. It's like a browser.
I'm not sure I can do it from here. Is it rad on the guy's head? You take pity on the poor
drunken want to help him, but his odor convinces you otherwise. Oh, fuck. There we go. Oh, Jesus.
That's so much better. All right. We're going up? Down? Where are we going? Into the bar?
Through the toilet. Did it crash? I crashed. I think it was like fucked up. Something happened.
I saw Leisure Suit Larry's dick and then like he started shitting. So no, we're not
gonna do that one. I'm sorry. I'm not doing that one. Uh, not gonna happen. Nope. Sorry.
We'll get him next time. No, vetoing all of them now. I'm gonna use my actual real veto power.
Call me a tyrant. I'm using my true veto powers. So that brings us to here. Now we've done three.
Let's go down to here. Make sure we get the ones with the text only. Text only. Remember,
that's very important. And here we go. Please click what you'd like to see. Wow,
this is all over the place. This is very, very, very spread out, but there is a clear
winner. Very much so. With 35% or 37% of the vote at this point. Everyone seems to be changing
their mind. Thank you for voting. That's all we need to see. To spread out. Where in the USA
is Carmen Sandiego? Thank you for voting. 1993. C is Mount... whatever that said. I think this
is the Zumbini's people by the way. I already like this one. Where are we? Where in the USA
are we? That's a huge antenna. That would be poking you in like the mouth and nose and
shit. That would go up your nose and kill you. You would like, you would sneeze and that antenna
would go into your nose, through your nostril, into your brain and you die. What are we doing?
Eject. Eject. Where is she? Where did she go? She went somewhere in the United States.
This is me? Vile. Vile. Vile. What? Is this Carmen Sandiego's like group of people?
You're taking a very long time to do this. Why couldn't you just pick them up?
They're like the airport. Okay. ACME. Okay. Come choose. ACME Detective Registration.
Enter your name. No. Okay. How do I go back? Can I delete that? Where's backspace? Is there
no backspace? Use the keyboard? Oh fuck. No, it's cancel. Okay. Transmit. Verifying identity.
Updating ACME Detective Roster. Stand by for an important message from the Chief.
Hey. I'm gonna turn this up. Agent Germa rank gumshoe.
Okay. Location New York. We have until Sunday at 8 p.m. It is Monday. We have a week
in New York. All the lights on Broadway have been stolen. Let me turn this up for you guys.
Every light. Okay. So let's call the ACME Travel Services. We're gonna get to New York.
To start your investigation, call ACME Travel Service. I was gonna click it.
We only have one option anyways. I can't. It's gonna just do it. Manhattan Island.
The heart of New York City is connected to the mainland by a number of
bridges. Perhaps the most famous of these is the graceful arching Brooklyn Bridge,
which links Manhattan to the borough of Brooklyn. Speak to student. He cried
off for Omaha. Who did? Check campus. Item book description titled Adventures on the
Old Oregon Trail. There's a chapter missing about the trail along the Platte River.
Oregon Trail. Oregon. All right. Telephone Crime Net.
Message from Crime Net. Plane closed. Cop reports seeing suspect in the plane
state north of Kansas. What? Okay. So we got to go north of Kansas. We don't have,
I mean we could go here. Should we go to Lincoln? Go to Florida. Lincoln, Nebraska. Let's go.
She's going to be in the car and drive off. Sleeping, sleeping, sleeping, sleeping, sleeping,
sleeping. Nebraska has top notch hunting, fishing, and camping to attract those who
love the great outdoors. For those who prefer to take their outdoor recreation sitting down,
that person died. There's a multitude of rodeos to visit. What is that supposed to be?
When I think of Nebraska, I don't think of circus performers.
Okay. So let's speak to the violinist. He said he had a capital idea to infiltrate
the capital building of the spud state. He asked me if I knew a good mambo teacher.
That would be Idaho. Check the pit. This is the dictaphone. Description heard on tape.
It all boils down to this, small fry. When searching for the spud state, look under capital
I. Dustin. All right. Idaho. Keep your eyes peeled for the criminal in the spud state.
You've got it. Boise. What the fuck is this game? It's called Freelance Palish. Open up.
Although much of Idaho's mountains terrain is not well suited for agriculture.
There's ice skating in Idaho? That was a, what's going on? Okay. Some parts of the state
can successfully support ranches and farms. Cattle ranching and dairy farming are both
important here, but Idaho's most famous product is the potato. Let's talk to the jogger.
He indicated he'd be transplanting himself to Baltimore for a caper at Johns Hopkins medical
school. Beware of anyone who challenges you to a game of go fish. It's fucking Mario. Super
Mario. Call it in. Okay. So, but just Maryland? Do we just have to fly back and forth?
U.S. Naval Academy on Chesapeake Bay. Yeah. Okay. So we just have to go to Maryland now.
What day is it? Do we have any evidence? Enter evidence and press transmit. Oh no. Oh no, no,
no, no. Wait, wait. I didn't want to do this. Cancel. This game is nonsense. A coquette
made this game. What? What are you talking about? All right. Let's go to Maryland.
Why would you, what does that even mean? Okay. Question jogger again.
Oh, gold teeth. Is that him? That's the worst one yet. That's not how you hide to Ivan. Okay.
He was determined to lose himself in the largest state in the nation. He collected recipes from
Paris. Okay. Um, well, I know, mail, hair hobby, card games, gardening, painting, star
card games, go fish. Do we get my, we should have been doing this.
All right. Let's like enter that into evidence. Transmit that.
Warn division. Wanda here. Oh, no, no, no. I don't want to, I don't want to warn. Stand by.
I know that he's mail and likes card games. I've sent you a list of possible suspects.
Every Magic the Gathering convention. That's it. Hallelujah. And Ray Zerumpis are the only
two people in the country that are male and like card games. Okay. This is the fair city
of Fairbanks. Our biggest state in the, what is it? Fucking Alaska, Texas. Which one is it?
California. Are we talking like volume? It's Texas. Yeah, let's go. What do you mean?
It is Alaska. I had it right. Okay. What do you mean I didn't know that?
You're dumping trash here? What are you, why are you dumping trash in Alaska? That's not even like,
hey, I'm a bad guy spying on you. We're just dumping in Alaska. What? Okay. So let's talk
to the actress. There are a lot of shady characters lurking around here. I'd be
careful if I were you. By the way, do you have a warrant? That's Carmen San Diego right
there. Arrest. How do you arrest a person? She's gone. File written in large black letters
in the front. Okay. I just let Carmen San Diego go. There they go. We're going in the Ghostbusters
car. Did we get them? Urgent report. Ray Zarumpis has just been tracked to Alaska by
Gumshoe Jerma. However, the suspect could not be held because the arresting officer
did not have a warrant. No, you're going to have to try. Okay. Are you ready for another
case? No, I don't really want to fly from city to city. That was fun. That was cute. It was fun.
It was like a game for kids. That's going to be it for that one. It was like a game. You know,
it was like a game for kids. Alright, so we got a couple more to do here. Get the list back
on. It was right here, if I'm not mistaken, right? Right here. This looks correct. Is it
correct or was it down more like right here? Yeah, it was right there. Okay. So remember
the text on the screen. Do not click ones that do not have text. Like don't click down here.
You're not going to be valid. Only places with text. Here we go. Please click on the
screen where you'd like us to go next. It's up to you, not up to me.
Interesting. Interesting selections. How many times can you click once? One click per person.
That's as many. It's not going to count if you do it again. It's only going to count the first
time. So we got 32%. We're going to burger time. Thank you for voting. We will come back here
and we will do the last one on this list. So yeah, I'm not going to click. I'm going to
actually open a new window. Burger time. This is by 1982. This is really old. I failed to
download the metadata. Oh no, why is that? Good places to be. Mattel Electronics presents
Burger Time. Type joystick or keyboard to start. I mean we have to use keyboard. Press the space
bar to start the game. Press the zero key to select options. To pause game. What were the
controls? Which character am I? What's going on? To pepper, press the space bar. To move
the chef, use the up down left right. Okay. Here we go. If you don't know how to do
burger time, burger time is you have to make a hamburger. Wait, don't you have to
knock them down? Oh no, you have to kill them by knocking them down. Now I remember. I thought
you had to make. Oh no, you do have to make a burger. No, no, I'm right. I was right. I was
right. Oh, I got it. All right. I got to get this one right. See if we can get them all.
Get it. Oh, I need a bun. Bait them over here. Down. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops. Oops.
It's okay. Let's close this one out. Bingo. Oh, I thought they were going to go hey.
They're all clumped up too. Oops. There's one burger done. I'm just going to do buns.
Fuck. I thought they're going to keep walking. What is this thing? Is it like a power up?
Got it. All right. Let's do. Let's wait. We got time. Oh, not good. Not good. Not good.
I have to bait this one. Let me get all four burgs all the way, all the way, all the way,
all the way up, all the way. Bait them all over here. Every single one. Oh, that was close.
Get them all. All four. No, I'm going to get collapsed on. Oh, no, no. Pepper, pepper,
pepper, pepper, pepper, pepper. I'm dead. Fuck. I'm so mad. Oh, my god damn. No, I got an extra life.
Shit. I try to get them. I got to go all the way up. Coffee. Oh, fuck. Right here. Right here.
Right here. Got it. I have no pepper left, do I? Uh-oh. I got to go down. Now. Fuck.
I got two more lives. I'm losing them here. Oh, I lost it. I can still do it.
Oh, no. Ah. No. Fuck. This game is so much fun. Come on. I can do it. I get to level three.
I can do it. I have two more buns. Baited. Good work. I hate it. That's it. Fuck.
I had it too. I was doing so well. Last try. Last try. This is the last one. Straight up.
No, come up here. Straight up. No unnecessary deaths here. And then smush them. Smush.
I can't believe I didn't get it. I'm fucking done. I'm exiting. I just. I got too greedy.
I really did. I didn't get that. I'm losing it. That was greedy too, but it was worth it.
Too bad I don't have anything to do anything right here, but I can get something right now.
If I get up there quick enough, I can get at least one of them. Stupid. Stupid little
lettuces. Whatever you are. Give me points. All right. Last one. And then I'm going to go
for the clothes here. Oh, fuck. I got to go up. Oh, no. Pepper. It's close. They're
pickles. You dill. What are the other things? Onions? Ah, too greedy. Don't do it. I got
so greedy. I'm you. I'm doing too much pepper. I need this pepper. I'm going too fast. Oh,
dude. I'm going to, you know, I'm going to watch somebody do like a full speed run
of this game tomorrow. Why tomorrow? I don't know. All right. I'm going to do this one.
I'm going to get it. Perfect. After that person speeds by the house as fast as they can.
Start from the top. Didn't get it. Didn't get it. It's okay. No, he went up the other
way. He went up the other way. Damn it. I thought he was going to go down. Get over
here. What the fuck was that shit? He walked to the right. What was that little juke to
the right? I can't fucking believe he went that way. Oh, God damn it. That game's a
lot of fun, but it's really hard. Okay. Where are we going? Gamer in his natural habitat,
making noise to attract his mate. That's one of those old arcade cabinet games.
It's a good one. All right. Um, Catacombs 3D. I believe this says gamer's edge,
the gamer's edge, apparently 54%. Thank you for voting. We're going to Catacombs 3D.
Here we go. Uh, it's gamer's edge. This looks like a bloody game is by id software.
If you're curious, this is like a doom game or video molds, CGA, EGA, VGA, um,
keyboard memory. I think this looks all right. Catacombs 3D, gamer's edge. It's a 1-800
number. id software. You know who those people are. It's high score. Joe, Steph, Sir Lancelot,
and Boombi. New game. Normal. Entering the approach. Oh, I can use the mouse.
Woe be to he that entereth my domain. Grem, Grelminar, the lich.
Whoa, I just threw a fireball. Path to keep. Okay. I guess I throw fireballs
and I can throw a nuke. I'm just going to queue it up the whole time. Just hold it.
Got him. Holy shit, that was creepy. It's like bullet travel. Keys, scrolls. Okay. A portal.
Actual Diablo portal. What's wrong with my face? Why am I wearing a... Okay, I'm in the keep.
The charge is the best. I hear somebody walking. Fire walls? Oops.
Chest over here. Potions? Help? Heals. Okay. There's just money in that chest.
Ooh, nukes. How does one use a nuke? Oh, that felt pretty good. Heals and nukes.
I hear somebody. And I got a key. Where is this person? They're freaking me out.
What is... I don't understand. Oh, here's the key. Let me check over here. Did I go this way?
Maybe H is to heal? H. H is heal. I want to get to the boss, at least.
That's my footsteps? I'm talking about this. That just means you can't go any further.
I have the key. I also got lightning bolt. Yeah, this is just operation. All right, key.
We're in here now. All right, next level. B for bolt. Well, I don't need it yet.
Is it N for nuke? Good. Two bolts. Three bolts. Motion sickness. Yeah, I'm getting it too.
I am getting it too. You're right. Why'd you say that? Now I'm getting it. Oh, no. Yeah. Yeah,
you're right. It's bad. Eject. Eject. Eject. No, no. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. I can
handle it for like another minute. This is the bad type of motion sickness. This game's fun,
though. It's a cool game. Spray and pray? I'm not spraying and praying. I'm landing shots.
Blue key. Out. Let's go. Anybody remember what anything was? Drop a nuke? I'll drop a nuke
before we leave. Here we go. Blue key. All right. I'm going to barf. All right.
I'm going to nuke and then I'm still alive though. I need red key. Just get it. Just
stand like a few feet away from your screen. Oh my God. That was bolt. Bolt's just rapid
fire. Big ball. I'm going to nuke the next person I see. Nuke. I'm hovering over it.
It just goes out around the whole room. Okay. It's very fun. This is a cool game,
but I think we have to move on before everyone pukes. You missed the nuke?
I can't do it again. Yeah. Okay. This is really cool though. I don't want to make
everybody puke because I'm like feeling it. That's a cool game. Cool. It is cool.
That was very, for how long ago that was? That's, you know, that's the titans of the video game
industry. Come on. So now we're going to go down. We're going to scroll for the first time
tonight, right? Oh no. Did we scroll before? No, no, no. For the second time. So we were here.
This is what we did. Now we're going to go down here. Here is, okay. So like right here.
There we go. Because that, oh, because Hocus Pocus, no, Hocus Pocus was up there. Right here.
Remember it's the text on the screen. So that looks, was House of Horrors up there?
I don't think it was. It's just weird that they're in such strange places.
That looks all right. All right. Are you ready? Please vote right now. Girlfriend
construction set. Oh God. Girlfriend construction. Resize the zoom. I actually, before the stream
started, I tried a bunch of stuff. I tried going zooming in and out. I tried refreshing. I tried
clearing cache. It's something about when you go down a few times, it just kind of does this.
All right. Well, this is girlfriend construction set. I'm going to, thanks for voting.
First of all, second of all, I'm concerned about this one because this could be a porn
game. Let's see. Um, let's see. Uh, start a new game. Enter your first name. I don't want to
put my real name. Bill. Enter the first name of the girl you wish to create.
Didn't they make a movie on this like a long time ago? It's not going to do Kim. Something
like, um, Janice. I don't know. Henrietta. Jen. How about just Jen. Select a face.
All right. I want like one, I think. I think it's going to be number one.
Definitely one. No, I'm picking this. It's one. Enter Jen's height. 60 inches is five.
I'm 62 inches guys. No, no, no, I'm not. No, I'm not. No, I'm not. 60. What am I? What
is like five eight? No, that's five. That would be five two. Um, I'm like 60. What is it? 68?
That's five two. No, I'm, I'm, that's like, I'm 68 or 69. Just don't. So 60. We'll do 63.
Um, Jen's overall body rating is zero. How attractively does Jen dress?
Rubby. How trustworthy is Jen? Uh, seven. How often does Jen get jealous? Um, not really.
How would you rate Jen's personality? Very friendly. What's Jen's type of mood? Jesus.
Uh, seven. How well do you get along with Jen's friends and how well does she get along with
yours? They hate each other. Is Jen desperate to get married? Very desperate. What is Jen's
level of sexual activity? Oh, she can be a while. Um, I don't know, right in the middle.
Overall rating of Jen is 34. Bill's status points is 50. Date selected. Go out to dinner. Call
girlfriend. Jen, do you want to go out to dinner? Yes, I'd love it. You get to the
restaurant and find your table. After taking your order, the waiter returns and accidentally
spills soup all over your date's blouse. Jen says, oh, that hurts. You punch out the
waiter and get arrested. Jen waves at you as you are being fitted with handcuffs. Nice.
Get off me. Get off me. No, I'm gonna go to dinner. Yeah, I'd love it. You go to dinner
to a fancy restaurant. When you get inside, you see a really hot lady in a low cut dress.
You stare intently at her cleavage. Jen gives you a dirty look. She's not my type.
You sit down at your table while you're waiting for the waiter to come and take your order.
Jen reaches under the table and starts acting bored. You each have a very enjoyable dinner,
Jen asks. Do you want to order some rich fattening desserts? Sure, let's do it.
What happened? Can we do anything besides go out to dinner? You get to the restaurant
and the waiter comes over. Oh, excuse me. Oh, whoops, I spilled. Fuck you.
You get arrested. Get off me. Next week. You want to go to dinner? I'm sorry,
Bill. I can't go out with you anymore. You got dumped. No, no, no, no, 180. This person's
like a stick bug. Skeleton weighs more than that. I fucked it up. Okay, date list. Jesus.
Go horseback riding. That sounds like fun. Gene, do you want to go horseback riding?
I don't think so. Go skiing. Gene, do you want to go skiing in the Alps?
Okay. You and your girlfriend arrive in Switzerland and you hit the slopes. After a very active day
of skiing, you retire to the lodge and snuggle up to a warm fire. Just the two of you sitting
by the fire. Gene says, isn't this romantic? It really is. I suppose so. I guess so. Let's
just shut up. Let's go drink some dark beer. Um, I suppose. You two are sitting together
enjoying a moment of great intimacy. She looks long in the eye with glazed eyes,
then suddenly Gene sighs, let's get married right now. You're kidding? I don't think that
would be such a good idea at this time. I think we need... You two decide to get married and
have your honeymoon right there. Gene looks stunning in her beautiful wedding dress. She
brought the wedding dress with her on our first date. The happy couple lives happily ever after
in the suburbs for a few months. Eventually you both realize the marriage was a mistake.
You have more and more bitter fights. Finally, Gene divorces you and takes half your money.
Oh shit. Go to... How about go? She's an aunt. Go to the big party.
Jessica, do you want to go to the big party? No way, I'm not that dumb. Do you want to
go to the zoo? She's gonna get like licked up by a giraffe. No way, I'm not that dumb to
go to the zoo. You're not stupid enough to go to the zoo. What about the opera?
Do you want to go to the opera? I'm not that dumb. Um, do you, uh, you want to go
fly to Vegas for the weekend? No, I'm not that stupid. What is not stupid? Go to Hawaii for lunch.
No way, I'm not that dumb. These are all extravagant, incredibly expensive, insanely
awesome dates. Do you want to come over? No way, I'm not that dumb. Aren't we dating?
Aren't we... What are you talking about? Go to, uh, go mail strip joint. No way, I'm not
that dumb. No, I'm not that stupid. Go to dinner? No. Apparently that's not stupid,
it's just no. You want to go shopping? Forget it. You want to go to the bar? No, I'm not
stupid. Would you like to just, would you like to go to a rock concert? Some other time,
maybe. Would you like to go to a Broadway show? No, I'm, I'm smart. Would you like
to go to a party to one of my friend's place? No, I'm, I'm smart. You want to
play strip poker? No way, I'm not that dumb. Do you want to go fishing? Uh, no way,
I'm not, I'm, I'm very, fishing is for stupid, stupid idiots, huh? Uh, play strip
monopoly. You want to do that? No, no, monopoly's dumb, it's for dumb people. You
want to go to a hockey game? Hockey's not even, she likes hockey. You arrive at the
hockey game with your date. Early in the game, one of the players gets thrown into
the boards right near your seat. Jessica is startled and puts an arm around you impulsively.
Oh my fucking god. Oh my god. Uh, relax, it's fine. The game starts to get really
exciting. Someone almost scores a goal. Suddenly two players start fighting. Then
four players are going at it. Then the entire teams are fighting. The bench is
empty. All the players are out on the ice fighting. Then the crowd starts
fighting. A couple of bald guys with beer belly start punching away nearby.
One of them is thrown sprawling into you too. Jessica starts punching
with wild abandon. Why? Why would I do that? What? Aren't we on the same team?
We're on the same team. There's no reason for that. Just like, oh yeah, oh here comes
a big fight. Get him. Two bald guys are fighting us. Hey, honey. Wrong person.
What the fuck are you talking about? We're on the same team. She's punching.
No! Are you out of your fucking mind? We're on the same damn team.
That was certainly a messy scene. The hockey game is finally over. Neither of you has any
idea who won. Does it really matter? You both get back to your car while avoiding
the hyper drunk fans. Jessica remarks, hockey is really stupid. You're a moron.
Wasn't she just... She started fighting before I did. She was throwing punches before I even...
She was beating people up? Hey, want to come over to my place? She thinks over your offer
for a moment. Then Jessica says, no way. I'm not that kind of girl. Here, have a flower.
You pull up in her driveway and shut off the engine. She gets out of the car and you
follow her and walk to the door. She frowns and says, get lost. Okay. So long. So long. See
you later. Whatever. I can't win with you. I dump her before she dumps me. Quick. Yes.
So every idea is stupid. I don't want to go to dinner. Finally, I want to go to a hockey game.
She says, yes. Uh, the crowd starts fighting. She starts punching people in the face.
She starts beating people up. I joined the fray and I'm like, we're on the same team.
Hey, that was crazy. You're stupid. You're a moron. Okay. I'll drop you off. Loser. Get out
of here. We noticed what? What happened? I think we're going to have to, I think we're
going to close it on that one. I feel like we saw the best possible ridiculous scenario.
One more. All right. We'll do one more. One more. Um, eight. Okay. Overflow redo. I broke the game.
She's like, how tall is that? Jip. I broke it. Jip. Press any key. Deo rating is two. Okay.
Let's see. What do you want to do? How about let's go fishing? Um, I don't know. She's
going to be fly to Vegas for the weekend. No, it's not going to be hockey again. Let's
go scuba diving. I'd love to. Here we go. Good. You and your girlfriend arrive in
Cozumel, Mexico and hop on a boat for some exhilarating scuba diving. After carefully
checking the equipment and reviewing the fundamental rules of diving, you dive off
into the deep and do some exploration and practice some buddy breathing. After a very
active day of diving. She's such an active woman, isn't she? During which you both get
quite wet. You retire to the villa and have a little siesta. Just the two of you.
Jaxette says, isn't this romantic? Uh, Jaxette is also, I think, uh, two to three,
about two to three hundred feet tall. Let's go have some like beer. You two are sitting
together enjoying a moment of great intimacy. She looks long at you with glazed eyes and
suddenly Jaxette blurts, let's get married. You two decide to get married and have your
honeymoon right there. She looks ridiculous in her rented wedding dress. The happy
couple lives happily ever after in the suburbs for a while. Eventually you both
realize the marriage is a mistake. You have more and more bitter fights. Finally,
she divorces you. Oh, well, uh, let's go. Four. Uh, that, that's fine. Why? What are
you talking about? I can't distribute. Uh, I don't know, 30, 25, 26, uh, 20, 20,
23, 25. I don't know. I don't, I don't, there's no such thing as a perfect
person. Okay. I can't, I don't have any points left. Okay. Let's go to,
let's go bowling. That's easy. Are you kidding? No way. Go baseball game. Sure.
Okay. Baseball. You can, there's no fights in baseballs. You arrive at the stadium with
your girlfriend and sit down in your nice, comfortable box seats on the third base side.
Perfect. Goes off and buys t-shirts and caps and spends 50 bucks.
Concentrate on the game. Concentrate on the blood. A few seats away. Concentrate on your
girlfriend. Read the program. Don't concentrate. It's too hot for that. Uh, let's concentrate
on, concentrate on the girlfriend. You and your girlfriend are sitting drowsily in the hot
sun. The game is dragging on. A slow reliever is on the mound. It takes about 10 minutes to make
each pitch. He winds up 10 minutes later. He pitches. It's a well-hit ball. Foul up the
third base line. The ball was coming right at you. And before you can quite realize what's
happening, you've caught it. Ouch. Ouch. Baseball. I like baseball. What's wrong with
baseball? All right. So I caught the ball. Give the ball to your girlfriend. How sweet.
Hurl the ball at her head. I keep the ball. Hurl the ball at the old lady. Three bros away.
Throw the ball at the blonde. Hurl the ball at the third base. Why is this just weirdo,
like fucking psycho simulator? Nothing happened. We went home. I have no idea.
How about come over and go- oh did we drop some frames? Yeah we did.
Come over and go in the swimming pool. I'm sorry I can't go out with you anymore. You've
been dumped. I don't know. Swim at. It's in your name. You have to like swimming.
Six? Where's six? Sure. Face negative 14. What? Come over and go swimming in the pool.
No way. I want to go swimming. No way. Hot tub. This is gonna be another one of these.
I have to restart the game to get somebody to- okay I'll restart it.
Let me just physically go like this. You lose status points when you get dumped. I see.
I think I broke it. I may have broke the game. All right here we go. New game. My first name.
Okay. No not like swim at again. How about just like- I don't know.
Tiffany? How about Tiffany? Okay Tiffany. Tiffany. Okay let's get it. 62.
I don't know. 130. Measurement in inches. I don't know these.
Uh overall ratings are three. Okay you dress- all right. A trustworthy. Very trustworthy.
Tiffany doesn't really know. Doesn't get jealous that often.
Personality. Friendly. Very friendly. Uh happy. How long do you get along with Tiffany's friends?
Get along well. All right let's go. I want to go swimming. You don't want to go swimming.
I want to go in the hot tub. Uh let's just drip monopoly. Local beach.
Forget it. Why? Horseback riding. Sounds like fun. Here we go. Finally.
You go horseback riding with your girlfriend. You follow the trails at the old west riding
stables. You bounce up and down on your horse and your balls start to get sore.
Your girlfriend seems to be used to it though. She knows her horse well.
Very very well in fact. What? After riding for a couple hours,
Tiffany says this is so exhilarating isn't it? Sure whatever you say.
You're right. That's what I think. Grab your- grab your girl. Aren't we on the horse?
Yeah you're right. That's what I think. That's it. Let's go horseback riding again.
Okay grab your horse. Is there any other options? I think that's it. Let's fly to
China for dinner. Why would you fly to China to go to dinner? What kind of like
billionaire are you? What better place to enjoy fine Chinese cuisine than China itself?
You fly to the capital city of China and eat at one of the finest outdoor restaurants
in Tiananmen Square. You decide to order Chinese food. Okay. The food arrives and you both dig in.
Tiffany says I just love Chinese food. I don't get it. Wait. Wait hold on a minute. You
suddenly- wait why? Wait wait wait wait wait a second. Wait a second. This is not good.
You've run around- wait this is hundreds of- troops storm the area. You look all- I gotta
get out of here. What the fuck? What? What? Um um get out of this. Out. Out. Out. Out.
Get us out. Out. Get us out. No no no no no. What the fuck is this? Dude I- I can't.
This is fucked. Oh my god. You've got to be fucking kidding me. I just wanted to- oh
that's so terrible. I don't want to- no I'm out. I'm out. God damn it. What the fuck?
Throw it into sub- throw it into sub mode quick. No mods? Oh shit. Well that was um-
I'm a little shocked at the thing that we just witnessed. It was fucking kind of
ridiculous. It was very ridiculous actually. Uh we're moving on from that one. I ain't gonna
play that one anymore. So let's go. Here's the list again as you see. I think we have one more
or two what? Two more here. So um okay. Wait this is not right. Uh bingo sunshine thanks
to the five community subs. Appreciate it. Thank you for that. Five community subs coming
in. Thank you. That was um girlfriend construction simulator or whatever the hell
that was. Girlfriend construction set. We have I believe one more here to do. Please vote when
you get a chance. We just did- I'm not going back and playing that again. No. I'm not going
back and playing it. I'm not doing it. Not happening. I have to pee too. Two more. Two more
yeah. All right whatever it is I will- it looks like it's gonna be roadrunner. So when
I come back from taking a piss we will open up roadrunner and we'll play it. Be right back.
I ain't gonna let you get that. You know I'm not gonna leave with the clicks on the screen.
Be right back. All right here we go. Roadrunner. Let's get it done here. 1989.
This is probably gonna be a side scrolling video game. If I were to take a random guess
that's what it would be. Best roadrunners. Roll. Play when using the keyboard. Okay so
KP789. What is this? Instructions. Demo. Redefine keys. So this is- it's the number pad.
$50 just came in from Amferik. Thank you so much Amferik for the huge amount of money
and you had community subs earlier too. Thank you. Yeah we can- we can- we can- what's
happening? Wait, wait, wait. What's going on? Oh okay. You can take it off sub only. But
thank you for the 50 bucks Amferik. Just want to say thanks for the streams and all the
content over the years. I'm pretty sure I've always almost died from laughter too much during
some of these streams but totally worth it. You deserve all the support you get so keep doing
you. Thank you. I'm gonna keep doing it. We're gonna keep doing- I'm gonna keep doing it as
long as I possibly can. Let's press escape to play the game. But thank you so much for the
50 bucks. That's a lot of money. Wile E. Coyote and there's me. That's a pretty- that's
you know that's a cute emote version of these characters. What does jump? Let's get the bird
seed. Roadrunner you missed a seed. Roadrunner you missed a seed. You get hit by a car?
I know I missed a seed but what about what do? I got five. That's- I need five right?
Well he- we both got run over so does that really matter?
All right let me get the end of this. Peepo dance. It's hard to see the cars just coming
out of nowhere. There's like not even a foot in front of the screen to see where the cars are
coming from. Can you jump the cars? Maybe it's just spam jump. Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa!
Don't go down down down down! That's so hard to do. Okay oh god again. Down down quick
get up! What's wrong with him? Why is he drunk? I missed 18 bird seeds.
No go this way. Why is he going over there? This is so fucked up.
What the fuck? Why? I'm laughing for a very specific reason and I can't even say anything.
The numpad are the controls. I can't even play this. This game is fucking stupid.
All right. Rude. I mean yeah rude but you have nine different buttons for up, down, left,
and right. Nine. All right here we go. Oh I fucked it up. Sorry. I opened it in a tab last
time. Why did I do this? All right so we have one more to pick from this list. Please pick
it. I wish you luck. Hopefully you pick something good. Let's see what you get. One, two, three.
Please vote if you can. And remember only click on something if it is on the screen like text
on the screen. So 20% of you just don't want to be counted as a vote. That's okay. And
you guys want me to play Qbert? You actually want Qbert? Dude I had this sick tattoo I was
gonna get. You guys would have thought it was fucking awesome. Dude it was gonna be Qbert
with like weed eyes and he was gonna have a joint like on his hand. It's gonna be fucking
so awesome. All right let's play Qbert. New tab. Qbert is a very old one. For all you guys
talk like making fun of the boomer shit you certainly do pick the boomer games.
All right press space to play. I think it's just to jump on the Qbert is. If I remember you just
have to turn the yeah no up. You have to turn them all the other colors right? Yes you need
to change everything to that. So how do I move? Is it space? How do I why can I not jump?
Number pad? Use your mind. Um let me try it again. I'll try it down on number pad.
Oh okay there we go hold on. So it is like the what's weird it's one and one three what are
you doing? Can I all right what's I think it's one three seven nine. Let's try it again.
Yeah it's one it's definitely it's one three seven nine. Let's go on the numpad.
That is Qbert. Oops I was looking at chat. Okay I got really I got really bored for a second.
I don't know what it was man. It was like ultimate hyper boredom for five to tenths of a second.
Here we go. I like to do this technique with Qbert. Go down in the middle here.
No I try to hit seven. Let's give me a controller god damn it. I'm sorry I can't play
this game with two hands. I'm up I'm up playing Qbert with two hands on the number pad.
You know what I mean like put your put your hand on your numpad and like seven nine one
three. It's like I'm like playing the guitar. I can do that just fine. I don't I don't believe
that because you have to you have to go from seven to one it's too it's a long way. If you
need to go up and then down left it's like seven then you have to go all the way down.
Now I can play that. Put one finger on each button. Yeah but that's what I'm saying I
don't want to do. What do you mean one finger up. Do I have a claw like index thumb?
What are you gonna claw the numpad? You're gonna claw the numpad. It's not gonna happen.
You're gonna accidentally press like two buttons at the same time and then you're gonna go what
the fuck? What the fuck? One of you probably just did it. I'm just on camera so you get to
see me do it. I'm thinking about getting like a tattoo of Qbert with like wicked fucking weed
eyes and he's got like a fucking Guinness in his hand. You know what I mean? Where are we
going? Does anybody have any clicking? I'm not gonna do girlfriend construction set again.
Okay we got King's Bounty or we got Bruce Lee. King's Bounty. This is the last one.
Did three already? Did we? Did we? Oh no we did girlfriend construction. Oh fuck! Uh oh.
Ladies and gentlemen we're gonna have to go here with uh yeah Qbert didn't count. That's
true. We're gonna do Bruce Lee. Yeah I didn't play. Qbert didn't count. My hands hurt too
much when I play it. It's too much pain. I'm gonna throw my fingers. All right let's do
Bruce Lee. Weed. Oh yeah thinking about getting like weed. TV set on composite. I don't know
what that just said but okay. This game sounds like it's underwater. Play versus computer
or Terminator. Let's just try this. Is something wrong with the game? Is this thing fighting
me? This one hurts. This one hurts more than Qbert. I think I lost. Can I climb?
This probably looks better on a CRT. Oh absolutely. Just like in the movie. All right I can't look at
it. I can't look at it anymore. Okay so it is time to scroll. Two games that don't count
equals one game that counts. So all right so where are we going? We're here. We're going down
here which gets us to this. Like right here should be good and that should get us in a good
spot. Remember if there's no text on the screen it's not going to do anything.
What the fuck is this? So it looks like Ford Simulator 5.0. I don't know why you'd have
four other versions of this game but it seems like that's where you guys want to go.
We had some Sim Life. There's some good ones on here. There are some good ones on here.
You're right. All right we're gonna do Ford Simulator 5.0. Pretty good graphics for a DOS
game. Here comes a gigantic advertisement. This whole game is going to be an ad. Probe. Tell us.
Spec it. Paint it. See profile. Drive. All right spec it. Crown Victoria just picks the car.
Tell us. Welcome to the Ford Customer Center. To tell us what you think of Ford Simulator,
press the page down key. Thank you for participating in Ford Simulator 5.0.
By completing the following questionnaire you can help us make future programs
more informative, more entertaining, and easier to use. Please print out the results of your
questionnaire and mail them to us. On a scale of one to ten, ten being the highest, please rate
the specific production quality of paint it colors. I'm sorry. Goodbye. You print that out
and then you mail it to them. Chat votes for a marketing ad. LUL. Where's a cool car?
How about a Mustang? Let's get a Mustang. What? I don't want that. That's what I want?
I want a Mustang. Paint it. Okay. Let's see what we can get with different colors.
I think my browser crashed. Nope. Hmm. All right. What about like Bumblebee? All right.
Looks good. Hey, I just painted it. Paint it. Is it painted? Canary-o-o. Drive. Uh, beginner.
Do you want sound? Of course I do. Choose a vehicle. Mustang. You are on the road and ready
to go. The objective is to get to Lake Wakatanka as fast as possible. Accelerate. Up. Okay.
Steer, brake, and then shift is space. Why can't I just? I'm trying to shift. Gas maps food
one mile. I'm so hit by a truck. Shift up. Shift into second gear. Oh god.
Oh god. Fifth gear. I'm 90. They're trying to. I clocked you at 32 miles per hour. Over the
limit. I hate to do it, but I'm going to have to write you a ticket. Uh, sorry officer.
I won't do it again. Have a nice day. You're gonna have to write you a ticket. Uh,
that's too bad. I'm only listening to instructions to get there as fast as possible.
It didn't say follow the rules of the road. It didn't say take your time. It said get
to Wakatanka as fast as possible. I'm sorry. I'm listening to instructions. I gotta go like over
a hundred. Come on. 98, 99, 100, 102, 105, 110, 110, 100 and fucking 20. Oh, damn it. I
clocked you at two miles per hour over the limit. I'm going to get a ticket for going
like 35 and a 30. Like a 30 what? You're going to clock me at like 32 miles per hour
and a 30. You were going 42 and a 40. What? You're gonna get a ticket for that?
Your average speed was 16 miles per hour? No, I don't want to do that again. All right,
I had enough. Let's go back. I don't need to do any more of this. All right, let's go again.
Where are we going? We've got some good ones here. Sim Life, Wheel of Fortune, Doom 2,
Neuromancer, Sim Earth. We seem to be split, but Sim Life I think is going to be the victor here.
Give it another few seconds. Five seconds left. I think we're good. 31% of the vote. That's a lot.
Sim Life. This is by Maxis, one of the old ones. One of the old Maxis games. All right,
I don't think I've ever played this before. 1992. This is not, that's not a real animal.
That is a snake with a grasshopper's body and bird feathers. And there's a toucan butterfly.
This could be good. I'm looking forward to this now. Oh, fuck, this looks like a lot.
Experimental mode. Do whatever you want. Craft your own plants and animals and let them loosen
a world of your own design. Or pick various species from the zoo to inhabit your experiment.
Can you establish a food chain? When will disasters strike? You play a scenario.
All right, let's, I wonder how hard this is. If you're new to Sim Life, why not try out the
tutorial? There's no particular scenario to solve. You've got the basic features of the
game. Okay, let's just, you know, let's just check it out. Sim Ant. Jerma lied about Minecraft
VR. Five community subs. Lots of community subs tonight. Thank you guys. And thank you
to Jerma lied about Minecraft VR for the five drop. Thank you. Welcome to Sim Life tutorial.
To quit the tutorial, select new game from the meta, the meta end menu. Use tutorial menu
to repeat a message at any time to go to the next message instead of waiting for it.
Okay, so just let's go. Is that my animal? Another five community subs just came in from 1914.
Five more subs. Thank you. Five more community subs. Fuck yeah, thank you. Sometimes I was
asked to click a button. I'm usually okay. Yeah, sure. All right. So day, not as a day
night cycle. Yeah. Okay. Can you tell me what to do? The whole days are going by.
More. Gnarly gave five community subs. Even more. Yeah. Now they're just coming in
like, okay, there's another, there's five from Gnarly, 10 from Cyclops Parker. Jesus.
Thank you. All of you guys for these insane amount of subs, chaining them together.
Thanks for the 10 Cyclops. That's fucking thank you. Here we go. There's a mutagen button. Okay.
Help button is right into the yellow and black mutagen button. Yeah. Dashboard, whatever.
It's just like, Hey, you can click help and click help and click help and click.
What else am I supposed to be doing? 10 more just came in from MGS fan and DJ
Conde. Thank you. Both of you. What is going on? I thought this is supposed to be a tutorial.
Five more from Tingy. Thank you, Tingy. Hold on. Let me just new game for a second. Hold on.
So hold on a second. Help. Terrible lizards. Let's see what it looks like.
Look at all these fucking community subs coming in. Oh my God.
10 more from JermaLightAboutMinecraftVR. Thank you for the 10 community subs.
So you can switch them. All right. So look at this. We can make.
Oh my God, guys. Five more. 10 more. Five more from Jill Crungus. Oh man. Look at this
thing. It's like a donkey starfish. Low intelligence herbivore. Donkey starfish
with a snake tail. Nating difference. This thing is called the triceratops.
That's not right. Food, source, plants, nectar. Okay. I feel like this is a very
elaborate simulation. You probably have to be here for a while. What about the other
animals? You guys are still going. Nat five community subs. Multi-trip five community subs.
You guys are still. This is like a legit sub train right now. You guys are fucking
going nuts. Thank you to all of you. That's like 100 community subs that just threw in
here right now. Thank you guys. Make it so. Let me go back out here. Tool. What is this?
I can mutagen. Build world. Click on any of the control names for help messages when you
have set parameters as you prefer. Okay. You can do like. You can make a new world.
Add more lakes. More. You can just change the parameters. It's interesting. Barriers,
mutagens, toxins. No, I don't want to do that though. Nevermind. Oh my fucking God.
I have nightmares about these kinds of animals. 20 community subs from Ampharic.
Ampharic dropping hundreds of dollars tonight. Thank you so much Ampharic. 20 more.
What is this? You can like paint five more from 420 squid. We are just going all out community
subs right now. You can do custom art. Thank you guys for real. Like this is fucking ridiculous.
Anytime you guys do this shit I just can't even believe it. Thank you everybody.
Big Saturday subs coming in. I'll be honest. I feel like this is going to take a while
to like kind of do a lot of stuff. This seems kind of like sim ant where you need to
have like some time and just watch things grow and stuff. It seems like a fun simulation though.
Wait, pterodactyls? I can do sea urchins in water. Make it so. Oh shit. It seems cool but
might take a while to do something interesting. Yeah, this seems pretty cool. I just think I
feel like it would take a while for me to figure out everything that's going on.
But I'm going to move on from this one. It does seem very interesting but I think
I wouldn't want to stay here and put that much time into it. But very, very, very cool.
Let's come back here. Let's do it again. That was sim life.
A hundred percent. That's a lot for wow. Here comes the fight. Will of Fortune, Doom,
and Neuromancer. Do Neuromancer you normies.
Why? What is it? Why? All right. There's no coming back from this. 66%. There's no way.
Will of Fortune it is. This is a DOS version of Will of Fortune. This could be
all over the place. It could be really good or really bad. Let's find out.
What is this? This is a song. Why is this some Will of Fortune?
Hit any key to begin. That's what I'm trying to do. Okay, here we go.
We of Fort. How many players? One. Are you a returning champion? No. I have to earn it.
Please enter your name. Okay. Round one. What do we got? It's an event. Your choice. Spin.
Time remaining. Spin. Spin it. I'll lose it on. All right. Enter a letter. Let's go with E.
Oh, fuck. You have to buy vowels. Oh, no, no. I forgot you had to buy vowels in this game.
And you went bankrupt, Brian. Who cares? Yeah, this sound kind of hurts. T. There's one T.
Something the. They the. They. Time to. It's an event. Time of the. Time of the. Turn of the
century. I win. Turn of the century. I'd like to solve the puzzle, please. I win. Turn of
the century. I got 200 points. Round two of 200 points. Oh, yeah, I forgot. It's not about
winning. It's about getting letters and points. Oops. So I just look like an idiot. I'm
just a dickhead. Okay, this is people. Don. Chris. I don't know. I only got 200 points.
It's not Donald Duck. Ron. Ron. Ron. Ro. Don. Don. Ron. Donald. Ronald. There are no Bs.
Ronard. McDonard. Spin. I'm going to say O. O. No, it's not like Ron. It's O. Oh,
my God. I fucking am so stupid. I just forget the rules of this game. I've run runner.
Something runners. Run. Okay, I got it. It's you. Go bankrupt. No, give it to me. Give
it back to me. These people are stupid. U is a vowel. I'm not going to do that again.
It's not runners. Spin the damn wheel. P. T. T. I'm going to say T. Okay. Thomas. Tom.
No, there's no Os. People. Um, all right. It's all right. All right. All right. I know,
no, no, no, no, no, no. I know what it is. I know it is. I'd like to solve it. Texas runner.
No, not Texas Ronald. Uh, I don't know. Texas. This is not people. This is a baseball team.
Oh, this is people. The Texas Rangers. All right, here we go. I got 1200 points. No,
it should have said team. This is a title. Well, it's definitely the T. It's going to
be a bunch of Ts. That's nice. The time of the Lord. No, it's not the Lord of the Rings, guys.
There's a D at the end. The word of the Lord. I think it's the word of the Lord. I think it is.
The word of the Lord. That's what I'm going with. That was only one D. The time of the
Lord. The land of the Lord. No, the work of the Lord. Why hasn't even T yet? It's free
points. T is actually free points. So let's see if it's the. The something of the. So H,
we'll do H. Let's just game those points. The. H. The. The. W. The word of the Lord. No, the,
the, the will. The, the word. The, the, the Lord of the word. The word of the. We need R.
It's the word of the Lord. It's the, the world. The Lord of the world. R. Already used.
What do you mean already used? Somebody already did R? There are no U's. I know what it is. I know
what it is. It's called a while. I'm not reading answers in chat. Everybody read this book in the
fucking eighth grade. It indicated begin the bonus round. Congratulations, Jeremy. You win.
Move the cursor up or down to select your prize. A luxury bedroom set. American sports car,
17 foot fishing boat, or a dream vacation. I want the boat. Okay. It's a thing. This is
for boat. Five consonants. C. No. R. D. R. D. R. D. S. One more. B. Please want to enter
one vowel. A. E. R. A. A. R. Two R's. A. R. R. R. R. It's a thing. Carriage. Marriage.
Marriage. Marriage. Marriage. Courier. Ferrari. P. Porridge. Portrait. Portrait. There's no way I
would have got that. Ferrari. Sorry, Jeremy. You didn't win the boat. Your one day total
comes to 3,000. Again. Again, again, again, again, again. Let's go. I'm not a returning
champion. I have to earn it. Here we go. I know I'm supposed to take you on a fishing
trip. I'm still working on it. Just give me a ton of money here. It's twice in two games.
There's a person. A. Anthony. No. David. Donald. Cor. Bar. Spin it. Let's try like B. Barry. B.
No B's. C. C. Computer. Rick. Richard. Bacchus. It's probably, it's probably Rich. Richard.
Cron. Carl. Richard. Well, I can game some points here if it is Richard. R. I. C. H. Huh?
It's not, what's, what's, what name has the C right there? Mike? Michael? Oh, god damn it.
It's Michael. Who wrote Jurassic Park? Michael, uh, who's the guy that wrote Jurassic Park?
Michael, um, no. It's too long. Michael, Michael Criken. Well, yeah, it's definitely
Michael. What about, yeah, I think I know it. Free spin. Shut up. Is it every single,
no, it's all vowels now. You have to solve it. L would be the only thing. You're not going to
use your free spin. All right. I'm going to go L because it's Michael. And then the rest of
all, it's just it's all vowels. There it is. All right. What, I get 300 points? Yeah. All
right. Let me solve this. This is, this is Michael Cain. Yep. That's, that proves it.
Uh, is it E.A.? Or A.A.E.? Is it E.A. or A.E.? Mike, yo? I don't know. Is it E.A.?
Oh, no. Michelle is the other way. That hurt my tummy. The category is title. There are dashes
here. What are the dashes for? What is this? Um, T? Something, at was two. All right. Uh,
oh, that's a vowel. What's going on? Spin it. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. There's an E.A. here.
Oh, no. It's Sargent. Sargent. Sargent. E.A.E.? Nancy's destroying me. Nancy can fucking
shut up. She ain't even a good, she's getting really good roles and guessing. She keeps leaning
over and going like, I'm just guessing. I have no idea what's happening. And that A.E.E.A.
thing. I, I don't, I wouldn't fuck that up too. Sorry, Pat. Better like next time.
You know, don't feel bad about that. I have trouble with like, uh, neighbor.
And I said, E.I.I. Sometimes I screw it up. All right. Ah, G.G.G. I'd like to solve
the puzzle, please. It can, it's only A. I got 200 points. Sargent. What? Oh my goodness.
All right. This is a phrase. The, the, the, of, of, the, the, the, of the, something
at of the. Let's see. We'll try, uh, F because of the, could be of. A lot of T's.
A lot of T's. Try F. Holy shit. That's a lot of money. Um, let's do F. Font?
Fort? No ofs. Um, let's go with H. Don't land on, don't land on bankrupt. Don't land on
bankrupt. Thank God. Uh, H. That. The. With. The. These. That. The. That. The. These. The.
O. Fort. Foot. It's definitely an O there. It has to be. No. That's a fucking vowel,
you motherfucker. I keep, I don't know why. I just keep thinking it like will
automatically buy it. I have to press the button. Now that we've got love. Now that not.
It's definitely now. Okay. Now that the, that the is. Let's get the, let's get the S.
Because it definitely is. Now that the sh. Now that the shoe. Uh, put this on puzzle please.
Now that the shoe is on the other foot. I would have had that fucking long ass time ago.
I just keep forgetting you have to buy the vowel. It's like, oh, would you like to buy that vowel?
It just deletes your turn. All right. I want the boat. This is a person. It's a person. But
is that the pope? Um, the. I'm not going to do T or H because I know it's the. But it might,
there might be T somewhere else too. I'm going to do P. S. S. There's a lot of places
for S's here. Uh, R. H. B. No, I always do B. P. D. There's lots of like does. One more. P.
And then want to say then that's five consonants. Lock it in. And I'm going to say either E or I.
E. Always E. So it's the. The. Pop. The. Prince. The poor. The pre. The press. The press.
The push press. The purr. Peer. The prez. The prize. T. The far. Parish. Parish. Free. The
priests. No, there's no T. No. Pray the parish pre. So what was it? I had it right. I was
reading chat and I thought it was wrong. Yeah. I thought I just, I didn't want you to think I
was cheating. I'm closing chat now. I'm not even going to look at it. I'm putting you guys
out here. T. T. A. Attached. Let me see. No C's. A. T. T. A. C. H. E. No. Title of B's.
I'm going to say N. A. T. T. E. Ten. Let's spin it again. What has two T's in the
beginning? Um. M. Let's think of something. Um. R. I'm going to say R. There's always an R.
Always. Oh, come on. Why is it even on there? Out of all the dumb game show things, why is it
bankrupt on the wheel? Just make it zero. P. No. Do an R. If I get bankrupt again,
I'm going to harden, turn off the computer with the power button. I think I know what it
is. But I want points. Yeah, I know what it is. I want a G. Solve, please. I know what it
is. The Attorney General. There's no way you could ever have attorney be up there. What a
district attorney? Attorney? No, that's what you guys are saying about me. You're
polite about Attorney General. That's the first thing I see. All right, you guys can
stay up here now. Okay? How's that sound? Fake typing. You don't know what you're talking
about. Put us back down there. Place. Person, place, thing. This is the last attempt and
we'll do something else. We'll do another one. Nancy going with D. Some D. Door? Door
to the old. Door to the old mall. Door to the old wall. Door to the old. Dawn of the
old. Door, Dawn. Well, let's just, we'll do T because it's definitely up there.
If that's, middle one's that. Door of, Dawn of the old will and testament. Um,
Dawn of the, spin it. Let's H. Don't bankrupt. Don't do it. Spin it again. Dawn
the old will. Mall. F. Wait, I already checked. Who did F? I was so confident that it was F.
Somebody else did F. I didn't even fucking realize it. It's Dawn. Dawn. Oh, no. It's
Dawn out. Dawn to. Dawn is. Dawn on. Down B. Down B. Dawn B. The old. Down. Down. Door.
Dawn B. The. Down. It's Y. It's going to be Y. By the old. What's the, what is the last one?
Down by the old mill? Will? Bill? Down by the old mill? What's the last word? Down by the old
mill. By the old mill. Uh, I don't know. Bankrupt. Bankrupt. Mike is killing it.
So definitely W. Down by G. Where would G go up there? Down by the old mill.
Well, let's get it up there so I get points. Cram. Stram. What's even left up there? P. R. K.
J. E. It. Down by the old mill. Stram. Down by the old. It's the job I have. Streamer. Nice
acting. You guys do understand that. It doesn't matter what happens. I could type this in
first try like I did before and I would have read it from chat somehow. You can't play a
game like this. You always, I always have to be cheating. Always. Every time. I'm going to win
this one. Just cheat anyways since no one will ever believe you. That's true. That's a good
statement. I'm just going to watch the chat. No I'm not. Because I want this to be my win.
It's a thing. Superman. Stew. Um, something stew. Succotash. Stew. Something stew. It's a
food. It's like something stew. Something stop. Something stew. I went fucking bankrupt
again. I get it almost every time. This is a thing. Come on Nancy. Bankrupt. Lose a turn.
Bankrupt. Anything. Something bad. Right there. Door. Stir. Stir. Stir. Eye. But what sir stir?
Something stir. Something stir. It's an eye. Stir. Suh. Something stir. Stir. Screen peeker.
All I'm doing is peeking at the screen. I'm cheating. I can't cheat on this one. Bonus
round. Get the boat and that's it. We're done. Here we go. This is an event. I, you guys, nobody
can say anything. You can't say I'm cheating because I'm gonna do it right now. Here we go.
An event. It's uh T. B. Uh G. H. Uh L. Okay. Done. And uh E. You can't tell me I fucking
cheated now can you? Here we go. E. E. E. Got a lot of E's. Tons of E's. We've got L's. P's.
E. We hope you enjoy your 17 foot fishing boat. Oh man that's so fucking funny.
Where the hell are we? We're down here. So that was it right? That was three. Ford, Wheel of Fortune,
and uh Sim Life. And we have to do Doom as well. Ford sucked. Why are we doing three?
We do three and then we scroll. So we're gonna follow the rules guys. We're gonna follow the
rules. That means we're gonna scroll. Ford sucked. It didn't count. I liked Ford. Should
I just do like a streamer's choice and play this? The rules are dumb. Chat picks three
games that they want to see and then we scroll down. There's four thousand, there's four
thousand three hundred of these. All right I'll do, I'll, I'll do streamer's choice
because I'm curious what this is. Neuromancer. Load game one two one. You're at the cheap
hotel. I have 753 dollars. Uh okay. Packs. Items. I have 758 credits. Guest pass on the
cyberspace two. Packs. Public access system. Free side. Skill chips. Oh no. Send
die. Verification code. I'm in. Uh first time packed user info. Access banking
interlink. Uh first orbital bank of Switzerland. A name. Data Dan. Uh I download
credits. Um download fucking like five thousand of them. Thanks. Thanks for the
money. All right let's go. What else we got here? Cop talk? Ice breaking.
Cryptology. Microsofts. Can I go in sewer? Shins. Let's go this way. Can I go like
can I change my cursor to go in somewhere? Pawn shop. Metro holographics.
Is there am I missing a function here? Disk options. What was that?
Holy shit. I missed some subs here. Jeremy lied about Minecraft VR. Just
gave a ton. Was it 20 community subs? Move along citizen. Streamers choice. Yeah
well everyone told me everyone would want to be to play this.
So I wanted to check it out because I thought it was gonna be cool. It still
is cool. What's wrong with this? It's nothing wrong with this.
What's wrong with this? It's interesting. Uh could decide by which
company are you employed. You're at the maximum security gate.
I got 5700 bucks. Is that enough? I feel like I'm missing something here.
Guest pass. Operate item. Guest pass? Go back over here.
I'm a volunteer for a Hitachi biotech. Sorry I just stumbled in here by
mistake. I work for. I'm a volunteer. What?
I have to put. Do I not know the company? I work for
Microsofts. All right can I talk? Apparently not. Can I go in
some of these buildings? Cyberspace. What's cyberspace 3?
Exit. Erase software. Blowtorch? No no don't erase.
No no no no. Operate item. Battle chess. It's a boomer open world game. It's not.
It every wow you got everybody so quick to be angry at these choices.
First it was play neuromancer and then it's get out of neuromancer and
then it's go in and as you get out it's which one is it.
All right well I can't figure out what to do so we're gonna move on.
Seemed like a cool game. Before everybody was extraordinarily upset that
I clicked it for more than four minutes. All right coming back. So that uh we're
gonna do a scroll. So we were here. So now we're gonna go from here down
to get to here. So we've got. Robocop is not up there. So this is
what we got here. That looks correct. Right there should be
good. Right there. Uh right yeah we had
colonization was on the last one so right there looks good. Which is hard
to line it up correctly. All right here we go.
Let's see what you guys want to do. Give it a click.
Wheel of fortune's not currently on the list. You can't click it. So we got
the incredible machine. Lemmings 3D. Big business and monkey
island 2. Incredible machine is the one that's
being picked. So that's what we're gonna do.
Thank you for voting. It's winning by a lot.
So I don't think anyone's coming back from that one. The incredible machine.
Oh this is what you make think of Rube Goldberg right? Original Sierra game.
Okay it's like mousetrap. We're gonna make let's make mousetrap.
Puzzle one tutorial. Put the ball in the hoop.
Make the basketball go through the hoop. Sure thing.
Okay so um let's play it. Make this is the hoop I'm assuming right? Make
basketball go into the hoop. So we need uh do we just place them?
Wait wait wait wait. What are the what are the controls here? It's a
ramp like this. You make this bigger? Now first of all how do I like start
start machine? Okay let me just see what it does already. All right so that's
what that does already. So like let's clear it.
So this has to land and like knock into this one.
Okay what does this one do? What is this? It's like a
machine? Power? What do I need power for?
Does it have these bands? This is to move the balls right?
So this is to power a generator. And then do I have to attach the
bands here? You know what I'm saying? Like does this is like does this I
I don't know what one's supposed to do. So does this like have to be
attached to here or something for like it to work?
Okay how do I turn this on? How do I power that? Oh damn okay hold on.
Is this for wine? So then now this has to go.
I have two of these. Okay so I get it. Gotta be closer.
No no no what the hell? Why? All right don't ever right click. So now
it's going to be bang. He rolls over there, bang. He rolls over there, bang and
that. Okay there's only difference though.
This is not this could be closer. How does it have to hit the top? I
can hit anywhere. It works. All right and then you go
like this. You go like this. Done. Started.
End of the hoop. Ding ding. New password.
Do you want to advance to the next puzzle and replay your solution?
Advance. I know I'm kind of getting the idea here.
All right put both bowling balls into the metal baskets.
To solve this puzzle you must place and flip the mouse cage
and then hook up the pulley belt to the conveyor belt.
Place and flip the mouse cage and then hook up the pulley and the
conveyor belt. Okay so you get these both have to go in here.
This one's already going. So that's that's it.
So now they'll both just go in right? Oh no somebody. Ah no no no. I have to drop
this here. This is easier than the tutorial.
I did it. You must pop all the balloons.
All right so let's just see what these do.
So the ball hits the you gotta blow it into the scissors.
Okay so we need one of these down here. Flip it and then this one's
got to do the same thing. Flip this one
because this thing can get destroyed by the
wheel. Tied up. Yes. Oh flip it.
You've achieved IQ up 68 to 69. Hey good. Hooray.
My IQ leveled up. That's great. Make the bowling ball fall off the bottom of
the screen. That's the bowling ball. What happens
right now? So we boink and that boinks.
Yeah I think I understand what you want me to do here. And then get this
one down here. So
see if that goes far. How far does the last one go? And then
knock that one and then do it again. Okay so this has to be flipped.
This looks pretty awesome though. This is good shit.
This is really good shit. All right let's see.
Oh we might be off a little bit on the physics here.
Maybe. No I think we're okay. And out.
Yeah sounds like Donkey Kong Country 3. Yeah I'm getting Donkey Kong Country
vibes. You're right. Use the boxing gloves to punch the
baseball up to the metal pipes. Punch the baseball up to the metal pipes.
What happens right now? This rolls. That punches.
So we got let's see. So we got basketball punches that ball.
This ball goes down here. This ball needs to be punched.
So actually hold on. That shouldn't. Can I move things?
I can't pick anything up that's already there. Can I put this here?
Because that drops going. I almost feel like I should put this up.
Should it just go up and over? What does this do?
No not quite. What do I do with this thing? Because it is it has to be
activated to punch. Yeah it has to go up over there
because then this has to punch this one right?
I hate when it does that. Can I flip this? Like
where can this go? No I can let go left and right.
So that was probably that was correct but it just needs to go higher.
I just learned this last puzzle. Literally one ike. I'm just like
yeah I just did it. But like this has to go doesn't have to go up.
Hold on what if I do here? Can I do it up and like over again?
Like what if I do this? Oh stop! Flip and then put it under the
black ball. I didn't think I could fit it here.
I tried I tried to put it here before. I didn't think I could even
fit it. Yeah I would have done that first.
It's just I didn't think it would it didn't look like it didn't fit.
Yeah I didn't think that was gonna fit down here. Just look at it. See the
white? It's like going over the I didn't
think that was gonna fit. All right well now I'm gonna go like
this. Punch the ball. Go for it. Too far.
Just far enough. Make Mort the mouse run in his cage!
Spring. I'm just doing random placement. You gotta use all four.
Where did it bounce to? Let's see right there.
Right there. Further in. Further in. Yes. Is that gonna reach? I don't think it's gonna
reach. Oh fuck it's not. Okay so it's gonna
be a little bit further. Can I move this one a little bit?
Each one is like one to the right.
Hmm not really. Lower? Now does it
I wonder it doesn't matter how far it falls.
No see I don't think steeper is gonna be better. Yeah it's definitely lower.
How far does it go the first time? No so there's actual physics in the game.
That's what I was wondering. So it will fall if the more it falls.
It's a DOS game. I don't think it had like actual real physics in this.
That should do it. All right we'll do one or two more.
Make the jack in the box break the fish bowl. You got it.
Jack in the box. Let's just see what happens right now. Okay.
There he goes. So we just set to make the jack in the box happen.
Goes up. We got two jack in the boxes here.
What does this do? Pretty good hand breaking here. Yeah.
So it just jumps up and that bounces over here which will turn
this. Let's see here. Oh god the right. Okay why even have a right click?
Oh no right here. Do it again. Spin spin spin spin spin spin spin spin
spin. Break the tank. We killed the fish.
All right a couple more. Like one or two more. That's it. Pop the balloon.
Note that you must flip the windmill to select which direction it turns.
Pop the balloon. What happens? Okay we got
a windmill. Are the windmills just wind?
Sure it is Jeremy. There's no power here though so you have to do
I wonder if there's a way. Wait is it can I connect this to this now?
Every genre. There's a lot of tracks in this game strangely enough.
What does this do? Do I need to place this in this particular place because
do I have to like hit it with something? Does it have to spin?
It does. Okay so you need to have the wind spin so you have to put one of
these down here which will spin that. You have to
hit it with something. So this has to go over here and then
push this for that to move over here. I'm generating clean energy.
All right well I can move this one. That doesn't really do anything.
Another windmill to push that all the way? Will this move?
Hold on a second here. Let me just do this. Can I move this one too? No
just that one. Because then this has to be tied to
this windmill right? I'm gonna bring this back over here
which moves it that way. So I need to flip this.
You go all the way over there that drops and then in the meantime
that will hit this windmill. Not windmill this thing.
Spin it that way. Attach the cord. And we should have a finished product.
No no we won't. Wrong way. Now it's a finished product.
Oh it was in the right spot at the beginning.
Nice. This is fun. This is a fun little game.
Your goal is to lower all three buckets. To do this you must cut both
ropes with the scissors. So we're gonna cut all the
ropes with the scissors. Gonna drop the buckets.
What happens? Just drops. Lower the buckets. Cut the rope.
So just out of curiosity. Will that cut if I...
Okay so that cuts two of them. So we need to have
our scissors here. Gonna cut them both so we need
like this. Because that'll just drop right? I think that's it.
You're right. Every genre of music is in the game.
Gun. All right. Bang. Bang. You must shoot all three guns.
Shoot the guns. You have to pull the... Okay that shoots.
So we have... You have to tie the gun to a rope.
Rope to something else. Bucket. I mean let's see. You gotta get this
to here to there and then we have one more of these. There aren't even more
buckets though. All right so what happens first? Oh
that just shoots. That's it. Hold on. Wait a minute.
Can I just like buck this whole thing up and just do it stupidly?
Too far away? I wonder if I can just do this just dumb.
All right you can only have one. You can go here. That should work right?
Something has to weigh this down. Other side. There's this balloon.
What's the balloon for? How do I... I want to get this back.
Is this enough tension to do this? On the other side?
There it is. Yeah! All right. I'll do like...
I'll do like a couple more. And then we're going to move on.
So this is uh turn on all the fans. You must flip the light switch to
provide power to the electrical plug. The initial state of all plugs is off.
So we have to turn on all the fans. Power is power.
Okay so we gotta do this. I mean we've got to bounce the ball because
it's turning it off. And then where does that go? A fan
maybe?
Because that's just gonna flick it on and then the fan will...
Well you probably... Will this blow into here?
What if I... I need power for this though don't I? I don't have to connect
these? What happens if I do this? There we go.
That flicks that up. That flicks that up and then the ball
is... gets blown. It's almost like the ball...
Because then this blows over here but what do I do with that?
The ball powers this which blows the balloon which then knocks into there.
Well how do I get this one to stay on? Can I just blow this
from here? No I can't. Maybe I can. Let's see if it'll just do it. That's
flicking it away. That's... Oh. I thought that was turning it off.
Never mind. Okay. They all started off. Yeah I know but
when you see it in practice it's like wait
shouldn't the foot switch be up? All right this is the last one
and then we're gonna move on. We'll do like one or two more games.
Make the tennis ball fall down into the pipe hole. Generous will take
turning motion and provide electricity. Electric motor must be plugged in to run.
Okay so going going so these I need more cowbell. Actually hold on don't
do this. Can I not move that? Can I have another fan?
Excuse me. Uh all right no wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong.
Not enough. Not enough power to get that to blow this way.
I mean it kind of is but not really. Um windmill connected to here.
The thing is though I knew what what did these do again? I kind of just glazed
over when I was reading that. Windmill to power the generator but
hold on back it up. I want to read that again.
I like I just read it out loud without even comprehending what was
going on. How do I like go back? Is there a way to go back? Because
I just just two new items that I just
didn't even comprehend what they were doing.
I just I can't do it. Right click. Oh right. All right make the tennis ball
fall down. Generators will take turning motion
and provide electricity. The motor okay so this is a running
man. So this is a generator. So what the
hell is this? The electric motor? Which one of these is what is this is
a motor now? Full Jupiter. That's pretty good.
All right so this is this one is powered already.
So I don't need this because it's plugged in. How do so will this spin?
That spins this. Does this need to be do I actually need to
connect this? This movement the windmill turns from here
which in turn will that turn? No. All right get this off
because then that probably okay now this will power that which then will
power the
this. What is this thing for? This powers the switch.
Does this need to be plugged in? What does this thing do?
What's the other fan for? The ball the ball needs to be
because now this is powered. So that's a generator and then this is
now has power for me to attach to this which will then knock
oh it's gotta be the other way then hits that which then bounces
okay so then this this goes over here and how do I power that? The rat runs
but just can i power i can't power the fan with the rat can i
no i can't put that up there and this needs to be near a switch
oh this comes with a plug i didn't think this came with a plug
i thought you just had to pump it in okay well that makes it
that's all right okay over here that was fun
did it hooray all right that's it that's it for bad rats the prequel
i just uh for some i didn't think there was gonna be an outlet attached
all right we are gonna do uh one more
compare this to bad rats i mean it's just i was kidding
let's go over here all right let's do we have
what was that the first one so we probably two more then because that was
the first one in that list so we'll do two more
that should take us to about six hours
which is where i was probably gonna end in any way so
all right here we go that was the incredible machine that was fun
little interesting little game so we've got
these here right i feel like these are moving
all right here we go one of the final two of the night which one is
it gonna be big business is where the scroll is on
chat just always clicks girl 37 percent how many votes are in
all right looks like we're going to big business thank you for voting
let's try it digitech software presents
making fucking cash uh all i need is 50 bucks
i'll turn that 50 dollars into 50 000 i'm just gonna invest in gold
and then wait 500 years this game work oh big business off the wall
productions desk so i'm the chairman if you have a
halo above your head you're obviously a bad guy
somebody did somebody just what's going on why people falling
why why are people falling why are people doing that
uh okay desk about b biz all right do you have freaking me out
start game the fortune three player one has twenty four thousand dollars we all
start with 24 000 wake up it's your turn is a board
game do i have to what is it three minutes on the
clock too much caffeine can make you nervous
oh no borrow repay profit losses you left the vault open and someone
took thirty five thousand dollars what
what who did i have no money raw material purchase gravel
sand lime uh i have uh i've lost so much money sand
buy sand sell gravel sounds good how do i get out of here escape
okay so what do you do production cement
factory production schedule rates 67 percent
they make a million units okay what about
einstein does einstein do anything research and development
rats what do i do with what do i do in our r&d
gravel raw material needed in production i need sand lime and gravel
all right easy enough improve r&d let's do a mill was that
a billion dollars how much was that that's 10 million dollars how do i
get worst and i can't i'm getting like
stuck in menus why is it a sound all right this guy's
gonna give me some good info here so is this sales advertising but
advertising what what are we advertising i have seven
seconds until what the room explodes i don't
understand what's going on it's after four go home will you
okay i'm going player two's turn so we're competing
borrow borrowing money i lost 35 grand player three production i'm losing yeah
i'm losing because somebody robbed my vault in the first 10 seconds of the
game oh my god buy buy buy buy
r&d a million trading for gravel is this us why are we getting mr
fantastic arms buyer sale player three units transferred
what's happening do i have to put do i have to buy
where's my hand is that me in the top left i have no idea what this is doing
uh i don't get a hand trading for sand here we go
how do i make my hand go up this is the oddest way to teach anybody about
like stocks and bonds and trading i can't
even raise my hand trading for lime all right am i going to
get to raise my hand this time or are we gonna have to sit here like an
idiot that's a tap i'm just i'm just confused
it's in the mashing buttons like an idiot at least we got to see the uh
the vault get robbed which was funny i guess it was funny
all right we'll do one more and i'll do well maybe i'll do one more like
streamers choice that sounds like a good idea all right
restart i already see streamers choice by the way it's
not even on this list lemmings 3d lemmings is a uh it's a great game
it's kind of all over the place though we'll do it we'll try for a
little while yeah 50 there's tons of clicks 50 percent of the vote going to
lemmings thank you for voting i don't think
anybody is going to be able to pull that back
47 here we go so lemmings is you have to
they just walk in a line and you can't stop them right
you just have to have each one of the lemming classes do something to
get the all the lemmings to the other side
what's this 3d right jelly belly the original jelly bean they were the
original sponsor of this game all right so uh play if i remember
correctly how this works they just walk forward and you have to
have them do things right select item to practice uh boomer
builder turner yeah they like move them you have to move them in different
directions basher what's basher do number of
lemmings 20 this is not running well tend to be
saved it's time for practice maybe that's just the way that looks
when you're in the menu okay so oh man it's been a while
don't you have to like don't they come out of the wall or
something reach here oh bash here
holy shit it's gonna take a look at the seconds counting in the top right
456 one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten ten seconds for one second we are doing
with quick silvering right now uh i'm not sure this is going to be
playable i can barely even move the map around
damn it that's too bad i can't like go anywhere
i need to get that one frame to like actually
turn the camera oh boy yeah i gotta i gotta can this
unfortunately yeah it would have been fun
lemmings especially lemmings 3d because i'm not sure any actions will even work
unless i catch it right in the frame then the one frame that i can do
anything do you mean like no all right that's
it let's see what the comments say there
are no reviews oh well all right um that's too bad
that's okay though i'm gonna go for uh streamer's choice here
and you everyone's gonna be like wait wait wait don't just trust me on this
one trust me on this one all you need to see
is the title screen that's it
activision presents tongue of the fat man
okay wait is this like a is that a porn game
did i actually do that no i didn't greetings
no mundo welcomes you to the fight palace
welcome to the fight palace who do i want to be
underdeveloped person or blue guy or other guy
i don't know like should i be like the weird box i didn't make any model
character okay i'll be i'll be cube guy
cyber droid origin zactin industrial zone
a mixture of delicate high technology and durable synthetic materials
although originally designed as robotic labor slaves
an occasional battle model is imported by group gamblers
bio character flaws software for viruses destroy the intelligence wrong
require maintenance service and recharge every 800 solar rotations
sure enter your name cyber cube cybergex
why would it be cybergex no
cyber i like it cyber what the fuck was that
we was like was that gonna diaper welcome to the game slime ball if you
don't get your cockers carried out of here
you may have a few bucks and that's all you can read
your holdings a thousand purse 500 opponent rex bid my weapons
jesus greetings friend i'm dr kadavra let me show you my specialty
you see i have almost anything you might need to give yourself that
little something extra let's see what we have available today
hands super eyes chocolate slime rubik's cube
or dna jack wheel of pain explodes on impact takes the fire
out of a tough fighter yeah let's get it it's very loud
wait there's more okay let's go wagers
okay so we have opponent bid win time and fight a 30 second win time
win time fighter can i change this all right do you what do you think two
minutes two to one five to one think i can beat him in 30
seconds i think i could do it in 30 seconds
i'm gonna bet how much money do i have 500 bucks
let's go how do you play what was that why does somebody like throw up on
the screen what is punch q w e
why are they just am i dead it's like puked blood
i'm just being laughed at poor aside mark you were bound to get
beaten you should have listened to my warnings take this body to the doctor
uh opponent bid rex okay i but how do i how do i play
fight number pad click they're just showing random aliens
i'm pressing every button i like dough hold on
k l o p a shift space control alt
seven num lock on no num lock's not on escape is it controls down here
thanks for the thanks for the salty bucks i figured it would be like
num pad or like slash dash i tried clicking the mouse
google the manual do you think that would be anywhere
let me try this one more time i mean hold on
i'm doing like something weird i'm like blocking
am i doing that too am i throwing him this is so confusing
he's just stomping on me maybe i should have been the cube guy
all right i i can't do anything i'm on the ground is dead
all right streamers choice again that was streamers choice again
we'll do another one i picked that one because the thumbnail was insane
it was called tongue of the fat man you just don't think i'm gonna click
that one okay here is my other streamers
choice this one's not gonna be very long
everyone's gonna be so mad that this is the end of the stream here
you're gonna be furious oh how do i change that back i don't want to be
game boy no i don't have a joystick how do
i say no champs no no no no no what are you doing
okay yeah i just want to play some baseball
okay do you have a joystick no how do i say no
all right what how do i run it the illegal command
all right well that was god damn it all right last try
now then i'm gonna call it i saw this one earlier and i wanted to try it
this one was uh this one looked fun people were picking this one too
earlier didn't get to go through though
here's the actual streamer's choice not the two ones that i couldn't get to
work king's bounty okay this looks like there's some
stuff going on select character a d or l to load save games like character
uh do i want to be shield sword um guy with the guy with no clothes
or magic lady so no no no that's see see i wanted to be d
oh come on no i wanted to be the guy with the
apparently i was in the wrong spot so we're gonna be the sorceress difficulty
uh sorceress name this is zelda blaze um star starlight um
what what light zoom no that's the zoomer
what happened now sticky keys got angry
no i'm not doing that starlina starina normal starina the sorceress a new game
is being created please wait while i perform
this is just might and magic isn't it town of hunterville
somebody very clearly casting spells at us gp 10k get new contract rent a
boat gather information bridge spell buy
siege weapons how much is the boat i got a boat
cancel boat rental new contract um murray the miser alias nun reward
5 000 gold was last seen in continentia in castle
unknown distinguishable features treadbare clothes bald patch with hair
comb to cover it up incessant cough murray's wanted for
various petty crimes as well as for treason
he allowed a group of pirates to enter the castle and free criminals
okay uh let's go so we've got to get that guy i got my boat there cool rent
a boat and sail the seas explore the easy way
and i did just rent one continentia well we're gonna find continentia
oh that's a big person your scouts have sighted a few skeletons a few
zombies a few orcs how many men do i have this is
might and magic holy shit it actually is heroes of might
skeletons move i have 30 peasants want orc shoot peasants yeah you lose
view that's how many peasants i have by the way
is there a way i can attack sprite no that's pass
peasants retaliate all right how do i peasants m
mouse one options okay yeah because you have to get close enough to
attack they're just going after the peasants
okay why does the bow have explosions that's a really good question
better than final fantasy 13 area well everyone's dead
i think i'm about to lose uh so the way might and magic works
is you got to get an army first 250 peasants are available 10 each you may
recruit up to 40 recruit 40 so we got to build an army
up first oh treasure sign reads treasure island
no shit after scouring the area you fall upon a hidden treasure cache you
may take the 400 gold distribute the gold to the peasants
increasing your leadership by eight let's get some good morale
here's a might magic three is one of the best games like ever
i that you know what what do you guys think for heroes of might and magic
three stream i love those games i feel
like there's a lot of material for us to have like a lot of fun there
oh yeah absolutely here's a might magic is
is a great great great game this is we're just playing
a very very very early suit this is about the same people possibly
the ring of heroism at a piece of the map to stolen scepter this just makes
me want to play here's my magic yeah we'll do that very soon i we could
have a lot of fun on that stream there's a lot of material like we
were saying i'm not ready for that i need some more um minerals and
shit i'm now i want to play that i want to get a new contract cancelled
boat rental no didn't they they've remade might
and magic too didn't they and it was kind of a flop
didn't they come back with like a remaster or something
do it right now i'm i can't do it right now i'm about to stop streaming
let's okay i gotta actually have to pull up a calendar for next week i
gotta figure out what's going on here because of my colonoscopy let's see
what's going on the remaster was bad yeah i remember
they kind of redid it let me just hold on i gotta look at a
calendar this saturday so we did we went thursday friday
saturday i have i need to take three days
off from my colonoscopy let you know it was his will do
so this exactly one week from today is
my appointment the day before i can't do anything
and maybe potentially it depends on how i feel about the day after it should be
okay but at least friday and saturday i won't
be live so what we'll probably end up doing
here is i'll come back on
we'll do tuesday wednesday thursday and then
probably sunday that sounds about right but i just need to look at it
on a calendar tuesday because then they'll give me
the day there so tuesday i can tell you exactly what
we're doing tuesday we're gonna finish sam and max
we'll at least try to get you know a couple episodes in because i was
supposed to do it yesterday and the day before but it
all the internet bullshit stopped it from happening that was really the
start up when it got real bad and then wednesday and thursday
maybe i'll maybe i'll play my magic now i'm really into that
those of you that don't know what it is it's really interesting
yeah so then yeah we'll do tuesday wednesday thursday sunday
that's probably what's gonna happen all right let me zoom back in here because i
was gonna go tomorrow too but i feel like that taking the days off
would because then i would be that would be four days in a row
and that's what i but then the fucking shit next weekend and then
all the internet bullshit i think that plays out better doing it here
instead in the middle this guy's just
fucking following me around today he said well it's getting late
uh i don't want to attack no no no don't take either
well i have to because they but i look at the i can't go anywhere
a few orcs now oh this makes me i can't wait till we fucking play that
you guys are gonna love that game i guarantee it you think heroes 2 is on
the archive i don't probably not i wish i had audio that'd be great
just hit the road in the archive with sam and max hit the road i don't
think so yeah i want to do this i want to do
the real deal with this one all right guys i think that's good
i think that's it for tonight aren't you glad you gave them 400 gold
now you got me excited end of the stream voice
yeah that's it for tonight yeah i'm looking forward to heroes of my magic
it's gonna be fucking awesome we're gonna get we're gonna get
through so much cool shit in that game
but that was dos saturday hope you enjoyed it i did let me see
cool this should do the bits and the subs and everything should take us to
six hours which is exactly what i wanted
was it good for you it was good it was great for me i hope it was great for
you too i will see you guys again on what we're
doing here right tuesday right tuesday wednesday thursday
that sounds about right that sounds right to me
next time on dragon ball z somebody in chat just said that
let me get this up here sounds good what how long has this been on for
no not for did i just turn it back on hopefully i don't flake out on sam
and max no i i won't i i wouldn't have the only reason why it happened is
because the internet was so bad i just couldn't even stream it
and i'm not i don't want to power through a game like that that
requires you know tons of dialogue tons of choices tons of things to pay
attention to and it you know the internet just drops to
fucking zero and i'm gonna be honest with you here
the internet problem is gonna be a potential long-term issue
for a while because it's just at the point right now with us changing to a
few things and then doing something we're at
uh 9,300 drop frames in about six hours
which is that's not unbearable but it's not good
we're just barely at that level where it's not
unwatchable and hopefully i mean what we're hoping is
that we get through this couple weeks of just terrible internet for some
reason or they actually do catch one of the
noise problems or packet problems whatever it is and they get it fixed
so you know we probably gonna have to just deal with
one percent two percent potentially drop frames probably for a little while
lol
oh that's all those call of duty players no that's all good
but i'll see you later have a great rest of your weekend guys
the last few days have been very very fun i've had a fucking blast
on these three days here i'll see you for another three days in a row on
tuesday wednesday thursday get some rest get some food here's
hoping that over the next couple of days
can because i'm gonna be running tests i'm just gonna be streaming to the
test servers all tomorrow and i'm gonna try to
catch a bad moment so i can just immediately fucking call this person
i'm gonna go for it we'll see if i can get it so let's do the bits
go back about six hours ago we had five dollars from dr stein thank you dr
stein it's been at least a few years since
i've seen these movies i read the book like years ago i kind of don't
remember who you eat oh talking about the hobbit
thank you dr stein for the five dollars we had a ton of community subs
today guys thank you that was a lot it was like a hundred
something at least like 150 or something that's a lot of fucking subs
thank you thank you thank you thank you you guys are
fucking too kind seriously thank you we also had 250 from c4g
thank you c4g you will be kissed on the nearest possible friday by the love
of your life tomorrow will be the best day of your
life now you've started reading this don't stop this is so
freaky but if you read this and ignore it you will have
very bad luck send this to 15 people in 144 minutes when you're done press
spacebar and your crush's name will appear in big letters on the screen and
it's so freaky it works i mean does it does it work if i
send it to 2000 people because i mean i just did yeah it has to
work now like 2000 people got that thank you c4g for the 250 hey groove
wizard thanks for the 250 groove wizard
german just want to give you some thanks to the no give some thanks to
you now that i have some bits money this year has been the
worst year of my life as i've recently been doing very bad
in school ended in a long term and ended a long-term relationship
i only recently started watching you and i bwd well almost every stream
as the year has gone on watching these dreams i'm slowly getting my
life back together i passed all my classes this semester
and have a somewhat stable job working for my dad so thanks for
keeping me sane i'm really glad to hear that things
are turned around much love to you welcome
to the stream and you said you only recently started watching
we're glad to have you welcome to the community i don't know how long you've
been around but uh thank you we have a lot of
there's a lot of good people here a lot of fun interesting funny people
you'll fit right in everything's great here and much love to you i
i anytime somebody says something like this i always just think about
you getting your life back together and that's so
good that's really good that's very good
if i had even a tenth of a percent of something to do with that
i'm floored i'm fucking grateful i'm i'm thankful that that can happen
so thank you that was groove wizard thank you uh
tibet for the five dollars you should hire some
russians to rig the debates okay yeah i stepped on like the gas
i'll be honest with you the first i sometimes i do this
the first like two to three hours of the stream i was like a hundred bars per
hour and then i just like all the air got
let out of the balloon like an hour ago
sometimes it happens but yeah that was a lot of fun though
thank you for the five dollars appreciate it uh germa lied about taco
bell thanks for the 250 jnn exclusive report psychotic
politician jeremy 995 elbertson has made shocking gains in the polls
recently in the state of rod island the german news network dispatched a
reporter to interview a hardcore elbertson supporter
big dave um mority mority had to say this
elbertson i freaking love that guy one time i saw him in a taco bell he
screamed at the manager and shit on the floor
i smoked meth with him a couple times he's actually that crack house
over there thanks to the 250 and i love how you
put taco bell in here and it's in your name too
that's a good one thank you thank you vela me for the 10 dollars
thanks for the 10 bucks vela me germa you have to take things slow with a
giantus that game was insane that was like
there's too much for me to handle that one thank you for the 10 dollars
smelly boy thanks for the 250 just like how active combat can lead
to uh just like how active come can lead
to a feeling of uninspired by daily civilian life you experience with a
girlfriend construction said will make all of the forms of media
insufficient i was talking about building the
girlfriend he's saying it wasn't fun i mean i thought it was fun for like
10 minutes i thought it was fun for like 24
minutes however long it was that game's fucked thank you though
for the 250 then we had we had a ton of community
subs a lot hundreds there was a hundred and
something at least let's put them on the screen
because i just it's going to fly by your
generosity never ceases to amaze me guys thank you
look at this just flying up the screen
that's fucking insane uh yeah the end of that was just so
out of fucking i couldn't even i couldn't handle it i was like i'm
not doing this shit uh but to all the community subs all
people that are subbed not from community subs just on
their own right thanks all of you i look forward to
each day that we get to hang out and get to laugh at shit and have a good
time i look forward to it every time and
then we had germa lied about taco bell again for 250 let's see we've got
mike debra and you you you you the adam sandler
noise i wonder which one is germa
oh i can't believe i guys i got so embarrassed
like the ea thing everyone's like you're so dumb and shitty like
fuck man i just like wasn't thinking quickly um
uh that's sad like why not i don't the thing is i don't have a rebuttal
there you know you hey shut up you guys
leave me alone i don't have a i didn't have a rebuttal for that
there is no like what what am i gonna say you're wrong
no i was just so that was just defeated
you can't fight back with that one you have to just be like you got to take
the loss when i took it hard it's all right
though we all make mistakes some of us just admit them completely
like i am right now made a mistake it's okay imagine spelling
a word wrong yeah i know all right hope you guys had fun
we did it was very fun kim uh only a few more bits to do we
had germa lied about minecraft vr i want to touch bond like the
how many how many subs did germa lied about minecraft vr give tonight
like 50 40 something like that there's a lot so thank you we came in
like an hour ago and did a huge one so if you're still here thanks a lot
man flug boy we had 250 from plug boy so
i'll have you know germa that last night i had a fever
it was pretty much passed out when you were rambling about some game of
throne shit and i fully like fever dreamed
brawn walking into my room with you behind him
and him slapping the piss out of me i woke up crying because i thought it was
real i still have a fever
oh that's some that is some next that's some low-key
next level insult think about that thank you for those of you that are
game of thrones vince think about that for a second
even if it wasn't even if that was the action if you actually had that
dream yeah that's fucking hilarious thank
you flug boy for the 250 and the uh insane dream i wouldn't
want anyone to hurt you so what i do is i drink and i know
things that's what i do it's supposed to be
tillian hey bingo sunshine thanks for the five
dollars hope everything goes well man dot dot
dot hashtag play oblivion again in 2k19 no rush
go bruins go bruins fuck yeah and finally we had invader z for 255
thanks for the 250 i want to thank you because you always cheer me up when i'm
down even if i'm only able to watch pre-recorded stuff
thank you jerma really thank you every time i turn the stream off
i hope that everyone just had a good time and i hope that people thought
things were funny things are fun it's all i care about don't care
about really anything else and however i can make that happen is
how i try to so thank you for watching thanks for being here
thanks for choosing to spend your time on this
channel with me you guys are fucking incredible
thank you again from the bottom of my heart
i will see you all very soon see you on tuesday
sam and max we're gonna i'm gonna just restart the episode because we got
like 20 30 minutes in and it was all
fucked up and i got like i was irritated so
uh we just just started over we'll try to get two in
and then i want to get might and magic three ready for the next day
next couple days after that have a fantastic rest of your night
i'll see you real soon take care everybody