Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jermok here with Facecam Fortress 2.
The first episode in quite a long time, as most of you will probably recall.
The kit. Pyros.
Playing on pipeline, as you can probably tell, Sniper, you're gonna die in 3, 2,
Oh, even before the countdown ended?
He did not see a 150 on me. Did you? Oh!
Did you see that 150? Spy, get out of my face!
And just like that, you can get like 4 kills in a row.
What are we voting on? Kick somebody?
I don't know. Should we kick this guy?
I need health. I forget what the health is in pipeline. I'm such an idiot.
Oh, watch this. Watch this.
Oh, that's all he needed to do! What's wrong with me?
If he had gotten one tiny little pellet on me, he would have killed me.
And he did.
God damn it, Jerma. Sometimes I just want to fart in your face.
Get up! Do something!
Jump on his jump over there!
Come on, come on, come on, we lost.
Oh, I didn't even say like, I'm using the direct hit, and I have,
Hold on.
Flying Pyro! Flying Pyro!
I probably should mention the hat I'm wearing too.
It's this weird, like, stupid Pilgrim hat that was in my closet.
I think I wore this in a very old Facecam Fortress from like at least a year ago.
So if you see this hat again, and you recognize it, then hell yeah, do it.
I'm wearing an old hat. Where are you going?
Where are you going?
Where are you going with your goddamn sweater vest?
We did it. We got it. Get the health.
Pick the health up. You just called.
This guy's calling for a doctor, and he's looking at the health pack.
We're getting smoked again. All right, I'm going to put my tri-hot pants on.
No more messing around. No more messing around.
Come on, get me out there. Get me out there.
I'm going to kill everybody that's out there. Come on.
I'm going to land every single direct hit shot when I get out there.
Everybody watch this. Here we go.
Oh, we'll just get spawn camped.
Oh, do you see? I picked up the guy's brass beast.
Using my detective work, I think he died up there.
All right, let's actually win this goddamn round.
Well, can that be a thing? Can we win a match, please?
Should I change off direct hit? I don't know.
No, I'm not going to change off it.
These two guys are running around with their BS.
Oh my God, this is too hard.
Oh, death from above.
Got to hit that medic.
There you go, Sergeant. Nice try.
Don't let him get you with that.
I'm going to go down and defend the actual burp cop.
That guy got wrecked.
That guy.
Look, look, look.
Oh, come on.
Come on and get this.
Will you land a shot?
So in the land of...
This is my password book.
Oh my God.
I almost showed my passwords on screen.
I was going to do a thing where I...
I got to go on a complete rampage right here.
I have to make this happen.
Put on your pants.
Even though I'm not wearing any pants right now,
I'm wearing just like underwear.
This is what I do.
Whenever I want to do like a face game video,
I'm like, God, but I got to put pants on.
No, you don't.
Because like all you can see is like right here.
The magic of video editing.
I'll get out of here.
Get you little pricks.
Don't worry.
Oh, I wonder what's going to happen in this round.
We're going to get steamrolled.
Is that really a surprise to anybody on this team?
This is just ridiculous.
Keep them off.
Come here, dude.
Come here.
There you go.
There you go, beef.
Get this...
Get me off me, beef.
Come on, beef.
Somebody kill this guy.
Somebody kill this son of a bitch.
Thank you so much.
Oh, I need health.
Abandon the team.
I don't think we're going to win this,
but at least we're probably going to have the match go longer than 30 seconds.
All right, let's do this after this Uber wears off.
Don't let the heavy die.
He's going to die.
The heavy is going to die.
Oh, goodness.
Come on, overdose.
Overdose, you got to pull through here.
Just do something.
There it is.
There it is, baby.
Come on, do it again.
Oh, my goodness gracious, beef.
Beef.
Look at this guy going absolutely beast.
That's how you do it right there.
I got you.
Watch out.
We got to watch out.
Get him out of the spawn.
That went right by my face.
Let's go.
Somebody got to get that sniper that's up there.
You prick.
You know what?
I should probably go get him.
Turn around.
You want to play that game?
That's fine.
All right.
Wait.
Holy hell.
Help me.
Somebody help me.
Oh, boy.
I'm going to have to use this.
Keep it going.
Shoot some down that hall.
It's all right.
Nice job.
It's okay.
We got to move this guy.
I'm dead.
What is this guy doing up here?
Oh, my God.
Free overcharge.
Come on.
I don't want to crit him.
Get him, Iron Man.
Watch out, Heidi.
They got two medics.
Two asshole medics.
That crit.
Not fair.
Push it.
Remember, guys, what you're seeing right now is what happens when somebody goes medic.
When one goddamn person on your team goes medic, you can win the game.
That's a good PSA right there, because we were just getting destroyed the entire time.
And then we had one medic on our team, and we won the game.
So that's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching Face Game Fortress 2, and I'll see you all next time.
And of course, how messy is my hair?
Take care, everybody.