Hello everybody. I've been away for a little while. Just returned. I had a nice entertaining
four days. I got to hang out with a close friend. It was very, very, very cool. It's the first time
I've seen anybody from back in Massachusetts in almost six months. So that was great.
And I have, since the last four days, have developed a cough. Kim got sick.
She got a cough, a cold, and passed it along to me. So I'm gonna have to be muting. It's
not bad. I'm fine. But I'm gonna have to mute every so often to cough into a tissue.
So quarantine him already, yeah. But hopefully you guys have been doing well.
You are going to see another one of these four to plus day breaks again sooner than you think.
And I'm sorry that these are kind of all compound on top of each other. But apparently
like springs the time to come visit me. My mother is coming up to visit as well. But
that's not until, that's not like another month. But still I'll be taking another probably
four or five days off when mom comes up. So I just want to make you aware of that now.
Speaking of other things to plan and get ready for. What's tomorrow? Something going on tomorrow,
right? A video game that I have been looking forward to for years by a company whose video
games I've played for years. And I'm talking all the way back to the original King's Field.
I beat that game. I don't even talk about that. But Sekiro comes out tomorrow. And yes,
I know that there's like 200 million people watching it right now on streams. But I don't
have access to the game. I don't have like an early deal or something. So I'm just going to
get it. I'm going to play it when it comes up. It's already preloaded sitting in my steam
inventory. Inventory inventory inventory. It's going to be an amazing horrible time for you.
Sorry in advance. I'm looking forward to it. I love and this is the best part about a
brand new From Software game. Everybody in the chat is, you can't talk shit to me.
You can't because you don't know either. You know, there's no Wikipedia page with like
5,000 articles about, oh, this is the best thing to do. This is where you go here. Nope.
Nobody has any idea. You're going to be just as lost as I am. I love it. I don't have to
know in order to talk shit. That's true. That's true. You are correct. He's dying.
No, I told you I got a cough. It's just annoying. It doesn't hurt or anything.
But so I'm going to give you a plan. Let's go over the plan of action here.
So today is we're going to play this game called We The Revolution. It's a game that was
inspired by Papers, Please. It's a game where you have to admit you're a judge
and you're presented with cases and you either send people to the guillotine,
you acquit them, or you put them in jail. And you got to be careful because there's a lot of
crazy shit that can happen. Fighting in nations and political powers rising. It looked
interesting just to play because I didn't want to start something elaborate because tomorrow
I'm going to be streaming all day. Tomorrow, Saturday, Sunday, I'm going to, I'm going to
play that game a shitload. So I figured let's just do something for a little while so I can
prepare my body for the inevitable like 30 plus hours of streaming I'm going to do over
the next like two and a half days, right? After Sekiro, when Sekiro is done, or maybe
even to take a break from Sekiro, Monster Rancher 4 is the next thing. Because I
want to go back to play it. I want to play Monster Rancher 2. Monster Rancher 4 was when
we didn't try. And that's what's going to happen later on this coming week. There's also other
collaborative things, collabs with other people, that are still kind of floating around. Maybe
we'll get a new Beanbag Sonic. Possibly, yeah. But for now, for today, we're just going to
chill. I just got back, I have to be completely honest. I didn't really look at anything. I
haven't been planning any streams or anything for the last four days. I've just been hanging
out with friends. So I kind of just have what am I going to do today, right? This is what we're
going to do. Let's go ahead and open it up. Again, this is called We The Revolution. And
there it is on your screen. Do a collab with Quaker Oatman. What is it? What do you do?
The guy on the on like the cereal box? You're talking about George Washington, right?
I thought that was George Washington for like the first 30 years of my life.
It is George Washington, isn't it? Is it? Who is on the front of the Quaker Oats?
Wait, no, no, no, for real. Who? Who's on the Quaker Oats box? The Quaker man is not an actual
person. His image is that of a man dressed in the Quaker garb chosen because the Quaker faith.
Wait, that's not supposed to be George Washington. Well, I knew it wasn't George
Washington. I just want to make sure you knew. I got to turn this down. This is loud.
No, I knew it wasn't George Washington. I'm just fucking around. All right, new profile.
This game just came out today. So we're going to give it a check. You know that steam review.
Let's see. Let's just make sure this is correct. Full screen. Yeah, that's yeah,
let's get a tutorial just because we don't know what the hell we're doing.
Game options, audio. I always hate having music. That's something I got to tell.
I got to give some developers a little bit of audio lessons here. You know,
I'm the master of audio. Don't have music be the same volume percentage as sound and voice.
This should always be like 30% lower. How many trailers you ever watched where the music was the
same volume as people talking? Music is supposed to be in the background, not in the foreground.
Some people even do it like this. That's wrong. If you have people talking and sound effects,
you want the music to be at a decibel much lower because you can hear them talking.
No wonder he didn't like doom. I liked doom. What did I give doom?
That's better. Okay, see maybe even a little lower, like 47.
Why did it go to zero? What? Oh, it didn't. Okay, the song ended.
Okay, we the revolution. This is like Ace Attorney. Just imagine playing Ace Attorney
for all of the Ace Attorney fans. I wonder if I'm gonna have to do any voice acting.
Let's see if I can do some voice acting. Oh no, they're gonna be way better than me.
Never mind, I'll just be quiet.
This takes place in the French Revolution, if you didn't know.
Play as Jean Paul Gosseau. He used to own a Marine tank.
He was nothing. I am better than he was. People will follow in my footsteps.
I know this factor. Father.
Who is he? That like people will follow him in my footsteps, like I've heard it before.
Music's too quiet. I can't hear. The game is louder than me. France, turn off the 18th
century. Turn to the 18th century. Prologue. I hope this is a fucking musical.
Everything from France is a musical. Has to be. Every piece of media, every TV show, every film.
Is he but a puke too? Is that me? All right, so now I get to talk. Remind me next time I
want to stop drinking this cloudy rotgut. Remind me before I drink it. We're disgracing
Thomas. Is someone coming? This was bound to happen. I told you. Papa, you said we would go.
You promised. Papa had a lot of work. Yes, a lot of heavy glasses. You promised me.
I can't anymore. I'm fed up with asking. Mama is angry because- Quiet. Today it's hard to
do four people at the same time, okay? All different ages. Today your favorite son wanted
to prove he was more honorable than his father, so he started a fight. A five-year-old boy,
for God's sake. Our neighbors wanted you to explain that to them, but well,
you were fighting for justice. At an inn, damn you, you bloody drunk. Mama.
Is this kid on trial? Oh, this is like a trial. Okay, hold on.
Drag and drop documents to manage their layout click to display their contents.
React to events. Ignoring them may have severe consequences. Okay, so that's events, documents.
Review detailed information about current events, actions, and characters.
Okay. Choose- Consider the effects and decide the defendant's fate.
And you can change the settings from here. Review the current balance of power in Paris
and your position therein. So that's the balance of power. Intrigues are complex conflicts
between you and another political player. A defeat may turn out to be disastrous for you.
This is how many influence points I have of the main currency in the game. Use them wisely.
And then we got like a Sims notification field. Pay close attention to the changes
in your influence and relations with factions. Okay. Some of your decisions and changes in the
world of the game may cause global modifiers to come into effect. These factors affect
relations, reputation, and influence. You can review them in the notebook.
All right, so guilty. No, punishment. Make the most important decision. Condemn the defendant
or deem them not guilty. Sign the document to legitimize your verdict. Okay, so choose a
verdict. What if I just say you're guilty? I'm dead, right? All right, so here we go.
Case file. Review charges and facts. This will make it easier for you to unlock questions
for the defendant. Okay, so review charges and facts. But where are these the facts?
All right, so case file. This is an assault. Skip this? I'm not gonna skip this. I have to,
what am I gonna go off of like how I feel? We have not expected this kind of behavior from
your son, although apparently we should have. Innocent child's play turned into an assault
on our children. The younger one, Antoine, now has a chipped front tooth. We hope that
you will punish your child accordingly. Should the situation repeat itself, we will react more
decisive decisively. I am sure we can deal with the gambler and drunkard even if he is a judge.
We will not let our children be hurt. Okay, can I click these? We should have. Innocent,
an innocent child's play turned into an assault. Innocent. Finding links. I'm not
gonna put my son to the guillotine. Find the correct links to unlock questions for
the defendant. Choose a line of inquiry and link it to the right category.
Okay, what the fuck? While linking lines of inquiry in categories, you can make a limited
number of mistakes. If you make too many mistakes, the whole system will become locked.
Oh god. And there are traps here too? Some cases may contain traps. Read through the
files thoroughly to find the lines of inquiry that are irrelevant. Okay, so child's play.
I thought that you said eating children. I was like, that, where did that come from?
All right, wait, wait, go back, go back, back. Course of events. Wait, wait, hold on,
let me look at this. So, innocent child's play turned into an assault. The younger one.
So, Antoine has a chipped front tooth. So, innocent child's play turned into a chipped
front tooth. Should the situation repeat itself, we will react more. So, okay,
innocent child's play into a front tooth being chipped. Okay, so let's take a look.
Child's play to, all right, so we've got course of events in victim. Wait, this isn't a
Jerma game. Yes, it is. All right, this is the victim. Fighting children is the
extenuating circumstance. No, no, no, chipped tooth is the extenuating circumstance. Oh, fuck.
That's all right, we have a question. Hold on. Gather information to influence
the jury's attitude. Why is there a jury here? Why am I bringing this? This is what happens when
you have a dad judge. All right, this is the embarrassing shit that you have to go through.
What exactly were they saying? Okay, who started the fight? To ask questions, you have to first
unlock them in the inquiry linking menu. Okay, being in the jury's good graces allows you to
find out which way they will sway after you have asked a question. Okay, so you can sway
on home. Let me go back to this. So an injured Anton. So we've got possibility of repeating.
We've got fighting children is the that's the course of events. Okay, chipped tooth is also
the course of events. All right, that's I get it. All right, what's my son's name? How did
your play turn into a fight? That makes sense. How did your play turn into a fight?
Our neighbors, Antoine and Jean, they were saying mean things about you.
We were playing guards and they asked me to pretend to be a drunkard whom they would,
you know, you were fighting both of them at once. I had to. All right, so they were making
fun of me. And then he started fighting two people at the same time. All right, who started
this fight? Did you start it? Or did somebody for a rocket? Who started the fight? I can tell
you who ended it. He didn't have a bruise or anything. Oh, he did. I think it was me. I
kicked the one on the left and then wanted to get the one on the right. But but they ended
it. They knocked me to the ground and paid me back for hitting them. Okay, so you so they
made they made fun of me and then you kicked one of them. Okay, what did you really break
Antoine's tooth? There's a really noisy courtroom with nobody being here. Yeah.
Frederick is just a child. I don't know. I don't think so. I don't think I broke his tooth.
Did you hit him in the face? I think I kicked him, but not that hard. Okay, but in the
face. Did you kick him in the face? What were they saying? Are you too drunk to guess? Who
is this person? Can I contempt a court this person out of here? I was not asking you.
They were yelling that you are well, I told them that it's not true. And they started
calling me names. They called me a drunkard's son. Okay, so let me look at this one more
time. The young one now has a chipped front tooth. He probably fell down. Let me look
at this shit. Negative relations with factions mean negative consequences for you.
AKA the fervor in Paris rising. So this is my relations. There are factions. Yeah, reputation.
Reputation impacts everything in the world of the game. Factions, family relations,
the audience's attitude. That's you. That's you guys. The fervor in the sections and even the
ability to persuade other characters. You have a set amount of influence points per day. In
the future, you will be able to increase this limit. All right, so how many death penalties
do I have? Zero. So this is the common folk. This is how the common folk feel about me. This
is how the revolutionaries feel about me. This is my reputation is pretty much right in the
Okay, this good to know. What's this? Events. Here you'll find okay, this is information about
events. And then this last one is people and family and okay, you can see detailed
info. So this is my wife. This is my oldest son. No, it's not. Yes, this is my oldest
son. This is my youngest son. I have my dad and then my mentor. Got it. So this is all family in
here. All right, so look at the hierarchy for a second. This is me. A judge of the
Revolutionary Tribunal, generally considered drunkard and gambler, a protege of Raymond
DuVoy, who introduced him to the world of law and regulations. In private, he is an
unremarkable character. We'll just wait till I make it up to like top 1000 streamer
in Vegas. All right, so let's let me get this straight. He started the fight. Somebody if
somebody calls me names, you just tell them you just you just tell them to shut the fuck up.
Okay. You can't like attack somebody you can't you're guilty. You say leave me alone.
You say oh yeah well my dad's a judge. What's this? Make your decision. Each action may
require a different number of influence points and have a different chance of success. Consider
them carefully. Intimidate parents. We can go right to evil if you want. Your addictions
are no longer a secret. The fact that other children are bullying your son because of them
is a minor problem. But who is spreading those rumors? It is likely to be one of their
parents. They could have whispered into their children's ears whom they shouldn't play with
and why. They might even have spiced the story with a lie. But who will but who will hear it next?
Now I can't just go fall on chaotic evil. No. Let's talk eye to eye. This is one influence
point. Talk eye to eye. Neighborhood gossip. So now what does that do for me now?
Neighborhood gossip. Yeah I've read this already. So this is reputation influence. I mean I
already read this. Did that show up in a different place? Maybe we'll see later on.
Because I don't think I can. I think that just means I'm going to talk to them. Any other
questions? Now what about you guys? Can I interact with anybody here? No I think that
just happens at some point later on. Because now there's nothing really else to do. Vertex
form. To the gallows. No. I mean I found the defendant guilty of the offense which they
were charged. You kicked somebody. How am I supposed to prove that you didn't, right?
Here's my signature. I'm not going to give my actual signature because I don't want anyone to
have that. What's my name? I'm scared to even do anything remotely similar. How about um
oh there we go. I did it. Guilty. Unfortunately you should not start fights regardless of
the reason. Look come on. Does my son go to prison? Those children are so small and they
already know the truth. The father of my children is a lying drunk and a gambler. Bernard used to
worship you but he soon grew up. Now it is Frederick's turn to learn the truth that echoes
in the streets. He's no longer fearing your anger. He knows that your threats are empty.
Frederick is only starting to learn the truth about his father from the streets.
I was unaware that Matilda had such a temper. As was I. We will wait outside as always.
Congratulations. You passed the first judge exam. Paris. Liberty. We were enchanted by the idea
of freedom. Could not resist it. Is that me or am I taking these pictures? Yeah I'm taking
these photos. Whole families took to the streets. We're on like this is like vacation photos.
France was never so happy. We were enchanted by the idea of freedom.
Yeah this is the revolution. Yeah I know it's very loud. It's one of those games
it's very loud if it's in a cut scene. Act one. All right here we go. Liberty day one.
Okay here we go. So expected sentence. Find out which verdict is expected by the factions
and your close ones. Okay so acquittal and prison. The common folk and revolutionaries want
prison and this is um nobody expected but who is it? Police file. Okay hold on. Wait wait wait
everybody hold on a second. I need like a minute to get ready. There's no timer.
I can take as long as I want. Imagine a judge saying this. I can take as long as I want. I
just I need to review the case first. I might need to get a coffee too. All right so this is
in difficult times people like to seek peace at the bottom of a glass.
Please introduce yourself. My name is Jean Renard and the Montserrat is huge. Nothing but a fraud.
Systematically opposing the opinion of the jury may lead to serious consequences.
Okay so everyone wants this guy arrested. Let's see what he did.
Compiled by Richard Moneur. Fraud. Jean Renard, a 45 year old innkeeper, has been charged with
fraud. He's accused of diluting alcohol in his tavern, tricking his clients into paying extra.
Okay. Guests came with their mindset on a specific goal, getting roaring drunk,
but instead of staggering out after drinking two pitchers of wine or several pints of beer,
they would sit in the inn until morning still sober and completely penniless.
The innkeeper's fraud came to light when one of the customers discovered the scam
and caught the cheater in the act. The man entered the host cellar and witnessed him
diluting the alcohol in the barrels with ordinary water. As a result, customers received
only four parts of what they had paid for and one part from the water carrier.
So he was diluting alcohol, but all right. So let's see. So diluting alcohol. So the innkeeper
exposing the innkeeper, customers drunkenness, adding water was the method.
Okay. Diluting alcohol was the method. But what about, I need a motive. What's going on here?
Motive for the innkeeper. Caught in a trap. What does that mean? I wouldn't even caught in
a trap. Did he set a trap? I can't ask any more questions. What? No. Customers drunkenness,
are the witnesses. Fuck. Shit. Exposing the innkeeper is the motive.
It's the motive and exposing the innkeeper. We need witnesses, right? Okay. We're good.
Here we go. So we have influence on the jury's opinion. This is people are going to want like
guillotine. Should I just call in the witness? People want this guy dead. How long you've
been involved in the illegal practice of diluting alcohol? Yeah, that means like,
do your clients drink a lot? Okay. Please call in Thomas Leclerc to the stands.
Please introduce yourself. Thomas Leclerc. I'm the regular Gene Renard's establishment.
Okay. How long have you suspected that something was wrong with the alcohol?
How did you catch citizen? How did you catch him in the act? How'd you catch him in the
act? I was having one drink after another. So I had to, you know, I'm Monterey. I think
that means Pete. So it happened that one time I got lost and instead of, you know, I
ended up in the cellar where I saw Renard adding water to the barrels.
Fuck. They want him in prison. All right. So that's a witness testimony.
Wait, wait, wait. Can I tell her, can I like, is it like, where's my gavel?
Please call it, okay. Review the trials records so I can review what happened previously.
All right. A button news here. Here we go. Neighborhood gossip. The father had a rare
episode of foolishness when he decided to stand up to someone stronger. Threatening
him with a fist and showing his children they are safe by his side. He did not listen to
your arguments. Furthermore, he gave a precise description of where you can shove them. What?
Why am I getting this right now during a case? Like somebody just slides that on the
desk. I know you're busy with this, this case, but somebody, what? I don't know,
man. I might, I might say fuck this guy. Okay. So threatening him with a fist and
showing his children they're safe by his side. He didn't listen to your arguments.
What we don't, oh yeah. Like I'm supposed to be doing a case here.
I'm hiring thugs not to hurt them. They're going to go do the, two of them are going
to go. I had two influence points. They're going to both raise their fist at him like
he did to me. And then he's going to hire three thugs and do that to me. And we're
going to keep going until one of us eventually wins the auction. All right. So let's take a look
again. We already know. All right. Let me do some more questions. Probably let's question them.
Okay. So how did you feel? Do clients drink a lot? Tavern regulars usually drink a lot.
So you have been selling plenty of wine. Quite a lot. Yeah. And yet you have been
paying taxes on the amount of wine you bought, not the amount of wine you've been selling.
Correct. I don't understand. You've been paying taxes on four wine barrels, but by adding a quarter
of water to each have actually made the money for selling five barrels of wine.
Oh, that's one way of putting it, but perhaps it is correct. I'm not good with numbers.
You are not good with numbers, yet good enough to have calculated that fraud pays off.
I wasn't aware. I will take this answer into account.
The judge has exposed the bastard. This guy's an idiot. Okay. How long you've been involved
in the illegal practice of diluting alcohol. It's not an illegal practice. Everyone adds a
little bit. In your case, it was a bit of wine in the water, not the other way around.
Have you been doing this for a long time? A few weeks at the most. It's been hard to
earn a living lately. I used to run an honest business. Pure wine was overspilling the
glasses. Is there any proof to support your testimony? He lied to his customers. No reason
he wouldn't lie in court. Does he have anything? Give me some documents. Anything.
You don't got anything to give me here. How did you feel about tricking the citizens?
Terrible. But all I wanted was to keep my business afloat. Others don't mess around for
sure. No diluting would be the end of me. So you decided to commit fraud so as not to lose
money. If I lost my tavern, my family would starve to death. Do you have children? I do.
One son and two daughters. Time to start saving up for the dowry. Then why don't you send them
to work? Idiot. All right. It's, uh, jury's opinion is prison. They're getting inflamed
here. People want him in prison. Uh, let me see. Yeah. Let's take a look. What do we
got here? Choose a verdict to see its influence. The jury votes in favor of incarceration.
The defendant, they find the punishment sufficient. Choose a verdict. Prison.
So this would, uh, give me a reputation bonus with common folk and with revolutionaries.
Reputation bonus if you can get up there. Okay. Uh, what about a quiddle?
Go on. Go free. Just don't do it again. All right. I'm sorry, sir, but you've been,
I mean, we've got witness testimony. We've got your own testimony. You're talking about tax
fraud. You're going to prison. Sorry, but that's the way it is. I sentence citizen
Jean Renard to prison. Lead the condemned out. Huzzah. Long live pure wine. All right.
Moving on. After trial, click to move on to the next part.
We're going to get some big like fucking M. Night Shyamalan twist.
Verdict form. Here we go. Okay. May I remind you that you promised to join me?
I have a feeling that tonight's moon favors gamblers, though it does not favor spouses.
God should grace us with wives who understand the importance of an evening game of dice.
They should also know that the right amount of wine guarantees a lucky role.
I should go home. Bringing a judge to the game has benefits. Other players will surely not cheat.
That is not a strong argument. My name is Jacques-Louis David.
I am but a humble painter, not a silver-tongued judge.
You are a sly politician, Jacques. As a politician, I understand the
importance of keeping promises. And you, my friend, are trying to get out of yours.
Go out or go home? I just got in trouble with my wife for going out.
Go out. But this could be a good political move for me.
Send thugs. Oh my god. But what about my career? Nah, I'm gonna do the right...
Not tonight, Jay. Now he's gonna work to undermine me.
Oh, how boring! I could be sitting in that seat right there with my coins.
The same cold meatloaf and cold peas and cold potatoes and cold gravy and
cold thyme leaves and cold plates and cold eyes staring back at me, angry with me.
Late evening at the judge's house. Uh-oh. What?
Do you not want to berate me like you always do? I'm glad you're home.
Are you aware that Frederick sometimes imagines you as a deep sea sailor?
He dreams that you visit distant countries and have wonderful adventures.
But he would rather have you by his side, on land. We all want that.
I don't want to watch the storm blow your lifeboat away and bury it beneath the waves.
There are no waves. The storm is getting closer.
Dark clouds already hang over the shore. Just wait until they finish building the guillotine.
Your oars will break at once and the waves will take you to a place you'll
soon wish you'd never set foot on. A place without us. Your family loves you.
But we won't find you in the darkness that has already begun to reach for you.
Relations with family. You have to choose an action. What?
Oh god. Upon returning home, you can decide how you would like to spend the rest of the day.
Each action will affect the other members of the family as well as their attitude towards you.
Okay. Each character's attitude can provide you with or deprive you of certain bonuses,
like reputation or relations with factions. Your youngest son is special.
His attitude makes the other family members, like you slightly more, take good care of him.
Okay, so hanging out with grandpa gives influence to the people.
Hanging out with Bernard is influence on the revolutionaries.
Hanging out with Matilda is influence on reputation and then influence on the family.
Opening night at the theater. There's a new play opening tonight on stage at the
Comme des Francaux. It is a good chance to take a breather from reality. Political debate.
It's time for the grown men to talk about the revolution's achievements.
It should be an interesting exchange. Spend your evening and your energy on carefree playtime
with your sons. Your wife's needs can wait. Reading together. There's nothing like sitting
with your family in a good book next to a warm fire, even though some may think it is dull.
Why don't we just all go out to the play? Everybody gets to go to the play.
Playtime with grandpa. Debate the child? No, the child is not. It's only these two.
No, all right. Let's involve everybody. Let's just hang out with the kids and just have fun.
We're gonna, okay. Why did you not? Oh, your wife's needs can wait. You weren't you not
involved? So that influenced, oh man, my god. This is just, there's a lot going on here.
Okay, today the people of Paris commemorate Jacques Guillemin Simon, Mayor of Vintampes.
He was lynched by a furious mob for performing his duties to France.
This march shall symbolize the unity of our society in the hope that the most
violent stage of the revolution is past us. Let us make sure that no other loyal
servant of France becomes a victim of such hatred ever again from King Louis.
Oh, Simon, you was a good loyal officer. Those bastards lynched him for observing the law.
Will you join me at the march? We have to show that we oppose the self-appointed
executioners and stand alongside. I wonder why the king has taken the trouble to show up.
Louis marching in arm and arm with the people of Paris, that is unexpected.
King Louis, continue please. I am merely an observer. Do not change your habits for me.
I heard a thing or two about a young and ambitious judge at the tribunal.
I was curious as to he guided by justice or by entertainment, as some would say.
Oh, we've got this theft and burglary. Hold on, we've got a dozen notifications here.
Good relationship with a younger son. Your younger son adores you like he used to back
in better days. This is a drawing, an invite. Oh, well thanks. That's nice of you.
Okay, so we've got a new case here. Got a good relationship with the son.
Is that, that's, that's, that's King Louis. I got some news here.
All right, neighborhood gossip. Uh-oh. Most parasi, I don't even know what that is,
ordinary. They have ordinary problems, ordinary consciences, and an ordinary's
resistance to pain. They were not hardened by the revolution. The father of the family
that spread the rumor about your weaknesses was no different. A few punches were more
than enough to convince his instincts that it was time to stop talking. Parisians.
Most, why does it just, why does the judge say most people from Paris?
Most Parisians. Is that what they're called? Parisians? I did not know that.
All right, so common folk endorsement went down by two, but my reputation went up.
So that may not have been a great idea. Common folk minus two, reputation plus one.
That's from the gossip of the neighborhood. All right, let's go.
All right, here we go. Who do we have here? We have, the defendant is Oliver Muggler,
a 65 year old master locksmith who was famed among Parisian burglars as an expert on
unopenable locks. Okay. Last month, he was commissioned by the owners of a Parisian
glassworks, Jean Rude, Louis Rowe, and Ferdinand Salon to construct locks for ornate chests for
valuables, presumably as gifts for their wives. The craftsman praised his latest creation as
thief proof. Shortly following their completion, the industrialist houses were hit by a series
of burglaries committed by a recent newcomer to Paris, Hector Vian. The thief from Orleans
was caught in the act and shot by Ferdinand Salon. An expensive
Turgo map of Paris, but the houses of the recently robbed industrialist marked on it was
found on the deceased. Surprisingly, Salon had given Muggler an identical map as advanced
payment. This deposit was an addition to the agreed remuneration from all the employers.
Okay. So he had somebody do his dirty work. All right. Let's see. So we have master locksmith
who is a famous locksmith. So a month ago, these three people commissioned him to make
an impossible lock. Oh, there's more. Oh, right. Okay. So let me just, let me just get this,
make sure I get this straight. So construct locks for ornate chests. So he's like,
yeah, I can make a lock for you and nobody will be able to break into it. Okay. Great.
After they were done, all their houses were hit by burglars
by a newcomer to Paris. Okay. This guy, Hector Vian, this is the thief from Orleans
and shot by Ferdinand Salon and anybody these people. Okay. So Ferdinand Salon
was one of the people that commissioned. So he was caught in the act at one of the houses.
I got it. Further interesting information came from the owner of the Ginger Margo Inn. She
recalled that on the night proceeding the burglary, the locksmith met there with a
man she didn't recognize. Based on her description, we were able to identify him as the affirmation
to Hector Vian. The men allegedly engaged in an evening of drinking sponsored by Muggler.
And then we have a map of Paris found on Hector Vian. Let's take a look.
Do I have that in my, uh, that's protocol. Where's, um, notebook somewhere. Kind of want
to see the, uh, kind of want to see it. All right. So even though this is very obvious
evening of drinking, a drunken evening. Uh, that's not an accusation marks on the map
series of burglaries. Uh, been to master locksmith. We got, we only got fucking a few
questions asked here. Sentence and thugs. No, the famous thief. Try like accused that,
you know who that is. This is that's evidence. Master locksmith is what about the drunken
evening, the construction of the locks series of bullets. That's that's, but that's like
a course, it's course of events. Okay. I still have six more questions to reveal and I can only
make three mistakes. Marks on the map or I mean, come on, like you got marks on the goddamn
map. That's an accusation, right? Like yeah, drunken evening, course of events. Yeah. Lock
construction, uh, personality, famous thief. I guess you could say that's extending winning
circumstances. Maybe law construction is course of events. It's probably course of events.
Yeah. And then finally the master locksmith is extended. Okay. We got them all. No mistakes.
Uh, the jury has not revealed it's for it gets okay. The acquittal is for common folk.
Think this guy's a common folk. Think this is a good guy and the revolutionaries, uh,
think don't want to think he's a bad guy. We got the king in the court here and I am ready
to start my questioning. Robbing the persuasion is no crime. According to the case file,
you are citizen Oliver Muggler. Is that correct? Uh, uh, voice and see. Indeed it is.
More sure as you may have a request. I'd like to sit down. I'm an old man. You see
basic respect for the judiciary requires that you remain standing. The names salon,
rude and row mean anything to you. Why are you so determined to harass an old man?
They sound like the names of my debtors. Debtors. They are the victims of activities.
You conducted. You mean look smithing. You were commissioned by the victims to make
chess locks. Did you know Hector Vian before? Do you recognize this map?
Were you the one who marked the addresses on the map? How much did you charge for
your services? We'll start. We're gonna start at a zero. How much did you charge for your services?
3000 francs. Tidy some that is. If you were a master locksmith, you charge that much too.
That is quite a substantial fee. Indeed. That's how much it costs to have high
quality locks made by a master with nearly 50 years of experience. And those bastards never
paid me a single franc. The victims did not pay you the agreed amount. Not a franc. I'd
beat that money right out of them, but I'm too old for that. So you didn't get paid?
Cases break it open wide. All right. Um, that rumor has it that you're one of the best locksmiths
in all of Paris. I should deny it for modesty's sake, but I will not. That cannot be true,
though, as a random thief from Orleans was easily able to open your locks. Well, then
he must have been one of the best thieves in Orleans. I should be serious. Every lock can
be picked with the right talents, even mine. Okay. So we're going down towards
revolutionaries here. All right. It's time. I think it's time we, uh, we bring out the big
guns here. Hmm. You were commissioned by the victims to make chest locks. Did you know
Hector Vian before? This is the first time I've heard the name. That's interesting as
you were seen draining several bottles of wine together at the Ginger Margo Inn.
Is that a crime? No, but the question is, why are you denying it now?
Was your drinking spree just a deception for discussing the burglary?
Nobody I had a drink with introduced themselves as Hector. I didn't plan on heist for Vector,
Victor or Hugo. I'm a locksmith and I earn good money from it. Burglaries are for vagrants
without a job. Okay. So you may have been drinking with them. There's no way to tell
that you knew them beforehand. Okay. You recognize this map? No, I don't recall ever
seeing it before. Ferdinand Salon claims that he gave you this map as advanced payment
for your services. He claims what? That wicked wretch of a second rate merchant. He gave me
a scrap of old paper as payment for making three locks and said it's supposed to be worth
more than 3000 francs he owes me. And honest labor is being judged while frauds remain
at large. Silence. So this map does belong to you. It doesn't. So where's the map that you
received from Citizen Salon? I lost it. Oh, what horse shit. I lost it. But it wasn't even worth
a loaf of bread. So I surely won't shed a tear. But if you have it, maybe you stole it from
me. You better make a note of that Oliver Muggler demands rumination from Rude, Roy and Salon.
All right. Hold on a second here. I didn't pay him though. Can I call somebody to the stands?
Can I? Did they not pay him? So circumstantially he could have been just drinking.
That might he just may have been out there hanging out. And maybe he he got the map stolen
from him by the guy he was drinking with. Right. And if he didn't get paid, then maybe
he's just kind of disgruntled. Common people don't like that. Prison is not something that
the common people want. I have more questions. Do I? Is there a penalty to? Well, I mean,
I guess look, right? So depending on how I want to have this play out here,
I could ask another question. This one. This is balanced, right? Let's bring this up a little
bit. Or the neutral ones. Did you give Hector the map? I gave nothing to Achilles, Hector or
any other Greek God. Call on the witness citizen Jean Rude. Oh, there we go. Jean Rude in the
flesh. He will not speak unless called upon. Naturally, of course. What went missing during the
burglary? My house was the first one to be robbed. And in my case, it was mostly valuables.
At Rue's house, he will not say it himself. And I do not want to go to prison.
It was the letters he had exchanged over the years with King Louis. Oh, damn monarchist.
Salon did not lose a thing. He shot that vermin in the act. That is what he said. What happened to
the items that he stole? That still remains unknown. According to Salon, Hector had nothing
with him. Ferdinand suspects he had hidden the other valuables somewhere. He hid the other
items before robbing the last house? Strange. Huh. Advanced payment in the form of a map,
its disappearance, the murder of a burglar, and a lack of payment for services.
You look upset. What are you afraid of? Yeah, look at all this shit.
And a lack of payment for services. It all makes for a rather strange story, a suspicious one,
too. I do not. What are you mumbling? If I say something, will I be free?
He knows something. Please testify what you know immediately.
The map was Salon's idea. He told the thief about the advanced payment we gave
the locksmith and proposed that Hector steal it. And he did? Indeed. But when the bastard robbed
us, later we were forced by Salon not to pay the locksmith because he sent the thief after
us. And that's when it all went down a drain. That's the bourgeoisie for you. He fooled them
all and went in one fell swoop. It sounds like citizen Salon had everything planned.
However, there's no evidence to support the claim. Perhaps it is citizen Rude that is
plotting against his partner and wants to frame him. And Vion is dead, so he will not be able to
shed light on any of this. If I was younger, I'd give that Salon a drubbin. I'd peep that
good-for-nothing lying bastard. Please restrain yourself. The testimony of a witness is still
not evidence. Neither of citizen Salon's guilt nor of your innocence. Oh shit. Well,
I don't I don't think that you are I don't think you committed a crime here.
This is the jury's opinion. Yeah. Yeah, I think we got enough information here.
That's an acquittal. Ask the neutral questions? I don't think I even need to. Did you tell
Hector how to open the locks? I understand what you're implying, but consider this. If
he sold the secret of my locks, then my business would be over. Wood spreads fast among
thieves. Yeah, I guess I could probably ask one of these. I don't think it would go up much higher.
I need to know. Were you the one who marked the addresses on the maps? No,
no, he didn't do shit. He's he's innocent. Yep, we're gonna be I got some we lost with
the revolutionaries though. Risk of being removed from office. We can't let this go down that
far. Kill him just in case. This is risky, because that makes it I gotta think about my career.
All right, acquittal. That's my verdict. There's way there's way too much going on here.
The verdict for citizen Oliver Muggler is not guilty. Lead the defendant away.
Bravo, Muggler. Away with the bourgeoisie. If I may, to be honest, this does bear the marks of
social justice. They would not pay him so he had them robbed. There is a balance here. Grandpa,
that's not really what happened. Common folk. Okay, lost with the revolutionaries, but gained
with common folk. Senile old man couldn't even hear the case. Is that am I good to go?
Well, that's because I lost some common folk. So I just gained it back. What am I doing on
the hierarchy? I'm still just oh, wait a minute, hold on. Who are these two? David. Oh, that's the
guy that came to me and said, who is this guy with the sunglasses on? He's widely referred to
as the incorruptible. As leader of the radical Jacobins. He preserves order in the national
convention with an iron fist and of need be terror. Undeniably the most powerful man in
Paris in the age of revolution. As yet none have dared defy him. That's me. So this is my friend
and I don't know who that is. I guess I don't know who that is yet. All right,
we've got plenty of good names here. All right, congratulations, you're free.
I think that's good. Let's get out of here. Next. Look, an authentic map by Togo. It would
be a pity if it rotted in a safe deposit box. We cannot do that. These are court deposits.
Well, the tilde did tell me long ago to take care of my study at home.
There you go. I know someone who can remove these marks without damaging the map.
The king is just still hanging out here. Is he sleeping? King Louis the 16th. There were people
who truly loved him. He reminded the French they had noble ancestors. Do not be manipulated
by people who are not bearing the burden of responsibility. Good George Washington right there.
Well, this saddened me. Someone had advised him to say that. Someone who was well aware
of the cold, inevitable wind of change. I did not pity the king, but those who will come after
him as they will not have great ancestors. Okay, one of us. A Frenchman marched in the
streets of Paris side by side, one line after another to commemorate Jacques Guillemin
a mayor of Entemps. He was murdered by a furious mob, punished for a law he did not enact,
but was obliged to observe. Freedom of speech killed him. If we understand this as the right
to cast stones to show one's discontent, the right to murder people because you deem them
responsible for your miserable life, surely the people of Paris would prefer if we said that
nothing happened. Lost common folk. Gain revolutionary. Your son is rather good with
the violin. He is both talented and enthusiastic. I'd prefer that he was as enthusiastic about the
law books I give him. I look so defeated. Maybe his destiny is to become an artist,
not a lawyer. Mother likes to hear me playing, and there is nothing more boring than law.
See? He would rather let his career rely on the humours of the people. There are many ways
to re-zoo-escue France. Believe me, our country desperately needs something to ennoble
it. The power is in the hands of simple, illiterate people. Let him rescue their souls with music.
That's better than boring laws and clauses. See what you're doing? You are spoiling my child.
I do not have my own children to spoil, so I am focusing on yours. Speaking of which...
Oh, no, no, no, no. Here we go. Locked action. After various important events,
you may find yourself in an action forced upon you. On this day, you become the victim of
your own decisions. Oh, c'est manuel. You cannot change. You attended the parade in memory of
the lynched official. So that's what we did. That's what we're going to do. People influence
Bernard, influence on revolutionaries. Wife is not that happy. Son's doing all right.
Libert. Day three. That is our new symbol of freedom. You can still smell the fresh wood.
Do you feel free looking at it? Individuals like us do not need symbols, but France does.
Did you hear the news of the day? People are running around like headless chickens
and yelling about Louis and his entourage escaping Paris.
So we will not be enjoying the aroma of fresh wood for long.
Monuments like that are not installed solely for the purpose of punishing thieves or lesser
aristocrats. Do you think it wants to taste royal blood? Louis' flight was a stupid move,
yet it seems it was planned. One of us will sacrifice him. That is, if they catch him.
Is that why Louis visited us at the court? To manipulate us? Maybe deep in his heart he
felt what the builders of the guillotine did. That someone has to be exposed as a traitor,
even if there is none. Interesting. Okay. This is Antoine. Welcome, citizen Fidel. My name is
Antoine Quentin Faquer de Tinville. I am the public prosecutor that has been assigned to assist
at every tribunal trial starting from today. Okay. I should warn you that I am uncompromising,
although I hope that we quickly find common ground. In happier news, the construction of
the guillotine has been finished. We may begin using it today. Yes, we've seen it.
The king is gone. Treason. Anyone with information about his whereabouts should
immediately disclose it to the authorities. From Rasputin. Okay. Anyone with information
about his whereabouts should immediately disclose it to the authorities. Okay.
So I'm assuming this is a little law here. What does this start? Okay, so this is
burglary. Notifications. Let's see. Uh, good relations with the father. Yours,
pride and joy. Keep it up. Anything else? Okay. So father and son, both very, very happy.
So we've got death penalty, prison, and then acquittal. That's the common vogue and
revolutionaries. The jury has not revealed its verdict yet. We need to use the new toy. Oh,
God. Do it. Do it with no questions.
Immediately do it. You got, hold on a second. They just, they're not even done building it.
I want blood. Do it. Do it. At least once. No. What? There is no save game.
Do it. They just built it. Oh my God, guys. That's gonna,
the defendant confessed to the crimes.
No. What made the defendant famous in the eyes of the people? Uh, uh, this one. How did the
defendant explain signs of assault? Um, I don't know. I don't know. I sentence citizen
John Ilver to be guillotined. I just got an achievement for doing that by the way. The
evidence against him was not conclusive. Outrageous. What are you doing? You fool,
traitor of the people, murderer of our hero. A verdict already? What about the trial?
Bad job. I got an achievement for that. It said, I think if you guillotine somebody within
10 seconds of it starting, you get an achievement. Rumors are spreading. Rumors
about your careless approach to your duties are spreading. You'd better shape it up if you
want to keep your job. That wasn't worth it. Maybe it was for the achievement.
Well, no, maybe I could win the heart of the crowd. Earn the favor of the crowd by delivering
a speech or proceed directly to the execution. I have to give a speech on me? Just remember,
once you start your speech, there's no going back. An awkward or clumsy speech will earn
you nothing but ridicule from the audience. Depending on your reputation, the crowd will
be more or less aggressive. Strategy building? What? Before attempting persuasion, you may
explore different approaches to all the topics of the conversation. After employing every
kind of emotion, you will receive an evaluation of your choices. Okay.
Each attitude comes with a set of emotions that have a positive and negative impact.
Learn their effects to manipulate the people of Paris in any way you please.
The higher your reputation, the more you know about the other speaker's attitude.
You can also obtain this information by spending influence points.
Okay. Choose topic. Humility. The defendant. Manipulation. Revolution. Okay. Oh my God.
Crime. Aggression. Defendant. Humility. Revolution. Manipulation. I got points,
right? Oversensitive. Okay. So they go. A strong argument. Good. And they're attached.
So maybe actually, yeah. Manipulate humility and we'll go with some aggression here.
If they're oversensitive, why would I want to be aggressive? If they're attached,
why would I want to be aggressive? No. What are you talking about? I don't think I need
it. Here we go. Today marks the what? What's going on? When there is a crime,
there must be punishment and we shall dish it out. Oh, yes. Even the convict's ancestor
Scheffler, the cold edge of the guillotine slicing through their necks. The criminals
belong in the grave. Only then we build a better future. The reign of the previous
rulers whose goal was to bring injustice to the people ends with their swift deaths.
They were doubtful. All right. I understand. You can reveal it.
You decapitated a man for a scuffle in the streets. People, I rescued you and now you
murder me. What? Off with his head. Pull the revolution. Oh, I have to do this.
I'm just the judge. Pull the ro- Due to the establishment of a revolutionary tribunal,
we need to prepare an official stamp. I was told to ask you, citizen,
because President DeVoy is indisposed. How much did he drink? He was not able to say,
shall we? Design your stamp. Okay. My base. I want it to be three dots. I like this. I like
that. Emblem, the crow, the chicken, the compass, the horn, the scale, the book,
the White House, the owl, the quarter, the judge, the tree, the surrender, the time,
the key, the lady, the goblet of fire, the lion, defense, eagle, bow and arrow,
musket man, and then two crayons. I think I'm going to do two crayons. I like, no,
something a little small. I like that. Change the base. If we're going to have two,
if we're going to have the crayon crossed, then it needs to, that's all right. That looks
good. Thank you for your time. I know it's late. The stamp should be ready tomorrow.
Good night. Look, okay. Work on tomorrow's trial. All right. Now that I got that, like,
you can't ask for that again. You used your one chat joke Trump card, right? Not again.
So work on tomorrow's trial. You will unlock more question effects in court. I have to do
this because I need to make sure this trial is done correctly. The wife. Go gamble. Evening
gambling. You should spend some time with your father every now and then. Show him your world.
Perhaps you will get a taste for it. Your world. Go lie down face up with the neck in guillotine
and pray for soft winds. Paragraphs and codes. Needs to learn some more
perspective skills and law can be taught. And law can be an art in its own right.
Your eldest wife is going to hate you? I only have one wife. What are you talking about?
You take your family for an evening stroll around Paris. It will let your father stretch
his bones a little. Let's take the family up. Wow, he hated that. He liked it. Okay. What about
the son? Nice. Almost got a fall bar. He's old. He hates walking. You only read chat when
they give you shitty joke advice. Why? I read chat the whole day. What? What are you talking
about? That was okay. That was a unanimous chat decision. All right. There was only a couple
of one guys that didn't want me to do that. You cannot go back to your chat logs and you
look at that unanimous chat display. It was, I didn't even need to do a poll. It was so
overwhelming. I got the achievement. I got like the kill a guy without even looking.
Achievement. All right. Anyway, let's go. I wasn't joking and I'm glad you killed him.
All right. All right. Here's Matthew. Tragically, we are losing control of the streets.
People feel betrayed by the king and some believe him to be a spy trying to elude justice.
Special means are recommended when suppressing unrest. We only need an opinion from the judges
to make sure. I'm going to read that again because I have to do that again. I wasn't paying
attention. Special means are recommended when suppressing unrest. We only need an opinion
from the judges to make sure we are working legally. In other words, you need their
blessing to shoot at protesters. People can't control their emotions and are hurting at the
citizens as a result. Look at the windows. Next time they might do something worse than
just throw rocks. It pains us to see unrest growing in the streets of Paris.
Commander in Chief Burel has informed us that the guard is no longer able to control the
situation through peaceful means. It is recommended that he be allowed to use more
immediate methods to protect the innocent civilians. But we would like to know the
tribunal's opinion on the matter. I approve of the National Guard's use of force against
running, ruining the capital. Accept it. Chat deserves karma.
No, no, I'm with Grandpa on this one. Yeah, no. The authority should not use force against
the people. If it has to, it already has lost. I do not approve of this decree.
Oh, right. I just put it on my signature. It's the first time I've done this. I don't know.
Without this document, we can only wait for the citizens of Paris to start killing each
other before our very eyes. I hope you know what you're doing. The convention may have issued
that decree, but I have no doubt it was Robert Svearie's idea. Executes a guy with literally
no trial. Whoa, violence against civilians. Ah, that's not okay. That wasn't me. I was
out sick that day. Chat took over that day. I was out sick. The mob wanted to act as both
judge and jury again and hang people from the street lamps. Poor Pochard was almost hanged.
Pochard? Claude Pochard? Exactly. The beloved tutor of your Frederick. You had to dismiss him
after the incident with the oath of the clergy, did you not? Yes, Frederick tells me from time
to time that he misses his teacher. What are you doing? The trial is about to begin.
It's about Monsieur Pochard. News travels fast. He's been accused of counter-revolutionary
activities. You know him. It can't be true. It's not so simple. Leave before somebody hears
us. Papa, please go home. Think about the family for once at least. Papa. Uh oh.
Good relationship with the elder son. Got good relationship. Okay. All right. Let's see here.
We got the family wants acquittal. This is the revolutionaries want prison and the common folk
want the death penalty. Okay. Interesting. You are, please introduce yourself. This is Claude
Pochard. Monsieur les jours, you know me. State your personal information or there will be
consequences. Claude Pochard. Monsieur les jours. You stand accused of spying for the
counter-revolutionaries and criticizing the existing order. Do you admit to these crimes?
I am innocent. The accusation is exaggerated and comes from the ill will of the accusers.
Suggesting that the revolutionary government is acting in ill will. Typical of a priest.
All right. Let's see. Okay. Counter-revolution and treason.
Claude Pochard, a 26-year-old vicar and tutor, son of a cobbler, believes in enlightenment ideals.
After refusing to endure the civil constitution of the clergy, he was removed from his parish,
prohibited from carrying out his duties, and sentenced to banishment. Despite this,
he stayed in Paris and continued his work as a tutor, which he started before 1789.
Pochard was captured in the streets by fortuitous circumstance. A guard officer
present during his trial a few months ago recognized him and didn't hesitate to act.
Following an investigation, Pochard was accused of spying and spreading
counter-revolutionary propaganda in order to prepare for an intervention that would end
the revolution. Correspondence with Archbishop Jean Arsne des Bretus was found in a room
Pochard had been renting from Marie Gimmett. In it, the clergyman asked for information about
the unrest and the supporters of the monarchy in hiding. Riches were also found, a golden
chalice and a reliquary. Moreover, the director of one of the orphanages Claude
Toddin testified that the tutor would question the law of the revolution in front of the students,
stating that it was less important than the laws handed down by God. A letter to Claude
Pochard.
prepare for a foreign intervention that would end the revolution.
They would riches also found. Let's take a look. So ban it, let's see, see, see. Okay.
A letter from the church riches spreading propaganda espionage. Tudor. Tudor. It's
banishment. So you were banished for speaking against, right? So this is this would be
counterrevolution. Fog. It's Tudor. Tutor. Tutor. Church riches. That's evidence.
Spreading propaganda. That's counterrevolution. Espionage. That's an accusation. Four more
questions possible. Parish priest. It's a personality question. Another possibility
for propaganda. I mean, that's an accusation. Letter from the archbishop. That looks like
evidence to me. Banishment is a course of events. We got them all. All right. We don't
know where the jury stands at the moment. So we can just let's just do what do you teach? Why
did the accused stay in France despite being banished? Sekiro unlocks in three hours.
Wow. No, but I can't. I can't. Don't even tell me that. Don't tell me that. I already
got it loaded. Don't tell me that. All right. So why? That's a good question. Why are you still
here? What are you? Why are you still here? I had to take care of my sick mother. Without me,
she would surely have died. Why did you not take her with you? Good. Make the filth squirm.
I was in no position to afford that. I'm just a poor parish priest who is unable to
even carry out his duties. I have to teach every single day to survive. Is that why you
started spying for money? No. What information could I glean that would be useful to
emigres? That of the supposed persecution of priests. The main argument that Archbishop
de Pertoux and Pius VI are using to convince Catholic monarchs to strike against the
revolution. I do not correspond with emigres and I certainly do not write about the
suffering of our clergymen. I would like to remind you that we have evidence.
Away with the liar. Okay. We already got that one. Mother was sick. What do you teach?
The caregivers in orphanages only pay for reading and writing lessons.
So why did the accused teach children that God's laws stands above that of the republic?
You spread superstition and counter-revolutionary propaganda.
This is a misunderstanding. The children I teach are unable to understand such complicated
matters. The accused's explanation further incriminates him. If they are unable to
understand the topic, why would he even discuss it at all? The church spreads
ignorance and takes our money. I was only answering questions from the director of
the orphanages in Gambines. I said that God's laws stood above my banishment.
It is God's law that prohibits me from leaving the country. I have a duty to help
those in need. Okay. We're currently leaning towards acquittal at the moment. I need more
info. All right. So hold on. Who? Okay. This is my family would think this is a good idea
because this is a friend of the family. Common folk want the death penalty currently
leaning. All right. Here we go. What information did the accused manage to convey to Archbishop
de Bluthy?
to the letter? What a coincidence. Archbishop de Bluthy currently resides
in Switzerland. It is indeed a coincidence. Many clergymen reside in Switzerland.
You believe that? I mean, that's come on. The accused travels extensively around the world,
around the Paris department. To what end? Why? I teach wherever I can find students. Doing
that requires time and effort, I admit. Is that why you received gold from your fellow
conspirators abroad? He travels around France to spy on people. The only money I see comes
from my students' caregivers. It's not at all immodest. So where did the riches found in
your room come from? They were litigar- they were lit- they were literally accountants.
Oh, yeah. They were liturgic- they were liturgical accrotrements. I- everyone's gonna
make fun of me now. They were liturgical accrotrements. I saved them from the
plunder of the church and compents. I would rather go hungry than sell them.
They were literally- okay. Fanatic, thief, peddler of superstition. Boy, I know what
donation words I'm using next time. What- what does that mean? All right. Hold on.
All right, some of the witness. Marie Gim. Citizen, what is your name? Marie Gim.
Monsieur Lejeu. Was the witness aware that she was renting a room to an unsworn Catholic priest?
Did the accused maintain extensive correspondence? What if this is a- what if this is also a spy?
I'm gonna say this one. Did the accused maintain extensive correspondence? Meaning?
Did he receive many letters? I don't remember any letters with his name. Perhaps he had a
rich social life. Did he entertain many guests? I don't remember anyone visiting him at all.
He wasn't there most of the time anyway. He just used the room to sleep.
Where would he go? I don't ask my guests about things like that.
Did he pay rent on time? Did he ever criticize the revolution and its accomplishments?
Wow, did he pay his rent on time? I feel like this is much more-
this makes more sense. Did he pay rent on time? Did he pay rent on time? Sometimes I had to
threaten to kick him out, but eventually he would always pay. So the accused did not strike
you as a person who has a substantial amount of money to operate with or spend freely?
No, he lived like a poor man. I mean, a normal fellow would never get rich from teaching.
Okay. What stipend does the accused receive? So he is- maybe he's hiding it though.
What do you get from being a teacher?
I'm realizing this now. Yeah, this is not England. Let me rephrase this.
I don't know how to do a French accent.
I can't do that. I'm going back to English.
Why did the accused continue teaching instead of leaving?
All right. I think people are going to start chanting for his head here. I got to-
Hold on. Where's the evidence?
Oh, I can do this. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
It's not sacrament, merely prayer.
Stupid!
Oh. Why did the accused continue teaching? Why did you do this?
Your knowledge is a Catholic propaganda!
I prefer the term- all right, hold on. They are both of the same-
I'm trailing into like Jamaican. You're right. All right. Hold on.
I prefer the term. I prefer the term Catholic values.
Okay. Jury's opinion is- doesn't- don't need to kill him.
Family wants to be acquitted. Hold on. Let me see anything else I can do here.
Did the defendant confess? No.
Was his act counter-revolutionary?
When and where did the defendant corrupt the people of Paris?
During arguments? No. It would be here.
During the reading and writing lessons in the orphanage, right?
During arguments? No.
Maybe they went during- yeah, in the orphanage.
Was his act counter-revolutionary?
I mean, yeah. Yeah, close.
I'm not going to kill you.
All right, acquittal. Wow. That would be bad.
Prison. Death penalty.
Nah, I can get some points of revolutionary here.
But I need to do- the common folk need to be appeased.
The people want blood, but they're not going to get it because
the revolutionaries will actually come and remove me from office.
The joke fucked you up so bad. Yeah.
Sorry. Prison.
Sorry, family. That could be anybody's name.
I sentence Citizen Claude Pochard to prison.
Lead the condemned out.
He saved that priest!
He showed mercy to an enemy of the revolution.
He ought to have been killed. I have nothing else to say.
All right. Correct, correct, correct.
Three to three. Good job.
My influence went up. My reputation went up.
I played that pretty much by the book.
So for the next case, unfortunately,
I'm going to have to play some politics here and we need-
I need- we need to sway people towards like execution for them.
Cool. This game's fun.
I like this. This is actually really interesting.
Okay, so I still- I'm still at the bottom here.
Take him away.
Is it as fun as Sekiro?
I can't start Sekiro three hours from now.
I'll be almost five hours into the stream.
I can't start Sekiro.
I'm gonna have to- if I start Sekiro in three or four hours,
I will actually burn out for tomorrow and I won't stream tomorrow.
I'll be- I'll be live for like 16 hours or something.
It'll- no, I can't.
Who's that? Who's that?
That was a dad. No, it's not.
One fool spewed out one word to many.
The other fired a musket.
They fought for freedom, each for their own.
The man who was forbidden to shoot.
Commander Buell paid the highest price for our decisions.
The defender who kept watch over ordinary citizens,
but was denied the right to protect himself.
Whether I like it or not, his death is also my fault.
That's because I've rejected the- we made a nice profit.
There was a chance of prosperity.
Why would the Renard family want to take over your shop, grandpapa?
For profit and power.
It's always the same and it's no different in these times.
We get the same like hair energy coming to realize.
Today is about equality so that not only the aristocrats can live with dignity.
Grow up. Grow up, boy.
I only saw the truth when they attempted to sentence my son, your uncle, to death.
It suddenly dawned on me that the only things that mattered were the power I never had,
and the connections I never cared for.
You wanted to be righteous while the injustice spread like a plague?
You should not- you should not be sorry for that.
Sorry, I misspoke there, dad.
Now this is my son.
Who is this- wait, who's the kid?
Who am I?
No, that's the kid.
Where's me?
Which one of these is me?
That's me.
No, that's me.
Why does my kid look older than me?
He's dressed like an old man too.
I am not, but I would rather your brother live so that I still had two sons.
No, this is dad.
He looks different in court.
You have a brother, daddy?
Where is he?
He died a long time ago before you were born.
Why did he die?
Do not talk so much while eating.
Your uncle went to war and died in battle.
Your generation will soon realize the extent of the damage we inflicted upon the world.
In the past, decent people like Puchard never had to worry about courts or tribunals.
But now, do you even consider the possibility that Puchard was guilty?
No, not Mr. Puchard!
He was no guiltier than any of us, son.
Keep an eye on the Reynards.
Jermyn, when you stream games, do you stream with your monitor on or off?
Typically on.
I get it.
Fuck off.
How does that sound?
Fuck off, mate.
Very rare occasion.
Why did you read that?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
That was really funny.
I'll give you that one.
All right.
So let's read together.
It's been a rough couple of days.
We're going to read together.
Some people think it's dull.
No, no, no, no, no.
Political debate.
I'm going to bring the sons doing political debate.
Although, influence on reputation, influence on the people.
I need dad to be happy.
What?
No!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, come on.
What?
They're going to kill me.
I thought dad wanted to debate politics.
What?
Oh, my God.
All right.
We've got to kill.
We're going to have to just drop the guillotine on somebody, I think.
Oh, this sucks.
What's my reputation right now?
Oh, yeah, yeah, this is bad.
Revolutionaries want to quittle.
Common people want death penalty.
I have to pee.
Give me a minute.
I'm going to pee.
I also want to get some water.
By the way, if you weren't, if you're not aware, I have a cough,
which if you've been here for even remotely five, 10 minutes, you'd know.
So I'm trying to keep my vitamin C levels up, stay hydrated.
I'll be right back.
Oh, man.
I drank a glass of water.
I've just been in a coughing fit this whole time.
Oh, I was laughing my ass off.
So remember when we played The Sims modded?
And I was when the guy was peeing and he was mid piss and he sneezed
and like his pee stream kept going.
And somebody said, that's fucking impossible.
I was like, I don't know why I keep thinking of that.
I keep seeing that image and seeing that person in chat write that.
And it makes me laugh every time.
Because I started coughing while I was peeing and you know what happens?
The fact that that sim was just mid piss,
sneezing, coughing, and the stream was just perfect the whole time.
All right.
Let's get back to this.
Sorry.
Hold on.
Okay.
Sekiro's out now.
Comes out in like a couple hours, doesn't it?
Anyway, here we go.
This is murder.
Murder.
A tragedy occurred in one of the ten minutes by the...
Oh my goodness.
Fuck.
I picked a great day to do a talking stream, right?
Like not at every stream is a talking stream, but a reading stream.
Set your VPN to Japan.
You can play it now.
Yeah, but I mean, I can't stream through a VPN.
I can't stream through a VPN.
What are you talking about?
Why would I do that?
That's fucking illegal.
All right.
It's not illegal.
Yeah, but I'm talking about like pretending that I'm from Japan to stream the game early.
That's like gotta be illegal.
You guys would put me in the guillotine.
Yeah, no, you can't.
I'm not sure that my internet is powerful enough to be able to stream through a VPN.
I really don't think so.
No, we're doing that tomorrow.
Look, I got to get more vitamin C and drink more water and like go to bed early
because tomorrow I'm going for like 10 straight hours.
You heard it here first.
Put the bulletin on the board.
No, yeah, we're just hanging up like this.
I'm good here for a little while longer.
This is interesting.
We got a whole...
Look, because I've been gone for like four days, right?
I mean, I'm going to play the absolute hell out of Sekiro.
That's like the...
I'm not going to stop playing that.
You know what I mean?
I'm going to like be eating pizza on stream again.
But anyways, let's go.
Ahem.
A tragedy occurred in one of the tenements by the scene near the point new.
The fourth floor collapsed.
Okay.
The tenants, horrified by the crash and ubiquitous dust, ran outside.
Only after a few minutes did some of the braver men
run upstairs to look for survivors and remove the corpses.
Jesus.
Rubble and timber buried two families, 12 people.
Three children managed to survive by hiding beneath a wooden table.
Neighbors dug them out and carried them to the hotel due.
We cannot comprehend what the orphans are going through,
and they have not eaten or spoken for two days.
Okay.
The owner of the house testified that he had ordered the construction of an extra floor
a few years back.
Works were supervised by architect Maurice Lorty.
The National Guard found the architect,
who was also the construction foreman, at an address given by the owner.
Maurice Lorty was not surprised when the gendarmes knocked at his door,
and he did not resist when they handcuffed him and took him to jail.
So this is like criminal negligence, right?
Construction of an extra floor.
All right, let's see, there's four questions.
All right, so we got additional floor.
So we've got the corpses, that's the victim.
Collapse floor is the circumstances.
Oh no.
Isn't that the, that's like the additional floor
caused potentially the circumstances of the collapse floor.
All right, crowded flat.
That's the circumstance.
Okay, yeah, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it.
Get a dictionary, I'm fine.
Okay, so common folk want death penalty.
I have to sway towards the death penalty.
The people, the people are angry and scared
and expect someone to be punished for this tragedy.
Your name?
Maurice Lorty, Mr. Judge.
Do you build houses?
That's right.
I've earned my living from construction and renovation for many years now.
Did the floor collapse because of your mistake?
I don't know.
I have worked at many houses since then.
There's children are dead because of you.
Let me just say that I always build the best,
I always build the best work I can.
Uh, citizen, a few years ago you were assigned
to perform some construction work.
It was nine years ago.
I was supposed to remove the roof, add one floor,
then build a new roof.
Is that a hard task?
It is known that it is easier to build a new
than to improve something already there.
Did the owner have any objections regarding your work?
If he did, I would have made as many corrections as necessary.
Which floor was built by you?
The attic, the fourth.
Before that, the third floor was the attic.
Oh, I'm ready.
They're sharpening the blade.
Citizen, with your knowledge of construction,
what could have led to this tragedy?
I can't be sure.
Pests, poor materials, too much load on the structure.
Every house is different.
This should have been checked
before the room fell on people's heads.
You did not mention a construction error.
Yes, unfortunately, that could also happen.
I could have made a mistake
and my calculations are wrongly assessed
the quality of the timber.
You are not denying it.
If you judge that I have contributed
to the death of those children,
I will accept whatever punishment you choose.
Two weeks ago, a disease took my wife
and I no longer care what happens to me.
Oh, fuck.
Did you talk to the tenants,
the ones that pulled the victims from the rubble?
They came to me in the night angry and hurt.
I understand their pain is too...
I too have children.
Answer my question.
Did you talk to them?
No, I was forced to hide inside my house
and close the window shutters
because they were throwing stones.
So the building collapsed because of your mistake
and you did not even have the courage
to talk to the victims?
I'm a coward, I know.
How did they know where to go?
I don't know.
Only the owner of the tenement knew my address.
Oh, fuck, we're about to prove...
We're about to call in the witness and like prove...
All right, but the thing is,
how long in prison?
Can I say like just like a little while?
If this drops, I die.
Prison's the most...
Okay, I'm going to do prison just because it's...
I'm corrupt as hell,
but you have to understand something.
They're going to come after me.
Did the defendant confess to the crimes?
Yeah, kind of.
Does he act counter-revolutionary?
No.
Call the witness?
Yeah, but if the witness...
If the witness comes in and says a bunch of shit,
then the people might not be so inclined.
Are you the owner of the house where the floor collapsed?
Yes.
The floor and the attic collapsed
and fell on the rooms beneath.
Did the tenants complain about anything prior to the tragedy?
The apartments were small, correct?
They said something about squeaky floors,
but that's not unusual as they squeak at my place too.
So what?
Did you inspect the floors?
I planned to,
but this tragedy happened before I was able to.
Thank God he managed to take their money.
So no, so he didn't.
According to the witness,
did the tenants complain about anything, squeaky floors?
All right, prison, death penalty.
Prison is probably the best choice
because he might not have...
Kill him for the love of God,
but my conscience is at stake here.
Squeaky kill is the best,
but kill him because he mad at squeaky floors?
Really?
He just said something fucking horrible.
Architect Lordy shall be sent to the guillotine
for the terrible tragic death of two families.
Long live justice!
Incorrect.
And I did a good job.
Okay, here we go.
I got some common folk reputation.
Let's try to make...
Let's do the speech.
Take a breather.
No, I have a cough.
It's been annoying the last two days.
Maybe I could win the heart of the crowd.
They're irritated.
Skip...
Speak to the common folk.
Okay, so the crime...
Carelessness.
I would say carelessness, right?
So they're bullheaded right now.
Aggression.
The defendant...
Let's reveal this.
This is attached.
Let's manipulate.
Manipulate and then bullheaded.
We can do either aggression or humility.
Aggression, right?
And the crime would be carelessness.
So that's...
I think that's good.
Carelessness is the approach.
Well, isn't that the crime?
Let's just see.
Attached.
Well, manipulation again.
Manipulation, manipulation, and then aggression.
That makes sense.
There we go.
Yeah, I was right.
That one would...
This one was strong.
This one would have been okay.
So now we're going to do...
So it's manipulation, manipulation, aggression.
Let's go.
Manipulation.
Future generations will remember that we were not cowards.
They will remember us delivering punishment for such heinous crimes.
All right?
Defendant, manipulate.
Will you just stand there and allow criminals to tell you what to do?
And then aggression.
You have gained power in France.
Now spill the blood of those who oppose the Republic.
Oh, come on.
What?
That was perfect.
That was strong, perfect, perfect.
Is this justice?
Will someone punish the owner of the house?
Do I have to do it?
Can somebody else do it?
What's that famous line?
The one that carries out a sentence.
Should carry out a sword, right?
He's ours.
Uh-oh.
Uh.
There can be no more demeaning experience for revolutionary Paris
than the escape of Citizen Capet.
He escaped, slipped right from their hands,
and the revolution now seems feeble and weak.
The people resemble a child that could easily be duped by anyone.
However, the Republic quickly composed itself
thanks to a postmaster and his people
who were able to catch the fugitives escaping to Montmidi.
Ordinary citizens led to the fall of a monarch.
You will have a chance to serve the Republic as well,
for Citizen Capet will face the tribunal tomorrow.
You will choose how he will be remembered
as a traitor and a coward or as an unlucky statesman.
If it were for the prison guards to decide,
there would be only one outcome.
Allow the guards to rough up Citizen Capet
or leave him alone until the trial.
Does this get me points with people?
I'll get points with the people.
I need those right now.
Or the fair trial.
Let's have trial.
Get him out of here.
Work on tomorrow's trial.
Opening that at the theater.
Let's go to the theater.
Fuck, am I getting worse?
I might be.
This is bad.
I didn't feel this coffee earlier before it started.
Work on tomorrow's trial.
I think I've...
No, I have to get this up.
Evening with granddad.
Sit down with your father and listen to stories of days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely.
Where we can lose some of that.
You can lose some of the sun, that's fine.
Listen to grandpa ramble.
There he is.
The king.
The people want death penalty.
The revolutionaries want death penalty.
The family wants prison and nobody wants acquittal.
Okay.
My lord, should any reason appear,
shoot the rebels without hesitation.
Just as his majesty ordered,
have no mercy for they shall have none either.
VF Bugleberry.
Counterrevolution, treason, fraud,
advocating monarchy and neglect of duty.
What's in here?
Victory.
Okay, minus four reputation.
Plus one revolutionary endorsement.
My reputation is so bad.
Any more notifications?
All right.
Louis Capet, I hereby open your trial.
Answer the questions when you are asked.
Capet is the name of one of my ancestors.
My name is Louis August de Bourbeau.
That may have been your name before you raised your hand
against the people you had sworn to defend.
As a king, I have never done a thing against my people.
I love them and I still do.
Objection!
Ah, that hurt my throat.
I'm just gonna say the word.
Objection!
There's evidence of Louis Capet's treason
against the people of France.
He should be tried as a foreigner and an enemy,
not a citizen of the Republic.
This is the audience.
Questioning the defendant will stir the impatient audience.
Once angered, the people may even start a riot.
I can't do voices.
Drink some tea, I got something right here already.
See?
It's a brick.
I'm just like licking it with salt.
Let's read.
Compatriot Citizen Capet, previously known as King Louis,
the ex-V.I. of France,
must be punished for conspiring against the people of France.
Louis Capet tried to defend his absolute authority
by plotting against the National Constituent Assembly
and the people of France.
We all remember July of 1789,
he gathered an army, fifteen foreign regiments,
and ordered them to surround Paris.
Soldiers led by Baron de Bessignolles
were to capture deputies and shoot at citizens
defending the reforms.
And so they did.
The Royal German Regiment drew first blood.
After the plot failed, Louis tried to flee the country
with his family and scheme with foreign monarchs abroad.
Is that not the reason he took flight from the Tuileries
one night in June of 1791 using someone else's passport?
Was he not heading to Montmedie
where his loyal armies were stationed
ready to take him to Austria?
If it were not for Postmaster Dore,
the scheme could have ended tragically for us.
Louis Capet will never abandon the thought
of suppressing the revolution by force.
Before the events of 1792, he gave orders
for the Swiss Guard stationed in the Tuileries to be doubled.
He conducted a public muster in front of horrified citizens.
The people had no choice.
They had to act before Capet attacked
citizens of Paris who tried to stop the madness
was shot at, even after Capet's escape
to the National Assembly.
And evidence in order issued by Marshal de Broglie
to Baron de Bessignolles.
Oh, god damn it.
I'm starting to turn into dust.
All right.
So, hey, we got anything else?
Equitable.
If I equate them, I'm dead.
If I press this button, then that's it for me.
I'm going to, they're going to throw
like a fucking spear at me.
So let's, let's start the questions by,
and by that, I mean, let's take a look what we've got.
Oh, there's a lot.
Ten questions to reveal.
Surrounding, oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Suppress the revolution is an accusation.
Doubling the size of the guard method
shooting civilians accusation.
Okay.
Defending his authority.
Gathering armed forces.
The attempt to flee the country is,
that's a, that's a motive.
Fake passport is evidence.
No evidence there?
Shit.
I was just going to kill him.
Fake passport.
Okay.
International plot is motive.
How is that?
How is the proportional plot not the motive?
Isn't that like the plot?
Suppressing the revolution is the motive.
International plot, you're accused.
Is the method.
No, that's what it is.
Okay.
Witness.
Postmaster DeRay was a witness.
Gathering the armed forces.
That's a method.
Surrounding the city of Paris.
That is an accusation.
Suppressing the revolution.
Doubling the size of the guard is also a,
they're a method or an accusation.
That's also a method.
What's the third question?
There could be two here?
This isn't a game.
This is homework.
All right.
So this is making me feel tense.
This is making, I'm going to sneeze.
I'm trying to figure out how to do that
without being annoying on stream.
Somebody just gave 100 bucks too.
Cora Monster gave $100, 10,000 bits.
Thank you so much.
100 large bits.
Hey, Jerma, I got accepted to the
studio arts program at a college I applied to.
Well, that's awesome.
First of all, congratulations to that.
Your own brand of creativity
has been really inspiring for me.
And your Discord channel has given me
a great outlet to share the stuff I draw.
Your streams have been very helpful
in de-stressing during the time
I was getting ready to apply.
And I'm very thankful for your streams.
I say, Jerma, one guy.
That's fucking incredible.
I'm so happy that you got accepted.
It's a great feeling.
Do good work.
Stay focused.
Have a good time.
Glad you can hang out here and de-stress.
And thank you for the $100.
That is an absolute shitload of money.
All right.
So on top of we're going forward here, art.
Yeah, art.
No, that's there are a lot of
talented fucking artists that are here.
I've said it before.
Streamers stealing money from poor art students.
Buy some pencils and some paintbrushes,
some crayons and some pastels
and some textbooks.
Suppressing the revolution is a method,
is a motive, it's an accusation.
Doubling the size of the guard is a method.
Suppressing the revolution is a motive.
It's an accusation.
I'm getting fucking worse.
Shit.
Am I really going to have to like
cut this stream short?
God damn it.
Does the itchy, you have to cough now
is happening more often.
All right, we're good.
I missed one.
That's a motive.
I told you it was a motive.
Everybody said that I was wrong.
All right.
Who issued the...
Let's go right off the bat.
Top questions.
You're on my show.
Who issued the order to fire at the citizens?
Either Marshal de Broglie or Baron de Bissenbaum.
The one responsible should be the one standing here
as he was not authorized to issue such orders.
Really?
Not according to this document
it was signed by the Marshal.
Marshal de Broglie went too far and lied to us all.
I swear on my crown I did not issue that order.
De Broglie is a sworn monarchist
and was given an army to suppress the revolution.
Would he work on his own without Capet's blessing?
People sometimes do stupid things.
Has the accused ever considered Paris
and its citizens to be his enemies?
Absolutely not.
I asked that you explain the question.
How can you deny it if you do not understand the question?
Your army surrounded Paris.
Is that not what you do to your enemies?
My soldiers were there only to ensure public order
while the National Assembly was in session.
Adequate forces were already present in Paris.
Was that not enough?
Who helped you suppress the revolution?
Frederick William II?
Francis II?
Catherine II?
Or maybe it was somebody that wasn't a two in their name.
Maybe it was the guy with the three or the four.
Charlie IV, huh?
Was it four?
Justice awaits them as well.
Nonsense all of it.
I only desire to take my family out of Paris
as I did not wish for them to suffer house arrest.
We all know the European monarchs
despise our ideals of freedom, equality, and brotherhood.
Am I to understand that you try to prepare
a joint military intervention?
I deny any such accusation.
There is no evidence for such outrageous claims.
I would never turn against my beloved France.
Liar!
Oh, that hurt.
I can only go so loud before it hurts.
He'd sell his own mother, never mind his country.
Wait, people want me to quit them?
How does that make any sense?
That's, no.
The people are getting aggressive.
How do I calm them down?
People are aggressive.
What do I, is it, what am I, like, book?
Do I have any way to calm them down?
Let's relax.
Let's go to an easy,
let's go to like a softball question here.
Was he accused planning to reclaim his authority in Paris
and reestablish an absolute monarchy?
Well, that's actually very inflammatory.
That's, that's very inflammatory.
Why would I do that?
According to the constitution,
I always, yeah, this is very, very, very bad.
Pick red, no.
They're gonna fucking freak out.
I am still the king.
Then why did you raise a number of troops in the Tuileries?
I feared for my family's life.
It is not a mystery that the citizens of Paris
were incited to seize the palace and capture us,
especially as it was Mr. Danton's goal.
Ah, it is clear then that the guard
were organized against the citizens of Paris,
many of whom did fall in the Tuileries.
Against violence and disorder?
Mr. Tinville, not against my people.
Who is responsible for the delivery
of the passport of the man called Pinet?
My butler.
I ordered him to prepare all the formalities
regarding travel to Montmedy.
The city hall has not received
any submissions from your butler.
I do not know what to say.
Mr. Judge, Louis Carpets' butler
was seen at the Austrian embassy.
They sure took care of all the documents
for the defectors.
What's your Tinville that there's mere hearsay?
Who said such a thing?
Bring him here so that I may repeat it.
There's no need.
That is hard evidence,
especially in light of what the accused has told us.
What did the accused plan to do
with the constituents' deputies?
Well, we're getting close to a riot.
Nothing.
The assembly that I joined on the 27th June 1789
granted immunity to its members,
and I intended to respect that.
And yet you ordered your soldiers
to seize and imprison the deputies,
and perhaps even execute them.
Nonsense.
There's no evidence of that.
My enemies spread rumors to get rid of me.
We don't need evidence
against a coward who runs from his own people.
That person was waiting to say that
for like fucking 40 straight minutes.
They were practicing over and over again.
They were practicing it in the head,
and they finally had an opportunity
to drop out and say it.
All right, we're getting the imprisonment.
Call on the witness Jean Dor.
Okay, introduce yourself.
Jean Dor, postmaster of Saint-Main-Haut,
Monsieur Les Jouges.
Bad judge.
What?
What did I do?
Did the accused Louis Capet
introduce himself to the witness
with his full name?
No, he didn't introduce himself at all.
They only produced someone else's documents.
So he tried to hide his identity.
You could say so.
I used the name from the documents
after he showed them to me.
He never objected.
Then how did you learn his true identity?
By the image of the paper assignation.
Then a messenger from General Lafayette
confirmed my suspicions.
I ran as fast as I could to Varennes
to inform the authorities.
The accused tell anyone
the destination of his journey.
Acting like a defector,
was he nervous or in a hurry?
I say, I say, foghorn, leghorn.
That was pretty good.
There's a lot of French names
and it's hard to pronounce French names.
I don't speak French.
I didn't even take French 101 in high school.
I'm gonna say, I'm gonna say the top one.
Does anybody hear the end stream song?
Did he tell you the destination?
He asked for the way to Montmidi.
I told him to go through Varennes and Argonne
and warned the coachman to be careful.
The road is difficult out there.
Would the accused like to comment
on this testimony?
It confirms that I had no intention of escaping.
I was merely traveling
and is the right of any free citizen.
Bad judge.
People's patience has its limits.
The trial went on for too long
and the audience was extremely agitated.
Okay, fine.
Put an ax in his head.
What happened in real life?
Because we could just cheat, right?
By using actual history.
King Louis the...
What happened to him?
He got the guillotine.
Okay, imagine if I just changed the history
and put him...
He's still alive.
Oh god, that's so stupid.
All right, unable to know.
All right, just death penalty.
Get my reputation back up.
Sign it.
Everybody's on board.
The crowd in front of the building is enraged.
There may be soon a massacre.
Oh god, a rumor has spread
about hidden evidence of Citizen Capay's treason.
People have gone mad.
What evidence?
I will go to them.
I would ask you all to stay in your seats until I return.
Uh oh, this is bad.
Why do I have to do this?
People, what vexes you?
Why are you so angry?
Is he the one talking?
The king lied to us.
That coward ran from us.
He'll surely run from justice as well.
No, we're gonna kill him.
I already did it.
We found proof of the king's treachery
in his secret iron cabinet.
Oh shit, okay.
Citizen Capay shall not escape justice.
Aggression, humility.
How many points do I have?
Believe in me.
I'm just winging it.
Yeah, that, like, he's not going to escape justice.
The evidence from the iron cabinet will be examined,
manipulate, and then believe in me.
Humility.
They're all withdrawn.
Manipulate.
Full aggro.
All full aggro.
No, no, this is aggressive.
And then probably humility,
because people are already,
humility and then manipulation.
People are withdrawn.
I can, like, do the dance, right?
Or humility.
I would even do humility.
Maybe both of them.
I still have the points.
Yeah, the withdraw, withdrawn, withdrawn.
Manipulate, manipulate.
Aggression, manipulate, manipulate.
Or aggression, humility, humility.
I'm doing it.
Fuck it.
Let's go.
Yes!
Yeah, I'm so fucking pumped up right now.
I'm so fucking pumped.
The king has been imprisoned.
He will not escape a second time.
If he tries, I will kill him with my own bare hands.
Ah, doubtful.
You're not that strong.
Each new piece of evidence will be thoroughly examined.
The republic's standards demand nothing less.
I shall follow them to the letter.
Okay, I guess.
Intrigued.
I know that you might be angry.
But you have chosen your representatives to protect you.
Believe in me.
Yeah, they bought it.
Plus two reputation, plus two influence,
and then plus five common folk endorsement were back.
So what happened out there?
It is true.
Evidence of Capete's guilt has been found.
Really?
Would the defendant like to explain why he concealed his secure iron cabinet
and the documents hidden within from the convention?
I hid nothing from the convention.
No one asked me about the existence of such things.
You kept your correspondence well hidden under lock and key.
It could only be retrieved only the assistance of a master locksmith.
Any affluent Parisian has a lockable cabinet.
I for one am keenly interested in locksmithing.
Let's go.
Wait, is there more?
Oh shit, there's more?
No, no, no, no.
What is all this other stuff?
It's like a fucking bunch of papers.
Get these both out of here.
What is this?
Shoot the rebels.
No, no, that's this one.
What is this?
The deputies of the so-called national assembly are to be carefully questioned,
and if any of them should display common sense and cease to support the assembly,
reward him with an extraordinarily high allowance and forward his majesty's thanks.
We trust that with God's grace and help,
his majesty will soon arrive within the imperial borders for us to grant H.M.
as well as our beloved sister's safety and to potentially take the steps necessary
to reestablish the natural European order within the borders of France.
His imperial majesty, the Holy Roman Emperor, King Hungary,
Bohemia, Croatia, Dalmatia, Slovenia, Galicia,
Latin America, etc.
Whoa, your country doesn't get to be added, you're in the etc.
I'd be pissed about that.
You start wars over that shit.
A.D. 1791, 15th of May.
And your grace, soon we will come to your majesty's rescue.
However, for the time being, I implore you, Y.M.,
to muster local troops that remain loyal.
I shall issue a warning to Y.M.'s subjects that any and all who dare raise a hand
against Y.M. would suffer the du-rest of consequences.
My armies await my orders to curb the tide of anarchy in Y.M.'s country.
Duke of Brunswick, Lundberg, Charles William Ferdinand, A.D. 1792, 9th of June.
That wasn't even a cough.
It's a pretend cough.
All right, get them out there, get them to the gallows, let's go.
How is the jury not reached what they think?
Wait, what?
Must be pun- try- all right, there's more.
There are new questions.
Louis Quipet tried to defend his absolute authority by plotting against
the National Consistuate Assembly and the people of France.
We all remember July of 1789.
He gathered an army, 15 foreign regiments, and ordered them to surround Paris.
Soldiers led by Baron de Bessenval were to capture deputies and shoot at citizens
defending the reforms, and so they did.
The royal German regiment drew first blood.
After the plot failed- I just read this.
No, I didn't.
It was more after that.
Whatever, we'll do it.
Louis Quipet tried to flee the country with his family and scheme with foreign
monarchs abroad.
Is that not the reason for him leaving that one night in June of 1791?
Who knows.
Louis Quipet will never abandon the thoughts of suppressing the revolution by force
before the events of 1792.
He gave orders for the Swiss Guard stationed in the Toulouse to be doubled.
He conducted a public buster in front of horrified citizens.
The people had no choice.
They had to act before Quipet attacked.
Citizens of Paris who tried to stop the madness were shot at even after
Quipet's escape to the National Assembly.
An order issued by the marshal, instructions issued by the minister,
a letter from the emperor, and a letter from the duke.
Let's bring it down.
So a letter from the duke.
I would call that evidence.
We've got a letter from the emperor.
What'd you call that?
I'd call that evidence.
You got the minister's order.
I would call that, hold on, attempted escape.
I would call that a fucking counter-revolutionary term
or course of events.
Suppressing the revolution.
That's your method.
That's your method to do that.
That's the method.
It's not.
That's the course of actions.
Uh-oh.
And that's your method.
Bingo!
More questions.
All right.
Were you aware of the plans of the emperor and the duke of Brunswick?
Why did you not...
Why did you not warn the National Assembly and the army?
You need to speak up.
I did not deem their threat serious.
Treason.
Allow me to quote you.
My armies await my orders.
Does that not sound like a serious threat?
Prince Charles is impetuous,
but I never once thought he would dare attack France.
All right, everyone wants him dead.
Did the accused intend to lead the emperor's forces to France?
I certainly did not.
In his letter, the emperor was quite clear about his intentions to return order to France.
I do not know plans of Emperor Leopold,
but I do know that I would never allow anyone to spill French blood.
But you must admit that such an offer from an enemy government paints you in a bad light.
Dear God, is it merely personal correspondence from my brother-in-law?
It's not personal when the letters exchanged are by rulers and deal in matters of national security.
All right.
Let's calm it down a little.
Oh, shit.
They're going to riot.
He's going to die.
Did the defendant confess to the crime?
No.
Who was corrupting politicians on Citizen Cafe's request?
Did Citizen Cafe explain his reasoning behind Roland's mission of corruption?
He denies the situation took place, and I don't know who did this.
I think it was, was it Roland?
He literally just said it.
Say a letter.
Look at that boost.
I, Sigward of Katarina, sentence Citizen Cafe to death by guillotine.
Take the convict away.
Long live the people.
Down with the tyrant.
Oh, damn.
Good job.
Got some extra influence points.
He's ours.
Okay, let's go watch.
No one's upset with me.
Yeah, but everybody wanted it.
Understand?
Their excitement was stronger than the smell of the fresh wood the guillotine was made from.
Know what's about to happen?
Turbo vs. Star.
Sheep that only now realize they used to have fangs and claws.
Oh.
The guy in the bottom right is every created character that allows me that haircut
has that haircut for every game I play with the creative character.
I was unable to understand their screams.
I only tasted the stench of their sweaty bodies.
But I could hear one thing perfectly.
Bring us the king.
Time for a speech.
This one's important.
All right, so we have oversensitive, crime, revolution.
I have points.
So they've withdrawn.
They're oversensitive about the king,
which means we could do humility here.
Revolution.
Manipulation.
Full aggro.
I'm not going to do full aggro.
Humility is better for withdrawn, I think.
Why would you use carelessness?
And then oversensitive.
That's, yeah, I mean, that's either manipulation.
Aye, yai, yai.
All right, well, defendant is manipulation is perfect.
So withdrawn, is it all?
Nobody wants to be shouted at when they're withdrawn.
Maybe carelessness.
Maybe aggressive for the crime, but not aggressive for revolution.
Maybe, I don't know.
I would say manipulation for revolution.
Crime aggressive might work here.
Aggressive manipulation and then, I don't know.
Let's try aggressive here.
Disorder shall be suppressed with the brutal strength of our truth.
No turning back now.
All right, that was good.
And then manipulation for the defendant.
These offenders want to go back to the old ways they defend them.
Intrigued.
And then revolution.
Let's go with manipulation again.
Aggression.
These criminals think that because we are tolerant, we are so weak that is not enough.
Speaking of not enough, who comes?
I die as an innocent man.
I forgive my enemies.
For the revolution.
All the road.
Do they ever clean this thing?
Somebody probably does.
Maybe like once a week.
I must be dreaming.
Is that the map from the Muggler's case?
You stole evidence from the court?
I did not steal it.
Only found a use for it.
It will be more useful in your room than in the dusty drawers of the court archives.
After all, this is a map by Turgo and should be traded with respect.
What a lovely explanation.
Consider it a gift.
Take it.
And try not to talk so much.
You should be more concerned about the events with the king.
Because this whole situation just seems pretty.
As your superior, I should be the one judging your ways and case.
I failed to understand why Rumpus Spear asked for your assistance.
Wait, are you jealous?
Of course I'm jealous.
It is an important moment in history and people will be reading about it.
People hate this.
It seems there will be trouble.
I have a feeling that someone is toying with my life
as though an unknown force were pushing me into utter chaos.
Keep your eyes open.
You came to the political world of this city from out of nowhere.
And that means someone will have to step down to make room.
Do you have to sound so defeated?
My husband is a renowned person now.
We should be happy about it.
It is easier to shoot someone in the spotlight.
Evening stroll.
Whoa, we just unlocked one.
Demonstration.
Let them see real life up close.
No, no, no, no.
We gotta chill out here.
Evening stroll.
No, hates that.
Political debate.
He hates that too.
Paragraphs and codes.
Take a walk with dad.
Let's go to demonstration.
Let's go see it.
Let's go.
Full bar.
Alt is ready.
The people have shrugged the invisible burden off their backs.
The streets seem more peaceful.
Even the windows at the courthouse were soon replaced.
That's the whole day?
Oh, okay.
Oh, look at all these points.
Dear Citizen Fidel, I am writing to congratulate you
on becoming a part of our country's history.
Citizen Cafe's trial is on everyone's lips.
I would also like to discuss the important topic
of appointing the new commander-in-chief
of the National Guard who will replace Citizen Burel.
It is my honest belief that I am the best candidate.
So would you give me your permission?
I would like to pay you a visit this evening.
Long live the Republic.
Francois Henriot.
All right.
So we have burglary, assault, theft, destruction of property.
And we have people, revolutionaries want prison.
Common folk want acquittal.
All right.
Let's take a look at the case.
One of the two.
But first of all, Juno.
Juno Obsetto.
Juno Obsetto, thanks for the five community subs.
Five subs.
Just rifling in right now.
Thank you.
Really appreciate that.
That was Juno Obsetto.
So we have, before the court stands, Claude Garnier,
a resident of Paris and a baker's apprentice, arrested for robbery.
He led a group of people who broke into the house
of citizen Dominique Fournier, a wealthy man.
According to Fournier's testimony, the robbers insulted him
and then began beating him.
All right.
At the same time, Claude told his accomplices,
which expensive belonging should be taken,
and the group left the battered Fournier lying on the floor.
Many witnesses saw the whole incident.
Fournier's servants saw present during the events,
while some passers-by looked through the windows.
Garnier not only admitted to leading the group,
but he actually boasted about it,
calling it a revolutionary deed of which he was proud.
He supposedly found out that Fournier is funding
counterrevolutionary leaflets
and decided to relieve him of his funds.
The accused would not reveal the source of the information.
He handed the guards a lampoon of Robespierre,
claiming that he had found a thick pile of them
in the victim's house.
Garnier claimed to having burned all but one,
which he kept as evidence.
When the guards arrested him,
they noticed a gold signet ring on his finger
that belonged to Fournier.
Okay.
Garnier often takes a stand during the gatherings of the Engrage,
demanding that all wealthy people be hanged.
In the year 1789, he took part in the storming of the Bastille.
So let's go.
So we have the...
There's a trap here, though.
Assaulting the victim is...
Who is the witness here?
We have...
There's one of the servants.
One of the servants was a witness.
So that's one.
Freeing the Bastille prisoners.
That's a...
The gold signet is evidence.
I'm afraid of a trap here.
Break-in is the accusation, right?
I mean, I want to see what's going on.
He led a group of people
broke into the house of Dominique Fournier,
a wealthy man.
God.
According to Fournier's testimony...
All right.
So break-in is the accusation.
Assaulting the victim is an accusation.
I feel like the funding thing is a trap.
Funding leaflets...
No.
Shit.
We need more people like Gagn.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Claude Gagn.
You are accused of breaking into the house of Citizen Fournier,
whom you then brutally assaulted and robbed.
I led an investigation of his house.
Viva la rvolution.
Good.
Is that what you're gonna yell?
That's the reaction somebody has
when they've been paying attention to their iPhone.
And are asked for a comment.
Good.
Yeah.
Who gave you the right to represent the revolution?
The people of Paris.
Sure we did.
Is that sarcastic or...
It's motive.
Fine.
No.
One of these is a trap.
Fine answer.
There's the trap.
That's okay.
All right.
So he was beaten.
Why was he severely beaten?
He could have avoided it, yes.
I punched him once or twice.
Only because he kept squealing like a pig.
Are you proud of yourself?
He got what he deserved.
Royalists are animals.
He kept squealing when you were turning his place over.
He was plotting against decent Parisians.
Isn't that enough?
We'll kill that dog.
Okay.
Would you like...
Would you...
Why would you think that the victim had anything to do with...
You were found with a gold signet.
Yeah.
I have reason to believe that it belonged to the victim.
Am I right?
Why do you keep calling him a victim?
He's a rich traitor.
The true victims of the people of France.
You know what we're talking about.
And we will take care of him in due course.
Now what about that signet?
Oh, yeah.
The signet.
Nice, isn't it?
Those swines got fat off our hard work.
And they refused to give us a tiny part of their wealth.
Not even the tiniest.
Huzzah!
What did you plan to do with it?
Nothing.
Looked nice on my finger.
Much better than on that pig.
The signet was not only the thing you took.
It wasn't the only thing.
Was it?
I heard the house was stripped of everything precious.
I was especially fond of those gold-plated candlesticks.
All right.
Well.
Why would you think that the victim had anything to do
with the counter-revolutionary activity?
Ask anyone on the street.
They all knew about it.
Only no one had any proof and we were tired of waiting.
How did they know?
Did the rats talk to them?
Well, I just knew.
People always know what's going on.
We always smell a filthy royalist.
So you decided to find evidence of Fournier's guilt.
Whenever someone's suspected of a crime, there's an investigation.
No.
We decided to do one.
Do I understand correctly?
Let me just make sure I understand.
Do I get this?
You assaulted Citizen Fournier because of some rumors.
Am I getting that?
Do I get that correctly?
Mr. Judge, are you implying that Parisians are liars?
I'm the one who asked the questions here.
Not you.
The judge is on the side of the bourgeoisie.
Uh-oh.
That was a family guy to your joke.
Oh, give me a break.
Whatever.
Let's get the witness in here.
The victim's servant, Gaten Cave.
Why did you not try to interrupt or defend the victim?
Why didn't you do that?
Me?
Yes.
I only said why.
What chance would I have against a group of thugs?
Did they attack you as well?
Fortunately, they didn't.
It is clear that their aim was the bourgeoisie and not the common people.
Did you call for help?
I yelled, but nobody came.
I yelled.
Why didn't you call the police with the phones that don't exist?
They screamed out the window like they used to do.
All right.
After you were arrested, you handed the guards a slanderous leaflet about citizen Robb's Pier.
I found it in the royalist's pig's house.
There were scores of them there, and we burned them all in the street.
Wonderful.
You did not burn that one.
I saved it just in case, you know, I needed it for something.
How can we be sure it belonged to Faunier?
Where else would I have found it?
Tell us exactly where you found it.
He had piles of these leaflets in a recess there.
Plotter!
Scum!
Why did you not go to the guard with the leaflet at once?
Why would I?
With evidence like that, you could be sure the accused would meet the guillotine.
He's right.
You should have brought the leaflet to the guard.
They're on my side now.
Did you really take part in the storming of the Bastille?
I did.
What a hero, one of us.
There's just chat back there.
It really is.
Was your experience helpful?
The only thing missing was Delaunay's head raised on a pike.
That's another difference.
I wasn't arrested for doing it.
Everyone knew what they were doing, the right thing.
The Bastille was a fortress.
We are talking about breaking into the house of an unarmed man
and that is why we have doubts.
You mean an unarmed, royalist pig?
All right.
Common folk want acquittal.
Revolutionaries want prison.
Why meet you?
Did they confess to the crimes?
Yeah.
Common revolutionary in nature?
No.
What made the defendant famous in the eyes of the people?
He took part in the storming of the Bastille.
Kill him is a joke.
I'm not going to kill him.
I'm going to put him in prison.
Nobody wants that.
Prison.
Acquittal.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Reputation bonus.
No, let's keep it normal here.
Prison.
Sentence to prison.
That'll be balanced.
I quit.
No.
I want to keep this balanced.
I'm a judge.
I don't acquit somebody
because somebody in Twitch chat yelled at me
to like turn around and pick up the item.
Actually, I do that all the time.
We've changed entire game sessions
based on what like three people have said in chat before.
So I sentence Citizen Glaude Garnier to prison.
Lead the condemned out.
What?
Check, check, check.
Good job.
Reputation and influence.
What?
Good work.
So I notice when I like beat that guy up
and like sent thugs to his house,
no one's done anything since.
Hold on.
Okay.
That was a big juicy one.
I can feel that one down here.
Oh, I wasn't muted.
I went to be muted when I said that.
Fuck.
It caught embarrassing.
What?
Like a hot mic.
Your wife told me that I seek the support of just people.
I should look for them in your house.
Yes, Citizen Hanria.
My husband will be more than happy
to endorse your candidacy for the post of commander in Captain Crunch.
Why does this feel like a fait accompli?
Please do not be angry at your wife.
I am sure that they acted in good faith when she made those promises.
How could anyone refuse to support such a respectable officer?
I'm certain that my husband will acknowledge your merits just as I have.
Undoubtedly.
But how can I be so sure when there are so many other candidates?
Well, I respect the other candidates.
They are decent people.
However, I can offer you the most precious gift.
Money.
Working together, we can greatly benefit each other
and maybe Barry too.
Our family has a high regard for sincerity and loyalty, does it not, my dear?
Moreover, we respect each other's boundaries.
At every turn.
Yes, sir, those ugly rumours about you being an addict should be put to an end.
Nor that I never forget those who have done me a favour.
Words, words, words.
A lot of words, Citizen Hanria.
I am certain that no other candidate has asked for your endorsement.
They do not think that you are worthy of their friendship.
But I, Francois Henry, am different.
And so are my words.
I am sure that my husband has already noticed that.
Thank you.
Regardless of what the masses are yelling,
Paris is only as strong as its united elites.
I will not retract my wife's promises.
But in the future, make sure you come to me first.
But of course.
Words, words, words.
Okay, I need to hang out.
Okay.
But now I need to learn how to deal with stage fright
if he wants to be a professional musician.
You will have to endure an hour of racket.
Opening night at the theatre sounds fun.
But the wife is happy though, right?
Yes.
You don't like that?
I thought you wanted to be a musician.
Oh, is that like me?
Is that yours?
Is that my head?
Decapitation still had not lost its charm since the beginning of the revolution.
A group of people were gathered in a Parisian street surrounding something on the floor.
Your prestigious position allowed you to make your way to the centre of the mob,
only to find a man's severed head.
What had caught everyone's attention was that the head's facial expression,
it was grinning.
It was so unusual that the crowd stared hypnotized for no apparent reason.
You wonder if anyone had thought to ask about the rest of the corpse.
A lone severed head should deftly cause curiosity,
even if for purely scientific reasons.
And now you're staring alongside everybody else.
Order the guard to get rid of the head.
Leave scratching your own head.
No, get that fucking thing out of here.
Come on, the smiling head was removed and people dispersed.
That's Paris.
Yeah, I mean, that's absolutely fucking ridiculous.
I don't want that on the street.
I'm gonna get booed for that.
A paris of a new era.
Weak, vulnerable to attacks.
Waiting for someone to reach for power.
Waiting for someone who, once again, will take control of its soul.
The pawns are now in play.
It's just like Los Santos down here.
Revolutionary holiday.
Recent days have proven that Paris can win,
that France can win.
We managed to overcome our past,
divesting our last remaining tyrant office power.
Now it's time to rebuild.
To create symbols that inspire future generations.
That is why during a gathering at the convention,
several enterprising citizens proposed the construction of a statue
to commemorate the revolutionary victory over injustice.
You were given the honor of supervising the construction.
There is no better candidate than the one who vanquished Louis Capet.
You have an opportunity to leave yet another mark on Paris.
Do I get to say what it looks like?
Can you not speak these common words?
I'm trying not to cough in the middle of them.
Like I just did.
Each section can be controlled by you, by an enemy, or by a neutral.
They're opening up a game, a board game now?
All right.
Each section you take over provides you with one additional influence point.
The chance of mission success is higher in your territory.
Enemy agents can also take over your sections.
Actions performed in enemy sections are less likely to be successful.
Some sections are locked.
I'll lock them with any agent to carry out actions without them.
To unlock a section, you have to scout it first.
You can only unlock sections adjacent to the ones
that you already have unlocked.
A fervor.
Each section reacts to the situation in the game,
causing the fervor of residents to rise or fall.
If the fervor becomes too intense, it could result in destructive riots.
Geez.
So I have agents here.
Send agents on missions, manage unruly crowds, and fight for influence over the city.
Click an agent and choose the action you wish them to carry out.
The bruiser is good at fighting and gaining reputation and managing crowds,
while the diplomat takes over sections,
nurtures relations with factions, and lowers fervor in sections.
Weaker in duels against enemy agents.
This has opened up a whole new game here.
You can move your agents freely between your sections.
Unfortunately, in hostile or neutral sections,
they can only move one space per day.
So this is controlled by me.
So does the red faction the people?
Attitude neutral.
Lower the crowds fervor in the section.
District fully upgraded.
Can I move here?
I'm going to send a diplomat to the people.
Lower the crowds fervor.
Increase your influence over the district.
And what about down here?
Take over an enemy section.
Raphael Clovis is unlocking a section.
Okay.
There's a lot going on here.
I still haven't moved up?
What happened to you?
Did he die?
Fell?
Oh, that was the...
Right, right, right, right, right, right.
I can't move up a slot here?
Oh, we got two new people.
This is not the guy that I just sent out.
He's not...
No, no, no, no.
You guys, this is the...
He's not dead.
Is that guy dead?
No.
All right.
This is the main section.
Let's go back here.
Wait.
I have something here.
There's nothing in there?
What the fuck?
The more sections under your control,
the faster the monument is constructed.
Each subsequent stage of completion
allows you to take over another building
near the monument.
Uh, I mean, I have to do the...
Look at me!
I like that pedestal.
I don't like that pedestal.
No, that's fine.
That's good.
Why is the judge commissioning statues?
Yeah, it's almost like they added
another video game here.
Each building lets you perform
a different kind of action.
Take over the ones
that support your play style.
Whenever you finish a stage of construction,
you'll be able to seize another building.
Why am I seizing my own residence?
Spend more time with your family
or facilitate the persuasions.
I need points.
I only have one influence point.
I don't think I can do anything now.
How do I get back to the judge game?
End of the day.
You're gonna unlock the battle royale mode
in 10 days?
There's a lot of stuff.
Yeah, this game just came out today,
by the way, if you're curious.
A bloody beginning.
A violent prologue
announced by a flowing red curtain.
The wrath of strangers
made me sick to my stomach.
Feet stirred dark puddles.
The air tasted like iron.
Their heads, someone cried.
Anger hidden in the shadows.
Thousands of cries from a single throat.
Here was a beast
with hundreds of claws and teeth.
What, was that a monster?
A kicked, abused,
and physically wounded soul.
Their heads.
What a cold and urgent order.
The beast's eyes
showed a long disguised bitterness.
Yesterday's envy.
It has waited too long
to show mercy now.
Too long covering its ears
while others laughed
at its inadequacies and feebleness.
The beast's bark was filled
with a thousand smiles
of those who worshiped this bloody moment.
The day when their enemies will perish.
Is this a metaphor?
They're brothers.
You think?
It's just dogs attacking each other.
This is murder.
It's all literal.
All right, so let me,
oh, let me look at this.
Let's see.
Bruno Hugo, 26,
is a groom working for the wealthy
and influential aristocrat
Jean-Claude de Jacquemart.
During a quarrel,
he was seen to push his employer
down the stairs,
resulting in the aristocrat's death.
It is significant for the case
that due to his origin and low intellect,
Bruno Hugo is known
in the local community as a village idiot.
The witnesses testified
that Jacquemart returned from a ride
displeased with the way
Bruno had prepared his horse.
Apparently, the saddle had become so loose
that Citizen de Jacquemart
almost fell from his mount.
The victim called for Bruno
in order to scold him
and began insulting
and physically abusing the stable boy.
When acting on an impulse,
Bruno pushed his employer away.
As a result, Citizen de Jacquemart
landed at the foot of the stairs
with a twisted neck.
The incident happened
in front of other employees.
Bruno Hugo escaped to the stable
where he was later found,
pale with fright
and whispering something
to one of the horses.
A quiddle from the common folk
and from family
and prison for the revolutionaries.
So we got some info here.
Let's go ahead and start this theory.
So, twisted neck is
no, no, no, no.
The village idiot is personality.
Groom is what the witness does.
Loose saddle is the accusation.
Loose saddle, no, that's the motive.
No, it's not.
That's the method.
Uh-oh, there was no motive.
Hold on.
God damn it.
I'm going to go like Gargo with salt water.
This is starting to get really fucking annoying.
All right, return for his ride.
Okay, the witness testified that
Jacques returned from a ride,
displeased from the way
that Bruno prepared his horse.
The saddle was so loose
that he almost fell.
Okay, so that's the method.
So then we've got
return from a ride
that was a witness, right?
There's been too much learning
on these streams recently.
Shout and struggle, uh, that's
I mean, is that method?
Twisted neck is
that's not an accusation.
That's not a witness.
That's not a motive.
That's the method, right?
Like if you break your neck,
that's the method by breaking your neck
was falling down the stairs
or it could be a trap.
I don't buy that.
So he was
the victim called for Bruno to scold him
began insulting and abusing the stable boy.
So shout and struggle is the method
or the accusation.
It's method, motive, or accusation.
Okay, yeah.
Then it's only three more.
Groom is the offender's personality.
Oh, that's a trap.
How is that the trap?
What?
The twisted neck method is not the trap?
Well, that sucks.
This is a simple case.
The accused is guilty of murder
and the only problem is
that people feel sorry for him.
What's your name?
Bruno Hugo.
I'm Bruno Hugo.
Do you work for citizen Jean-Claude de Jacquemin?
Yes, I worked there for a few years.
Quite a few.
Leave him alone.
He's just a man child.
Do you admit to the murder?
Yes or no?
But I...
Poor thing.
He's shaking all over.
All right, I need three more.
I can't fuck this up.
Twisted neck.
There's no more trap.
Twisted neck is the method
that he broke his neck.
Shout and struggle is...
What?
Is another one for shout and struggle?
Return from a ride as the witness said, right?
Let me see this.
The witness has testified
that Jacques returned from a ride, right?
Village Idiot Streamer.
And then the personality of the...
Yeah.
Okay, we're good.
Because that's the personality
of the guy that was fucking strangling him.
Okay, here we go.
Do you know how local people refer to you?
Bruno does not know.
Does not know.
Village Idiot.
Do you wish to comment on this?
Why am I doing that?
Bruno does not like that name.
No.
Do they often call you that?
It's mocking him.
No, I don't like it.
And that's that.
I already have a name
given to me by my mother.
She gave me one.
What is this?
Well, is this nickname
the reason you push Citizen Jacques Le Guard
down the stairs?
The master was shouting
and I don't like it when he shouts.
I don't like it.
Uh...
Are you aware that you have killed a man?
Do you understand that?
I know.
I just swung my arm
because he was shouting at me like that.
So loud.
Wait, I thought he was...
I thought he was attacking.
Were you aware that you could hurt him?
I didn't think so.
I didn't.
Did you swing so hard that he fell down?
I got so scared I can't remember.
I squinted my eyes, sir.
And when I opened them again,
there he was lying down there downstairs.
He plead guilty.
How did Citizen Des Jacques Mar
treat you?
He was good to me.
Sometimes he shouted,
but he fed me and was good to the horses.
Good.
How often did he shout?
Sometimes he shouted.
Sometimes he didn't.
Aristocrat scoundrel.
Is that why you decided to kill him?
Uh...
First he was tormented by the nobleman
and now by the revolution.
Please call in, uh...
Please call in.
Call in.
Please introduce yourself and state your duties.
My name is Colin Bouffieu.
I am the major domo at the residence
of the Des Jacques Mar family
and saw exactly what happened.
Please tell us what happened
between Citizen Hugo
and the master of the horses on that day.
What do you think of the groom?
Tell us what happened.
Citizen Des Jacques Mar
was furious at Bruno
because he hadn't tightened the saddle.
Could have caused an accident.
How did your employer react to this?
He started shouting at Bruno.
Tugging and pulling at him.
Bruno pushed Citizen Des Jacques Mar away
causing him to fall down the stairs
they were both standing on.
Nasty bourgeois.
Uh...
How do you plead?
I don't know what I did wrong.
I don't understand.
These people wanted me to come here
so I came.
I meant no harm to nobody.
No harm.
You're facing the death penalty
for murder.
Do you realize that?
Is he?
I'm jumping to that.
I just want to go back to the horses.
I don't know if they've eaten today.
If a horse doesn't eat for a long time
the master isn't happy
when the horses aren't fed.
Are you more worried about the horses
than your own master?
The master is dead.
What can I do?
And the horses are still alive.
They're alive.
Did the defendant confess to the crimes?
Yes.
Was his act counter-revolutionary in nature?
I mean not really.
What was the reason behind the argument
the defendant had with the victim?
A loose saddle.
Does the defendant understand the indictment?
No.
He didn't confess.
Yeah, he did.
He said like, yeah, I did it.
He's dead.
You're responsible for preparing
the horses for the victim.
Yes, I combed them and fed them.
Horses eat a lot of grass.
I combed them.
Was the saddle loose?
Hello?
Citizen?
No, impossible.
I pulled the straps.
You can't pull too hard
or it crushes and hurts the horse's stomach.
Horses are good.
Better than humans.
They...
Did you want your master to fall off the horse?
Did you deliberately leave the girth strap loose
to get back at your employer?
I never.
I liked our master.
I wouldn't hurt him.
I liked him.
You can see that he's just a gentle child.
People are aggressive.
Let him go.
Riot incoming.
I'm not a bad judge.
I just need to get there.
I got to get all the facts.
You still killed somebody.
This one makes the most sense to stay balanced.
Manslaughter, not murder.
Balance or justice.
Saddle didn't fit.
The saddle didn't fit.
Yeah, that's the best for game purposes.
That's the best option.
It's death penalty.
Can you imagine that if I had done that?
I find Bruno Hugo not guilty of the aforementioned crimes
as he is unaware of what happened.
What does it matter?
A crime is a crime.
You have to be careful with the likes of this one.
His employer should have known better.
Good job.
Bad judge.
I didn't get bad judge.
I got influence points.
I got to get some more water.
My name is Jean-Marie Rowland
and my name should not be unknown to you.
After all, you wiped your shoes on it
during King Louis' trial.
Citizen's cafe, not King.
King Louis Auguste Babin.
Thanks to you flinging around half-truths
and speculation.
Everyone is calling for my head.
Accusing me of corruption and treason
while you used our backs as a stepladder
on your way up the social hierarchy.
Corrupting politicians does not always work out.
Danton does it.
Melville tried to.
But they caught you.
Happens.
I will probably be dismissed from my station.
I may even end up at the guillotine.
But I will make sure your head rolls right after mine.
You will be my comrade in misery.
Threatening the judge of the tribunal
is an even worse idea than supporting a despised king
and corrupting politicians of the convention.
I will get rid of you, a candidate for captain of the guard.
And then I will go after you.
It took me and my wife too long to get used to where we are.
I will not die because of some over-boozed maggot
that likes to call himself a judge.
You will see how we wage war in Paris' salons.
You treacherous mongrel.
Dear comrade, I heard the news of Minister Roland's unexpected visit.
I have to confess that Roland knows about me
something that he should not have.
I am certain he is already weaving an intrigue against us.
We have to start working on one against him.
Francois.
Play something for me, son.
No, that's the wrong voice.
Wrong guy.
I have work to do.
What if we just...
Everyone gets the same voice.
Don't you guys understand?
As you wish, father.
Support the construction of the statue.
Increase the rate at which the statue is constructed.
Who cares?
Opening night of the theater.
No, I think dad's got to get happy here.
Reading together.
Yeah.
Dad will think this is interesting.
Wow, mom really liked that.
A lot.
We must get four altis.
Ooh, what happened?
Ooh.
Ooh, unlocked.
Uh-oh.
Enemy agents will fight with your agents for territory.
They can take over your sections with neutral sections.
This combat.
When at least two hostile agents meet in one section,
combat ensues.
Remember that a diplomat has little chance against a brutal fighter.
After defeating combat, your agent becomes injured.
They can still move around, but are not able to perform any actions.
Your main section is vital.
The buildings here enable you to influence the rest of the game.
Protect it at all costs.
If you let it out of your grasp, you will lose the game.
I'm sorry, I didn't mute.
Okay.
Go fucking get them.
Fighting. This is a diplomat, right?
Revolutionaries.
Construction of the monument, okay.
Why does the judge have his own militia?
What's down here?
Let's go take a look.
Unlock this section too.
Now, this is a captain versus a diplomat.
This guy's going to be coming out of the library with a bunch of books in his hand,
and this guy's going to just walk over and shoulder-attack them,
and he's going to go like, oh-ho, and fall backwards.
I'll see to this that you hang, and he's going to run away.
Easy.
Okay, so that's good.
Intrigue.
Well, there's more.
The documents discovered in Capay's iron cabinet raise suspicions regarding Roland.
The minister hates the tribunal for openly ridiculing him,
and he will not forgive you for it.
His intelligent wife holds an even stronger grudge.
Number of successes.
Three number of successes.
Five.
Action blocks.
Perform actions correctly to fill the progress bar.
If you carry out too few, you will lose.
If you perform more than necessary, you will receive a bonus.
Perform actions correctly to fill the progress bar.
If you carry out too few, you will win.
Okay.
The documents.
Successful intrigue.
So, convincing a witness.
So far, there are only rumors that Roland destroyed the documents.
If we find someone from his social circle to corroborate this,
we would gain a powerful tool.
We have a potential candidate, Philip Cotet,
who was among the people who opened Capay's iron cabinet.
For an action to be successful,
you need to persuade the required number of people.
You can also send your diplomat to do it for you.
Remember, you can only do this while the block is active.
All right.
So you can send it.
It's two points.
I only have like three points.
What if I do it?
Convince.
Can I do this?
Is it like a certain chance that I...
Oh, shit.
We have a string of dialogue?
Thank you for coming, Citizen Cotet.
How could I say no to a person who holds the lives of kings in the palm of his hand?
I presume that our meeting is connected to Minister Roland?
Exactly.
I'd like to talk about the incident with the iron cabinet.
It is indeed rather ugly.
The minister could lose his head because of it,
although it is currently nothing more than gossip.
Yes, but what if the gossip suddenly turned into the truth?
Then things would certainly get nasty.
I want to get him.
What are you going to do to help me?
Carrots and sticks.
All right, withdrawn.
I want to get Roland.
Aggressive.
What will he get out of this?
Manipulate.
Carrot and stick.
Carelessness.
Bingo.
Fuck.
No, that was right, except for this.
So I think it's...
That's...
This is not perfect.
These are both good, but neither one of them is perfect.
Manipulate would be perfect, but this one's not perfect.
What will he get out of this?
Maybe carelessness for this one?
Will strong, strong, and perfect.
We're strong, strong, strong, convinced.
I wonder.
Or humility.
I'm going to do aggression, manipulation, and humility.
Here we go.
I need Roland's head.
He is a pest.
By bribing politicians, he has harmed all of France.
We need the witness that saw him opening the iron chest
to reveal his identity.
We need you.
Sibyzen.
Roland has his vices,
but are they enough to justify my betrayal
because that is what you ask of me?
Manipulation.
Minister Roland will not save you
when matters become troublesome.
I can save you from charges of complicity,
for example, other things.
All right, and then humility.
I believe that you are a man of reason, Citizen Coat.
Listening to it, telling you that you do not want
to pay for Roland's mistakes,
and I do not want to make you pay for them.
Got it.
I will help you and testify against him.
Let us see where this leads.
But hopefully to you,
hopefully to my head staying on my neck,
as you promised.
Got it.
Thank you.
Oh, God, spreading rumors.
Choosing how to resolve this.
Some actors require you to make decisions about tactics.
Each decision may have a different chance of success.
What is this one?
Courtguard Raphael Clovis,
your loyal subordinate,
will have to talk some sense into a few heads
so they realize how big a threat Roland is.
Or a few casual remarks made by the respected Jacques-Louis David
should unleash an avalanche.
Chance of success is 10%.
Or plus 10%.
Does that not get-
That's not gonna-
10% chance?
Or is that added on top?
I don't think it's worth doing.
We'll do, ah, diplomacy.
Intrigues are carried out in a matter of days.
The results of some action blocks
may only be seen the next day.
So that's plus 10%, okay?
Okay.
How is that a failed intrigue?
I think we're good.
Added from the one before, okay?
What happened here?
They're just-
They're fighting.
All right, we'll end the day.
It's a cool game, it is.
All right, here we go.
Revolutionaries want the death penalty,
and common folk want acquittal.
He fell in love with Marie Antoinette.
Are you Mr. Antoine Barnet?
I am.
Did you and your mistress Marie Antoinette
plot against France?
There are so many lies in your-
No, wait, wrong.
There are so many lies in your question
that I cannot decide which one to deny first.
He tries to defend himself with pretty words.
So are you not pleading guilty?
Of course not.
All we got here, we've got-
Your Highness, I am certain that our shared efforts
will convince the people of France
to preserve the monarchy.
The loss of your wisdom and kindness
would be too tragic a blow
for the state to afford yours, Antoine.
What else do we have here?
We have this case file.
Treason, advocating monarchy,
and counterrevolution.
Defendant is Antoine Barnet, a 32-year-old politician
and famous orator.
Parisians remember him from his fiery speech
defending the constitutional monarchy.
He is known as a fierce enemy of the republic
and protector of the king.
Seeing that his political efforts
were fruitless, he joined the National Guard.
Excuse me.
In 1791, during the notorious flight to Varans,
the Capets were detained by the Guard.
Antoine Barnet and two of the soldiers
were ordered to escort the fugitives back to Paris.
When Barnet met Marie Antoinette,
he was absolutely charmed.
The two developed a potentially sexual,
potentially sexual relationship.
Later, they were frequently writing to each other.
In her letters, Marie Antoinette often expressed
hope for the survival of absolute monarchy.
Not long after, Barnet joined the Jacobins,
hoping to help the Capets
and alleviate the radical approach
of the revolutionaries
towards Citizen Capet and Marie Antoinette.
His efforts, however, were futile.
Due to his sympathy towards the monarchy
and the Capets, especially Marie Antoinette,
he was under constant surveillance.
Now we have finally managed to collect enough evidence
against him to file an indictment.
One of the pieces of evidence is
his correspondence with Marie Antoinette,
which potentially proves
his counter-revolutionary tendencies.
Antoine Barnet ought to be punished
like any other enemy of the revolution.
And the evidence is a letter
Barnet wrote to Marie Antoinette.
Okay, so, famous orator.
Ordered to escort the fugitives back to Paris.
Okay, met Marie Antoinette,
was absolutely charmed.
They developed a relationship.
They write back and forth.
Had some sympathy towards the monarchy
and wrote some letters.
Okay, so, famous orator.
That's a personality.
We have letters addressed to Marie Antoinette.
That's evidence.
Sympathy towards the monarchs.
That's the not motive.
That's personality or counter-revolution.
Charmed by the queen.
That's what we like to call a Marie Antoinette.
That's it.
Okay, four more questions.
Letters addressed to Marie Antoinette.
This is evidence?
No, this is the motive.
Personality.
Fuck.
Escorting Citizen Capay.
That is motive.
Dude.
God damn it.
I didn't even need to click that.
Okay, after this,
I gotta get some fucking water.
Get some fucking salt.
Uh, I can't make any more mistakes, though.
So, we've got...
This is just...
Letters addressed to Marie Antoinette.
Is extenuating circumstance.
And then, is Marie Antoinette the motive?
Hold on.
No, no, wait.
Yeah, he's either too developed to say that
later they were frequently writing letters to Marie Antoinette
to express hope for the survival of absolute monarchy, right?
And then, the evidence is letters that he wrote to Marie Antoinette.
Replenish your electrolytes.
Yeah, I'm going to.
Unfortunately, this stream is gonna probably cut short.
Because this is really starting to cause me anguish.
Charmed by the Queen.
I don't know if that's motive or just extenuating.
No, the absolute...
I'm not going to not stream Sekiro tomorrow.
You kidding me?
If anything, I want to get ready for it.
I want to get some rest and save my throat.
I'm not going to play Sekiro off stream.
Oh my god, I've been waiting for it for so long.
That's motive.
Well, she was fucking playing him.
She was playing him.
Whatever, this guy's done.
I don't need this shit.
All right, not long ago you were on the path to a grand career.
I remember your famous speech in defense of Citizen Capay.
Your charisma could have taken you to the top,
but instead you are here.
Do you not regret it?
That speech was not aimed against the revolution.
I only wish to appeal to common sense.
Many remember that performance as an attack
on everything that started in France on July 14th.
Nonsense.
The changes were essential.
Constitutional monarchy is a reasonable alternative
to the old order.
So in your opinion,
people who brought misery to France
should continue living in a palace.
I do not think they should be guillotined
only for their ancestry.
Did you ever express your feelings
to Marie Antoinette in your letters?
Did you not read our letters carefully?
I would not have dared to woo the Queen of France.
You wrote about her wisdom and kindness.
It sounds like you were paying her compliments.
Those were just pleasantries.
Maybe she was wooing him.
The Austrian whore was insatiable.
Kill him.
It would appear that in your letters,
Marie Antoinette, you tried to convince her
and her husband to support the revolution.
What would you gain from that?
I believe that we would avert the terror
we were currently facing.
Why do you think there's terror in our country?
I would not be standing here now otherwise.
You're there because you're a royal swine.
The Capais were not interested in the Constitution?
Unfortunately not.
And how would you benefit from it?
I only...
Did I catch that?
I think I did.
I only wanted what was best for my country.
Were you not afraid to openly support
the monarchs on the eve of the revolution?
That could be interpreted as treason.
I may be young and idealistic,
but I'm no traitor.
If that were true,
you'd be standing on the right side.
I love this country,
and I'm certain that the republic
which the revolutionaries are fighting for
is not...
a...
Anassia.
If you fight the republic,
you fight France itself.
What is it, snowing?
French YouTuber voice.
I'm sick of listening to your shit.
We already saw this movie.
I've no further questions, thank you.
I said to citizen Antoine Barnard,
that by the Aguiq team,
that's how every court should operate
swift and bold.
And does it matter what we have to say?
You'd better take us into account in the future.
Look, it's all balanced.
Enemy at the courthouse.
The jury noticed you making the wrong choices
and forgoing justice.
The rumors spread fast.
That's what happened in reality.
I'm basing my shit on the book.
You can adapt your Game of Thrones season fucking seven
however you want.
You can change the ending.
Not me, I'm going right to the books.
Hey guys, welcome back to part 143
of my YouTube series.
Today we're going to get
sentenced to death for supporting the monarchy.
It's agent, you ordered me to silence.
It is done, but there's something
you need to see for yourself.
Who is this?
All right, speak to the comic book.
Carefree for the crime.
So should I be careless with this?
Whatever.
They're oversensitive about the defendant.
Carelessness, they're oversensitive
so we can do some humility here.
And then revolution,
let's go straight up aggressive.
Perfect, strong
and revolution.
Manipulate or humility?
Probably manipulate.
Careless, humility, and manipulate.
For this convict here,
killing was as easy as breathing.
That's how this guillotine is to us.
I'm telling a joke.
Humility.
The criminals belong in the grave
only then we can build a better future.
Yes, and then manipulation.
Future generations will remember
that we were not cowards.
It needs to be done.
And everyone's happy.
Reputation plus three.
I performed my duties
when the king was equal to France
and this is how France repays me.
Boo, for the revolution.
Boo, why are you always booing me?
That guy's usually happy.
Oh, he didn't get a good seat this time.
He didn't get her quick enough.
Do you want to show me a common dead body?
It's not just a dead body.
Look at that necklace.
It's Winston.
A fleur de lis.
That's the Winston voice actor.
There's more hidden under his clothes.
We found a message in the inner pocket of his cloak.
No, it's not.
It's an order.
Someone told that man to build support
for a mysterious R in the district.
Who is arrogant enough to take Louis place?
You guys thought my French accents weren't good.
Only aristocrats are powerful enough
to secretly organize people like him.
These guys have an American accent.
I'm at least in the same hemisphere.
Even they would need help from someone in the convention.
So who is R?
Robespierre, maybe.
If he's allying with aristocrats,
we must tell someone, everyone.
It could be Minister Roland.
As long as we are not sure,
we would only create panic.
If that's the case,
we'll have to hunt down other agents.
This one won't be telling us anything.
We have no other choice.
If this R is trying to gain support,
you must do the same for the greater good.
It's that Robespierre guy.
He's at the top.
When are they going to add vibe support?
The evening is warm,
so you decide to take the long way home.
Near the Caf Chantilly,
you spot an amusing scene.
Two drunkards fighting over a bottle of liquor.
Cursing like stable boys.
The first is shorter
and dressed in a disheveled officer's uniform,
possibly a colonel.
The second fighter,
although significantly taller,
is just an ordinary street thug.
You listen to the gibberish and tangled epathies,
only to reach the conclusion
that the bottle contains one last gulp of drink.
Try to settle the dispute between the drunkards.
The two enemies unite in the face of a stranger
in an elegant coat.
It surely looks comical to the observers
when, in a fit of booze-driven solidarity,
one tries to hit you in the head
with the disputed object,
while the other kicks at your ankle.
He dodges the bottle,
which smashes on a nearby wall,
spilling the remaining alcohol everywhere.
However, the kick is a success
and immobilizes you long enough
for the drunkards to disappear down a back alley.
It takes some time
for the bystanders to stop laughing.
And I'm a judge
and I could literally,
I could have your tongue out.
Should I do this?
How should I do this?
Evening stroll.
No, we're gonna,
everyone's doing so good.
Evening with grandfather.
Yeah, it's okay to lose points here.
He's hard to please.
That's an entire evening with grandpa
and it's not even a centimeter dead.
I would.
Why is this on fire?
Riots block agents except the bruiser
and prevent you from gaining influence
points from the section.
When not quelled,
riots make a section neutral
and can quickly spread.
Get in there.
Let's head back.
Increase your influence.
Just increase influence over here.
Jerma lied about Minecraft VR.
Five community subs.
Thank you for the five subs.
Let's try to quell the unrest here.
But did you, did you,
hold on.
Your name used to be an all lowercase.
Didn't it?
Did you change your name
to add uppercase letters?
That's what you did.
Why?
All right.
I'll be right back.
And I actually,
I'm probably gonna have to stop here.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting raw in the back.
Sorry for like the four
to five hour stream.
Hold on.
I just, it's starting to hurt.
Let me, let me, hold on.
I'm not gonna say that yet.
Let me go get some,
like I'm gonna gargle some salt water
and like have a drink of water.
And let me just see how I am
in like two minutes.
I'll be right back.
And yes, regardless,
Sekiro is tomorrow.
Sekiro tomorrow.
Probably all day.
From the moment I get up,
I don't know when the stream's gonna start,
but I'm just gonna play
the absolute hell out of it.
So I'll be right back.
We'll just, we'll see in a second.
Too sick for Sekiro tomorrow, guaranteed.
No way.
I've been waiting too long to play this.
No, that's not gonna happen.
I don't care if I have to mute myself.
It'll be like a no talking stream.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Hooray.
Cough syrup is coming in.
Rejoicing.
But I am gonna just call it.
I was down there talking to Kim
and I've decided
it's probably for the best
because if I like keep going,
I keep talking and keep like
irritating the area that I did tomorrow.
Sekiro, you know what I'm saying?
Like I want to be fucking ready to go
completely all day.
Can you hear her?
Hold on.
She's coughing too.
Yeah.
She got it first.
She has it bad.
Mine's not that bad.
I hope it doesn't progress.
That'd be terrible.
But I'll be honest with you here.
This game is actually fucking fun.
And I would recommend that you play this game
if you think, you know,
if you like doing this kind of thing.
What a terrible, terrible review that I just gave.
It's good if you like this,
if you kind of like this kind of thing.
Yeah.
No shit.
Italics is not sick.
I don't know how me and Kim got this.
I have no idea.
It's really only been the last couple of days though.
But yeah.
I'm gonna just get ready for Sekiro tomorrow.
I'm gonna do the thing that I should do.
And unfortunately,
we're gonna have like a four and a half hours stream.
But, and I'm sorry.
I haven't been gone for four days
for unrelated friend of mine came up.
And really the day coming back,
I don't want to be like,
see you later after like four hours.
But we are gonna go
probably Friday, Saturday, and Sunday.
Because I'm just gonna,
obviously Sekiro is gonna be on the mind.
So with that, I'll see you tomorrow.
If you don't want Sekiro to be spoiled,
then by all means,
I'll just see you again when that's over with.
And later on in this coming week,
Monster Rancher 4 and probably Monster Rancher 2,
depending on how bad or good Monster Rancher 4 is.
I'll be going back to it.
So that's kind of the plan.
Maybe go back to VR a little after that.
Possibly.
So, so, I will see you guys tomorrow for Sekiro.
I'm fucking insanely excited for it.
And again, sorry for the short stream tonight.
But I'm gonna rest up my voice.
And like I said,
of course the day coming back and having like,
oh, let me pick a game where I read,
where I'm gonna read a shit little dialogue.
What a, what a dope, you know what I mean?
Friday, yeah, the Sekiro,
Sekiro is technically out in like 30 or 40 minutes or something.
But I'm gonna wait till tomorrow.
Thank you so much.
Hope you enjoyed the time that we had here today.
I'll see you for Sekiro tomorrow.
Have a great one.
Catch you guys later.
And with that being said,
we are going to do the bits we pulled up.
Okay, so we have earlier today.
Out of the way.
Okay, so we had sad Vega for the 250.
Thank you, sad Vega.
They say Sekiro tomorrow.
As you know, it's gonna be amazing, horrible time for you.
Sorry in advance for all the day one backseating you're gonna get.
I'm going to blitz that game tomorrow just to see all the shit you go through
and laugh gleefully like a shit goblin as you suffer what I suffered through.
I'll be rooting for you though 100%.
Also, your mother is coming up to visit.
Don't you mean down or left?
Because you're in Vegas, which I'm sure is southwest of Boston.
That's true.
Yes.
But I always say up no matter what.
Coming up somewhere, coming up somewhere, I always say up.
Coming down left just doesn't sound right.
But I'm looking forward to it.
Hey, how do you know you're gonna blow through it?
What if you get stuck?
It might happen.
Labo VR is out now.
The video is.
Yeah, I can look into that too when that's coming up.
Tutorial boss.
Maybe I'll get stuck on it.
I don't know.
I hope I do.
I hope I get like locked at an encounter for like 45 minutes to an hour or something.
I miss that shit.
I miss not knowing what to do and it's a whole new experience.
I cannot wait.
Every death gift of one sub.
I'm not gonna do that.
Only an hour.
Yeah, it's possible.
But thank you.
Thank you Toshiro.TV for the five bucks.
I'm super excited for you to play Sekiro and I'm gonna be playing the heck out of it too.
But remember that there's not just dodging anymore.
It's gonna be weird to adjust.
But the posture system is really well designed.
Yeah, I've read some reviews about it.
And no, I thought there was one coming.
We're good.
Yeah, there's a whole system now on parries, right?
Not like there was before.
The parries are not the same throughout all the From Software games.
It's now there's an indicator and there's three different moves that you can do to block or parry.
It's not just like the,
DOOM!
Knock the thing up.
You have to actually do a certain maneuver, right?
Not just like hit left trigger, from my understanding.
And you get like a telegraph of when it's gonna happen.
So I don't know.
I'm so sorry.
That was bad.
I'm sure a lot of people probably just like so sick of hearing this tonight.
Which is another reason why I'm like, it's probably for the best to stop.
So, sorry.
He's dying.
No, I'm fine.
But yeah, there's a whole, there's like two health bars, right?
One of them is the posture system.
One of them is the health bar.
I'm sure it'll take a lot of getting used to, but that's, you know.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
WildFox1 for the three bucks.
Dear Jeremiah, on behalf of your recommendation,
I have bought some metal straws and I can say it was a good buy.
So thanks for that.
Yeah, metal straws are awesome.
The liquid stays cold going through.
As for the question, I present each with each bit message.
Why the fuck did you let that globalist mutant frog out into the wild?
Do you want to watch the world burn?
Referencing Seaman, if you don't know.
I had to see the credits.
That's my reasoning.
Thank you, though, WildFox.
Thank you, Jules, for the 250.
Have you thought about playing role-play games like GTA RP?
It's been getting a lot of attention recently.
I think you'd be good at it.
I think it would be a lot of fun, but I think I've, at least me personally,
I don't like to jump into random sessions with people that I don't know
because it's hard for me to bounce off of strangers.
If I get a few friends and we kind of all are in on the same jokes and the same material,
it's really easy to create scenarios and create fun.
But I don't really like to jump into just complete stranger scenarios
where somebody says something.
I mean, it would be fun, but it almost feels like, in a way for me,
when there's like a ton of people all kind of doing a bit at the same time,
it's hard to have your bit be a thing that you want to care about.
You know what I mean?
If you've got like 10 people all making something happen,
realistically, only a couple people can talk at once.
And what it ends up being, it ends up being one or two people's stories
that everybody else has to kind of find out how they're going to fit
into involved inside of it, right?
You could pretend to be a traveling salesman and pass through town
and only play for like a week.
Yeah, and don't a lot of the RP servers have pretty staunch rules
on what your character can do?
Isn't it like a commitment you really need to go in there
and follow like terms and you need to take improv classes?
No, it's just when there's so many people all doing the same thing.
Improv is improv, but when like 15 people are all doing improv
at the same time, it can just turn into noise.
That's what I'm saying.
That seems to happen with a lot of kind of,
it's almost like the scenario where, and this is,
this might sound like I'm talking shit or something, but I'm not.
But back in the day in YouTube, everybody was making a video, right?
So what would happen is if you got like five, six, seven people
that you're all new or you were kind of all going into a scenario with,
all of you were recording at the same time,
and all of you want to make the video,
and all of you want to make the joke.
So what ends up happening is just like,
it's almost incomprehensible.
Everybody's got their own intros,
everybody's got their own like characters,
everybody's got their own shit that they want to say
because they're making a video too,
they want to be the spotlight because their people are watching,
you know what I'm saying?
That's why it was always so much easier to, you know,
get like one or two people together,
and everybody knows kind of what we're going to do for this bit,
and where we're going to say,
how fun are we going to make it,
and what we're going to do this time.
And even if it was completely all off the cuff and improv,
which a lot of it was, most of it was,
30 main characters and no supporting cast.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
And that's not intended to like throw like shade at somebody,
it's just personally I don't do well in an environment
where everybody's all trying to make a joke at the same time,
because everybody has their camera pointed at them.
You can hang out with only one or two people,
lots of streamers have just broken up into gangs.
I mean, I don't know anything about it.
All I know is that it's really, really popular right now,
and anytime you jump into something really popular,
you kind of, it's kind of inevitable
that you're going to just get landed somewhere,
and all right, where's the camera pointing,
and where are we going, right?
And that's not me talking specifically about GTA RP,
that's just talking about the nature of kind of online playing
or making a video or streaming with a bunch of other people
that are all doing the same thing.
But it's not something that I think it would be a lot of fun,
it's just I'm not sure exactly even where to start
with something like that.
Because I really would just be like every,
like you said, people break off into like gangs and stuff,
and I would just be the one dickhead walking around,
like I said, trying to find the content to be a part of.
Oh, we got like these like five guys are doing this,
these like four or five people are doing this,
and I'm just like, hey, I just joined.
Alert, alert, it's me, alert, I'm here, alert.
Like, I don't even know where to start.
But anyways, hopefully that kind of answers the question of
why I don't typically do RP based stuff on stream or on video.
Especially people that I don't know.
That's the number one reason.
Number one is with people that I don't know, right?
But thank you for the 250.
Thank you Mad for the $5.
Hey, Jerma, hope all is well.
I'm heading to Boston on Saturday for college,
so I might not be able to see some of your streams, but hey.
Well, welcome to Boston.
Boston is a wonderful city.
Enjoy it.
Going to college in Boston is that,
that's, I don't know if it's a new thing
or something you've been doing already, but good luck.
And I don't know how far away you are, but hope you enjoy it.
All the people I work with from there are pretty straightforward.
Yeah, I mean, Boston is kind of one of those cities
where it's just, who are you?
What do you want?
And how do I get it to you as fast as possible?
So you leave me alone.
That's like a lot of like Boston.
Who are you?
Oh, my name is Jeremy.
Okay, what do you want?
I want a sandwich.
All right, here, here you go.
It's done already.
I didn't even order.
Are you sure you didn't?
And then they bring the order that I was going to order.
I, that's what I thought.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Thank you Tingy for the 250.
Jerma, I don't think I could wear your shirts in public anymore.
Why not?
Over the weekend I was out
and someone saw me wearing my night sky shirt
and it must have angered them.
He pointed at me and starts yelling
shpee compact streamer another weird thing.
This is bullshit is what you're saying.
It's a great shirt.
You should wear it.
Thank you though.
I'm going to like turn my mic fucking down.
I hate being a coughing.
It's all right.
Thank you for the 20 bucks earlier.
Thank you.
Jeremy the Jerm, the big Jerm.
I have a request.
My dearest friend Haley is having a birthday bash and I need you.
Okay.
Her favorite hunk o' man.
I need you, her favorite hunk o' man
to wish upon her the happiest birthday
you've ever wished upon anyone upon reading this.
I need you to go hard on this one for me.
As hard as you can.
Possibly get for 20 dollars.
Well, all right.
Somebody clip this.
Don't get this first part though.
Haley.
Hold on.
No, no, not this part.
Starting now.
Haley.
Happy birthday.
Just want to make that very clear.
Hope you have a wonderful birthday, Haley.
I don't know what your last name is
but I just know you're Haley
and I know that you're going to have a great fucking birthday.
You know why?
Because I just deemed it necessary.
I want one.
Is that somebody somebody right there?
I want you to load up the crowd right now.
There's at least 400 people at your party.
Look at one, two, three, four, five.
Stop blowing the horns.
Put on the party hats.
Get the ice cream out.
Because it's your birthday.
And everybody on earth should be celebrating.
I want this to be broadcast on fucking TV.
And it will be.
I'm going to spend the 645,000 dollars it takes
to put this and put it on every station.
Happy birthday.
And tune into like MTV in a week
and when I pay Viacom, that's a lie.
But happy birthday, Haley.
Hope you have a great day.
Of course, you got friends.
You got all kinds of friends that care about you.
That's good.
Looking out for you, you know?
Happy birthday.
Hey, Professor Breen.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
And that's it.
Thank you so much, Professor Breen.
No message.
Just 10 dollars.
Thank you.
Thank you, Smelly Boy, for the 250.
All these characters in the hierarchy are real.
Jacques-Louis David was a world-renowned artist
who operated during the revolution.
He made some of the most famous art pieces
of the period like this one.
Oh, this is Jacques-Louis David, Bonaparte,
Francis Le Grand, St. Bernard.
Google Art.
Okay.
Oh, he made this?
That's the guy who made the famous
rearing Napoleon painting.
That's cool.
Didn't know that.
It's a very educational game.
Thank you, Smelly Boy.
Thank you, Dork Cube, for the 250.
You say 10 straight hours as if it's an amazing feat.
But at this point, nine or 10 hour streams
are common for you when you got to read bits for hours.
Yeah, but that hasn't happened that very recently, no.
All the streams recently since that the 250 change.
The end of the streams have not been that long.
They've been maybe 30 to 40 minutes each.
Not anymore.
A nine to 10 hour stream is really like
has been recently a nine, an eight to nine plus hour stream.
Remember when he only streamed for like three or four hours?
Yeah, I do.
A few years ago.
A couple years ago is really what it was.
A five, a four to five hour stream like two or three years ago was
that was a long stream for me.
But also I was so not used to that.
That's another thing.
Remember, I was making YouTube videos.
I wasn't just broadcasting straight for four, five, six, seven, eight, nine hours.
It took a long time really for me to really understand how to
limit myself energy wise and because what I would I would just blow out for like an hour or two.
And sometimes I still do that.
But sometimes I'll just blow out for two or three straight hours and then just be exhausted.
But I've learned sort of how to keep my energy levels up
to a point where I'm not just blown out after three hours.
Somebody said Vinny streams are like three hours max,
but he also streams almost every day.
Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of ways to do it.
There's a lot of ways to I know there are people aren't the people that
will stream for like three, two or three hours and then they'll take a break
and then come back in the night time and do another three or four hours.
People do that.
So, I mean, everybody is different.
And I've found over the years that if, you know, I give myself a day or two off,
a couple days off here or there, once a, you know, once a week,
take like two or three days off,
then I can usually sit here for more than five to six, maybe sometimes 10 hours.
It's taken me a long time to figure out how to do that
and be comfortable doing it.
Stream for five minutes every half hour.
You would get unfollowed in a second.
But thank you, Dorkcube for the 250.
You say 10 hours straight.
That was Dorkcube.
I don't even know if I said your name, but thank you.
Yeah, CoreMonster.
CoreMonster gave a hundred dollars, a hundred dollars and two cents.
Thank you, CoreMonster.
It's a shitload of money.
We touched upon it already, but it's fucking a lot.
Thank you.
Yeah, nothing.
I don't have any other issues though.
I don't have, you know, my head doesn't hurt.
I don't have a stuffy nose.
I just have this irritated throat and like an annoying
cough that originates down here in my chest somewhere.
So here's the shitty part about that.
If I, if this doesn't go away in a few days,
I'm probably going to have to go to the doctor
because like chest cough is, you don't, you want to take care of that.
So it's just like throat down into the down here.
But I'm fine.
I just have a cough.
It's not a problem.
And if it becomes an issue, I'll take care of it.
That's all there is to it.
No shirt.
Yeah, I just proved to everybody that I don't have a shirt on.
That's all it took.
I love how somebody just said that.
No shirt.
No.
Nintendo tried to sue you recently.
Who fucking made up that bullshit?
Nintendo tried to sue me?
Give me a source on that.
Hey blue comet, thanks for the $23 blue comet.
Here's some bits, Jerma.
Thanks for being so entertaining and funny, Jerma Hart.
Thanks for paying me a shitload of money
and watching the stream and being part of the community.
Thank you.
That means an absolute fuck time.
Thank you so much.
Dr. Pepper, thanks for the 10 bucks.
Have some bits.
You deserve it, girlfriend.
Thank you, Dr. Pepper.
For the $10.
Really appreciate it.
I'm honored that you think I deserve your money.
Did I talk to Skrillex yet?
No.
No, I did not.
Hey man boy, thanks for the $250.
Hey Jerma, Nintendo tweeted out a video showcasing Labo VR.
It's seven minutes long.
So you should watch it on your own time.
Too bad it probably won't be good for streaming.
That's what everybody said about the other Labo streams,
but that's not going to stop me from streaming it.
I'm going to stream Labo VR.
That is a promise.
Why would I not do that?
You have to put the switch on your head.
Well, it's switch on head or pre-recorded.
I can make that joke.
Don't clip that or anything.
I want to be able to say that on that stream.
But thank you, man boy, for your $250 again.
They forgot to link.
I will definitely take a look at this.
But thank you for the $5, man boy.
And then Dorkcube, thanks for the $250.
Get well soon, friend.
I can't wait to see you play Sekiro tomorrow
and die to this game's version of Pinwheel.
Now, but nobody knows who that version is.
Nobody knows anything about Pinwheel.
I don't know and you don't know.
So even if I do die to Pinwheel tomorrow,
you're not going to know that for like another couple of weeks
and then you'll forget.
Repaired joke.
Somebody just clipped it.
I just told you not to.
Oh my God, he did the thing.
Oh, switch on head.
Oh my goodness.
All right, let's roll the credits.
Let's see the subs and resubs tonight.
A lot, a lot.
A lot of people subbed and resubbed today
and gone for a while.
So thank you, guys.
German with the credits music.
What? The music's on?
What's your opinion of the French Revolution?
It happened.
Started watching your Stardew stream while working and it's cozy.
Yeah, that's a cozy game.
I can't wait to check out that multiplayer, right?
What's that burger restaurant in Vegas called?
They're going to be in Vegas tomorrow.
I want to go to their hash house at Gogo.
It's at the link.
You can, you can put the stamp of it.
You can wear a t-shirt that says,
German985 said this was the best restaurant in Las Vegas.
The burger from, they do a stuffed burger.
They do, it's a specialty from hash house at Gogo in the link.
Is probably the best fucking restaurant in Las Vegas.
There it is.
Sponsor.
Nope.
They just got the best burger in town.
Did you really die to pinwheel?
No.
That is a, what they call a funny joke
that the community has kept going,
you know, to crawl under my skin and say it and I get really angry
and I say, yeah, I didn't do that.
Never had the Gordon Ramsay burger.
I've been to Gordon Ramsay's steak, which was incredible.
That's the thing about Vegas.
There are hundreds and hundreds of amazing restaurants.
You kind of just have to pick one.
This is the guy that beat, yeah.
So, all right.
So I, I beat flame lurker first try.
Let's go over this real quick.
Flame lurker first try from Demon's Souls.
Blind.
We got champion gun deer first try.
Dancer first try.
Who else?
Because I want people to understand that
that's going to happen over the next couple of days.
I'm going to first try a hard boss over the next few days
and everybody is going to remember it.
God, I'm going to make sure I talk about just as much
I talk about the other ones.
Well, no, Jevil's not from software related.
I'm talking from software here.
Gwyn first try too.
Yeah.
Any new stream starting soon or BRB overcards
you mentioned sometime before you're going to be?
Yeah, oh yeah.
I've just been away from the computer
so I haven't really had a chance to get in touch with Blordel.
But it's going to happen.
I've been not here for about a week so.
Are socks feet gloves or are gloves hand socks?
They're made out of like cotton.
That's it.
They could go anywhere.
You can put cotton like on your penis
and it's just cotton.
I don't know why I said that
but that's pretty much where we're going to end.
Thanks for watching everybody.
See you soon.
See you tomorrow.
Are you going to make any more E-Bots?
Uh, yes.
Like that one, I don't know why that was the first.
I could have said like fingers
but that would just be gloves.
Anywho, I'll see you guys tomorrow for Sekiro.
Yeah, I ended early.
Who's streaming right now?
We got any streamers right now?
Okay, we've got who's live?
I don't know.
Why is it taking so long to load?
Let's run on Twitch.
Twitch, what are you doing?
What the hell was that?
Does it lose internet?
All right, we got...
What are people playing?
Vinny's playing Devil May Cry.
Joel's playing a game called Bad Smell.
What the fuck is that?
Nova's just hanging out.
Kiwo is playing, doing GTRP I assume.
Kraken's playing Sekiro.
Well, then we don't want to rate him
because I want you to watch my Sekiro stream.
Uh, yeah, let's rate Kiwo.
We rated Kraken a few days ago
and we rated Vinny like a few days before that.
Let's rate Kiwo.
Go say hello.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow for Sekiro.
Have a great one.
Go to my channel page here.
So here we go.
Bingo.
Ready to raid GTRP.
Hope you enjoy it.
You don't know who that is.
She's a very funny, talented person.
Go say hello.
Take care, guys.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, I missed right at the end here.
Hey, bath bath, five bucks.
Thanks for the five bucks.
And it's all another birthday as well.
So happy birthday.
I want to make sure I caught that.
I didn't see it.
Happy birthday to the bath bath as well.
And happy birthday to the rumor.
See you guys tomorrow.