Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some Counter-Strike Global Offensive.
Now, this game is released. It is out. I want to say that very first and foremost.
I haven't done a video on CSGO in quite a while, and that's because I was really waiting for this mode to come out.
I was waiting for it to come out to retail so I could buy it and play on this map whenever I felt like...
Oh, no, sorry, this mode, whenever I felt like it. And this mode is Jailbreak.
If you do not know what Jailbreak is, I'm going to give you a very brief synopsis before we cut into some of these goofy moments here.
And I have a video coming out in a couple of days that is pretty hysterical. It's me as the warden.
But we will get into that later in a couple of days, but I'm going to give you the basics of this mode.
I'm going to talk about a little bit why I love it so much, and then we'll get into some goofiness that happened during these playthroughs.
So what is Jailbreak? What exactly is going on? What is this game mode all about? And why is it so much fun?
First and foremost, Jailbreak is a game mode that pits two sides against each other, but not in the typical sense.
You have the prison guards who are there to construct order and to make sure nothing crazy happens.
And then you have the prisoners. And then you have the warden.
So pretty much there's three different things going on here. You have one guy who is the warden giving orders to all the prisoners.
Now, as a prisoner, you can either take these orders and follow the rules and follow the guidelines and survive till the end of the round, maybe.
Maybe make a couple of friends while you're at it.
But if you do not want to listen to the orders the warden gives you, you do not have to.
And that's why it's such a crazy social experiment, because you can start uprisings. You can just attack somebody.
You're probably going to die, but it's still fun to see reactions regardless.
So if you are playing as a prisoner, if you are on the side with the majority of people, that's where the most people are going to be.
Most people are going to be a prisoner. You start with only a knife and you start in a jail cell.
Some of these cells are going to have weapons in them.
Very, very minor weapons, something like a pistol or a grenade or something like that.
And the warden and the prison guards are going to be looking out for that.
So you really need to be cautious if you're going to plan on using these items that happen to be spawned in your particular jail cell.
So right at the beginning of a round, every single round, this is how every single round plays out,
they're either going to give you a free day or they are going to give you specific instructions.
Now what a free day is, a free day is they just open the doors and you can do whatever you want.
If you happen to attack one of the prison guards, you're going to die.
But you don't have to follow any specific instructions during a free day, in quotes.
So you're probably asking yourself, Jerma, how the hell is order even kept here?
Why don't the prison guards just open fire on everybody and why aren't there trolls everywhere?
Now they do exist, but you have to remember these admins are very, very strict about who they allow to play these games.
So if you jump into one of these games as a prison guard and you just start unloading on the prisoners for no reason at all,
you are going to get permabanned from this server. You're going to get kicked. If you do it again, you're going to get banned.
They're very, very proactive about that. So nobody really does it.
Usually everybody plays along and tries to fit in their specific role.
I, for one, when I play these games, I have such trouble playing as a prisoner.
I always try to find a way to sneak away or try to get a gun and shoot one of the prison guards.
It's so much fun trying to find different things to do because there's all kinds of little hidden areas you can find your way into.
It's so much fun, guys, and I highly recommend you jump into a jailbreak server.
Whether if you're going to try and play as the warden and give instructions and keep order or play as a prisoner
and either follow the directions and play till the end and try and last till the very end or try to start an uprising.
It's just a great experiment, guys, and please, please, please go find some servers that play jailbreak.
There's only about a handful of them, though, so you got to really look for them.
So that is going to wrap up my post commentary here. I'm going to cut to a couple of funny moments in the next couple of minutes.
So sit back, relax and enjoy the jailbreak, guys, and look forward in the next couple of days to Jerma the warden.
And I'll leave it at that. And of course, take care, everybody.
What did he say? What did you say?
Another free day. Free day. He said come within five feet and we get shot.
There's a sniper rifle just sitting right here. I want that sniper rifle.
Oh, Tio, Tio, Tio got it.
Jerma, do it.
No, dude, there's four of them just sitting here pointing at me. I'll never get out in time.
As soon as he does, hell will break loose.
Spoon, are you still alive?
No, I said I'm free and ran away and died.
I'm just waiting for an opportunity to try and grab that and run out of the room.
I'm just staring.
Oh, he just made it easier.
I got it. I got it.
CT's on the top floor. I want you to walk towards the end, walk down the stairs and join your buddies.
Walk down the stairs. Are these the stairs?
Why are you shooting me?
No free killing, guys.
Oh, I got an opportunity to knife this guy right in the back.
Oh, no, I've been doing way too much of that.
Face the wall.
Are we playing Red Rover?
We sure are.
Someone go up there and check to make sure there's no one left up there.
This is so scary.
I'm getting so fucking stupid.
Oh shit, what is this?
First reaction, last reaction.
I forget how this works.
I think it's the first person to do something.
I hope you guys know the rules, CT's.
Explain the rules, please.
First reaction, the first person to do something gets killed.
If I call last reaction, the last person to do it gets killed.
Okay, thank you.
What is going on?
Where's the gun? Where's the gun?
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
All right, all right, guys.
We're going to start playing now.
Fuck everybody!
Dude, there's only like three people alive.
What?
I got given a grenade. Should I throw it away?
Throw it in yourself, please.
Don't kill him, don't kill him.
Don't kill him.
I did it.
Oh, what the hell?
What the fuck did you kill him for?
He killed me.
Son of a bitch.
Don't pick up his gun.
Dude, he's giving me the gun.
He just gave me the gun.
Go drop it, go drop it.
Did he steal the gun away?
What are you...
I don't know.
Dude, the guy walked over and threw the gun at me.
He was like planting it on me.
Did I have a grenade or something?