Okay, so the next one I'm gonna move to, and I'm only gonna... I'm like drained already.
The next one I'm moving to is probably gonna have this, but just about 5,000 people here.
Probably about, probably 1,600 of you are gonna leave. I'll show you why. I saw it on
Steam, I had to buy it, even though it's probably gonna be terrible. I don't know, it might be
good. No, it's not Picross VR. Take a snapshot, okay? I'm serious. How many people are here
right now versus how many people are here in five minutes? Okay, let's see. Opening it now.
Change the title. Why? It says my own reality, playing games and demos. That's what we're
doing. Get out of Minecraft. Okay, and here we go. I apologize everybody, but it had to be done.
This is Rick and Morty of Virtual Rick-ality. Can you guys even see this? All right, I'm
ready now for a Rick and Morty. Look at that tension. How do I do anything? What do I do?
This is, this is, this is really awful. You couldn't make this quote out of fucking Jello
or something. Big disc. Do Rick's laundry. That's unplayable. And no, I don't mean the
game. I mean the headset. You wanna see a fucking magic trick? Oh shit! I probably just
made everybody throw. I'm so sorry. I have to sit here and let this unwind. Oh my god.
It's so tight back here. How does it even get like this? All right, let it spin. Come on,
let's go. Get in! There. There we go. Now I can spin. I physically couldn't even turn it.
Bunched up. Finally. My god. Can have, take like a powder break. Someone has to come
in here and powder my face, untangle my cord. That's fun. It is though. This is way too
fucking loud. All right, here we go. All right, let's come back. I'm sorry if I made
you almost throw up there, because I almost did too. Okay, do Rick's laundry. Hey,
look, we're ready to play a video game. Let's go. Rick and Morty. Okay. Can't wait to
hear more like made up words. Why am I playing this? Because this is my out.
Because this is my way out. Minecraft VR, I'm out of gas and this is my way out.
You'll be begging me to turn the stream off in about 20 minutes.
It's me, Morty!
You'll see I wrote instructions on what you're supposed to do.
This looks like when the Simpsons went into 3D and it looked weird. Okay.
How do I move?
You can drink. You want some? Right in your fucking eyes. Oh, look at this. It's
our dirty underwear! Oh, what the fuck? How do I move?
I don't know how to move. Morty, how do I move?
Dude, the physics engine fucking fell back. No, I'll take something. Oh,
okay, one. I thought I wanted me to put it in the...
Morty, listen to me. Listen to me, Morty. Morty, listen to me. I got it. I need that.
Your shot asides your blog from the Simpsons. I figured it out.
Lawsuit!
Do it again.
Thank you.
I'm gonna need you to grab the watch and put it on your wrist.
You'll be able to call me using the watch. This is very important.
All right, Morty clone? All right, Morty clone, we gotta go.
Don't touch any of my stuff while we're gone.
What's this one called? Rick, wait. I think I can figure it out.
That's the Schmeichel box. That's the Floggin' Flaggin' Blagger, right?
This is the Groobin' Grubbin' Globbaglover, right? Something like that.
Oh, and this is just a crown, Morty. Hey. Hey, I'm Mr. Basics.
Look at me. No. No, I didn't. No. What? Look at me. Everybody did that. Come on.
That was fucking actually kind of brutal.
Give me another one. Give me another one. Give me another one. Give me another one.
How many can I have? Let's say I have like five.
I can only have four. Okay, so what do you want to do?
What the fuck just happened? All right, so what do you want to do? Call me?
Got it. Throw it to me. What just happened? Like this. Like this.
Okay, what do you order me another one? I wasn't paying attention. I'm sorry.
Why did you die? All right, what does it want me to do?
What the fuck? That just makes you small? Okay. All right, give me something, right?
Give me an order something. What does it want me to do? Turn up the game audio.
It's already pretty high. Please don't. What did I have to do? He wanted me to...
I don't remember what he wanted me to do. Nitro dark matter.
No, you actually. All right, hold on.
Okay, what was the actual goal? He said, uh, order me. Order me. What was it?
To use the phone.
Oh, what? Oh, it broke. Rick, your computer's broken.
RAM, CPU, GPU. Got it. Okay, RAM goes in there. What is this? Crystal. It's broken. And then,
fuse. Okay, use that to get fuse. Don't forget he has RAM. Okay, so don't forget he has RAM
down there and down here. That's carrots. You just spit that back into my mouth.
I need to make a carrot hammer. Carrot hammer. I can use that portal machine.
What was the portal machine for? Use to get fuse. Wow. We're looking at Earth.
I need to charge the battery. With what? With a Super Nintendo game? How about one of you?
All right, charge the battery. Charging station or something in here.
Can't pass the IQ gear check. I'm actually just exhausted for some reason.
I don't know why. Charge it. That's pretty close to Jerma's son. I did it. This is stressing
me out. Goodbye. I got a battery for you. Battery. Open. I got him. Two fuses. Done.
It's in. All right, now I need a crystal. And I need to make a fucking carrot.
A carrot thing. Or a weird apple. Metal apple. How the hell am I gonna make a metal apple?
Is it metal? Well, this is a crystal. Do both these. Thank you. Oh, he's eating both. All right.
That looks pretty good. Nope. Not right. I need something else. Screwdriver. Hammer. Hammer.
Look out. All right. IP. Rick and Morty's Rick-ality.
Boot it up. Now, what do I, what do you want to do with this? Rick?
Okay. Do I get to choose? Oh. I thought I was gonna get a drop down. Into the toilet.
Look. I'm just a baby right now. I'm not even talking. I'm just a baby playing with fucking toys.
All right. Got it. Plunge the toilet. What, now what? Oh, come on. What? Lactatives.
I need like a, something to fix the toilet. Here we go. This is the toilet fixer thing.
Rick, I don't know. Do I do it? What the fuck is this?
This. Okay. It's almond. Oh, they're back.
Sure thing, Rick. They didn't get it.
Why can't you just tell me right now?
So, we're, we're.
There's nothing in there. Can I wear this?
I don't want it on. Do I have to charge this thing in the? Oh, God. Really? I, this is gonna,
I have to, I have to end the stream after this one. I'm running out of fumes. I don't
know why. I'm so tired. Look at how long this takes though. The fate of the universe is in my
fucking hand. One fuck up and his whole thing, the whole planet goes down. Look. Where, where's it?
What? What happened? I didn't draw. Help diamond. Help the, on, come on. I actually have to get
out of the headset. After I plug in the fucking car, I think it's time for me to go.
This is, if you're a fan of the show, this is probably really cool. And yeah, I know this is
the, this is the other VR game I played today, but don't worry, we're gonna come back.
I can't fucking hear anything. It's got, you know, I can always tell when it's time for me to
stop. When the, my, I'm sweating so much inside of my ears that this thing won't stay in.
It's oiled inside of here. It's oily. And it just keeps falling off. That's how I know it's
not. Okay. I'm holding this. Now what? Let's get the repair kit.
Curl 40. How does this thing work? Let's go check it out over here. No, what?
Incorrect combination. Please try a little harder. I need to, I need a match. So I green to green.
You're at green. It's only one match. It's a lift. Watch out. No more than five bands total.
No more than one blue and at least two reds. No. Do you call that fuckery? So there's one
red and here's two. I can't, at least one link with no duplicate colors. So that's this one.
No more than five bands total. One, two, three, four, five. And it's got, okay,
there's code zone here too. Hold on. One link ending in a number and one ending in a letter.
Oh my God. I need to like see what the, all right. So one has to end in a number,
one has to end in a letter. You got yellow, yellow, six, five, I'm done. Oh, oh my God.
I'm so tired. Did you enjoy your stay? I, Minecraft VR was really cool. That was cool too.
I'm just completely out of fucking steam. I just got nothing in tech. Oh, it's been,
yeah, this, this usually is when it happens around like four and a half hours,
just about like four to five hours. Oh yeah. How bad do I look today? Oh, all right. So
cold, but no, no cold right now. I look like fucking somebody diarrhea all over me,
but that's going to be it. I will see you guys. I'll see you guys in a few days because I'm
going to take the next few days off. I've got some things to take care of. I got some friends
that came up, so I'm going to see them for a little while. I'll see you guys real soon.
We'll do the bits. And as much as like the, I was taking the piss on the Minecraft thing,
but it was actually really, really cool. And it doesn't cost me anything either. That mod is free.
I usually, I typically like to go a little bit longer, but no, I got nothing. I'm not going
to pretend I do, you know? Anyways, let's go through the bits. Thank you for joining me,
everybody. When I get back, we got, I'll be back on probably Wednesday is when the next
stream will be. So Wednesday afternoon, we'll be back. Joel and I are going to do our
gamer competition in Pogo Stuck, Pogo Stick, whatever it's called, Pogo Stuck Rage,
Pogo Stick Rage. Joel, as in Varg Skeletor. I don't know if that's going to happen on
Wednesday, but we'll be talking back and forth about it. So we'll see. That's going
to happen probably next week if we can get our schedules correct. Five community subs,
thank you so much. That just came in right now. Those came in from Bingo Sunshine. Thank you so
much. That's a shitload of community subs. People give a lot of community subs on this channel.
Every stream is at least like 50. It's insane. But yeah, then there's more. I want to do
mine show, but that's going to be a whole stream. I really did not expect Minecraft VR
to take up three and a half hours of this stream, but it did somehow. But there are
plenty of things lined up. If you're taking off, I'll see you soon. See you on Wednesday.
Much love to you. And let's go back to the Cremator. Cremator a few hours ago gave five
dollars. Jerma, I see your place in memecraft. Good job. Oh, and I played. Oh, is this the
fire dude again? All right. Well, good luck. I don't, I've already said five piece. Thank
you for the five dollars though. Thank you. Alf the librarian for the five dollars. My
library filed for chapter 11 bankruptcy. That's not good. Your library data. Sorry to hear that.
We're liquidating our library because chat stormed in and bought all the good books.
Well, at least chat has some reading material. No. Hey, dork cube. Thanks for the 250.
Can't watch the stream right now, but I just want to say thank you for being a man of
your word. Even if chat kind of sort of cheated at pick Ross. I told you guys I was going to do
it. I'm a man of my word sometimes. I like to be a man of my word all the time. I try. Hey,
snoozing copter. Thanks for the 250 snoozing copter. Every time Jerma plays minecraft,
he gets the rarest spawns. I think I don't keep up with minecraft is the ocean thing
rare. But minecraft actually is kind of fun. I should play it again. Nevermind. What I
wanted to ask, I have trouble gaining weight. I'm 21, Jerma. I know you've struggled with
that too in the past. Or maybe you still do. Any advice? You even got the calorie drinks.
Careful with the calorie drinks. Those, they've got a lot of like mouth of dextrin in them,
which is just heavy sugar bullshit. They're full of almost cake batter. But when I was
working out when I actually cared about lifting and trying to be physically fit and all that
years ago, just, you just got to eat, especially if you have like a lightning
metabolism like I do. You just kind of have to, you have to eat high calorie foods,
but a good, you don't, you don't want to just dump empty calories in your body. You'll get
fat. You'll gain weight that you don't want if you eat, you know, 50, 60, 80 grams of
saturated fat. You could eat a whole pizza every day and you'd gain weight, but you'd,
it would be bad. It would be all over the place. But yeah, I eat a lot of tuna fish.
You have to really like it though. And I don't really, I'm not sure if like the medical
science there would tell you to eat a bunch of tuna anymore, but I wish you luck. It's a
journey. What are you doing? Skrillex tweeted you. What? Hold on, is this Skrillex?
The giant rat that makes all the rules. This is a real account? Why did you, why is this,
or is it weird that I automatically assume his account got hacked?
Like that, is that real? Wow. That's kind of, that's kind of crazy. I did. That's,
he's a fan. Well, if you're watching this Skrillex, that's high. That's,
I did not think I was going to get up in the morning and see that Skrillex has a tweet of the
rats song, but yeah, cool. Very cool. But anyway, respond to the tweet. Yeah, maybe later I'll like
do something, a reply or something. That's wild. Anyway, let's get, let's keep going with the
bits. Uh, door cube says, I can't want, thank you to the 250 door cube. Can't watch the
stream right now, but I just want to say thank you for being a man of your word. I just read
this. That's how slow I am right now. I am on, I, I am like, pull it up to the fucking gas
station, but that was snoozing copter and door cube. Uh, thank you code man for the 250.
Thanks code man. Be honest. You're, but you shower in your swim trunks, don't you?
No, I don't. I shower naked like every normal human being. Thank you. Zero giblets
for the bits. Thank you for screaming like the judge from Roger Rabbit being dipped when you
fell in the lava. Who showers naked? I'm going to take a bath today. That's what I'm doing.
Somebody said, look at the comments on that, on that thread. What is that fucking image?
What is that like third image down? It's just, which one? The one of my face with
teeth stretched out and my face squished in. Show, show. I mean, here's the tweet. Just go,
just look down. But thank you. Thank you some guy for the five bucks. And it's a,
it's a YouTube link. I'm back for the first time in forever with another meme video.
I'm still too lazy to edit together an actual good Phantom meme. So here's another place
holder. I actually have to change so I can see this. It's going through the vibe still.
And make it so it's coming through the actual desktop and not the headphones on the bind.
You guys are fucking, you guys are fucking too much. How's that? Can I hear? I can hear now.
I say can, can you hear though? That's important. Speakers. There they are. Testing.
There we go. All right. So this is a meme video. I wonder what kind of meme it is.
There's this dog, dog them style T-Rex. Is that, I don't,
somebody came in and said, did he play nothing but Minecraft? The unfortunate answer is yes.
And then I played Rick and Morty. I thought Rick, I, oh, how many people left during that?
I wanted to have five minutes later, like 200, about 200. I can't believe like this
four or five thousand fucking people. That's, you guys are two kinds. Seriously. But thank
you for the meme video some guy. Thank you. Oh, we have a Jane Dole Walken,
$15 from Jane Dole Walken. They say making evil meals, making evil meals.
I'm not sure that's a reference to, but thank you, Jane Dole Walken. End the stream
so I can watch the VOD faster. Not much longer. We're only going to get a few more.
And by a few more, I mean like 10 maybe. Here we go. Jerma lied about Minecraft VR,
gave $10 and they say, first of all, thank you for the $10. I ain't changing it. You lied
somehow. I just don't know how yet. Upon further investigation, you did not reenact
JermaCraft The Adventure Begins episode one. You paraphrased it at best. I called the police to
ask and they said you lied. I, how am I supposed to memorize the entire first three minutes of that
video? I've seen it. I, I know it kind of. Half of chat has it memorized. You lived it.
Yeah, I lived it. I didn't see lots of fails. I didn't say lots of fails, lots of triumphs.
That's not good. But thank you, Jerma lied about Minecraft for the $10 and for the
community subs as well. Thank you. Thank you. Al the chemist, Al the chemist for the $3. Hey
man, I'm pretty fucking drunk right now, but just want to let you know that I think you're
an incredibly funny and interesting person and you bring me such joy when you stream.
Thank God you stream later now. I can actually watch your stuff.
LOL. I'll send more bits later because I bought the 500 pack, but next time the message will
be less coherent because I'm still drinking. We'll fuck. Let's see. We'll see. That's Al
the chemist. That was about two hours ago. Thank you so much. I'm honored that you think
that I'm interesting. Thank you as always. Thank you so much. He's drunk so he doesn't
mean it. No, he's drunk. So he does mean it. That's the reverse of what you're talking
about. Uh, Freudian weapon gave $10. They said this stream made it makes me really
want to pick my Minecraft back up again. Good way to de-stress. Yeah, we caught that
one earlier, but it's true. You can't really just hang out and hit some trees. I had it.
That was, I thought this was a great, this is a good stream. I liked just kind of
experiencing that again, even though I wish I could have done it a little longer,
maybe go and explore some more, but it was scary in VR. It was good. It was a lot of
fun. Highly recommend it. And if you have a Vi that's free, the VR portion at least.
Al the chemist, an hour later than his first message. Thank you for the, I mean, this is
under the bit minimum here, but I'm curious. I need to know. This is the second cheer from
my drunk Memei. Dude, I hope you had fun. Minecraft is def a game that has its merits.
Hope you give a modded Minecraft to try sometime. That'd be cool. Have a good night.
That's, no, that's, that's very coherent actually. Now under the bit reading about
unbelievable. No, it's not like one of a, it's not like, I don't like Minecraft. I give it
shit, but you know, I'm just kidding around. Oh, it's a kid's game. No, it's an any,
anybody can enjoy that experience. I'm just fucking around. I hope you know that guys.
And now he's backtracking. That's, I'm the master of backtracking. I say something
and then I think, eh, probably shouldn't have said it four hours later. I go, Hey, by the way,
but thank you Al the chemist. Thank you smelly boy for the 250. This is actually horrible.
Please go back to Minecraft. Was it Rick and Morty? Was it the Rick and Morty game?
They probably should have just stayed in Minecraft for another 30 to 40 minutes and
do the whole four, four and a half hours in Minecraft. No, I blame part of that on me
because I wasn't really talking. It wasn't really saying much. Blasted. When I get tired,
when I, you know, start to slow down, I shut off and just, what's that? Oh, okay. Yeah.
And that's why I decided it's like, it's probably time to stop. Demonic cucumber. Thank
you. They say I witnessed one of the rarest events in the game. Lightning will randomly
spawn maybe a skeleton trap horse with a chance of 0.75 to 1.5% chance on easy. It's a, wow,
and I got four at once. And there's a 1.5 to 4% chance on normal and a 6.7% chance
or 2.8% chance on hard. On top of that, skeleton horses have the rarest spawn rates,
making the chances of you seeing that less than 1%. In fact, I'd wager that you are
the first person to ever experience that on a VR live stream. You've literally become
a part of Minecraft history. All right. Hey, it was crazy. That's why I didn't want to just,
I was going to move on after I got out of the dungeon. And then what did he do?
I got on the horse and I rode it for a little bit. I died a few times. And then the first,
the last stream, I got a woodland mansion on spawn. Why is your Minecraft, why is your luck so good?
Didn't you guys ever hear the character sheet that Star made for me? I've said it before.
10 charisma, 10 luck, zero in every single other category. I would say I have,
I got to give myself at least a few points in strength. You know, I'm not just going to have
zero strength, but I don't know. Sometimes there's, I don't know how. 2012.
Seven strength, two intelligence. What is the intelligence point level for at least an eighth
grader? I have an, at least an eighth to 10th grade intelligence to give me some credit.
Four, I'll take a four or five and it are apps. Definitely. I'll take a four or five
in intelligence. Anything below eight is an animal, is animal level. What? But if that is true,
if that really was one of the rarest Minecraft events you could ever see, I, that's cool.
I'm happy to have been able to show it then. Hey the Jack, thanks for the $5. Everyone in
chat only hates the Rick and Morty VR because of their low IQ scores. Rick and Morty. Thank
you. Get dunked on. Hey Jerma, I did a rat's mashup. Really hope you like it. Rats mashup.
This sounds elaborate.
I'll just show it. Might as well just put it on the screen, right?
This is the gentleman of the jury.
What is hard for others?
I'm sure you'll get it. Speed it up. Speed it up.
Special day. Shut up idiot. Come on Michael, you ruin your fucking birthday every year for
everybody else. That we get it. It's my birthday today. Not anybody else's. It's my birthday.
Calm down. Do you hear what they just said? Now hold on just a second. Pause the movie.
Hip-hop. Just dance together as a family for once.
Rats. Rats. We are the rats. Celebrate another one of our big backs. Michael, it's your birthday today.
Take it actually. We are the rats. Michael, it's your birthday today.
Come on then. It's your birthday today.
Which is iPod conversion.
Rats. Rats. Celebrate another one of our big backs. Michael, it's your birthday today.
Welcome to the dog camp. Trust you're all right.
In that case, walk away.
It's pretty good filler content, yeah.
I'm waiting for you shit to find a dirty toothbrush.
This is just to make sure you understand the story.
What is this voice for this character by the way?
I know exactly who we can sell these to.
Rats. Rats. We are the rats. Celebrate another one of our big backs. Michael, it's your birthday today.
Wait, what's this? Who's this in the car? What TV show is this?
It's fucking birthday every year for everybody else.
We get it. I went through so much trouble to get you these rats.
Wow. Shocking. That's a real shock right there. That was ridiculous. That was very, very,
very good. Thank you so much for that. That was very well put together. That was get dunked on,
by the way. It was absolutely perfect. Thank you so much. Get dunked on. Glad we got to see it on
stream. And then we had three dollars from al store H2O. Thank you for the three bucks.
Hey German, for the first time since the start of making videos for fun,
I'm trying to record an audio track for a video. The thing is I don't think my voice
is pleasant enough and I don't think I can physically convey the emotion needed for the
video. What do you do to get the right voice and emotion for your jokes and videos?
And is it okay to just give up and try to work without one if I can't make it work?
Thanks and I hope you have a great night. Well, there's three or four kind of just probably
two or three actual questions in here. And the first one I would tell you is,
if you're talking about recording voice lines, in almost every single thing you've ever heard
me say, all the voices you've ever heard were based on somebody in real life or somebody that
I've heard before. Grandpa is actually based on the grandpa voice, this one here. Grandpa,
this one, is based on my actual fucking grandmother. That's how my grandmother talked.
And I would just imitate all her friends. That is my grandmother's voice. And I think
a lot of it comes from observing and imitating, whether it's somebody that's a celebrity or a
friend of yours that talks in a certain way, has certain cadences. Picking up on mannerisms
and cadences is actually potentially more important than having a voice sound different,
especially if you're trying to do voices. But for the second part of that,
it just comes to practice. And look, I'll be real. I'll be completely real.
You see, you mentioned, is it okay to try to work without one or to just give up if I can't
make it work? If everybody has something they can do, right? And even if, let's just say,
for instance, if you're really into voice work, you really love voice acting,
you love cartoons, you love voice over artists, you live and breathe in something
you fucking love so much. There are other jobs in that industry that aren't necessarily
recording the voice work. You don't have to be the one that's producing the sound out of your
mouth. You can be an engineer, you can be a writer, you can be an audio technician,
you can even work in the field. And I think a lot of people maybe get a little caught up in
needing to do that one specific thing, right? When that one specific thing has a lot of
branches with a ton of leaves on them that are different things to do in that field that
will scratch the same itch from doing the thing that you really wanted to do in the first place.
But that's not to say to, oh, just give up. Give up on your dreams. No. Give them a try.
Go for it. But there's more than just that one thing. There's a lot more. I hope that
answers your question. Look, if people gave up on their dreams, we wouldn't have
half of the shit that we have in society today. Half of the stuff that we like,
that we all know, that we care about, probably wouldn't even exist at all.
If everybody was like, nah, you know what, forget it. But thank you so much. I wish you
the best of luck. That was Al Storr. Thank you, Al Storr. I also have to remember that
half of following your dreams is luck. Yeah, it's a lot of factors. It's a complex,
complicated thing. And that is trying to live up to your dream. Because there are so many
outside factors that are in play that you might not even be aware of. That luck plays a very,
very large role. Being at the right place, in the right moment, talking to the right person,
somehow being in the right place at the right time. It means a lot.
Yeah, you got it right there. Luck, hard work, talent, more. It's a complex mixture of a
bunch of different things. But not necessarily when you're following a dream. You're usually
following it because you have a plan in mind. You have factors that can influence your path
towards that dream. Yeah, but I can tell you right now as a 33 going on 34 year old, plans
always change. They just do. You might have the end goal in your eyes at what you want to
do, but the plans are always changing. Stuff is always changing in a plan, especially in a life
goal. Because the way that I had my plan set out and the thing that I really cared about
has warped and changed directions and moved around. It's the goal is still there. It's
still there, but that path changes. And you might not even know you're on a different one.
You might be doing something that you don't even understand until years later is a branch
of a path that you were on in the beginning. Be flexible. Yeah, that's a really good point.
Will I play Monster Rancher VR when it comes out? Yeah, whenever that is. You could use that
anywhere. Whatever your dream is. Whatever you want to do. Whatever the message here was about
voice work. But apply that to anything. Apply that to anything that you want to do in your
life. But thank you Al Store. Good luck. And get dunked on again. We just touched upon the
video that we just watched. You gave another five, six, seven almost dollars here. Thank you
for that awesome video. Hey, Freudian Weapon, thanks for the 250. I say to Jerma Hart. Thank
you. SereneFP, thanks for the 250. You know, Jerma started regularly watching your streams
exactly a year ago during your speed run of Monster Rancher 2. Wanted to thank you for
being one of the few streamers who can genuinely make me laugh. Yeah, I'm fucking grateful
and thankful that you came. I'm glad you think the things I say are worth watching.
Really appreciate that. And you bring up Monster Rancher. I actually think I'm going
to go back to Monster Rancher 2. I have this weird itch to play it. I don't know why.
For some reason. It's just I feel like I want to do it again. Hey, Magellan, thanks
for the five dollars. Had a great time tonight, Jerma. Glad you decided to stick out Minecraft
VR for a bit longer and make a session out of it. Definitely seems like you enjoyed it.
Thank you for all the laughs and wonderful times you bring the community and I. Have
fun with your friends in the next few days and rest up from all the VR. Thank you.
I will have a few days here where I'm going to take the days, you know. It's been a
little nicer. It was really beautiful out today. Get some sun. Hang out with some friends.
And I got a little bit of work I can get done as well in a couple of days. A little
bit of not stream or video related type stuff. There's things that I've kind of
been on the back burner that I have to get done. But thank you. Let me add a Dorkcube.
Thanks to the 250 Dorkcube. You're getting a rare spawn in Minecraft despite your love
hate relationship with the game reminds me of that Futurama episode where the professor
accidentally disproos evolution. Yeah. That was a great show. This was such a perfect moment.
You called exactly what was going to happen. What do you mean? What did I do? Oh no.
Where's my house? Like that was going to do anything. What's one of the four horsemen
doing here? What? It really did look like the four horsemen. That wave though. That's like
that had a giant lollipop. Get away from me. Get away. He summoned it. I have expected
Metallica to start playing. That's so funny. But thank you. Thank you. That was Demonic
Cucumber. Thank you. Anything else show official for the five bucks. You're the man.
I've been working on a new Vegas mod for you and wanted to say thank you for the inspiration.
All the models and stuff I've been working on are in the creative channel on Discord.
I'm not finished with the mod but I wanted to tell you that. My life has been busy
and stressful in the mod and streams is the one thing I've been excited about.
I can't wait to see what you come up with. That's somebody making a mod. That's awesome.
I sincerely fucking look forward to what it comes up. Thank you. Anything show. Anything
else show official for the five bucks. Keep us updated. Keep us posted on it.
The Jack. Thanks for five dollars, Jack. Do you actually yourself like the silly memes
from years past that we still use or are so detached to how you are now?
No, I mean, all jokes aside, they're locked away inside my heart there in the chest
pump thing that puts blood through into your brain and into your body.
So no, I don't hate old references and memes because at some point that means that this
is like a living breathing community, right? That makes me happy to know that. That people
are using references that from years ago or things that they're coming up with. That means
that we have a great community. That means we have a very active, lively community.
But thank you, the Jack. I do not hate the memes. No. And thank you to Al Store again.
Four dollars and 50 cents for Al Store. This is compensation for accidentally putting
in so much in one message. I already spent like 25 to 30 hours on a video so the voice work
might be supplementary and I think I'll be proud of it regardless. But I still needed to hear
what you said and I can't thank you enough. You're always so comforting and practical with
life advice. I really wish that whatever you do, it's something that you like doing.
Something that you can enjoy. Something that you can work on
and be like, that was good. I liked that. I enjoyed that. Thank you so much Al Store.
And with that, we are going to run the credits. All the new subs and all the old subs
coming on the screen right now. I will see you all on Wednesday. So three, so four days from
now. Yeah, one, two, three. I'll see you on the 20th. I'm going to go take a bath and get
some food. Have a great rest of your beginning of your weekend, right, Saturday. Still fairly
early on Saturday Pacific. Hopefully you guys are going to enjoy your St. Patrick's Day,
right? That's today, right? St. Patrick's Day is today, right? No, it's tomorrow.
So happy St. Patrick's Day for all of you. Let's celebrate tomorrow. It's Sunday afternoon
here. Well, there you go. Happy St. Patrick's Day. Highly recommend looking to the Deluxe
Audio Strap for the Vive. Makes tightening it up a lot easier and the headphones are on
ears so no worrying about them slipping out. Yeah, but it's also my problem too. I do one
earphone because I lost my mind and I can't find it. No, I, for some reason, 10-15 years
ago, I came to this assumption that I cannot do two headphones in. And even with in-ear
back, you know, the open back ones, it still just makes me feel claustrophobic. I don't
know why. I'm just a weirdo. And then finally we had a Leos BM came in right now with
three bucks, three dollars. I just resubbed. Can't donate on mobile, but I thought I'd
ask, I'd like to ask this here. I've always liked to do impressions of people, like
you said, and seeing you as an inspiration. I know I want to do something with that
talent and streaming seems great, but I feel like it's too late to get into it at this
point. Do you think that being a comedy streamer is something that I could viably
pursue? Thanks. It's hard to answer that question because content and what people
want to see and what people watch, it's hard to say, hey, that material is going
to work. That material won't work. You need to do this for material. It's a hard
question to answer because on one hand you have the true just reality of Twitch,
right? And that's thousands and thousands and thousands of broadcasters all at the
same time, all going, all trying to get people on their streams and hey, come on
to come to my stream. Hang on to my stream. Look what I'm doing. I'm doing
something here. I'm playing this game. You like that game, right? It's a lot.
So trying to differentiate yourself and put yourself out there as it's very
difficult to do, but that doesn't mean that you shouldn't try to do it. Just
make sure you be realistic. Make sure that you are doing it because you want to
and it's something that you want to do. It's something that you care about,
not something that you're doing because you think you have to. And you can take
that last conversation we had about it and apply it to this too. You need to
enjoy it regardless of how many people watch. Yeah, you have to just...
When I made my first five YouTube videos, I just was doing them because I
wanted to do them. That seems like fun. That seems interesting. That seems like
something I think is really cool. That's something I want to try to do.
The only rule is you can't stream when Jerma is streaming. You dig?
Now it's all about the money. Now the thing is though, you'll never know unless you try.
You can't fail unless you try. I was thinking about that, but I didn't. I think
I just would fail at it. Just do it. There's no reason not to try it.
And networking goes a long way. Hanging out, trying to help out in other people's streams,
finding similar interests and collaborating. Only if people want to collaborate. You never want
to throw yourself into a situation where you're like, hey, what's going on? How are you? I see
that you do this too. Let's do a video tomorrow. Which is natural. The only way to get
up is to fall down sometimes. Go watch my first 50 YouTube videos.
And tell me that I didn't figure out more things to try and did some things wrong.
Maybe I shouldn't have uploaded that video because was that video good?
My latest videos from the last two years ago, you learn. You grow. And you keep trying.
Go watch my latest videos from two and a half years ago. But I wish you the best of luck.
Is it Leos or Leo? It's probably Leo SSBM. I think I called you Leos.
Yeah, but you can't figure out what you want to do until you try to start doing it in the first
place. Everybody has this big painting that they have. And there's a giant canvas on the wall.
It's an empty canvas. And it's just sitting up there. And it's, I can't wait for this
painting. It's going to be, look at this fucking huge painting. Oh, there's the Mona Lisa
is going to be there flying. And over there, there's a cheetah that's going to be over there.
There's a jungle. But it's like, you got to start painting. Yeah, yeah, I know. But look
at the cheetah. The cheetah is coming out there from the jungle. And then you go and you start
on the cheetah. And everyone's like, all right, man, I can't wait to see the huge
15 by 15 foot mural on the wall. And then you start painting the fucking cheetah portion.
Maybe you start painting the tree. And it's a little bit of brown paint. And it looks like
a little smudge. Eventually that little smudge turns into the bark. And that bark turns into
the branches. That branches turns into the tree. And then that tree turns into the cheetah.
And then the cheetah turns into the Mona Lisa. You have to start painting. Somebody said,
you lost me. Point is, everybody has a big picture that they want to paint. Well,
maybe not everybody. But a lot of people have this big painting. And you have to close
down a little. And remember, you have to start, you have to start painting that painting.
And it's not going to look like the painting that you think it is until it's done,
potentially months or years later. Start small and put realistic goals in front of yourself.
Just use a spray can. But that's my time. I will see you guys on Wednesday. Have a great
rest of your weekend. Take care, all of you. See you on Wednesday. Ta ta. Goodbye.
Oh, and uh, what's the way he'll somebody's birthday?
Happy birthday. Happy birthday. Was it bath? Happy birthday tomorrow on St. Patrick's Day.
Have a good one. See you Wednesday.