So I just recently beat Firewatch, and I came across a feature that I haven't really seen
very many people talk about. There's a disposable camera in this game that allows you to take
pictures. You can take a picture of whatever you want. It never leaves your inventory,
and you have it throughout the whole game. But the cool feature is they actually ask you if you want
to develop those photos, and they will mail them to you. And that's exactly what I did. They got
here today, and I kind of want to just go through them with you guys, like I thought it'd be a really
neat idea to look at them together and see what I took pictures of. Now, it has been a while,
so I don't actually know or remember what's on these. Hey, your memories have arrived, huh?
That's real cute. Photo dome. Look at that. Okay, let's open them up. Let's see what we got.
First one is the sky. Skies can be cool sometimes, I guess. That's a rock. A pretty interesting
growth of a rock. The way that it was growing out of the ground was pretty cool. I think that's the
inside of a bush. Yeah, that's the inside of a bush. I think I was trying to take a picture of a...
These are fucking terrible. Seriously. What? Did I take these? What even is this? Is that a thumb
print? Oh, there we go. There's a little selfie there, you know, selfie action. Sometimes you
gotta take one. Okay, that's a private one. That's gonna go in a different pile. It's gonna go in
the privacy pile. Hey, a fence. Take a look at that. Interesting, right? It's a... What am I even
taking a picture of here? Hey, here you go. I got a picture of the toilet, you know. Oh, this one's
great. I like this one. This one's like, there was a rock on a stump, and I thought like, whoa, that's
such an interesting rock. Like, that's so odd. Why would there be a rock on a stump like that?
Uh, I don't know why. There is a box up there, I guess. Ooh, here we go. Here we go. I remember
this tree. I remember saying to myself, man, it's got such interesting moss growing on the side. I
gotta get a picture with it. So there you go. There it is. Privacy pile. Damn it. What the fuck?
Who am I? I don't know who the fuck this is. I have no idea. I've never met this person before
in my entire life. Another rock. Good one. Oh, look, another rock. Oh, cool. And it's a sunset
that you could have taken a picture of too. Oh, good rock in the way. Come on. Come on. You know
what? I apologize for this. Oh, my God. That's somebody's asshole. I hope it's not mine. No,
that's mine. That's mine. Do something cool. Oh, look at that. I did something cool, guys.
Hey, Ma. Don't look in the trash.