Got Homa, you got Mod, you got Bot, all of them. They're all in the same place at the same time,
they're all driving fucking cars around. That's the plan for tonight, how you guys doing?
Simpsons hit and run, uh, got it to work. There was a theory that I might not have gotten it to
work, but we delayed, and uh, kill code came through with the, some files, some patches,
and I was like, well would you look at that, so we can play it. I do, uh, I own it on
PlayStation 2, but I figured try to get it on PC to work, right? So that's what we're doing,
give me a minute, I'm just gonna sip my coffee and make sure I have my OBS configured. Gonna
see you guys real soon. That just kind of jumped out at you, didn't it? Sorry about that.
Sorry, you know what I wish, here's the thing, you know what I would love? I would
love if OBS had a feature where I could, like, when I activate a source, right, and maybe they do,
I, hold on, turn that down for a second. If I could like have a way, there's a plug-in where
I can make it so every time I activate a source, it slowly comes up from zero.
That might be hard to do, but man, I wish I could do that, because some of these games,
they just blow your ears out. But, uh, here it is. Simpsons hit and run working on PC.
This is actually on PC and there are, like, a bunch of mods and shit that you need to have
to get this to work. So it is possible. I don't have any, like, funny mods. This is not, like,
a funny mod thing. This is, like, get the game to work effectively. Funny mod thing. So,
are you ready? How does he, how do we, how do we get the audio? No, it's not a funny mod. Sounds
pretty good. Louder. Kind, it's, it's kind of loud. How's that? That's probably better.
So, uh, you can still hear me. What have we got? So we got, and plus I can have a controller
plugged in. That's the best part. All right. I, people have been waiting for this for a
long time. I don't see enough hype in the chat right now. You know, I want to, I want
you all to spell it out in one gigantic letter. You know, everyone, you all have to work on
H and then P and then E. The one resident sleeper.
That you stand out so much. If you're resident sleeper-ing right now, you are.
I can sit and look at that toy train that guy's got there. Let's go. There's even 3D
animations. Oh God damn it. It's not that. Turn it up. Why is it so low? I can't bump it.
We'll fix it. This reminds me of when, remember when they did that episode where Homer went
into the 3D world and it was incredibly off-putting? All right. So let's, let's move
around. Talk to Marge. Let's jump. Let's move. Let's sprint. This actually doesn't
look that bad. How's that? The audio sounds like it's okay right now. How do I turn it
up a little bit? Voice and sound. Music a little bit. Yeah. Is that better?
That sounds all right. All right, Marge, what do you got? Is this fully voice acted?
Homie, somebody ate every dessert in the house. I need you to run to the store and pick up
some of that ice cream with the miniature pies in it. Homie, you have to go to the store and
pick up that ice cream. Hire me. Hire me. Do it. Go to the quickie mart and purchase some ice
cream and cola. It's crashing time. Uh, Homer, that's not a nice thing to say.
It's crashing time. Drive to the quickie mart. This is like a, can you crash into people? No.
This is like a licensed TV video game. You actually can run. That's it. I can't believe
that. That I don't believe it. I don't believe you can do that. What? I thought they were going
to jump out of the way. I'm very surprised. All right, drive to the quickie mart and I'm
getting points for this. All right. Okay. I got my controller set up. What is this for?
Oh, wait. Oh, this is, there's a coin. All right. This is a puzzle.
I'm getting on the roof. I can do the sprint, right? Oops. I might have to change some button
configurations here because right now B is run. That B and A don't work together is run and then
jump. I have it on like the dark soul settings there. Hold on. What does this do? Oh, I can
kick. All right. This is kind of cool. Who made this game? Can I just vandalize? From
software I made this game. Now imagine if they did.
Hey, hey. Okay, hey. Oh, boy. I need to get myself some ice cream and some extra cola.
Hire me. I'm available. Wait, what's this? New shirt. Oh, wait. No.
That's definitely the best one. So this is what you do with coins, huh? Okay. How do I
talk to Millhouse? Hey, Millhouse. Don't you have some problems, Millhouse? Hey, here. I'll help
you. I'll help you. Why is he Canadian? Now let's go back. I love how it tells you. Okay.
I have a handbrake. Why am I playing the shittiest games?
Hold on. I'm going to give you a quick story. This is one of the most requested games
on this whole channel. I think people have been telling me to play this game
through messages and in chat for two years. So I, it's, come on. One guy said that. Well,
I have to comment on it. All right, hold on. Can you dive out of the car? No, you can't.
All right. You can't kill Mark. All right. I got what you need.
Uh, raise principal Skinner to the school and give Lisa her science project. Why do I,
why do I have to race the principal? Collect Lisa's science project.
It's all right. Drive to the school. Where's principal Skinner? Apparently I just have to
get there for, wait, what's that Krusty Krab thing? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stay on the road. Oh, there they are. Okay. That person just tried to kill me.
That person tried to kill me. Two out of two. How do you like it? Can I run them off the
road?
Are we going to get that all game? I think we're going to get that all game, aren't we?
Whoa, into the school. Wait, through what door?
I beat him, right? The front door. Can I, I'm inside. Oh, there you are.
Thanks for bringing me the model of a digestive system. Where's the garb ladder?
What's this? Go to Shelbyville and steal me some math books.
Shouldn't you be in class? Leave me alone. I'm calibrating the protractors. Oh, that's
the principal's office. Please, I'm busy installing asbestos right now. What? That's
not good. Uh, I want that one, so that's 125 points. Why would you install, install
asbestos in a school? Oh, I didn't know that. I thought I was moving the, I was
moving the fucking, I thought I was moving the bookcase. I didn't know I was pulling
the fire alarm. All right, let's go. Press all the actions. Are there more than one?
No, that's it. I got his. Go to Shelbyville and steal me some math books.
Oh wait, no, no. It's like a, uh, it's like a point and click adventure game.
You can press every button. I think that's it. There's a lot of lore. That's cool.
What's the dice for? Who are you? Race for wager race. Entry fee 20. Time to beat 315.
Best time, difficulty medium. Complete an entire lap before time runs out.
An entire lap. I got 60 bucks for doing this? I guess I have to do it before I can talk
about how I did it. This is a medium. Just don't run into anything. Just do it gently
and get it correct. No! I'm fine. I'm thinking, I got it. What the fuck was that? Wait, what?
Oh, that's not it. I thought that was a complete lap per second. Okay. Well, I don't,
I thought that was it. I thought that was like the end. What was that big circle?
This is cool. I don't think I'm going to get it now. This car is going to explode.
I still might get it. He's going to rage a lot this stream. What? It's the Simpsons.
How can you get mad at Homer Simpson? Am I going to eat my own words in like 45 minutes?
All right, this is a little road. If I bump into anybody else, I'm going to explode.
Use the shortcuts. Uh, I think I want to just try to win the first race ever.
Is that it? Oh my god. I'm almost there. I'm really close. Come on. It's right there.
I did it. No, I didn't. What the fuck? What? I'm not going to get it. I'm not going to get it.
I'm not going to get it. I'm not going to get it. I got it. No, I didn't. No, I didn't. What's
in? Oh, I can do that. I can do that. I know I can do that. Because I didn't know that the
blue circle wasn't the end of the race. So I like turned around and I'd run into the wall.
You didn't use any of the shortcuts. Well, no, this car is like all fucked up. I can't do it
yet. What is this? Pay and spray? Well, I need to like drive my car into the garage.
Kick the kids into the road. Um, easy psycho. Holy shit. Ooh, how much is this? Can I like
repair this? Can you come and get me? I'll pay you in back rubs. Who did I just call to come
get me? Who just came to get me? I just called me. Well, somebody said that you can go to the
phone. I mean, I see a giant wrench. So let me pick that up. That's okay. You pick up
the giant wrench. The vibration tickling my feet. I wish I had a dog with a saddle.
All right. What do you, what do you got Marge? Oh my go talk to Ned Flanders. He seems
miffed and PO'd. Why me? I'm the world's greatest neighbor. I even have a mug to that effect.
Cone, the cone, the phone is for when the car is completely destroyed. All right, so go to
Flanders house and talk to Ned, but first I'm going to take some pizza coins. What else is
back here? There's a lot of shit back here. What is this? Buzz, a buzz card. Hmm. Uh,
okay, I just turned on the grill. What is this shit in my backyard?
I can go on the swing. No, I guess you can't go on the swing. Interesting. Okay. So I want to get up
here. Probably have to go on the roof somehow. There's probably a drop down from the roof.
There's a, okay, there's a double jump. I did not know that. Why would I know? Why would
I think there was a double jump? There's a double jump. Oh, I can tell this on the
internet. You mean I gotta get more? All right, let's go to Flanders. Please don't sue. Hey,
Flanders. All in a dither, Homer. So many of my possessions have disappeared. I called the
police to find the culprit. My lawnmower, my cooler, my lawn chair, a family portrait,
even Rod's inhaler. What kind of sick individual would take this stuff? Oh no. I borrowed
all of Flanders stuff. Quick. Think of an excuse to get out of here. Uh, excuse me. I
think I have to go shuck some corn. All right. Collect all six of Ned's lost items before the
time runs out. Get into your vehicle. So I have to go find all of Ned Flanders' stuff.
Find his tuxedo. Do I have to get out of the car? No, I don't. Okay. Find the lawnmower.
Uh, I can't, I can't talk to you right now. Whoever the fuck is calling me.
Flanders cooler. I gave it to Barney. I'm trying to pick up Flanders fucking toys.
Damn it. Fucking cell phone. Give it to me. No, give me the cooler. I gave you for your
birthday. Well, Flanders wants it back. Now what will I use for a toilet?
I need the lawn chair. Oh God. Why? We're get out of the way.
Okay. I just killed him. I don't, there's a bunch of shit. Oh, wait. I don't care about
anything else. Just give me the coins. Holy shit. That's more money than I've ever seen.
I got plenty of time. I can finally, I can buy the huge fat homer outfit. I can't wait.
Okay. Last one. Now where did I leave Rod stupid in here?
All right. That was pretty cool. What a classic game, huh?
What are the vibrations tickling my feet?
I love sensuality. I return to stuff before the cops find me sitting around talking to
myself. Before the cops? Is it the ever wanted level in this game? No, it's not.
Is there? There is. How the hell does that work?
Homer is a criminal.
Well, hi, Italy. Hello, Homer. See? Thanks, neighbor. I'm kidding. Let's not be doing
it for real. Cool. All right. Hold on. I wanted to see if I could, let me just look at
stuff. There's money everywhere. Let me just examine people's backyards. What's in
Flanders backyard? Tire swing. That's kind of cool. You get like a bunker back here?
What the hell is this? What the hell was that? Was that some camera? That was weird.
All right. I'm just gonna bank all my money. What? Is it all? I'm gonna be honest with you
guys. Now, don't take me as a bad person or an idiot or something, but
I think there's only like six episodes of The Simpsons that I've ever really actually
watched from start to finish. I don't get any of this shit. I've seen, I saw the original
Treehouse of Horror and then the episode where Maggie's a murderer. I don't know
any, I don't even know what their last name is. There's a lot of references.
Wow, I need a disco nap. Wait, what? That's it. What do you mean? That's a, that's a spoiler.
I thought that was like the thing that they all talk about every episode. What? Wait,
I, that's, this show's like 25 years old. And today's your workplace evaluation with
Mr. Smithers. Only one person can help me. Lenny. The Simpsons, The Simpsons is not like
a movie that came out last weekend. Oh my God. Did you just really spoil an episode
from 1996? I want to look around. Yeah, and guess what, guys? Ross doesn't date Phoebe.
That happens, it happened in like 94. That's not even The Simpsons. Wait, that's not The
Simpsons. I gotta talk to Lenny. Ross isn't, what if somebody was watching Friends for the
first time? I mean, Friends has been, I don't know, I'm making that up. I made
it everything up.
I completely mean you will need The Plow King. Purchases from Barney at the gasoline
station for 150 coins. Use phone boost to access vehicles you already own.
150 coins. You're killing me here.
Just don't shoot me with that dark gun.
Whatever. Holy shit. All right, that was, uh, F1 is show stats, but I don't have that in the
controller, so let's do it. Top this. Handling. Yeah. Uh, purchase it. There goes 100 hit the
coins. Destroy Smithers' car before it gets to the power plant. Get into your car. Is
there a way I can turn the camera? I feel like I can't. Is it the mouse?
All right, we got all these timed missions. God damn it. Well, this thing handles like
shit. Oh, this is hard to control. I want the pink family donut car.
All right, looking for the shortcut.
Oh, I wanted a peanut. Oh, that was not a shortcut. Or maybe it was.
All right, destroy Smithers.
Kind of have to get some speed here. Uh, look at that right there. I want to go over that.
I think I just have to ram him. Yeah. Right into the wall.
Oh, that was a lot of damage. That was a lot of damage. Perfect. He's dead. Yeah,
spoiler alert, guys. Sorry. This is where, like, you kill Smithers' best friend Smothers,
whatever his name is. Why is he still? Uh, why is he not exploded? See? Spoiler.
Streamers, Smothers, Smothers. What's that? Did I have a horn? Yeah. Spoilers. Hey, who's that?
Why does it have a money symbol? Duff truck. Oh, this guy's just, you just sell trucks.
No, I don't need anything from you right now. A lot of random people.
Cool. Jeremiah, I have not watched this part of the game yet. Please stop.
By the way, Santa. I don't even mind.
Is this a blind run? Yeah.
Go to the gas station. Get me some of those cardboard tubes. You know them.
I'm gonna build me some indoor plumbing. When you finish with that, knock down all
them tobacco plants so the youngins can clean them up for market.
Find cardboard tubes and collect the tobacco harvest for Cletus in under 230.
Get into your vehicle. This is not the kind of car I think I need for this.
That's the kind of car that I need for this. That one right there.
Can you drop it off? Actually, that'd be all right. I snuck through there. I'm good.
Where are you trying to get me to rip around? That guy's got low gravity on.
That guy's flying around through space. I had nothing to do with that.
Through here. This thing is so slow. Can I break through this?
Oh my god. That's not a shortcut. Okay, I can't just like break through the doors.
I see this. You get points for this.
One minute to... that was a school bus.
Is this a shortcut?
Why is that on fire? Shortcut? Collect the... Oh, I have 25 seconds to get this shit.
Should I get out of the car? I'm getting out.
Oh! That... no, that's not it. What? Oh my god.
Holy shit. I need another car. Yeah, I can't do it with this fucking thing.
How do I get it? I gotta like... I gotta... how do I just cancel this?
You just steal cars? You can actually just steal a car.
What? I didn't think this was possible either. Wait, what? You can steal cars?
It's actually just GTA. All right, well how do I restart this?
Homer really is a fucking criminal. Well, now I got the school... oh, I blocked off the road. Hold on.
I mean, this is worse than I'm in the school bus. Actually, the school bus is probably a little
bit faster. I made it on my own roadblock. I think I can still get it. I think I'll be all
right. Don't get out of the car. As long as I get back there with like two minutes.
Well, that's why... that's what happens when you look at the chat for no reason.
All right, give me a better car. I'm gonna restart it with a better car.
Come here. Telephone. Uh, damage. Four percent. Thank you. All right, this is my real car.
All right, let's go. Homer Simpson did his own mocap for this game.
Really? That's interesting. That is pretty interesting. All right, nice and easy.
Oh, come on. What the hell? I had to go over that lip? Back there. I'll get it. As long
as I get back there with about a minute left. I love how I looked over at chat and the first
thing I see is stop looking at chat. This is the right way. I remember I went through this.
All right, now I gotta get this right.
Don't read this. Oh my god. I can't help myself. I didn't even get the bonus.
What does this mean? All right, I got it. I got it. I got it.
Here are the cops that show up. Too much heat apparently.
27 seconds. I'll make it. I'm almost there. All right, I brought it back. Hello Cletus.
Boy, I'll help you. You just yell into one of those magic talk boxes and I come a running.
Oh man, them things is crazy. Bonus mission complete. Congratulations, you've unlocked
Cletus's pickup truck. Go to a phone booth to use it. Oh nice. Does Bart Simpson drive in
this game? No, they wouldn't do that, right? Bart Simpson drives in this game. Okay,
uh, let's try that. Let's try the new car. Wow, I need a disco nap. Pickup truck.
Toughness handling speed acceleration. This thing sucks. This is just a shitty plow cane.
Can you come and get me? I'll pay you in back rubs. Yeah, I'll give you a ride.
The back seat's swarming with chiggers though. Wait, he's gonna...
I'm not driving. Wait, it's, I'm him now. That's kind of cool. Look at that 180 degree neck turn.
Just put some butter on the wound. It'll be fine. Yeah, I'm just hitchhiking right now.
That's that. That's really cool. All right, let me get this this time.
Got it. That was better than the booby box. I still have to turn on this power plant mission.
That was easy as pie. Wait, that was supposed to be a race?
My car's allowed in here? Vengeance will be mine. What the fuck?
Holy shit. Okay, this is freaking me out. Hold on. You got real purty acceleration.
I need to get out of this car.
Take that! All right, Homer's workstation. Thanks for the ride. Almost got it. Yeah.
Whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's this button do? Well, I hope do not press means press
right away. Well, now you got me all fucked up because this is, this probably sound like a
secret chest up here or something. Yeah, ain't gonna fuck me up. All that for what, one coin?
Oops, I gotta change that button. Jump can't be B. I mean, run can't be B.
Because I have to like turn my hand around and do B and A to jump. I gotta change that to,
what the hell, X maybe? B attack? Yeah, that makes more sense. Yeah, attack would be,
should be B. Jump should be A. Sprint should be X. Get in is Y. Okay, that's better. Plug
in a controller. That's what I'm playing with. I'm playing with the controller right now. Yeah,
that feels better. That feels more correct. And I keep forgetting about the double jump.
It's all right. All right, here we go. Wait, I want to look around Homer's station.
Oh, am I breathing in these fumes and getting going crazy? I don't get it.
Destroy all the power couplings before time runs out. What? What is this? Hold on. I just killed
somebody. Destroy all the... No, this is going to suck absolute ass.
This is going to be real bad, but no, I'll get it. What does stupid like a fox mean?
Did you hear how low that was? Stupid like a fox mean. No, I got it. I'm good.
If you're so smart, how come I broke it? I got stuck on that. I got fucking clipped on that.
Sorry, I got a ton of time. Like anyone likes these things. Stupid like a fox. All right,
I got it. Whoa. Whoa, where are we going? Buzzkill on the blades or over the railing?
Uh, just walk on a blade? Oh, now I have to get that though. That was a little bit
a little bit hard to do. I think I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I get it.
I get it. I get it. Jump from the blades. Yeah, maybe I can make it like this.
My bikini zone's chafing. Try it one more time.
Just go. I want to just get the thing. All right, when you were playing Simpson's Hit and Run
and you saw like a little secret here and it was kind of tricky to jump to get it,
did you give up after two times? See? Like, why would I do that? I got it.
Drive to the Simpsons house. Wait, is there anything? Can I look at stuff in the office?
Is it a bug farm? I can't interact with anything else in Homer's office.
There's no fall damage. No, not in Hit and Run. No, now I'm in trouble. Okay, I see.
Uh, I can't drive up this. I had to get some momentum.
263? That's not bad. All right, back to the house.
Our safe direct. Seven days since the last accident. Actually, none considering that I just
melted somebody in there. Watch that meter. Yeah, I do need to keep my eye on the meter.
You're right. That's the urine trouble meter. I want to give it to me. There is a card back
here. So what do these do? Mr. Sparkle Box. There's also something to do here. Yeah,
there's a lot of, like, random shit to do. Get them all. Get all the cards. I don't think I'm
gonna do that. It's a pointless collectible. Didn't he say he could sell them? All right,
I want to get rid of this car. All right, give me a phone. I want my other car back.
If I'm gonna do a race, I need to have my other car.
I need your help.
Kill Millhouse. You can't kill anybody in this game. Why would I do that? All right,
let's do it. What are you doing here? Patty and Selma won't give me a license to ride
a bike without safety wheels. Unless I run the driving tests. Reach the finish line
before time runs out. Don't destroy your vehicle. Five laps. Oh, they really like
to throw these at you. This is a drift map. Am I actually gonna be able to do five laps here?
Maybe, but I don't know. That's gonna be close. There can't be any mistakes.
No! Oh, I'm actually, I'm so mad right now. I'm actually fucking angry. Oh, slow down. Easy,
Jeremy. What the fuck was that? I went from, like, a zero to a fucking thousand.
I can just break the damn tree. It was going so well, too. I still get it.
The scale is just tipped. Somebody put, like, four weights on the other side.
I almost didn't hit it. This is something I rest in. I'm going to feed your driver's license
to Jub-Jub. Everyone sucks but me. What do I get for that? Nothing. Apparently nothing.
That's what Homer wanted to do all season four, right?
Spoiler. Oh, please. Don't even. That's not a spoiler. There's no such thing as a spoiler.
I mean, there is, but not in this context. Wait, cross to the crab. Nice. Complete all
three races. Well, when they pop up, I'll do them. Homer wasn't introduced until season six.
Do I get to, can I drive around his grandpa?
What? Uh, investigate and follow the black van. Don't let it get away.
Do this thing. That was comedy, apparently. Follow the black van. Let's go. Uh, I'm assuming
that's the meter at the top is don't fill that, otherwise mission failed. Fucking escort
mission. They put these in this goddamn game. Fill it. Why would I fill it? Isn't that the
meter that is, hey, don't get that close. You're too close, Homer. I know what that
meter is. I've played a GTA game before. All right. School bus. What are you doing?
No, I'm not going to get baited from chat for the 4,000th time.
To fill the meter, get up real close and have it be like, oh,
nuclear power plant heading into the power plant. What are you doing in here? Spy van.
Did that just drive off the edge? No. Okay. All right. All right.
No, too close, too close, too close. Does that hurt me? Shit. No, wait, wait. I hit the car
stuck. Wait, give me a car. Cletus, Cletus, Cletus, Cletus, Cletus, Cletus.
Yes. What? I did it. Okay. I did it. I tailed him for long enough so that I could get the
information. Get rocket. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Rocket car. Why is everybody freaking out?
Rocket car. Rocket car. Get rocket car. You want me to get this? Okay. Is this secret?
I love to sit. How does this work? Mistakes were made. Do I get this forever now? I'm dead.
I almost spilled my sundae. This thing's already going to explode. I forgot my mission.
Oh, that just startled me. That thing sucks. Pick it up here, people. This is really fast.
But, oh, do the, oh, I should have hit the rocket car for this, right? I know you.
You're the kid that sells me bootleg CDs on the street corner. Yeah, well, I've been having some
legal problems lately, so I'm stuck running these races for the DMV. It was this or read to the
elderly. Probably all laps and finish the race in first place. Don't destroy the vehicle.
Oh, no, I do have the car. How do I do this without blowing up the car?
This is not going to happen. All right, here's my plan. My plan is to be very careful
and then go punch it as hard as I can on the last lap. I'm just going to hold down right
trigger. Holy shit. They're so dumb. Okay, I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm going to punch it.
He doesn't matter. He can tow the fuck out of me if he wants.
Oh, no, I don't. I can't do that.
This is not going to work. It's not going to work with this thing.
I need another car. There's no way I can do it in that. No, no, don't retry the mission.
Give me a new car. I'll do it again. There he is. He's crusty.
That was brutal. That was brutal. Now I'm ready. I was about to win.
Was I though? Hold on. There's a button to press.
Yeah, crystal eggs in the crotch. Who lives here?
Cool. Secret. Watch this. Nice. There we go. All right, I'm ready.
I mean, it still starts in three, two, one anyways. So why does that matter? All right,
I'll get it. Just going to stay in first place. Go around the lap here. All right, I got it.
Just drive normal. You don't have to do any crazy moves. This is race number two out of three,
right? And then once I do race three, I get the secret costume, right? You get a car. Oh,
okay. This guy's going to run up my ass though. I got to punch it.
He's right up my ass. He did crash into the wall.
He's going to say that a thousand more times. He's going to say that so many more times.
Two, four, six, eight. Over here. Here we go. Great. This is it. Last wrap around. Oh, smooth.
Very smooth. Don't lose it here. Come on. Did it not know what place I was just in?
This is terrible. I'm going to drown my sorrows at the golden banana. I am so smart. I am so smart.
S-M-R-T. I mean, S-M-A-R-T. How did you guys know that? You guys have played this game before?
I'm surprised at how many people have actually played this game. That's very surprising to
me. It's from the TV show. Yeah, but how did you know it was going to be right there?
Ouch. My bikini zone's chafing. I just want to look around.
Okay, I got to take a car up here because I'm going to blast through that.
All right, give me my car. How do I get up there? How do I get up here?
Okay, I got to go around there. Why is everybody part of the power plant?
They just walk around? Should I be in one of those suits? Oh, this guy's driving the car.
I didn't steal the car. Why? Okay, hold on. I'll get it. Damn it.
I got to go back further. I'm going to start from over here.
Holy fuck. Look at that. Whoa. Hold on. I'll get that later.
I just overshot the hell out of it. I need to get the help.
Did that guy just die? Did that guy dead? I might be able to get over this.
I got to go off the right way though. No! Why did I?
I died. I died. I did it. Didn't I do it? That was offshoot?
I need the rocket car, but it's an invisible wall. There's nothing up there. Oh.
Watch it. Well, let's do a mission. That was a jump. How would you break that one? Other side?
All right. Talk to Marge. But first, hold on. Wait. I love that sound.
That coin collection sound is perfect. We've got to follow him. Not now, Homer. A new violent
video game has hit the streets and we need to get rid of it before it warps any children
with its bloops and bleeps. But that game sounds awesome and therefore should be destroyed.
I get it. Hit the delivery truck and collect the
bone storm games before time runs out. Everyone better stay out of my way.
Oh, it's Marge. Hit the delivery truck and collect 10 copies. Well, that's the truck.
Marge, you sure do care about children. You're running over a lot of them.
You really just have to sit right here and just pop it a couple times.
That hitbox is not that big currently. Just wait for it to spawn.
Easing. It's not that hard. You just have to be patient.
Just tap it. Break. That wasn't enough. I'm not sure how.
Last one. Do I have to do something else? There's always like a part two
in this game. It seems like. No. Sell the copies to G2A.
Now that's topical.
Well Homer, I am evil.
Where am I going to put all these?
What happened?
If only kids would play more video games about sharing.
Marge, you know I have four crazy plans. Now if you'll excuse me, I have to go spy on my boss.
This is what happened to my Amazon package. Drive to the power plant.
Not yet. Where's the other race? Give me the phone.
I want to explore around. I don't want to just blow through.
Can you come and get me? I'll pay you in back rubs.
Blow through the game? No, why would I do that?
I don't want to blow through the game.
All right. What's this? I want to go in people's backyards and
I want to find the other race. Because there's another car I can get, right?
I did not explore. And that's why you gotta take a minute sometimes.
Because there is a collectible Pokemon card up there.
How do I get that? There's a huge jump. All right. Just wait. Relax.
That didn't really do anything.
Not going fast enough? Or was it? Was that?
I missed the sign. I gotta go through the sign.
Aye. Okay, hold on. I'll get it.
Let me line it up. Where's the sign?
It's right, right there.
It doesn't do anything. It doesn't do anything.
So let me just platform. Let me look around for a place to jump.
There's some stuff over here. From here to here?
Come on, camera. Turn around.
All right. Now what? Is that it?
Oh, don't fall off. That's it.
You're on the wrong roof.
Oh, the clicking mark's over there.
Oh, I hope do not press means press right away.
So now can I, can I make this jump from?
Holy fuck. I didn't even see it.
Very nice. Oh, look at these pog champs.
That was too easy. Whoa.
Where am I? Well, got it.
Does this do anything? Don't do that.
Wait, there's another gas.
I gotta spend some money. I got a lot.
Oh, I'm going to the donut boy, right? Donut guy.
I jumped it.
Oh shit. Oh, can I get on his head?
I don't think I can do anything about this.
I could just hang out here.
Itchy and scratchy over there.
You won the game. Sometimes.
Run. Again.
ADHD stream.
Well, I wanted to take a look around for a second, get some money and.
Hey, I found my lost nachos.
Actually, you know, I want to buy that costume.
I have money. I'm buying it.
What do you have that is high in both bet and alcohol content?
I'm so glad you came. If I don't increase profits.
I just broke his machine.
Oh, I'll just ruin it.
Did I just get arrested?
Did I just steal a bunch of money from the fucking ATM?
What is that? Wait, hold on. I thought I could play it.
I just skipped the cut scene because I thought I was playing the game.
Restart the whole. There we go. There we go. Here we go. Here we go.
Let's watch it.
Holy shit. Was this game rated?
Can I take the duff truck?
Right, I want that.
Interesting platforming. Coming right up.
There's another one of these.
Ooh, from here to there?
Like I can make it from here over there.
This thing gives so much money.
Oops. Okay. No, you can do that. It's fine.
Doesn't hurt you.
All right, let's go. Let's move on.
Holy fuck Homer is strong.
This car is fast. This is just screaming by.
Do the final race.
Where is it? I haven't seen it pop up on the minimap.
I have to go to the church.
Oops. We're good. It's on two wheels.
I keep going that way. I have not driven down this road once.
Did that one.
I don't really know where the church is.
I'll have to stumble upon it after this mission.
Fine.
That's so unfortunate.
Carl. Hi Carl.
This is the last mission of the game?
Oh no, it is not.
Beat Smithers to Mr. Burns Mansion.
Sorry.
I like the car though.
It's got the perfect handling.
Perfect safety features.
Ooh, almost flipped the whole thing.
Oh, he cheated too.
Fuck. I didn't know they do the cheats.
Move out of the way.
He's got to stay in front of him.
He's going to get stuck right there.
Good. Perfect.
There's not enough room on the road for both of us.
Should I go straight through?
Straight through?
Yep.
Oh, I just fucked him up so bad.
I just ruined everything for you.
Don't pass me.
I don't know where to go.
I don't watch this TV show.
I don't.
Oh, I don't watch this show.
I would have known.
You stupid asshole.
Oh, come on.
I had it too.
Right at the end, I cut him off.
But this car, just look at this car.
What a piece of crap this car is.
What a piece of crap.
I almost didn't make it.
Well, I am destroying him right now.
What is he doing?
And I didn't even go through the...
Oh, I just cracked my neck like in 50 places.
Just trying to cut corners.
How many school buses are here?
He just hit that.
Good.
I've got itchy.
My whole body is itchy.
Oh my god.
My whole fucking body is itching.
That just helped him.
Unbelievable.
That same motherfucker right there.
It was the same guy.
No.
I still got it.
Where am I going?
Holy shit.
I beat him.
Did I win?
I won.
Final cutscene of the game.
First try, Eddie.
I thought I just failed the mission.
My heart just sank into my stomach.
Bonus mission.
Street races two to three.
Collector cards.
Character clothing.
Vehicles.
Wasp cameras.
Gags.
Did I beat it?
No, I didn't.
Oh, now I get to play as Bart.
This is a different place.
This is like the 20 years in the future.
She baited.
Ooh, what's this?
I want to look around.
Hey, that's great.
You better get out of here, Bart.
Principal Skinner's looking for everyone that skipped school today.
And when you're caught, it's expulsion, Bart.
Expulsion!
Avoid Principal Skinner.
Drive to the try and save before time runs out.
Bart Simpson at your service.
I guess I'm going into the rocket car.
And this is a, like, seven-year-old driving a car.
I'll get you, Bart.
Just like I got Charlie and Nam.
Braid not.
Braid so.
Don't let him.
Braid so?
Do you stand your lightning fast with fire in the hole?
Ah, this is...
This is a grown man trying to drive into a kid in a go-kart.
Does that just avoid him for a minute?
I'm doing a pretty good job avoiding.
Smell you later, stinky gator.
The Bartman knows all.
The Bartman.
Empty the bar.
What do you mean, empty the bar?
Easy peasy.
Easily.
Wait, free stop.
Oh, awesome!
Here, the money carries over to the next, uh, next land.
Too late, losers.
I got the last game.
Four-finger discount.
Some crazy lady destroyed all the rest.
When will they learn?
Video games don't kill people.
They just kill their minds.
And the crowd goes wild.
Drive to Herman's.
I want to get in the thing.
Home.
Oh, God.
Okay, I thought I just did that.
I thought I just kicked him into it and blew it up.
This sucks!
Hey!
What do you got for me?
It's me, Bart!
How am I gonna get that new game?
Who cares?
That was a gag.
Video games are so late 90s.
Illegal fireworks are all the rave now.
Better make it snappy though if you want to be part of this trend.
A lot of self-referential video game.
Video games are bad referentials.
Collect fireworks from around Springfield before time runs out.
Fine by me!
For some road made.
I only have 60 seconds to do this.
That's not a way to turn.
These people are jumping.
They're just jumping into the...
I don't know.
I'm not doing that.
They are.
It's right over two people's heads.
There's the car wash.
No, don't tell me to go that way.
It's right here.
Oh, hey, Otto.
All right, got it.
Enter Moe's.
I do have to...
Am I gonna prank call him?
Can I interact with any of this stuff?
I can't jump.
I'm gonna...
Can I call him?
That's the joke, right?
Drink at the bar as Bart.
Sorry, Bart.
I can't serve booze to a miner.
It ain't right.
I'm here to buy fireworks.
Oh, hell yeah.
No problemo.
D...
D-jar?
Oh.
I won.
What do I get?
One coin.
Do it again.
That was the coolest thing I've seen anybody do in the game.
He just did a full backflip.
No hands.
Cold fish.
One more.
Get it again.
I'm pretty good at this.
Why is there a mirror world?
Yeah, that is strange.
That's something to do with how the game is being rendered.
I don't know why it's doing that.
Let's go.
Drive to the Springfield Town Hall.
You got it, Bart.
Wait.
Not yet.
What's this?
It's not...
That's a reference that I don't get.
It's a reference.
That was anti-climactic.
I should have drove through that.
Oh, my god.
A fucking timer up there.
No problemo.
Oh, damn it.
Not a joke.
No, I...
No, it wasn't.
I wasn't even paying any attention to it.
I just...
For some reason, just my brain turned off the fact that the top corner of the screen was a timer.
And that every single mission is timing.
The whole thing again.
God damn it.
Boomer memory.
No.
Wait, Moses is right next to it.
Fireworks.
Yeah.
Talk to him.
Sorry, Bart.
All right.
I think my...
You know what it was?
It was the fact that the timer's not there now.
Timer's not there.
You know what I mean?
Timer is not here.
I didn't pay attention.
And now it is.
So that's why.
And I wanted to look at the city.
All right.
Got it.
No timer, right?
I can do this?
Here are your fireworks.
He's still going.
Still timed.
Don't make...
Don't let me forget that.
Because I will get out of this car and just start pressing buttons on stuff.
Don't explode.
I don't want to do this whole fucking thing again.
That's terrifying.
That's a terrifying Ralph.
All right.
Hold on a minute.
I need a new car.
Oh, fuck.
This is going to explode.
My car's going to explode.
Can I steal a car as Bart?
Am I going to...
I don't understand what the bar is for.
This is saying don't go this way.
Is this the end of the game?
No, it's not an invisible wall.
Okay.
I was just making sure that was an invisible wall.
Drive to the go-goplex.
Incoming great song.
Can I just plow through this?
No, I have to go all the way around.
Wait.
Where's it...
That guy is driving in the wrong place.
Too many detours.
Is the passenger still in the taxi?
Yeah, that's the one driving the taxi.
That's how they can get away with this.
All right.
Comic book guy, what do you got?
I think...
Ready?
Here it comes.
Race to the nerd.
Race the nerd to the Java server.
You got it.
Don't forget to ride.
How do I...
How am I racing the nerd when I'm in the nerd's car?
The other nerd.
There's two nerds.
Well, this nerd's car sucks.
Glancing blow.
I spilled my squishy.
We don't have deflector shields, you know.
Bart Simpson at your service.
Warp speed.
Oh, bullpup.
Aww, loser.
All right, let's power through it.
You can drive through trees.
This is not...
Man, this sucks.
Unbelievable.
Well, that just got a little more rare.
That was totally...
Engage.
I think you could have avoided...
I just...
What was I supposed to do after that?
Total failure at the beginning.
Right, now I'm losing.
That lady got fucking destroyed.
We don't have deflector shields, you know.
What the fuck was that?
I blame no one.
Whoa, wicked.
I'm happy to report...
Lucky break.
...that your quest for Bone Storm 2 is quite futile.
Professor Frank posted a message on my news group,
alt.furyanimals.fanfiction.net,
that he has bought up all the remaining video games.
I'll thank you not to moan in my mid-sized vehicle.
Furry animals.
Wait, can I take his car?
It's gone.
Okay.
So there's Family Sedan,
Fire Truck Limo,
World War II vehicle,
Surveillance Van,
Duff Truck,
Electorus,
Speed, Acceleration, Toughness.
This is the best thing.
All right, give me that.
All right.
Good old Bart.
Who doesn't like Bart?
There's a race right here.
Let's do it.
I don't...
You don't like Bart?
Pass all checkpoints and cross the finish line first.
Don't destroy your vehicle.
I mean, that was...
That was cute.
Why is there a taxi?
Oh, boy.
I'm sure I'm not driving against...
and racing against ghosts of my own driving.
I'm just facing my own ghosts.
This guy's gonna be hard to pass.
We're going on the highway?
Yes, we are.
Just pass him.
No, he got to do the cool thing and I didn't.
Oh, did not expect that.
It's over.
I lost.
I need a better car, probably.
Yeah.
Maybe if I can get up there real quick.
All right, so...
If you ain't fast, you're last.
Yeah, that's true.
Does this count if I don't...
It does.
Okay.
I don't...
You don't have to...
I don't have to touch them.
I don't have to touch those.
I just have to go...
Okay.
That changes everything.
I thought I actually had to go near that circle.
No, you ain't gonna fuck that up.
I'm in front now.
The car's faster than mine, so I...
That's not fair.
Not fair.
Just like in NASCAR.
Gonna stay on the inside.
How dare you?
How dare you do that to me at the very end?
Oh.
Oh, I had it too.
I just...
Unbelievable.
That was so stupid.
How fucking...
Come on.
That was bullshit too.
It was just a bunch of bullshit.
All right, I'm all right again.
Good.
Just don't let that happen again.
She's got a fast...
She...
She got a faster car than me.
That's Lisa, right?
Stay on the inside.
She's right behind me.
She's gonna pass me.
No, she's right here.
I got a left-hand turn coming up.
Got it.
Okay.
Don't...
That was so close.
Give it to me.
Give me the car.
I can't take the car.
This car's so much better.
Is it Lisa?
I can't do anything about it.
Not allowed.
Who else has that hair?
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
We got a side mission.
It's Grandpa.
What do you need?
I need your car from the war.
The war?
What?
Is the Kaiser at it again?
I'll teach him.
He stole my best girl and my best box of saltwater taffy.
Grandpa, you're not making any sense.
I'm tired because I let Jasper borrow my blood.
I didn't think I'd need it.
No.
Saltwater taffy?
I love saltwater taffy.
Now you got my attention, chat.
What is it?
You need something?
What's going on?
Boomers like taffy.
This camera control is in the menu.
Camera left.
Oh, hold on a minute.
Numpad 4.
Camera left.
Camera right.
Camera move in.
Camera move out.
Camera zoom.
Camera look up.
Well, that's okay.
Thank God.
Well, that changes everything.
How many times have I said that?
Six.
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where is it?
What?
I don't know why I did this.
I have to keep going into modes over and over again.
Hello.
Action button.
I pressed it.
I'm interacting with the DD jar.
Well, what?
Come on.
I'm standing right here and it's like press action.
I'm right here.
Wait, what?
I thought he just gave it to me.
Why does it?
I fucked that guy up bad.
Too many cars on the road.
I'm collecting everybody's blood.
This is a little weird.
I got a minute to go back to grandpa.
Eat ass?
I'm gonna set the cops on me.
Don't touch anybody.
That's Bart's catchphrase.
No, it's eat my shorts.
Is that enough?
I need another car.
Take it.
Oh, I'm gonna pour this on my flapjacks.
So I got a new car.
You've unlocked grandpa's World War II vehicle.
Go to a phone to use it.
Okay.
This thing's not bad.
It's not eat my ass.
Why?
No, it's eat my shorts.
There it is.
Move it, you milkshake!
This thing is kind of tricky to move around.
Did I do something wrong?
Had to get that.
What is this up here?
A little place to go.
Ooh, would you look at this?
What's that?
No.
I'll get it.
One, two, three, go.
I can go over there too.
Oops.
Hurry!
Give me the coins.
All of them.
Can I reach these without falling?
Yes, I can.
What's this one?
Mr. Honey Bunny.
I'm gonna go this way too.
I can platform over this thing.
Having the camera controls make this a thousand times easier.
All right, there's a box over there.
Got the camera.
Can I get them all?
I think I can.
I have to get it.
The boxes have a lot of coins.
I gotta get it.
Stop moving.
All right, now just get it in the right spot.
I almost blew the whole thing again.
That's too many coins to just ignore.
Sweet.
Wait.
No, that's not them.
Nothing over there?
Let me just take a look.
I got, uh, Krusty the Crab.
I can't make that jump.
Can I jump over here?
All right, Grandpa, let's go.
Take me to my destination.
This handling is ridiculous.
Is this car way
30 pounds?
Look at this thing.
All right, this is a gamble.
I'm now, I got controls.
I know how to play the game.
I think it's time to do one of these missions.
25 cents and then 75 cents.
Complete an entire lap before the time runs out.
Let's try it.
Oh, I just realized I'm using this.
I see it right there.
All right, I'll work the pedals and you steer.
Oh, this is too cool for school.
Let's make the scene.
All for March.
We call sandwiches.
Glad Freddy.
There goes 25 cents.
Get out of my way.
I thought that was a place to turn in there.
It's not.
You go, you can turn the other way.
What the fuck am I on two wheels for?
Why did that happen?
What?
Wait, I'm getting, hold on a second here.
I'm getting more time.
I think I'll still do this.
No, I'm not.
That was a lie.
This is, I have to do the whole thing and yeah, full lap in two tenths.
I don't know why I'm doing this anymore.
I should just delete and go do the mission.
I just gave that guy 25 dollars.
Downtown to the stadium.
I want to go this way.
Nice.
That was cool.
Talk to professor Frank.
I will do that in a second after I break the vending machines.
No, wait, I want to get on the phone here.
I got a pregnancy test.
I want to get up there.
No, the cards or coins or anything.
Nope, not yet.
ADD.
Well, I got to get these coins.
That one's gone forever.
Oh well.
Again.
Video games, video games.
Go to Herman's Military Antiques to find a World War II radio for Professor Frank.
Okay.
So I need to tail this to the military place.
Press select.
I can't press select.
Fill bar.
All right, I'll fill the bar and then you'll see what happens.
I can't believe we lost, Bart!
Where is this guy going?
What the fuck is going on?
You have to follow it, not tail it.
If it slows down, you slow down.
And then they said, idiot.
Okay.
All right.
Is that really that big of a deal?
Apparently.
I'm gonna find a thief.
Everyone's telling me to press select.
But I don't have, I can't press select on the controller.
It doesn't do anything.
So, like, there is no select.
What is it on the keyboard?
Like escape?
Because that's, I can't.
The select button.
It doesn't do anything.
Start doesn't do anything either.
Press the select key.
All right, can I, I'm just gonna play the damn game.
Press the N-E key.
I know that reference.
That's Homer Simpson.
I need that radio you borrowed.
No way, little dude.
This radio is going to help me score Bo Q Day chicks.
Uh, last time I checked, chicks like fast cars, not vintage electronics.
Why don't we race for the radio?
Oh, I totally agree to your proposal.
All right, Snake.
You and me.
All right, there's other cars on the road.
I don't want to fuck this up.
Why is everything solved in races?
That's a great question.
Can't they just do like once, twice, three, shoot?
Do we have to put everybody in danger?
I wasn't first.
I'll get it.
Hold on.
I'll cut them off up here.
Extreme to the max.
You cheated.
How is it even possible that you're still ahead of me?
Don't forget the ride.
I don't even, how is this possible?
I, I'll accept it.
Apparently I'm going to accept this.
Oh, now come on.
I can't believe I just won.
That's unbelievable.
There's no way that that just happened.
I won though.
He's a god gamer.
All right, peel it out, grandpa.
Let's go.
We had to say dickity because the Kaiser has stolen our word 20.
What a big idea.
Jerma, press select.
Uh, I already did that one.
My dad will pay for all the damages.
How about them apples?
What did I do something wrong?
What's this?
Hold on, is it catapult here?
Wait a minute.
I need to examine a catapult.
Really?
Who can I?
Was there an animal in there?
There was.
Why am I launching?
Why am I doing this?
That's not right.
We got a race.
A catapult.
Trebuchet.
Nelson, why are you hanging around here?
Stupid community service.
I dip Martin in the sauce like Quickie Mart.
Anyway, get your license and you get some stupid prize from those jerks.
Complete all laps and finish the race in first place.
Don't destroy your vehicle.
Three.
Press select to win race.
Eat my dust, dust eaters.
I'm not going to do that.
Oh, there goes more memories.
All right.
That guy.
I should enjoy this so much.
This is what they do.
Every mission so far for the race missions have been we're going to put two dickheads
on the road and then the guy in first place is the one you're actually racing against.
The other two people are just obstacles in your way.
Because now I'm so look at I'm so far behind.
How am I going to catch up in time?
I got to get first immediately.
Is there a shortcut I can do?
Stop having a cow.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do it.
Oops.
I don't think I'm going to do it.
I'm going to restart.
Because there's no way.
I'm not going to catch up with this guy.
There's no way I'm going to catch up.
Just go faster.
I'm holding down right trigger.
See watch this.
It's Lisa.
It's Lisa again.
Your car is great and you're a great driver.
All right.
I made it through the.
No I didn't.
This is still here.
All right.
Yeah I told you why I ought to.
What's my name?
All right.
I'm not in a bad position.
Just going to keep it up.
All right.
Get in there.
Good.
She lost it there for a second.
Having trouble.
Stay on the inside.
Running to you.
That's exactly what I didn't want to have happen.
What did he just say?
What?
Hold on.
All right.
Good.
Every time I end up bumping into you here.
Come on.
This is the end.
Right here.
Throw that.
I got to do the last one and get the car for this stage.
Right.
I'm not going to lie.
I was just pressing up on the d-pad to call the horse.
Look at me.
I'm free as a bird.
All right.
Look at the last race.
Where is the final race?
I don't know.
Wow.
That was interesting.
And go through here.
Oh, I spilled my sea bag.
Press select for the map.
There is no map.
Yes, there is.
I just pressed M.
Select to use boost.
Oh, how do I get that?
Get out of here, B.
All right.
If I climb up there, I should get it.
Right here.
Wait.
Kind of hard to see.
Damn.
That's tricky.
Camera doesn't want to stay in the right place.
Big butt skinner.
For the crusty burger.
Speaking of burgers.
I could go for a burger.
A huge one.
Nice one.
A double at least.
I would take a triple.
Out of my way, man.
No, that's too much.
I'm going to sneeze now.
Can I mute and type?
Hey, slower traffic to the right, please.
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Easy peasy.
Hey there, Mr. Slackjaw Yokel.
That be I.
Can I borrow your satellite dish?
Sure.
If you help me scoop up my flat meat, sophisticated city youngster.
Best burger place?
I'm a big fan of Shake Shack.
No problemo.
I'm going to get all these.
Five Guys is good.
Shake Shack.
But I would put Shake Shack above Five Guys.
We're talking like counter-serve burgers and yeah.
Shake Shack, yes.
Can you please not be directly in the path that I need?
And the train's coming.
Best restaurant burger actually sitting down at a restaurant.
I had the best burger I've ever had in my life.
And it's down on the strip.
Oh fuck, I have to deliver this now.
The Hash House has the best burger I've ever had in my whole life.
From a sit-down restaurant.
It was absolutely fucking unbelievable.
Am I going to make this?
Am I not paying attention?
Did I fuck something?
No, I'm not.
I'm fine.
If I had In-N-Out.
Yeah, I'm not a fan of In-N-Out.
I don't really know.
I'm not like a big fan of In-N-Out.
I think it's just kind of like a Wendy's cheeseburger that's
cheap.
Sorry, guys.
What?
Get away from...
I don't hate In-N-Out.
I think it's good.
But I think it's like a step up from a place like Wendy's, I think.
The best thing about In-N-Out is In-N-Out is really fast and it's really cheap.
I wish I had some really big tires like I saw on the TV once.
Am I going to lose right now?
This is too cool for school.
That's the bomb.
But I don't know.
Me and Star went to In-N-Out and people were like,
go to In-N-Out, go to In-N-Out, go to In-N-Out.
We went to In-N-Out and it was...
Both of us said the same thing.
We were like, oh, that was all right, I guess.
I'm going the wrong way.
There's nothing wrong with In-N-Out.
Rusty burgers are made of roadkill?
It's just...
That explains the tire tracks.
I don't think it's at this extreme God-like level that some people say it is.
Thanks in Red Hill, Billy.
Torrent nothing.
Stop it, stop it.
Got it.
But I think that that's the problem, though,
because it's just like a good hamburger.
People lift it up to be this thing that you have to eat and God will come down
and grace you when you put it in your mouth.
Once you take a bite of an In-N-Out burger, God appears and says,
don't you like that?
I made it for you.
My compliments to the chef.
Do the last race.
Is this the last mission?
Maybe I'll just cancel the thing.
Well, I guess I'm not even doing it, so...
All right, where is the last race?
We got one here.
Where did that one?
Not yet.
Somebody just said In-N-Out is a slightly better McDonald's.
I don't know if I would go that far to say that.
Where did that one?
Where's the last one?
Well, there's the two there.
They're right next to each other.
Anybody know where it is?
I have no fucking idea.
Why is everybody...
Hold on, wait.
Why is everybody adding...
What are you doing?
No, stop this.
Stop this nonsense.
What is this?
Sorry, I just saw them and I...
You guys are distracting the fuck out of me right now.
Did I break the phone?
Get out of the taxi.
I can still use it.
All right, I want the family car.
All right, all right, all right.
Am I gonna have to like put it into fucking slow down mode?
Last race is next to Sneed.
Where is that though?
I haven't seen this television show in my life.
Over this way?
All right, am I going the right way?
If I go through the Buzz Cola sign.
Did I just say something I shouldn't have said?
It's near the fire truck ramp.
That's kind of far away.
Did I actually just say something?
All right, here's Moe's head down here.
This is the factory.
I really don't know where the hell I'm even going.
Guys, just be honest with me.
Am I even going remotely in the right direction?
No.
I passed it?
No, I didn't.
The mini map.
But there's nothing on the mini map.
There's just that flip.
I'm looking for the race.
Downtown.
Sneed is not downtown.
Just go in any direction long enough and you're gonna find it.
What the fuck?
All right, you know what?
I found it!
Let's go.
I'm fucking pumped now, man.
I'm so amped up for this.
This is weird.
Did I do something wrong?
I don't...
This is weird.
Am I going the right way?
Do I have to actually...
I'm so confused.
One more lap?
What the hell is going on?
Somebody said go through the roundabout and I don't know why I even looked at the chat.
Go through the roundabout.
What am I doing?
You can't.
You have to go around the whole thing.
Go through the roundabout.
There's a roundabout.
What are you doing?
And I'm like, aye, aye, yeah.
Yeah.
He's very smart.
This time I'm not gonna look at chat.
I'm just gonna do it.
I'm so fucking mad.
It totally took like...
Well, how long did it take?
Was it about two hours?
No, it's been a while.
I haven't had like a meltdown yet.
No, there aren't gonna be a meltdown tonight.
This is Simpsons Bart Simpson drives around and throws stuff and runs away.
I'm not gonna get angry at it.
Why would that happen?
I just saved two or three full seconds.
You already are.
I am not.
You would know if I was.
I would have made like a weird sound effect.
You know what I mean?
Do it.
It's right here.
Next time you stay at our place, you can have the steamed vegetable of your choice.
Photophone booth to get Moe's Sedan.
Let's check it out.
Moe's Sedan.
It's not bad.
This is one, one and a half, two and a half, four.
One, one and a half, two and a half, four.
Two, one and a half, two and a half, three and a half.
That's better.
It's not actually...
It's not Moe driving the car.
This is just...
This is actually a child driving this car.
I mean, I gotta go over that.
How could I not do that?
Not enough speed.
Come on.
What are you trying?
There are over 5,000 people here.
You're gonna just drive over that slowly?
Kidding me?
Come on, screamer.
You gotta impress us.
All right, Professor Frink.
I got your stuff.
There you go.
Everybody...
Look it over in the chat.
It's just so many emotions.
I don't even know which one to interact with.
There's so much going on over here.
All right, talk to Dr. Nick.
Hello.
I have tortured them horribly, silly.
There's no way I'll be able to fit all those monkeys in my car.
I better get a big truck or something.
No, I ain't playing...
I'm not playing a fucking OST.
I'm not playing an OST right now.
That's not gonna happen.
No.
You'll need the plow truck.
Purchase it from Homer in the hospital parking lot for 200 coins.
Don't I already own it?
I already own it.
There was a T-pose there.
I can't wait to see it in chat.
I need your truck, Homer.
Why should I give you that?
Because I love you.
Pay up, sucker.
You're charging your own son?
Yeah, I guess I am.
Now we're in emote only.
Emote only.
Oh, the fucking title sucks.
This title sucks such ass.
I forgot.
I was gonna...
That's a placeholder.
You've got it.
I just looked over and saw it.
Oh, well.
Find all the monkeys before they escape.
30 of...
Oh, god.
Okay, I gotta go to one corner of the map.
This is not good.
How the hell am I gonna do this?
All right, they start here.
No!
I just lost their mind.
Why is everybody freaking out?
Oh, I gotta pay attention.
All right, I'll...
We'll have a chat later.
Cross here in town.
I'm good.
I got...
Almost halfway there.
I got plenty of time.
Oh, dear.
This platforming involved in this.
Platforming is involved.
I thought it was just driving.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
How do I...
Get up there.
I see it.
It's right here.
That's it.
Turn around.
Any more on top of roofs or anything?
In the car.
17, 18, 19.
Come on.
Get through there.
I got plenty of time.
Just don't freak out about it.
I'm still missing five.
Where on earth are the other five?
Forget about the B.
It's not important.
Jump to light speed.
Bark.
That doesn't exist.
I got it.
And then end it on the stairs.
All right.
That was not...
I didn't need to panic at all.
That was...
I'm done.
Drive to the Screaming Monkey Medical Center.
What?
Got it.
Don't deliver them.
Why wouldn't I deliver them?
Oh, I see.
I kind of like the plow.
I didn't like it at first, but now I do.
I'm back.
Unfortunately, there are too many people using cell phones, and the interference would then
cause the monster to malfunction and kill many people.
What were the popular cell phones that existed back then?
This is what?
2004?
Was the original iPhone even out?
Destroy all the cell phone users' cars before time runs out.
Get into your car.
No, this is like old flip phones, right?
This is going to be a horrible mission.
She just baited me.
So bad.
Did you really just do that to me?
Phones that are attached to cars.
You motherfucker.
I swear to God.
No!
Look at how easy that is.
It's almost done.
Great alien music, too.
You should be done.
You should be dead.
Destroy?
Ah, there's another one back here.
Are you turning around?
What way are you driving?
Oh, dummy.
Get out of the way.
Where are you going?
Perfect.
I think time is added for every car that's destroyed.
That would be really bad if it didn't.
I think my face cam's not on.
That would have been an embarrassing face.
I just bit down on my low emote.
I like ate the bottom half of my mouth.
Fucking tubers.
That's fucking tubers.
Get em!
Would you just get em?
Why does that not count?
My car is going to explode.
I need a wrench.
I just know I'm going to be blind for this.
I got it.
All right.
Where's the wrench?
There's a wrench up here, I think.
Right at the top, right?
Yep.
Stupid!
You're stupid!
All right.
You're fine.
You're smart.
Stupid!
Full throttle, right in the back.
It's no damage at all.
His car used my car as a brake.
Now, all the way around.
Come here.
Are you going to...
All right.
He's doing it to himself.
Good.
I win.
There's a sign right here.
Got it.
I got three and a half minutes.
3.50.
I'm good to go.
Just going to wrap around.
That vision sucked.
Hey, slower traffic to the right, please.
What a hard one next time.
That was a hard one.
Well done, sociopath.
Is this the actual game's music?
Now there is no chance my truckasaurus will go on a killing rampage
with the screaming and the sadness and the hosing of blood off the robot.
If you stay in your car when it blows up,
you can drive around in a blown-up car.
Really.
The source is some kind of truck slash dinosaur.
I never would have guessed.
First boss.
Jimmy Neutron dog.
What's the dog's name from Jimmy Neutron?
Gertrude or something?
Goddard.
Did I just get abducted?
707, 101, 33.
I didn't get any new clothes for Bart.
No new clothes for Bart.
It's time for Lisa.
Yep.
I get Lisa's car, which is the best car in the game.
Might as well look and see what the other costumes are.
Lisa, cool.
Hockey.
I mean, I'd have to get that.
Toy train?
I know what it's like to build one of those.
Is there a dead person in that costume?
It is the YouTuber outfit, you're right.
This is the streamer outfit.
Funny streamer outfit.
Yeah, it is.
Now, I must get the last copy of the new Itchy and Scratchy Adventures comic.
It's the controversial issue in which they finally kiss.
Assist me and I will aid you with your dilemma.
Raise the nerd to the Itchy and Scratchy store.
Get the comic book back before time runs out.
Oh, it's a different nerd.
There's like...
I don't like the nerd car.
Impatient.
No, I just don't.
That's a guaranteed loss.
I'm so far ahead of them.
Should I go over this?
Got the comic.
Oh, shit.
They don't let you take a break.
It's just...
Now it's time to go fast again.
You have to go really fast.
They stopped.
My squishy.
Sorry.
No.
Nice spill joke.
Get this inky treasure into its mylar sanctuary.
What a bad start.
I asked you, have you seen him?
I think I saw him at the Noiseland arcade.
Video games.
What a waste of money.
Now to go online and bid $1,000 for itchy and scratchy corncob holders.
A terrific, terrific expense.
I am the queen.
Oh, really?
I don't think you're going to be doing that anytime soon.
Hold on.
I don't want to do this yet.
Don't you mind looking around?
There's money everywhere.
Secrets.
Gags.
I don't want to just blow through the whole video game.
Plus, I gotta pee.
Don't you know?
That Jeremy goes pee every two to three hours on the dot.
Which is what happens.
I missed a coin.
Who cares?
All right, the machine over there.
What is this?
Gag.
It's time for a meltdown.
Is this a meltdown mission?
I don't know if it is.
Please change the outfit.
It sucks.
Thanks.
No, I can't.
Not that quickly.
This is $250.
Am I old enough to drink coffee yet?
Not until you're like 16.
You don't want to drink coffee until you're at least like 15 or 16 at least.
Ooh.
Why is that?
Because I started drinking coffee when I was 20.
I just look like Gumby.
Didn't Gumby drive around in a car like this?
All right, I gotta pee.
I'll be right back.
See you in like three minutes.
Beer be...
Let's go.
Don't scare me like that.
What?
I muted the mic and I just went,
Hey, what is Lisa's double jump?
Hold on, let me just open this fresh beer.
Ooh.
It's a ginger ale.
Relax.
It's a Canada Dry.
Prove it.
I can't.
I don't have any clothes on.
I'm gonna go like wrap a blanket around myself
and then turn the camera off for a second.
Well, that somehow fucked me up completely.
At least his car is the best.
Oh, I don't know why you just freaked me out doing that, but you did.
Are you really coming up behind me right now?
Oh, what?
Easy.
All right.
I gotta be careful going down.
And you went perfectly down there.
No way.
I don't believe that for a second.
You're in second place, Lisa.
All right.
Now go down gently.
I can still get it.
Still pretty, pretty possible.
Okay.
Easy.
Got it.
Oh, it's gonna be close.
Right up my ass.
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, it's oh.
I'm speechless, Lisa.
That was better than you have any right to do.
We're good.
Can I get my car back, please?
Thank you.
What is this?
Bonus.
Gone?
What a tragedy.
To get your mind off this terrible loss which we all feel,
why don't you run a few errands or as I call them grief helpers for me.
But Bart's only missing.
Well, looking for that little monster.
I mean, treasure can't help anything.
Skinner looks like a bird.
Lisa Simpson at your service.
Now you might as well pick up my dry cleaning for me.
You might as well pick up my dry.
No, never mind.
You're ruining the tires, Seymour.
I'm not.
Fine, mother.
No.
It's so hard.
It's real hard to do that on an empty stomach.
Whatever you say, mother.
You've got to eat a shitload of like greasy food before you can do that voice.
Here we are.
This clean house dress is an old lady on principle Skinner.
I really should get back to my search.
Maybe these gold stars will change your mind.
And to the stream voice of what are you on about.
I'm still enjoying the Simpsons hit and run video game.
Why would I turn the stream off right now?
Care for a steamed ab?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I've seen that video.
I have nine seconds.
It's like candy to me.
The more the.
Yes, mother.
Sweet.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Stupid.
The worst driver than you.
Yes, mother.
Are we in Europe?
How am I a bad driver?
It's principle Skinner driving.
But I have seen the hams video.
Oh no.
I swallowed my gum to the emergency room.
I've seen it before.
Wow, mother loves clean house dresses and old lady underwear.
Principal Skinner, I really should get back to my search.
Maybe these gold stars will change your mind.
All right.
I can't believe he's playing my childhood game.
It holds up pretty well.
It kind of does.
If this was on the PlayStation.
This isn't on PC, by the way.
I have it for PlayStation 2.
But I feel like it would be better on PC.
The graphics and shit.
The PS2 version runs at like 20 FPS.
That probably would have been unbearable to watch.
I need principal Skinner's dinner.
Here, do you want to try a new-
I'm a vegetarian.
Oh, there's no meat in it.
Just paste an MSG.
Hold on.
All right, I think I'm okay.
Now I'm going to sneeze.
Do you guys ever choke on air?
I just talked and I said too many words on my throat.
And I just choked on my own voice.
Where's my car?
Principal Skinner, I can't help me.
Oh, the casino.
To search for Bart.
Lisa, I apologize from the bottom of my Vietnam veteran's heart.
I promise this next stop will be the last.
I don't like everything's timed out.
Everything's timed.
It makes it too stressful.
Let the city pay for it.
I'm missing a place to jump down quickly, I think.
It's right ahead.
This is right-
Okay, I'm going to get it, right?
The jump.
No, it's right there.
I don't have the timer anymore.
Soiled myself.
Why did I try that move?
Perhaps it was hubris.
Okay.
Relax.
Get up there.
I just have to go near it and activate it.
I forgot I was this character.
Principal Skinner's personal items.
Hi, little girl.
Hi, you're so cute.
Here's the principal's anti-fungal cream.
Ew.
Thank you.
Push him into the ocean.
That wasn't even worth the jump.
That was fun.
I can't believe that one.
That one over me taking 15 minutes
to sync up and queue up a Nightcrawler line from X-Men 2.
Really?
Speaking of fucking really-
You tried like a girl.
A handicapped one.
Yes, mother-
No!
What the-
I pressed-
Like, ah, they came up so-
Whatever.
I could be so angry at this.
God dammit.
Ah.
I don't-
Wait.
Can you just fail missions?
I'm milking here.
Haven't seen him.
Frozen yogurt?
You just don't finish them.
I'm throwing two dry toppings.
I'd be a Wally Weasels.
He likes the smell of the ball cage.
So I just-
I can't do that one again.
I just skipped it.
Oh.
The time for action is now-
Who's driving the car?
It's some millhouse, is it?
Hey, what?
Wasn't I just talking to you?
Mmm, smell that fresh air.
I was just-
Millhouse?
I was-
What are you doing here?
What's going on?
Lisa!
What a coincidence.
Hey, is that a new dress?
No, I've been wearing this dress for years.
Now, where's Bart?
I think he's at the Planet Hype.
Stop.
Drive to Planet Hype.
Uh, do they go back into-
In the chat, please?
Can't go that way.
You idiot, get out of my way.
I'm not gonna make it.
What just happened to all my money?
What?
How much money did it take?
They just took so much money from me.
I'm here.
Pegasus.
I'm just going through here.
I thought it was a shortcut and I could go through.
Apparently not.
Speaking of shortcuts,
this one right-
I missed it already.
There's another one right there.
Is this gonna work if I go over this?
Because I had to go down all the way to the beach.
Can I drive through this?
Before I do this.
Get the car in the right spot, please.
I need speed.
More speed!
Efficient to drown.
Maybe.
I pulled-
No, there's no way to pull left here.
Except to stay here.
Straight down and then there's-
I don't know if that's a little shortcut
that I can go through with the Krusty Clown thing.
It looks like it,
but maybe I went the wrong way?
I mean, it looks like I can go through here.
No, I can't.
It's just a debate.
It's bullshit.
It's horse shit.
It's just horse shit.
That's gonna happen again.
Oh my lord in heaven, give me a break.
Oh my god.
You have a gift for speed.
This reminds me of when I was a little girl.
I don't want you a shitty car.
Give me back my good car.
Where's a phone?
I should have paid more in the gym.
Give me the Lisa Simpson best car in the game car, please.
Oh, come on!
Give me a wrench so I can have-
Oh, there's a card up there,
but you know what?
Here's a wrench.
Sweet, these are recyclable.
Can't turn that way.
All right, I'm gonna try.
I got enough speed, I think.
Oh shit, I made it.
I did it, I did it.
Okay, we're fine.
Everything's fine.
No, now we relax.
I'm ready.
This is the last time I'm gonna do this shit.
Here we go.
Go.
Don't-
I can't just drive on the boardwalk like this
and not get in trouble.
There we go.
Go.
Don't go through the fake shortcut.
It's not real.
Just drive there.
What is happening with the car?
I did it.
All right, Mailhouse, what do you got?
Kick him into the water, no.
Okay, this is the end of the mission that I will.
All right, mission complete.
Oh.
All right, I'm going for it.
No, never mind.
I was trying to drop the car on him.
Why am I doing that to Mailhouse?
Just drive.
Drop like a car on him.
Nobody likes Mailhouse.
Somebody does.
I'm sure somebody does.
I do?
Yeah, I see.
Hold on a minute.
What's this shit right here?
Look at that.
Platforming?
Oh, would you look at that.
Hey, almost fell off.
The geyser.
Evil braces.
Ooh, something else over here.
What's this?
Don't get cocky here, because I want to see what this is.
Okay, I got them all.
Whoa, where am I?
Oh, that's a little area that you're not supposed to find.
All right, well, cool.
Anything else?
Don't forget that one coin.
People will scream at you.
That's cool.
Why is there no selfie mode?
Ginger ale riot.
Oh, God, hold on.
Can I even turn this on from here?
This crashes the game.
I'm going to be very upset with you guys.
See?
It's off, right?
Yeah.
What?
Save, save, save.
It's all right.
I don't think there's a problem.
I just thought the camera was still on.
Thank God it's not.
We good?
Did I, I didn't.
Did I fucking crash it?
I hope not.
When was the last time I saved the game?
Why did that have to happen?
God damn it.
Un-fucking-believable.
Oh, no.
That's not good.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
It might not be crashed.
It just might need a second.
Hold on.
Come on.
It's coming back.
It's got the black screen.
It looks like it's trying.
Come on.
What have I done?
I don't know how far back that save is
because I had to alt tab and prove that I'm not drinking alcohol.
God damn it.
I think my whole computer is broken.
Well, give me a fucking break.
I'm going to try it again.
Fucking come on.
Really?
I can't believe that.
That's absolute bullshit.
God damn it.
And now I can't get the fucking game to launch.
You got to be kidding me.
The game physically won't launch.
I might have to restart my computer.
No, it's not in the task manager.
It was just going so well and I had to alt tab.
I'm going to try one more thing.
And then, oh, I'm so angry right now.
Of course, I hit the fucking alt tab button
and the whole stream has to turn off.
God damn it.
Let's try it again.
No, it's not in the task manager.
It's just, for some reason,
it doesn't think I have DirectX anymore.
I'm going to have to restart the computer unless I can...
No.
This is going to kill the whole stream, too.
I'm going to have a pain in the ass.
All right.
No, no, no.
Don't change my password on...
What do you want?
What am I doing?
It might be because OBS is still running and it's...
I don't know.
I'm trying to find it in the task manager
and I don't see anything here.
Oh, I was enjoying that, too.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's go.
Oh, this is the first mission of the game.
No, it's the first...
Slow down.
It's okay.
Shit.
All right.
I'm going to do it quick.
God damn it.
And a bunch of people left, too,
because they thought it was over.
So did I.
Oh, come on.
Quick.
Do everything I did really fast.
Speedrun.
Actually, legit speedrun.
I ain't fucking around.
We're getting there in five minutes.
Watch this shit.
I'm so...
I'm so flustered.
There's a shortcut.
I just missed it again.
Spilled my squishy.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Quick.
Come on.
That was it.
That was a bunch of anger and rage
building up in my stomach.
Hit select to boost.
Oh, I know.
I don't care.
No hot tabs.
No, like, fucking choked dick.
No, I'm not doing it.
We're playing Simpsons.
Smash the like button.
Ah, fuck off.
Did you guys not hear...
Did you guys not hear the car?
That was...
That was beefing at the car.
Did you guys didn't hear that?
Ooh.
Did you guys didn't hear the car?
All right.
Bingo.
First try.
Don't fuck it up.
Go.
You ain't ever seen anybody go fucking as fast
as you're going to see me go right now.
What?
Oh my god.
I don't know what happened there.
Why did that happen?
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Which town in America though?
Which one?
Tell us.
We want to know as loyal viewers.
Which one?
What town is it?
Just go over the...
Just do it normal.
Normal.
I'm normal.
Okay.
Get out of the way.
Welcome back, everybody.
Sorry that like 500 of you left.
As I press the alt tab button to put a fucking cape on my body.
Maybe if I just wasn't sitting here without clothes on,
I could just press the camera turn on button.
What's up there?
Yeah.
I was so just...
I was so sad.
I was angry but sad.
Sad angry.
Not even like upset angry.
Because I'm like I want to play this game.
And I almost just almost lost it.
Forever.
Show dick.
Don't make me turn this camera on.
What's in here?
Where am I?
Coin.
It worked.
Oh wait.
Is there a new clothes?
Normal.
Because I am.
What are you doing out there?
Not millhouse.
Grill house?
Bill house.
What's that guy's name?
Ralph.
He's not out here.
Pump it.
Wait.
What's that?
Just one of those one, two, three, four, five, six sided die.
Three sides.
I need to get this card again.
Fast.
I'm not gonna stop.
Just do it quick.
It's right here.
And then the gag is right there too.
Here we go.
Quickly.
He doesn't even need to see where he's going.
Officer Jackson's on the case.
All right.
We are now up to date.
Camp Krusty.
What are you doing here?
What's this?
Can we see the beer again?
I am never gonna alt tab for the rest of my life.
School bus.
Yeah, sure.
I don't know.
Distracting.
I don't like the lights in the back and I don't like the transparency on top.
Safe.
Okay.
I don't know.
True.
Talk to Poop.
Hey, Poop.
Come here.
Whoa, this is terrible.
A very bad man is delivering roadkill to all the Krusty Burgers, which are cheaper
than my quickie dough.
I'm not gonna save again.
Stop it.
To meet the meat eaters, hit and collect meat from Cletus's truck before time runs
out.
Nobody in my store will not be robbed more than four times while I am driving
around today.
One, two, three, four.
Let's just do this, babe.
Yes, sis.
Get off of me.
Giant crowbar just ruined everything.
Here's the meat.
Where's the meat?
I just got so baited again.
Yuck.
Yucky.
Does that count for me?
It doesn't.
No, this car's not gonna explode, right?
I need speed.
More speed.
I am a lean, mean, Vindaloo machine.
Come on.
Perhaps I should refrain from doing that in the future.
Come on, Gwen.
Oh, we gotta go.
Perhaps I should consult Professor Brink at the observatory.
He seems to know everything.
Except why I ever came to this jerkwater burglary.
I just drove on the wrong side of the road.
That wasn't even my fault.
Move your clumsy vehicle.
Cut me off.
Wait, I probably could have driven up, but it's okay.
What just happened?
That was a I died sound.
Action.
Professor Brink.
Let's see now.
We build a monster and then disappeared in a bright light.
Wow, this is crazy.
I need someone to talk to who's wise and learned.
Karma sounds sad.
I am the lizard queen.
I'm alright now.
I was very sad earlier.
I like the saxophone.
That's pretty cute.
This is so cute.
Grandpa, can you help me find Bart?
He's missing.
Maybe I'm just a senile old man,
but Bart's lucky red hat fell out of that black car.
Wow, Grandpa.
What a great call.
You showed why senior citizens are valuable members of the community.
I think my baby teeth are growing back.
That's why I had to punch that nurse.
I better use something big if I want to take that car out.
Like that school bus.
Destroy the black sedans to find a clue.
Don't let time run out.
Lisa Simpson at your service.
Can't jump off that.
Nope.
I do get the school bus though.
Maybe a soy pop would perk me up.
Go, go.
Speed, more speed.
Dude.
Dude, get out of my way.
Oh, I gotta go.
I gotta get outta here.
Why is everybody spamming I gotta go?
Why are you still alive?
Oh, Lisa said it.
What do I think of the movie Pixels?
I didn't see the movie Pixels.
It's probably the Adam Sandler movie.
I didn't see it.
I don't have an opinion on that movie.
Why would I see that movie?
Pac-Man is in that movie.
Yeah, so is Adam Sandler.
Is that Homer?
But so is Pac-Man.
But so is Adam Sandler.
Adam Sandler's not that bad.
You know, he's just a dope.
428, 428, 428.
Oh no, he went over that number right there.
That's funny.
Adam Sandler is not Nicolas Cage.
What, you think they're the same person?
All right, I only have 25 seconds.
Can you, why can you drive to the casino?
But there's a race over here.
One of them talks like this.
You know what I'm saying?
Nicolas Cage talks like this, unfortunately.
No, I'm doing, I'm doing.
Nick, what's his name?
Nick Offerman, the guy from Parks and Rec.
Now let me tell you, as a man, as an American, I...
This is a surprise.
Yeah, Ron Smonson.
That's like Nick Stevenson.
Nick Offerman?
What's his name?
This dip is that his name is not Ron Swanson in real life.
Why, I'm not getting a ha-ha right now.
Don't even think about it.
I'm very fragile right now.
I almost just all tabbed out of the whole world.
It's not ha-ha for you.
It's ha-ha for Nelson.
Why?
I'm here with the school bus for some reason.
I already did this one.
I did this before the alt tab.
Why did I just...
What happened?
That was really weird.
What do I think of rocks?
Or what does Ron Swanson think of rocks?
Well, I do kind of like rocks a little.
I'm just doing Jora Mormond?
All right, I fucking restart the stupid race.
I already beat this.
It's not even fair.
I already won.
This guy is doing this on purpose.
What are you all doing?
What are you doing?
Why would you do what you just did?
This person's not supposed to be in first place.
Ever.
This is not happening.
He's just radically driving around like crazy.
Like a phrased person.
I'm so mad.
I gotta catch up.
That was pretty good too, but you can't even control it.
Yeah, I know.
I understand that I am losing to the sedan AI.
I know, but like something really weird happened.
Can we not have like a freak out moment
where everybody just drives into each other and drives into me?
Like this person is still doing it.
Fucking sedan AI.
Get out of the way.
I'm in first place, Lisa.
You're supposed to be the smart one.
There's so many more laps.
This is 40 laps.
45 more laps.
What am I going to do with all that?
I'm fine.
I'm about to lap you.
I gotta lap this guy.
No, I'm not going to lap him.
I'm speechless, Lisa.
That was better than you have any right to do.
BM.
Yeah, that was BM right there.
But you can't BM sedan AI.
It's the fastest thing I got right now.
Could you come get me?
Mr. Plow?
No, I like the sports car.
Finish all the races.
Yeah, I gotta come across them though.
It's hard for me to remember where they are.
Thank you.
All right.
Here's this mission here.
Wait.
I'll go too fast.
All right, Chief.
What is going on?
Be getting paid in potato chip coupons.
So what disguise do you have?
Well, here's one of Ralph's old Halloween costumes.
Fine.
Wait here and I'll get changed.
Let's meet in the middle.
Show a singular toe.
Need to disguise, purchase Lisa's cool clothes.
The house is not a disguise.
It's not a disguise.
I hate seeing the Florida.
Thank God.
All right, where do I buy a shirt?
Somewhere over here?
Can I phone in a t-shirt?
Where's t-shirt?
They just told me where to go.
But it didn't put them thing on my mini map because I'm stupid.
Oh, it's not the gas station.
What's over here?
Nice.
I don't have no idea what we're doing.
Wait.
Yeah, I do.
Never mind.
I thought there was something up there.
Comic book store, comic book store, comic shop, comic shop, comic, comic, comic, comic, comic, comic, comic.
Comic book, comic book, comic book, comic books.
No, that says coffee books.
No, that says cafe books.
I thought it said comic books.
What is this?
Arcade, books, cafe.
Whatever.
I know what's right there.
I was trying to get it.
There's a card on top.
Lisa, cool.
I'm running out of money.
Return to the casino.
What sucks?
Stream sucks?
Did you just say?
Did you just say the stream sucks?
Oh, all right.
You know, we have to have a 1v1
Cod Wager match.
Now that you said that.
Follow Snake and find three strikes of evidence against him.
Don't miss any items.
Jeans.
That guy just ran somebody over.
For a second, did he just drop a lamp?
No, he ran that over.
What'd he drop?
A person.
An elderly person without a license.
That's a moving violation.
All right.
Don't give me shit.
That's bullshit.
The game decided that it was.
If I was in a competition right there,
I would have just been very mad.
That's not a wager right there.
You're just lucky I can't remember faces.
Score one for Wiggum.
Sorry, sorry.
Extreme to the max.
Strike two.
Running over an elderly person without a license.
That's showing him what for.
He really wants to go on that bridge, doesn't he?
I need speed.
More speed.
I can't do that.
How am I supposed to do what you just did?
You just magnetized over all those rocks.
Legally sanctioned violence.
Strike.
Counterfeit designer jeans.
The foulest of all things.
I need speed.
More speed.
Cursed streamer.
You want a cursed streamer?
I hope you're recyclable.
Smashing.
Strike two.
Running over an elderly person without a license.
No.
I'm going to hold on to that one.
That's not funny.
I was getting close.
There it is.
Okay, thank God.
I was going to do a whole thing where I put a curse on everybody.
As a witch.
But I could feel the eyeballs on that.
Get out of my fucking way.
And I missed the shortcut.
It's going to be close because I missed the easiest shortcut in the video game.
Sorry, I got 20 seconds.
And strike three.
Literate.
Got it.
We got all we need on this lowlife.
Now, about your brother.
I've seen lots of mysterious government types over at the docks.
Uh, maybe they send him on a nice cruise.
They got some great package deals these days.
Five buffets per boat.
I want...
Oh, a buffet.
Sometimes I fucking forget where I live.
Ooh.
That sounds...
That sounds great.
Did I just do a handstand?
Oh, I could go for...
I could go for just some dog shit buffet chicken nuggets.
You know, when you go over to the chicken nugget buffet,
there's like 400 chicken nuggets there and you just load it up.
You just keep putting them on the plate.
You don't even give a shit.
And sometimes there's just a random vegetable there.
You load up on asparagus.
Who's this person?
Who's this random dude?
Who is that random seahorse?
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
I'm trying to get in the car.
No, I gotta take a...
I gotta take out a fish.
Okay.
You missed seven.
No, I didn't.
How?
I got it and it didn't even do anything for me.
Ooh.
Buffet.
They have like fish sticks there.
Sometimes they got some fish there.
That turned way faster than I thought it was.
Fish sticks at a buffet?
Sometimes, yeah.
They got like fried cod.
Not necessarily fish sticks, but fried fish sticks.
I know what that is.
I don't get it.
Why did I even turn...
I look at chat and I see somebody says,
Jerma, you seem off today.
You seem off today.
No, I'm just having fun, man.
Did I...
I already got that.
Yeah, I got that interaction, right?
Chat seems more off than Jerma does.
Yeah, what's going on?
What's wrong with you guys right now?
What happened?
What's going on here?
I guess I have to go down there.
I'm here watching the world's worst gamer.
I don't think that's true.
I think you're just saying that.
Watch this, buddy.
This kid's still here.
Thanks for delivering me catch of the day.
Now, I can tell you, I saw your brother.
Really?
That's great.
He was in the long black limo.
And ahoy, there she drove.
Took me hours to finish this when I was young.
Get her to the black limo to find Bart.
Let's just do this thing for speed.
Uh, doesn't seem like the right car for this.
Into the water?
How did you just turn that around on me?
Into the water.
Get into the water.
I'm losing this fight.
What kind of limo is this?
Strongest damn limo I've ever seen.
Drop in frames.
Ah, crap.
It's alright.
It'll pass.
Usually does.
My car is gonna blow up before this does.
Give me that wrench.
I'm only halfway there.
How am I gonna do this?
I need another car for this.
I thought that was full speed.
Gonna push you into a wall or something.
Drive him into the wall.
Into the wall.
Ah, let's just do it again.
If I see a phone, I'm getting out.
There we go.
How are you on top of my car?
Yeah, I'll be alright though.
I'm good, I'm good.
I don't need a phone.
You just have to drive him into the wall.
Like this.
I have to stay behind him.
There we go.
Just keep the momentum behind him
and he will drive into walls.
See?
At least that's what I'm talking about.
One more.
Right into the wall.
Into the wall.
Come on.
Right there, bang.
That's not enough.
Drive into something.
I'm being towed.
Ah!
You have no idea how hard that was to keep that up.
Alright, let's see.
Captain?
Went down the wrong tube.
Sorry.
Punch it.
He ate his pant?
Ate pant.
Alright, what's next?
It's timed!
No!
What?
Oh my god, what am I doing?
I was just...
Okay, I'm good.
What happened?
Did I get barred?
Did I find barred?
I found him.
Shit.
Alright, I found barred.
That's fine.
What?
What's going...
Where's barred?
Where does this want me to go?
In the boat?
The arrow stops here.
I gotta go to the other side.
Can I make this jump?
There's a ramp?
Did I miss the ramp on the other side?
Where is this thing?
There it is.
Bart!
Oh no, this is not good.
Where was the ramp on the other side?
I just...
I drove around in a circle.
Did I...
I missed it when I was on the way up?
God damn it.
You know what?
Like this...
For the love of god.
I'm gonna do this in five seconds.
Or not.
You just have 500,000 health.
Right into the wall.
Rash.
They made this way too tough to kill this thing.
It just has too much health.
A child could do this?
No, no, no, no!
Remember the person in chat that said
this mission took them like seven hours?
No, this is not a...
Get out of the way.
No, and I'm looking at fucking chat.
Yeah, as a child...
Do you know how hard these old
fucking games from like the 2000-1998 era are?
They're so hard.
They're incredibly hard.
They're difficult video games.
Go load up Donkey Kong Country.
I guarantee you rage quit after the first world.
All right, so where's this jump?
If I follow the arrows here...
The arrows are pointing me to go this way.
Why...
Then they stop.
Why would the arrows tell me to go this way?
If I don't have to go this way.
That doesn't make...
Why are they on the ground there?
Was I actually in the right spot last time?
Like in here?
Just hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
So do not follow the arrows on the ground,
which for the entire, entire video game,
it points you in the right direction
to where you're supposed to drive.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Right there.
I just...
I don't see it.
I'm serious.
Like over here...
Where is this?
I know it's right there,
but how do I get in there?
Just drive this way.
Oh my fucking God.
Well, it's not even pointing me in the right direction.
The arrows didn't even remotely go this way.
I can do it.
Oh my fucking God.
No!
No, God!
I can do it in the jump!
Bart!
Where is he?
Oh!
He didn't tell me to go...
Whatever.
They didn't...
I know I did that jump before,
but the arrows to get there weren't...
I thought I had to go a different way.
Why wouldn't the arrows point like to go over the ramp?
Oh, I get to be Marge now.
Wait, let me play with the TV.
What is wrong with Bart?
Bart, what's causing your ooga booga talk?
My special little guy's nougat has turned to goo goo.
The whole town's gone nuts.
Security cameras, mysterious vans, crop circles.
There's got to be a connection.
Yeah, something's wrong with his...
I think the game might be fucked up.
You hear him?
He's like blah blah blah.
I think the audio fucked up.
That's how...
Why is Marge running like this?
Easy come, easy go.
Marge Simpson, at your service.
Hold on!
Send the bill to...
So am I on the final family member?
Is this the last chapter of the game?
All right, I did it.
Now I gotta talk to you.
Chief Wiggum, I need you to find out what happened to Bart.
Could you show me where the crop circle is?
There's got to be a clue to curing Bart.
Ha, that's cute.
I'd love to help, but I got sugar withdrawal real bad.
The doughnut store is closed and I got a monkey on my back screaming for crawler.
Oh, he's screaming.
Oh god, hit the doughnut truck to get the doughnuts.
I need 10 doughnuts starting now.
We're gonna we got a first try missions here.
I can't do any more scream missions where I scream.
Hey, thanks for the doughnut.
Uh, it's not gonna happen.
About this late.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
They give you plenty of time for this one.
I'm so glad.
Oh my god, I would be like, what the fuck?
You know what I mean?
I'd be like, what the fuck?
Let's get a stupid fuck.
Oh, how's that for a turn around?
No, I didn't want the camera to change.
I wanted to be able to see where I was going.
Man.
Oh man.
Oh, get...
Oh, all right.
My whole body just almost exploded.
I want a new costume for March.
I had one for Homer, had one for Lisa, had two for Lisa.
Let me take a look.
I need some money.
I need money.
I need like 300, 400, 500.
Something like that.
What is her attack?
You want to know what the best Simpsons video game ever made is?
And I kind of wish I could play it.
I wonder if there's a way to play it.
Remember the Simpsons arcade game?
That game was amazing.
The beat-em-up.
That was probably the best Simpsons video game ever.
How about that side?
Is there a card?
There's a card over there.
I wonder if I can make it from here.
Not really.
It's going to be a tough jump.
Didn't even...
Whatever.
Goodbye.
There's a version of the 360.
Is there really?
That's actually awesome.
All right.
Inmate March, Classy March, or Police March?
I only have 300 points.
I need 400 for Police March.
No, no.
I'll save it.
Speaking of saving it.
All right.
So I can just try collecting money.
Save Millhouse.
Kill Millhouse.
Why would you want me to do something like that?
Millhouse is a great, great young lad.
There is a race available.
I didn't do the other ones.
But I need to do the three races.
I have to.
What is that car?
All right.
Do I get that?
For doing the three races.
How am I ever going to compete with this?
Oh.
That, apparently.
I was going too fast.
The SUV, you can't turn it very well.
If I do that again, I might be able to do it.
This is not the right car for this.
No.
Not going to happen.
Clown car.
There's a lot of cars, huh?
Sedan is probably the best one.
Or Lisa's car.
And Lisa's going to drive.
How do you get the clown car?
We were promised a clown car.
How do I unlock it?
You've got to buy it.
How much is it?
It's not nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
He's still playing this?
Yeah.
I'm probably going to complete it tonight.
I can't start Simpsons hitting a run and not finish it.
He thinks he's going to do it.
Oh yeah, I'm going to do that.
I'm going to try this.
It's a minimum of 11 hours.
Well, is it?
Straight through.
I don't want to go too fast.
That's why, but I'm the first still.
All right, now stay in first.
Holy shit, this car is so fast.
How am I going to keep in front of you?
What?
Marge?
You went over that and it turned out it was a bad idea.
I got to hit every one of these like secret jumps.
I'm not ready for this one.
That car is too good.
I need the clown car before I come back.
Try it one more time.
I have to beat all these to get the clown car.
Rotten Fresh just gave $50.
Hey, Jerma, I just got a job.
Want to give back?
It's the people that meant the most.
So here I am.
Plus, I loved this game when I was a kid.
Enjoy.
Thank you so much, Rotten.
For your $50.
Your huge $50.
Thank you.
That means a lot.
$50 bucks.
Yeah.
Congratulations on the...
Is there a skip right here?
Is this a skip?
Nice skip.
I wish Marge would just sit down.
That doesn't really do anything for me.
I feel like I shouldn't even do that one.
You're just so much faster than me.
Ooh.
You screwed up, though.
He can go over that grass better than I can.
No.
I...
I think I need a better car.
I think I need to come in with a faster or better handling car.
There's always twists and turns and...
That car is just twice as fast as mine.
I'm gonna take more shortcuts.
Well, I have to memorize where the shortcuts are
and that is not gonna happen.
I can guarantee you that.
I never underachieve at anything.
Is this going to affect my insurance?
We both just about...
Holy shit.
He fucked it all up.
Come on.
Pay attention.
No!
He went over the thing.
Whatever.
The giant thing.
I don't know what it was.
He's doing every single...
You have to hit every single shortcut.
I just don't know where they are.
Ah.
God damn it.
You have to hit every single shortcut.
I had it.
I don't even know what I fucking hit there.
No.
He's taking all the shortcuts.
It's not even a race.
It's just cheating.
This is not a race.
This is who can cheat better.
Which one of you two can take the cheat codes better?
No.
I'm done.
No thanks.
No.
No thank you.
Nope.
I know.
Hold on.
Just give me a second.
Wait till the cut scene's over.
I have to alt tab.
Save the goddamn game.
All right.
It's saved.
Okay.
Here we go.
I don't know why my streamlabs is minimized.
And I don't know why the hell that happened.
It's actually gone.
Why is it gone?
That's weird.
Did I like X out of the window?
No.
I had it up.
That's very weird.
All right.
Now I can see.
So we had huge money.
We had 50 dollars from lightning rider.
You can be here.
I believe in you.
I'm sorry that that's not true.
Thank you so much for the 50 dollars.
I wasn't going to spend the next two hours trying to do that.
Sometimes you got to accept when you can't do something.
And I'd rather just enjoy the game.
And why is the-
Who's holding the fucking horn down?
Okay.
Apparently I was.
It's a blank screen.
Shouldn't be.
Why are you doing this now?
I think I'm going to have to restart the game.
Yes, I am.
Let's try it again.
Okay.
Come on back.
Hey, look.
I didn't save right there.
So we're fine.
Resume game.
But no lightning rider.
Thank you so much.
50 fucking dollars.
And then there were 20 community subs from-
How long ago was that?
Feels good to stretch my games.
That's from Great-
Was that from Great Canadian?
Excuse me.
I don't care if you is from New York.
You ain't taking pictures of our decrappitude for no magazine, no life.
No, Cletus, it's me, Marge.
Marge.
But that's 50 dollars as well.
So thank you so much, guys.
There's been like three or four 50 dollar donations.
And then like a bunch of subs to-
Everyone better stay out of my-
Thank you.
I need some roll range.
Eat pickup, city folks.
Uh, I wasn't paying any attention to that.
I gotta hit you and then pick up your stuff that falls out of your trunk.
What the hell is going on with this game?
Sure hope no one saw that.
What is it dropping?
I'm gonna lose them.
Oh man, it's getting close to me to break my controller in half.
Arch Simpson, at your service.
Come on.
Break it.
There it goes.
Oh, I did it.
It's into- I made a switch control.
Are you serious?
Comfy.
Pretty comfy.
All right.
Can you drop another one?
Or do I have to ram you?
Why would I bring the biggest car in there?
Where are you going?
No, don't go down.
Up on two wheels.
Ten more community subs from 64fanatic.
Thank you.
Another big drop.
Speaking of big drops, can you drop the last item?
Did I win?
Thank you so much 64.
Thank you Great Canadian for your 20.
Thanks a lot guys.
Number four hours ago when you said you wouldn't get mad at this game?
Well that's- there was a lot of factors involved.
There's like four factors.
It's not just the video game.
I just have to pee.
So I'll pee again.
Who could get mad at the Simpsons?
No, I'm mad at like my computer.
That was like the alt tab bullshit from like an hour ago.
That was- that's what started the whole thing.
I was fine.
I gotta pee.
I'll be right back.
I will be right back.
you
Hello.
All right, where we going?
That guy looks like a cat.
Don't get your clothes dirty.
Oh, I have to buy those?
Do I have to buy them?
I don't have- I need more money.
I don't want this car.
I hate this car.
I want a car they don't hate.
How about this one?
Junk it.
Junk that one.
Lisa, why do you have to hold the horn down when I get in every time?
All right, I need to go to the uh-
Change my clothes, which is literally right in front of me.
Is this mission money or do I have to pay for this?
Do I have to pay for this, don't I?
I don't want to pay for this.
Shit.
It sticks to the gun.
It's the first gun I've seen all game.
Game save, slow skull.
Oh, no, no.
I want to use that car.
Oh, bye Lisa.
Harvest ketchup packets for the winter.
Don't let time run out.
I'll do my best.
God.
I have two minutes to get 18.
Thank god I figured that out in a quarter of a second.
Help me fetch them.
All right, hold on, hold on.
Oh, shit.
What is going on with the grass?
Fix the grass.
I don't understand what happened here.
I don't even know what I did.
I don't even know what happened.
Oh, I see another one.
It's still possible.
Don't worry.
Remember these shortcuts.
Oh, I'm not gonna.
That was better than the movie box.
There's a lot of shit down here.
This last one.
I'm sorry, no, but that person should have watched where they were.
Where is it?
Is it up?
It's up.
Okay.
What?
I'll do my best.
I don't understand.
Why was it above me?
I have to go off a ramp?
We need them ketchup packets people done
thrown out to feed on during the long winter.
Help me fix you.
That's not very nice.
Hey, I know another dumpster's around here somewhere.
I can feel it in my stank bone.
I could have made a good septic system out of that.
Oh, don't crash into it.
I'm not that smart.
This is real fine.
This handling feels like shit and I'm not the one playing.
Well, this car is.
That part right there is.
Oh my god.
Before I did this mission, I looked over in the chat
and I saw somebody say, I hate this mission.
Now I think I was like, well, I wonder why.
I could have made a good septic system out of that.
I need to start over.
Oh, I can drive 55.
We need them ketchup packets people done
thrown out to feed on during the long winter.
Help me fix you.
Why are you making a septic system out of ketchup?
I know another dumpster's around here somewhere.
That's not all right.
I can feel it in my stank bone.
There's nothing even in here.
What is it?
Is it the vinegar that's in there?
Oh, that looked expensive.
Weave the needle.
All right, this is the part that gets me every time.
This little spot.
I'm not sure there's a clean way to do that.
Help me load.
Right here.
Oh, that was sloppy.
Thank god it's okay, though.
All right.
Now, so I was supposed to just drive around
and go over a ramp or something.
I wish I had some really big tires
like I saw on the TV once.
Am I supposed to?
Which way am I supposed to go?
Down here?
And then what?
Around?
Oh, I got 40 seconds to get out of here.
Oh, man.
Okay.
Please don't make it.
How do I?
Thank god.
Get away from the sedan.
That was, that one was not good.
Do it!
Don't worry, you got teleported, Marge.
Excellent work.
Look, you mind should ask some other old folks about it.
Maybe try around the graveyard.
Thanks, Cletus.
Twernt nothing.
I won?
I think I'm gonna sneeze.
I'm sorry.
In advance, I'll get it.
Okay.
Hey, you.
You just gotta help old Gilog.
Clown car.
350 coins.
The curator.
300.
I'm gonna go find some coins.
Because I need that.
Where can I get coins?
Any more secret coins?
That's a different clown car.
Well, a clown car is a clown car is a clown car.
It is.
A clown car is a clown car.
They're all cl-
It's a clown car.
When you have one clown car,
and another clown car next to a clown car,
they're all clown cars.
Who needs a clown car when you have those?
This is my new car.
Forever.
Can I save this in a garage somewhere?
All right, mole man.
What do you need?
Excuse me, Hans, mole man.
Can you help?
I'm hiding from the police.
If the police find me out past curfew,
they'll throw me in jail.
I won't survive another night in jail.
Well, I was wondering if you've ever seen a crop circle.
Talk to Abe.
He mentioned crop circles once.
Hurry up and get to the home
before the police lock the doors.
Race Chief Wiggum to the retirement castle.
Everyone better stay out of my way!
I wasn't ready.
You can't just one, two, three, go blaze by me
at like a hundred miles per hour.
Ah, I didn't go.
This thing's actually kind of making me free.
This is like hurting my brain.
When I turn the whole world,
it's like Mario Kart, man.
This is like, it hurts my head.
What the fuck?
All right, this thing's cool, but-
It's like old school Mario Kart.
And the whole world spins when you turn the car.
Oh my, really?
Okay.
Maybe I shouldn't pick this thing.
I'm gonna try this one more time.
I lost.
Unbelievable.
I gotta get rid of this thing.
I need to-
My whole body hurts.
Dude, I'm not even gonna get on this stupid thing.
Just get on a regular car.
Oh, I just killed Grandpa.
Dude, Grandpa's voice?
Okay, sure.
I can't.
No, that's not gonna happen.
That's not gonna happen.
Just kill him!
With a timer, for what?
I tried to-
Tried to correct it.
They just throw these like 25 second timers at you.
Like, all right.
That moon is massive.
This is pretty big, isn't it?
Uh, probably could have gone off.
Yeah, I could have gone off that.
Is that the-
Oh, that doesn't-
No, I gotta talk to-
You give it back right now.
Oh, we traded it to some dudes in a black car for these playdudes?
Check it out, man.
This one's got an interview with the guy who invented the wah-wah pedal.
Even Marge thinks it's nice.
Where are you going, boy?
Are you?
Okay.
I'm hitting the corner, apparently, somehow.
All right.
Like, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but like, follow the guy while he drops items for the 50th damn time.
I, like, come on.
What the hell?
I'm gonna lose.
You just realized you've been doing the same four missions the whole game?
I think I just realized that right now.
Am I actually just coming to that realization right now?
Let's try it again.
Hooligan's still an old man.
Leesic's driving me insane.
Give me that money.
Actually, it is.
It's quite a lot of money.
Easy, Marge.
There are reading chat.
All right, let's do it.
Oh, he did the same thing.
Which way did he do it?
Down here?
This dude's doing all kinds of fucked up moves.
Hold on.
Oh, and I have another timer.
What are you guys spanning?
What is this spam?
Dude, I can't read this yet.
Just, I can't read it.
Just wait.
I can't read that.
Get away from...
Hold on, I don't wanna fuck this up right now.
Oh my god, another...
Where?
Why?
Don't even think...
You gotta be kidding me.
That's unbelievable.
Don't...
This can't be how this ends.
Like, this can't be how this ends.
Okay, grandpa.
Power is good, Jesus.
All right, dude, you seriously suck at this game.
Play an easier game, dude.
I don't think Simpsons Hit and Run is the one for you.
Uh, I...
I should say that I put at least 2,000 hours into this game.
It's more complicated than this.
All right, that's...
Okay.
You're such a crazy, innocent grandpa.
Why?
No!
We need medication!
Gimme, gimme, gimme!
Now I need something to wake him up.
You guys...
You guys are fucking out of control.
Wait, keep the same clothes?
What, is that...
Is that a copypasta thing?
Am I getting copypasted right now?
Stop this freaking time.
Tell me about the crap circles.
There I was surrounded by Tojo and his Nazi henchmen.
When one of them, a raccoon as I recall,
hit me with a banjo.
Now I never reason with a raccoon,
let alone a Nazi one.
So I...
Grandpa, what does this have to do with the crap circle?
Not a thing.
Where was I?
Right, now.
The first time I rode in a water car...
You guys...
You guys are gonna get yourselves in trouble.
It was so long ago that I'll have to describe it in sepia tone.
You guys are gonna get in trouble.
I just got let out of a bottle.
I was inside of a bottle
and somebody like shook it and let me out.
Clown car or get wrecked.
Why don't you get wrecked?
Clown car.
Clown car or get wrecked.
I'm gonna do the entire gnome video.
You guys don't start behaving.
Over and over again.
I'm gonna do for like 20 minutes straight.
Maggie!
He's melting down.
No, I'm not melting down.
I'm not.
I've had a couple of like...
Oh!
Moments where you go...
What the fuck?
Oh no!
Am I missing something in there?
What?
Go to bed?
Is it going to somebody's door?
What's going on here?
In the backyard?
The door was blinking.
Give me that trading card.
Oh!
I can't believe it!
This will be Marge's secret.
I hope this isn't stealing.
Ooh.
What?
I'm not gonna help!
Oh, he's freaking out.
He's freaking out.
Clown car time.
Not yet.
What a fucking psycho.
No, come on.
Give me a little bit of credit here.
I'm playing an old 2000s game.
It's very hard.
It's considered one of the hardest video games of the last century.
And I'm talking, yeah.
Back when...
Fucking...
Saddle's Tees, whatever his name was.
The guy, the Caesar...
That was putting people inside of a fucking dome and making them fight each other.
I'm talking that harder than that.
Dude, you seriously suck at this game.
Do something easier.
I was so worried.
I have...
I'm going to the arcade.
2,000 hours in this game.
Because the spirits eagles all the way to the top.
I need a little extra firepower.
As Officer Marge.
Serve and protect.
Purchase Marge's police uniform at the Quickie Mart Barth's room or...
I mean, there it is.
I don't have enough.
Bathroom, bathroom, bathroom, bathroom, bathroom, bathroom, bathroom, bathroom.
I'm going.
There's no bathroom in here.
Why is everybody yelling bathroom?
Enough?
No.
I have to steal money from fucking slanders.
Hold L and R and press A, B.
I'm not cheating.
No, I'm beating this game.
Legitimately.
I got enough money.
Ready to go?
Jerma, I have over 2,000 sucks at this game.
Why did I just read that?
There's no reason for me to read what you just said.
Look at your new outfit in the window.
Run and collect all the evil Cola cans before time runs out.
What?
What? You mean out here?
Is Marge on drugs?
Aerobics classes.
Just let me catch my breath.
Should I be...
I have to be walking, right?
Listen to how my...
How would I ever do this without...
Go all the...
Yes!
Cones.
Get the coins.
Did I miss any?
I think I missed two.
Where are these?
Wait, is it...
I can go...
I can get them around, right?
Get it!
I don't...
Oh my...
I couldn't see where I was going.
I don't think I'm gonna do it.
You know, like, get these trees out of the way!
Yes!
Hold on a minute.
Can I even...
What?
Okay, so I have to go...
I guess...
It's still possible.
Maybe.
Not though.
And I figured they're all in a line.
So for next time, where's the easy way for me to get up here?
Is it around the building or from...
Do I have to jump from...
It's over here.
Camera.
I almost could have had it.
Everyone better stay out of my way!
I need a long aisle and ice tea!
I'm not allowed to fail the mission once?
To see where I need to go?
Why?
No, first try only!
Only first try!
Only!
All right, so then now I go from here.
Can you please pick it up?
Get the ones down here.
Two.
Uh...
Get a wraparound.
Why's the running and the jumping...
Is it...
I'm doing it wrong, but...
Oh man.
I still can do it.
I can still get up there, I think.
I'm just running in circles.
Yeah, whatever.
There's a better way for me to get up there.
Can I get over there from here, though?
Is it the most...
I don't even know the way to get over there.
I really don't.
Go up on the billboard.
Billboard.
Get off!
Get off of it, Marge!
What are you doing?
Get it?
Come on.
Okay, Marge.
Let's go.
I will get to the bottom of this.
Well, it made Bart go crazy.
And if I find the distributor, I'm gonna give them a piece of my mind.
Careful, Mrs. Simpson.
This cola makes people do irrational things without guilt.
It is as though they have bottled the effects of a raging fratkegger.
That's it.
I'm going after it.
And any other evil cola trucks I can find.
I'll do my best.
I will destroy them.
I will try.
Okay.
Kill trucks.
Slow and steady wins the race.
Dump fucking toxic waste on them.
Isn't I the right vehicle for this?
Am I gonna have to do the whole Marge thing?
No, sit up!
Because I might have to do the whole stupid soda can thing again.
Oh, God, no.
Smashy, Smashy!
I'm so totally embarrassed.
Gamer, sit up!
I'm not doing enough damage.
Oh, somehow I pancaked him into the wall.
And that...
That...
Alright.
Whatever.
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
Let's do it!
This car doesn't stink too bad.
Come here, loser!
Get over here, loser!
How's that not any damage?
Alright, when he drives accidentally, gently into the wall,
it's more damage than flying off a goddamn cliff.
I just polished that.
Into the wall.
Yeah, I love the Tom Arnold music. No, that's an actor. What's his name?
What the fuck are you doing? Why would you do that to me? I need you to drive into a wall or into another car or anything.
Into this wall!
Into something!
Into the wall!
Why does that not do any damage to you?
Okay.
Those two head-on car crashes.
He got smashed into that car head-on.
How did it blow up the first time? Because it bumped into a pole.
It smacked its side into a little medium and it destroyed it. I have to get a bigger car.
Yeah, probably.
I can't, this is just gonna get a lot better. Just, hello Superman. I'd like to fucking report a disturbance.
I'm sorry. Could you give me a lift? Too bad he didn't use the clown car. I am. Just wait till he comes over here.
Come on.
Look at these full rams. Get very good at this. Same, that was the same guy.
He's gonna drive.
I should pay more attention. Do I get credit for that? No, he's still alive. He's still alive. Yeah. Okay, great. That's fantastic.
He just drove off the cliff into the ocean and he's still alive. All right, he just-
I don't understand. He just crashed like three times.
Here comes another one. Maybe I can get- see? Where was the damage on that? He just drove straight into that guy.
I used to give my controller bite marks because of this game.
Wait a second. That's so funny. Oh no, did I blow it?
I'm gonna lose. Oh, die. Bite marks.
I just beat every mission. Oh, give it a rest, all right? No way. I don't believe you. I don't believe you for a minute.
I see some of you guys in this chat with your mouths going
You bit your controller because you lost one of these missions like 15 times in a row. I know it. I'm certain of that.
I mean, I didn't even have to say it. Somebody just talked about how they were biting things.
So, come on.
I have two thousand hours.
No, this car is gonna explode. I can't do it here. No, I don't want a bite me thing.
If this car explodes, I'm turning on the webcam and I'm biting someone.
Jerma, how is it possible that you could be this bad?
Oh, is it possible?
It's the only thing that gives me the courage to take off my shirt in the station locker room. You're going down.
Adam Sandler. Adam Sandler.
Jerma, I mean, look at me.
30, whatever. 30 percent? Did he get 30 percent? I don't, I can't, there's no noise I can even do.
30 percent? I can't, I can't. Wait, new character? Nice.
Armored truck. Armored truck. Armored truck. Jerma sucks. Jerma sucks. All right. I don't want to like keep pushing that.
Just stop throwing rocks at my house.
I hear like, this is all, this is what I hear right now. I hear like,
get him. Did they fucking throw rocks at my house? Who's doing this? All right, open up my front door.
In my mouth. And then I close the door really fast. I got hit in the face with a rock.
We got him cornered. What does he want me to do?
300 million? How? Hurry up or my arranged bride will chastise me.
I have been selling tainted cola. Unless I redeem myself, I will be reincarnated as a sea cucumber.
Throw more rocks. Or worse, a land cucumber. I must find the source of this evil beverage.
The Soda Invo is commanded I go here. They're just whipping rocks at my house.
I look over, I'm like, what are they even, why, what are they saying?
I am the greatest driver in all the land. Follow the coal truck and collect all the evidence.
Don't miss any coal. I must admit the smell of fresh air is much more pleasing than the
odor of the hot dog machine. Who put this here? It makes no sense. This is just between me and
you, random object. Is this the armor truck thing that you guys talking about? Holy shit.
Will I know if it's the armor truck level because will there be rocks thrown at my house?
What is that? I don't know. Talk to Louie at the legitimate business thing. I will later.
Hello? Hello, stereotypical Italians. Please do tell me the source of the evil cola.
We don't know nothing. Except that the brands are controlled by mysterious strangers.
Anyway, you shouldn't stick your nose in other people's business.
It could come back to haunt you and your family. Oh my gosh, your thinly veiled threat
has reminded me of my fatherly duties. I'm supposed to pick up the octoplets at the doctor's.
Drive to the hospital before time runs out. Avoid them all. Hopefully my store will not
be robbed more than four times while I am driving around today. There's a time limit
Got it. I'm actually not sure what the hell I just did. Oh no, my babies. Your babies
are about to go to the bathroom all over my waiting room and diapers aren't covered by your
insurance. You better hurry. I heard the parents of the Shelby bill nine are grabbing
every diaper in town. I will get the diapers but there's no way I could fit them in my car.
Maybe Mr. Homer will have a large gas guzzling American vehicle that I could use.
To complete this mission you will need Homer's custom-built car.
Purchase it from Homer in the hospital parking lot for 500 coins or call it from a phone.
How much money do I have? Thankfully there's bugs over here with money.
500. I'm gonna have to do some exploring. Hmm I see over here. Sick. Please drink water.
It's been six hours. I haven't I've been getting a drink. You guys don't really think
I'm just sitting here like. Help! Help me! I'm trying out! If you give me a ride I will pay
you a million dollars in the next life I promise. This is not good for my insurance.
It's a couple of coins and there's a wrench. I need way more than this.
Well we got another mission here. Excuse me nice Mr. Shopkeeper person. Have you seen a
hovering death machine? No nothing specifically of the hovering kind no. Oh this was to be my
greatest invention since side burns in a can. They make you handsome and lovely. What are
you talking about? I call it the hover car tm. So don't try to steal the name it's tm'd.
I installed the onboard computer and it came alive and attacked my person. With the love
of all that's gliding you gotta help me here. Okay what on earth can I do? Knock the
flesh rigging the thing off the road before the authorities come and take me away again.
Prisons ain't kind to pencil neck geeks like myself. They they stomp and they kick.
Jerva died hours ago we're just hearing the gases releasing.
Better hurry. That's why I left this door hoodlums put pornography in the bridal magazines.
What are you talking about?
Oh look you fucked it up didn't you?
What are you trying to pull with this crazy driving?
What in the hell were you thinking? It's a Futurama reference. I know when they squeeze
on him and he goes. I've seen that video. I've seen that movie. I've seen that TV program.
That's not a shortcut. So I get this car. Don't you guys tell me?
Move. The opponent in every direction arrows.
No no no. Hey professor how are you? Great my Hindu friend. Do not patronize my faith okay.
Sorry terribly sorry. Look if you need a ride instant message my cortex by which I mean
call me. Thank you all for coming. I'll see you in hell. Professor Frank's hover car. Go to a
phone booth to use it. Is it good? Damn. Can you hide all the spoilers?
In the game there are no spoilers. What are you talking about?
You better hurry. I heard the parents of the show be building on to grabbing every diaper in town.
I will get the diapers but there's no way I could fit them in my car.
Maybe Mr. Homer will have a large gas guzzling American vehicle that I could use.
Oh that's right. I need 500 coins. Shit. Find them. This is just between me and you.
I need a lot. Oh okay. This way. Some coins. I need to go explore.
Looking for some kind of... close enough. Yes I am. Am I...
Am I enjoying the game? Uh yeah. I think so. I mean no. Am I in... I am not.
He's not. Why? Because I went...
Something along those lines. And I said he's throwing rocks at me.
That's what I think that's what I remember saying. Oh that was pretty badass.
I need you. Come here. Did I go far enough? Can I even jump on this?
It'd be just great if the camera could turn. I guess I can't go on that.
Did I not get that coin? All right there's probably a box up here. Or a bee? Any bees?
I don't see a bee and I don't... oh there we go. And there's a box up here.
500 right? And there's another bee. Good. Uh come here. I don't want you to spill coins.
All of them. I'm not gonna be able to get them. You're shooting at me. Okay. I shouldn't have
bought all those dumb clothes. I'd have way more money. I'm not even close. Actually I can go
from here to there. Ah interesting. Can I get up there still? Windowsill? No. Well I need to get
back on that roof. What else can I do? Something on the other side? No. Nice jump. I couldn't
have made it. I could not have made it. I see you with a rock in your hand. Put it down.
There's no reason for that. Can I get up here? Let me see. Can I make it? I guess I can
make it from here to there. Can I? There's that little ledge right here but can I just make that?
Am I lined up? It's like the claw machine. Okay. Uh this side is more important.
No! What the fuck? What the fuck? Uh it just pushed me off. I didn't touch anything.
I just kind of fell off. Well let's do it again. I think I can just jump. But I could
probably do it. Okay. Now let's try this again. All right. Good. Good. Good. Kill the bee.
We're almost there to the last mission of the game. Can you see how close we are?
Final mission incoming. There's another platform over here.
No. There's like three more levels. Yeah so we're at the final one. After those two.
From here uh is this the other building? Not the same one. All right. Need more money. Car wash.
Nothing. Wait. Nothing in the car. I already got the car wash money. The next level is bot and then homo.
Bot, bot, homo. Mod. I see coins up there. Is there a way for me to get up there?
Uh what's the blue one right there? Can I interact with this? I don't like it.
Hurry up or my arranged bride will chastise me. What do stairs do? Are there stairs over here?
On one of these box cars? You did this earlier. Yeah I know but I'm one of the
characters. Can't go in. That was an incredible move. There might be another way. I guess I
could go on a car and then anywhere inside that I can go. It makes no sense. No random place I can
go in the corner or something. I don't think so. Well I can probably jump from. I can't jump from
that. Can I jump from this? I'm stuck on that. Uh can I? I don't know. I'm not going to go
from there. Just go up the stairs. I mean talking about all the way back here.
Can I make it from here to there? I'm going to have to run very far away.
I have to go all the way across. Is there anything over there? There's nothing even
over there. What am I getting? I did this earlier. Yeah but I'm talking about over
past that top of that thing over there. No that's what I get.
I'm not talking about getting to where those coins are. I'm talking about the other side.
I'm talking like down there. So do it. 500. Is he on drugs? Uh no. When you hold run in this game
it makes you it forces you to go into a straight line.
So for about a half second when you run you have to go in the direction that you
started the run. You can't turn. So it's like whoop. Sometimes you fall. Sometimes you slip.
Why did I jump down? Because I have 500 coins. I don't want that card.
All right. Buy it. 500. Where is it? I thought I could buy it from the
from here right? Can I buy it from here? You have to buy it from home. I thought you could
buy it from a phone. No. You have to talk to Homer about that.
Were there a bunch of other scenarios where I just get it from home?
He said you can summon it at a phone. That's what I thought. If you own it.
Get out of the way. Excuse me. All right. Springfield Park. Springfield Hospital is
down this way over there. Park. Hello Homer. I'll take your custom car please.
Do you have an oversized vehicle? Whoops. Okay there it is. Car built for Homer. 500 coins.
Must admit the smell of fresh air is much more pleasing than the odor of the hot dog machine.
I hit the van and collected the diapers. In Homer's underwater taxi.
I thought he was going over the thing. Hold on. Itchy nose. Not good. I gotta restart.
All right. Who is in this car? Who the fuck is in this car?
Uh ambulance come please. Use horn. Use horn.
This guy's driving me wrong. This guy's freaking me out. Bad big time.
Okay drive to the hospital. All right talk to Dr. Hibbert. All right final mission incoming.
Shiva H Vishnu. My jubilation knows no bounds. Here we are at the destination.
That was way too fast. Here we are at our final destination. It's just between me and you
random object. I know my face cam is not on. Why? There's no reason. Put down the rocks.
Famous American clown. I wish to ask a favor. Everyone wants to wet their beaks.
Require information about drugs delivering evil cola. How can I get this classified data?
Sorry Apu. I'm a drink squeezy punchy lowlife. You need a professional scumbag.
We're putting them down by throwing them. Follow a cop until you find one.
You'll have better luck if you, you know, look American. Thank you horrible man.
Need a disguise purchase. Who's American clothes? Another 425 coins. Shit.
My giant gut is is slowing me down. Oh Shiva smiles on such behavior. 57 coins.
All right we have to scrounge around now. Fathering eight children has really hurt my
stomach. We gotta find boxes. We gotta find soda machines. There's a box over here.
Do a wager race. To catch my breath. We've seen how much of a disaster those were.
I should sleep more. All right not a bad start. My cardio is shot. Destroy cars.
Another box right here. And a bee. That took a lot longer than it should have.
400 right or was it 425? Nothing, nothing, nothing. My giant gut is is slowing me down.
What about the statues? I need to get in a car. How about one of my cars?
Fathering eight children has really hurt my stamina. Try doing a race with a hover car.
Sure my robo roommate is being a jerk and I need to get out.
So let's try whatever you got here. There's a box behind you.
Hey aren't you the boy who nearly drowned in the nacho cheese? I was in the newspaper.
All right. Do I actually get money for these? I'm gonna hit it.
This is a slippery course. Wait. Did they block off most of these ways to skip through?
Um I think I'm gonna have to restart this.
This is a lost cause right now. Unless I can... I don't think I can do anything. No.
Maybe I could have like spun around. Um is this even this is not even gonna give me money.
If I beat this do I get points? I don't think that's gonna happen. Maybe.
The journey is the reward. No that's true.
Mmm floaty. I'm really floaty. I will tell you. I don't think I'm ever gonna do this.
He's about to beat me isn't he? I wonder why. Maybe it's because you are literally floating.
A little too floaty. It's not even gonna give me money at this point. The fresh air is somewhat
confusing. Hit it. What? I just fell off. I got a feeling I'll get it up here. Maybe.
Possible. Oh god. Almost there. 100 more coins and it's done. Ride the mon- ride on the monorail.
Bites the monorail. Oh what have I got this? This looks...
All right I'll try to get on the monorail. Wow that was close.
Okay well hold on a second here Jeremy. Um this little lip right here? Okay. Oh why am
I sliding? I just had it. Okay well that's... I couldn't get back up there. Not allowed up
there. You're just very silly. You're a foolish person. Now he's gonna think that's the right
way. No I think that's the wrong way. Hey watch it buster. I think that's the incorrect way.
Or do I? We'll never know. I'm stuck on my car. All right I got uh there is...
Can I get up there? I'm trying to like look up. So I already did this though didn't I? Hold
on. This shit over here. So close. Gag. Any more vending machines back here? When I see a truck
I'm gonna go on top. This looks platformy doesn't it? 95. Oh really where is it? It's not...
Can I not grab it from there? I... oh all right. I thought I could get it by just jumping.
Can I get up there? I think I can. Hold on. I don't think so. Whatever I need like three coins.
Let's just go. There is another vending machine over here I think. What was it? Something up
here. Done. All right let's do the last mission in the game.
Speaking two bodies cannot eye the same seat. Why have I been streaming for seven hours?
Um I don't know. I like streaming. It's fun. I want to beat this game and
I don't know. He only kind of likes streaming. Professor Frank rides again. Crusty. I must
finish quickly or vomit. Uh do I have to buy the costume? Or can I get it from somewhere
besides? I think I have to buy the costume first don't I? Yeah I need the clothes right?
300 horses of convenient power. I need to buy clothes. Can I get some clothes in this
vicinity? Clothes are at Moe's. This is not good for my insurance.
You should not have stepped in front of my car. I wish there was a indicator where a
place like that was. Because I'm not I can't I can't memorize where every storefront is.
Perhaps I should refrain from doing that in the future.
It can't be like a shirt blip or something. Okay I need this. Now we go. Wrong clothes. I
know it's the right clothes. I know it's the right one. You would have heard a very loud
panic if I figured out that I did something wrong. Thank you for not dodging the famous
American clown. I wish to ask a favor. Everyone wants to wet their beaks.
I require information about drugs delivering evil cola. How can I get this classified data?
Sorry Apu. I'm a drink squeezy punchy lowlife. You need a professional scumbag. Follow
a cop until you find one. You'll have better luck if you you know look American. Thank you
horrible man. Look at my new outfit. What? Follow the police to find a criminal.
Follow the trail of donuts.
What is here? It makes no sense. 21 donuts. You're weaving them around don't they?
This crazy driving. What the hell is that guy doing? I smashed my skull.
Got it. Follow Chief Wiggum to find a professional criminal.
He's kind of hard to follow. He's kind of insane. Find the criminal please.
No why would you do that? Why would you just try to kill me?
Found him. This is totally a mugging. Well what good luck a criminal.
Huh? Surely a violent filth bag such as yourself could find out who is driving the
black cola vans. Well I do have a connection at the DMV but it will cost you. You have to
pick up the litter from my community's service. It is a deal. Deal. Now hand over your wallet.
Yes yes whatever. Not fun mission coming up here. Collect all the garbage before time runs out.
Don't miss any pieces of garbage. The smell of fresh air is much more pleasing than the
odor of the hot dog machine. I am a lean mean Vindaloo machine. Follow the garbage truck and
collect the garbage. Armored garbage truck? Garbage truck is what you guys were talking
about before. I shouldn't be getting time docked down for this. Four and give me a five. What
do you say? Give me. Drop it. Collect the remaining garbage. How did I just lose time?
Wait hold on. Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
do I have to go up top? Do I have to get out of the car? No I don't. Watch out.
Oh fuck I do have to get out of the car.
Back to the train. Oh no. Oh I didn't think oh man I thought I had a chance. I thought it
wasn't. Man all this. Oh I hate this. Oh no. What am I doing in this car? Now give me a better
car. I need I need to have like the best possible scenario here. No no no. I need
I had two minutes. I probably yeah but I didn't want to give myself the opportunity to do that.
This just wasn't going to happen. I would have got to the end and it would have been
ten seconds left and I would have lost and I would have been so angry.
I'm just gonna get the sedan. My giant gut is slowing me down. I mean this car is pretty
great actually. I will pay you a million dollars in the next life. What's the difference
between this and the homework car? Where is it? I can't let this mission be physical pain for
me but it could be. The pain has already begun. Put it like right in the fucking side of the building.
I must admit the smell of fresh air is much more pleasing than the odor of the hot dog machine.
You gotta get out on foot. I just got up. I wish I didn't have to do this part.
What are you doing?
All right so he just drove straight into the other one. That wasn't even my fault. I
wasn't even touching him. All right get the last of the garbage. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm
ready to do it. I'm ready to do it. Here we go. We've got um I'm gonna turn. Here's
what I'm gonna do. This way first. Go over the jump. Out of the car.
A ranged bride will chastise me. Okay out. The car's right here.
I think eight children has really hurt my stamina. Just give me a minute.
I gotta be careful. Can I even make this shit? I should sleep more.
All right that's it. Get me back in the car. Oh my god. Punch that guy in the face.
Around this way. In here? Oh Jesus. Why? The like clippy little bullshit.
I'm trying to double jump. Just do it. All right now what? I got this over.
There's so many other ones that I missed already. Give me the car.
This two back there. Wrap around this way. Where are they? Get out of the car.
Out out out out out out out out out out out out out out out out.
Can I walk it? Do I have? Get out of the car! No!
G-Money crickets. The fresh air is somewhat confusing.
My cardio is shocked. Looks like the end of the road for Apu.
Hopefully my store will not be robbed more than four times while I am driving around today.
Oh no. That's not fair. That's not fair. It's not fair.
No! Oh I'm so defeated. I did it too and I- no I had it. I win.
I'm so defeated.
I didn't fight any controllers. No and I like forget everything already.
I just every extra two seconds being in that extra half of a second being in that car.
I could have just used the car for the last part but I didn't know. I didn't I didn't know.
I didn't know. I got it. I'm gonna get it. Oh I've lost it. I've lost it. All my energy is expelled.
Get out of here! Punch that guy in the face! Okay here we go. Just remember.
I have to remember. You must remember. Go around. Jump. Grab. Car on the other side.
Why would you put that last one there? Why did you put the last one in the worst-
No! I haven't lost yet.
I haven't lost. I'm getting stuck in everything. If I don't make this jump
a bite mark is gonna go. Oh my god mommy! He can't sprint faster than this.
Let's go.
Get in!
I got him. What is the blip doing? What's the what was the what's the blip doing?
Why was the minimap freaking out? Out of the fucking way. Get out of my way. Out of my way.
Finish quickly or vomit. My friend has the information. The DMV. Go pick it up pronto.
Thank you. Thank you my violent associate.
Okay I did it. Empty. I am the victim of the canary most vile. That's it Appu.
Make them like it. That was not that bad but it was. If I even took- wait hold on. If I took
even five one or two three extra seconds getting the items I would've lost. Sir this
folder is empty. To rob me is one thing but I never expected you to lie. Dude relax okay.
I've got the info you need. I just need help with a little more. That mission was actually pretty
easy. Don't worry. Oh I'm totally evil. I should know better than to trust that demented
chuckle. But okay. Help Snake with his community service destroy the armored
car and avoid Chief Wiggum. Has this seven hour stream culminated to this point right here?
Don't throw any rocks. Don't throw rocks at me.
We both would have gone. Listen you two. This is not the time for you to do this right now.
Let's lose the tail. That person got fucking destroyed.
Still got a tail on me here?
Destroy the armored car.
Come on into a wall and I'll get it immediately.
This car's gonna explode. I just gotta get him to drive into a wall.
You better not have scratched my car. You just drive this motherfucker straight into a wall.
No timer. That's a good thing. I am a lean mean vindaloo machine. I'm going to mess you up.
That was pretty good but didn't do much damage. Right into the wall. Oh fuck you.
How did you get so good at driving a car? That's the one time I needed to do that
and I didn't do it. I scratched right into the fucking wall. Do it.
That was a lot. Oh he's gonna fuck himself. He's gonna fuck himself over.
Look at me. I'm in trouble too. Uh oh. Can I get out of the car? I'm not touching him
until I find a wrench. I saw one earlier. Wrench wrench wrench. Maybe he'll just blow
up into a wall. There's a wrench right there. How do I get that? I have to go over like that
jump. I gotta go over the jump that's over there but I'll lose him won't I? And then the mission
will be over. Don't touch him. He'll do it himself. Good? Good? Got it.
Oh that's wayyyy. He's so close. Get it.
I'm well aware that I just did a full-on pall bearer. I just screamed for Kane.
Kane! We undertake! All right so did I win? Did I beat the game?
What in the hell were you thinking? Pan pan pan pan pan pan pan pan pan pan pan.
What? What do you mean? What are you talking about? Oh my fucking god.
I am a lean mean Vindaloo machine.
Lose the fucking tail. It's at zero. It's at zero. It's at zero. What just happened?
No way. I gotta slow down man. I'm gonna fucking pass out. This has been like a cartoon
character scream. If you do not tell me who owns the cola trucks then I will be forced to use
vanity. Okay okay. Calm down dude. No I'm just kidding. The cola trucks are registered to the
museum. The museum? What? Each level of this adventure is more exciting than the last.
I feel like a Brahmin. I mean yeah this is a cartoon you're right.
Dr. Bart. What the hell are you doing here? Well Mr. Bart I have discovered that the evil cola
is being made in the Springfield museum. But that closes in five minutes. And my car is out of gas.
Just fill it up at the quickie mart. At those prices? No way. Fine we'll take my car.
Drive to the museum before the curator leaves. Bart Simpson at your service.
Must admit the smell of fresh air is much more pleasing than the
odor of the hot dog machine. G-Money crickets.
How far from here to go? Ten seconds. Oh it's right there.
Oh we're good. Destroy another destroy the car mini game. Just whipped a fucking brawl
bar at us. This one is timed. You're gonna turn! Oh you just got absolutely absolutely ruined.
You come back! I don't know why I'm doing it like this.
You blew it. You just keep at the last second getting the fuck away from me.
How are you still living after that? You just crashed. You just crashed. You just. Get him!
Oh I gotta go to the museum. This is not good for my insurance.
You idiot! I don't care! Give me a ticket! Write it up! I don't need it!
No and I'm talking about what do I need the money for? In the Simpsons video game.
What the hell was going on?
Spoiler.
and their behavior our show is down in all key demos but our show concept was so perfect
we filmed these idiotic bipeds with hidden cameras and beam it into every television in
the galaxy these aliens have been secretly filming an intergalactic reality show in
springfield i knew there was a simple explanation i'm going to introduce the evil cola into the
water supply people will go mad i like it then we distribute laser guns at the squid port tourist
area i like it the cola maddened humans will go berserk can you do rinse destroying themselves
and their town delivering big big space ratings for foolish earthlings good to prevent the
aliens from putting laser guns in the hands of cola drunk townspeople why that sounds
hilarious i watch that show tell you what you're a bad little boy fail fish
we're in all the land get it 50 streamer that's fine okay so
i believe we've made it to the uh to the end part end of the game right oops
you've got to help me warn crusty about this two more missions save the good people of
i'm sorry sir but i cannot speak english i only speak hindi but you're speaking english now
yes i learned these words phonetically well you're just scared of being vaporized by the
space monsters up down up down go hot dog buttoned shirt blah blah blah i need a ride
no can do little dude i gotta round up these other little dudes and get them to the studio
okay
you should be a little lower collect all the kids and get to crusty lou studios before crusty
leaves one two three go it's time for some road rage do i have to stop or just run over
okay
self-explanatory just get them in the car
i didn't i was assuming we were gonna be going the other way oh this is too cool for school
i wouldn't want to be that guy i didn't do it
do the old driver's license somebody have to go through the fire
did i get
we didn't make it we didn't make it and that didn't pick him up hey no fair dude
apparently just leave the driver to me dude
here come the cops
just remaining five there's only four more get plenty of time
13 14 15
oh my god well i ain't gonna get there in 15 seconds
yeah that was awesome no problemo eat my dust dust eaters
transmission
hey no fair dude
just leave the driving to me dude i just know i'm gonna be blamed for this
oh this car can take it oh man this sucks i can still get it just don't drive into the studio
symbol this is not about speed it's just about getting there in the time you don't have to go
fast you just have to get the kids just pick up those kids whoa get them in the school bus
i have plenty more time
i have this straight shot here's the studio right up here
don't worry about the time it's just there to make you panic
i'm fine i made it there we go straight ahead forget about the time i have
get out of my fucking way i win any uh money i don't see any money barney where's crusty i have
to warn him crusty's not here little homer he's down at the squid there's that kid again
a promo for this new bus the weird kid that just the aliens are standing right there
what's it why don't get it human behavior no beverage could do that oh no i haven't
had enough in two hours my life is over i have to get to crusty before the limo does
and i have to stay here and go through the dts sounds like a plan find crusty's limo to
find crusty talk to crusty before his limo picks him up you got it uh well it just blew by okay
where did that's not a shortcut i thought it was get in bart hurry
don't even worry about it everything's fine let's roll hey thanks for the boost motherfucker
you made this much easier on me and i thank you for that
changing lanes twice in a row change lanes change lanes change lanes talk to the limo driver
hey slower traffic to the right please no problemo what are you doing what what just happened he
just peeled out um i see he's in my sights hold on out of the way out of the way
oops i'm just glad i'm not no problemo oh my fucking god what happened when i went to go
talk to the limo driver it was like time to race and that sucks and blows just park your car i'm
gonna park my car in front of his yeah why the hell was that okay don't do that shit again
yeah what do you know good luck you fucking asshole safe and sound yeah i totally rule
it's not even possible i did i did the shortcut and it just got stuck in a fucking spokes of the
wheel i what why is that thing here what is the point of that thing i can't believe i have to
do this again all right i'm gonna park a different car in front of him no you know what fuck you
game i'm gonna park like five cars in that road yeah i'm gonna fill up the whole road with cars
i'm gonna put a truck there i'm gonna put yeah make sure i got my car up here yeah okay
hey have fun good luck getting around this it's gonna take a goddamn christmas miracle
for you to get out of here i'm going there we go okay nice driving man i'm too raw
oh this is too cool for school okay i need any more cars i think that's good
he's gonna back out don't no no no don't you worry about that he ain't backing out
eat my dust dust eaters it's time for some road rage bark simpson style
yeah eat ass good luck you're gonna need it
he got you get out of that so quickly no way there were three cars in front of you
he fucked me up he fucked me up so bad don't get in my way
get this correct do i go over this thing do i go through this thing
talk to crusty crusty how are you finish my game please
got to find evidence who do i know that's smart enough to prove this alien conspiracy
bumblebee man comic book guy disco stew that's it a nerd professor frink
find and follow professor frink bard simpson at your service okay time to lay some rubber
down very people conveniently just drive right by you you are magically not hitting any of
these obstacles in the way when i beat this game i'm gonna reward myself with a triple
cheeseburger i'm getting a triple cheeseburger and jack gets to pick from where go to the
crusty burger so cool from a garbage can uh i'm not gonna do that and we're gonna get
that cut scene where he stops and this sucks order you can't you can't order a burger
from amazon can you uh am scoots ten community subs thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you tons of community subs tonight guys you guys rock i almost didn't make
that jump the crowd goes wild amazon restaurants is a thing it's interesting
that's a freak you've got to help me no one believes my story it's just like the boy who
cried wolf except instead of a wolf it's an alien conspiracy aliens well that would explain
these strange transmissions from dollar tree burger i must have intercepted an alien
it says they're hiding the lasers in the duct trucks the plot is convoluted now relax
nerdlinger i'll knock the lasers out of the truck so i can show them to crusty
drive to the brewery and stop the aliens plan to hit the truck and collect the laser guns
fine by me all right i think we're about we're about to see the final mission of the game
before homer simpson has like eight more missions guys we'll get these they're right here
how did i get up here oops park there i'm gonna have to redo it i'm gonna have to redo it
it oh my god it happened again i did the thing where the mission ends and it just goes to the
end screen and i pressed up the car's about to explode god damn it i may as well just have a
thing blow up professor no problemo i don't have a car anymore though does this still
think this is my car oh get a new one okay try to get there in one piece part if you could
try that would be wonderful what is the speed run on this game what's like world record three
seconds how does that work is there like a way to clip through the map and cheat or something
by the way where the fuck am i going what is happening
man you got it eat my dust dust eaters do i really not have that much time to get down there
i have to go through some kind of shortcut or something don't i all right well i need to
i was just looking at chat again because i'm asking questions hour and 28 minutes
bart simpson at your service i think i need to take a bath after this
and just lie there with my eyes closed with cucumbers on my eyes is that horseshit man
all right i'm just going through here fuck it why would you tell me we did it what do i do hit hit
the duff truck and destroy the boxes hit the duff truck get the boxes i need six two good rng
there good rng good rng nothing nothing from that either back to duff brewery back to duff
brewery let's go don't drive off the cliff or something no and the police are on the way
find a laser gun to use as proof where do you want what is it what's what's what is it what
chat help me out here what's going on what happened here find a laser gun to use
pick up a laser gun go right through the glass i show this laser gun to crusty you have to
believe me i can't believe i have a working laser gun and i'm using it for good
drive to the taffy shop there you got my attention chat helped i probably i would i
probably would have driven off the cliff speaking of which no don't do that what if it ends in
this year hit apparently doesn't hit you save game thank you so much for that
i don't know i've never mind i was wrong i thought i was going to say something that
made sense but it was not going to make any sense save save save save save i got principal
skinner principal skinner aliens are distributing deadly lasers all over springfield we gotta warn
everybody all we've got to do young man is get that illicit goo gaw out of your dream until
twitch shuts you off at 48 hours policy on lasers uh why would i do that destroy principal
skinner's car and take back the laser gun before time runs out i'm going to block them
and push them into the ocean no problemo i need some speed yeah i'll educate you a new one
odd felt like i did some damage to you but apparently i didn't
apparently i didn't do any damage to you i just hurt myself you just took a huge hit
take that lousy laws of physics use a stronger car it's time for some yeah but i mean
when i string together the mission like this i kind of i guess i could just jump out right
now i can get it i'll educate you a new one he'll run into a wall in his car and explode
here it comes look at how fast he's going he can't control it right into this wall straight
ahead fire in the hole take that no damage on that one bastard almost dead i keep like
peeling him out when i don't mean to do that convenient just go two miles per hour into me
see this is where he could have done it i need to slow down and just get right up him
all right maybe i do need to beg your car just to drive into him because this is not
working just doesn't do enough damage when you hit him i'll educate you a new one i hope
that was expensive figured that would have done a lot of damage but apparently not
i'd have to get like the plow or something okay that's just where the fuck did he my brain
i thought he drove off the cliff and then oh man
and
skinner is dead uh skinner and his mom they were both in the same car so they were together
shebar the car is on fire i'll pick her up at the moment mother
well what do you know you were telling the truth you've taught this old clown a lesson
prepare to be stuck on this level for an hour et cetera et cetera stay in school i just wish
you told me before i let them set up those free laser gun stands oh man i better get some
heavy artillery if i'm gonna take out that much private property kurti should have something
good to complete this mission you'll need the globex super villain car purchase it from
yeah for 600 coins how many coins do i have now i need more coins 200
these expensive somebody just said cheat i can't cheat that i gotta play the way the
game was meant to be played once you cheat you can't go back there's no turning back
after a cheat all right which way do i want to go let's go this way first
um so what was the point of that there's nothing up here oh my holy shit that's a lot of money
wow didn't even need to cheat the code is right in here all right that helps a lot
any more hidden rooms that have money there's a spot to go over here um i guess i could have
jumped over the other side i wonder what's over there let me get over there again
what is it all right cool
i thought this is gonna take a lot longer thankfully there was this shit over here
and i got another thing to platform around on which where will this take me over the
back to the back to where i was hi yeah save again good call you missed a bonfire
oh box over here i'm gonna guess yes there's quite a lot back here it's
gonna be done all right did it 500 coins that i wish from software would make a simpson's souls
look at the amount of characters that are in this universe it'd be great
more like dumb my 985 get it you know that's the first rock i've seen thrown in
at least at least probably an hour or two all right i almost got it so i have to go
buy i guess i can buy it from right there right can i
i need we need a little bit more money i think that there's probably some over here i can get
maybe did i miss anything 559 where's this music coming from here the boat
it's break ship i'm looking around for like a b or a box who well may have found something
come on over here i just saw it that's very dangerous part you shouldn't be doing that
okay b you gonna appear no b no box they should make a simpson's tv show
these are really interesting characters uh is there a box on the boat
kind of up here for no reason aren't i it's very funny i appreciate that thank you
i tried as hard as i could i'll never lose these love handles
okay well i guess there's nothing here to get this much exercise that was a gag well maybe there's a
bug see a box down here but what about over here there's one down here
just give me a sec here is the rest of the money that i'll probably need for the rest of
the game maybe depends on how much longer it is maybe i should stockpile a little bit
just so i can have it so i don't have to take time out
because there's another way to go over there let me just check a look back here
energy depleting need sugar okay out on the lip
the hell are you doing barb
seven twelve i'm thinking top of the lighthouse you know i'm thinking top of the lighthouse let's
do it first let me get these can i play this at times two speed i need this money
i gotta have this money i'm definitely gonna need it so and you're gonna it's gonna happen
at some point really there's nothing up here did i already do something up here
nothing well at least i have enough to keep going so tired so very tired i think i'm just gonna
jump off the edge no i'm up that red arch in the box right here toy boat toy boat toy boat
toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy
boat the wolf is that old what do i need armored truck what else you got
little situation here wrong guy i need to get out of here
okay i don't know why my nose has been bothering me so much it's time for some
road rage my nose into my throat i've just been super dry and shit
it's really annoying all right no house all right crusty studio is
crusty studio is not is it down there where is crusty studio it's like down here to the right
isn't it asphalt asphalt eaters
isn't it where i was before am i out of my fucking mind is it it's past the boat
i'm not i'm not crazy it's probably not good all right i have enough money to buy the thing
from stinky whatever his name is hey kerney i need to do a lot of collateral damage in
the minimum amount of time i've got just the thing i've got a car that was owned by a
super villain he used it to conquer the east coast lobex super villain car okay destroy all
the free laser stands in springfield before time runs out let's see one out of
the placement on that one these are just trying to park with you aren't they
charlie horse charlie horse not too much time do they
it's time to lay some rubber down it's all good you mean there's more i think i didn't break my
memory card all right i didn't do it get out of the what are you doing there what are you
doing there what are you doing there why would you be there he's been here before got lucky
on that one come on crusty the stupid lip the lip just fucked me over so bad i can't even see
the smoke is everywhere there's no way i did this in time i am i need like another 45 seconds
how on earth i need like another 20 seconds to do that holy shit this this is you gotta be
perfect and go full speed oh my god people are giving a ton of money uh fitty just gave
a hundred bucks two fifty dollar donations back to back all right i'm going to do this
right now fitty is for you they say hey germs i meant to get some sleep before the stream
but i accidentally slept for almost 10 hours straight i rushed out to bed to check if you
were still alive and accidentally full-on kicked this bucket of bits with my little toe
my eyes were filling with tears so i almost stumbled into my walk-in oven and locked myself
in these bits almost killed me so please take them i'm really sorry about that thank you again
fitty for your 100 fucking dollars total also in buying these last bits twitch told me there
was an error with the transaction and i should try again that error was apparently a lie and
now i bought them twice don't worry i did have enough money for that might just be a while
before i donate again that's well uh that's a 50 dollar error i will gladly take it thank you
thank you so much fitting uh 10 hours chicken wings no triple cheeseburgers tonight on me
this one's for you fitty you ready watch it go
no do it again i fucked it up i need every second is that supposed to be a penis or
something hold on a second is that a dick is that a dick thing that they're doing a penis
thing they're doing oh no it's a laser right okay dust dust eaters
this one's for you video get this one writer bart simpson at your service
i can make one mistake like that how the fuck are you supposed to get that one you
need to my tail drift into that thing
that thing's tucked so deeply into the whatever i don't get how it's possible to get that i
don't understand yeah it's got to be a perfect drift apparently i don't know
thanks thanks a lot for ruining everything please
no problemo i can't imagine trying to speed run this game and getting to this part
how many thousands of times do you have to do this before you get it perfect
you got it
i'm so focused on getting the one that's in the corner
i of course blow it of course hey thanks a lot thanks a lot cops that should not be in the game
thanks a lot appreciate it
oh my god you have to go on the wrong side of the fucking road to get these it's just how
are you reliably supposed to do that jesus christ you gotta you have to go on the
a 10 year old is supposed to beat this game no problemo no this game this game is designed
for like people i don't even know who it's designed for made for fans of the show
what no way i'm just gonna try to finish it no i'm not you've got it
i'm stuck in a fucking infinite time loop part collecting popcorn machines
fucking pumped into like trying to avoid the people and you bump into a fucking trash can
now i know why you guys want to be playing this game because you were waiting you wanted me to
play this game because you know that this that this shit is going to make me scream this is
why this is the most requested game now i figured it out i get it you wanted to watch
me drive with a minute and 40 seconds to run through the fucking claw machines
these people but they're just all in the way and i have to get the police after me every time
we're doing our goddamn oncoming traffic and i got the yeah open the door please
i'm out of time i got no time for this all the fucking sirens are blowing my brains out here
they're just like i can't even hear myself dream
oh it's right here no come on just a few more no problemo is this shortcut oh oh my god
you mean there's more
no bark we've lived through this life before
oh
jeremy please it's you have it it's right here i didn't even get the wrench
i gotta go for the jump don't i it's gonna explode it's gonna explode
do you you have to take the shortcut on the beach
otherwise it's physically not possible to complete this mission
right well you have to go down on the beach or this this is just it will not ever happen
fucking video games man i swear to god fucking video games
placement of cars
again the same guy same guy just sitting parked on the corner
not even on the road all right on the beach here we go dumbass
oh my fucking god why are these why are the police in in the fucking game why are they
in the game they don't serve a purpose it's just to be annoying
oh if i didn't get crushed by the police officer going 200 miles per hour
did the people that made this fucking level have like a fucking bot completed before they
pushed it through you know what i mean did they just run an algorithm that completed the
level they're like yeah that's good but hey did the bot make it with one second left
yeah that's fine that's good good shit i love god i love this show
some of the time that homer got stuck in the dunk tank
it's all right you get the same amount of time i'm going all right here we go
we missed the fucking wrench i almost blew it there with that stupid
rng of when is the thing gonna close i shouldn't enjoy this so much see i tried oh man i
wanted to go down on the beach but the thing it's just how do you even determine where you're gonna
end up i'll have to go through the boat too don't i i don't even remember i need to like
look at where that shortcut is because it's it's it's you have to be perfect and use
every fucking shortcut to be perfect and use every shortcut where is it well i need to go
look at it because when you're driving a thousand miles per hour and there's shit
happening all around you i can't pay attention to all that stuff at the same time like where
is it i need to go i'm just gonna i need to go look at it because this is this is like
outrageous even if i fail i just want to see where it is
i almost had it that other time too but i didn't get screwed over
don't run people over you know how difficult it is to do that
and collect everything in one minute and 40 seconds that's almost impossible he's being here
before oh my why why why god the three dumb motherfucking sedans why are you
and what and i went over the fuck is that even possible i went over the wrench
i don't i need to go look at this shit i need to go see oh my god this is unbearable
no mission in the whole game is compared to how horrible this is
i don't even care if i lose i'm i need to go look at this where is this shortcut
where is it this way i can't even see
no problemo i just can't even understand how do they expect people to reliably do this
and it only gets worse from here you know i don't give a shit about any of this stuff going on
right now i'm gonna quit the mission and i'm gonna go find this exact route to take to do
the job where is it i need to like where where's that like spot so somebody said the
boat is closed boat is closed so i can't even do it in the so why is everybody screaming at
me to do this if i can't even do it in the first place is that for real it is for real
it's not closed no no no no wait wait wait no i need to see how this connects there's the
jump but where's the direct route from where i come off of not that way so i'm gonna bang
a left once i get to here or is it a left which what it's this little corner what what
direction do i come from spray through here and then you bang a right because this starts down
here around and then once you get to this with uh that dude up here i get it i get it yeah you
put you put these people in the game because of grand theft auto you thought it would be
great i need to i need to get out of the car so i can see i'm gonna look up to the phone that's
where the phone booth is so i gotta take go straight and then bang a right once i get to
this portion here because i'm gonna be coming from this way right so if i'm gonna be coming
from this way then it is just straight through where the ketchup guy is right through the boat
it's a way to go through here too there's a way to go through here so hold on so there's an alley
right here which goes straight and then you bang a left and then a right germa finding the speed
run tactic so i'm trying to find the complete the level the base level all right so that's
where you land this is where you land from the jump forget about the beach so it's just
right there and here and then here all right i got it
land right there all right i got it let's fucking go i have to go back to crusty's lab right
i'm gonna do that i'm gonna smash it right into it test the boat just to make sure oh
that's a good call i didn't go that fast what do you end up after this
you end up right here oh that saves a fucking dickload of time all right crusty fuck you
face me this way how would you die how would you die i'm surprised there's still 3200 people
here watching me bail out a fucking popcorn collection again thanks for sticking around
and dealing with my fucking rage i hope you're having a good time restart i don't need to why
restart no i don't care about this i can do this the part that's the problem is
once you get the 49 seconds 50 seconds this is not a problem at all it's just i need to now do the
uh
you're gonna drive into oncoming traffic i mean this is like stupid dust eaters
i'll be fair though it is oh i just i don't even care about this just get me up to where i was
and i got chunked it's okay okay there we go i'm gonna go through the
uh
it's not what i wanted to have happen right now here we go thank you for ripping out of the way
he knew that was somebody in chat that's this is too cool for school eat my dust dust eaters
i remember these being here before it's time for some road rage part simpson style
i'm not gonna make it it was not it was just so sloppy because it's stupid
stupid claw that comes down and crushes you it didn't even like help oh my god
this somebody just said this might be slower no it can't be
beat shortcut instead let me know let me try this again where i oh you vey
i can imagine being like 13 and in a crime at this game and not understanding what was wrong
with tears streaming down my face because i don't get why i can't win the game mom
hold on wait for the fucking gong to hit wherever the hell that thing is
is
i'm so glad i went over that okay now slow it down no oh my god why in the name of god
do you have to do this to me you have to go straight in it's it's actually hard to do that
it's actually hard to do that that is as wide as this car is that's as wide as the car
oh my fucking god i'm gonna get out there and fucking just crawl
and so i'm turning into ice right now i can just feel my body cooling like the
devil is taking over i can't skip it because i know this sucks but i have to do this
okay this is wide as the car oh satan leave me satan leave me now
i'm never gonna watch the simpsons on netflix ever oh you're never getting a view from me on
netflix oh my god you're in standards right look at this
this is actually going to be just a struggle up for me to fit in there
no problemo beach go on the beach no everyone told me to do this everybody said german you
gotta go through the alley try the alley and then try the boat i know you guys are trying to help
me all right i'm really i appreciate it i do but i'm trying i'm trying i for everyone
we're first we're gonna try the beach now we try the boat i do appreciate it i really i do
thank you but uh satan leave me be gone satan ignore the alley but my puny six-year-old brain
that's the only thing i know what to do now i don't know how to do anything else right now
it's just to just go to that alleyway and go through that's the only thing my brain can do
okay hold on i'm gonna get it now i'm gonna get it now i'll get it now right now
just gotta hit every single tree on the way over there here we go
relax no cops i'll get it i promise or i'm gonna do 500 push-ups
i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it
come on just a few more seconds
oh you've had it don't i that doesn't count because the 500 push-ups only if i fuck up
that didn't count that doesn't count as a fuck up for me that counts as a fuck up from the
video game dropping the school paper cutter on me that didn't count as a fuck up either
he's not fucked up yet
skip one skip one of the popcorns what do you mean skip a popcorn is it more than 25
beach all right i'm gonna go beach this time i'm gonna go to the beach but i don't know where
it ends up i'm gonna play calm you understand i'm calm i just gotta get up there i got plenty
of time i'm gonna fucking start i'm gonna start slamming things no stay calm i'm not even gonna
get him so cool stay calm
you mean there's more jump the light
the name
it's always right there i can get it
why is this game so hard why is this game like this is this one of those secret hard games
tell me the truth this is one of those secret hard games right where the game is holy shit
it's secret hard game right it is please please tell me this game was made for children
stop that enough of that how am i doing that how's the car doing this i got i need a fresh start
here skip number 22 skip 22 thank you for the help skip 22 i remember these being here
before i'll try out i'm gonna skip 22
it's the one that comes after 21
who did that who said that
18 19 20 21 but 22 is right here 22 is easy to get it's not gonna none of because because
look when i activate the next part when i get the 25th one it just goes to 50 seconds
because i don't think it matters when you pick see watch ready 50 right so it's not like
it matters when i pick them up or am i not getting this somehow this is the one
this is the one
why didn't i just do this in the first place
why didn't i know that show girl last night was a guy hindsight's always 20 20
that was for you fady 45 minutes ago for the record 20 skipping 22 what would it do
let's roll there's more to this game what the fuck do you want me to do now
i was paying attention save save save yeah yeah yep yep yeah yeah i got it i got it i got it
save for the love of god okay why is there a problem here you get 22 last on the way
back we're setting the timer oh you're all mine is it in the studio
maybe okay eat my dust six iq boomer doesn't believe this chat no that's not what i'm saying
i didn't know that if look i don't know the super cheat exploit way to do it that's an
exploit i read on the wikipedia page for simpsons hit and run that the developers were really
upset that people were doing the collect 22 last because it fucked with their only bots can complete
this algorithm so i mean i'm sorry but that's what i read no i was i was thinking about it
no not at this stage i got one more mission okay hold on a minute like three hours ago
somebody said i had two more missions there's been probably 14 missions two more levels two
more chapters hold on i only have 21 dollars dad the aliens have taken over the duff brewery and
they're using it to store laser guns life ever had to do so much explaining what this is duff's
worst disgrace than stuff ice it's time to use my secret weapon remember when i told you
i sold my old car so you could race the aliens oh amazing oh thank you i appreciate that damn
automatic transmission this car sucks bullshit it does this car this car is bullshit this car
sucks is what i'm trying to say
why does it put me in front of this lip why would you do this to me i just know i'm gonna
be blamed for this nothing last thing goes up on two wheels so easily and that guy's blocking the
secret he's doing that you see what i'm talking about i had a choice don't forget to ride
homer shut the fuck up homer shut up stop it i'm stop it over
oh he's breaking no he's not he's fine he's doing just fine
it's not the line that gets me it's the
he just said learn to drive dumbass i ain't ever watching your show
i heard it's a classic american piece of television no i ain't watching it
oh it was like that when i got here great now i'm losing
why did i do the same thing you just did
we're doing the same things why didn't i just pass you
he crashes into that thing every time i just need to go around it but it's hard to go
around it because the beach is not desirable ground
somebody somebody go the other way at the start and i listen to him
i got break he braked at the worst possible time
what's up with that he'll fuck it up don't worry he always does
i'm going on the edge i'm going over no i'm not no i'm not just go around him
he crashes every time went around and this is where i win he used a cheat code
unbelievable i fucking can't believe it he just he his character just as now look at how much
faster his car is right now he just goes 5 000 miles per hour in five seconds and i lose again
so look at how much faster the car is he just go he from crashing into the wall he goes 80
see he's always faster than me so he always causes a fucking bunch of shit in front of me
this is an unfair race it's not even a race it's hey i'm just gonna go in front of you
and crash into everything and then you're gonna have to deal with the outcome i'm ahead of him
yes he's not even don't do it go down to the beach down to the beach he's there's no way he's
catching up he's fucked up bad just compose yourself i win i did it
oh yeah where's the finish line okay i told you to do that five minutes ago well i wasn't looking
this game sucks
that's just somebody wrote uh i oh this is fucking hilarious what a stream man i went from like
fun to to joking to anger till now i'm this i'm fucking this is hilarious to me
it's not done this is dlc there's a halloween dlc i don't have to do this
hey thank i beat the game there's the fucking halloween skeleton dlc
you can tell you're mad because you haven't done any of the extra stuff
like you were doing in the beginning
no not anymore i love something we go through stages
you're gonna give me a time limit to go talk to flanders we can't do that this is dlc
what the hell is going on flander give me your first aid kit well i was hoping to save it for
rotter and totter to you know bandage their brain eater boo-boos look just rub a Bible on
him will that work to fend off zombies who am i doctor science
okay okay here's the first aid kit
what's with the camera i need something to board up the window i'm just threw up
oh my god what's the busy even i have to
why do you torment me so let's do this thing talk to this whole thing is timed but it's not
but it is but it isn't but where's my car flanders get
i need something to board up the windows i know i'm gonna get my car out oh my just give me the
car just give me a car because well you have to have the time limit here before i even have a
car well i have so many locked cars where's that cool one can you come and get me i'll
pay you in back roads okay things are kind of slow here on the playground anyway
okay from around here are you eat my dust dust eaters can i make it from i don't think i can
make it from here i've never even seen inside of here before this is the first time i've seen
inside the cemetery i don't know what it looked like in here how am i supposed to know
what it looked like in there piece of cake is the car at least there it is oh my god
talk to flan but i need the car take that out of control flanders give me a flanders
zoom my camera to make me throw up something to board up the window i know board i don't
okay i know that i know what the inside of the cemetery looks like no
oh my goodness so glad to be of service
hi mo
i need your chainsaw to chop up attacking zombies but then how will i defend myself
it's 12 how long have i been playing the game for go to save people who what
yeah i guess so i think i made my point well
better grade my hair before the zombies get here
huh my life stinks who is the rate who's the rate was great was a raid
2200 fucking people just came in the short bus holy shit
it was nova oh what's up dude thanks for the free uh i a lot of people are probably
gonna leave immediately because i've been swearing i've been saying bad fucking words
like why would that matter i'm playing simpsons hit and run i'm having a tough time okay let's
just do i have to do the whole thing again welcome everyone no for real thanks for the
raid i have to do the whole thing again no why having a hard time playing a children's game
it's not a chill we've come to the conclusion this is not a children's game this is a game
for robots only because they're the only ones that can fucking complete these things
give me the car this cheat codes to drive i can't do that i gotta do it legitimately
here we go landers give me your first aid kit let's go
it's just so many tiny there's so much small i can't you words are not coming out right they're
just not that was so lucky i can't words go to the secret entrance
here we go all right done aim the car the correct way i'm gonna go back this way
here we go i need your chainsaw get it and here we go run 40 seconds get in the car
that took five seconds that was not that was a ton of time i should have went to the cemetery
i should have gone to the cemetery but i didn't know
that's fine i think we're good everything's fine drive to the school playground
i'm driving like this still a time limit but there's not i just gotta relax
mr smithers can you help me out there's some scary weird music is too stressful stuff going on
not now simpson mr burns wants it really is but i have a brunch date you know whatever just give
me the mission help smithers find the items for mr burns before the time runs up let's do this
dang find the socks first let me walk around while my son's right
you got it you got your t-pose after 10 hours of streams
here you go mr smithers oh thank god his socks have been pooling around his
i can stop this is his favorite brand allen quarter mains keep him up
what next just why can i not just get them all why do i have to do this again
it's crushing time why you little dinghy goes up bouncy bouncy all right get it again do it
again like a candy wrapper in the camera why are you over here like this what the
what and then how do you how do you get that one in 10 seconds nope i need a disco nap drive
optional don't do it don't do it man are the new costumes that's interesting dirty homer
evil homer i don't like that noise what is something that people do at the beach
um uh eat let's say eat that was not worth it
just go to the school for crying out loud
hey we're just gonna go to the school because we're going on we're going on 10 hours here
i didn't do it make sure you save it okay you're not from around here are you this is too cool
for school hey so it was the giant flying saucer is probably an indicator of where i need to go
but hold on hey you there smelly sam get homers green car alien craft is using some
sort of tractor beam to suck up trespassers to their doom worst effects ever but that's real
worst effects ever what's with the cool black car my knowledge of sci-fi movies is correct
which it is the black car is an advanced probe for the mothership now if you're through i will
spend my last hours on earth complaining about movies on the internet the gift of life is
wasted on you yes i recommend you obtain a zombie car it will protect you well more money it runs
on human brains it's like drawback i get plenty of those you need the zombie car purchased from
the zombie at the springfield cemetery for 500 coins or call it from a phone booth if you
already have it i don't think i have that money yet but i can go down the slide and
maybe collect some cash something i think something's supposed to scare me right there
there's a spider there well i gotta jump from here 500 i i really okay where do i get some money
human cookbook can't grab the spider or anything all right look at the boxes
don't play hit and run at 3am well i'm pretty fair i'm fairly committed so
i'm gonna get to the end of this tonight this might be like a 12 hour stream
if it takes that long i'm committed we're already here you know i'm sitting right here
because i'm so close i'm currently addicted to the game even though it's infuriating
and i've probably lost two or three hundred hairs just normally because i'm starting to
lose my hair a little bit but i mean it's been about 12 hours so that's how many hairs i lose
in about 10 to 12 hours but the game's really frustrating that too anything else over here
i'm gonna be homer by the end of the stream
big money on the roof of the school well i just get out of the way i want the coin that's in
here on the roof of the school and there looks to be a place to go
whoa can you get up there
there's no ledge i can stay on here it seems like it should be there try one more time
i'm storing like a candy wrapper in an upstrap
that was a little more difficult than it should have been but i made it double jump
yeah i was trying to i was pressing the input there was one little bit what about up here
bug no bug there's one something over this way there are a lot of boxes here very good
yeah i would have just jumped off but i was kind of scared that there was going to be
nothing underneath me beautiful still not quite there now what do these do can i these blow you
three i start with me i knew i knew it was going to happen but i just for some reason
was not expecting it all right a little bit more because i'm drunk i've been i've all i've
had is i've had a coca cola a ginger ale and water there we go three 393 90 i can't read
that number 394 but over here something over there i probably can i change music tracks
this is giving me extra anxiety playing the game all right it's you know what i've been
i've been on the internet for too long that's a gnome that's what i thought that was
i thought that was a gnome or something and somebody modded it in
but online for too long all right this looks like something could be back here
yes 440 so close can't get over there has germa done anything silly in the last 10 minutes guys
i don't think so no i don't i don't believe so well i see a lot of shit over there
what is that thing there's a little go-kart over there that's not gonna knock me into the air
do i have to jump with a car i got it let me get this first this thing's tiny 500 not quite
this thing is cooler than it how do you say the thing i'm trying to say
this thing looks cool but i don't know
oh the vibration tickling my feet all right back to where we were we're gonna go talk to
where was i going before i thought i got gnomed and that's the correct way this way right no
cemetery says it on my right no i didn't spend this shit i i have to go back up that
way don't i have to like jump i jumped this and get all the back where i was
get out of my way jerk ass i remember this wrong way wrong way wrong going the wrong way
wrong way no i'm not it's right here isn't there somebody i can buy it off of here
eat my dust oh right okay no this is just what bark was just call me air homer mistakes were
made he brain is fried i'm all right i'll be good for another five minutes all right cemetery
yes i thought that was a hill all hills are green i didn't do it it's a witch up there
no all yeah all hills are that's what i meant to say i thought i could drive up
the hill is the cemetery i don't even know if i'm close or not back here i'm driving in
circles is it giving my blip i just want the bike blip on the map that's all i need
you passed it again it's the thing next to the fire truck can you please get off of me
my brain might be too fried for this by the fire truck this is the fire trucks right here
one guy was trolling me all right you ready i'm gonna go this way and then i'm taking a left
yes wrong way wait didn't you guys just say left i said what wait hold on
wait what can't you see i'm driving here it is left not the wrong way
why wouldn't they just put an indicator on the map they have it for everything else
all right i'm gonna i'm going left here sure all right what i'm going left here all right
all right i'm going left here driving in like oh man see oh it's by the fire truck
where is the alien car heading no i can't save it at this stage in the game i wish
they would just delete all the cars these people look like witches flying around
people rowing boats on the road missing shortcuts it don't even matter i'm gonna
first try this mission if i first try this mission i'm going in the discord and i'm going
to the voice chat and i want to hit with the screaming no that's way too late for that
shit it's like it's like four in the morning all of the alien car
i'm gonna give you one second to even get your bearings you just it just go we should
start time go now go go go what is this gonna put me thank god
it's crashing time just go why just drive around me
i have to move out of the way he's just gonna drive into me
all right get out of the fucking street just gotta stay with them that's it
those boats just look like i can drive through them i should be able to
to if they're ghost boats why can i just drive through them
i don't understand what was that what happened to the car what did i do
sorry didn't fail
i am evil homer i am evil homer shut up over
i am evil homer i am evil remember when i screamed that i almost built my sunday
the power plant and i'm bored of this level in your face talk to professor
and i know how to use it
look that wasn't part of the deal i'm glad you're here my morbidly obese ally based on
five more i figured out the alien's weakness it's nuclear waste yeah five more well it could
say the life of you and your family and look i've loaded my vehicle with nuclear waste from
the power plant it's going to deliver this toxic here is the alien ship risking myself
and my delicious brain to zombie snacking which if you've never undergone that i can
tell you it stings what a hero and i never knew his name ah it's professor john frank are
you still here all right protect professor frank from the aliens deliver the nuclear waste
to this spaceship let's do this thing so i don't have to protect them i just have to drive
to okay just get to where i need to go this car not this car i saw the thing i looked
you see that guy they got blended in with the ground it's crashing time you see i
i didn't you didn't see that guy people on the road like midnight what are you doing here
i guess you could say the same thing about me you could say the same thing about this stream right
now move it i don't know why i could have just driven past but for some reason i was like
oh go there do that smooth could have gone through there too oh dear i could have done a
lot of things impact learn to drive dumbass i i feel like i've gone in a circle i'm still
going the right way right
what what happened where is it where is it where is it where is it where is it i got it i did it i
did it just i'm not gonna ask any questions i'm just going wrench give me that
i'm not sure where's the indicator pointing
i don't care about this mechanic that was put in in eight minutes
this thing is so hard to drive slippery sloppy thing all right did it good job
drive the school smoke is just causing too many problems i need a wrench
wrench there's a wrench i don't have time for it there's a wrench right there too there's a wrench
right there too
how close am i do it do it where is this thing come on it's right there
i thank god i just have to do this part what the fuck was that
what i don't get it so you have to this thing can explode let's do this thing
so this has to be driven without hitting anything wait wasn't smashing into everything
before i crashed so hard and i say i'm crashing it's not not enough apparently
get out of the way you're in the worst possible spot
where am i gonna put all these professor frank right there's a drive right in front of you
the placement of the other cars is just like look at these three
get out of the freaking god out of the way i'm going the wrong way god
can't see nice alien craft now to just get out of the path of the
put it in the tractor beam okay i did it
jesus
oh i thought i was in the car
laser distributing reality
i'm gonna need some more toxic waste
holy shit i can't kill a bug all right that was fun what's next
germa did i did you find the hot dog i don't think i found a hot dog i hate this game
why tell me your hate tell me your reasons i'll tell you mine
i'm just kidding i need to find some nuclear waste
and fast why don't you ask mr burns his buried is in springfield for years to come
good old mr burns he'll save us this is the worst mission really piece of cake
get into a vehicle it's really really helpful stuff that i'm counting down already and i
haven't even got outside yet can you come and get me i'll pay you it back robs
it's just it's unnecessary stress i can't go pick the kind of car for the mission that i
wanted no no no hurry up walk out and get in the car you have 25 seconds bud can't you see
i'm driving here uh-oh it's that black car again it has the speed of a stuff was
combined with the tenacity of a level stay away from the alien car i had to have lost you by
now now that's driving vengeance will be mine what happened here this is zombies
the zombies chief oh i wanted a peanut that's not a big deal go over just make the whole
thing i almost built my sunday another one am i gonna make it generic villains i don't think so
i'm not sure i'm gonna make this no no way let's see you do better the important thing is i'm not
imagining these guys it's crushing time lousy rotten karmic retribution coming through
reckless driving is my pet peeve uh-oh it's that black car again it has the speed of a stuff was
combined with these witches every car in the road every car in the road they just try they
just try to get in your way should i know how to use it learn to drive dumbass a few more
i'm still not even close take a beating i'm a lean mean i gotta go pee
move it there's no way i'm gonna make it because i don't even have the indicator where the hell i
need to go i just finally got it it's i feel like i'm playing operation with a car
they got a time limit in operation it's like don't touch anything
like look at all these fucking cars just everywhere
i fucking can't anymore man why
why
there were two cars all right listen there were two cars in the right side of the road
you understand i had to how was i gonna what's happening climb the building
a lot of money now what the hell do you have to keep climbing
camera this is probably the worst possible spot it could be in there
fuck don't move instead of just double jumped forward should have just put no i'm not i'm not
gonna talk shit yeah i am please put oh he's gonna do it he's gonna do it he's gonna say it
yeah he is is he i don't know he might think he's gonna say it please put four four out of
ten platforming in a car game oh yeah i didn't mean to say that the camera is i can't see the
shadow all right i'm not i don't give a fuck get me up there
like well uh yeah great can i drive a fucking car now what
trap trap not trap i can't get them this one's safe
safe right here okay number two on left is safe what about number three on
just talk to mr burns i'd love to do that okay these two are safe
jesus okay oh my god oh that don't get the top right three this is safe this is safe this is
safe he has to be safe spudkins is it you merryweather come to haunt me again i killed you once
i mr burns it's me oh miss simpson so you were not the ghost of my former partner
well that was well look i need to get some barrels of radioactive waste to save springfield
from the aliens i agree get it illegal aliens are a nuisance not leaf blower aliens tentacle
aliens next game here's the map to where i buried nuclear waste barrels all over springfield
we're almost 10 hours into this game next let's let's move on now i got two missions left
collect and deliver the nuclear waste the spaceship don't let time run out
now get into your vehicle but these are all still activated aren't they still active
actually better that way i should have just done in the first place where's my car
move it this is the worst possible vehicle to do this as you see why i could just no i need
another car i need to get my car it blew up this thing sucks such ass i'm sorry lady good luck
can you come and get me i'll pay you in back rubs okay nice car let's do this thing
finally i got a car out there just fall through fall through
the time stops that's what a speed runner does the time doesn't keep taking
big bear why did we say big bear driving off without the juice okay sit up
i'm gonna get i'll be right i'm gonna get a drink i'll be right back
you
where are we restart yeah piece of cake
hey i'm drinking alcohol you guys made me crash my game to prove it to you like six hours ago
i love to stick i'm gonna try one of these tech just back out it's crashing time
let's roll the vibrations tickling my feet here we go jerk ass okay so far so good
you and the worst possible place you could be go in the i didn't go in the fucking science fair
what is that place a cemetery
come on come on come on come on i wonder if i could just go right right there and maybe
150 i could go right there too but i can't it just pops up on me too fast
i'm imagining this guy eat my stuff what are you doing what's happening right now
imagine me getting busted with a total switcheroo just go what will you do if i don't
flip you the bird okay don't get freaky i can't even get a hamburger anymore it's so late right now
my god i can't believe it i was gonna get a triple cheeseburger i'm gonna have to eat like
camels out of the can cold yeah i'm gonna have to get some camels or some tuna i'm gonna have
to eat just cold wet tuna that's what i'm eating tonight this town is going to pay for
totally awesome oh no watch it there's somebody on the car
oh like no still on my tail really how are you still on my tail so get rid of this guy
get away from me how hard is it to lose an alien
oh come on he's spawned that guy's spawned
i got there i'm good
where is it why is the timer what did you just see the timer what's going on get in the car
wait i have to do that again no i don't do i
oh the vibration tickling my feet i thought that i had i go from that point you don't go
from that point but that went from that point last time take that springfield remember you
guys remember right hey that's totally the car exploded the car exploded the first time too
you should be in cannonball run like out of my way walking dude
hey welcome to the new show you people driving into you you shouldn't be there in the news
get over there grab it and then i have to go all the way back but then if i it explodes
then i do the whole thing again like i started not i don't get a checkpoint halfway through
i i have to do the whole thing over again
let me see all right in and out reverse reverse i've really got to learn to enjoy my parole
he's getting stringy he's getting really stringy then i missed the
shortcut don't miss another shortcut and you're fine it should be a felony
no like this don't miss this shortcut it's right here for you not supposed to happen this
town is going to pay for this the important thing is i'm not imagining these guys i'm
going to mess you up and god damn miracle that this thing hasn't
this town is going to pay for this sweet acceleration what i'm a lean mean speed thingy
um i have so do i have to i have to go all the way back that's what's happening so what
this is just essentially why don't i just reset because it's doing the same thing again
oh no why did like did they just like give the fuck up when they made the end of this
game supposed to happen are you telling me that this is the third time drive the juice from
really this is the climax of your whole entire game and it's dried back and forth from the
goddamn power plant they had a dinosaur four and a half hours ago
tell me now i need to know somebody tell me is the final mission of the game drive back and
forth a bucket of sludge to the school tell me
okay wonderful fantastic i got two shortcuts eat deer eat deer mistakes were made
i don't what deer are you talking about no where did this go please just i still have it
everybody's in my way forever permanently i'm almost there
i didn't do it just going too fast i have road rage and i know how to use it
like kind of close my way walking dude there's no red light here you're in a cartoon land
there are no red lights why don't you stop in the middle of the road the goddamn
simpsons there are no lights yeah i have to do this again for another mission
they just copy and paste of the final three missions in the game
you know i would be really upset about this but it's a fucking simpsons game
i'm i'm shocked this game even functions that's totally not supposed to happen
i blame society like there's a convention in town i'm not gonna make it i'm gonna fail and
end up right in front of it aren't i you're almost done i know i have to see this through
where are they what what are you why are you facing the car this way sir
why did i face this way why when i go to the other end what one side road hog dude nothing
lasts forever like no here's this dumbass again another variable that like out of my way
greg down the hall in fucking modeling decided to put in take that springfield i'm going to
mess you up driving why are you blaming greg he was the anchor that held this project together
there's a convention in town one side road hog dude i love what somebody just wrote jeremy
this joke has run its course for it's been 10 hours imagine this is just a big bit i was
doing i'm gonna beat the whole simpsons hit and run on stream that's just like i'm just
fucking around i got you every time i do that i do it every time
like out of my way walking dude we're starting to get to like melt my brain level here
they've just seen the same image on my screen i i haven't even seen more than probably four or
five episodes of the simpsons but i feel like i've watched all of them i know every i know
everything i know every scenario i know every joke i'm certain i do i can tell you them all
i'm gonna have a simpsons dream i'm gonna start making my pancakes in the shape of homer's
ass they're talking like marge
no yeah it was pretty painful now i have to do that again all right last one one more one more
thank you uncle sucker give me a lift i gotta save springfield now you're not gonna sacrifice
me for the greater good are you son we'll see dad we'll see oh it's crushing time
oh i'm going to a better place where is it what's happening where's my indicator
where's my indicator do i not get one
i have to find my own way same place race the alien car i can't i am gonna sneeze but i can't
mute it why do i have to race this car
the game is fucking crashing i'm flying i'm flying no i'm not
i just all tapped it's not gonna move and it'll hopefully come back i just saw i just saw a
thousand times join the discord and i was like fine i'm already frustrated and i've all tapped
and i pressed and now we i don't know when the last time the game was saved
is the last level was the last one but is there like some kind of magic i can do to bring this
back do anybody have any ideas some weird pc fucking magic curse shit to bring this back
cheat okay yeah i'm gonna cheat i'm cheating oh we're cheating absolutely what's the cheat
code to get the uh to the last level thank you uh cas af for the five community subs
you can try looking for a save file uh i appreciate the help this is my own fault though
no don't blame the people in the discord that's my that's my fault for alt tabbing
and forgetting that that happens all right i'm gonna i'm gonna cheat but i don't it doesn't
oh okay i'm just gonna do it quick i'm gonna do it nice and quick look at how softly i'm speaking
now this is like the third time i did this what's wrong with me i had so many opportunities
to not do that at least i heard people screaming in the discord all right here we go i'm gonna
punch in the bank you know what i talked a lot of shit about this game it's this game
from like 2003 so you i can cheat and just get back to where i was that's great this is like
an athlete taking drugs right before the finish line no it's come on hopefully you can see it
though i might have to do it again now you got it but good but good but good 20th century
all right what buttons do i press what's the combo how do i do it simpsons hit and run up
down left right a b a b start what's wrong can i just skip i think i know i can skip
the missions i was gonna do right holy shit this is far away all right so i'm just gonna fail and
skip let's do this thing just look at how long ago this was okay options so he's got options
f1 right up right up options f1 right up right up what was it that's not real
oh okay here we go just i'm gonna fuck up and i'm gonna change here we go lose
you can skip missions but yeah but i have to fail them first what's the fastest way to fail
the mission it's that black car again it has the speed of a sub-force combined with the
tenacity of a low off the car yeah this is gonna take a long there's a cheat to unlock
all the missions it was like that when i got here options f1 f2 f1 f2 up down up down
i have no endurance wow this car sure can take a beating just get out of the car
jesus google it i can't google it i can't don't tell me to opt-tab and google this shit
phone oh i have a telephone okay simpsons i i can't believe i'm doing this
simpsons hit and run pc cheats all right let's see retry mission like sure cheat codes
uh that by the way that i was not getting baited in the chat that person was actually
telling the truth but that doesn't help me that much it's just all characters all vehicles
different camera angles invincibility higher acceleration that's still gonna oh my god
main menu options
i you know the reason why i didn't save is because i think a bunch of i looked over and
people said that i had a corrupted save file and i just didn't save it i was so
pick and choose what to believe all right what am i trying oh man i feel so defeated
i was at the end of the game god damn it i should have just stared at the screen
i mean so i guess i still so let's see here load game scrapbook options bonus game
i'm on pc if you fail a mission five times let you skip but i have to fail
like five missions five times just reset the mission can i i can i just reset the
mission five does that count i guess it does right see what happens if i do that
i need to find some new download a save i'm kind of afraid to do that for one reason
because i feel like it this is like to get the game to even run there's mods and shit to get
the game to work feel like i can fuck up a lot of shit maybe all right here we go
let's see if this counts
it doesn't count
you must fail it not restart it i was right there why did i not save it i don't know why
i'm just my brain is so fried i don't know how to cover up people saying corrupt save don't save
why are you doing why you continuous bro rocks at my house i thought we were over that
uh i i feel so unfulfilled though i'm so unfulfilled
what's the fastest way to lose drive into the ocean
just drive to the just like go to the power plant i guess the start of this mission has
a 20 second time just exit the car in the beginning of the mission
it might be faster to just beat the missions
i was done it was so close oh just wait the 20 seconds
am i i'm not emulating the game this is uh this is the pc version
dude i can't just like fuck it up destroy the car i wonder what the fastest way to do that is
maybe the actual mod that i have can use i can use it maybe
well i love what we're trying to figure out ways to make this go back to normal
just watch the ending on youtube all right hold on here i think i think i got away kill
code might save us here let's see kill code you're gonna save us let's find out the all
mission cheat is in the mod manager oh yes that's how cares it's under it's under unlock all
missions oh would you just love it there it is it's done all missions have been unlocked
let's go bet you were gonna debate me into alt tab and this discord huh
how do i do this so how do i select a mission let's do new game yeah i can still see you
load game which is resume new game plus resume game okay let's go let's go let's go
let's do it i'm ready get that let's go let's do this thing let's do it come on first fucking
try check this out three two one come here again losing homers smash use the cheat code
and people say i'm slow wait a minute that was an insult i don't know why
it was like that when i got here damn it i dropped my kebab please don't tell anybody i did this
get off two wheels oh god it was there i'm not gonna make it and then
a piece of cake i can't go to the barn it's too much it's been 11 hours
i can't focus it's gonna take me like a week to recover from this scream i may have even
shit my pants and i don't even know it's possible i'm trying look at him just ruining
everything look at him fucking ruining everything just flipping cars over good thing you're
stupid
clear it
i'm gonna turn off the voice i don't want to hear talking about his feet i used to
fucking thousand times a fucking thousand times
i don't care about homers feet anymore i'm here i'm here just driving to it
this is the only time that i have to get back no way that's less than a minute
my feet need a wrench right now is there a wrench here is it there's no wrench
i'm so much trouble yeah ghost is going to work at the power plant
brainless ai path no there's no way this ain't happening it's just it got less than
you gotta hit everything perfect even this is a pain in the ass i gotta you gotta beat him
there and then what kind of drugs were these kids taking back here to to beat this what
i don't understand the random ai drivers are infuriating they just sometimes are in the worst
possible spot he just squished me and it saved my life oh my god i'm focused to be able to do
this all the way back it's volcano and then since i'm squinting right now cemetery volcano
i got double dunked out of the fucking way yet please and i'm already smoking
fucking witch the witch i just i gotta go this way oh my god
everybody's a witch now i didn't even say that okay come on how will i imagine the only way
this is possible to beat this on the first or second try ever i mean we're talking
fucking did it we did it together we're in this together alien good i'm glad i'm killing this
witch i hope i broke every bone in that witch's body wow slow down easy unnecessary
it's right next to me we're both gonna do the same thing he's gonna hit me
you can hear him he's right behind me i think he crashed yeah that dude crashed
thank you thank driving to me please does anybody else feel like they're flying through
space right now fucking get out of my way i'm feeling like a time warp okay no witch
if there's a witch i'll puke there's a witch get out of the way you fucking stupid i still
am okay i'm okay no same spot it's possible still no it's not a glimpse of which again
it was the witch's fault again okay so um somebody gave a hundred dollars thank you for the
hundred bucks uh yes is online thank you uh the discord apologized us for their actions we were
just having fun and didn't mean to ruin the stream uh he didn't ruin the stream thank you so
much for a hundred dollars as long as you have it don't matter if you're having fun i'm happy
who cares did the game get louder am i seeing my hearing things did i did the game get louder
i think the game got louder just for a second there they roll yourself off a cliff dickhead
get out of my way see he's easy he's having trouble with the robot people too and the
witches i don't even know he just crashed i think i cleared it the game's getting louder
this is it's just me the music i'm about to go into like another plane
i think i feel like the rapture is happening right now and i'm going up
okay is there a wrench what's this wrench is there a wrench in here
oh no no reverse in that's a great idea fuck oh why did you do that i hit perfect
these fucking idiots on this absurd nearly impossible part of the game you have to have
these guys like all over the fucking road do i want anything from mcdonald's yeah two big
backs two big backs two large fries and a large shake and i want it i want it i want it now
i don't know where i'm driving um please and thank you thank you it's not the
route it's not the shortcuts it's the random dickheads that just drive around and make it
impossible but one guy in the boat that just gets in the way because you have a minute to
drive across the game and this guy just rows out in front of you in the middle of the
fucking lake unmute the voices for the finale all right maybe as the fish out there you kill
the same guy every time you have no remorse for that do you feel nothing with that
look sorry it's fishing with my friend i eat shit i don't know what just happened my car
but it's just like fucking goes i'll get it there's a really big shortcut i'm missing
is there the grave guard is the one i keep jumping into the fucking wall
i'm doing i'm going too fast turn on the face game i don't have any clothes on
so i got to stop reading god i'm going the wrong way again
something happened yeah all right let's try it again
all right somebody had a great idea punch it it's throwing me off it threw me off
this is the jim carrey movie where he deletes his memory of shit eternal sunshine don't want
to remember my girlfriend whatever fucking name the thing is i wonder if they exist for
you know i can't go to bed i have to beat this i can't i'll you think i'll ever live that
down i'm not going to be the guy that almost beat simpson's hit and run on screen i'm not
going to be the guy that got to the end of simpson's hit and run on screen i want to be
the guy that beats simpson's hit and run on screen is this the last vision this is it this
is all that matters is this i have an idea call me crazy on this one go ahead i got a great idea
trust me too many distractions too many loud sounds too many fucking screaming
here we go second alien car oh second alien second alien car i didn't why is there another
second alien how is he in front of me what a weird stream this has become
i'll try it again this he just exploded i need that wrench so bad i don't care
the wrench is over here that's worth it
oh my god no no no no don't do this to me i was i was i went i got in i got in the beam
and then i got arrested in i got arrested inside the beam and it put me out i didn't really know
where i was and then i one of the time i figured it out grandpa i don't know what to say about
that one i can't believe it it was there it was over i got impressed in the beam it's not i need
to have no sounds though no sounds really does help if you did it once you can do it again
that's true and i can do it even cleaner this time i'm on life support right now i think
this is the first time i've ever had a stream longer than 11 hours it has to be simpson's
fucking hit and run i'm gonna get a tattoo of this game up my ass on my ass
ah hey how's the boat how's the boat where's the skipper i'm still gonna beat him this is
what it sounds like in here guys this is what my room sounds like it's just quiet since
your car has passed by okay i know that there's two dickheads over there on the left
here we go i did it once before i i what are the cops doing here i didn't what did i do
wrong at the end there there's a wrench right here i'll get it okay everybody relax
i got 30 seconds to get in there and spin around if i oh man all right no cops better good there's
the end of the episode oh i did it i beat it i beat the i beat it i did it yes it's over bye
i win i win the game i'm not alt-tabbing i can't even react to winning stop the graphics
can't hear the cutscene do it again it's all right you can youtube it
he sounds manic i mean i probably am
when we died at least we don't have to sit through the stupid video game credit
hooray well that was a game that was wild simpsons hit and run swirl it
thank you for the 20 community subs 20 from swirl yet next simpsons game no i okay i'm gonna
be honest with you guys i did not think for a second when everyone was like i'll play
simpsons hit and run oh it's funny mark simpson oh and you drive around and you pick up stuff and
i didn't think this was going to be a hard game first impressions um i wouldn't i
i wouldn't wish what i just did on my worst enemy fun game though is it worse or easier
than dark souls i can't make that comparison it's a simpsons racing game it's so easy what
the first six hours the first like five or six hours of this game was fine
and then they just came up with a few missions that were just like hey uh good luck i beat this
one i was eight why am i but 3am yeah i was planning on streaming in like 11 hours or
something what time is it 2 30 3 30 4 30 i don't know if there's gonna be a stream tomorrow
we might have to push tomorrow's stream to uh to monday it is monday today is monday what is
today is it monday i mean tuesday because i'm probably not going to get to bed till about
four or five that means you gotta play today this that this doesn't count guys no no no no
this is not a 16 remember i had to skip i had to time travel because of the alt tab
bullshit see the story missions and the bonus mail all that i did all this already
well there's a lot of people there i did not expect this many people to stay up to this
i know we got raided uh i think a couple times if you still stuck around from those raids
thank you welcome hope you had a good time i know nova came in with a raid so
so all of you that came over from there much love to you thanks for sticking around
and wherever you came from thanks for watching this turned into an eu stream it kind of yes it
did two three four five it's almost six is it almost six a.m it's 5 30 a.m eastern well well
i will see you guys um i'm gonna go over the bits we're still gonna do the bits but i'm gonna
go through them faster and i'm not gonna read every message sorry but it it's very late
but if you're taking off i will see you guys on tuesday and let's go ahead and put the end
screen on so people know it's really old take care guys see you soon i fell asleep while you're
streaming and i'm getting ready for work now yeah i mean seriously how i there are people that
do 10 and 12 hour streams all the time twet 10 plus hour streams man that's tough that is
tough shit man it really is but um more respect and power to him right but that's where i'm gonna
end it see you tuesday for taking off we're gonna go to the bits and we'll do the subs as well
in the form of the credits so i gotta go back uh a while ago glad i stayed up been busy
doing stuff tonight on the computer well thanks for coming up i had a lot of fun
beat a game every stream i don't know if that's gonna happen uh it's time for slime
thanks for the five dollars we hit some roadblocks but in the end we persevered
we tried smackles more thanks for the one dollar thanks for saving the stream with your epic
computer and gamer skills and jex we trust alec thank you for the one dollar alec come on down
to germa's stream where we talk about dr phil and adam sandler while playing simpson's hit
and run today we did do that uh thank you shiggy for the one dollar watching you play this
game brings back so many memories of never playing it and just watching my older brother
play it when i was little it's an old game more than a decade old i mean i i talked a lot of
shit and i complained but remember 95 of the things i say are just horse shit and it's me
opening up my shirt and cartoon bugs bunny steam coming out it wasn't even alive a
decade ago what but thank you too shiggy thank you too demonic cucumber for the one
dollar adding to the point i made earlier about you needing to spend more time to
explore the levels and maps not only are you missing out on really cool secrets and puzzles
but you aren't exploring the maps so you have no idea what shortcuts or routes to take in
missions you need to explore uh i i stopped halfway through there and really wanted to look
around for a little bit i stopped caring well okay the last two chapters i would probably
agree with you that's true because it was getting late and it was getting hard and
frustrating and i really just wanted to do it and try to get it done but thanks for the tips
uh rotten fresh again fifty dollars lightning router fifty dollars huge money thanks both of
you i really appreciate it we stopped and talked about him but again it's a lot of money
uh eu frontio live thanks for the one dollar can you please play big chung i don't want to
say that i don't know what it is chat's gonna love it is it okay what is this big
c-h-u-n thing g you know the joke is this a bad thing to say is it like it is bad
it's bugs bunny the bugs bunny's fat i get it what fat bugs bunny oh well i don't know
what that is uh thank you carlos the clan for the one dollar they just say jupiter thank you
speaking of that i want to make sure i say it again for those of you that were not here
yesterday shirts are actually i can tell you that for real they're coming at some point
before january is over so there'll be a new shirt and i'm gonna bring back the glue man
shirt for uh potentially potentially permanent and i hear a dog barking so that's gonna happen
probably in the next couple weeks i'm gonna say at some point probably within the next
two weeks i'm gonna try but it will be here it will be here thank you alec for the two dollars
what's your opinion on cheddar jack cheese it's well those are uh good cheddar jack
cheez-its are really good they're delicious i like extra toasty cheez-its or the tabasco
cheez-its that'd be great it's my recommendation dark soul thanks for the one dollar hey germa
i'm the one who made the firemane shirt donation last night just wanted to add that
i love you and your streams because of you i found a new appreciation in twitch never liked
twitch or streams in general but watching you and the amazing memes and chat makes me want
to watch you every day keep what you're doing because it makes a small part of my life so much
more enjoyable yeah hell yeah thank you i'm just happy that you guys still think it's
fun to be here sometimes i wonder you know sometimes i think about people still having fun
is this fun people having fun and i want to make sure that's still happening you know
i do think about that all the time so thank you sly pickle thanks for the two bucks hey germa not
trying to get too serious but i came out to my parents today and the stream has been helping
me since then love you man hell yeah much love to you thank you so much for the two
dollars that was sly pickle good luck take care thank you so much we got rye tannic for
a dollar was that a marge simpson impression or a toad from super mario they could that
went in the same all you need to do is just pitch shift toed down by five percent and you got
marge mostly lost thanks for the one dollar uh subtle tease for germa rumble 2019 this was
so long ago but i don't know what you're talking about how ridiculous is that it was
like 11 and a half hours ago or something how long goes up i think i said something maybe
maybe but thank you i don't remember either and you're the one that that's i love that
that's amazing rye tannic thanks for the one dollar foot fungus thanks for the one dollar
check your ass okay seems all right double d thanks for the one dollar we did it guys we
bullied germa into making weird noises again i muted myself which is that's what happened i
just put on the rocks okay you don't even throw rocks at me radio trophic thanks for the five
dollars uh they say never never buy a keyboard off of why is this so small my like eyes can't
even read this largest gnome in the world where's the link for this uh do you really want me to
give you the link of a gnome in the chat do you really want me to do that someone's
gonna not even be paying attention and click that and they're gonna be like what the fuck
oh it's a tiny text meme joke all right well uh all right thank you for the five dollars
appreciate it radio trophic john horns thanks for the three bucks hey germa just graduated
from college just want to say how much you managed to brighten up certain days by putting
me in physical pain from laughing so happy to see you prosper in vegas can't wait to see what
kind of crazy shit you pull next uh hook them horns hook them horns tremor heart thank you
john horse or jordan horns i'm calling john hey john thank you i'm having a blast and i'm trying
to uh trying to get some stuff going you know germa you gotta go through the boat teleporting
me back uh jobo thanks for the 10 bucks i just want to say thanks for giving me the deepest
belly laughs i've ever experienced i gotta thank you for 10 dollars and thank you for
watching my stream it means a lot glad you're enjoying yourself elizabeth thanks for the
one dollar they say uh they say poo poo pee pee thank you uh germa is the best thanks for one
dollar i'm remembering a monologue for the august wilson monologue competition and you are one of
the people that motivated me to do it you also influenced my love for theater believe it or
not speaking of theater are you ever going to rent out a whole theater for a joke
uh yes yes that is something i want to do i have a plan maybe not soon but
this year i had a couple of plans but yeah that would be fun and then fitty gave the hundred
dollars there was like two or three hundred dollars that jumped up bang bang bang with
the course for a couple hours thank you fitty thank you uh f g w g w f for the one dollar two
dollars uh keep your fucking eyes on the road men and then hey germa you're great and super tall
managed to catch every stream so far this week which is rare with my work schedule
but every one of them has been great thanks for being the best thank you appreciate it f g w
g w f die cord thanks for the four dollars oh boy germa stream that i can watch it's not in
the middle of the night it's probably because it was in the morning heading to bed have a
great night thank you die cord frisky mcfrisky thanks for the five dollars eat bits eat bits bit
eats thank you for the five dollars uh f g w g wf came in again with another dollar
it's a youtube link an mrrl it says this reminds me of the fetch mission gold night
all right streets agent 112
show us this is the video here reminds me of the fetch mission 112 streets agent
it's pretty pretty nice it's a speed run the legendary speed run meme uh fitty came in with
another six dollars on top of the hundred i mean i said that i wouldn't donate again but
getting the top donator spot two weeks in a row was too tempting you spoil me you're spoiling me
too much fitty thank you uh z stink loser thanks for the one dollar hot dog fitty for one dollar
hey man we really do live in the future don't we i didn't want to miss a second of the
stream but i also really needed to pee loudly so i just took my phone to the bathroom and
i'm watching it on the toilet this is great hey dragon thorn thanks for the five dollars
no message just cheer 500 thank you no there actually there is more thanks for the 15 total
dollars here dragon thorn uh i fought in the great war settled down with my wife had three kids
and died at the ripe age of 85 since i last checked in on you streaming this game thanks
to the 15 dollars dragon thorn and thanks for the one dollar thank you so much for 15 bucks
for real and the cap david thanks for the one dollar it says eat deer and there's a
the billboard that's had somebody eating deer on it that's what you guys have been saying okay
uh not much more getting close to the end thank you holly or hollyu holly for the 15
dollars sorry about the crash thank god for cheating also will you ever play chrono trigger
you seem to love it so much why not stream it no don't worry about that no it's just
fucking around i'm just messing around don't worry guys uh chrono trigger on stream i don't
think so we've had this conversation about it a couple times it i don't like to stream games
that i've already done multiple times because then it's just kind of me showing you guys
stuff oh hey look i know what this is i remember this part wow this part's cool you're like
that guy at the movie theater that's like hey look at this this is the best part and it's
like all right thanks oh this is my favorite part my favorite weapon in the game okay
shea look at this part okay cool thanks and i you know i'm watching the movie right now
i don't want to be that guy so i don't really typically stream games that i've already played
a lot bloodborne comes to mind i've gone through that game like five times maybe more at this
point chrono trigger but probably not thank you for the 15 dollars thank you cassif
cass af af for the 10 bucks i've got you earlier but you said we're sorry germa
uh discord didn't do anything wrong no it's everything's gonna be fine don't worry
patriot patriot tales thanks for the two dollars and 82 cents glad you got that mission select
code me too that would have been such a somber ending to the night i would have been sad but
we're good x doubt yeah no no no star saber thanks for the one zero zero zero thanks for
the 10 bucks star saber jeremy take my energy pretty low on it right now but thank you for
your energy and thank you the 10 dollars thank you so much star saber loopy lou thanks for
five dollars they just say shamrock bream bin thanks for the five dollars don't give up jeremy
yeah i couldn't end it like that i was struggling i could have just turned the stream
off but no no no no i wouldn't turn it back on i wouldn't go back to simpson's hit and run
i'm gonna go back to simpson's hit and run to suffer through the last two three missions
i had to get it done thank you brevin yeah yes is online 100 dollars this is the discord
apology here thank you don't you don't have to apologize but really appreciate it that's a
huge amount of money i am monk thanks for the two bucks good game well played party 100
thank you nitro lemons thanks to the one dollar you are a legend for beating this game in one
setting probably not probably not but i will definitely say the least i did it you know
but i appreciate the uh very kind words devlon two million thanks to the one dollar germ i'm
really proud of you for beating the last mission it means a lot techno toast thanks
for the two bucks jeremy my boy i'm so proud of you this is crazy this is a crazy hell
game sent by satan himself once you get to the last two to three levels but i'm so glad to see
you survived it it's surreal to watch this on stream because my little 10 year old self lost
her damn mind over this fucking shit back in the day legit i thought it was just because
i was an impatient kid that made it so hard but you've shown me that the game is actually
bullshit welcome to the i beat the simpson's hit and run club fellow gamer i could have
done it a lot of different better ways i know and what initially turned into me being annoyed
turned into trying to figure it out and then i just kind of lost my mind
but yeah that was it was that was quite the journey but thank you techno toast
glad to be part of the club here here almost done sroilet just gave the sroliet
sroliet gave a shit load of those community subs not even 25 minutes ago thank you so much
mantan min thanks for the four dollars and 19 cents it is done thank you mantan
it is done l giant rat thanks in three bucks he beat it on stream grad gradivus thank you
gradivus for the two dollars and 50 cents you deserve this thank you glad a lax and thanks
for two dollars had these saves but you deserve them thank you thank you guys thank you incredibly
kind to you thank you unstoppable thanks for the one dollar when you finish this game you're
gonna turn yellow like a simpson thank you for the one dollar thank you holly holly you again
for the one dollar wow what an epic gamer put that on your resume thank you bop rip for the
one dollar the search for corbin blue for four dollars god gamer thank you the search for
corbin blue tingy thanks for the one dollar i have this self-ongoing joke where anytime you
mention anything about years in the past i say i wasn't even alive then so far i've said that
three times and you've read it all three times i mean it's just an interesting thing to say i
guess i don't know maybe that's odd that i've caught that every time interesting stuff that's
weird thank you tingy for the one dollar choco starfish thanks for the one dollar germa
amazing stream loved it please host liquid wi-fi he's a speed runner who is running this game
right now well when we get done with the credits here definitely go fucking watch that stream see
what a god gamer can do and not a screaming man child like me actual god gamer no i'm kidding
i did all right i did okay i did pretty good i did great i did fantastic could you be
can anybody be better i don't know no but yeah that's that's awesome go go check out liquid
wi-fi when the stream's over go watch or if you don't want to watch this anymore we're almost
done check it out i might actually pop in there too while i eat my hamburger hamburger
saying that weird but thank you thank you the detective for the one dollar hey germa you
just wanted hey germa just wanted to say thank you for the laughs throughout the years
my first video viewers was a live tf2 commentary from seven years ago much love to you thank you
thank you the detective for the one dollar and thanks for being around for seven years
it's a significant portion of somebody's life thank you dragon thorn thanks for five dollars
this is one of those games i'm so embarrassed to have told my friends about the game does
not hold up it's like three levels 300 times if it's hard for the almighty jacks
what of us mortals impossible for us i didn't even realize that was happening until we almost
got to the last two chapters of the game that i was having a great time and it was just like
wait a minute is are we like collecting shit off the back of a car again but then you have
you you have to remember this game is from like 2004 this doesn't come out like a week
ago i know i thought i i i i hate when i get i mean i'm half the time i'm just
fucking around but sometimes i'm just like oh what a stupid game what an idiot who fucking made
this and it's like no i i don't want to be like that i don't want to be that guy but it's an
old game thank you dragon thorn thank you lazy look for the one dollar can you scroll up
to watch youtube videos you skipped like this one uh scroll up maybe um you don't go into
bed like trying to scare me you know you know what i just went through
marge blimpson i just got away from the simpsons and and now we're gonna watch this
thank you kill code for the five dollars and thank you kill code as well for a couple of
things there's a couple of things kill code 345 needs to be thanked for number one helping
uh because really this i was gonna do this tomorrow because i was having trouble with
mods and stuff kill code gave me all the files i needed it was great kill code also helped with
the telling me where i could unlock all the levels in the mod manager so i don't think i
would have ever probably found that it would take me a little bit longer i would have to
search around i would have alt tab crash the game thank you kill code and thanks for five
dollars right now hey germa this is one of your best dreams ever i was glad to be part of
this and was happy to help out get some sleep though germa fired thanks a lot kill code two more
clueless sniper oh wow that's 12 hours of talking that's how it happens to you
clueless sniper thanks for five dollars get yourself some fries to go with that burger
you've earned it jex thanks a lot guys let's get the credits on here thank you for
subbing to this channel all of you uh mom985 says congrats on completing the world record
for longest germa stream all the resubs all the new subs you guys are amazing thanks a lot
so many people support this stream now thank you thank you thank you thank you all i can say is
thanks another special thanks to the the couple of raids that we had i talked about it before
but nova thank you like two or three thousand people came in from nova's stream thanks a lot
man i think there was another one too did i miss uh there was one maybe a little bit later
vinny it was vinny yeah both of you both the communities i know a lot of people have kind
of trickled in over the last six to 12 months from vinesauce and from uh vinny streams and
shit so thanks for sticking around hope you have fun wow you're really gonna end the stream
at only three a.m six i i keep forgetting i'm on pacific how the hell is some of you guys
awake somebody gifted oh god stayed up all night i'll hope it was worth it yeah i'm gonna go eat
probably fall asleep around like four four thirty and uh yeah tomorrow i'm gonna i'm gonna take
tomorrow off we're today today now morning today that's weird to think about so i will
see everybody again on tuesday i think we're gonna slow gears down a little on tuesday
i've had some incredibly intense streams over the last three or four days but the
metal gear rising and then simpsons hit and run i think we're gonna slow it down we're
gonna just chill on tuesday maybe play a little bit more kenshi something just to relax
we'll figure it out do the labo stream no no no no seven you know what if i can get it
700 000 games part two sounds like a really great just just who cares hangout stream right
i don't know if i can get that for tomorrow though yeah that's pretty low key is it
primable if it's primable i'll try to get it here in one day that's another 11 hours at
least i don't think so i think it'll be fine but i had a great time thanks for putting up
with my bullshit halfway through i was i told you i was feeling the grip of satan on me
just about 12 hours here have a great rest of your day rest of your morning hey good morning
see on tuesday around the same time three o'clock pacific time take care everybody and
go watch liquid wi-fi if you want to check out some uh some insane simpsons hit and run
runs take care guys i'll see you soon no the twitch.tv slash liquid wi-fi there it is give it
a click see you later guys