Hey, what's going on everybody? How are you? What's the deal? Cool. Alright, we've covered that.
Let's uh, let's go over what we're doing today. Today we're gonna be doing uh, you know what's
weird? This is the first time I've talked in my clean office. I don't like it. It's echoey.
Usually there's a bunch of trash on the ground. The trash and CD cases and old video game consoles
that took up a majority of the floor and the closet have been sorted. They've been put away.
Now I can hear myself. I don't like this. Show us the clean office. Nah, make it messy again. No,
I have those, I have a bunch of those bass traps in the corners. I've got the foam all over the
place. My whole wall in front of me is all that audio foam over here. Am I right? I got it all
over the place. Don't matter. It's like I, you know, like anybody that streams on Twitch,
they're really looking for the grandma house. You know, when you go into grandmother's house
and there's just stuff everywhere, you know, houses full of things. So the audio quality
is incredible in a fucking old grandma house. You can hear your grandmother on the phone loud
and clear with no echo. It's because she has six bureaus in that room and her carpet is,
it's like two and a half inches thick, long strands. And there's probably six or seven
coats of wallpaper on the wall. I want that house. I need that house. But that house is like,
nobody wants to live there. But anyways, hi, how are you? We're going to finish Dead Rising 2,
off the record. Should be fairly simple. I know how it is with me. We're always very simple.
It's not going to be. Don't worry. I think there's only about three to four hours left of this game.
We'll see. But this will be the final Dead Rising oriented stream for a while. No, ever. No, not
ever. I'm going to play Dead Rising 3 eventually, probably like another month or two. I don't really
want to play that right now because I've played it before and I don't remember it was all right.
It was fun. I guess it wasn't like these though. But this is the last Dead Rising stream
that you're going to get for a while. So let's hop right into it. Those of you that weren't here
before and those of you that have never been here before. Hey, appreciate the follow. I want to look
at this first though. Did I get anything new? I have a shit load of time for 8-2. That's where
we are. Where the hell is this guy even on the cases? He's here. So we've got a huge amount of
time and a day for 8-2, then 8-3, and then the facts, and then overtime. Zombie mutating gas
seems to be coming from the underground. I've got to find the source. But take a look. I've got a
lot. We're not going to let this get to yellow. TK is also infected. That's the only two things
I have right now though. TK needs Zombrex, although I'm not sure he deserves it. When do I need Zombrex?
I'm just gonna go buy one. All right, I'm gonna go buy like two Zombrexes from the store.
I got plenty of good items. You still have 21 Connect games to play. Don't think we forgot.
There's not that many, I can assure you. There's probably seven or eight Connect games.
All right, why is this so loud for me? What's going on here? I have to turn this down.
Why is it so loud for me? Is it loud for you? No, it should be fine, right? Why is it so loud for me?
I don't know. All right, so what's this magazine? I'll write edge weapons. So these last a lot
longer break this fucking box. I've got a good, I don't have to do anything. This is great.
Just go buy Zombrex from the store and end it. Oh shit, I forgot they, I forgot they coughed.
I forgot about the coughing mechanism. Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
He's already angry. No, I'm fine. I just turned it down to like 30%. Did my computer get louder
in two days, three days? What is going on? Did I get a Windows update? Increased your volume
permanently by like 200%. All right, watch out. These, this, every time I come in here,
these fucking idiots stroll up behind me and they cause a huge problem. I'm ready for them
and they're not going to come in this time. He's already mad. No, I'm not mad.
All right, they're not going to come in this time. All right, I'm going to buy Zombrex. I was going
to buy like three of them. How many of these do I need? Look at, I have tons of money. I was
going to buy another one. I have three now. All right, I'm done. Okay, so now I'm going to go to
the maintenance place. Big bits already. That was a pretty good lie. Give me the coin. Got the coin.
So now I've got enough Zom, TK is infected. I have a long time for this. Save TK.
I mean, I'm just going to go do it, right? I should just go do this right now.
I need to do this. Well, I mean, I have the opportunity to, so why not just do it?
Play it on the map. That's why in Grand Theft Auto 4 and 5, even if I played the game for 200 hours,
it doesn't matter. I still need the GPS. Blame technology for that one, guys.
Blame like the invention. I was going to say the inventation. Like it's a different noun when
you're talking about something that was invented versus the invention of satellite tracking and GPS
systems. Inventation. That's like incantation. All right, let's make the defiler. Let's go.
Blame the incantations. It's always their fault. Did you mean innovation? Yes, innovation and
invention combined. Inventation. Just give me a minute. I'll be okay. All right, let's go save TK.
Don't get up from your seats. Everything's going to be fine. Save TK. He's lying down on a bed
somewhere, right? Which bed is he in? The security room? Where even is this dude? Everybody's just
crying. Yeah. You wouldn't be crying right now? Where is he? Downstairs? Which storage room?
I know he's lying down on something. All right, maybe everybody crying is a little odd, right?
Maybe I would assume some people would be crying. But every single person is crying. You're right.
It is a little odd. All right, pick a door. Where is TK? Somebody help me. Upstairs next to the
cafe. Thank you. They're waiting for me to get close. Then they start crying. All right, TK.
Don't make me regret this. This was $150,000.
Now the move right there is to not flinch and to look right in the eyes and say,
is that supposed to hurt? Wait, what? I thought I just hit him with a box
because my head's too big. Just spit on my mask. I'm fine. All right, cool. So thanks, little man.
I was starting to feel real hungry. I knew you'd come through. You're welcome. The only reason I'm
doing this is so you can do the time, scumbag. No easy way out for you. I, whatever. All right,
this is it. The only lead. Let's go. Just one once. Man of my word. All right, let's do the only
lead. Now where is this? This is all the way in Atlantica Casino. Let's do it. Might as well
do some fun stuff. Yeah. Those of you guys that have played this game, is this a scenario where
I'm going to have a funny time or can I just go dick around and level up and go find stuff?
Do I, is this, is this one of those missions that takes 10 straight minutes to do?
You never have time. I know. It's pretty quick. All right. Well, I have a save point right at
that checkpoint. I got a checkpoint here. All right, let's just, let's just look around.
Then something might pop up. You never know. We're going for a coffee creamer.
Look, if this is the final Dead Rising 2 stream, I've, I've got to milk it. That's
someone that's going to run to the finish line. No, I got to milk this. This is the last time you're
going to see this ever. I will never play this game ever again. You are never going to see this
game on stream and video format ever again. So why not? Like check this out. Pretty good swing.
Okay. Okay. Good swing. Pretty good swing. What's this? Jello? Chili.
Uh, if this is one thing I would never eat, it'd be one of those. I'm not going to eat a cup of open
chili, even in a zombie apocalypse. I'd rather eat one of these people. Is that gross? That was a
little too gross, I think. Wasn't it? I'm not sure if it's untrue though. It, I don't think it, it
might not be untrue. True. Sneakers. Stupid. Well, we got you. I need to be in my final outfit though.
I, I really like this. I really like this outfit. I don't think I want to get rid of it.
I feel like this outfit's perfect. No shoes. I can't have no shoes. I already looked it up.
I looked it up. I went to Fextralife slash Dead Rising 2 off the record and I went to all
available shoes. It's not there. Wait, somebody said, wait, we, this is our opportunity. Let's
roll a seven. Three. Ooh, no, almost. This is real, right? There's a six. Give me one. Oh,
that's real. That's actually a real thing. Are you serious? Nice work, person that said that
four days ago. Should I go back to the casino? I got, what do I do? Should I just play casino
games for like four hours? Well, I'm going to be in the casino anyways. Oh, by the way,
if you're wondering what's going to happen either later today or tomorrow,
uh, we're going to be playing Katamari. I don't remember. It's Katamari adjective or Katamari
forever. Katamari. Beautiful Katamari. The one with 360. I don't know. I don't know the names.
It's not like Katamari one. Katamari two. Beautiful Katamari. There it is. All right.
Let me go this way. Queen. Let's replace Queen with Queen. I'm almost level 31.
Let's go upstairs. Forever is PS3. I also have the DLC for it. I heard it's a pretty short game.
So I got DLC. Uh, there's a cap though. No, I can't take this off. One piece pajama.
Oh, it's this thing again. It's this. I've had this on for way too long though. Didn't I?
This is the thing I had on before. Goblin activate. I, you know, fucking let's go.
Let's go. Final Dead Rising 2 stream. Whatever. I'm getting in the car. Let's go. Let's fucking go.
Bro. Bro. I didn't say bro. Why does it want, what is it trying even to do? Um, find the source
to get in the only underground tunnels. I, oh, I can't bring my car. Have I been here? Machete
and machete and drill. Drillachete. Machete and I know I can make this.
Roman machete. But is that even worth taking? I don't think this thing's very good. Is this
thing very good? Flashlight and gems. Yeah, I've made that already. I mean, it is pretty good,
but then I run out of space. Just drink the coffee Kramer. Not like I'm going to need it.
Because I don't want to lose the katana. Katana's really good. How does this not, uh,
calcify, how does this not calcify as a blade weapon? Big bits. Huge. That's enormous bits.
That is the biggest bits like ever. Hold on. That was, how much was that?
12,000 bits from Freddy Dredd. There's not even a message here. It's just 12,000 bits
from Freddy. Freddy, thanks for the more than $100. 120 converted currency dollars.
Okay. There's people here. I didn't know. These guys are blue. Does that mean anything?
Yeah, there's no message. It's just a huge drop of money. Thanks, Freddy.
It's the blue team. I think I got good weapons. I actually, you know, I want to run these guys
over a thing. When's my last safe point? I don't know. I did. I need a safe point right here.
They blew it up. I need a gun. If I'm going to be dealing with guns now,
do the make the wheelchair gun thing. Yeah, I really should do that. I'm just so indecisive.
That's too slow. I think it's coming up here. Hard hat and beer is an estus flask. How am I
supposed to get up there? How am I supposed to reliably kill these guys? I'm going for it.
Stop puffing. All right. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Stop it. I think there's a gun in
here. No, I got a security uniform. Are they going to come in here? Oh, I got to get the big,
big guy is going to come up with this. This is where I get my gun. I'm going to just baseball
swing them in the face. Come on in. I'm just going to spin when he comes in the door,
kill them for me. So I don't have to do this. They'll get it. They'll come in.
Shoot them. Thank you. Thank you. Nice. All right. Now make your way in here. How did that miss?
They just have the door covered. How am I supposed to, are they going to come in?
There's a shotgun. Where's there a shotgun? Oh, that you mean that thing. All right. Okay.
That's what we like to call a double Q. Okay, I gotta go. Salt rifle and I'm going to replace
let's another assault rifle. It's going to be machine gun people. It's not worth it. You know
it. I know it. I'm not going to pretend like it's worth having that. Wait, coffee creamer.
No, it's just coffee. It's not worth taking. Make gun wheelchair. All right. Hold on.
Wheelchair, wheelchair, wheelchair, wheelchair. I'm getting it. I'm getting it. I'm getting it.
Um, oh no. Just, is it just one gun and wheelchair? Hurry, hurry up and do it.
It's not gun and wheelchair. What are you talking about? Wheelchair plus battery plus gun.
Wait, it needs to be electric. This is a double combination. Oh fuck it is. Are you serious?
Let me see. Holy shit. Okay. Can I get in it?
All right. Why doesn't professor X just have this on his wheelchair?
Wouldn't this help a little? Like there's no reason to not have that attached, right? What's
the downside of having this as professor X? They're behind. How am I supposed to get behind
this sandbag? This is the stupidest thing. It's not even hitting them. Yeah, it was pretty cool.
All right. I don't want to waste it. I would like it if it went faster.
200% screen shake. Yeah, it actually kind of sucked. I'm going to wrap around this way.
Okay. That's a rocket launcher potential, but I can't get out.
It's not even good. What am I supposed to do? Give me the other one. All right. That wheelchair
thing is not very good. Find the source of the gas? Found it. It has infinite ammo.
So just hold, but the screen shake is a downside. This is a wheelchair gone. I sort of blend in.
I'm just the cartoon caricature version that you get at the theme park of the zombies.
The only thing that's missing is I need to be on a small bicycle,
riding a surfboard, or holding a huge lollipop. I'm pretty sure all those things are in this game
too. So that works. Not like this. Why? Why do emotes? Emotes have just taken over our thoughts.
Seriously, when I think of something that's unnerving or kind of scary, I just see that
Pepe face, the monk ass that I just see it. I just, Oh, fuck. I don't even make that face.
I just think about somebody in chat writing that face. I didn't save the game. Like anytime I'm
in a scary scenario, if it's terrifying, I'm just like, Oh, somebody in chat just wrote monk ass.
Like I'm not scared. I'm just, somebody else is scared for me. All right. I gotta be careful.
Should I not have shot those? Is it, was that a bad idea? Did I, am I causing a problem?
Uh-oh. Wait, hard hat and beer, right? I'll take it for later. But first I need,
Oh, am I going to get over there? Onion rings quick. Done right there. Nice. Pick it up.
Pick it up. Move. My, where's the gun? Put down the fucking keyboard. Put down the keyboard.
All right. You know, some games have like, Oh, if I pick this up, just automatically trash it.
Can I add keyboards to that list? Can I just auto just trash keyboards? I probably needed that.
Boxes. Let me just, what? This is like a laser blast frequency gun. I'll change that up for a
keyboard. What does this do? Another blast frequency gun. Which one's better? It's a lot
of food here. The hard hat. I need to, should I WWF somebody? Okay. Gun. Uh, eat this. Just eat
something. I want full health. How many, what do I have for healing? Uh, it's all right. It's not
terrible. Hit somebody with a steel chair. I don't have enough room for it. Hold on. What's over this
way? No, don't want it. Make room. Yeah. Things are going just as predicted. Absorption of the
compound is at 80% of ideal. And maturation rates are 10 times normal. Yes. I changed.
Not supposed to be in here. Oh, it's Dave. It's Dave. I work here. I just thought it'd
be funny to come out on Halloween like this. Wait, kill them? Uh, what is this gun do?
It just makes them grow up. What a way to die. That was not fun.
Desktop. Clean up that desktop. I hate, that's an anxiety desktop.
Move those icons. Put some folders there. You're freaking me out. Taking the coffee. Oh, and by
the way? Well, I don't think this guy makes it Frank. You should have just let me borrow
your phone, boys. Somebody just brews a pot like 12 hours ago and it just sits on the heater.
Of course it sucks. Like I didn't like make that. There's no French press in here, Frank.
All right, here we go. The source of the gas is a paramilitary operation underneath the city.
The others need to hear about this. All right. So what we got? Full heel. I told you.
I'll take a queen. I'll take a full heel. Um, give me the, I'll replace this. What is that? Like a VR
military case defibrillator. Take a computer. Take a computer. Why am I taking a computer?
Take a computer. A puke gun and the computer. All right. I'll try it. I have to carry it though.
No, take it with the amp. Amp. Puke gun and amplifier. Where's there an amp?
The guitar amp. Well, why am I taking this then? He doesn't see it. There's no amp in here. Where
do you see an amp? I gotta go. It's behind you. Stop reading chat. Yeah. Good idea. That's a
fantastic solution. I thought that was an amp right there. Ooh, urgent. Yep. Do I answer? Why
am I not answering? Amp in here. Amp. Oh, is this what you guys want? Super BFG. Blast frequency
gun and amplifier. 15 shots. All right. I'm not going to use it. I'm going to hold onto it.
Guitar and guitar and flashlight. Wait, flashlight and computer. That's just a
that's just a zoomer jack-o-lantern. No. Um, I don't know.
You can't even make a jack-o-lantern. How many times do I have to talk about the
jack-o-lantern portion of that stream? I was covered in slime and had knives in my hands
and the whole ground was covered in slime. That's how you die. That's how you end up in
the hospital. I canned that portion of that stream. Uh-uh. The whole ground was covered
in a substance that if I take a quarter of a step to my right, I go and split backwards
and you want me to hold a knife while I do that. I don't understand. Does he just not know how to
carve a pumpkin? Why won't he hold the knife in his hand that's covered in slime?
Oh, beer. Do I still have the hard hat? No. Sorry, guys. I don't have the hard hat.
This thing's actually pretty good against zombies. You shouldn't have gotten slime.
All right. Whatever you say. Am I carrying a magazine? Yeah, it's for sharp weapons.
15 shots in this thing. Do I even still have it? Yeah. I have to save the fucking game, guys.
All right. Hard hat, which I replace. This thing's pretty much broken. What about the gun? Oh, but I
need it. I need this gun in case. Get rid of the edged weapons. The magazine. The queen. Let me
at least get a use out of this then. The wrench. No, let me get the... I'm gonna use this. I still
have the katana. Yeah, the katana is a good weapon. Sword is broken against the bosses. That's true.
You're wasting time. Fuck. They're right. No, they're right. They're right. No, they're right.
They're right. No, they're right. No, they're right. No, they're right. No, they're right. They're
right. No, no, no, no, they're right. They're right. I just... I'm almost 31. All right. Just
give me a hard hat. I can't get rid of the gun. It's so good at range. It's just... It's so good.
Is there money? Suitcase. Wait, can I... Nothing in these? I guess not. Okay. Wait. Don't I have
keys? Is this the safety deposit box room? What if I have another keys? Any case.
Does money even matter anymore though? Let's be honest. That's $150,000. That's pretty good.
All right. Ooh, you got a gun. Oh, shit. Get away from me. I just... Okay. Good. Salt rifle.
That's what I wanted. That's what I wanted. There's a queen there, but I don't care.
Use the super BFG. Not necessary. All right. Where am I going? Oh, I gotta go back. Like, hurry up.
Through the trail. Try it out. No. There's a safe point right here. I'm not off locked.
I've got time. Look, I got time. 8-2. We're gonna do the middle one. I got time. No, I actually do.
Get away from me. All right. I'll use it once. Oh my god. That's ridiculous.
Okay. All right. I gotta go. All this because I saved it. I should have just ran down the...
Kill me. Just kill me. I'm gonna restart right there. I got, I got, I got screwed over because
I saved the game and I turned around and there's 10 people behind me. There's no reason to take,
like, seven cheese slices of damage. There's no reason to do that. I have, like, full health.
See? Like, why would I do that? I don't even care about the katana. The thing's broken anyway.
Are you seriously gonna interrupt my attack with that, with the sneeze?
Use the BFG. I'm gonna use the BFG for the last helicopter that's in the game.
I'm gonna shoot the helicopter, like, five times and I win. Oh, don't stop the stun. Okay, it's
actually kind of fun. All right. No, I'll take it down to 10. I shouldn't really take that coffee,
but I kind of don't want to stop. There's orange juice right here. Oh, that's nice. Let's move.
I'm almost there. It's a crotch weapon, crotch weapon, crotch weapon, boomerang.
You're really good at throwing the boomerang, friend. Okay, third time's the charm. Third
time's the charm. Let's go. Why are you side arming it? You should, uh, BFG. Hehehehe. L-U-L.
Wear the Shaun of the Dead shirt. No, I'm, this, this is not a licensed stream.
This is an unlicensed stream. Okay, save it again. This is the final thing, 8-3, and then we got the
last mission coming up. You're wearing a street fighter mask. Um, when did I ever say the word
street and then fighter next to each other? No, this is big green man face. Where are you
getting that idea from? Okay, I'm, is there alcohol? Get the beer hat? I know. There's
gonna be alcoholic right here. It's the Zombrex company. They wanted to infect everybody so
then they could sell everybody Zombrex. It's a conspiracy.
Yeah, but if the world was all zombies then what the hell, what are you gonna do with money?
Burn it?
Oh, they're lining up for Zombrex. They're paying with like cash.
What the fuck was that? Did I do that?
Oh no, she grabbed my gun. The backstab.
No. Fake hair? Wait, did I just pull her whole scalp off? Is it wig?
Oh, obliterate. Okay, well that was a little... Stacey is with the Fentatrans. She's harvesting
all the zombies and trying to kill me. Go right, right. The cutscene is way less emotional when
you're wearing the mask. All right, the facts. So I gotta wear the beer helmet. That's important.
Any whiskey in here? Wait, you could have been a great, you could have been a great kid.
We could have been great. I'm reading that wrong. You didn't deserve this,
Sullivan. I can't believe I didn't see through that bitch's lies.
Sicko, psycho, sicko. This is for the police, guys. Come on.
So that's the final boss? Where's TK? Oh, it's all right. I got the fucking BFG.
Is there whiskey in here? No, it's snacks. No whiskey? All right, whiskey is everywhere.
So I have to make that before a thousand people unsub this channel. So bear with me here for a
minute, guys. It's beer. Okay, right. TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK, TK,
TK. Okay. Everybody saying TK. All right. Let's go see what's going on. TK, how are you?
It's the same conversation I had before. How long are some of your guys and noses at this point?
You guys tell any more fucking lies, your noses going through the monitor.
I'm surprised you can even make it through a doorway. Well, no, that's just straight on.
So you'd be fine. Don't turn though. You'll break in half. Jill Krung gets thanks for the
five community subs. No beer? All right. The facts. I'm just looking for the fact.
One beer is all I need. I'm going to go to the bar. There's usually a bar. Where's there a bar?
The closest bar. The drink bean. I mean, this is the drink bean, but they don't have beer here,
do they? You don't serve a beer at a coffee shop. No, Vegas does. Yeah, but that's different. All
right. Where's there just a bar or a beer? I know there's one like all the way down. Sports. What's
in the middle here? Something in the middle. The craps thing. Yeah, there might even be one over
here. I'll take another orange juice. Yes, I will. I love minestrone soup. That's pretty good. Yeah.
It's very, it's very good. I'm with you on that one. All right. Beer. Just coffee creamer. Oh my
goodness. Can I puke with the mask on? Oh, they have anti-puke shields. Wait, he has one. Why is
it working on me? It's because I'm infected. Oh, that's what it is, huh? Weird. All right. I need
a beer. Beer. No beers in there? How's that possible? It's a craps table. Perfect opportunity.
Check it out. Nice. That felt good. All right. No more. Looking for a beer. Wait, see one?
That's, is that a beer or is that ketchup? Damn it. It's ketchup. What about the security box stuff?
I feel like I missed a whole portion of this game. What's it called? Jump scare, jump space.
Fortune city bank. Let's go. I don't think this is a car. I really don't. It does not operate like a
car. This thing floats. It's on air. That thing controls like an air hockey puck. What's going on?
Bastards. The world has got to see this. Photo time. This is unbelievable.
Ah, the tree got in the way. No, it's not. It's a very bad photo actually.
But I think I still, I think I got it. Where am I going? This way. Save point. I don't want to get
too overzealous because I don't want to activate the final game. Frank needs Zombrex. Oh shit,
I forgot I could take that. Watch out. It's a pod. Did I kill this? God damn it. I got a picture of
the pod. No, that's not what I want. All right, let's destroy this thing. Destroy it. Nice. What
did that do? Why am I playing with the controller? Because I prefer controllers. For third person
action games, I play GTA with a controller. Playing with a controller. I know it has terrible
analog aiming, but moving around and walking around is a lot better than WASD for third person
games. I just like it. I like the analog. There's WASD for subtle turns like what you just saw right
there. Son of a bitch. Mouse is only good for first person. It depends. It depends. Oh my god.
Oh fuck, this is very bad. Where is he? Okay, so they're just everywhere. They're everywhere
and they're wearing like all gray, so they blend in with the background of the game.
You know what? No, it's not. There's not enough people to do this.
Get the fuck away from me. Is there a reason for me to do this? Does anybody know?
Queen. I definitely don't want to get rid of that. Here, just back my machine gun.
Let me back my rifle. Let's go. Wait. Okay. Easy, easy, easy. All right, watch out for the military.
They're like right over here. Just hug the wall. BFG. Doesn't matter. Well, it takes just one guy.
There's a beast standing near you. That's it, right? Yep. Boom. All right. Any assault rifles?
Have I screamed yet? Not yet. Blueberry Buffet. Let's go. Turn, please scream. Why do you guys
want me to scream? All right. Save points right ahead. I'm going to do that. I'm going to take...
Do I have room? There's a lot of food here. They can't get over here, so.
They can't get over here, right? I still need a beer. Did anybody see a beer?
No, there's a large soda. No beer. Beer? When you don't want one, they're just never around.
But when you do want one, you can never find it. Money? Go to the bar? Well, let me go to the bank
first. Because I have all these security keys that I don't know where the hell they're for,
and it's the final, like the final portion of this whole game. Save it, please.
I remember this fight. Wow, look at all these memories we made in Dead Rising 2.
Too many to count. Let's do this one.
Yeah, remember we came in here? There's a boss that ran around in circles and stuff.
Beer in the trash. Does vodka count? No. Scrounging into the garbage cans with drinks.
Two bottles of vodka, for real? I don't even want it. I wanted to see it break. Go to the bar?
Yeah, I know, but if it's like here, I'm going to do it. Because I need a maintenance permit anyways.
Where the hell am I? Oh, this is the bank. No, it's not. Food. Coming soon. Music. Bagged. Sports.
Venice Touch. Where's the actual, is the bar right in the middle here? Space, jump space. Right here.
I'll get it after this. The bank. So I'm in the bank. Security clearance accepted.
Look at all these boxes. Security box one. How much money was in there? $50,000?
Hold on, this is all this money? 329. No, why didn't I just come here? Locked. $900,000 in there.
Oh, $40,000. Thank god. $185,000, $10,000, $999,000. There's Zombrex in here. That's unbelievable.
Okay, let's just, might as well open them all. I'm here. There's Zombrex in here, too.
Gems? I don't need, I don't want these. I have four Zombrex. Should I just take two?
What happens if I stick myself a Zombrex twice? Just gems. That's shitty. Well, that's an extra
almost $500,000 from the security boxes. You become immune. Well, buy the car again. That's
not gonna do anything for me, though. Well, that was cool. Now let's go to the bar and then I'm
gonna go to the maintenance room and get, people will resubscribe. Imagine not buying the Hummer
and buying the sports car instead. Oh, mega lol. I don't know what that means. All right, there's a
beer. You ready? I'm gonna do it. Where's that maintenance room? It's like right here somewhere.
Don't accidentally drink it. That kind of looks like fun. You can play these, too. Maybe I should
play these. Time you've been waiting for. Wait, closed door, closed door, closed door. I know,
I know. I got it. What a ricochet. What a ricochet. And beer. Here you go. Beer hat. So,
okay, cool. So who cares? It's kind of cool. Save the game. Straight ahead. I got my beer hat.
I got everything I need this way. Best healing in the game. Who cares? Is it the best healing
in the game? How often can I use it? It's going the wrong way. Don't ever use it. Oh shit, I have
to finish this. I only got five hours until the whole game explodes. How do I get over here?
Can I not get in there? Fuck. I can't get into that save point from here? There's a tunnel. Oh,
okay, that way. Anything else over here? Orange juice. I'll take the orange juice. Just in case
I need it. Softlock Albertson. I have not gotten softlocked once and you know it. A softlock
would mean that I have to start the game over. I haven't had to start the game over yet.
I'm fine. All right, the facts. Let's move. This thing's really good for just clearing the path.
So just bang left. Something you never do. I've only been able to do this with this weapon for
the last like 20 minutes. And stopping and clearing a path is actually kind of hard because
you have to, if you have people with you, they just don't listen.
You want to go through the window? What do you want me to do here, game? Softlock. I have to make
sure. Not yet. Come onto this. All right, this is it. Harvester. There's another harvester here.
Uh oh. Military. Goblin mask and battery. Not the best time to tell me all this.
Wasted. Let's destroy this thing. That gun. Still good. I'm gonna have to use the BFG here.
Uh oh. Yeah. Okay. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Just.
He's not a Freddy. He's the rope gun.
Give me that. Uh. Gun on you? It's not very much ammo.
Warmoot, thanks for the 10 gifted subs. Thank you Warmoot. Sorry, I couldn't really look.
All right, we're gonna try the hat. Should I drink out of the hat? No, I still have an arch,
too. I'm free of the slot. Flashlight. Box and nails. Uh. Box and nails and propane tank?
All right. It's a hazard. I have to. All right, I gotta use it.
Going this way. Uh. Wait, there's gems right there. This gem's right here. Hold on. Leave me alone.
Stop coughing. You coughed so long. Light saber. I can't do anything with that. Laser sword and
blast gun. I know I'm probably getting one guide right now. That's all right. Let's move. I gotta
move. Facts, facts, facts, facts. I don't have any guns for this. Shit. Um. I'm just gonna avoid
them. I have to go that way. All right, see if I can do anything about this.
Fuck. Whoa! Holy shit, you just came out of nowhere. All right, that's actually the best
thing that could have happened. Fucking aiming. Guy with a gun. All right, we're good. Give me
your gun. Why are you holding a serving tray? This old gun, right? Give me that. How many more
of these are there? I tried to aim at you. Okay, I got it when I need it. I'm gonna need it right
over here. Here we go. I'm gonna line it up. Are they dead? Where's the military? These things?
I picked up an ice cream. Shit. Okay, I gotta. I want that gun back. All right, my crutch is
almost gone. Is this thing gone? It is. Go! I got one more shot in this thing. Make it work.
Did I pass one? Where the fuck did I go? All the way down here. Is that all I can get? Is there a drink
out of the helmet? It's probably out. No, I have to move. Okay, the thing is actually pretty good.
Wait, picture! That's not a secret picture or something? How? Is there a save point? Is this
one straight ahead? Wait! All right, save point. Right in the middle. Hopefully I have enough time
to do this. Come on. Where are we? Day five. I would say this is the safe one. We'll do this one.
I don't know. I have items right now. I have the beer hat. That's it. Wasted. Wasted. It's all right.
I have to get through this. There's some guns up here, definitely. Yeah, I think we can just
solve like this. Give me the grenade! What happened? Was that a super queen? Was that like an ultra
queen? Did I throw the grenade? How? Get away from me. There's so many. I need that gun back.
It's okay. Oh, fuck. No! No! Give me that queen! Okay, 45. Okay, there's still more to do here.
How the fuck is this possible? There's more of this shit? Oh, man. I need to get that boot over there.
I got the assault rifle. What do you mean? A dope? What do you mean? A dope? Uh-oh. Oh, shit.
I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble. I need to bring out the thing. No! The queen, quick. She's right
here. Gun. Defiler. Give me this other queen. How many are there? Uh-oh. Okay. This feels like I'm
cheating. Who cares? I don't even know what I have for items. Oh, fuck. Okay. Don't puke. Don't puke.
Another fucking harvesting. Holy shit. That took a million years.
I'm so glad I did not dick around any longer than that. Well, here's your last harvester.
Come and get me, you interfering bastard.
Uh, save the game record. And then I'm gonna go wheelchair. Let's go. What? Get this fucking
thing out of the way. Get it out of the way. I want to save. Day five, four a.m. Day five,
twelve. All right. I'm gonna save over this one. No. That. I don't know. This one. This one.
Sloppy ass fucking thing. Give me a break. That's just so unbelievable. Just drive it.
Oh, that's what I wanted to do. I want to pick up and push.
Push the wheelchair. What are you stopping you? I'm so angry. Seriously.
Well, I just took like three fucking pieces of damage for no reason.
Place it down. Stand behind it. Circle. Are you in the right? I think you're in the right area.
Yeah. Okay. Now you can push it. What ride is she on? I don't know. I'm almost out of stuff to eat
and stuff to drink and stuff to consume. Is she on this ride?
All right. Just eat here for a second. There's always beer in the beer hat. Yeah, I know,
but I don't want to like be throwing up. Yes, I was about to eat the spoiled hot dog and then
I immediately came to the conclusion it was a bad idea. Let's go. Right here?
Is she going to get into Metal Gear? Yeah. She's going to stand up in a giant.
Haven't you? You work for Fina Trans. So this is all for what? Money.
You're even more of an idiot than I thought. This is about saving lives. Saving lives. You
created a panic to drive up demand. You're missing the point, Frank. This is funny.
We can't save your precious sombrex without for our country. TK losing the keys. He was
well paid for giving us access to the cages. His show was going down the tubes anyway,
which was obvious. He decided to get here. Oh, look at me. Look at me. Make it hard for us to
finish the job. So what? He dragged you into this? So why didn't he give you up? You think I'm stupid
enough to deal with an asshole like that myself? But enough talk, Frank. I had a feeling you'd show
up, so I prepared a little toy for you. I hope I don't have to do this from the very back of that
last cutscene or whatever. I hope this is the checkpoint. All right. Let's go. Well,
um, good pick. I got a lightsaber. All right. So let me see. Should I shoot the arm?
Shoot the eye. Shoot the light. Shoot the eye. Climb anywhere? Maybe just lightsaber the arm?
Oh, well, you got to take off the armor first. All right. I get it.
I don't get it, but it's okay. What do we do with the rockets?
I guess. That's definitely lightsaber. You got to get close and knock off the armor.
All right. Well, you guys are right. All right. Good. It's going to happen now.
I don't have any more. You said I had infinite drink. You guys lie to me. I don't have infinite
drink. Let's get this off. Come on. Still throwing up. I don't have any more heals.
There's probably heals in like a box, right? There it is. All right. Box looking for heals
in a box. Great. There's a military crate right here. There's nothing in that. Oh fuck. Yeah,
there is. Look at this. I don't want to pick up the stools. You still made it through. Get the
fuck out of here. What's the queen going to do for me right now? Eat that. Oh shit. What's left to
destroy on your arm? I have no more food. There's nothing in there. There we go. Oh shit. Don't kill
me. I'm about to run out of time too. Yeah. Okay. So we have to take out the. Where is this? Where's
this putting me? Why is this putting me all the way back here? The damn game has checkpoints
everywhere and you wouldn't put one before like the last boss. Why is it? Why is it back here?
All right. I'm going to keep the gun. The lightsaber is all right. Actually, this is not that bad.
All right. Shoot off stuff. That's actually, I'm not a terrible visitor. Here we go.
I understand what happens now. We got to dodge, shoot. Actually, that actually sucks. That really
sucks. The gun is absolutely pointless. Bring the stool. If the stool works better than the
lightsaber, I'll be so angry. Do it. Do the angry thing. Bring it down again. Got greedy. Rockets.
All right. I'm going to stop reading chat because somebody just wrote Wubba lubba dub dub.
Like that's going to help. That's going to help. Thanks for the help. Swing it down.
Rockets. What is phase two even going to be? It's kind of like injectors. So lightsaber's almost
broken. All I have is the defiler after this. Hopefully it can last. Uh oh. All right. Here we
go. Phase two. Now what? I don't know what that means. Okay. Uh, clap, clamp, clamp, and then
got it. And then, okay, that's how it goes. It goes clap, clamp, clamp, clamp. I'm so scared to go
This thing is really fucking slow. Boxes now. Clamp, clamp, clamp, and then the middle.
Is this thing almost broken too? What? I'm going to have to kill it with a stool.
Clamp, clamp, in the middle. I hope I can kill this thing with a stool. What if I run out of objects?
Okay. Dodge. Right in the middle. Clamp, clamp, clamp, middle. Take a picture. Got it. No.
Shit. I need a new weapon. What's this? I'm trying to take a photo. All right. Give me a stool. Give
me a stool. Vodka and a stool. Okay. I'm fine. Here it is. It's already broken. Fuck. Is that
not hurting you? Got it. Oh shit. Oh my God. Okay. I gotta slow down. I'm like panicking for no reason.
That doesn't hurt you. That doesn't hurt. That doesn't hurt. I just don't ever shoot the gun.
Another stool. Knife. Stool. Get the fucking stool. Pick it up. I'm almost out of time. I'm
almost out of time. Time's about to be over. No. God damn it. I'm out of time. Do it. Do it. Do it.
Do it. Don't. Just please plant down. I need to hit you like three more times. Go down into the
ground. Oh my fucking God. Go down into the ground so I can hit you. What is it doing? What's going
on? It's the gun. It's not doing anything. The gun's not doing anything. No. I was literally
shooting the weak part of the claw and it did no damage. I had an electric stick. The electric
stick only had... It was red. Did I... Is it gonna lose or what? Okay. Well, that's my ending
apparently. All right. There's no record of the shelter dwellers having made it out of the city.
Sure. Reload. Reload it. Of course they give you two stools and a knife. Like there's nothing
else back there that could be put back there. No. Two stools and a knife. Why is there not
a fucking like pipe or something? Why is this stool? Why would you put stools back there?
I can't even skip this. I can't skip this.
Okay. Let's open it back up. Before I go in there, I'm gonna bring... I'm ditching every gun I have.
I'm not bringing a single firearm into that fight. I'm gonna bring as many melee weapons as
possible. They just do so much more damage. He's gotta hit the hand.
The guns were... Yeah, but why would I bring six guns when they do like...
They don't do any damage. You see how much damage I was doing with the defiler? That thing was
taking like fucking 10% per swing, folks. Why wouldn't I just bring like a rake? All right.
Which one is it? Okay. Give me a fucking rake. Give me... I want a rake? Check this shit out.
All right. Two by four and a knife. Two by four and a rake. Two by four and a battery.
Two by four and a lawnmower. But I'm not gonna use that. Just bring the two by four.
Knife and... I have the lightsaber. I have the defiler. I have this knife. Rake? I think that'd
be all right. Battery and mask. Head and battery. How do I take the head off? I can't remove my head.
Rake and battery. Let's try rake and battery. All right. Let's do it.
All right. Now I'm gonna use this to get there. I'm gonna bring a two by four.
Just in case. All right. I'm ready. Let's get the hell out of here. I actually know I have
to walk with this. All right. Fine. Fuck it. Let's go. Rake. Get away from me.
Ah. All right. Here we are. Same deal. Why are you dropping the rake? Why are you dropping the
rake? Oh, I jumped and landed and somebody touched my foot. Whoops. Oh my god. It's gone?
Like, why do you keep doing this to me? Why is he doing that? All right. It's over. Let's go.
See? Why would I shoot a gun right now? Can you please get up? Leave me alone. Please. Thank you.
Look at this shit. Are you kidding me? Got it. Taking a broad picture of rake. Hey, we settle down.
Look at that. Already at phase two. Let's do it. Come on. Clap, clap. Middle. Clap, clap.
Right there. See how good this is. So good. That's insane. I'm so glad I did not bring any
guns. Right in the middle. Clap, clap. In the middle. No. Stop. What's this RNG dog doing?
Oh my god. Do you hear what he just did?
Do it. It's a gun. Quick. That gun was doing an insane. What do I do? What do I do?
I have to use a gun. How is this possible without a gun? Just slow down. She's gonna
bury her head into the ground. Now what? Activate the racket? What the fuck just happened? Why? Did
I activate missiles? Oh fuck. Fight Stacy. What? Okay. I get it. I get it. I get it.
I have to get back up there. Okay. That was very fast. Just get up there. What? He's stupid.
Can I not activate this one? I can't jump over the arm. Wait. Just slow down. Give me the orange juice.
I'm running out of time. I have about like 12 minutes.
Okay. Fight Stacy. Let's go. Let's go. Please.
Activate it. Okay. Here we go. It's a good thing she's an idiot. Oh god. Did I lock it?
I think it's locked. I can't do anything anymore. I think it's over.
Do I have to go to the other one? This is fucking outrageous, man.
Coming? No. No. No. No. No. No. No. I have to halt. I have to stop. Pause the game. Pause the game.
Pause the game. Pause the game. I have to do this again. It's all right. The rake is
phase three. Oh my fucking god. The rake was perfect. Just use the rake and then you have
to jump from platform to platform and activate the fucking terminal. God damn it. I blame everybody
that told me I'm to make the hack because I'm just drinking booze and it's fucking ruining
everything. All right. Let's go. Rake. Fast. Nothing matters. I only need a rake. Rake and
battery. Let's go. Save time. That's the only item that matters. Check it out. Watch this.
Save the game right now. Please get the beard trimmer out of the way. We're going to slot one.
Let's go. Why save? So I don't have to make this ever again.
Two fucking stun mechanics in games like these make me want to puke blood. Just reload. Just
reload the goddamn game. This is unbelievable. I could drown myself back in this. There's a zombie
on top of me and I think I take more damage when a random person swipes at me running through the
crowd. Why is it like this? Here comes a 45 minute sex scene. There are no sex scenes.
There's no shame in restarting with my current level. That would be a really good idea if
I wasn't in the last like 12 minutes of the whole game. If I were to go to the very beginning now,
oh uh-oh. It wouldn't take that long to rush. No. No, no, no. I got it. I got it. I got it. I
got another mechanic. Pretty clean run by the way. This is a good checkpoint. By the way,
if it looks like I'm going to lose, I'm just going to quit. Make another rake. I can only
hold one at a time. If I make a second rake, it's not going to work. I'm going to bypass pretzels.
I don't need it. Here we go. Clean. For the part here. Good. Missed it. No, I don't need the
pretzel. I should not take damage in this first phase. Maybe the second one, but not this one.
That did so much damage that it hurt his hand and he pulled back. Good. Good. Good. I'll get a few
photos. Don't worry. That bad. Give me that second phase. Give me that second phase.
Let's go. Nobody touch anything. Good RNG here. I need it. That's not good RNG. It's bad RNG.
That's also very bad RNG. 50% on the first swing. All right. The rake's almost done.
It's a toss. Nice. Do it again. Bang, bang, bang.
Sorry. I'll get it on the next run. One more. All right. One more. And then, oh, good RNG.
All right. Let's go. Clean. This time, it's a QTE fight. Don't fuck it up.
Got it. It's okay. I got it, right? QTE. Did I do it? Okay. Let's go. It hurts.
One more. What do I have for alcohol? No, orange juice. Just take it slow. Orange juice.
Don't drink any booze. Don't aggro. Okay. Why can I not activate this? What happened?
All right. Back to one. Back to one. Back to one. Back to one. No soft lock for me.
I thought I was going to screw that up on that last one. I think that's kind of scary.
It's like you're a little out of your league, boy.
It's Agent S. I'm ready for extraction. Yeah. I just have an old newspaper
that needs to be taken out to the trash.
That's such an anticlimactic way to die in a game like this. It's just like,
no, you're just instantly dead. Dead, dead, dead.
Wait. What do you mean before the firebombing begins?
How many hours are left before the firebomb begins?
Okay. I thought I had to get to the roof again.
Go get TK. Where is he? Wait, where where's she? Sturned to a zombie?
What did I just do? I skipped it. Yeah, but I didn't, I didn't think I was going to do that.
Did I skip the cutscene too? No, no, we're here.
She's alive.
Is this a dig at the first game having like a gigantic fetch question in the game?
Compromising photo. Oh man, look at all this shit. All right, it's pee time. I gotta get up a
stretch. I'm gonna pee. I'll be back in like two or three minutes. Stretch your legs. You'll be
right back for overtime. So instead of doing overtime, I was probably, I was thinking about,
thinking of going back to the save where I lost Juan and just going from there. I felt kind of
really bad about it. I missed core, during that little final boss there, core monster gave 20
community subs. Thank you for this huge sub drop core monster. I missed it, but just touch upon it
now. That's a lot of people. I have plenty of Zombrex, so that's good. You have to do a perfect
run. There's no way I'm doing that. All right, so let's go. Zombrex stat. I'm gonna go,
uh, start on the top right. Start over here at, uh, painkillers. Yeah, I'm gonna go all the way
around. Oh, what's the one right next to me here? We'll go this way. Find the compromising photo.
Let's do it. What? Okay, that was strange. That was very weird. So what does it look like now
outside? I'm so happy. Dead Rising 1. Overtime. True ending. Dead Rising 2. Overtime. True ending.
No resets. Time? Yeah, I'm just, I'm going for it. Are they military everywhere like
that wasn't the first one? There's only one reason why I would be upset at this game,
and it would be if it was just a cop, just a carbon copy of Dead Rising 1 when it was just
people's. Okay. It's not, I don't think it is. I can still gamble too. Maybe kind of compromising
photo. Where is it? Okay.
Wait, what, what the hell was that? All right, let's go to Zombrex Stash. That's the next one,
right? Where is this one? Is it up? It's down. Okay. It's in the garage. Underground tunnels.
Check the photo. Yeah, I haven't looked at the photos in a long time. This one sucks. This one
really sucks. Oh, right. That's one. I almost threw like a grenade at these two. Who's standing
there? All right. I like that. Strange. Whose boobs are these? No, that's okay. That's the bum.
I don't know why I took a photo of this. Half of these are just on accident.
I never got rid of the snipers either. Oh, that's important. This one, is this one saved? Wait,
I'm sharing these. I don't want to share them. I just want to lock them. This one sucks. This
one sucks. Oh, that. I was trying to throw it at it and hit her in the head and right when I hit her,
take the picture. That one sucks. That would've, but it was a good one before when you got run
over by the thing. These are just like, I need to get rid of them. Okay. The people hugging photos
just don't need to be saved. Okay, cool. Zombrich stash. He hates when people are in love.
There's no reason to have it. Do you guys really think that Disney World keeps all the photos of
you going down the crest of the roller coaster? No. The second that you don't want to buy it,
they delete it. Am I not going the right way? What's happening here?
I am. I'm going the right way, right? Yeah, I gotta go underground. They sell the photos to the
government. If you really think the government wants you going down Splash Mountain, I mean,
I don't know what to tell you. Where are they storing all this stuff? So you're telling me
that the government has a photo of everybody when they've ever gone down Splash Mountain.
What hard drive is this on? Just Disney photos alone is probably 7,000 to 10,000,
probably like 55,000 petabytes or something. It's on the cloud. Queen's here. Just give it to me.
Give it to me. Yes. Oh, man. Oh, man. That's how you get somebody upset.
That's how you get somebody really upset. This is what just happened right there.
Look at that car. And imagine being the government employee that goes through those.
That would be the most boring fucking job ever. It's just going over hundreds of millions
of going down the Splash Mountain photo. For what? What are you storing them for?
What would you have to have that for? For face recognition. I mean, it's fun for the police.
Wait, what? We're going to get the staff. I grabbed again. I swear I need to heal now, too.
Oh, it's in the train. I can't just climb this. I know I'm going to puke. That's good.
I kind of don't need this magazine anymore. It's useless to me.
I dropped the helmet. Yeah, because I puked and I don't want it anymore.
Trans left a nice little gift basket. What do you guys think your CIA profile looks like in the
photo regard? Do you really think there really just is like 600,000 photos of you? Imagine getting
that like on the drive. They're just like here. Here's every photo. It's just you walking down
some street. Cut his mic. No, keep my mic on. Where do I need to go? I need a car or something.
Car, motorcycle. Grab me right now. You guys just extra grabby. Oh, for the love of God,
just kill them. They're not going to stop. They're never going to stop. So why not just get rid of
them? I hate it. He hates it. He does. He does hate it. I got it. Don't worry. Okay. I'm just
making sure I'm going the right way. Did GPS freak the fuck out? I got it. Oh yeah. I'm ready. And
amplifier and gun. Amplifier and flashlight. Amplifier and defiler. Amplifier and beer.
Amplifier and this thing. Nope. I don't have the BFG. No, I don't. Sad. Motor oil. I never
use this for anything. What should I do with this? Drink it. You can't drink motor oil.
You should check the combo page in all caps. There's a lot of info here. Money. What else
can I do with the computer? I don't see motor oil anywhere. There's no motor oil on this list.
So the person that screamed at me, I'm going to scream back. Spray paint and knife. Eh,
another handgun. All right. I'm going to waste one of these. Handgun and spray paint.
Pipe and what am I looking for now? Right here. All right. Expensive champagne.
Turn off the face cam. I don't have one on. Wait. Orange juice and beer. Nectar. Orange juice,
orange juice. No. Is that a waste? I feel like I want these orange juice. No, whatever.
I need this spray paint. Just cover yourself in paint.
Beard. Double beard. I can't fucking believe my just drank that. I was trying to punch you.
Flip it. I want you to clip that. Clip that because it was nothing in my tray.
Flip it. Go look at it. Go look at it. I want to punch this guy. There was nothing in the image
right. Go clip it. I want you to look at it. I can't put a coin in there. All right. Get me out of
this. Wait. There's a beer. Beer and vodka. Let's do it. Nectar and queen. I can't put
queen in there. Nectar and queen. Wait. Let me flush this out. Let me flush this out first.
Okay. So that's randomizer. All right. Nectar and queen. If I do this and it's wrong,
I'm not going to scream for two months. Okay. Are you sure you want me to do this still?
Good. You can't. You can't even put the queen in there. See. In two months.
Look at all these fucking handguns. All right. I don't even need this anymore.
I've been holding on to it for no reason. Sounds like a shotgun though. I have to redo this.
Stupid idiot meat on bone. Stupid idiot meat on bone. Meat on bone. Meat on bone. Meat on bone.
Stupid idiot meat on bone. Stupid idiot meat on bone. I'm just trying. Oh, there's the expensive
one. Okay. Should I do one more? Yeah. I'm going to do one more time and I'm going to replace
the queen. Queen and nectar at work bench. All right. I'll do queen and nectar at the work
bench. If it's not real, I'm not going to scream for like six years. I'm just going to come back
when I'm like 45. Be like, remember me? I really got you right chat. Okay. Give me that clean back.
I'm going to replace the, this thing's pretty much toast anyways. So fuck it. Give me the queen.
Let's go workshop. There's a bunch on the way, but wait, this tube right in front of me.
Let's go get, okay. We got, that's going to be last. Let's go get,
let's go get men's silk thong and then come back and do the other ones.
And anybody that like disagrees with what I'm saying is getting a timeout.
If I swing and miss and I don't hit a zombie and you say, like you swung and missed LOL,
timeout. I can't talk. This thing's pretty much done. Let's do a grenade. Fine. Yeah, sure. Boom.
I didn't get a chance to see it. Let's go.
Did you guys watch the stream? If I was constantly like this, like this, ready? Like,
no, no, no, shut the fuck up. Let's just shut the fuck up. The next person that says anything
like that. I'm going to go guys. Shut up guys. Stop, stop, stop. I swear to God, I hate you guys.
What if I was like that? Are people like that? Yeah. Well now you have forever.
Anytime I get frustrated in the game or I get mad about something, I never want to get like actually
like, the stream is ruined to angry. You know what I mean? Cause there's a certain line where
you just are so upset that like the stream is ruined and your day is ruined. Mario tennis.
Oh, it's upstairs. Yeah. I think I've allowed one in five years of streaming.
I'm not allowed one stream where I'm like fucking stupid, fucking games,
fucking stupid, dumb fucking idiot. Fucking game is stupid. I'm not allowed one of those.
Ooh, you didn't use it. No, I didn't.
All right. So that gives us that. Let's move. Uh, what's faster? What do you think?
These two last. Yeah. We'll go down to the uh, sutures.
Change mask, please. Fucking not change my fucking mask. Fucking stupid fucking thing.
He's not even trying to string together a sentence. Just saying, just being angry and saying swears.
Come on over the top. I can't throw him over the top rope. What we got here? Randomizer.
Let's see what it does. What does it do? Nothing. Just pew. Nothing. Stupid. Fucking dumb.
We've talked about it a million times before, but there's always a way you can tell when somebody's
really mad. Instead of talking like this, they drop the voice down like this and they talk kind
of fast and they just fucking say like this is fucking stupid. I'm not even, this is like seriously
fucking dumb. You drop down to like normal I'm talking on the phone voice with like,
no, you wouldn't be like that mad. Who are you that mad at? You're like really, really angry with
somebody on the phone. What is this? Spin the wheel. Should I do the wheel? Spin the wheel.
A thousand bucks. It's $25,000 to spin this again. Oh my goodness. I keep talking over and over and
over again. Let's spin the wheel and see what's going on with all my money. I'm not sure that's
gonna happen. Yikes. Is this one super defense? The queen. No, no, no. If I use the queen, so
when people are gonna write stupid fucking dumb fucking idiot, I'm telling you, I'm not supposed
to do it. I lost. I lose again. How do you win? I wish I could just play this. You know, I really
wish I could just play this. Instead of being cough, stun locked. I wish I could just play that.
I need a weapon. Something that's not a serving tray. This should be a fucking internal clock
that like you can't talk more than once every 20 seconds. Do you upset me? I don't know. I'm
just going. This is ridiculous. Look at how long that lasts. It's a full five seconds.
Fucking dumb fuck. Fucking, fucking thin. I'm using a toy and it's almost broken.
It comes with throw up. Don't do it. Can I have them? Just go over here and go in the maintenance
room. Okay guys, see you in three months. Nope, I get a stream. Wingman. Wicked. What does it do?
Where is it? Is it the first one? Unleash this ruthless wasp against the zombie menace.
So it's just a, why is this in here? An oil? What does this do? Sword, training sword and oil.
Ready to rumble. Well, that's awesome. I'm going to hold on to that. Brum and is there a machete
you're on? Brummin something else. Maybe. I just drank the thing. I need a good, thank God. There's
one right here. This is a good one. I already have one of these. I have two. I'm not even using them.
Zombrex. Almost didn't do it. Oh my God. That would have been so funny. All right. It's gonna be a brum.
Get it out. Then we go all the way out and around. Is there a safe point in here? No,
it's out this way. Okay. I have a weapon. Y'all better run. Think of the funny drama that I find
moment. There's a rocket launcher. What? Where's there a rocket launcher? Liar. Where? Oh, no lies
here. Not a liar. It's a good trait. I'm gonna take the sword too. And I'm getting rid of the hat.
Take a sip and then get rid of it. No, I want to throw it. Okay. Give me my, I've got my sword. I've
got my rocket launcher. Let's move. 100 in here. This game is sick. Seriously, this game is sick.
Would you guys still stay here and watch it? I, all right, let's find out. I'm curious.
Game's fucking sick.
I was gonna say, somebody said in the chat, I was gonna go, y'all, this is dope. That's it.
All right, we need gauze. Save it. Do a rocket jump? No, that'd be cool if we could.
Dynamite. Not bad. Not bad.
Am I stuck in here? I just look over and I see that now. I can't get out of this. I really can't
leave with this. Can I throw it? Nope. Throw backwards like this. Throw it. Why won't he throw
it now? It's getting fucking dope. Come on. Is that close enough? That guy. All right. I'm
getting real sick of this thing. Give it to me. Why can't, okay. Sick. That's annoying. That's
annoying. Why can't I get this out of here? Sorry, I went down into the waterfall thing.
Didn't mean to. I do want this gun. If I don't. I jumped into that guy's arm. That's how you know
it stinks like a turd. When I jump into the guy's hands. Like he was waiting for me to jump.
All right, they both right over here. I'm gonna go read a book. This is too sick.
I hope the book is good. What is the book? You can't leave without saying the book. Title.
Plus the title. Let's go. Flashlight in case I find gems.
Save this guy. What was the point of saving this person? I could have given that Zombricks to the
whole lady. Not very big brained of you. What books do I read? I like to have a certain amount
in my possession at all times. Sunday morning cartoon pages. The Bazooka Joe bubblegum.
The back of the glade when I'm taking a shit. What else do we got?
Anything that has ingredients in it? The newspaper. If the newspaper was still
cold I would get it and read it on the toilet. This is not. I don't like the way a newspaper feels.
When you pick up a newspaper and you touch it and you it's like a sandy weird
awful feeling on your hands. I hate it. You can almost feel the ink kind of coming off. It's
uh I really don't like it. It's a weird thing that I don't like.
Yes I also don't like the sound of tape being pulled and I don't like popping balloons.
Hey you found a real weird one. Return to the arena.
Now let's try this again. Just was not meant to be. Ever. Where did my sword go? The cool one.
He swung and you missed. It's all right. Boomerang plus knight makes a boomerang knight.
I got it. That guy's dead. Boomerang knight. Uh can I get a couple uh can I get a couple of
hyucks in the chat please for the boomerang knife that somebody just said? I don't want to break it.
Last opportunity I'm gonna get to do the 25th of 10 000. Can I do it again? Let's see if I can do
it. 25 grand. Now I did it. Didn't I have a weapon? Oh that guy got faced. That guy was not even
paying attention. He was looking at his fingernails and he's still instagramming.
Instagram? Is that what I said? I did not say Instagram. Don't forget to save.
That person just saved the whole stream. Seriously. If you don't think so look it up. I go on the
wrong one every time. No German. No no no no. Let me know. 5 20 12 52 2 a.m. This one right here.
Turn on your face cam. You don't need a face cam. It's not necessary. Give us content. It's not
necessary. I need a face cam and like oh and like it'll be called face cam fridays. Remember that
was a big deal. I used to have a series on youtube called face cam fortress because that was a big
deal to have your face cam turned on during the game. I know a lot of you are laughing right now.
This was like 2011. 2012. That was a big deal back in 2011. Wait wow you can actually do that.
Pretty sick. Arena time.
Where's Darth Vader? I can't even say it. Where's Darth Vader?
Start what?
I just came to the stream and I don't understand this like my weapon writing number is minus two
plus two. Like I don't fucking get this stupid fucking thing. It's fucking dumb.
Why don't I just chat? I'm fucking the stream is fucking dumb.
All right survive. I don't have any weapons. Climb up there. Climb over and kill him immediately.
Coughed. He pre-coughed. He pre-coughed on me. I'm oh it walls up. This is my like worst nightmare.
Just being surrounded by these things. I'm gonna fucking believe. Why would I drink that up here?
I don't know what's going on with my mind. Why would I drink that up there?
I'm so angry about fucking coughing that it's it's malting me. I'm malting. Not malting. I'm
gonna drop my skin. I need a weapon. Stop coughing when you get up on top. Oh my god. What is that?
Oh my fucking god. Right? I'm not saying that. This is the last time you're gonna hear me say
oh my fucking god. What the hell is that? What the hell?
Oops. Perfect timing. Come on. Activate. Activate. You have to escape? No it said survive. Five
thousand bits from David. Saved it. Thank you for the five thousand bits of German. Why are you
being so mean to me? You're making me cry. David. You're fucking sick. You're the best.
Final fight with TK. But thank you David. Thanks for the fifty dollar. That's a lot of money.
Five thousand bits. I'll drink to that. Jesus.
Where's the checkpoint?
What a bad photo.
That would have been so good. He docked again in the worst possible time. What's wrong with Rebecca?
Stop the bleeding. This won't be hard for me. You know how I do. Rebecca I'm sorry. All I have
are pretzels and snacks. Devators you have like a fucking scepter that activates the ground.
This probably looks bad to Rebecca. Like holy shit dude. Like you can't handle this. Watch out for
fire. Let's go get it. All right. Do you have anything else besides like nails and orange juice?
I'm trying to get like something out of the box. What is this? I just need weapons.
Cement saw. Okay finally. I just threw it over the cliff.
Wrench. How did I miss? He's dead? Is he dead? Why would he do that?
All right he's a big wave. All right I need to heal. That's not a heal. How do you avoid that shit?
I need to heal. Heal. Heal. I can't. I can't. I can't do it. I need more healing. Oh he's gonna
activate the shit. How do you blithely get over here without getting killed?
Orange juice. I don't have. I know but fuck. Oh no I can see it but he blows the shit up.
Oh they're gonna hit Rebecca. How do I prevent it from activating this stuff over here?
Like he's just gonna. Here we go. I'm dead. Can I like jump anywhere?
At least I got to taste it before I died. Okay I wonder if there's a. Do I have. How do I.
How do I interrupt him from doing that? I have to do that whole thing again.
So aggravating. I have to do the whole arena thing just to stand around arena thing again.
I'm so. I'm so. I'm so mad by this. That it's making me go the wrong way. So before I fought
that guy somebody said this is the worst boss in the game. I can see why. Not because of how
how hard he is to fight but because I have to do this again. Does anybody know where that guy was?
Where the fuck was that guy? He was over there. God damn it. All right I'm gonna start to save
this stuff. I'm gonna try to hold on to as many weapons as I can. I'm just gonna jump around.
I'm not gonna fight anything. Save the pretzels. Save the food.
Save the bat too. I'm gonna try to see if I can get through this without. Oh I forgot the coffin
exists in this game. Delete the coffin. Right now like the developers of this game like play this
back and they go fuck man we should never play this like that. Hope nobody notices. Come on.
Come on. What a great start.
You never know if I just have to activate this like three times or something.
It's just a time limit. Let's see if it's time. Saw saw saw saw saw saw. I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble. I didn't even want to fall off. That's three times. It's not three times. It's
just time. Oh ladies and gentlemen for the worst checkpoint. I don't want to do this again. I have
to win. I don't want to do this again. I'm not doing this a third time. No human wants to do
this for like a second or third time. I know there's like computer programs that like that
to do this. I don't want to do that. Okay I still have not. I don't understand how
this works. Because when you go too far away. Watch that.
Why is he not getting hurt by that? Pick up the fucking orange juice.
Stop tilting. He comes over and does that? Why didn't that hit him? Okay let's run around the
circle until you. I need to heal Rebecca. There he goes. Does he run to the wall? Is this like a
Mario game? Get over here so I can heal her. Just like taunt or something. How am I supposed to
keep her healed when he never lets up the pressure? Heal? Oh my god. Oh no don't let him kill you.
Don't let him kill you Jeremy. Don't let him do it. He's gonna try. Fuck that move.
Ay yi yi he's gonna run. I just got mortal combated. All right. Mortal combat 2. Great.
Should I just drink a bunch of shit? Just use the queen so we can see what it does.
God I don't even have the queen anymore. All right let's do it.
That is as effective as an attack fly from binding advisor. You don't throw it.
What else do you do? All right I'm gonna drink this and run in. Drink up all.
What is it? Nothing? I only got the painkiller. Is this last? I guess it works.
Get this shit before we go up. No why did you jump that way?
Okay. Okay. Get this queen? Holy shit kill everybody. I mean besides the camera freaking
me out here. Is the camera broken right now? I think it is. Maybe not. Am I out of my mind?
We're getting to wrestler levels of I was waiting for you to do that and we both knew
at the same time you're moving to jump with my heart.
Why puke? I didn't drink anything. Line him up. My baseball bat. Give me like the beer. Give the
bat. What else is over here? Anything? Any secret items? Special items? Queen? I need the bat.
Let me try this again. God damn. All right gotta hit him with the bat and then he'll run away.
I'm cocky with this shit. This thing's freaking me out. Get away from me B.
No! Rebecca please move your head. I want the snack. Why do you gotta do it like that? I'm standing
in front of it. You have to make it so messy. I want that not the three boxes surrounding it.
How is that so hard to understand? It just it like cycles through all of them in a half a second.
It's like just fucking stay on one of them. Molding! I didn't stop halfway. Where'd it go?
Holy shit! No!
Run away. Give me that health. Come on run away. Are you? I got baited. Are you what? Are you
kidding me? Are you fucking serious? Why is he not running away? Are you serious? Are you serious?
They're dead. I'll be back in Dead Rising 3.
Hey what do you say? Break the story.
Doesn't that exact same? That was just Sonic the Hedgehog 2006. Doesn't that happen? That's like
ice. There's a frame from that. That's Sonic the Hedgehog 2006. Nice try. I mean nice try for a
jump scare but he almost got me. That's the car commercial thing. Almost. Long time for that one.
Monsters Inc theme song. That was good. It was constant conflict in the chat before I picked
that in this game and sometimes constant conflict is you know I'm not even going to try it. Well I
even bring it up. There's no reason to say that you were going to do Dead Rising 2 after this.
That may have been a rage statement. Was it? All right let me ask you a question. Before I said that
did I just get grabbed by a zombie or was that potentially like the fourth retry of a boss?
Are we sure? Why did they say that? Was it like a quell? I think that may have been a
quell the audience state. No I'm not going to stream Dead Rising again tomorrow. Four hours?
Let me see what else there is to do. 10 of the last like 11 streams.
They're very good. They're fun. I know you can't know what I'm saying. You know what this music
sounds like so let's just turn it off. Hi. I think you can hear me now. So yeah I'm not doing like
10 out of 11 streams of Dead Rising 3. I do want to play Dead Rising 3 just not right now.
Maybe like in December. Somewhere. We'll put it somewhere. I promise. He's never going to
play it? Yeah yes I am. I said I was never going to play four. All right is there any after credit
sequences or anything? You said you played Devil May Cry 5. Yeah but in a world where we're spoiled
rotten with millions of probably video games and I'm counting iOS like trash can stuff too.
There's like thousands and thousands of great experiences. It's hard to do them all.
You got to find out when you want to do them. It's hard. I started God of War like two months
ago or so. I'm like 30% of the way through the game. I can't go back because I just
were overstimulated with video games now. Like 50 new games come out like every fucking three weeks.
Oh wait. ADHD? No there's a lot of games. A lot of games. I'm talking even ones that I never
played before like this. All right I got game ending S. Zombies killed 39. Say that's too bad.
It's not even 4,000. 25 survivors. 4.3 million dollars. Would you like to save the game? Yes I
would. What about the new Star Wars game? I don't know. It's too many things. Let's just go with one.
There are two DLCs. I mean there's DLC for the DLC. Wait start game.
Anything new? Looks like it's just ending S. Yeah new game sandbox mode. What is sandbox?
I'm assuming it just doesn't do the sandbox challenge. Do I have to like eat a bowl of
cinnamon? Right here. Right here. That's it. You too. Thanks man. Appreciate that. Just the two of you?
Oh all right whatever. You guys are fucking cool.
There's no time limit. Cray survivors roam the city. What? I'm going back in.
Play on the last wrong save. Use the existing save. Hold on. Hold on. All right I can't just jump
off. So load save one? That's not going to show us the credits again? Oh would you look at that?
You just did. Ah yeah. That's my favorite kind of pasta. Angel hair spaghetti.
Bad? How could angel hair spaghetti be bad when it's the same fucking thing? It's all the same
thing. It's just spaghetti. It's just smaller and thinner. It's too thin. No it it you don't I don't
want I don't want my pasta to soak up all that gross sauce. Angel hair pasta. A little bit of
butter. A sprinkle of olive oil. That's how they eat it in Italy. And that's how I eat it. I missed
the fucking first part. What was it? A little bit of olive oil on the pasta. That's how they
eat it in Italy. Well how do they eat it in Italy? Huh? How do they eat it in Italy? Hey you know
they made up lasagna for Americans. You know that right? I'm missing important stuff.
How do Italians eat their food? They relax and socialize while dining for hours.
Over lunch and dinner and coffee Italians enjoy a diet rich in fruits, vegetables,
beans, fish, poultry, olive oil, tomatoes, whole grains, dairy, red wine, and they eat very little
red meat. They dine for hours. Oh it's you. You guys eat too fast. We've already gone over this
shit man. We don't have to go over this again. Everyone just watch like. Oh it hurts going in.
Oh okay. Relax have a have a glass of water. Okay here's a challenge. Kill as many zombies
as you can in 30 seconds. 40 kills? How do I do this this fast? I know I wasted time.
Fuck it. This is sandbox mode. I just get to let my hair down. My hair. My hair.
This is actually kind of cool. All right let me try to get it. I gotta get at least 10.
What's better? Baseball bat's probably better. Go. I'm gonna turn around. Great. I wonder if
there's a gun or something. Less than last time. I need some. I need a weapon. I need some weapons.
Something better than what I have. Why did I drink that? I need a tutor.
Hey that was so funny. I forgot to laugh. That's such an old saying but that makes it. How does
it make any sense? That was so funny I forgot to laugh. Is there a grenade? No. Because you
aren't laughing. Why would you forget to laugh? All right so you probably have to come back up
here with better weapons. 40 people? There's no way that's gonna happen. Not with a wrench.
I'm almost dead. I forgot. Is there a reason why I don't have a super health? I have to wait to
go to the main menu and start from the main menu. Not the costume though.
No. Yeah this is the right save. Otherwise I wouldn't have the costume.
Right? Yeah. It is know you can jump on the boxes. How did somebody not tell me that?
It would last like 16 hours of this game. We did. No you didn't. Let's find another challenge.
I actually kind of like this. This is fun. Plus I'm never playing Dead Rising 2 ever again so
it doesn't mean. Let's go. A lot of snacks. Who the? Gordon? Gordon what are you doing? What?
There's a guy just waiting for me. It's Gordon. I feel like I'm playing. Where did he just drop?
He's got money. All right can you save them? Kill 41 more zombies to unlock this challenge.
That seems like a lot. I'm immediately playing the original version despite you guys. Is that
what I said? This doesn't sound like me. I don't know. I feel like that doesn't sound like me.
Well there's a chain. Okay well let's take the chainsaw upstairs. Wait wait wait wait wait wait.
Let's do this right. No it's machete and push broom. Yeah and then let's do just give me the
chainsaw. I'm gonna go back up and use the chainsaw and get 40 kills. Right? I did a second vote but
I was already in the game and I already bought the damn thing. Damn it. Paddle and chainsaw?
Does that work? Let's wait till he gets up. Paddle and chainsaw. Did you say palette? Paddle. Where's
the paddle? Is there a paddle over here? It's paddle on the dumpster. Nice eyes. Nice eyes.
Seriously. I was away for a while to de-start over it. Yeah I got really really frustrated
and like I was punching my desk and stuff so I just figured I'd start over. Paddle saw.
Yeah I know what that does. Hell yeah. I was punching my desk and going
and fucking tears were just streaming down my face. Should I go back up and just get the 40 one?
I feel like I can get it easily. Okay it was like screaming and crying.
It was really really embarrassing and then you heard that.
40? Let's get it. How many are over here? Come on come on over there. 40. Gold status. I'll take it.
Why does this guy remind me of Adam Sandler? What are you talking about like 1995 Adam Sandler or
like 2008 Adam Sandler? Boomstick. Nice. All right cool let's keep going.
2019 Adam Sandler. I'm not sure I agree. Holy shit.
I want to do the other challenge. I don't want to use this yet. It's probably killed like 30
zombies in 20 seconds. Gain as much pp as you can in 60 seconds. It's about to break yeah.
People saying you gotta go back to the menu and start in the menu.
Thousand pp. I don't think that's gonna happen.
That counts? You get a big one. Will all these people count?
They're not very much. Go back to the challenge area.
All right I'm gonna start the game from the menu because everyone's telling me that I somehow did
this wrong. I have the costume now. Why do I have the costume? Sandbox mode.
You guys you guys thought I got baited? No I did too. I was waiting for it. No that's real.
Actually you have to start it from the menu. That's the reality. I might be able to do this
all right hold on. I wonder if I can do it because I'm leveled up. Level 33? Yeah let's try it.
Yeah that's much better. I might not get 40 but.
Oh my arms just fell backwards in my chair. Oh without the bat maybe I can't. Yeah I don't
think I can do it. Sledgehammer? I might be able to spin. What's the spin with a sledgehammer?
Maybe. Maybe. I'm not turning off my face cam. You want a face cam? No. Nope.
This is cool. All right I think. I think. I'm gonna. It's losing me a little.
I'm gonna go down. I'm gonna go down and see. It's losing me. I'm gonna go down here and see if I
see if it can grab me again. I have to get into where I was before. Let's see. I'm glad for the
better inventory. Yeah the next game we're playing is Katamari. That's the next up on the list.
Katamari tonight? Yes. We will at least start Katamari tonight and we'll keep going tomorrow.
Because I don't. I'm definitely. Oh there's Gordon. Remember Gordon?
That's good stuff.
Pig swing. Got you.
Don't let me do that. Okay 13 more. Let's see. Knife.
It's starting to lose me. It's losing me. All right 10 more minutes and we'll see where I am.
No let's see a paddle. Don't play this for 13 more hours. I don't even stream for 13 hours.
We won Katamari do you? Hold on. Just a minute. I want to try. This is actually really really
cool though. All right let's go. I beat the game. Got the true ending. Got to overtime. I looked at
Katamari. Dead Rising 2 off the record was awesome. I suggest you play it. Just trying to get too
frustrated. I have to switch over to this. This might take a minute. Beautiful Katamari for the
Xbox 3. That was a fast 10 minutes it was. I got grabbed though and I couldn't handle it anymore.
It's really easy if you're not an idiot. What is easy? Are you talking to me? Dead Rising 2.
This game's not easy. I'm sorry. I ain't gonna have somebody with like their fucking
Boy Scout badges. I beat Dead Rising 2. I get it now too. I get to wear that badge.
Add it to the gamer license. Yeah I get it. It's a it's point. No I don't want it. I don't want
points on my license. You didn't 100% it. All right. Okay. Sorry. I'll bring my badge back.
I'll put it on the table. I beat the DLC and not the main game badge which is harder than the
original game. Do I get it? Thank you. I beat the hard one. Did you beat the hard one? Not cannon
points. All right. Let's get let's get on. I could use a different controller.