Let's take a look inside. Oh, hello. Hello. Yeah, this is the pizza place. Pineapples.
Here's the soda. Okay, I grabbed the soda. Here's a salad. And where are the french fries?
Right here? Yeah. Yeah. Look at those very detailed Google image french fries. Where
did you get that from? Like, oh my, what the hell? Why is there a chainsaw? Hey, look,
I'm doing a wheelie. Yeah. Okay, yeah. I just got a lot of orders coming in, honey. I'm sorry.
I just got to get the cheese ready. Okay, I got to get the onions ready. I got to get pineapples.
I got to feed that pineapple to my grandmother. Oh, okay. I got to get a soti. I want to get a
soti. Mmm. Yeah, soti. You got to get- Ooh. Ooh. Oh, shit. This is- I got to deliver this to the docks.
come on pizza dude don't mess around guys taking a shit what the fuck that I
just even said I was about to say pizza dude don't take any short don't I don't
even know what I was gonna say but I want these two pizza coins what is even
going on stop falling off you stupid punk that's probably why because I keep
on doing that yeah we're oh it's got to go all the way over there all right step
on it step on the gas nice and easy nice and easy nice and easy here we are here
is your pizza what do you mean proceed by foot what the hell are you talking
about what what the who delivers a pizza to a boat and puts like oh I know how he
can fuck with this guy we're gonna put platforms of boxes that he has to jump
on what kind of a dickhead do you have to be tomato yeah you got it tomato we
get salad you want some pineapple there it is pineapple delicious fresh from the
garden would you also like some rotten fucking tomatoes all right this one 25
seconds go go go go go go not messing around on this one do not walk into any
walls right here good perfect speed it up don't run into anything all right here
we are I wish you could break that would be nice if you could get off get off for
three seconds get what oh yes I'd like some tomato some cheddar cheese a little
bit of your rotten peppers from your garden some pineapple isn't maybe a
little bit of the ham from the chainsaw that you got from Jason Jason too
actually yeah that's my favorite movie and also I would like some more of your
good I even say tomatoes yet I probably did I already forgot the joke out go go
turn around if I get star I did that already want to go on some stairs go
this one's going to like a gas station ten seconds slow it down slow it down
here slow it down here slow it down I did it I didn't do it I didn't do it I
didn't do it and why does the resolution keep changing it keeps going from 12
1920 by 1080 to 800 by 6600 I'm sorry guys I apologize this video the video
settings are all over the place like right now it's an 800 by 600 why and why
they fucking blow up dolls I would actually like to complete one of these
missions that would be nice that would be real nice if I could actually finish
one of these missions and not lose every time I don't even think the game's
completable get don't get the fuck out of the way car I cut pizzas to deliver
there we go I remember this one this is the one with like the stairs that you
can't go up no no this is the one back here back here I remember seven seconds
I got this done deal nice I actually completed one can you believe it what
this dog attacking me this dog looks like a fucking pig doesn't even look
like dog get out of here look I'm gone I left your territory is this like pig
goat thing gonna just keep following me down the street I'm trying to just go
back to the restaurant and you are just making things way too difficult for me
what the hell's going on what's happening okay this is normal yeah that
was totally normal and he's still chasing me I need some gas excuse me I'd
like some yes yeah I need some gasoline for my car