Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, we got a couple of things to discuss tonight.
Well, first of all, there's a new update. And the new update brought a new sniper item.
Kind of weird in my opinion. Why did they do this? Why not just release a bunch of stuff?
Why release one item? Just, oh, here's an item for the sniper, there you go.
I don't know, I don't really agree with the item release schedule.
But, regardless of all that, we did get a new item, the Cozy Camper.
And this is a backpack. This is not like a miscellaneous item, this is not like a hat or something.
This goes right on your back, where the razor back, where the Darwin's Danger Shield goes.
It's an unlockable, and it is craftable.
So the blueprint's gonna be on the screen right now. It actually doesn't take very much.
So you can probably craft this right now if you have the materials.
But anyways, no flinching when aiming, and knockback reduced by 20% when aiming.
So what this means is when you are zoomed in, you are not gonna take flinching fire damage.
Because all we all know, when you get lit on fire, I'll show you in a second here.
When you get lit on fire, that tick tick tick tick, it makes your mouse cursor move up and down really annoyingly.
And when you get hit by anything, if you get hit by a rocket, if you get hit by spam, you're not gonna move at all.
Which brings me to the bad part of this weapon.
60% slower movement speed when you're aiming.
So essentially when you have this thing zoomed in, you're a slug.
And you cannot move really at all, and it really, really, really is very annoying.
Especially, especially if there is another sniper on the enemy team.
Because when you're zoomed in with this thing, you almost stand completely still.
Any sniper that's paying attention will be able to kill you so easily with this on.
Not to mention spies. Oh my god.
You are just a spy magnet with this thing on.
Because it doesn't block anything. This does not block a backstab, this does not block anything.
It just gives you the ability to not flinch when you're taking damage.
Alright, so now that we got the bad out of the way, let's talk about the good.
So what this thing does, this allows you to be a more aggressive sniper.
You don't have to run away from fights anymore, you don't have to back up.
Oh he's getting too close, I gotta run away. You don't have to do that anymore.
Now you can just stand where you are and plant shots on people regardless of if they are shooting you or not.
Because back in the day, and when I say back in the day I mean yesterday before this update came out,
you had to be really, really conscious of who was shooting you.
Because obviously it screwed up your aim.
I can't tell you how many times I would be aiming as a sniper.
And I would lose my aim because a scout 500 feet away was shooting me with a pistol or something.
That is eliminated with this setup.
And I suggest you try, it doesn't take a whole lot to craft like I said, so give it a go.
So anyways, the next part of this video is going to talk about the Flogistinator.
And the nerf it just received.
And really, I don't agree with this nerf.
And it's not because I don't think this weapon needs to be changed, because it really does.
I just don't think you can slap minus 10% damage on something and go, okay that's fixed.
No, this thing needs to be totally redesigned.
I think if you remove the taunt invincibility and change the crit mechanic a little bit,
make it so it was 8 seconds rather than 12 or 10, because right now the nerf, I didn't even tell you the nerf,
the nerf is minus 10% damage and 10 seconds of crit rather than 12 seconds of crit.
Now that's great, but again, I said it's sort of a band-aid fix.
They need to redo this weapon, change it completely, give it a compression blast,
because I don't think the no compression blast works on any of the flamethrowers.
It didn't work out well on the back burner, and they got rid of it.
So we'll see what they do.
Hopefully they continue to tweak things, because they always do that anyway,
so I'm confident in their tweaking abilities.
So now before this video is over, I want to go over my TF2 modeling adventure I've kind of gone off on,
because I have got a couple of PMs.
People are wondering, Jerma, what's the story with your Steam Workshop stuff?
Are you still doing that?
The answer is yes I am.
I'm currently talking to a pretty talented guy.
He's a nice dude.
He already has a couple of things on the workshop already.
I'll get into that at a later date, because I don't want to give away any of the potential information that we're working on.
So yes, I have been in contact with a modeler, and I'll give you one hint.
I'm going to give you guys one hint on what we're working on.
It is not a weapon, and it is for the heavy.
So there you go.
Let the speculation run wild as to what I'm working on right now.
So this is going to be the end of the video, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it, and I will see you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.