Oh, all right. Hello. Fuck this dog hair all over my boomer vitamin. No, I just like touched him.
I just like petted him. I was like, okay, Otto, it's time to start the stream. Now I've got
fucking dog hair all over my boomer vitamins. Yeah, sorry I'm late today. I had some major p-
Okay, hold on a second. Let's take, hold on. Okay. I had some major PC fan issues that I
have since resolved. Let's hope my computer doesn't explode. That my case fans stop spinning.
All of them. The front ones. So I had to figure out why that was. So, you know, I'll take it apart,
plugged it back in, changed it, fucked with the power supply. Here's the TLDR for all of you.
There are one, two, three, four case fans in here. One of them is permanently just doesn't
work anymore. So I really hope that my 3090 is not going to burn out because one of the case fans
doesn't turn on. But we're good. I might turn the graphics down a little bit. You're lying.
I swear to God. I don't know. I have this, this is a 30, I'm on a 3090 right now. You can make fun
of me all you want. I got, this is a 3090. You'll see it. This, this is the first real stream that
you're going to see with the 3090. What game have I played in the last like three or four weeks that
required anything more than like a fucking 780? That hasn't happened. The invisible hand, that
did not require a 3090. That wasn't getting the full capabilities of the 3090. Anyways, today,
yes, we're going to play Resident Evil Village. I have no idea how long the stream is going to be.
I plan on going two days. I might just get obsessed with it and play a shitload of it tonight. I might
be like after four or five hours. You know what? Fuck this. I'll see you tomorrow. We'll see.
Even if I give myself an extra hour, it doesn't matter. I'm sitting there like taking my computer
apart going like, I got to be live in like fucking 45 minutes. Every second counts. I get pissed off
when I have to pee. You get pushed against the clock and like a 60 second piss infuriates you.
I'm just sitting there going like, hurry the fuck up.
Why? I drank too much water today. That's 60 seconds that I couldn't have been inside the
computer. You're a goof. No, I'm telling you. All right. Yes, we're doing face cam today.
I need, let me tweet this. I'll be right back. Give me a second. Wait, it's, it's not, it's not
village. It's V-I-L-L-A-G-E. I thought it was V-I-L-L-I-A-G-E. Like village. Like a village.
A village. It's village. I thought it was village. Like a welcome to the village.
I, I, I, well, you must think I've been really stupid over the years. I've never,
I've never done A. It's IA. Village. I don't know why I'm still holding these.
Okay. I'm holding these for some reason. I want to take these on stream and I think it's like funny
for some reason. Like, I don't know. Explain to me why I think this is funny. Oh, hold on.
Taking my turmeric. Wait, why is that funny? Well, taking, taking my, taking my like B vitamins.
Like why do I think they're taking like drugs? They're not even drugs. They're fucking natural
supplements. They're not essential oils. It's fucking supplements. It's turmeric. I'm taking it.
My pain shit. You know, I got to try something. What is this? Oh, yeah. Right. I forgot. Uh, uh,
yeah. This is a Fiji water. Hold on. There's not actually Fiji water in here. See, when I finish a
Fiji bottle, I just refill it with regular water. I still walk around and drink it. So people think
I'm fucking very high class. Fucking pro tip. There's actually just regular water in here.
That's illegal. Illegal. He's pissed. No, I just, I'm just having, I have very, very
negative energy right now. I'm trying to like expel it before we start playing the game.
Oh, by the way, if you thought those were supplements, you fucking have no idea.
It's seeing 40 minutes where I can't even fucking read writing. It's turmeric and B vitamins. Give
it a, give it a rest. All right. So this is going to be interesting. Hopefully these fans work.
You see how big my arms look today? All right. This is resonable village. Hold on.
Right. When the edibles kick in, he's getting zonked. No, those are not. Why would it be? I
told you it's turmeric. Hope you guys had a good week. I found the piss bottle. That's not pee
either. Why is my, what are you doing webcam? Don't do that. I was a good place for the webcam
right here. They don't get scared. Oh, and you're like, you don't think I have more than one beverage
at this table. I'm prepared. I always am. That's the thing about being a streamer. Somebody said,
oh, what's it like being a streamer? You have any advice? Yes. Have like literally every liquid
you want to consume and all the food you want to eat for the whole day on the desk when you start
the stream. That's all. That's the only advice I'm going to give you. Okay. Looks good. We're
going to start resonable village on the brand new 30 90 not doing it on hardcore. No thanks.
This can too big. You guys hear it. Village of shadows. Long ago, a young girl went with her
mother to pick berries for her father who was hard at work, but the forest greeted them with a dark,
cold silence. The bushes empty, yet determined to find the berries. The rascal broke free from
his grasp and vanished into the trees. Mothers worried cries faded fast as the girl ran on
over vine and under branch and into the forest deep feeling strange eyes upon her. The girl
recalled mother's scary bedtime tales and her throat became bone dry.
Then the bat Lord appeared. He greeted her warmly and bit his own wing. Come child quench you a
thirst he said. So she drank the thick dark blood and smiled with joy passing through the
graveyard menacing storm clouds loomed and the air turned cold shivering in her thin clothes.
Then a dark weaver appeared and with a click of his fingers,
three spells from Harry Potter. Beautiful dress. Come child warm yourself he coaxed. So she clothed
herself and smiled with joy across waters. The wrong game she went. No, it's not hoping a boat.
She found this wrong game. I'm losing my mind. Hungers grip tightened and her heart grew heavy.
Then the fish king appeared and offered one of his many fins. Come child. So the girl ate
and smiled with joy once more. Continuing on she soon entered the forest dark heart.
Then an iron steed appeared bearing a beautiful golden gear.
I just wanted to cut to something. He's like nose getting closed in a book and snatched
what she thought was another gift. And that's the end of the story. Like right here. The horse grew
angry and summoned the other monsters. Terror filled the girl's heart as the wild wind rose
around the beast. Suddenly a witch appeared. Dark yet regal. Oh come on. Oh I just the skin
came off my mouth. What was that? What's going on? Don't do it to the baby.
Babies can't even fucking understand English right now. She's asleep. You literally could
have just said banana, carrot, strawberry over and over again. She's only six months old.
Woman at the store said it was traditional. A local tale. Besides,
Rose doesn't seem to mind. I'm getting a little screen tearing. What's going on 3090?
Thank god we moved here so that you wouldn't have to deal with any of that. Remember?
You're getting screen tearing. I am. There's nothing wrong with my memory.
You're just being paranoid. It's not. I'm sorry. But I'm not paranoid. I'm just cautious.
Then go cautiously take your daughter to bed. I heard there's a lot of weird PC problems this
game. I don't. I don't. I hate this. I don't like this. If somebody wants me to hold their
baby I just I hate to decline but I do because I don't I feel like I'm gonna like break it.
I can't blame her. You know what I mean? It's like oh why don't you hold the baby?
Like did you say something? Nothing. No I don't think so. How do we hold it?
And they teach you oh what you do is you support the head and you put the neck up and you have to
make sure that it goes that way you know but rest the bum. It's like I don't I can I just
watch you do it? I don't want to fucking do it. All right yeah the graphics are fucking what's
going on here? I know look I know I'm not utilizing the extent of the 3090. I'm scared because one of
my fans doesn't work. So look look I got 23 gigabytes of available memory but I'm afraid
of the fucking overheating. So I turned it down a little. But I need to fix this. Why is it is it
v-sync? Can I make my frame rate the same with the refresh rate? Is that the problem? Or should
I just turn on v-sync? Why is it doing that? Yes yes but what if it makes the graphics card
go faster? Oh that didn't fix it. I'm still getting a bunch of screen tearing. How am I
getting screen tearing? I have to turn on v-sync. Doesn't v-sync like give you input lag though? I
feel like I'm gonna complain about that. Should I just do it? Well let's see. Yeah I got input lag
now. I'll see how I fare for a little while. Sink off. Fuck it up. Okay I'll be fine. Whatever.
All right let's go. All right so what do I have to do? Feed the baby? Oh this looks fucking beautiful
on a 3090 if I will say. Oh wait you guys can't even see that because I have to I forgot to do
that. So like on the next stream I'm gonna up the quality of the stream to like 900p. All right we've
got tomato uh bread. Do it now? I can't do it now. It's not gonna work. Does we just eat bread and
sauce? Wait what is that? Don't get too close to me when I'm cooking babe. Did you take this? Oh right
you've you've you've. Watch out for that splattering hot oil. Is it european diet? Bread,
sauce, and apples is european? What are you talking about? What's this? Oh baby food. Mia makes
everything by hand so this stuff keeps piling up. I have to change that one. I hate F as I can examine.
I'm gonna make it uh one of the mouse buttons maybe. Uh wait we'll see. Give me like 20 minutes
we'll see if I hit it. What's the sprint button? How's the audio for you guys? Is it good? All right
put the baby to bed. Wait is this um those of you that haven't seen Resident Evil 7 or haven't
played Resident Evil 7? I don't have no fucking idea why you're watching this without if you want
like this is I'm gonna talk about the 7th game. Is this the house? Is this the the original family's
house? They're there. It's like I said to your mom. That book's too scary for you. This is like the original
house. That's cool. No it's not. Sure? Turn. Your mom and I love this song so much. Hey two hands,
two hands man. It's like a bicycle. Oh my god that's the top of the cake from our wedding day.
I think I gotta turn the brightness down. Oh wait I have to kill these. Why do I even keep this
around? I should get rid of it someday. These interact with the monkey toy into the spoiler.
Gotta do a deep clean before Rose starts walking. Wait is this the baby's sleep? No. I'm not like
wait why are we this is like kind of bad. Why am I bringing the baby into like the weird dusty room?
Somebody else will read this. Somebody else will read this. I hate reading these. I know people
are gonna get so pissed about this but I fucking hate reading these. I just wish somebody would
just say it like uh Bioshock. And I mean like just let me just let me pick up a fucking tape
and just play it in my ear. Like even Diablo 3 got this right and that game was fucking dog shit.
Well for the first year or two. Everyone's forgotten about this already. You wouldn't
pay attention anyways. Well at least I mean I've fallen asleep listening to audiobooks and like
12 chapters go by and I wake up and I'm like a third of the way through the book. I'm just saying
well oh well. All right I have to play with the monkey toy. Wherever the monkey toy is. Almost
there honey. I'm gonna get screamed at right? I mean this is I can't do two headphones. No I
have to hear myself talk. That's a cool toy. All right wait wait play with the monkey toy.
Rose is closed for tomorrow. Can you guys hear me? I think we need to move mic. I don't see a monkey
toy. Play with the monkey toy? I don't see a monkey toy. Ah I see a monkey toy now. I thought a car
was gonna hit us. I thought a car was gonna crash into us. I was supposed to scream. I was like what
the fuck? That is here. Yeah yeah Rosemary Winters. Screenings, hearing, vision, and touch reflex
are all good. Patience good. You're on the second floor. I don't know we could have gone off a jump.
Mia and I had another fight. I accidentally mentioned what happened three years ago and
she blew up at me. We finally settle down in our new life in Europe and can bring Rose up properly.
But I still feel like a part of me is trapped in that hellhole back in Louisiana. So this is
talking about the seventh game. I know Mia doesn't like to talk about it but can we really just forget
everything and pretend it didn't happen? Should we face what happened there so we can live our lives
with Rose without it hanging over our heads? We owe her that much at least. I know Mia knows this.
She wouldn't have exploded like that at the hospital if she didn't care. All right let's
put this kid to bed. Can you keep your mother waiting? She's scary when she's angry. Oh yeah
didn't she like she like chainsawed my hand off. All right Rose time for bed. There you go sweetheart.
Don't you worry. I'll be right downstairs. Daddy won't let those weird fairy tale monsters get you.
We're gonna get Ghostbusters 2'd here. Anybody that saw Ghostbusters 2.
Like are we is that gonna happen? I feel like that's gonna happen. I feel like that was like
the guy like oh VEGAL. Like isn't he gonna come and like steal a baby? If you haven't seen Ghostbusters
2 then what's wrong with you? People in chat aren't old enough for that. I would rather you
watch Ghostbusters 2 three times in a row than watch this stream right now. Watch out this.
I'm not gonna say that because that's an actual spoiler. I just went like I just made like a voice.
All right it's time for dinner. Is she okay? Sleeping like uh is that Mia? Like a baby. That
smells good. What's that? Oh hands off mister. It's churba de lagoon. It's a local recipe. Wish you
went like wow you've gone full native haven't you? Like my health bar went down a little.
But if you're gonna keep sulking all evening maybe you shouldn't have any.
What we got here? You really have to stop worrying.
I almost missed. Finding you in Louisiana. The pregnancy. Chris moving us here.
Military training. It all happened so fast you know. Well at least we're all together.
No the baby's gonna get VEGO'd. Everything's gonna be- Seriously think we can just forget
about what happened in Louisiana? It happened so long ago. I just I don't understand why you are so-
I've told you. Wait what happened? Did you snipe him?
What the fuck? Wait what? Why is it- Who's doing this? Why would you do this?
That was at every angle. It's-
What the hell? Sorry Ethan. No! No you're supposed to be Wesker! Why?
Go on move. All clear. What the hell you doing with my daughter? Package secured sir. Package
secured? Take him away. I said get your hands off her! Ethan no. Kills people by the way. I
never understood why people continue to do that in tv shows. I would be instantly dead if you did
that to my right into the middle of my head. What is photo mode? Did I have like paused it
at some point? Well whatever. Who's calling? Hey doc. No problem we'll be there. How's the doc?
She'll see us next week. Hey now think positively all right? We talked about this. I know.
We hardly talk about anything else. I keep telling you it's not Rose that I'm worried about. Well
then what are you worried about? Look she's gonna be fine. I just know it. What else matters?
We matter Ethan. You matter. You just- Nia what are you talking about?
Is there something you're not telling me? Come on talk to me. Damn it. Work. I have to take this.
Shit work is calling. Look at how the fucking 3090 really makes that look real.
But what happened now? Did we get in a car accident? Why did this happen?
Oh it's work. Shit I gotta take this. What are you talking about? Where's Chris Redfield and Rose?
Somebody just like fucking strangled that guy from behind like squished his windpipe.
Oh no that was where the edibles kicked in. What are you doing here? This is a secure oh boy.
Eliminate target. Recover body. Secure Rosemary Winters and Ethan Winters. Move the two
Winterses. Move the two Winterses to site C for further investigation. At least two
transport officers doing good. Why do they have to kill the girl? Any guns back here?
I don't think so. All right let's go. Is this 90 FOV? All right. All right fine. I'll put them both in.
Do I have like light up shoes? Work is calling. Turn the light off. This is why I didn't want
to start till later in the afternoon because it's fucking it's three o'clock in the afternoon in Las
Vegas. I this is just sunny out right now. I'm telling you this is why I wanted to start later.
But that's not why I actually started later. I actually started later because my fans didn't
work. What was the windows? The windows are closed. I don't have like blackout curtains in my house.
Oh that's you're gonna have to get a you're gonna have to get a shot for that one. Where the hell am
I going? Oh shit. Birds. A lot of dead birds everywhere. They're being hung up everywhere.
Turn the light off. I can't turn the fucking light off. All right somebody tell me is this 90 FOV
before I like immerse myself in this game or do I have to do something? Is it? Okay do your best.
No there's not a good fix for it. What? You need a mod. What the fuck are you talking about? What?
It's 80. It's locked at 80. You have to hack the game. What the fuck are you talking about?
That's not that can't be real. How is that? How can there not be 90 FOV in a 1920 by 1080 game?
Like the ability to have it without it being a that doesn't make any sense.
Mod manager and FOV trainer. Don't restart that. I thought that was said resume.
I would have. Fuck Capcom. Fuck you Capcom. Capcom sucks. That would I just ruined my game
experience. That would have like scared me and I would have been like holy shit that was so scary.
Are you fucking kidding me? You've already ruined my game experience because it's like wow the FOV
looks weird. We have to hack my video game to do something that should have uh that's been a normal
thing since like 2012. How does it even happen? How does this even happen? Is how does this happen?
Is everybody asleep? Meltdown percent. That would have been like a good scare too.
I'm fucking just almost came out of my nose. The first thing if you're gonna have a game go on PC
I'm sorry. I have no fucking I have absolutely no sympathy for any of this shit. If a game is
gonna release on PC and it's after 2008 if you if it's not 90 FOV just throw the whole thing the
garbage and start over. Like it should not even release. I can't even fucking believe it. Like
it's so simple. If they just release this for console and just copy and paste the fucking code
over here. Nobody cares about fucking PC gaming. Everyone thought this was gonna people people
thought like five years ago man PC gaming people gonna start to care way more about this. Well
companies are starting to take PC gaming way more seriously. No if they won't give a fuck about this.
Baby rage. It's true though what the fuck. It's available in photo mode. I can't believe you have
to hack your fucking game to do something that should be here from like 10 years ago.
You're whining now. Yeah I am. It's really fucking annoying. Oh is this the big lady?
It's already 90 FOV. It'd be so funny if it actually was. I hope it is so that I seem like
a fucking psycho. I really don't think it is though. Is there anything else I can do in here?
Can I pick this up? Under the bed? Books? Oh fuck okay over here. I can't see anything though.
Oh don't make me go into the basement. I thought that was a sausage. It's a banana.
Oh wait I wasn't done. It's pretty creepy. What's that? There's something in there. All right I'm
ready. I'm ready. Here comes one two three. It's gonna jump out. It's gonna be behind me. I grab
the broom and just turn around. I thought right now I grab this broom and I turn around. I just
start swinging as hard as I can. If any like horror games and horror movies have taught me anything
it's that just grab this and just just turn and swing as hard as you fucking can in a circle.
Damn it there's nothing here. Okay I knew it. Is that the rat? Is the rat doing that?
Hey! Hey! Hey! What's in all this? All right give me a weapon. I need a weapon. I need a chair. I
need a stick. I need a like a rake or something. Give me a rake. There's gotta be something right?
Rake? Run? Or a gun? Yeah I mean I was I'll take a gun but I'll take something just a rake or
something just to start. Where the hell am I? Wow this looks really cool. All right I did I may
have said fuck Capcom earlier. I want to just correct that. Fuck Capcom for this particular
instance. I love Resident Evil 2. It's like one of my favorite games the last five years.
I need to like get my emotions under control. I really am like Donald Duck.
I connect so strongly with him. I don't know I just like I get so just so frustrated. Oh look at
that poor miserable duck. I can't stand! He starts eating plates and shit. Okay there's like a stable.
Is this is this the big lady? Is this the introduction to the big lady? Even like a
is a big lady a bad character? Is it like a quest giver? Let's need some okay I need something to
to pull the well up. I got in here. Oh so there's some manure. I need a pulley to pull the well up.
Erin Erin. All right pull. I'm looking for like something to put maybe back here. Okay um
over here. Is that a horse? Is that a horse statue or is that a dead horse?
I kind of it's hard to tell. I think that's a statue of a horse.
I'll be sleeping in that bed. Maybe maybe they're out. An easy to pick lock. All right well let's
go. Let me do it. Is this tuber commentary? Oh what? Because I'm like wait somebody's still
making food here. I'll be sleeping in that bed. Oh it's that thing again. All right nothing in
here. Tuber reactions. Tuber gameplay. Why can I pick it? Do I need a lock pick? I don't have
anything. Oh no. Oh shit. Tuber. You're talking like a tuber. Hey this is just my normal speaking
voice man. What are you talking about? Is it because I'm playing a game that came out like a
week ago? Is that why everybody's saying this? I mean it looks great. It really does. Capcom.
App. Just out doing yourselves. Art direction. Phenomenal. Graphics. Unbelievable.
How did he just crashed it? Pick up that fucking rake. Pick something. Pick up a weapon man.
One of these rocks will do. Fuck Capcom. I didn't play the game for five minutes and I already just
said that. Don't worry I'll patch it in in three months. Locked due to missing homeowner. It's
locked. It's got one of those things on it okay. I believe this is where we need to go. Ah there's
a knife. Okay finally a weapon. Knife. Attack. Is it like a block? What am I hitting? Am I stabbing
myself in the stomach? They don't you don't get a knife and then not fight something. Nothing okay.
Here we go. Friendly. Friendly. How did he miss? Who are you? Who sent you? How did you miss? There
was an accident down the road. He shot me in point blank and missed. He looks like Ernest. One second.
Who is? What the hell was that? Do you have a gun? What? Please tell me you have a gun.
No why would I? Well give me yours. You can't seem to aim with it. Take it. Take it. Dude you
stopped shooting the gun. Are you listening? Stop shooting your weapon. You have no idea
what you're doing. This guy sucks. This guy sucks. Oh my god that guy was awful. Can I get his gun?
Shit. Dead body. He did his best. Wait there's more. Okay I kind of I want to toggle. I want to
toggle. I want to toggle for controls please. There you go. There you go. There you go. There you go.
Uh I want toggle. Is there a why would there be a toggle for like aim downsides right? It has to be
though right? Zoom in and out. Aim. No there's no. Why would there be a toggle? Of course there's
not. Why would there be a toggle? I like toggle. It's easier to do. Easier to use. Because then
you don't have to like depress down my middle finger. I know people think it's bad but whatever.
I like it. What the hell is wrong with this place? There's somebody there. Holy shit.
Shit. This guy keeps losing his hand. What the fuck was that? All right let's shoot him.
Shoot him. Space is guard? What? I could have just shot him to hit free time. These guys take a lot
of shots. Oh my god these are all headshots. Like every single one of those is a headshot. Every
single one. Holy shit that's a lot of time to shoot. What the hell? All right so don't use weapons
that often. Okay one is. Okay two. Do I have a flashlight? No why would I have a flashlight?
What am I talking about? Chem fluid. Okay view materials that can be crafted. Okay so first aid
is chem fluid and herb. It looks like they got rid of anything besides green. Like just green herbs.
See items. Family photo. Treasure. Okay let's go. Everything gives you ammo. There it is. All right
so herb. I don't think this looks like this. Just all right. Craft first aid. Excuse me. Get
out of the way. First aid. Okay do it. I made a first aid kit. Okay that. Do I have it? One and
collect the item to craft. Did I already do it? Okay am I losing my mind here? I've already made
it. Well it wasn't really. It wasn't like a good indicator. I don't need to use it. Not pretending.
Well I just. I didn't see. I don't have key to open this. This needs some kind of key.
He sucks. I don't. Does this guy have anything on him? Wait can I shoot this lock? Is it even the lock?
No. There's gonna be another one of those guys. All right bolt cutters. Here we go. Yeah let's go.
Don't let them bully you. Nobody's bullying me. I just played. Nobody's bullying me. I just played
this game six days late. You already know where the bolt cutters are. I don't. Cool. I gotta. Okay
is ammo really a problem in this game like it is in every single one of these games?
Yes. Oh god. Somebody gonna run down the stairs. Handgun ammo. Open inventory. Okay. Yes. I was
just discarded. Okay. It just. You have a huge inventory in this game. That's good.
What? Okay. Okay do it. Do it. Do it. Do it. Please. Hey. He gets just a scare. He can't get in here.
Can I just get. I got chemicals. Hey. We can get in. He can get in. Did he get in? Can he get in here?
Can he get in? Hey. Oh fuck. Hey. What do I do? What am I supposed to do? What am I supposed to do?
Go out here? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? Ah. Can I jump?
Or do I get him off? Fuck. I'm gonna die. What the hell? Why did I try to put three in there?
Is it over? He's taking three clips. Like oh shit. Which one?
Oh for the legs. Not for the head. God damn it. I didn't mean to do that. My
my mouse is really sensitive. Big lady. Survivors. It's the big lady. Go to the house near the field.
Okay. Those aren't any kind of standard zombie. Those things. Usually. Okay. Every Resident Evil
game has done this before. The first enemy you face is just a standard zombie. These guys are
very very quick. Okay. Go to the big field. Where should I go over? Oh my god. Okay.
I don't think this is the right way. I wish I had a flashlight so I could see anything.
First enemy in Resident Evil 7 is your wife. Yeah but it's really it's pretty scripted.
I can't break this. I don't even. Wait. Hold on. I gotta I gotta make another uh how many items do I
have? Got it. You missed the shotgun. Stop stop stop. This part sucks. What? What do you mean
missed? Go to the old house. What are you talking about? What? Use the map. I didn't even know I
had a map. Why would I have a map of this place? I just got like dumped here. You missed the
shotgun. Go back. Did I really miss the shotgun? Why would they give you? No. I don't I don't
actually don't believe you guys. Why would you get a shotgun this early? I can't even leave.
I'm stuck here. I can only go one way. Don't help him. I don't I really don't think there's
a shotgun. I think you're full of shit. Oh my god. I mean run. What? Oh my god. What did I do?
What did I do? What happened to me? Damn it. What did I do that for? I gotta run.
Ammo ammo ammo ammo. All right. Up up up up up. Survive the attack. Shotgun. Shotgun. Okay.
What is that? Gunpowder. What's in here? Shotgun. What's in there? Shotgun bullets.
Kick that down. Wait. What's that? What's that? Who is it? Gunpowder. Examine. It's full of flower.
Oh I can blow up. Why why do they think I can blow up the flower by shooting it?
Can I go down? There's no end to them. Why do you what? What's that? Rusted scrap. I don't want to
miss any items. I don't know. Wait. I need to look at the map. Straight up here. Scrap metals for hats.
Oh. Let me in. Let me in. Let me in. Let me in.
I want whatever fell on the ground. I want. I want what fell on the ground. I want what fell.
Close the door. That's. That is explosive flower. I want to shoot it. Oh my god. What the fuck is
happening? Where am I supposed to go? Survive? What? Where? They're shooting arrows at me. What
the fuck is this? Legolas bullshit. What is happening to this? Who's firing arrows?
What the fuck is this? Oh my god. How am I getting up here? Oh my god. Get back down.
Oh my god. It's a huge guy. What's this? Oh my god. What's this? Money? How do I?
Am I safe in here? I think I'm safe in here. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
Jump from roof to roof? Get out of my way. Get. Fuck. Who am I? I guess we're going this way.
Oh my god. Am I dead? White blockers from Game of Thrones. I want to zoom in. It's a perfect
picture. All right. Go in. How do I zoom in? Adjust the scope of the camera. Area of view. I
can't do anything with this. No depth of field. Here we go. Okay. Okay. Filters. Oh my god. I'm
going to get an Instagram filter. Okay. Lens distortion. No, none of that. Frames and logos.
Game. I don't know. Other. Grid. Off. Okay. Now what? Did I get it? Did I take the picture?
I guess I took it. At a heart. That's so stupid. Imagine this is what they were using as their
like PR shit. Frame type. That's perfect. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I like this one. It's a book
cover. It kind of is a book cover, isn't it? It really is a book cover. I can't change any
of this stuff though. All right. So I got it, right? Nice lock screen. So how do I take the
picture? I got it, right? I got it. I think I hit, I pressed F. Yeah, I got it. No, I, okay. No,
no, no. Now that I know that exists, I'm going to abuse it. All right. This is way too loud,
by the way. I have to turn it down. This is Mario Odyssey's camera, but worse. Is this a sleigh?
Why? Oh, why? It was a sleigh. I'm trying to kill that motherfucker.
Monster. Oh, I can't open this. It has one of those things. All right. I got to remember these
because this is important. The keys. I'm going to have to open them later. Backtracking Barry.
I'm not coming over there yet. Let me make sure. Let me like loot the place.
You're going to be sitting there for a few minutes, lady, because there was a bunch of
shit that I didn't get. I can just go get it now. And without all the chaos that was ridiculous,
that was absolute chaos. Did I miss anything? All right. Let me check. You're a loot goblin.
Well, look, I mean, it's important. I want to make sure I have like items and shit.
That doesn't waste the clip, right? Because I know that happens in some games.
Anything else I'm missing? All right. Yeah. Flower. Like, what's this for?
All right. So what it was, I don't know why, what that was for. That doesn't do anything.
The map would literally tell you if you finished an area. Oh, sir. Okay. Search completed. I get it.
All right. Well, that's new. That didn't happen before. Yes, it did. That was in all the Resident
Evil games. All right, we go back to the Jingle Bell lady. That's the big lady. Um, no, it's not.
Big lady goes like this. Hello. You shouldn't be out here. It's not safe. Hey, can you hear me?
It's you, the child's father. Hey, wait, do you mean Rose? She is in great danger.
No, since mother Miranda brought her to the village, we have fought this.
I'm trying to get like, uh, the monsters. I want to get her going like this
and then put make like a YouTuber thumbnail. Harold's danger.
I mean, I could have clearly just pointed the gun at this lady and been like,
tell me what's going, tell me what you know. Like I'm like, I have a gun and like,
you're like this weird witch person. Like I will shoot you. Just tell me what,
tell me what's going on. I have weapons. Like, where the fuck am I? You're a psycho.
I'm assigned to psycho. I just got literally attacked by all these people that were just
trying to kill me and bite my hand off and shit. This is not a regular place.
This is like, shit's going down here. People are killing you and eating you.
What the fuck? I thought I just grabbed it. It's Q. May they come to eat our flesh. May
they come to tear us apart. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to read that. And then what?
I'm not supposed to like carry my gun. A guy with a sledgehammer just jumped from a ceiling,
like 40 foot story and was swinging it at me and easy to pick locks. Shit. I want to get in there.
I don't know what made me just think about this. I'm just going to say it because I don't know why
I'm thinking it, but I've just, I was thinking it for some reason right now. Chewing gum is really
gross. Chewing gum. I hate the most. I don't know why that was. I don't know what that's from.
It's from Billy Wonka. It's still somehow it's cause I don't know why I had to say that,
but I just did. Why V? It's M. Look for Rose. Okay. Sure. We will. I move around. All right.
This is where I am. So this door is locked. I didn't search this whole place, but let's just
keep going. The vitamin B just kicked in. Oh, wait. No. Damn it. Okay. Well, there's two of those.
You never know what could be under the car. You're high on turmeric. Let's check and open
this door. Can I even go in here? No. You have a front door. What about this thing?
Ever? Okay. I just want to make sure I don't miss anything. I'm trying to complete the game.
Castle Dimetri Sioux. Well, that's where the big lady is. I know that's what the character's name
is. Talk from the other side. All right. All right. Let's just go. Let's just go get the
introduction. We're going to get like a, like an interesting, like violin, like piano mix.
She's going to waltz in like, Oh, hello. It's going to be like,
it's going to be like a violin and shit. It's going to be cool. I can't wait.
Oh, darling. I bet she says darling at least two or three times. I guess this leads to the castle.
All right. I need to find that thing and that thing. There's two circle depressions there.
Let's check out in here. What is that? Ooh, there's one of them. Ooh, what the hell? Oh,
type right up. Good thing my game didn't like crash. Something's still in here. What is still
in here? Ooh, disaster fall upon the village. Seek out the crests. One is in the care of the
church. The other is at Louisa's house. Okay. Louisa's house. Got it. So Louisa's house is
down here at Louisa's house. Which one of these is Louisa's house? Probably this one or probably
that one. This one or here. So we need to go that way. Go back. It's not fully explored.
Shit. What did I miss? How's this not fully explored? Look up. Crystal fragment. Treasure.
Whoa. I got a treasure. White mineral found in this region could probably sell it. Valuable.
Oh, shit. That's cool. Now. Ah, all right. Good. Good. I'm making money.
Fuck you, chat. What? Look at the map. Yeah, I know. Find a way to open the castle gate. Yeah.
So I have to go to this place. This place has keys and shit. All right. Let me go over there.
Making money. What? Explore everything. I don't want to miss anything, guys.
Another one of these wells that I can't use. Stop helping him. I want him to lose. See how
many headshots I got in a row. And by the way, that first part I've heard was very difficult.
I did it. I only had to use one healing potion. Okay. How many bullets in the shotgun? No, I don't.
All right. I got to be smart about this. Oh my God. They're running through. What is this?
What is this? Corn or wheat? What is this? Oh, God. He's right there. Um, can I jump over this?
All right. Just a, it's like blinding. I think the flower blinds them.
If I would take a wild guess. Here we go. All right. Reload this shit right now.
Well, how many arms do I have? Perhaps some ammo. Ammo. Gunpowder and rusted scrap.
Did I have wasted that? Did I waste it? Shit. Well, whatever. I'm going. Can't jump over this?
How do you not jump over that? I don't, how are you that can't jump over that? Okay. Here we go.
Ouch. My foot. Oh, I hate when they do that move. I step on his head. Yeah. I'm getting too close.
You think so? Ammo. Make it good. So much ammo. Just use the one. Okay. I want to go this way.
He thinks he's playing resident evil four. Do I? I got two heels. Oh, I'm not going to heal.
Why would I heal right now? I feel like there's something in the middle of that field.
Yeah. He's eating something. What is he eating? Should I just kill him? Will he notice me if I
don't do anything weird? Who the fuck is this? What? What? It's okay. I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm just glad to see normal people at last. Have you seen any other survivors?
They're all in Louisa's house and she's not answering and the gate is locked.
Quiet. He's an outsider. Oh shit. We're sitting ducks in here. Can your old man walk?
No, one of the monsters cut him. He's lost a lot of blood. We have to get into Louisa's house.
Quiet. Fucking alone. We're going to kill us. Let's be away inside.
When the outsider is sus. Be quiet. Don't move until I get those gates open.
My eyes just rolled back in my head and I think it caused permanent damage to them.
Can I have that? I'll trade you a knife for that. Okay. They're all in their own Louisa's house.
It's down here. I don't know. Good ammo. I need it. What is that? Well, gunpowder. Nice. All right.
On the roof. Take on the roof. When are we going to see the big sus lady? I don't know.
Oh, this is Louisa's house. Let's go. And no. Out of one of the crests is in there.
I could probably open it. What? I could probably open it by removing a screw.
Okay. I need like, I need a screwdriver. There's definitely a screwdriver in this house.
By the way, how does it look with the 3090? Did you get those two inside?
Looks like shit. Looks like total dog shit. Come on. It's clear.
Hurry. Took your damn time. You're welcome.
You have an RTX on? No, because I'm afraid of overheating it.
Because one of my fans in the front of the case doesn't work. We'll be safe in here. Won't we?
Safer here than out there. That's for sure. Hey, do you know anything about what's going on around
here? It doesn't make any sense. Mother Miranda has always protected us. Nobody's answer.
Father, we have to get inside. Audio cut off. Just hold on a bit longer, Papa.
The audio. All right, we have to get inside. Hello? Anybody home? Maybe a familiar voice.
Louisa, open up. It's me, Elena. Stop shouting. You'll draw the monsters.
I thought it was the same guy. Who's this? A friend. Stay back.
I thought it was the shotgun guy. No, they'll smell the blood. You'll endanger us all.
And no sudden movements. I learned how to aim from my father. Hold Ernest.
I would just run at him if I heard that. Go on. Go inside. Come now. This way. You're not from this
village. No, I'm Ethan. Julian, go make yourself useful and check the grounds. I said go. If Elena
trusts you, then so do I. Come inside, Ethan. Where's the huge lady? I'll check on the others.
They're gonna eat me. They're broken again. Got more of the livestock. I don't think we'll make
it through winter at this rate. Ernest is still... You guys know Ernest? Ernest is still missing too.
We can't find him anywhere. Has Mother Miranda abandoned us? Are you kidding me? Okay, whatever.
Did it tell me that before and I just... No, I don't think so.
Rotate your saves. Yeah, I will. Hold on. Let me look at this. Can I get a closer look? Oh,
whatever. These nice photos. Whatever. I don't care. Right this way. Who are the presidents?
Two presidents on the wall. Come inside. The others are waiting.
Outsiders, you're gonna get us all killed. He helped Leonardo and Elena.
We ourselves? Please, Ethan. Take a seat. Emergency meeting. Right in the front of that table.
I don't like that guy. In your entire village? All that's... There is no one. A worthless
invalid. A stupid, wailing bitch. And you! You drag a bloody man and an outsider in here like
it's nothing? I don't know. And expect to be all safe? They're all like around a table. There is no
safe. Sorry bastard out there has been ripped in half. Just like her damn husband.
Put a sock in it, Roxana. That's enough. This house has protected my family for generations.
And drunk or not, you are all welcome and safe in here. Whatever. Can someone please tell me
what the hell is going on here? We don't know. One day we were a quiet, devout village and the next
the monsters came and attacked us. And they kept coming. Wait, Louisa. Where is your husband?
Did they? No. No, he is out there. Somewhere. He went to get help. Yes, yes, that's...
I feel like this is an elaborate escape room that I like paid a bunch of money to do.
Let us pray. For him. For all of us. Good idea. Like, oh! I was gonna start clicking the lights.
Hear our voice, together as one in reverence. We call on thee, within the endless dark,
to deliver us into fate's hands. As the midnight moon rises on black wings,
so we make our sacrifice. Or stand up. In life and in death, we give you glory,
Mother Miranda. Now, the tea should be ready. The alien's gonna come out of that guy. Come help me,
Elena, please. This guy's gonna... He's gonna punch her inside of his chest. I've heard it before.
There was an old woman near the graveyard. Crazy as a bag of rice. There is wisdom
in her devotion, though. And I hope it protected her, as it shall protect us.
Sorry. I thought... I thought the fucking monster was gonna come out of him.
So I was trying to time the photo. I'm sorry. Whatever.
I got it! How do I move the camera? This guy's face over here. Filters. Oh, wow, that's scary.
I don't like any of these. Yellow? This looks like a loading screen for this game. Turn the grid off.
Okay. All right, that looks good. Why can I not change the camera shit? Adjust the scope of the
camera. What's going on here? And now, control, hide HUD. F. Photo. It's because it's a cut scene.
Oh, okay. All right, cool. F. Got it. When I hit escape, is this just gonna...
I gotta be ready for this. I missed that second one. It's why I blocked! I hit the block button!
All right, I have to stop doing this. Why did you tell me I could do this? I know. I'm done.
I'm not doing it anymore. No more. I'm done. I'm not doing this ever again. I promise I'm not
gonna do it again. Ever again. I swear to God. I promise. I'm not gonna do it again. I'm done.
It's over. Don't even do it. I wanted the shotgun to shoot him in the face. Yeah, I didn't do it. See?
I'm so sorry, father. Hey, hey, that wasn't your father anymore. You did the right thing.
Was he infected? I don't get it. There's nothing you can do. This entire place is collapsing.
We couldn't save him. He was already gone. Leave me alone. No, we're getting out of here together.
We gotta get out of here. Escape. All right, this is where the escape room happens.
Oh my God. This is so scary. Whoa, what's that? Hey, hey, there's a five? There's a five written
on the ceiling. Write that down. Under the car. I got a seven over here on the tire.
Maybe there's a padlock. Oh, wait, this is the house that was from the beginning of the game.
Whoa, that's a lot of money. I'll take 500 bucks. Why not? Take the screwdriver out of the key ring
if you need it. I'm really, you know, this company, this escape room company, they leave
little helpful, helpful clues. Truck key. Examine items. I examine. What is that? Damn it. I was so
hoping like a four was going to be written on this key for some reason. Oh well. Okay,
I got the screwdriver. What else we got here? Shotgun ammo. Let me make sure it's loaded.
One, two. Good. This has been explored. Let's check this side. Cool. Oh, I'm not going up
there yet. I think there's something in here. Yeah, there's something in here.
Something. There's a fire in here, but wait a minute. What about here? Come on. There's
gotta be like one of those shining things, right? A jewel? What the fuck? It's like that's a jewel
right there, isn't it? Isn't that a jewel? Shit. Where is this? There's something in here.
Oh, here we go. If we could just get through this wall. No, no, I can't. Whatever. If I,
if I, if I can't, whatever. Audit plant. Nice. Oh shit. We're like fucking dying.
All right. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. All right. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Go. Go get in. Get in the car. Stop reading chat. No. Hit the gas. Well,
that didn't work. Are we driving up the stairs? Did I think this was a Bugs Bunny cartoon? What
the fuck am I doing? Wait, what? The car? Oh, grab on. Hurry. You know, the craziest thing
probably could have used this car or something. Let's move and try not to breathe in the smoke.
I know. Thank you. All right. Move. I do too. Move. Move. Help me move this. Maybe you'll get to
meet them. This guy's fucking clumped. He's like Mr. Magoo.
Window.
Don't press P. I was hoping he was going to do the thing with like the stunt man. Wait.
Don't hit P. Don't hit P. I'm going to hit P. I'm going to hit P. I'm going to
rip P off the keyboard. I'm going to rip P off. I'm going to rip P off the keyboard, I think.
I won't stop. I have to take P off the keyboard, I think. I'm so annoyed with myself that I'm
doing that. No more. Don't do that shit anymore. It's not fucking funny. Don't do it anymore. You
don't fucking do that anymore, right? All right. All right. Don't fucking do it anymore. I just
don't get it. Let's go. Jump. This place is going mad. Why the fuck is this happening again?
Oh, what the fuck? Shit. That would have been awesome if that like cratered with his fist and
like the wood bent and broke and made like an explosion sound. He figured out that he had like
fucking powers. Capcom, what have you done? Hey. All right. I got to get the thing out of here.
Use the screwdriver. I'm really low on health. I need a save point too. This is not,
this is kind of getting ugly. Okay. Let's go in the castle. I used to just get this. When I
used to play like PUBG on my mobile device, you would hear that and you'd just be like,
where is this guy? He's fucking like 500 miles away. And I would stand still and he would still
miss. And that's how I knew if he was shooting at me, right? I didn't even care if I lost or died.
If I was standing still and I didn't get hit, then he was aiming at somebody else
and he doesn't even potentially even see me.
Who's there? What was that?
Chills. Anything else I missed? I have explored pretty much everything.
Although the plot. No, that, okay. I thought that was telling me like to go this way because the
plot is that way to like keep the story going. These guys are all dead, right? I need a typewriter.
Dad has visited them all.
This is just a MOBA character select screen. That's the one line and then she's sitting there
doing her little animation. And like the fucking stadium is screaming because they can't believe
that. Like, wow. What a counterpick. This is a low tier character. I'm getting too out of control
here. Oh, that's wrong. Wait, where is this? Oh, out here. Yeah. Death. Death.
Hey, get in there. Seth, behind you. Oh, it's Otto. What's the matter? Do you need something, Otto?
What is it? You see his tail? What is it? What is it? Hey, come over here. They can't see you.
Hold on. Let me just make sure I have pants on. Come here.
I can see you on cam. And when he's running out, he was like, fuck Capcom. I was like, wow,
holy shit, dude. What happened? Why did he even say that? What was that for? It was kind of rude.
It's like they make good games and shit. All right. Let me in. Here we go. We're going to meet
lady of the castle. Can't wait for the nothing but blood and death. And she's probably going to go
like this and like cool herself off of it. Right. It's just cord. It's cords going. Is that
electricity? Am I going to get zapped? Come on. There's something under here. Right. Why would
they have this? Are we for later? I hear something in the water. What's in the water? I just heard
that. What is that for? A rope? It was you. I didn't sound like me. Whoa. You guys can't see
how much ammo I have. Right. I wish I should. Does it matter? Lower left is now you can actually see
how much ammo I have. Save the game. I mean, I'm I doesn't know where I can save right now.
In the middle looks weird. Top right. I don't like top right. Flipped it. Yeah. Well, because now
if I'm looking at that way, that would be weird. I don't want to be looking this way because I need
to be looking at the game. Does it look weird? Turn it back, please. I think this is all right.
Wait, that does look kind of weird, doesn't it? Top right doesn't feel right to me, though.
It always feels weird. Right now. I hate that. I actually I actually hate that. I could go like
here. Where's the where's it come up? That's fine. I'm not I don't hate that. Right. That's OK.
There's nothing wrong with that. But that kind of then you don't get to see like kind of this side
of the screen, though, whatever. Well, you think anyone was left must be pretty tough.
Who the fuck are you? Oh, you're not local. Better.
Mother Miranda is going to love you guys. It sounds like Elvis.
Oh, Mother Miranda is going to love you when you're whining. We're almost there.
Where? Oh, what have you brought me? He's going to walk in. Oh, what have you brought me, darling?
It's to anyone else. My daughter's and I. Shut the fuck up. Where? You mean you'll screw around
with it in private. Where's the fun in that? Give it to me and I'll put on a show that everybody
can enjoy. Oh, so gauche. What do we care for bread and circuses? The man thinks suffering is a
gag. The man's dick is cut off in the castle. Blah, blah, blah.
Fuck is going on. I've heard all your arguments. Some of you were less persuasive than others,
but I've made my decision. Heisenberg, the man's fate is in your hands. Mother Miranda, I must
protest. Heisenberg is but a child and his devotion to you is questionable. Give the mortal to me and
I will ensure he is ready. Shut your damn mouth and don't be a sore loser. You'll find your food
somewhere else. Quiet now, child. What are the Avengers? They're like the evil Avengers.
You're the one who's arguing with Miranda's decision. You wouldn't know responsibility
if it was welded to them. Oh, keep growling. One day your head might actually fit your ego.
Fight, fight, fight. Hey, don't I get a say in this? Silence. My decision is final.
Remember from whence you came. Lichens and gentlemen,
we thank you for winning. And now let the games begin. Let's see what you have here, Ethan. Get
ready. Get ready. You missed. Nine, eight, seven. I didn't get any water. I just needed water.
One sip of water. All right.
This is a game. It's a game to them. It's a game. Whoa. It's a fucking game.
Why do I keep duck? Oh shit. I didn't duck. It's a game show. No, no, no, no, no. Joel already made
that joke. Fuck. I should have played this a week ago. What do I do? What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? Who says? Who said that? Open. Open. Break it.
Break it. What happened? What just happened? What?
I was trying to break the box. I couldn't break it. Break. Break. No, wrong way. Oh, I just. I
can't even. Wait. Oh, no. Never mind. I was about to do like a bit, but I cut it off. This is so loud.
I got to turn this down. Oh my God. Like I'm talking way louder than I normally would be.
Sorry. Building all this bullshit. All right. So I can't break that shit.
Okay. Wait a minute. So what's going on here? I can't break those. So I just have to run.
I don't think I can break them. Does it go this far? Whoa. Chill.
300 bucks. Handgun ammo. I've had my weapons too. Well, you tell me I couldn't like pick that up.
No, I couldn't have. Never mind. I could have shot the handgun though.
And you tell me I couldn't have shot the handgun. Is that going to move?
That's going to move. All right. Oh my God. All this is. Oh my goodness gracious. Okay.
Uh, it's going to drop. It's going to drop. God. I made it. All right. How is he communicating
with me by the way? I'm confused about that. The speaker. This is just a saw game. I mean,
it kind of is. It's good so far. I like it. Don't take the first five minutes of this game. What I
said just to turn if I like this game. Big burps. All right. So now we just got to go back in there
and just wait, go back to where we just were and just go through and like wipe the sweat off my
brown be like, all right, I did it. Got to be something over here, right? He's going to have
a stopwatch. He's going to be like, there you are. Record time. Something like that. Right.
That was like a test. See if I'm worthy to be the next Avenger. I've been waiting for you, Mr.
Winter. How do you know my name? Anyone who's anyone has heard of the likes of you. A hero
searching for his daughter. I must say that castle arouses suspicion. These are fairy tale
characters. This is like Humpty Dumpty. This is fairy tale characters, right?
Call me the Duke. Now to business. Weapons, ammunition, healing salves, anything you desire.
Holy shit. You really let yourself go since Resident Evil 4. I can't wait to buy something
happen. Be like, Oh, wow. Thank you. It's right. The same guy. I was just thinking of ways to pass
the time. Plies, guns, smithy, the Duke's purse. Everything has. Okay. What about supplies and
thousand extra baggage, increased number of item slots available in your inventory.
I only have 910 bucks. Shotgun ammo. Learn how to make shotgun ammo. That's really huge.
Sniper rifle, ammo, mines. All right. This is cool. Gun smithy. Oh no. I have to pick what I want.
I can't even afford any of this, but, Oh, I know people are going to be like, dude, you don't do
that handgun. Pick this other gun. Crystal. Ooh, I can sell that for two grand. 12,000 for the
shotgun. What if I just sell this and make the handgun awesome? That'd be kind of cool, right?
Don't dump dump. Well, I'm going to sell the crystal fragment. Why wouldn't I?
How do I sell it? No, don't. No, I knew this was going to happen. I just knew this was going to
happen. I knew I was going to, I was going to sell the crystal. What? Let me guess. You can put like
three crystals in like a crown and then the three crystal crown becomes like 50 grand.
White mineral found in this region could probably sell it valuable. I'm just selling it. I don't
care. Get mad. Everyone's going to get angry about this, but I'm just selling it. I'm buying this
because of our relationship, you know? Whatever. If I get it wrong, I get it wrong.
It literally says component. Securing goods is more important than anything. All right. Now
let's see. What do I got? Can I upgrade? Wait, I want to, how much is shotgun ammo? 3000. I need
100. I'm going to sell some stuff. Okay. I'm going to sell. How much do I need? You can sell
anything that says valuable, but don't sell things that say combinable. All right. I just need 90.
I'm going to sell six handguns. Little and often fills the purse as they say.
Okay. Now I want to buy, I want to be able to make 3000. Make shotgun ammo. That's huge. That's
really important. I want it. I see. Anything else? Okay. I'm skilled at all sorts of weapons
modifications and we'll do them until next we meet. All right. What does it take to make
shotgun ammo? Gunpowder, rusted scrap and chem fluid. Oh, that's a lot. I think in my head,
you have to restart. Hey, thank you. Hey, you already fucked it. Oh, oh, that's cool. I need
to save the game. Sell ammo to get ammo. Well, yeah, I want to be able to craft shotguns. Are
you telling me that the shotgun ammo crafting ability is more important than like six handgun
bullets? I'm probably going to need it like right now. I'm at the last boss. This is the
game's almost over. This is the demo guys. The game didn't even fucking come out. I don't know
what everyone's freaking out for. It's behind the curtain. Could Rose be here? Three daughters,
Bella, Cassandra and Daniella. Mm hmm. Okay. Mm hmm. Uh, January 5th, uh, redneck delivery of one
male, three females, a Miranda meeting with mistress Dimitrescu. How do I pronounce this?
Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu, the Duke business discussions. Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu,
Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu, Dimitrescu. Yeah. Dimitrescu.
Dimitrek. I not how you say this is a big house. Okay, hold on. Well, let's go away. What about
over here? Don't step on that. You like always step on wooden fall. Ooh, what's this? 500 bucks. I
could have saved that money. Whatever. Nothing happens. I'm going to turn that on later. All
right. Let's keep going. It's like an elevator room. They say it in the game. They do. You're a
liar. I, I guarantee they don't say Dimitrescu one time in the whole game. I bet you one wink
that they don't. Now remember, I don't think they say, like I could say it and like other characters,
but I'm talking about like the Dimitrescu family is not going to say Dimitrescu the whole game.
Like I'm lady Dimitrescu. No. All right. That's good. Hang on anymore. That was weird.
They literally said it. No, but for us again, my baby, that was the baby scream. Okay. Hall,
hall of the four. What is that? Oh, and mask the angels blinded gaze and you'll eat a shitload of
bugs. Hey, what the fuck? This guy's life sucks.
Mother, I bring you fresh prey. You are so kind to me, daughters. Now let's take a look at him.
Wow. Well, Ethan Winters, you escaped my little brother's idiot games. Did you?
Let's see how special. I don't want to play any more games. Yes, mother.
Can you just get out? Can we talk? Like why do I have to play games?
Starting to go a little stale. Then let's devour his man flesh quickly, mother. I am the one who
captured him. No, no, daughters. First. I must inform mother Miranda,
but later. Well, there will be enough for everyone.
Do vampires have like a blood filter? Like we filter water. Like wouldn't that just be the
equivalent of like drinking out of the sewer? I don't know. I feel like it's dirty. You need
like a vampire Britta. What the fuck was that? What was that? What was that thing? What was she
smelling? What was she just sitting at? What the fuck was that? All right. So if I sit here for 15
minutes, I don't do anything. The main character bad guy from fall out, fall guys. What's the game?
I've ruined the joke already. Well, what's the name of the fucking game? Far cry. I gotta get
out of here before they come back. Whatever. I was gonna say he kicks the door and he's like,
Hey, remember me? And then he lets me out. Whatever. It would have been funny. I couldn't
even think of the name. They're all like far cry. Far out. Fall out. Fall guys. Fall cry. Cry far.
Like how many? Whatever. His poor guy's hands kind of wish like, Oh, his fingers would be like,
like, Oh, cool. That'd be totally video game of this. Wouldn't it? By the way, why did I
wink? She didn't say it. She didn't say Dimitra Sue. That one was free. It was in glass.
It was a free wing. All right, there's a big lever here. I take that. Okay. Hold on. I have
yet to understand what the fucking goal is because every time I walk in a room, one of the main
characters is like, Oh, let's play with him. And then there's no goal. They just like do something
weird and leave. Look for Rose in the castle. Okay. Easy to pick lock. I need a lock pick.
Get in there. Oh, secret hidden tunnel. Not yet. Hold on. That's probably stuff. Yeah. This like
something in here. Books, things to read. Can I leave? Can I just open the door? Of course not.
All right. Well, I, there's a locked lock pick thing right there. I was going to come back with
a lock pick and let's go. By the way, I think since using the 3090, I think this room has
increased its temperature by five full degrees. I need like an air conditioning unit or my computer.
I swear to God, I think it's probably 80 plus degrees in here right now.
Scrap. Okay. I can make, um, some stuff. Pick up the baby. Rune eye ring. Throw your case. No,
I don't, I'm not, I don't want to do that. You guys are like, make fun of my cable management
or something. It'll always be something. Throw your case. Oh, wow. Nice cable management. Like
whatever. I don't care. Okay. We know the bed chamber is a hall of the four, which is,
oh, wait, I can open this door now. Wait, is that the coin in here going to break this
crystal fragment? Hell yeah. All right. And where's the next, um, wait,
turn on ray tracing for just a little bit. I don't know. It'll get, it'll be a hundred degrees in
here. Ray tracing is a meme guys. It doesn't matter. All right. So that's like a little
shortcut to the bed chamber. I mean, like it's cool, but it's really cool. Well, I don't know.
I don't really care to like increase my like graphics card energy consumption by like 150%
to like have the floors be reflective. I don't, I don't care. I would, I would, I have my like
comfort in this room of it being 80 degrees, way more, put it, I put it so much higher than
like a reflective screen, like a reflective mirror. This shit will be roasting in here.
It's cool. I don't hate it, but I need like a fucking car exhaust on here. Ask the angels,
blind the gaze, the ring. Okay. Mask the angels, blind the gaze. Oh, this is okay. I'll figure
that out later. This is like the ultimate puzzle. Probably. Let's go up. It seems to be the place
to go. It's a cool house. Nice. I got to save money. How many suits of armor? This is, that's
weird. I have a suit of armor. This many suits of armor in your house. It's too many. I can understand
one more than one is very strange than a T that lipstick of blood or both. Why would you drink
blood? Okay. Is it weird that I find it less disgusting if they were to literally cook me
and eat me than if they were to drink my blood while I'm alive? I find that to be like just less
gross. Can I unlock this? I can. Excellent. All right. So now there's a way to get around this
whole house. Let's go up here. I'm going up. I hear something moving. Wine room. Ooh,
this is going to be blood. All right. I can make shotgun. Whoa. I can be 30. Whoa. No, I can't. I
need two rusted scrap. Shit. Wait. How many rusted scrap do I have? Just one. Why am I making tech?
Whatever. I don't care. Put the ring on it. You can't use that. What? Like a gravy boat?
All right. I got to like put gravy in the gravy boat or whatever I need to do.
I got to remember this. The French champagne. It's always been celebrated for its excellence.
There is a California champagne by Paul Marceau. I love that guy. Ring. Maroon eye ring. You can't
use this as is. Why not take the eye out? Can I like examine it? Okay. Maroon eye. All right.
I know where that goes. Say Aaron. Okay. I'll do a Kickstarter campaign for 1.4 million dollars.
And if it gets to 1.4 million, I will say Aaron on stream. How's that sound? I need to save the
game very, very badly. I've not saved the game since. What the fuck? This guy's hands. What? Oh
God. Slice your jugular. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Let's not do that. I'm not taking a lie.
Dad, which would you prefer? Nothing. Neither. No. Can I hide in the closet? I can't hold back
any longer. What do I do? Oh my God. I thought that just said German 985. It's a German 985.
It was my first day working at the castle today. I was most shocked to see the other staff were
all women. The mistress and her daughters were very adamant that they wouldn't bite.
It was quite peculiar. It's been two weeks since I started working at the castle and I'm a little
afraid. Another maid, Adela, made a mistake and Miss Daniella slashed her face with a knife.
And at night I can hear wailing as if ghosts roam the halls. I want to go home.
I don't know what to do. The young ladies were complaining it was too hot and stuffy during
dinner. So I opened the window, just a crack. Shut it. Shut it now. They all freaked at me in
unison. Looks like I'm gonna have to suffer with my 3090 in my own bedroom in heat.
That was funny. I refused to see fucking minus twos. That was actually really funny.
I fear I may be taken down into the cellar and never to be seen again. I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do. That was funny. Don't fucking tell me it wasn't. I know when it was
funny because I know. Okay, now it's funny. Now it's funny. This game is really cool. I'm really
into it. Oh my god, is that Lady Dimitrescu? Hey Cabbagehead, PhD, thanks for the 25 community subs.
That's a lot of money, thank you. Tasting room, thanks for the 25 subs. I just went too far when
I looked over at chat. That hurt. Do they chase you around the house? Oh my god, they probably do.
Should I go in that door she just opened? Yeah. Oh my god, is she gonna come back in here? Wait,
something. Hurry, hurry, hurry before she comes back. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. I need a typewriter
room. So bad, it's not even funny. Snake in here? They still do that in these games? No. Dump that?
Trust in light. All right, light it up. What does that do? Boom, boom, boom, boom. He walks down the
hall with a sledgehammer. Where the hell am I? Fuck, it's covered in dried blood. I don't understand.
Was this like a, was it putting somebody inside of that? Oh, all right, I have to be honest with you.
I feel like this would kind of feel kind of good. I have like chest and like back pain issues and
I feel like sitting there and pushing back on those just lightly would hit like a bunch
of pressure points if I didn't do it too hard. You're a freak. All right, I wouldn't want to
put that on somebody. Wouldn't that be fucking terrifying? Like, oh yeah, go get the pig mask
thing. No, no, I don't want to do that. That's scary, man. Like that's fucking terrifying to me.
Can't we just like beat the shit out of him? Why do we have to like put like a fucking weird
mask on him? I don't, I don't want to do that. Help me. It's a horror game. I know, but like I'm
just saying like that's, they used to do all kinds of fucked up shit back in like the medieval times
and stuff. It's like, why would you want to do that? Like look at all this stuff. I don't want
to like pull somebody's fucking teeth out while they sit on like a bunch of spikes and nails.
I missed a save point. I did. Where? I just closed myself in a cell next to the angel.
Where? Hold on a second. This is a cool photo. Focus area right up, right up in the front.
Actually cool. It's a cool photo. Hold on. I wish I could actually use, scroll with this.
Wow, this is such a weird way to do this. Focus area. I want it like back.
Why can't I go back with the focus area? There you go. Okay. It's a console port. Blur strength.
Yeah, I want it to be like blurry up here. Focus area. Where is this focus area?
I don't even know what the fuck they're trying to tell me. Please play the game. I'm, this is,
I'm taking a, I took a picture in photo mode. I want to do this. I can't take five fucking,
less than five seconds to do this. I mean, it's been like probably two minutes, but still.
I think, I think it's a cool photo. Wait, I didn't know I could do these.
I could have had a newspaper for the, I could have had it on this animal display.
All right. That's cool. All right. I went in here. I don't want to miss.
I must have fireworks. Why would you do this to somebody?
Arena. Robust appetite. Mahala. Robust appetite. Lois.
Ingrid. Unstable. Overly alert at times. Somebody just said, bye. Bye. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
You're giving me a lot of shotgun bullets here. All right. What the fuck is that?
You want how to make this way scarier? I have just singing in the background,
the person, whoever this is just going like the itsy bitsy spider went up the water spot.
Down came the rain and watched the spider like twinkle, twinkle little star.
I need a typewriter. Why are you alive? Oh, money. Let me hit their head.
Hey, are you fucking invincible or what is going on here? How many times have I
shoot you in the head? All right. Get the money. Where the? Get the money. Get the money. Get the
money. Pipe bomb. Well, that would have been nice to use that. Wouldn't it have? Why is it doing the
fucking like cockroach sound? Where am I going? Stop doing the music. Stop the music. Pipe bomb.
Pipe bomb. Hey, browsing zebra. Thanks for the 20 immunity subs. Appreciate it.
Oh, I got a necklace. God damn it. I mean, this stuff, I want, I want to make sure I have tons
of ammo and tons of weapons and shit. Oh, like mother wasn't feeling well. This is just every
new, like 2020 plus 2019 horror movie trailer. This goes done, done, done. They're like dinner,
like eating, done. She changed. She was changing done. And that shows like the company's name,
the logo, still skull. Otto's not in here, right? I feel like I'm going to scare the shit out of
him. He is produced by the makers of get out. Yeah. Hannah just gave 30. What's one of the
community subs? 30 community subs from Hannah. Thank you. That's a shit load of subs. There's
like about like 150 subs have come in. I guess give me so much money. That was scary. Another
one of these doors that I cannot go into. Eventually I'll get whatever that is. Whatever
that would have a medallion that is. Thanks. That's a lot. Thank you, Hannah.
God, I need a typewriter. We typewriter. I'm not healthy. I'm very unhealthy right now.
Actually, you know, not even a bar of chocolate and cheeseburgers. I ate the last few years.
I need that. Whatever it is. Which tools do you prefer? I prefer
the
I'm okay. I'm okay. Drink the poison, whatever it is. Poison, poison, eat the poison.
No, I'm just picking up random items. Open it. Don't use those.
It's light. Light. Holy shit. Light makes you able to be injured.
I won't give you. Light allows me to fire at them. Die. Did I run?
Oh, did I win? Nice. That was fucking cool. This game is awesome. Besides the FOV.
And I said something very strongly about Capcom earlier and I'm going to backtrack on it. But
like fuck that. What the fuck are they doing? You're getting a lot of good like YouTuber
screams, by the way, this stream. Tons of like thumbnail images. I need a typewriter so bad.
Sangui. I don't know about that. I have no idea. Another one was sent to the cellar.
She only had spilled some soup. They're evil. All right. I need to how much chem fluid do I have?
Just three shotgun shells. I'm going to make it. I need some more chem fluid. That was intense.
Look at the name. It's virgin. It's a virgin strawberry. What about a little banana? What
about a little banana? Magic bullet. It can do anything. Save you idiot. I don't know what
saving even means. Recoil compensator. There's no typewriter. I haven't seen a typewriter in like
an hour and 20 minutes. I have not seen a single typewriter in 20 minutes. 30 minutes at least.
You missed it. Where is it? Sorry. I was being chased by like a murderous lady. There's a room
you missed. Should I hold on to this? This is for the lemmy. Okay. Nice. Recoil dampening.
Just keep moving. You'll get. All right. All right. I'm going to keep moving. Yes.
Do I only get one of these? Do I get one? How many do I get? Oh, one. Why did I use it on the
most obvious of things? Wooden angel statue. I feel like I picked up a bunch of random shit and
I have absolutely no idea where it goes. I have this. A vintage bottle of wine. Looks like it was
bottled a long time ago. Crystal fragment. Crystal skull. Crystal torso. Crimson glass.
Wooden angel. I just have a ton of this stuff. Crystal head vodka. Oh my god. I need a typewriter.
I know it's part of the game. I know that like, look, remember Resident Evil when we had to go
find a typewriter and use ink ribbons and shit. I know it's like, oh, look, it's like nostalgic.
Just give me a fucking exit. Like save game right here. Auto saves. Bad take. It's not.
That's not a bad take. Key items. Wait. I need a special key. Okay. Half of the four.
Put the bottle in the gravy. I like it. The typewriter. Just wait. Let's shot that. All right.
They point by the faceless statue. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Half of the four. Typewriter. Oh, we meet again. Hello. Duke, why are you here?
Where there's coin to be made. And have you found your daughter? Fake Fiji. If she is truly here,
the lady of the castle would have kept little Rose in her private chambers, would she not?
Demetresque? The very same. Why don't you take a look? Maybe you'll get lucky.
And speaking of looking, care to make a purchase? It's Demetresque. It's not Demetresu.
It's Demetresu. Demetresu. Demetresque? That's, I am very, very surprised.
Zim and put the wine here. Can't use that here. Craftsman, whatever. Naturally. Okay. Crystal
torso. Treasure. Valuable. Treasure. Valuable. Valuable. So should I do these? Something can
go inside of the chest there, right? Can things go? Wait a minute. Let me just check. Care. It
would say. Okay. You wish to make a purchase. Sell it all. It would actually say like,
combinable. Let's just get rid of sell it all. 1,905,000. Crimson glass. Wooden angel statue.
Necklace. Wait, wait. I should examine this stuff first? Because yeah, some of this. You can like
touch this stuff and like look around at it. Examine. All right. This, maybe the second
thing I can touch or open or click on. I get it. Hold on. No, nothing. I guess I don't think so.
It's an escape room. Wait, I know, but like I'm serious. There's probably like a button on this
shit somewhere. I'm serious. This is just Skyrim. It's not. All right. You owe us a wink. There you
go. What about the glass? All right. Please spam yes if I'm overthinking the absolute hell out of
this. Am I just overthinking this like crazy for no reason? Sell it all. I have 19,000 bucks.
Supplies. I can get increased item slots. Mines. I could just buy some first aid. Rock on ammo.
High capacity magazine. Hair trigger. Greatly increases fire rate. Well, more probably slots.
I'm going to do the safe thing. Ah, so you noticed that. Give me the safe thing.
I'm going to buy, I'm buying, I'm buying one of those and I'm going to buy, I'm going to buy some
shotgun ammo. How much should I buy? It's one, it's a thousand for one shot. No, thank you.
Can I get the boom, boom, boom for the shotgun? Greatly increases fire rate. I think I'm going to
do it. Yeah, I want it. Nice. All right. I'm out of money. I'm skilled at all sorts of weapons.
Thank you for your patronage. Well, this has just, he just yelled that at me. That was weird. Okay.
Way more space. All right. Let me rearrange. How do I rearrange? Shift, move. Okay. Let me clean up
my inventory. It looks, it's a mess. That's better. No. Yeah. See, that's much better.
Rock on ammo. Let's get it. It's a Tarkov inventory. Holy shit. Look at how far away this was.
This was an hour and 45 minutes ago. I would have been so sad if I didn't get it. Okay.
So what, what are you actually supposed to go here? Let me pick up some keywords.
Labyrinth, house on a hill, water wheel, iron tower, labyrinth, unique, special crafted metal
ball, special metal ball. Okay. I need a special metal ball. Where have I not gone?
Uh, I could, there's something, I could go this way. We'll go into Lady, uh, Lady Demetrius's
chambers. What's this? Is that guy all right? What just happened? Wait, what? What did he do?
By the way, that guy's definitely sitting on the toilet. I would be shocked if he wasn't.
Okay. We need to go to Lady Demetrius's chamber. Let's just go this way. Right.
Uh, bed chamber. Q is spin. I got to remember that. Nothing here. This is not Lady Demetrius's
chamber. Isn't this her bedroom? This is not her bedroom. I think it's upstairs. I'm just saying
it to piss us off now. I don't, I don't, I'm sorry. I have my own head cannon. Demit, Demetrius. It
sounds much more, I don't know. What was it? I don't even know. I don't remember even what it was
because I find it to be something I don't want to say. Domitresque. That sounds, okay. So like,
have you heard it like, oh, what would you, what would you like on your, on your taco?
I'll take a, uh, jalapeo, please. It's jalapeno. Like, I feel like domitresque is
Demitrisu. That's not how language works. I don't know. What do you want me to say?
All right. I need to go DEE. You're the one saying jalapeno though. Whatever. Is the wine room? No.
Okay. Now where are we going? Where is Demitrius's chambers? Here? Walk from the other side. Sure.
Where's this lady sleep? Oh, I have the bottle of wine. Oh, oh, oh. Oh, courtyard key. I got a new
key. Is it right? Nice. Let me look at what it says. Key for the door from the castle's dining
hall to the courtyard. Down to the dining hall. Get the bottles. I don't waste bullets. No.
Don't break all this shit. God damn it. Where do I go? Where's the dining room?
Dining room is behind me. So it's behind her. So I'm going to run. I'm just going to do a juke
and run right by her. Here we go. Oh, she's fast. She's fast. She's fast. Oh, she's fast.
Oh, she's fast. Oh, all right. That was not hard. Think fast. Think fast. I can do it. Think fast.
Sora, think fast. Think fast. I can do it. Think fast. Nope. Think fast. So it's close. Think fast.
Think fast. There it is. I need to do another. I don't know what that is. There's no doors.
Open. Okay. I'm getting the shotgun out for this one. I thought I had 38 rounds. I was like, wow,
I just beat the game wicked easily. Hey, Titans and Eren's voice. No, that gets me in trouble.
I'm not doing it. I got to like open the window so light comes in so I can shoot the people.
What have you done to my daughter? You know, I'm here. Oh, a map. Oh, dude. Dude. Dude. Yes.
We're going to, I'm going to kill Lady Dimitrescu. Dude. Hello. It's me, daughter killer. I'd like to
talk to you. I'd like to have a little bit of conversation. What are these? Why are they holes?
It's a gamer chair. That's so stupid. What do I have to do there? What have you done to my daughter?
My daughter. What do you do? My daughter. There's something I'm doing here.
Women are blind to male advances, but the poor shall take their chances
to give their lord their bounties sown so that soon the wine may flow. Like move them?
Women are blind to male advances, but male advances turn to, or what was it? Women are blind
to male advances, but the poor shall take their chances to give their lord the bounties sworn
so that soon the wine may flow. Okay. So they have to, this is the lord. Who's this? Women?
Women are, women are blind to male advances. So you look this way. Yeah, I got it.
That's the lord and that's the wine. I know. What do you think? I don't know what I'm doing.
Oh my goodness. What a gamer. Thanks. This is, I fell asleep. Well, then you must not even have
the volume on because there's, okay, if you're sleeping on this stream, the stream is muted.
There's been screams and shit. Shotgun blasts in your ears. Like there's no way you're watching
the stream muted. You know, the times I've screamed in the last hour, like as loud as my body can
probably do it. What the hell? Damn it. Okay. This is going to be scary. I know it. This is
going to be scary. There's going to be scary monster. Yes, there is. Can I, can I jump over
this? Nope. I just have to kill this guy. Where'd he go? He's in the water. Oh my God. Is that him?
No. Women are blind to male advances, but male advances take their chances for the lord they
seek to swore their keep. The wine will flow. Balls deep. I don't know. Whatever it was.
I think there's another one right here. That low recoil is awesome. That's really useful.
Oh, I got to reply. This is important. Remember that sounded like iPhone predict text. Sometimes
I feel like I actually am doing iPhone predict text. Sometimes my brain goes too fast and has
to just say words that just sound like they might fit there. It actually happens all the time.
Yeah. You're too close. You're too close. You were just way too close. I'm sorry. Way too close.
Well, what the hell was that for? That didn't do anything for me. There's a screwed everything
up. Now open this. I'm going to have to close this on somebody. Somebody's going to be coming
down this way and I'm going to close it on him. Like right now, like right now close it. Where'd
they go? Three shots. Okay. Worked out. Hypers drink the bong water, bong water. I can't see
anything. I'm going to make some handgun ammo. This game is actually pretty scary. It's really
scary. Run, run. All right. I got to make handgun ammo. Aaron, are you? Oh, that was not a smart
play. Very, very unintelligent play there. I'm making a lot of money. This is good. Okay. Hold
on. I need ammo. I have three med kits. I'm doing fine. Okay. Should I just make a shitload of
shotgun bullets or what? What do you think? Just make six shotgun shells and just have just a
massive amount of bullets. What should I make? Be safe. No, whatever. I'm going to make these.
Still something in here that I'm missing. I got a P too. I'm going to go. I got to do my first P
and then I'm going to refill my fake Fiji water. Why are you here? I get a lot of items.
I hear something. Oh wait, what is this? All right. I got everything. Look at this face. I just
came all over my mouth. As you're over there. All right. Demetrius's. I know whatever. I don't care.
Thousand bucks. Holy shit. I don't want to go in here yet. I want to go back outside here because
it's stuff. There's phones in residency. I didn't even think there'd be like a telephone in this
game. It's 2020. Hello. Hello. Hello. I'm sorry. I regret to inform you that Ethan Winters has
escaped that fool Heisenberg because he is in my castle and has already proven too
much for my daughters to handle when I find him. No, Miranda. Yes, of course. I understand the
importance of the ceremony. I won't let you down. Why does she have a reflection? Holy shit. To
hell with the ceremony. That man will pay for what he's done. What is going on in this game?
I have no idea what the story is. I'm the guy from the last game. In the last game, there was
that old, like spoilers if you haven't played Resident Evil 7, but what the hell are you watching
Resident Evil 8 for in the first place? There was the old lady in the chair was like the antagonist
and it was like this experiment, right? It was a boat. You had like this, your girlfriend was like
the runner of a project that like had to do with this little girl and the little girl like aged
rapidly into an old lady and like she was controlling everybody. Everyone was like under
her control. She was making them do like crazy things. She was the little girl's caretaker.
Yeah, right, right. But then we like escaped the island. Chris Redfield's like, nice job, nice job
partner. And now Chris Redfield wants to take my baby and like killed Mia and now we're in this
weird like fucking cartoon Avengers house. I guess we're going to figure it out with like this vampire
lady, this like little like corpse bride person, Igor, and fucking like cool like Mortal Kombat
Elvis. We're just going to find out. We were all called by Mother Miranda to decide the fate of
the child's father, me. Just thinking of that family meeting makes me shudder. I think I'm
treated like a sister to those miscreants, especially Heisenberg. That riff raff wouldn't
know proper manners if they slapped him in the face. I would have sliced him into ribbons if
Mother hadn't. OK, so Mother, why does she treat me the same as them? She gave me the
castle, obedient daughters, everlasting life. Did she not? Am I not her favorite? Am I not special?
I didn't even realize just how tall this how tall she is. That's fucking huge. Wow. Where are you?
Just realized. I mean, I mean, every time I've seen her, I've been like crouching looking up or like
in chains looking up at her. I've never like actually stood up face to face. She like picked
me up and put me on like hooks. What am I supposed to do here? Look for Rose in the castle.
I moved this? How is all this shit locked? Does it open the door from the other side?
Yeah, where am I supposed to go? I'm stuck in her bedroom. OK, the Mitrasue key. It's the one.
That's what these keys. OK, these doors. There's a couple of them I need to go to.
Lay your filthy manhands on my daughters. And now you even try to steal my property.
Go ahead, do your worst.
She's like falling, screaming like she fell in the same hole or something.
She lands right on her neck and fucking you hear just crunches her legs. Her knees hit the fucking
ground behind her and her neck just snaps off. If I fall through this, she falls through there too.
She's has she's got like at least fucking 300 pounds on me. How was the floor holding her?
If I fall through the floor, she put in so much force. I don't buy it. That's rude. She's like
12 feet tall. I'm just saying she's big. She's very large. She's like 12 and a half feet tall.
Nine feet tall. Sorry. It's OK. I got it wrong. She's like 10 feet tall. If you were 10 feet tall,
you would probably weigh like 300 fucking pounds. All right, let's go.
No, I wouldn't. Yes, you would. You'd that you'd just be a large person.
I'm going to look. All right. How much does Shaq weigh? How tall is Shaq?
Shaq's like seven five, right? Like eight feet tall. How much does Shaq weigh? Shaq is seven two.
So so Lady Demetrius is like three feet taller than Shaq. I'm going to guess that she's
probably 300 pounds. She's going to chase me around, right? This is a this is a boss room.
This is like a weird boss room. Shaq is three hundred and twenty four pounds. OK.
All right. Oh, God, what is going on? This is a boss room. I got to pay attention.
I could let you get away with a slice of your ribbons before you ever see me chuckle.
Boss fight. No.
Hey, where'd she go? Whoa. Whoa. My hand. Pull it. Cut the other hand off.
Whoa. She's probably right here. Whoa. Oh, a box. I can't. I can't do my hand.
Duck. Move out of the way. You actually thought I was going to let you get away, darling.
OK. Yep. This time, don't freak out. Just press it again.
Ow. Here it is.
I mean, no. What the fuck am I doing?
Any items, any stuff, stuff, any items? Nope. Go. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Open the door. Key.
Open it. Oh, geez. OK, I got the mask of sorrow. Oh, geez.
I guess I'll try. What?
Is this guy like a Roblox character? Like, what is he made of the Legos? Did it work?
Screw this castle. Did I use my guns? What the fuck is making that sound?
Escape the castle. I have, hold on. I have the Demetrius key, right? Isn't there another Demetrius
Udor right there? No. I swear to God, this is another Demetrius Udor literally right behind me.
All right. Where's the big, where's that fat guy? I need him. Everybody's spoiling. Spoiling what?
I'm not even looking at chat. If you're sending me that they will look out for spoilers,
spoiler alert. I'm not looking at the fucking chat for like at least 20 minutes.
Oh, nice castle map. Opera Hall. Can I go in? I can't go in the Opera Hall. I'm not looking.
I don't want to see. Let me actually, I need to do some crafting here. Yeah, give me another one.
How's my health? Am I okay? Please be aware, the mistress's lipstick is missing. If anyone
finds it, could they please return it to her bathroom? It is custom made and therefore very
expensive. I mean that, what's this? What's that Metroid thing? Three girls have stopped moving.
They see Momo's dead. An insect flew out of the eldest's mouth. It appears to be a common fly.
Three days since treatment, all three bodies are covered in flies. It appears the flies
are consuming their flesh. When I opened, I got a pee. I'll be right back. I'm back. I'm back.
I dropped a coffee on the ground. I dropped it on the ground and it was, it was a disaster.
Toilet. Yeah, the toilet got clogged. I had to plunge the toilet. It was, it was a joke.
You're lucky I wasn't gone for 40 minutes, but I'm ready to get back into it. Let's go.
Oh, I got a question for all you PC enthusiasts here. So, so I have a 3090 and this thing is loud
and runs hot. How hard is it to like put a new heat, like a heat sink on this? Like should I
get like a water cooling system for the GPU? Because this thing is going like it sounds like
a jet engine in here. Clean the fans. I mean, this is a, this is literally brand new. What 3090 is it?
Um, I don't know if honestly it was, all these graphics supplies are in such a low supply
that it just, whatever one was available, I bought it. I don't even know what the brand is. Let me
see who the brand is. Zotac? Is Zotac gaming? Zotac? I don't know. What's Zotac? I knew it.
Those are the only ones that are available. What do you want me to do? Zotac is one of the brands.
Yeah. Zotac is fine. Yeah. People are saying Zotac is good. Zotac is fine. Yeah. Zotac is
fucking fine. What's wrong with Zotac? I haven't had any problems with it. The only problem I have
is that I think it's a little loud. Like the fans. I just get to take the heat sink off,
put a new one on. I mean, if you're going to have a 3090, 3090 is literally like,
like a down payment on a house. Like it's like I'm buying a car. So like I may as well like
pony up to put like a liquid cooling system on it, right? I'm going back. 3090 is run,
just, just run hot. I got another fake Fiji. Why do you stream in 720p? Because I have only had
a 3090 in the computer like three hours. Sorry. It's been like a little bit longer, but whatever.
It's been like a little while, whatever. All right. All three bodies have almost completely
consumed by the insects. Insects eat people. It's just afternoon and the insects just started eating.
Those around the face turned pale and the lips turned red. The massive insects have transformed
into human bodies again. All three girls are woke looking at me like newborns. I sense a bond
between us like mother and daughters. I've already decided their names. Flies are turning into people.
Okay. Interesting. Every Zotac fan, uh, card I've bought had the fans die. Um, I mean,
that's kind of anecdotal evidence I think, but I mean, still they are pretty, they're,
they are turning right now, but it's just so hot in here. I gotta like get,
I gotta figure out a solution. All right. Escape the castle. Let's just go whatever I was doing
and go, bingo. Running out of bullets. This is bad. Need bullets. There's a big piano. Oh,
wait, this is a piano. Can I play the piano? Yes. Okay. You didn't even look at the stage.
What do you mean? What stage? Oh, we've got the iron key. Oh, all right. It's an opera.
The fan curve using Zotac software. You're running at a 10, you were running at 1080p.
You can make it quiet for a thermal ceiling of 78 degrees Celsius. That's good to know. Thank you.
Probably use that. All right. So the iron key, there are a few iron doors.
It's still in here though. All right. Looking for iron doors. Where's an iron door?
There are no iron doors here. There's an iron door down in like that like weird chamber place,
which is this way. All right. We'll go in there. Just spit on it. It would go,
that wouldn't do anything. That'd be banned that fucking person. Seriously. What are you talking
about? Odd. Okay. I need to go this way, right? Cause then I need to go down here, right? That's
an iron key, isn't it? Oh my God. It's Lady Dimitra. Who the fuck am I into the courtyard? Let's go.
Does she come down here? They really do have swords and shit. They really are dark souls enemies.
She come out here. Oh my God. She actually comes out here. All right. I need iron door,
which is I got to go right down through the kitchen, which is going to bring me
through here. I hope so. I don't know. Wait, she's I can burn her. Just run. Fucking down here.
Making a mistake. Am I making a mistake? I don't think this is a mistake. I think this is a good
idea. This is a good idea. I mean, if you're going to shoot that many times, just get the money and
go. I'm sorry. Open the door. Oh my God. What happened? Can they open doors? She's not going
to actually, she's not going to come in this room, right? Is she going to come in this door?
She's not going to, that's her. She's coming. I have to figure out what this is. What am I doing?
I have to burn this? Is she going to come down here? She can't even fit through the door. I'm
fine. Oh my God. Where are you? I got to break this. Come on. Come on. Break the door. Break this.
How do I get in here? I need to light this. I need to light them. How do I light them?
All right. I need to light this shit. How do I light these? Can I blow this door? Can I blow
this up? I'm going to blow it up. I didn't miss. I got to push these back and forth together.
Come on and get it. Fight this. Fight it. As your eye. As your eye. Money. Ooh,
crystal fragment. Okay. I cleaned it out. Now. Hey, where do I go now? That was down here.
Second floor is up here. There's a Demetrius. There's a Demetrius key over here. I got to go
to the hall of pleasure, but first let's, I got to grab some stuff because I am almost out of ammo.
Very important handguns. Good. All right. We're going to go to the hall of pleasure. So if I
bang a left here and run straight, that'll take me down and go through the kitchen
into the merchant's room. Let me stop there. And then I go to the second floor.
Okay. Let me go. I'm good. Let me, I got to get to the merchant room down here
into the main hall through the kitchen. Let's go. Shit. Pleasure room. It's kind of a creepy
thing to name a room. Here we go. She's going to show up here and I'm going to have to dodge
around her. All right. We're going to straight through there, bang a right in the dining room.
Okay. Here we go. Oh my God. I escaped myself a headache. I have a headache.
Oh my God. I escaped myself. I have a headache now. I just popped a blood vessel in my brain.
Wrong way. Shit. She saw me. Wrong way. Are you okay? Oh, I think so. I feel like I'm all right.
Okay. We got to go to the merchant's room. He is no wrong way. Turn around. Straight ahead.
All right. I finally feel safe. It's a pleasure to see you safe.
How were things? Coffee anybody? No sign of Rose.
Sorry. It turned out that way. You'll find your way to her once you're out of this castle.
Do you have need of anything for the road ahead? Yes. Welcome. Welcome. You're sure to find something
new. Okay. Oh, did I get any items I can put here? Ask of sorrow, the key, the iron key.
Eyes are like so watery. You wish to make a purchase. Valuable. Valuable. Okay. Combineable.
Crystal fragment. Crystal skull. Azure eye. Can the Azure eye go in the skull?
Or does everything? No. I'm buying this because of our relationship. Oh my God. I have three of
these. Holy shit. Okay. I'm going to hold on to that. All right. I got almost 17,000. New stock.
You got. Did you though? Okay. Power. I really do. I'm a shotgun user. I am.
Sell the shotgun. You schmuck. Ammo capacity or don't do upgrades. Am I going to get like
five more guns? I get it. All right. Just something an old friend of mine used to say.
Oh, there it is. I don't think I want anything. You know what? I'm going to. Yes, I do. I want this.
Leave this to me. It's I want it. It's just more power. I don't care about the other stuff.
It's 6,000. I can, I can. Okay. This is all an investment. Learn how to make mines. Eh.
Eh, let's go. Thank you for your patronage. I don't have anything to put here. Save it.
Now we need to go to the pleasure chamber, which is from here, we've got to go up.
So up the stairs and then down through Demetrius's dressing room. First,
put a mask on one of you. Find the four angel masks. One. Oh, okay. One out of four
into the pleasure room. Trying to work up my appetite, are you?
Yeah. All right. It's not going to kill this person.
Just what? Both. There's two of you. Why are there two of you? Right. Oh, hurry in, in,
in, in, in, in, in, in, in, in. Here we go. In, in, in, in, in, in. Holy. Holy. Turn around.
run what the fuck is that thing a mask silver ring yeah that's the second mask
so wait I have to put them I have to put a mask on here to open the door I don't
let's go that way okay what else when it was this I got a heel I got a heel I
have some good health I'm doing all right I'm okay I think look at all this
that's gonna move you know I don't even care if I'm wrong I know it's gonna
happen oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah oh oh oh boy
that way oh my god what's wrong all right you take a lie
crystal torso cool all right so there's only one more thankfully I can't get
Collapsed on by three of them anymore. Still something in here. What's in here? Oh
Mounted animals go
That's it. Nice. All right back to the Hall of Pleasure. How's my health? I think I'm fine
Played on hardcore and normal looks way too easy if I can spare Paris and I actually I heard that hardcore in this game
Is way too hard. That's what I heard really so like that doesn't go there. I have to put the mask back
Of course, there's a button on it
Okay
Back out we go. There's only one more of those sisters left. So that's all I have to worry about this
What's something in here? Thank you. I'll take it. So now what this is the Hall of Pleasure
I need to find two more map go into the Hall of Joy. I
Get in here now. This is blocked off. Maybe I can go this way in here. I go. I don't want to go down
What is it? What is it? What is it? Who is it? What's happening? I don't know what's happening right now
I go down. I don't know what I just did. What's going on? Oh my god. Is she in the room?
Chimp she's right. Where is she? I'm so good. She's out there. Okay, straight out right, right
Oh
My god, it's not two staircases. I thought it was two. I thought it was two stick
I gotta go down down down down down down down down down down down down down down. Wait, where am I going?
Where am I going? What's happening? Where am I? I don't want to go in the armory. I hate this
All right, just run by or whatever. Fuck it. I'm going I need to go this way, but this is blocked
You know I'm saying like I can't go in the Hall of Joy
I got rated was it was a rate who rated for why do you force your viewers to watch this?
Like the X on the top right of your window
Go read a book or something. What's the difficulty hot cool? Who rated go back to the courtyard?
Distraction I'm not as kind as my daughter
Okay, all right settle down this way
That's just
Distraction and throwing a grenade like into the air. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right
Where do I need to go Opera Hall will take me down here, which then the distillery where am I ultimately?
Where am I trying to go? I'm trying to go up to the library second floor. I'm right here
So if I go into the Opera Hall, I can go that way so get to the get to the Opera Hall
I need to go just bang a left right here. Hey, this is the Opera Hall
Now I should be able to go from here
Is there a typewriter anywhere? I don't know probably not
from the Opera Hall
Now we go up the stairs
Which will take me up here and then I go to this way
I'll be up here and then
This way and straight on this way. Here we go. All right, let's do it
Your typewriter anywhere. I thought I thought she just said you unlocked it
Break the glass the ceiling
Fuck glass and ceiling. What are you doing? Break the glass the ceiling? Oh
Close the window close the window. No, no, no open the window close the window
Let her get close Jeremy you learn nothing
All of the sisters are dead
All of them all sisters have been bank with
Well, what's going on what the hell just happened
I'm so just like pumped up right now. I can't this is why I can't play horror games
I get so bent out of shape about this stuff. I just started making noises screaming and stuff
I'm too I can't play these let me get everything. It's probably a secret. Oh, it's still more in here
This door won't miss it. Well, I thought it was locked what is still in here. He's playing on a normal like it's hardcore
Yeah, it's called. I'm fucking 36 this year and it's a scary game and I don't care how hard the game is
I don't want to fucking torture myself plays on hard
See anything there's gotta be something I can shoot or pull or push or touch her. Where is it? There's something in here
I don't know you're bad not giving it any more time. I got a feeling she's just gonna pop out
Beauty and the Beast clock looking motherfucker over there is gonna I don't know what's gonna happen with that. I'm scared of it
Yes, don't touch that on. Let me see what this is first
This goes this way. I thought that was her running by okay now. We're in this like in this weird place
I've no okay. Can I make shotgun bullets? I need them. I can't it. I'm running out on I'm running low on stuff
Hey, I only need one more mask
This is still this is let the five bells of this chamber ring out huge fanning
Let me just see where they are first because I'm probably gonna summon her you be like wall you're hitting my bells
Okay, like she's and then she'll run after me. So I got one here one of this. Well, whatever is
One there. Ooh
The bell the five bells of this chain. I've only seen two where these are the five are there's three more bells in here
Have no idea where the hell that would be keep looking nerd. It's not this entire
area, right
only that room with
Three more bells. I don't know what I don't I don't know. I really don't know
Three it's two more. Come on. Come on. What I don't I don't see them this chamber this chamber, huh?
Okay, where's the last one? This is the worst bit. I this is I this is not a bit
She she does she have one like on her or something. Ooh, it was beside it was behind the lady did
Mitrasu photo my eyes nobody scary. Nobody scary. Nobody scary. Nobody scary. No, I don't have my shotgun crutch
I don't like this a handgun ammo though. So that's good. What was that? Why did the magical goat just disappear treasure map?
Oh a dungeon. I heard there was something called the dagger of death's flowers somewhere in this castle
It's apparently an antique from the Middle Ages as coded in a concoction of poisons
Across the continent said to have been crafted to kill demons and monsters
Sounds fascinating, but no one knows where it is. It's hip. Oh shit
sniper mission incoming
F2 rifle nice
I'm pretty damn good at this. That's as far as it zooms. Oh
No, this is the worst sniper rifle I've ever seen in my life a horrible weapon. Okay. Well, whatever the ammo for it
I'm probably gonna have to use it. I'm gonna have to snipe these guys. This is what you're saying. You're gonna stop what?
Well, I'm gonna have to fight you on the ground. Hey grab me close. Whoa run
I'm trying to wipe the raid. I kicked that guy kicked that fucking guy right now. Kick him. Don't let him do anymore
Just kick him. He'll get it. He'll go he'll have to face out of the instance. All right, how do I get out of here?
Zip line sniper rifle ammo sick sniper rifle ammo sick
I
Got zip line quick
Mask of rage. I got all the masks. I should be able to get off shit. Stop me. I I want its money
How do I get out of here? He's money. Give me his money. Give me his money. Good. Okay
I need to get out of here. Oh, there's a ladder load this shit. I'm not going in here. Just completely blind
All right. What we got I have two of these I want shotgun ammo. Let me give it to me. It's more important than health
It's my panic button
Okay, I'm ready now. I need to just get out of here place all the angel masks. Just get the hell out of here
We're just go down the elevator. Get me out. Let's go throw a pipe on that the merchant guy. No, that's my health
Okay, this brings me back here
Which now here we go entrance hall. I have all the masks place them and then I should be able to continue
Good I want
else in here
Okay
The elevator comes back down. She's just sitting there waiting
She in here. Okay entrance hall straight and then bang a right. What the fuck holy shit, dude
I just go for it. Okay. I have to go straight through straight right. No. No, I'm just running straight
And I'm saying take a right so i'm just run straight ready one two
Two and a half masks put them on wait. What mask doesn't matter. Oh my god mask of pleasure
Oh my god. Oh my god mask of rage help me fat guy. Help me guy. Help me. Help me
Just hey, can you just go sit over there just just go sit over there just sit over here
Can you just sit here and just block it?
They fight holy shit
Just kill me. I'll start right here. Why does she know my full name? Why the webcam's like lagging?
I don't like how the webcam's lagging. It's mine. Okay. Well, i'm just gonna can we i'm gonna trade with you
I choose something for you. Why is she not allowed in here? Okay
crystal wing
Two of those crystal fragment crystal torso
Silver ring combinable
I put this in there
This should be enough good deal if I say so myself
Oh nice. Yeah, let's do it
Okay
You map view objectives and files discovered
As your eye ring
objective discovered
I can put that somewhere. Where can I put that?
Well, whatever. Let's just wish to make a purchase
28 000, let's upgrade some shit here. Okay sniper rifle
Should I do sniper rifle?
ammo capacity on the sniper rifle
happy birthday
Why are you saying that?
Well, it's happy birthday
Is raid who raided my thing is so fucked up and so behind. Hold on. Let me see
a raid from sock pens
Thank you sock pens
Welcome to the stream. Thanks. Hope you had a good stream sock pens and all the sock pen people
Thanks for the happy birthday wishes. Thanks a lot seeing the raid song. Sure
Thanks for the raid
I use the handgun so much that like why would I not upgrade at least once?
Right delighted to it may be
Our that's just 140. That's not that much
Reload speed. No, that's not that much either. Yeah, let's depart. These hands are more dexterous than one might think
I have 18 000. Why can I not?
Oh, what the hell?
Uh ammo capacity. I want more ammo in the shotgun
And let's just just just upgrade the whole thing. Just just let's go. I use it so often
Let's do
Um, that's fine
This is fine. Okay, that's all right
Securing goods is more important than anything
Anything my friend I just buy a shitload of shotgun rounds
buy eight
Crafts, nah, I might as well interesting selection and just buy these because they're here
I'm probably gonna need it at some point. Holy shit
Very valuable. Oh my god, it's 12 000. Nice. Okay
Very cool
Sell the ring. Yeah, that's something
Never buy something you can craft
Hey, where are you in this game?
Don't sell it
Upgrade the sniper rifle. Wait, should I not sell this?
How would I not sell it come again?
Can I use it somewhere?
As you wish you can you need it later?
I'm skilled. Good chat is dumb. I'm just gonna sell it do them for a small fee
Need it keep for secret ending. Oh
And buy it I will
Okay, now i'm gonna upgrade
Reload speed on this one moment, please
And rate of fire
Shotgun is good. We're gonna do pow. No
Ammo capacity on the sniper rifle
This simple modification can be done in just a moment. Excellent. Okay, good
There we go. Come again
Got some decent weapons now
Let's go save it
I'm ready
I have to put these so let me look at let me examine these masks because I need to know which one goes on what?
so
mask of rage
This one is three prongs
mask of joy
Is one prong
mask of pleasure
Is four prongs?
All right. So mat mask of joy mask of pleasure is the
Isn't she just standing out here?
pleasure mask of joy
mask of rage
All masks have been placed
Goodbye time for me to leave
the demetrius
Emily household
Okay. Well, this is definitely a hey watch out. There's a boss fight here. Well, I got I got what I got
Let's see what happens
Don't open it. There's gonna be somebody in there
Gonna be the baby
Oh, it's the magical dagger that kills people
Get her with it get her you drop the dagger of all things you idiot
Oh, it's so scary but god damn what a view you've given me just hold on a sec nice beautiful
Absolutely lovely
Okay, right, right, right, right
She's like a dragon
Right ahead
Oh shit, where do I go sniping at this close of range?
Oh shit what happened no tail whip no tail whip no tail whip no tail whip
Oh, jeez, where is she?
No
That hurt
Wait, she flies around spit be flying. Oh my god
On the air
Oh
My god now what
Pick up the fucking bullets
Don't be shy show me your terror
Oh my god, she's gonna get me with that bite. Oh my god, she bit me
You're the one who's cursed that was my favorite character and now she's not even in the game anymore
She was I was just like the weird guy with the hammer and the old lady
Fuck all viewers are gonna leave now
Looks like i'm getting out of this place
Dirty flask. Okay
I feel like I should look around for a second. That was really intense. I mean that wasn't like
Super hard
It was cool. I imagine that on hardcore is probably really hard. They actually left because she's not in the game anymore
Still looking for rose
We're still looking for rose
Still
Finish that item that was requested please deliver to the house with the red chimney go through the caves to the ruins then down to the village
Okay
Scrap now back to the back to the look for the daughter part. Yeah. Oh shit. That's a lot of handgun ammo. I'll take it
I thought it was 41. I'm stupid. Never mind
Let's go. Is it you actually your birthday? It is not my birthday. Don't listen to anybody
They're lying to you
All right. Well, that's where I need to go next
But I do want to see there's anything else here
bridge
All right. There we go. This is with the
Lady, let's go. Am I gonna have to ban happy birthday from this chat? I thought it was a monster
wait
fish
Can I eat this?
Boys together as one within the endless dark deliver us in two fates hands
As the midnight moon as the midnight moon rises on oh, she had to restart her line. We await the light at the end
In life and in death
Grab the hood pull it back look right in her eyes. Remember me remember me
I almost tell me what is going on around here. Can a man be almost whatever it?
That's a question for the wise
See he did it though. You know what I mean, and I still haven't found rose. Where did mother miranda take her?
You're too late
or maybe
Almost too late
The child will be sacrificed life for life. What kind of sick medieval shit is this? She's just a baby
Crest is not just a baby
Will you please stop talking in riddles? I just want to find my daughter
Riddle if you don't know the answer
That looks familiar, why am I letting her just leave hey, hey wait
Why not just swing just roundhouse roundhouse kick this lady in the face?
and when she's like
On the ground be like where's the fucking baby? Tell me winged key
This is an evil witch
Like warlock lady
She's like killing people. She literally is killing me
She tried to kill me that time in the very beginning. Maybe she was like scrape scrape scrape slash
And she like slashed and killed like somebody is the same person
That's the same person that like killed like a bunch of what there was a that was a bad person. There's a bad person
That's not the same person
Didn't she like slash somebody with like a fucking magic wand?
Whatever it's a different person. It has human skulls on her step
I swear to god in the very beginning of the game. She like was walking and tap tap and then she like tried she like slashed us
Oh, this looks great
And this isn't even an rtx on because i'm afraid to overheat my computer
This pattern looks so yeah, this is umbrella
Wait, is this like implying that umbrella has like existed for like 500 years or something?
What year is it supposed to be?
What year is this?
What year is it? It's supposed to be 2021
Oh, um, do I have anything I can put here?
I don't think so
Resident evil 7 takes place in 2017
Oh, it doesn't
Oh my god. All right. I need some more healing. I accidentally wasted a whole healing potion for no reason
It was really dumb
Where'd he go? Oh, I need to make some heals
Oh
Magic goat. I still don't have whatever this thing is
That's been there from the very beginning of the whole game
Bill oh my god bill
Wait, I thought it was gonna be like, oh, who's that?
Never mind just a guy easy
Something. All right, that's where the little turn tourniquet thing is
Um, I kind of don't want to leave yet
There's more money to be made
Yes, that's why I didn't want to leave. I told you
What what is this?
What how do I not have that? It's annoying. This is tomato town. Somebody said this is tomato town
There you are. I had a feeling you would pop up. It was all worthless
Is that so I assume you've picked up something of value
Not sure if it's a value, but
Ah
What are you saying
Was a liquefier rosemary's head
Her head's in there that flask seems to contain her head
Don't say another word
this
This is impossible. He dropped it. This just can't be your daughter's essence is still intact
Her powers are truly unique
Who could even do this? She can be saved, you know
saved
From this are you insane? There's a house with a red chimney on the western side of the village
Go and seek out the man who lives there and we can continue our conversation
Quit holding out and get to the damn point. He lives there. You don't have to trust my words
But do you have any better options?
your choice
The customer is always right
after all
I'll give you 20 bucks if you drink pickle juice. Hey, if I find out this is a lie
Titans
Goes here well, I have a lot of stuff to sell choose something for you louie anderson
Oh, wow, 25 000
Beautiful even in death that waistline. Yes. Yeah, he put something on that. He put a little twist at the end
I think it's just kind of tomato tomato at this point
There's another tier of upgrades
I'll take it. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
30 000 for extra baggage pipe bomb recipe
pipe bombs mines
Rifle customizable part for sniper reduces weapons sway while aiming
I mean should I even do this?
I saw you eyeing that handgun ammo. You need handgun ammo. I have a lot. How much do I have?
I see anything else. There's just a waste of money
One moment, please. I have a handgun veteran
You have a typewriter? Yeah, you do
Hold the fish
That's the plan. All right, go to that house over there up on that hill over there
Where where does he find the house with the red chimney? So we gotta go this way and find a house with a red chimney
Anything else I miss anything?
the
Decorated crest with four wings
Oh, I want you know, I want to look at the baby thing
specimen
I think the only door I can go in is the one that i'm currently going to yeah. Okay
Let's go find the red chimney
I almost was like, oh I found it. That's a red door
We load everything just in case I get
lapsed on
You know, I do appreciate this game. Ooh
Ooh, okay. Cool. We're going this way. Wait. Ooh, this is the first area. All right, let me go
Let me go around and just start opening shit. Let's go this way
I like that. They kind of went back to like the village era stuff. I like that. I think it's cool
Do I have any lockpicks?
I don't think so
I do actually
Reminds me of resident evil 4. It's like a first person resident evil 4
Which is pretty cool. I like it said the game name. I did say the game name. You're right. That's seven bullets. Holy shit
Okay, that's good
Anything else in here? No play postal two
Postal two not portal to one. I think you were talking to somebody in chat and I just answered
All right. Wait, there's something else in there
What else could possibly be in here?
Fabled monster wolves of old may they come eat our flesh. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
They're a diamond here
missing
Oh, it's 500. All under the bed. Okay, I got it
Clear. All right. We're gonna take a right
There's the house of the red guy. All right, I found it. There it is
This isn't open
Okay. Well, here's the house
Walk from the other side. Okay. Well now what?
What the fuck to go all the way around? That was a pretty chimney was pretty. Yeah
Okay, settle down
No pain. Nope. Everything's locked from the other side
What is that?
I climb this
How do I go?
Through here
Let's go. He's on the grind
I can't go that way
There's stuff in here
I heard a scream from the house with the chimney. I was going to take a look but the way was blocked by debris
Going to have to take the long way around
Who would have thought the hole in the stable walls would come in handy?
If i'm not back by morning, you should go to louise's house
On the stable walls, he said portal makes him feel sick. It does
Oh it does
It makes me feel like shit when I play it
Debris
How would you say it?
The different debris debris
debris
wooden animal body
Uh, is the plural of debris debris's or is it just debris?
debris's
Debris
You're lucky I didn't say debris to make you all fucking flip out
Okay, that's a little shortcut good
It's in here anything there is
Anything nope, okay, we need to go to the house with the chimney
And seek out the raven or whatever his name is
You could possibly move this somehow
You can move the tractor with something. What's this doing here? What is that doing there?
crazy frog moment
Do not enter do not enter crazy frogs workshop. Well, what's in the workshop?
What's going on
I love that so much. It's like my favorite thing in the world. So what's going on is my favorite sound effect
I think
It's up there. It could be it's really high. Whatever it is
Uh, this is a guy. It's like iron man
Look out the window. Whoa
Which one there's three
Is it four thousand?
I don't know. This is the escape room
Look out the window
Sorry, sometimes it gets a little weird like that. Okay. Oh four we got oh seven. Oh seven. Oh four. Oh eight
Oh seven. Oh, how many numbers are there?
One two, three, four five. There's six numbers. So it's oh seven. Oh four. Oh eight open and
It is an m 1911
and
a jack handle
That's a new weapon. Hold on a second
Holy automatic handgun. This thing's fucking awesome. All right, I want to put this equip this
Shortcut to here. This is it. Nice. Okay, cool
Holy automatic
It is whoa. What that's weird. I don't know if i'm gonna like this
I'm, not sure i'm gonna actually like this
All right, let's go back to the well over here
what
Shoot him with some shoot somebody
What am I doing?
I don't notice my voice is going like a lot recently. You notice that when I get really excited. It's like
It's really I don't know what's going on I think i'm getting older
He's some kind of item I think I have I have one and he's an other item don't I have one
It's like it's the jack, right?
I'm gonna have the jack this seems some kind of other item. I don't understand
Oh, maybe it's for the tractor. Yeah, it probably is for the tractor. You're right. All right, let's go
It's locked from the other side
Get up
All right. This same guy is just following me and pretending to be dead in different places
No, I feel I feel like i've seen this guy lying down dead like at every other scene not anymore
What the fuck the guy's fucking following me around
What the fuck my girlfriend's sleeping. You woke her up
Dude, we watch together
What are you talking about?
Well, what you're not watching together now, are you?
These sounds are so loud. It's so loud. Isn't it?
This game's too it's too loud for you guys a big strong loud blow up explosion noises happen all the time
I keep looking over here and i'm getting just drowned out. No, you know what it is
It's this
That's the problem. Okay. Now i'm good. I'm good now this can come back up. All right turn on rage
All right, I will turn ray tracing on
Like it I didn't see this guy
Fully automatic I wouldn't classify. This is fully automatic. All right, go this way. Wait, hold on any items
It's fully completely semi-automatic. It's fully completely kind of semi-automatic
I realistically I probably shouldn't even use it though
Because this is more powerful and until I upgrade it. It's probably not worth using the bullets with it, right?
Theoretically is a pig of animals nice in this game
All right, it's fine. It's fine. It's fine. I mean it didn't even hurt me
I'm not I don't have to kill it. Is it do I have to kill it? What can I feed it?
You eating the blood
You like is it good? It's a good pig. I pet him. He was just scared. I didn't know why would I shoot it?
I don't know nothing in here. Whatever. Okay. Well, I don't have a lot anymore lockpicks. So I got a
Chicken over there. Wait, why are these listed here? Why is there a chicken here? All right. I need to go to the chimney house
Where is it? It's over here. Go this way. All right, I gotta go back here. It's meat. Wait, I actually get meat from the pig
Really? You shitting me? Did I actually do that? Don't kill it. But I mean is it does it actually help?
You know, you're not gonna do the same thing, right? I don't want to kill the pig. It's gonna give meat
Pick a blt
I can't do it. I'll rather have a harder game. I can't do it. He's just hanging out. There's nothing. What did he do?
What did he do wrong? He rammed you. No, I startled him and then he freaked out
He had he ran at me because he was scared
All right. Here we go
You're on the roof. You're on the roof. Okay
That actually does that make them? Oh my god, i'm trying to shoot them both at the same time
He slipped he just slipped and exploded his head on the ground
I feel like I didn't even do that
All right. This is the house, right? No, it's not but might as well just look around
White bomb good
You'll kill zombies, but you won't kill the pig. The zombies are actively attacking me to trying to kill me
The pig ran by me and screamed
If that pig kept attacking me, you better believe I would have
That guy looks a little different
Is that hurting him? Holy shit. That guy took a lot of hits
perfect crystal skull
It's man bear pig
It kind of looks like what's that sign say lock due to missing homeowner. Hold on not yet open this
Oh, where's the door closing? Was the door closing? Whatever. Okay. I want to open this
Use the fucking knife. I have guns. Why would I use a knife?
Finally, I have the wheel well it took long enough took five plus hours into the game to get this item
All right. I'm gonna
I want to go use it
Back here, right?
All right, there's one well here
Are they only two
It's three. All right. I want to get all the wells
wheel
Where is it?
Where are you?
That's what the pig is. This is wrong
Go go go go go go
right
Yes
Underneath we're gonna have to crawl underneath here. Kill the pig. I'm not killing the pig. It's not gonna happen
I'm not killing any of the animals unless they attack first
except for the fish because I thought they were mutants
wheel well and
Lockpick, okay, there's one
Wait, do I need to pick it back up? No, all right. The second one is
this way
Can't open that. So where's the other one if I go?
Down and then to the right
I go this way. What's over today? Did I do this?
Yes
Well is over here down here
well
Where is it? Where's that? Well behind me. Yeah
shotgun
Wooden head. Oh, I got the I have a wooden body and a wooden head
I can bind them. I can complete the wooden goat now. Okay, do it
nice
Wooden goat very valuable
there's
Another one up here
Shit, I would never would have done that. Huh? A million channel points to turn the stream off. My stream would never turn back on ever again
necklace with two holes
there is
one more well
This way
Five five hours in and he's still in the first area
I like to take my time with the game. I don't want to rush it. I like to take my time
Yeah, I mean this is like the first zone. I didn't
I heard that there's like a like a big lady or something like i'm looking forward to that but I take my time in games
Is that something that's uh, was that bad because i'm taking my time?
I hear a person where are they?
Shit, where is it?
My god, I don't know where he is. Oh my god. I don't know where it is
Oh, it's
All right, well then oh my god the fucking wizard of osbats whatever they are
Oh, they're everywhere. I just want to all right just run
That was 1200 bucks
I died just I don't what's that? What is that? What is that necklace?
Close the door
God god god
In the bathroom with me
Can I get the money through the wall? I don't know a crystal wing got it
I'm gonna make a shitload of money. Oh my god. This is so much money
Okay, I need to get through here can I climb this let's say I can go through that
That's weird, right?
Explosive rounds
I'm really glad I came here. This looks like there's a wall here. I want maybe
Magnum ammo, holy shit. Where's the magnum? All right. I gotta run. I don't even know where the hell this is
I actually bait
I go through the shed
My god, I
I'm like map andy. I just keep pressing the map. Where am I map map? Where am I? Where's that map?
Where my map? All right, that's just pig. I don't kill pigs. Don't kill pigs
He's fine. He's fine
Stop, he's gonna try to kill me
He's fine
It was not he's fine
He's fine. He's not he's he's walking around talking and
Wait, there's something on the table
Stop it. Is you get do you actually get meat for doing this? I
I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry any oh, I hate it
I just okay quality meat
Give these to the duke. I have to get I had to do that. I hate that. I'm not doing that again
I didn't like that
I didn't know I did not enjoy that. I didn't like that at all. All right the idea I gotta go this way
At least I picked up a bunch of shit. Nice at the chicken too. I get the chicken. Holy shit. There are chickens
I just closed line to him
I don't want to do that. I hate this. I hate it
I don't like doing this. All right, no more. I can I can live off of this for the next like 10 years
Okay, map andy we're going
Up where's this stupid house?
You can open this door
What's back here?
Okay, I feel like i'm getting a ton of like collectibles and tons of money and stuff
So this is not a bad what i'm doing
Walk from the other side. Okay
You're collecting meat
Sort of yeah
andy andy
Uh, my name is
Need the meat. I just have to whatever i'm doing it. I give it to the guy the guy like I can make like chicken stuff
And I can make chicken
Stop you're making him cry
Okay, no more. I got all the stuff. I have so much stuff now
I i'll come back and do that later for something whatever it is
I got all the all right now. We have to go back to the house with the red chimney
That's the goal. That's what we're doing. That's what i'm doing. I'm going to the house with the red chimney
That's what i'm doing
House with the red chimney is I fuck I've I don't know
Looks like we have to go back this way. It's blocked by trees. We have to go over here
No back through the church through the door down here
It's confusing. It is
It's confusing if you can't read a map
Look, dude
It's like half of these things are blocked half of them are blocked by my it's i'm playing a maze here
It's you have to just one step by step
It's it's difficult. It's not easy to read this half of these roads are blocked. Look, man
All right, i'm going
Down here and then like around here and through here. Okay, straight ahead. Let's go
And it doesn't look like the same thing way that look it's this is it's blocked
This is block. It's blocked up. Okay, so and now I can't go this way
Read the map andy, right? It's blocked half of them are locked from the other side
This is locked
I gotta go through here and then like where the fuck am I going?
I have to get back to like the place with the pig and some places you have to go through houses
Okay, hold on. Can I like get through this way? No, what I all right i'm going down this way and
How do I how did I get here?
Through here through here. This is blocked. I gotta go down. I can't go through here
This way that way this way that way is he high or something this map is fucking this map is dog shit
You can't get I can't give a shit map and then be like why we didn't go to the birthday party
This is because your directions were fucking terrible
Remember back like 20 years ago 15 years ago those of you that drove like 20 years ago 15 years ago
Before gps people used to give you the most absurd directions
Oh at the fourth light you'll look over there'll be a clown and take a left at the clown and there's no clown
There's absolutely no fucking clown and there's like 12 lights and you don't know which one to take the left at
I remember looking at directions that were written out. It was like 75 steps and I I can't go this way
This is locked. Can I like go through here?
And like out that where do I go?
How do I get out of here? I'm fucking trapped
I'm trapped here. There's one little specific route. I have to take through this fucking map
You keep turning at the clown there is no clown this way
No, and I would love to zoom out but I can't everything disappears. All right, settle down relax
I am gonna lose my mind. How do I get over here?
I can't go this way. So I have to go straight and then right and then
Back to where you got the wheel. I have no idea where that is right from where you are now
It's blocked off with a fucking wagon
Flying back under the tractor. I don't even know where that fucking tractor is man. Oh shit
It's like there's a fucking diamond in here teddy bear. I hit the jackpot down here. Okay now
Look at the statue. Nice. There's the red chimney left of the wagon
Where the where is somebody hack my computer and just do it for me. Oh
Why is it this confusing?
This should just be able to walk down the path
Why can't I just walk down a path go through the shack? This shit isn't even on the map
It's not even on the map. Okay. All right
Great. Now I gotta go through this shit and then like back around this
I'm gonna shock out of no i'm not relax
I just walked around in like three circles to do if I could just walk just over here
Oh
And go through the shack which oh
Through the door back to the window. Oh, I've got a little window through the door. Okay
What I fucking made it? I I can't even go in this door. I can't go in here. Oh my god
What is where and climb up the ladder?
You ski what's even in here?
Relax
Yeah, wait, do I have to go back around and get on the ladder again?
Go through the house. Everything's just confusing me. I'm so confused right now
Every door is locked from the how many fucking doors are locked from the other side
Half of the shit in this game is locked. Everything's locked. What are these people doing in their houses?
Maybe that crystal i'm just throwing a fucking grenade into the chimney. All right, I made it i'm in your house
Who's in here? Do you not lock your door?
I what the fuck every door is locked from the other side. Everything's locked
Okay, is somebody this i'm so i'm just where is this person?
Oh my fucking god, it's gonna be like another the winged key is just a single piece three more parts
Are needed to make it a whole. Oh, no wing key is just one single piece three more parts are needed
combined with the winged key
I don't even know what I just did. Damn it. Better see the duke again
Oh god, I have to leave I have to leave I have to get out of the house
I have to go back to the duke
Who is over here? Oh, this is simple. Just walk out the door
Where is he this way?
Over here. All right. I'm good
Oh, you're an idiot. This map sucks. This game sucks. I'm kidding. It's a joke. Relax everybody
How was it? Did you learn anything?
I found these feathers now. Tell me how to fix this like you said you would settle i'm kidding
The game's fun first. You must use that key and collect all of your little roses flasks
Where are the rest of them?
There are four in total
You have the one and the other lords have the rest
lords
Mother miranda is the cold calculating ruler of this village four lords serve under her
The first you've already met the lady demetresque
The second lives deep in a valley of mist the dollmaker donna beneviento
Getting the hub world her playmates have ever come back from that dank old estate
The third is morrow a being of twisted flesh that lives in the reservoir past the windmills
He's pretty weak just one shotgun blast to his face. We'll do it in those waters
The fourth and most dangerous is heisenberg. He works in his factory on the village outskirts
the project
Let's just say parts of the human imagination are better left alone
Oh, okay. So we already claimed lady demetre
Now we need to go
and pick a
Pick some pick one of these turn the lights up. Hold on
If you truly wish to save your daughter, you must first gather the four flasks
I'll do you a personal favor. I've marked the lord's locations on your map
Gonna pee again some treasures still lurk in this village. I'm sure each one will prove of great use to you
Well, thank you. Why are you doing all this?
Maybe it's all part of our first class customer service
Please do come again soon. It's just dark souls now
Um, I have some welcome. Ethan. Ah, yes. I have you cooking find some quality ingredients and bring them to me
large crystal
This is just okay. It's not combinable
Perfect crystal skull very valuable
crystal wing valuable
Necklace with two holes don't sell that
Teddy bear slightly dirty teddy bear the duke will probably buy it. Okay treasure valuable
Wooden goat very valuable. I'm gonna have a lot of money
poultry fish
Okay, sounds good. Wait what expect the teddy bear first. Thanks for thanks for saving me
Thanks for saving me. Appreciate it
Do let me know if you find anything else of value, I thought he was falling over like forward
I was gonna just let him go
Okay, inspect the teddy bear
I don't think it's
naturally
All right. Let's take a look at these upgrades
done smithy. All right, so this is
150 power this is 160 power base
I'm gonna get the suitcase
Sorry speaking to myself there congratulations with this you'll not worry about missing anything
Okay, so this is 170 now. Yeah, i'm gonna use this
Let's do ammo capacity get it up there
Nine reload speed rate of fire the rate of fire is fine. Let's do reload speed leave this to me
Leave everything to me
Okay, and i'm gonna he's probably has something else I want right?
Hi. Oh, there we go. That's cool
Sell the should I sell the pistol the other one?
25. All right. So this one is just
I'm gonna I think of wait. Should I take the recoil off? No
I'm gonna sell this
sell the
limmy pistol
And i'll make some food too. Yeah
I suppose you'd call this
a farewell to arms
All right, the duke's kitchen you kill it we cook it all an investment even oh shit. I i'm this is permanent health increases
This is permanent stuff. You get i'm gonna go why why would I not kill every animal?
Damage taken when guarding decreases permanently increases health permanently
Oh my god, I can't believe that I was so concerned about like killing the pig
All right. Well, um, let's do this one because I can make it
Okay, two two, right? Yes
We've gathered all the ingredients health slightly increased permanently now for the weight. Here's your share
Sounds like you kind of just ate that in front of me
Not a bad dish
Okay, so now
poultry meat, okay, we just kill animals. That's all I need to know. All right, cool
We're gonna increase the rate of fire on this. No, we don't
Shotgun ammo capacity on the shotgun. Yes one moment, please and reload speed. Thank you
And let's make the sniper rifle more powerful. Yes
Sounds good to me. I'm skilled at all sorts of weapons modifications and we'll do them for a small fee
You know what? Let's just just i'm just gonna buy a shitload. Just give me more rounds
What are you eyeing that one have a wonderful adventure? Thank you
Uh, I need to do some organization here
I gotta pee though. I'll be right back pee time. All right
so
Does anybody know i'm assuming i'm probably almost at the halfway point of the game
If I do one of these areas and I get two of four i'm assuming that's probably somewhere around halfway
maybe
so if I get another
piece of
Rose and that would be somewhere with that would be 33 percent
Let's let's we're going here's what we're gonna do
That'd be about 40 percent
Lady dimitrisu is about third of the way through the game. All right, so if i'm gonna get one more piece of rose
From one of these areas and then we'll see where we are, but we will finish it tomorrow
All right. Let me fix my inventory. What's this? Oh shit. This is the extra space. Nice. All right
Well, we're gonna put weapons over here
All guns all weapons all ammo
No, what are you doing? Oh
Okay, that's just to organize. I thought it was an extra backpack
First of all, let me read
Wait, what am I all my weapons are gone
Let me reload everything
Everything reloaded. Yes. All right
Okay, so we're gonna do weapons down here weapons on the right. That sounds good to me
uh, okay
Type bombs up here and the knife will spin it this way up here
This game's really good. I like this game a lot
Turn off your lights. No, but you won't be able to see me
I i'm it'll be just dark
Lights off you're not gonna be able to even see me
You don't want it like this
This sucks
And this sucks to play
I don't like this at all. Actually. I hate this. This is good. It's not good because i'm playing a video game in a dark room
No, i'm putting it back on i'm putting no. No, we're not doing that. It's scare saturdays
Yes, I know
All right. Let me get back to this. I really like this game. I'm gonna give this game an 8.6 right now
At this at this stage right now
It would be like an 8 9 or like an 8 8 at the moment if the fov was scalable
And if I didn't just get stuck and beg somebody to fucking help me
Be an 8 6 at the moment. It's really bad for your eyes. Yeah, I know it is. It's horrible for you
It's like really helpful for you. It's bad for your brain
All right handgun with the handgun shotgun with the shotgun
Shotgun with the shotgun, of course
Handgun with the handgun
This is magnum. I don't have a magnum, but whatever I guess
Uh, we'll put the health in the top right
meat down here
Magnum ammo is gonna go with the pistol just because why not
lock picks up here
explosive rounds
Up here right here. Yeah right here much better. All right, I like it good
But where's the sniper ammo?
I don't have any clean. This is clean. Wait, hold on
That's better. I like that better. Okay
Upright what about I have a magnum. Where's my mag? I don't have a magnum
Okay, that's better. I'm ready. So where should I go?
The treasure over here peaceful. Haley just gives 10 community subs
Thanks for the community subs peaceful. Haley. All right. I said that like let me let me do that better. Thanks for the 10
Community subs i'm not turning
I promised I wasn't gonna get angry. I wasn't gonna get angry today. I already broke that promise like three times
All right
Who do I want to go to?
I kind of want to go to like the weird little doll thing
That's where I want to go. I want to go to the doll
We're an rtx on I will before the stream turns off. I promise. Hey ink cat. Thanks for the five community subs
You know what so
That is up
Here down here. I'm assuming it's probably just up this way
This way dim the lights. I don't have a dimmer. I can't dim my lights
This is a good game though. I like this a lot
So far, this is better than resident evil 7 if I were to give you a comparison so far
Resident evil 7 was really fun for the first like two or three hours and then I kind of just thought the game was boring
This has been consistently still pretty good
All right, here we go. We're going towards
this little doll thing
Please move. I'm gonna get attacked by dolls. Aren't I?
I thought that was a stormtrooper helmet
Like right here. I'm not turning my lights off
No, the lights stay on
Ethan come with me. There's something I have to tell you. Mia. Yeah
What's going on? What's going on?
Don't don't let me I don't want to miss that treasure
Don't let me miss that treasure don't open
Ethan you have to fix her
Okay, i'll try
Heck dude, what the heck is this? Don't be so offensive to me
This can't be real
I'm gonna invest in a lamp you absolute man. I don't want to live recess lighting. I don't want a lamp
All right. Here's the treasure
a
Viento 1987 to 1996 freed from the binds of flesh. She now walks the valley of death
Beneviento's treasure
Losing it. I don't think I can open this yet. I can't open that. I think it probably probably opens when I like kill beneviento
Put it in the mail slot
What's going on? Oh, what the fuck? Okay. That was very strange
Yeah, i'll do this. I'm gonna like make it so the uh
Let me just change this so like the it's not gonna ready
I'll darken it
There i'm making some people go. Okay. All right. Finally finally we can see
Now I well that's just making me look like it's like turning into a silhouette
Should I be like hold on ready?
Hold on. Give me a second
Like i'm i'm like one of those people that's just like blacked out doing one of those interviews
But they don't want you to know who they are, but i'm screaming. I'm a streamer. I just don't want you to know
Okay, so uh
Let's take a uh quick
Okay
That sounds pretty good
Imagine watching
Imagine watching this fucking stream. Hold on
Uh, like like for privacy purposes
That's good
So i'm just gonna stream like that
uh, right, so
Let's go ahead and
Head down this hallway here
You know, I I really would tell you more about like whatever my boss my boss really I could
Just say he was he was a fucking timer
And i'm not saying that because we're playing resident evil
He really was saying he was a timer. He was a terrible guy
You're not gonna we're not gonna use this anywhere, right? We're gonna make you make sure nobody can hear me
Oh, but uh, go ahead that follow button if you uh, if you could
Holy shit, those lights just flickered. Holy shit, man. That was crazy
Am I gonna happen?
Wait, I don't miss I don't miss anything
Come on, I gotta get those items. I gotta get those items, man
Why you why is this happening?
I just I mean we gotta i'm just making sure that I get protected because
No, it was part of a potential. Uh, there was 45 gold bars were stolen
I watched it happen
And I know I know who did it and I just gotta be careful
Okay, what we got here string on the ground
Aaron Aaron Aaron
Aaron
Oh shit, you're gonna know who I am
No, uh what I meant to say was
Um
No, I just you don't know who I am. I'm the secret streamer
Goku somebody's shadow right there. Who's the secret streamer?
That's so stupid
It's like
I don't want anybody to know the fuck I am. Are you kidding me? I'll be dead people are after me
It's a markiplier
Hello everybody, my name is markiplier and today i'm gonna be playing in some resident evil village
I just threw you off. You have no idea who I could be now
Is he is he markiplier? Who is he?
All right, I have to play the game. Uh, when can I turn this off?
This is literally sus. I don't know what that means. I'm not even I don't even play video games
Whoa
My god, that's terrifying
Let me uh here I figured you out. I'm contacting the thieves. Oh, yeah
Oh look at you. Oh look at me. Look at you. You think you know who this is?
What an idiot. What an idiot
It's impossible. It doesn't break what I move this
What the hell is going on in this house? What's happening in here? I feel like this is gonna be a really fun area though
Weird. I don't like oh, I don't like this doll stuff
This doll stuff is really starting to creep me out. I'm gonna get knocked off the table
They're gonna start chasing me and shit. I know they are
Uh, this is looks like corn
Plates
No, nothing even in here
This little doll person is going to be in one of these cabinets, right?
That person's so little they could be anywhere. That's terrifying
Doi doi doi. I don't know what that is
But if I was going to do it, maybe it would sound something like this
It sounds the same
Doi doi doi
Oh, we got him. You just you just roger rabided me
A toon can't resist a toon can't resist a toon of a little jingle
Wait, I need to hold on
Toon can't resist
Goofy, oh Zora
Think fast
How gorge, Mickey?
Uh-oh cracker is back. What makes you think we have a left
Rack evil go. Oh, yeah, I forgot. This is on
All right, whatever. I'm just going
Do arthur do do no, I have a plan
Don't you tell me arthur what we can't do. It's just everybody's i've already did this before
I hate you. I've done this before we've already been here before and I it's not you don't even know who the fuck I am
How many times do I have to do this bit? It's like I get where like a time loop
Okay, I open that. No, this looks like the
Resident evil house from the first game an herb. Oh, it's that thing. It's that corn
Was uh, it's the little doll lady
Uh-oh
No, Jimbo
In fact, have you not done your homework yet?
What are you thinking? Wait, hey, could you make me a little device? I could make you a swim faster Jimbo
I'm like ruining this game. I'm done with this bit. This bit is over. I'm going back to playing the video game. Thank you very much
Wait, hold on. Wait a minute. What did I just do? What does what just happened? I think I broke the webcam
I can't like change it anymore
None of my changes are doing anything
Oh god
You see like the movement just sucks
Well, I look like i'm
Why do I look so weird?
I look like strange. Don't I?
Get an actual camera. It's not my fault
That every webcam has the same technology from like
Okay, is that really my fault?
You want me to get a dslr and like have my room heat up by like another 500 percent
I'm gonna you're gonna you're gonna i'm gonna be hot boxed out of here
Hey jimmy. Oh, it doesn't work anymore. I found the key
It's my items
Where are my weapons?
Wait, the actual escape room
It's really it actually is an escape room
Okay. Well, that's funny. I have the key I have to oh my god. Okay, that's pretty
All right
What else can I do?
I have to remove any legs or anything
Why don't you stay and play with me forever?
deadly nerve agent
bring
Um, I am I taking eyes out? All right, we did pull over. That's gonna jump up. Okay
Okay, i'm in the left eye
Who's that? What is it? Wait, is it me?
Mia
So silver key
The banners are too tough. You need to cut something you need to cut them
Oh, shut up
I already cut them anything else. Can I pull anything else off?
I pull the arm off
Remove arm. Um, okay that way I didn't close the eyes
All right. What the hell was that? It's three closed eyes
Anything else? What about the leg? Pull the leg off
What's in there?
key
winding key
Anything to do with like the foot or something?
the right foot
Well, this opens this door
Bada
Wash this ring
Okay, I get it
Put the ring back on
wedding ring
I love ticking talk clocks locked on the other side. All right, I got a clean. Hold on. Let me reply
All right, talk. I feel like I have a huge on tiktok. You know what you think?
I think I would I would just sit there. I would start trying to I would do like the wisdom volume work
Come on wisdom volume work
wisdom volume wisdom value wisdom volume work
It would explode
everywhere
People would be doing different different
Cosplays and different versions of it and I would just be the original I would I could do it
I would be huge on tiktok
I would be probably I would be the biggest creator on tiktok like 10 years ago if I wanted to go for it
I would be absolutely fucking massive on that website
Think about it. It's like six second short form videos
I just this these streams are like six second short form videos attached together for like six and a half hours
That's like that's what that's all I do
That's what I do. That's fine
That's some volume work. Come on with some while you work
With some value with some value with some while you work
I'm huge
Fuck what I get. All right, what put the wedding ring inside of her mouth?
I need a tool
All right. Let me keep looking around. Let's probably have this shit here
God, I love video games. Oh shit. Okay, so this is
Oh, wait, wait, isn't it three closed eyes?
It's three closed eyes
Oh wait, you know, okay, so it's just okay. I gotta get it. I thought I had to do three eyes around
All right, so that's it
I thought I had to do one one one closed eyes
Stop
Talking to the biggest thing on tiktok right now
Okay
Put it out there now
Somebody keeps breaking shit over there. All right, what's about iron?
Is that the thing I need to take?
All right. Obviously there's more to do here. Okay, I need a tool to
Can't get in the mouth
Finding key
I need to get in the mouth. Okay
What's that? There's a date
05 29 11 got it
This is an it is an escape room. Yes
a nine
It just let me out i'm getting baby flashbacks when the baby ran into the wall in that game
And it was like the funniest thing i've ever seen in my life
It was like
You could have it keep happening
Memento of my time with ethan but this music box no longer plays
No, it wasn't pt. It was um layers of fear
Right. I was like crying on that stream laughing at that
Nothing like a pair of pliers or something on the wall. Come on. Give me something
There's gotta be something in here
There's nothing even in here
What down there? Oh, there's a movie. Okay projector over there. Wait a minute
Can't use that
All right. What's on the movie?
Our happy family rose's best friend in the whole wide world. She really likes this fairy tale
The most important thing in the world to us
A wedding gift from grandma proof of ethan's everlasting love for me
Well, I have like one of those pieces
Oh, hold on
alkaloids of mountainous plains
That's her favorite story alkaloids of mountainous plains. That's her favorite story
baby
wedding ring
Read a book and then was a coffee maker at five. I don't know what that is
He gets every word wrong
What is in here it's alkaloids of of the plains or something whatever it is that's like your favorite book
alkaloids of mountainous plains plants
Right. It's the plant. Okay, so whatever what what is this thing? Okay, well, there's nothing else in here
I'm leaving what about the music box music box. I can't do anything with this in the last room
There's a clock
I walked around this whole room. This one. I this is this could be a fucking toaster. Okay, how do I open it?
Damn it. He's not right. Thank you. Queezers take the thing out of the mouth
You put it in emote only mode to make me suffer. It was just it was just a wind
It was just a wind guys. Whatever. It doesn't matter. Wheezer is all right. What is it? It's a piece of film
Okay, we're gonna put the film. I know i'm getting close
Getting close put the film in the projector here comes more scary
It's really easy pt
Don't touch that dial. We're just getting started
Okay, what was it our favorite thing our okay
Select film looks like it's not in the right order rose's best friend in the world. That's the the doll
Likes this fairy tale the book most important thing in the world to us
Money a wedding gift from grandma wedding ring proof of ethan's everlasting love for me money
Right just didn't process any of that
Okay
favorite fairy tale
Grandma's ring the most precious thing in the world play that movie. What's wrong with it?
Favorite toy favorite story grandma's ring
Favorite toy favorite story most important thing in the world is baby. Okay, I got it. I wanted to grab it there done
Don't watch this whole movie. You're gonna get a phone call and you die in seven days
There's a well and then go into the well. Oh jeez
Oh jeez
Give me those. I didn't see this. This is fucked up. All right, where am I now telephone?
It's gonna ring in a second. I'm gonna have to answer it. Aren't I?
Hold on chug break
And for now everybody for your viewing pleasure
I am going to sing hold on and for your viewing pleasure
I am going to drink this water while singing chug chug by that kid that made that video
Don't believe me. Just you wait and see
That was really hard. You guys like it yet
All right. Nobody on the phone. Yeah
I didn't want to lose you again. I didn't want to destroy this family. Mia. What are you talking about? I love you both
so much
I had to I had to do it
Run, uh, I don't know. I think it's bitten the depression
Oh, it's a baby. Somebody's in there
Okay, I need to
Oh shit. Okay. This is the door. I couldn't open before wow
Every door has a fucking unlock mechanism from the other side. I just saw a person
Hey, don't do that
Is there gonna be a baby in here?
It's not right
Okay, I thought I was gonna have to take like a baby
All right is that
you know, I
I gotta tell you I have a little bit of an issue with this part of the game
This is just the same. This is like the same exact thing that happened in resident evil 7
It's like oh like the puzzle weird like escape room guy
Like they're kind of just doing that again
Wait, i'm gonna save it in a while
Why why is everybody doing?
Look, I understand the baby rage from the first 20 minutes of the stream when I was screaming fuck capcom into the camera
And yeah, I know i'm noticing a trend here
I'm gonna run out of companies to like hate
In the next like, you know every week. It's another one. It was nickelodeon
capcom
Nintendo
I I just
I'm gonna run out of things to dislike
And maybe it's me, you know if you what if I hate everything
Isn't it just me? Is it? I i'm the problem
And he looked over there and then he looked this way
I guess i'm just going in
Yeah, it's still an emote only i'm assuming there's something really really ridiculous is gonna happen here soon
breaker box key
Is it?
Believe that's it
Don't lock me in here
Where's my baby?
I get it. Yeah, I know it's me. All right, I have the breaker box key now
Hey, hey, let me in there
Hey, let me in there
Oh, what the heck what the heck goodness
flawed
What's that? Oh my god, something's in there. What is that? What is that?
What is it doing?
What I don't know what it is. He put it what I don't know what it is. Oh my god
I don't know what it is. I don't know what's going on
Is it a baby?
Oh my god, it's a baby. It's an evil baby
That's fucked up. That's
Fucked up. Yeah, that's that's really that's really twisted
Oh, I hate it. I hate that. I don't like this. Oh boy
Oh goodness. Oh goodness
Oh goodness, I don't like oh goodness. He's coming over here
Oh god. Okay. It is the thing I have to push this into
It's over here
Open the door get me the fuck out of here. That was that was really really scary
I did not like that at all
did capcom just
Play pt and then go. Yeah. Well, that's never getting fucking made. So let's go ahead and make something like that
That was terrifying. I just hated that mama dad. Yeah
That was well, I can't even tell you I hate it
It was just
I don't like how quiet this is. It's very quiet right now
I don't want to go under the bed. I don't want to go under the bed. I don't want to go under the bed
my god
Oh my god, I have to hide under the bed
Fuck I gotta do my hair for this. What did I pick? What did I get a fuse?
Oh, yeah. Yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah under the bed under the bed go go go go go go under the bed under the bed right now
Something in here
Oh, man
I have to go in
Under the bed under the bed larry larry get under the bed under the bed
You was the guy from wild thornberries
Just get in here. Oh my god. Oh my god. It's just a baby though. Remember
It's just a baby
That's just a baby. It's a this is just a baby though, right?
It's a very weird baby
That's it. It doesn't know any better. It just thinks that you're uh, okay, go go go go go
I don't like this. What am I? How do I get out of here?
and then um
Shit shit
Can't get up here, right? There's no way you're up here. Are you up here?
Are you up here? How could you possibly gotten up here? It's impossible for you to have gotten up here
Not even physically possible
It's physically impossible for you to have gotten up here
Where's the hidden secret compartment? Where's the compartment? Where's the secret hidden compartment? Where's the secret compartment? Where's the compartment? He's right there
Holy shit, okay, go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
Oh my god
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I agree mama
The aliens that would find us what are they gonna think about us? What are they gonna think about us?
They're gonna think we're fucking insane
Why would we do this?
Is this like some weird ritual like why are we doing this?
Oh my god run
He's genuinely scared. This is horrible. This is terrible. He needs to come down here
And then I gotta wait. What is wait? What if he's over here?
He thought he thought wait
Okay, okay
Okay
But the button didn't get pressed
Close it close it close it close it close it close the door. Holy shit. That was fucking horrible
Back. Oh, that's okay. That's just harley quinn
Oh, dr. J
Find me
There you are
No
You it's one of these little fucked up dolls. Are you?
Found you
It's uh, this is too much stimulation. It's too scary stimulation. I don't like it
It's too much it's too much scary stimulation fucking elevator
Which one of us is laughing like you I don't know
I hear you you it's you
Where is she?
Ah got you got you there you are got you. It's you. It's you I got you
You
God damn it. I have no health guys guys
There are like a thousand little dolls screaming my ears laughing at me. I just escaped a fucking mutant baby
I'm sorry. I can't find the doll immediately
I found her
Oh
Yeah, she didn't say oh come find me upstairs by the way
No, it was just like i'm laughing with my voice. My voice is gone. Oh, man
It's over. This is my career's over
My voice is gone. I was screaming
Okay, oh my god, this is bad
Oh, well, I gotta take the opportunity to do something cool here
Who sounds like this somebody talks like this somebody actually sounds like this who sounds like this somebody talks like this
Marge no marge doesn't sound like this. Oh homer. Yes, she kind of does
I didn't I thought I didn't know I was looking for her. I thought I was looking for like her spirit or something
shit
Hey
I can't listen to this
This is like tts
All right. Well, at least I know where the first one is
All right
All right, she's upstairs
All right, the next one is where I don't know
All right go
Downstairs are you in here?
Why would you be in there? Why would you be in there?
Oh shit. Oh god. Damn it
Blood on the ground blood blood on the wall
Well this way blood
Where where where where where where are you? Where are you? Where is there was blood?
There was blood over there. Did I lose the trail? Did I lose the trail already?
Did I lose the trail?
I think I lost the trail. There's no blood on the wall anymore
Fuck i'm just muting it. It's fucking annoying. I've muted it. Damn it. Fuck you. All right, turn it back on
It's dabbering ahead
What are you doing to my cute friends
That was it's over
That was horrible. Yeah, i'll make things right
What that area was fucking awful?
I need to get out of this place. Oh my god. That was terrifying and loud and annoying and lots of sounds
I got the key
Okay, touch a button on it or something
I'm good
So that's who was behind all this
I'm good. I'm good. I'm all right. That makes two
I'm not done. I'm good. I'm good. I like this is fun
Angie
All right
I got two
pieces of rose
Now I can get oh I get the treasure
This is gonna take me back up, right? Yeah
I've been alive for like 10 hours. No, I haven't
Been like six and a half seven
I need a bathroom break
All right
I want to get some water because I've apparently blew my voice up. Hopefully it doesn't stay like this
I'm supposed to scream. I'm supposed to be screaming tomorrow
I'm getting old man
like really
I can't even like
Yell about video games anymore
I want the treasure. Oh, no put the doll here. Where is she? Where's angie?
What wait did I not can't use that here examine the doll that would make sense
Wouldn't it it's like a button take like the head off pull like a leg off?
I don't understand. What do I do?
Stop press e
I don't think that does anything
Shit, so what am I supposed to put here? Oh, that would make so much sense if I just put the doll there
Well, what the I don't know
All right, we're going back and
Damn it. I really wanted that
I didn't fire a single weapon. That was that whole time
Now we are firing weapons, aren't we?
You can die. How many people are?
my goodness
All right. I gotta sell an upgrade because I have a lot of money
How much to reload reload what okay, so
Hey, hey
Hey
What's this?
Oh shit, it's a new gun. I don't want to use it yet
nice mine
lockpick
Whatever free kill and i'll take it
I dropped a gun. No, I didn't I just picked up a new one
All right, powerful widespread pump action combat shotgun
Very cool
All right. Nothing else here
I can go
Hold on nothing
Nothing
Whatever. All right
Oh, yeah
2000 bucks. I'll take it
Need to get a ray gun
I need to get water when I get i'm gonna let me get back to the the hub because this is going
This wraps around
Hold on. Let me see where this goes
It's like go
Yeah
Yes, there we go. Oh, I thought that was a bird cage. Damn it
Hyper focused andy. Oh
Uh, i'm trying to just leave to go get a drink
I'll be fine. Once I drink some water. I'll be back to normal. Just you watch
Finish it tomorrow
Um, I I probably will but i'm i'm good. I'm still having fun. I'm still going
Having a good time
You're a sponge. I know
I still like it. I'm still having a good time. So i'm gonna keep playing
Ooh, nice
I'll be honest with you. I'd rather do like eight nine hours tonight
What does that go then?
Uh
Have like seven or eight hours tomorrow if that makes any sense
What over a strange bird?
The blue bird
Is that is it? Do I put that down? Do I put the head down?
Shit
I think spherical. Oh, there's like so many of these little spherical things and I can't do any of them
Luthier is key. I don't sleep yet. If you want to keep going. Yeah, i'm good
Mistress donna is now mother miranda's adopted daughter and all my years have never been this overjoyed. There's a lot to read
Somebody will read it someday
Something else still in here. It's that
Okay
what else
Fully explored this zone
Let's go give places to be
Oh, okay another hour
Another one hour
And i'm good just beat the game
Oh, I don't I think it's gonna it's like I think there's at least another four or five hours left in the game
If I would assume
Where are you? Well, it's like probably three or four
um
Give me that whatever
Somebody's I think somebody's behind you. Holy shit. Where did you come from?
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I've had enough. I've had enough of you
I
missed a
Bofa
Oh, I didn't
Didn't even get a chance. All right. Finally I have returned. All right, let's sell wait. I can can I combine anything?
I need health. Let's do the smart thing. Let's make some shotgun ammo
um my handgun ammo
Another health. All right. I'm good to go now. Does this look familiar to you 28 000. Holy shit
combineable
Combineable don't do that. All right, so let's go. Ah, miss angie
Just adorable porcelain dolls are very popular, you know
All right, so this is definitely just gonna be better than the shotgun. So let's upgrade it
one moment 840
Okay, ammo capacity. Let's get that up
I'm gonna sell the other shotgun. Yeah, because that's okay 720
Go to 800
It's got nine capacity. This has six capacity
Yeah, i'm gonna i'm just gonna sell it. Can I take that off?
Or is that just for this weapon?
Please do take a look at my new stock
Pretty nice. Yeah sell it. Do take care selecting your weapons
I got plenty of money. Let's upgrade this too
Uh ammo capacity one moment, please
Rate of fire the rate of fire on this is terrible. Let's do power though
High magnification scope
Yeah, I saw you all right. You got anything else here explosive rounds flash bangs
Type bombs call me moron doesn't matter
Yeah, I don't care I just want more thank you for your purchase
Good day, then
Let's put that thing up here
So this thing is a combat shotgun very cool. All right looking good
All right. I'm gonna get some water. I'll be right back this last break of the
the night
We're gonna see if I can get to like through one more area
so then tomorrow
I can come back and
Finish it in a few hours. So we're going
Down here. I'll be right back final break
Okay
Oh, I feel so much better. I just somebody said I was a sponge
Yeah, pretty much
Oh, I feel like a thousand times better
Do you want to know how hot it is in here?
And so it's been like seven hours, right?
How much is in here? This is a quart of water
This would be the third quart of water i've drank today
It's kind of crazy if you think about it. Okay, so to go down
Let's go to go this way, right?
Because we need to get to this guy this like igor guy
We're gonna go down
I need to save it. I'll be drinking a gallon a day. Uh, I don't know about that
I don't know about that
How'd you find the doll section?
horrifying frustrating terrifying
very very very scary
Frustrating is not even the right word. It was like the the doll part
Um
What the fuck well
I go run. I the wounds are severe. I won't last much longer. I can hear it shuffling about outside
It barely flinched when I shot it. I feel like it's toying with me. That isn't a wolf
Still I won't lie down like a dog if I can get to the old water mill. I can stop it
I can protect you. It's so close damn. I'm so close. My legs don't work
Get to the old water mill
Okay, sure thing get to the water mill
Oh my god, i'm gonna have this sucks
Can you jump up here? I don't think you can jump up here, right?
All right. What's the plan? Let's plan plan is to go through that door
Wait treasure
I don't help make a noise chicken scrap. Can you break that? I don't know maybe
Shut up. Quiet
Dude, so when did this game become like the scary monster just finds you game? Okay, then i'm going from here into this building
I needed I needed I need a route. I need a route. I need a plan
There's a person in this one
Hey
All right, we're good that person just prone in like call of duty twice accidentally
Okay, can I break this?
Why does this looks like it's here for a reason doesn't it? I don't know what it's here for but
Whatever. Is he not okay? I can't go through this
Like there's weird like poison over there. So I have to go
Straight across here. What's in here anything? It's a safe house. There's a treasure in there
Damn it. Can I get there from here? I think I hear him behind me running. Do I hear him running behind me?
No, that's the water. That's the water. That's the water wheel. Oh, man. Oh, man
I don't know what that is, but that's a that's a rocket launcher. It's a grenade launcher
Holy shit. All right inventory management
Heals. All right, bring this down here explosive rounds pipe bombs
I don't have a magnum fine. Get that over here. I don't like this. This is gotta go up top
You gotta do it in order of the of appearance
Shotgun looks better. All right, let's put that here. Okay. So now I have a
Oh shit
Should I just blow him up? Can I just kill this thing like just by killing it like attacking it?
Or should I just not be an idiot and do do it do the way that I think i'm supposed to do
It's clean. You can kill it
You can kill it. It's not that crazy. All right, let's just fuck him up
You suck at gaming. That's not the question I asked
Let's just send him to hell
All right. Where's the where's the plan here? The plan is unlock this door first of all
I can't
Wait, it didn't say I can like kill him at the water wheel. Just don't miss
I'll try not to
I'm gonna let's go i'm getting him. I got a new shiny rocket launcher. I'm gonna shove this into his mouth
What's the trajectory like? I don't know
Where the hell is he? How many more how many more another one you want another one? How's that?
Wow
This is like wario like waluigi
That hurt me
Got him crystal beast. Oh nice. All right, he's dead. That wasn't that bad. It was way
That was yeah, he's dead
crystal beast nice
Okay. Now we just I can I can just walk through without any problems at all
I got the grenade launcher. I'm
We just get this way
wait
Yeah, what are the other treasure?
Yeah, let's go
Yeah, we're gonna slimy substance looks breakable
Nothing else, right? Yeah, we're good. Remember the ego man has a ps4
I don't blame him for having a ps4. It's not worth getting a ps5 yet
Probably won't be for like another year
Talk from the other side. All right, I gotta kill these pigs
Follow me it's because they're still releasing games with ps4
Most things that come up ps5 just come up ps4. Anyways, don't they still?
It's like three or four games you can only get on ps4 right ps5, right?
Yes, I mean maybe like in a year. They'll have a bunch of stuff. Yeah, that's good. I didn't say the ps5 sucks
Don't hurt me. All right. I got it. I have all right. We got to do it
I just I want it's permanent health upgrades
I hate doing this but it's for huge upgrades
photo of a rare animal
That's the white pig that I didn't kill
I shotgun him in the head once
And let him live
I don't think I I don't I know I don't think I killed it
God damn it. I don't think I did
I did kill him. Are you sure?
I don't think I did
This stuff too. I don't I don't get what this stuff is for
You definitely killed one pig. Yeah, but it wasn't like the rare pig
All right. Well, I have to go get this thing from the there's definitely like a
Just the thing I gotta get down here. It's like a laboratory down here
Or I gotta get like the thing to open the door to go to the laboratory and then shoot igor in the head
You got it, let's go
I shot him with a pistol. Did I?
All right question
How far in the game am I right now?
percentage wise
More than a little bit more than halfway
45 50 percent
55. Okay. So after I do this portion, I'll be about 60 percent of the way
All right, let's see it. All right, cool. We'll see how I feel. I don't know
All right
the labyrinth puzzle
Of course, it has to be a fucking puzzle. Doesn't it?
Reload get rid of these boogers, right? Can't get rid of these boogers. Why not? Oh, I can just walk by them
Yeah, yeah, you can't take it master. Yeah, it's mine pretty good igor. I'll tell you
I'll just be taking this
She's not hers what do you mean mother's special child
Don't screw with me
I love this guy. What's so funny? You're stupid
What are you
I won't let you be shit. This is my territory
And I won't let you leave
I gotta tell you I have an announcement to make you know, I you know, i'm an actor
This isn't me. I didn't do this one
I did an ipad game though like 12 years ago
All right, well whatever man, hey, I can't let you leave
Oh
I wish you would say ow
Oh that hurts
Oh
How do I get out of here?
Like this
You just did
I think no engine not no, I don't want to do that yet. I want to open this that guy sucked
I don't think that's the last that we're gonna see of him. Okay
I'm pretty sure that guy is the main antagonist for the remainder
I think the boat key
Oh, it's a giant swamp. Uh
Where's the boat key? I have to go back in here
No, no, no, you can't leave you need to get the book
Oh, no, you can't leave you need to get the boat key
To the canoe that's outside
Oh, you can't just swim in that water. It might be poisonous
Come on
This is fucking boat key break the wood
Didn't I try that before I tried to break yellow wood before and it didn't work
I don't know member. I tried to slash it and it didn't work
Oh my god, what kind of fucking super mario bullshit is that?
No, the earth moves
the earth moves
That's from that jeb from smite. What a great game. That one is my favorite character
Don't let him scream
Good night looking for a boat key to get out of here
Okay
Nope. Oh man. It's one of these guys
Oh, it's a lot of people. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, is he coming all the way around?
Is he coming around?
He can't go around Kenny. He can go around. Oh my fucking god. Oh god
Oh shit. Okay. Well
How did you miss
Ron I can kill this guy
I'm trapped in here. I'm trapped in here. I'm trapped in here. I'm trapped in here. Can I kill him? I think I killed him
Did I punch him?
Nice all right, reload everything did I get everything
No
Weird tree great. Ooh handgun ammo and boat key, right looking for a boat key boat key
Where is a boat key? Looks like a boat key, doesn't it?
Very cool. All right, there's still stuff here, but whatever somebody else will find it boat key for boat doors
Uh
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
Nice work boat. Oh god
Hi
All right boat key for the boat door, but hold on a minute. I'm happier now. I got a lot of health
Did you refill this from the tap? This is yeah, I refilled this
Well, i'm obviously gonna go get the chest
Never mind
Somebody said
Minecraft boat physics
That's pretty good. That's funny
It really is minecraft
Oh god, not another giant monster to attack you wait
I can go through that. Oh my god. Don't even tell me I can go through that
I'm gonna puke if I keep doing that. I'm actually gonna throw up if I do that anymore
I'm actually gonna throw up now
All right disembark everything reloaded seems like it
Very good. Let's go
Research post or something. What the fuck are they doing here?
Chris
It's chris redbuilt. No, it's hunk
Stay the fuck down
Ethan I gotta say i'm surprised you made it this far
It'd be a shame if something happened to you now
So chris, why not?
You killed mia now do me and finish the job
Hey cap, i'm getting some serious motion readings out here. We should move on
What kind of readings
What's moving unknown, but my guess is we've been here too long and miranda knows it. Hey. Hey, do you say miranda?
How are you involved leave it alone? Ethan you are out of your depth
What about the sample analysis? I don't know why you put on an australian accent
No, I hate when you do the fucking australian accent
You stay out of our business
Why did he save me oh my god is chris not a bad guy
Why did he save me
Is that him stay back?
Wait, that's him
I don't have time for this
His voice got deeper
What are you talking about
I
Just have like a long night of partying
That was like the couch. Oh my god
I am running
What am I supposed to do?
Yeah, I don't know down here
It knows you killed the fish
Why did you kill those fishes?
There was no reason for you to do that
Those were my friends
He said the exit's underwater
He's just a giant fish guy
All right. Well, he's just a big fish
Oh, no, okay
Red red all the way down
Oh, it's this guy. Okay
How do I get in that room?
Oh, that's okay
Hi
If it's just looking window shop away
crystal fragment perfect skull
Crystal beast that is yeah, so that was worth it killing him
This should be enough. All right. I did get some new shit though. Let's see
Yeah, I can't upgrade the grenade launcher. That's annoying
Pay me no mind. He's selling these food
Okay, hold on
Great leaders his recoil
his recoil
Hmm. I mean, I don't know
Oh, it's because they have all their upgrades that makes sense
I feel like I should get the shotgun thing
What do you think?
Should I just save money?
I don't really even need it though. I don't I really don't need it
Maybe uh crafting explosive rounds. Yeah, that's
Uh-huh
Have the grenade launcher
I'm skilled at all sorts of weapons. I'll save my money and we'll do these come again
Metal scrap herb and a gunpowder is to make an explosive round
Yeah, i'll do it
Does the duke sell catboy suits?
save save
Save yes, I will
Yes, I will
Good. Uh, I think i'm ready to keep moving
There's a weird puzzle here. I have to do
If I can drain the water
Shit, there's no power. Of course not
We're on the electricity to the sluice gate
All right, let's go
Look the meat
Very very very good idea. Thank you
You wish to make a purchase?
This one is
Oh, I can't do it
Ah shit, I need fish health increases permanently
I need juicy game
Okay, I need
I need fish
I need
Okay, I need two more chickens
or
I need four fish. I'm going for four fish
I'm sure i'm gonna get him in this level. Are you sure you have everything? That's him. What are you talking about?
All right, turn on the electricity
Which i'm kind of just going the other way. I have to go this way, right? Can I?
Wait, I'm losing my i'm losing my place here. I gotta go this way
All right up. Let's go around into the outhouse cool
Good very good
This crank is old and busted up. It feels like it's going to snap any second
I hope it doesn't break. The only other one we have is at the windmill over at windmill two
Well, where's when this is windmill one? Where's windmill two?
over there
gonna break
Seriously
Why would it have not broken? Of course, it's gonna break
There are chickens go back
And I think i'm gonna officially call it
Starting to get really tired. I'm starting i'm starting to like i'm starting to get tired
I will be back here tomorrow
Uh, let me do let me actually do this first. Let's go get the chickens. Yeah, i'm getting tired
I can feel it waving over me and i'm not I don't I we'll just pick up tomorrow. So theoretically
I should tomorrow as long as I don't
stall andy
I should be able to
um
Did you survive the gunshot?
Oh my god kills chicken
I think I have enough another fan's not gonna work tomorrow. Do not jinx me like that, please
I I should be at like the halfway mark. You think i'll be able to do it tomorrow?
If I do like another solid like five to six hours tomorrow, you think i'll finish the game. I should I should right?
I get this guy the hammer guy and then whatever the last part of the game is. Yeah. Yeah, that's
It's easy as long as I don't delay andy. Yeah, I won't
Yes, I thought he was eating that book, okay good let's make it damage taken when guarding decreases permanently or wait
I'll still have enough to do this, but i'll need more meat to do this one
I don't I don't think I I don't I don't think i've guarded once
So i'm not gonna use it. I'll use it later
All right, save the game
What time tomorrow we're gonna start around 2 pm tomorrow 2 pm pacific
I like starting with the car games later because then like it goes into the night time and
2 pm. Oh rtx, right? We'll do rtx
Let's see what it looks like
rtx on
Look, I turned this down because I was scared ray tracing. Let's go. It worked ray tracing on. Hi. Hi
Here we go
ray tracing on
Did I not apply it?
I need a light source
Is this doing anything?
I mean that's like kind of cool
Restarted yeah, it's because there's no like shiny floors. I need a shiny floor to look at
Yeah, there's no shiny floor to look at
Eh streaming at 720. We're not gonna see anything. Actually, let me see if I can get that for tomorrow, too
Shoot the gun
Whoa, look at that
Was it doing that before?
I don't it may have actually been doing that before
I don't think anything changed
Just don't save it
All right
Uh, we'll try to finish it tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow at two o'clock
Yes
Ray tracing looked good
Yeah, I think would be probably you'd want to do that in like the mansion
Actually, hold on
This is the castle, right? I'm actually i'm curious. I want to I want to see
I want to see what it looks like
Okay ray tracing is on
Okay, that actually looks pretty fucking cool
It actually does
Look really good
That looks really nice
Don't let the the auto save might mess up. Oh shit. Will it?
No, it's not gonna fuck it up, right?
Yeah, we're good. Okay
all right
Let me see if I can do uh
I'm gonna try to go to 900p
If I can
So tomorrow if all goes to plan this will be a 900p stream
Because I got an I got I gotta be careful though. I I got a replacement of the fans
Even this looks good, too
All right. Well, thanks for watching. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Let's try to finish resident evil village
I ran out of gas
We'll eat something
Uh, I
Sorry said fuck capcom. I don't mean that
I did very much so at the very beginning of the stream because I can't believe that a company in 2021
Would put a game on a pc
And have hard locked the the fucking fov. I don't I find that to be impossible
It's like they almost like it has to have been done on purpose
Still the wait the baby was the nascar fuel
That I just burnt through
I pretty much did
I blew out my voice during that segment
I can't wait to see the embarrassing clips and gifts that i'm gonna feed through in the bath later
And I cringe in the bathtub
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Thanks for watching
Thanks to all the subs. There were a lot of gifted subs today. I missed a bunch of them. I was very very much
in the zone here
Thanks a lot everybody
I'm now going to eat something to eat
And shut up and stop talking till tomorrow
Otherwise, it's gonna be really interesting waking up with a broken voice
like I was at a
Soccer game or something. I was just screaming
No, no, I feel like I was at my son's baseball game
And I was really really proud of them. It's already great. Yeah, i'm gonna stop talking
Drink tea. Yeah, i'll have some tea. That sounds good
All right. I'll give you the my rating of the game so far is still an 8.6. It stays there
We'll see how it ends. It might drop a few points tomorrow. It might go up a few points. I don't know
I think it's really good
Why is it not a 9 because it's locked at 80 fov and I find that to be fucking embarrassing and i'm not afraid to say it
If the fov mod is like easy to get I might just put it on tomorrow do a raid. Well, let's raid tomorrow
I feel like it's really late right now. We'll do a raid tomorrow. I'll dump you guys somewhere tomorrow. It's like 3 a.m
This time it's like 2 3 a.m eastern right now. It's very late
All right. I'll see you tomorrow. Have a great night
Goodbye
Oh my god. All right. I'm not talking anymore. Thanks for sticking around to know
A lot of you stayed up late. So
See you tomorrow. Have a good night