Hey, what is going on everybody? Derma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary and tonight
going to continue my sort of update discussion coverage on the new Team Fortress 2 bread
teleport bread update love and war or whatever you want to call this update this is going to
cover the demo knight the new demo knight shield or demo man shield and before we get started
i just want to say that it's crazy that stuff like this is now possible watch the ground that i cover
here i would you see where i started i started all the way back where the cart is and look at
where i ended up after four charges in what like 10 seconds i went back to their spawn got a medic
pulled up around the left side escaped with my life intact and i got three kills to show for it
this item really just makes you bounce around like a pinball like i feel like i'm inside of
the adams family pinball machine from 93 or whenever the hell that game came out i hope i
brought enough quarters because i want to keep playing like with the tide turner let me like
jingle them all out what 50 cents to continue hope i get a multi ball that's what i feel like when
i'm playing with this item and even when you're not using the tide turner to about i didn't even
explain like what the tide turner even is the tide turner is the shield that is giving the
opportunity to do this if you don't know how it works when you charge somebody and you get a kill
while you're charging you are able to immediately charge again which is why i say you turn into a
pinball and also you get the 25 explosion reduction and damage and fire reduction and damage so it
does the same amount of damage reduction as the splendid screen but it also allows you to have a
hundred percent like turning control you you can turn as much as you want with this item you don't
even have you know the wee booties you don't have to put those on this thing is totally negates the
wee booties in that regard but that's how the item works and on top of it being really good for
offensive measures bouncing around and getting a bunch of kills the escape mechanism of this item
is also really good as a demo night before when you charged into somebody if there was a bunch of
people that you saw okay there's a bunch of people on this point i'm going to charge in with my demo
night and i'm going to try to get a kill with it okay great you got one kill now you're just like
swinging around blindfolded at like a fucking pinata like go like where is it did you get
somebody else maybe you did but this item allows you to get out so if you charge around a corner
and you get like another demo or you get a scout or something you can immediately turn around and
get out and get to a safe position which is exactly what i did in the very beginning of this video i
get that i got the medic i got out and i was totally safe now if you have one of the grenade
launchers on obviously that's another way to protect yourself if you turn a corner you get
someone and there's a bunch of other people you can try to make something else happen with the
grenade launcher but if you just want to get out and keep a streak going this thing is fantastic
for that because it's pretty difficult to shoot at a charging demo night unless he's coming right at
you or you're a pyro and you can air blast them they move really damn fast and sometimes it can
be difficult to plan a shot on them and if you want my thoughts as a whole i think that this
shield is incredibly powerful i think it's probably the best shield out of the three right now there
are the other ones sure the other ones have a good place but the full turning control and the
be able to charge after kill i think are so huge that it's really hard at this stage right now to
argue against it being the best shield in the game right now and before this video wraps up i just
want to briefly go over this part of the update because a lot of people had a question about this
and they were and myself included i was asking okay we got day one we got day two and we didn't
get a day three and i was in the crowd of people that a lot of us thought we were going to get the
moon base the big new moon base map that valve was working on on day three and there was no day
three so what that means is there's more stuff coming pretty damn soon you got end of the line
you got this whole moon base thing i don't know if end of the line and the moon base map
are going to be tied together part of the same update and if they're not then that means there's
two updates that are coming to this game at a reasonably fast pace i'm going to assume it's
not going to be oh yeah end of the line is going to be out like next june no this is going to be
probably pretty soon with all this new stuff so keep that in mind there's still more things
coming to this game and it's a really great time to be a team fortress 2 player i know a lot of
people myself included thought okay that we haven't seen anything new in such a long time
does valve still care and apparently they do so it's good to know that it's really awesome to
see this game having a bunch of concurrent players uh jumping back into the game some new players
some old players that are checking it out again and it's awesome and if you happen to be one of
these people that just jumped in for the update keep playing it's fun but anyways guys that's
going to wrap up the video thank you all so much for watching just my thoughts on a couple of the
things in the update and i'll see you guys all next time and of course take care everybody and
you know it's been beautiful out it's been especially like in united states we're in the
middle of like pretty much the summer time right now go go like throw a frisbee you know just go
outside go outside and just throw a frisbee and just be like yeah just throw a frisbee