Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Theme Hospital.
Now, this is kind of going to be in the Enlightened series, I guess you could say.
Even though it's been a million years since you've last seen Enlightened.
But can you even read this text? I don't think, whatever, you can't read it.
I know how to play. This used to be one of my favorite games on the PlayStation 1, if you could believe it.
And you run your own hospital. It's one of the first, I can't really say first,
but it's one of the original hospital sims. It might even be the only hospital sim.
I have absolutely no idea what I'm talking about. But we're going to get right into this here.
I'm just going to play until I don't care anymore. Maybe like 10, 15 minutes.
If you want to see more of Theme Hospital, then let me know.
But I should probably get going because the hospital opens in like 35 seconds.
So let's go. I know I need a GP's office.
And it works just like the sims, where you kind of build rooms, you build individual walls.
I don't want the GP's office that huge. That looks good.
That's not a valid blueprint? Well, screw you. Now it is. Check.
Got to put the door on. Couple of windows. Alright.
So this is where people come into the hospital. The whole point of this...
Oh, damn it. Hold on. I didn't mean to do that. Pick that up.
Pick up the... Whatever. My doctor doesn't even need to face his patients. I really don't care.
This guy's going to give me tips and tricks as we go, but whatever.
So when people walk in the door with an illness, let's say that I have a cough, my like chest hurts.
Then they go to the receptionist who is not currently here yet, but I'm going to make her.
Where is facilities? Clinics? Treatment? Diagnostics? Where the hell is the reception?
Oh, there it is. Reception desk. And that's the build button.
So people come right... Should we make it like right here so they don't have to wait in line at all?
Yeah, we will. Got to hire a receptionist.
Alright, who can we hire?
K Kingsmith. She seems like a bitch. I don't think we want her.
F Petcliff. Enjoys river widening. Poorly trained and...
I thought that said reckless. Feckless.
What? Is that an F? Am I crazy? Why is that an F? Poorly trained and feckless.
Alright, well anyways, she's reckless. I don't want her.
Drinks wine dedicated to helping people with a smile. You know, she might be drunk,
but she's going to take the job seriously. Except she's like walking the wrong way.
Honey. Honey, you're the recep... Oh no, that's a nurse! Shit!
It's okay, we'll need her later. Here's the receptionist. Here we go.
Very friendly. Very friendly. There.
I accidentally made a stupid nurse that's not going to do anything until we need her later.
Okay, well whatever. I need a doctor. This hospital is going to open soon.
Got to get a doctor to in the doctor's office.
Alright, we could do this guy. An expert at DIY. Rude and abrasive.
Gets people's backs up. Gets people's backs up? What? What?
It's kind of an explanation. Tickles trout. No, stop it.
Enjoys French art house films? Alright, well this guy's alright. He likes like films.
Go work there, you son of a bitch.
Alright, we got our doctor that sees the patients. We got our nurse wandering aimlessly.
And we have our reception right at the front door.
So, we need general diagnostics. We'll put that right next to...
You are so loud, lady. I wish you didn't just scream in my ear.
We're going to put a couple benches over here. Don't worry, this is where people get diagnosed.
The changing screen will go right next to the window. I want people to get like seen naked.
This like weird machine can go over here. And there we go.
I believe we need a doctor to actually be in here to like take care of people.
And this guy's going to have to like do two things at once. Do we have any patients yet?
No, the door to the hospital's not even open.
Wandering the nurse is okay for the time being. I need a janitor, I know that.
Alright, grandpa collects World War II shrapnel and go back.
Well, you already got fired.
Smuggles fake watchers. Superb stamina. You know, he just keeps going.
You know, it's grandpa. Alright, well just go over there. Screw you.
Hospital's open. The hospital is officially open.
We're going to get some people with some weird diseases to walk up this weird like Tetris hallway.
Look at this guy. He's freaking out.
Hey, dude, somebody gave like grandpa too much coffee.
I gotta go. I gotta go. Where's the trash?
What a psycho. Somebody needs to slow him down.
Do we have any patients yet? Uh oh. Ladies and gentlemen, we got a live one.
Okay, he's going to go over here. Actually, I want benches. I want benches.
A bench to go right here. Come in. I'm taking a dump.
See, this guy diagnoses the problem. He sends them over to the other doctor that does not exist yet, but he will very shortly.
Doctor? I'm working on it. I'm working on it.
Whatever. You can do it. It doesn't matter.
Hey, I just got this job five seconds ago.
You've satisfied the financial criteria for this level.
Now keep your balance above a thousand while making sure your hospital is running efficiently.
Where are people going?
Alright, just diagnose this guy. Grandpa's still on crack. That's fine.
We got diagnosis. We could go for a psychiatric ward, I think, in case any people come in that need to get their mental health in check.
I know I need a pharmacy, and that gives a place for the nurse to go who's wandering around the pharmacy.
Yeah, he's going. Don't worry. Pharmacy will be over here. A little bit bigger.
Gonna put you to work, nurse, because you're kind of just doing nothing.
You're just wasting like $100 an hour for me.
Alright, get in there. You. Get. Get in there. I just put her in.
British lady, that's yelling at me. I understand.
Okay, we got another one. Where'd that patient go? Where'd that first patient go?
Oh, he's gonna go get like a drink.
Alright, let's see if we can cure our first patient.
How do you feel? You paid me $400. Sick.
Thank you for coming to the hospital, sir. I'm glad you enjoyed your stay.
Hopefully you don't go home and insta-puke.
Well, thanks for the high rating, too. I appreciate that. Thank you.
Oh, shit. Where is he?
Yeah, get over there, you chump.
Yeah, he's knocking on the door. He's standing in front of him.
Okay, I gotta make another... Facilities.
Need some... I need some bathrooms.
Bathrooms can go up here. Yeah.
That's a pretty huge bathroom.
Yeah, there's one... Oh, man. This bathroom's way too big.
And you know, just because I'm a cynical dick,
I'm gonna put the staff room next to the toilets,
because I'm just a jerk. I'm a bad boss.
And you should feel bad working for me.
Grandpa, get out of the way. I can't build this if you're standing on it.
He hasn't done any work.
He's just been running a marathon around this whole damn place.
There's the sofa. That's okay.
Got the staff room now in case somebody wants to chill out.
No, there's no trash. Where's this guy going?
He's going to get a potion, I think, to the pharmacy.
Yeah, pay me my money. I'm the goddamn hospital owner.
I'll inject you with this syringe I got.
We gonna cure our second patient? Oh, yeah.
How we doing? How we doing? We got a consistency...
What is this guy? Oh, my God.
Who let, like, Uncle Fester in here?
He's a baby. It's a baby.
This guy has a baby face. That's his disease.
Uh, yeah, doctor, you know, I'm not sure if you can realize this or not,
but I have a friggin' baby face.
How do you cure this? This guy needs to go into, like, surgery.
Apparently, the baby face disease is an epidemic in this city.
Look at this guy, except he's, like, blonde.
Oh, wait. No, I remember. I gotta make an inflation station.
That rhymed. Uh, clinics. Inflation. There it is.
This'll go down here. There's no space over here.
But, yeah, you can get this game right now on good old games.
It's a doozy. It's a doozy.
I believe... I don't want to say an incorrect amount of money. I forget.
It's, like, less than ten bucks. It's, like...
I think it's, like, six or seven dollars for this game on GOG.com.
Theme Hospital is the name again. You probably saw the title.
So, I mean, whatever. Do we need another nurse? I think we do.
Or does the doctor have to do this? I'm not sure.
I'm sure the lady will yell at me once I find out what...
No, we got the invisible man. He's, like, the invisible disease.
All right, now I need another doctor. Gotta hire another doctor.
How are my resources doing? Pretty good.
All right, I'm gonna find a good doctor.
Ex-Quiz Show host, rash and easily distracted.
Sings in a rock and roll band? Absolutely.
You are the new hiree.
Now, let's, like, take some of that air out of your face.
Oh! Oh, my...
Keep in mind, guys, that guy just paid me $850
to stick a needle in his face and blow his head up.
That probably was very painful.
Okay, okay, okay.
This guy...
That 72% is pretty high.
I'm gonna go ahead and say go for it. Go for it.
This is the guy, right? Let's see if it works.
I got one of the best nurses in the city working for me.
Dude, you'll be fine.
There you go. Good as new. Good as new.
And...hey, it worked.
For the money. VIP.
The mayor of Crater...
What? He's dead. You just killed your first patient.
No, it said there was a 72% chance I was...
Wait, he's alive.
Oh, no, never mind. See you later, death.
That was a 72% chance that it was gonna work.
I don't want to do that again.
This is an even less chance. What the...what?
All right, hold on. Let me get another diagnostic room.
Let's see if we can make this right.
Ward, pharmacy,
inflation, diagnostic, psychiatric...
Maybe it's all in their head.
We're gonna get a ward up here.
Because maybe we gotta send these guys to the ward?
That was ridiculous. I can't believe that guy died.
No, I can't go there. I can't go there.
Where am I gonna put this goddamn...
I did pretty poor planning.
I'm just gonna have to go over here.
Damn it. No, that's a terrible spot.
What about right here? It'll be next to the reception desk.
Holy hell, that's a terrible spot for this.
Hey, welcome to the hospital.
Place more benches? People are...
being forced to stand up.
What is Maya McCheese doing?
Is he like gonna...
Oh, shut up. Shut up.
We're good. Send the invisible guy over here.
Let's go...no, no, no. I don't want to do that.
I need another nurse, right?
I do. Oh, there she is.
But that means the nurse from over here just left.
Where's the nurse now? I'll pay for it.
I got the money. Why not?
Oh, benches, that's what she said?
Need a drink machine, too. Dr. Pepper.
Gotta have like a Dr. Pepper machine, like right next to the doctor's office.
Look at how popular this thing are.
$20?!
Did you just see how much money that was?
That was $20
for a Coke. $20.
I don't know what kind of weird, screwed-up
dimension these people are living in
where soda is $20.
I'm a bad man for running this kind of
organization. Get out of here.
Okay. Hall of Shame?
Did I just lose the game?
Did I lose the game?
What?
Dear Jerma, marvelous, you have handled the
running of this hospital superbly.
Us bigwigs at the Ministry
of Health would like to know if you'd be interested
in taking on a larger project.
This is a job we think would be perfect for you.
The salary would be $16,000.
I would absolutely
take that. Thank you so much.
I did it. I beat the level.
What do you know about that?
Anyways, guys, that's probably going to wrap up this episode.
If you want to see more Theme Hospital,
I mean, I'm not sure how much of a series
I'm going to do with this because it's pretty self-explanatory,
but it's a very, very fun game, Live
Enlighten, today, if you enjoyed it.
Then let me know, and I'll see you guys all next time.
Take care, everybody. See you all
soon. Inject the needle in his face.