23 hours and 55 minutes early for tomorrow's stream because this one didn't turn on before
two. I see what you're saying. So this is actually tomorrow's stream. I didn't stream today. This is
tomorrow's stream. Anyways, uh, hello. How are you? Welcome back. I'm going to be playing some sniper
ghost warrior contracts today. I saw it pop up on steam and I'm like, you know what?
I'm, I want, we played the last sniper game. We played the last two sniper games, the last two
sniper elite and then sniper go. I think pretty sure we played both of them when they came out.
So there is a backup plan. If, uh, if I don't think this is fun, if I'm just like, nah, I don't think
so. Uh, I got dusk, which is just everybody, everybody loves that game. I've never played
it personally, but, and we could also, there's a bit, we got like a bunch of other like mystery
games we could play. So who cares? I probably shouldn't even said dusk because now everyone's
far going to be like, just, just do that instead. Just play dusk instead. But no,
I am a AAA video gamer right now. I want to play the new AAA video games and the new AAA
game that came out yesterday was sniper ghost warrior contracts too. It's not a AAA game.
I know, but give me a second. Uh, I'm going to get it over on the screen here and we'll get started.
Give me one sec. All right. Let's chill for a second here. I've got to warn you.
You're about to get your eyes blown out. So just be ready. Ready? One, two, three. It's bright as
hell. It's very bright. I don't know why this screen is this bright, but it is. So in sniper
ghost warrior contracts, it's your job as the hit man to, I have no idea.
I didn't even, guys, I did not even read the description of this game. Greetings,
mercenary. I represent a third party who wishes to make use of your specialist skills.
Nice. We are aware of your usual fees and are comfortable meeting the cost.
In fact, you've seen my last place for you to execute.
All are in the newly formed Siberian Republic. Skip, skip. No, I'm not skipping. This gets on
screen. Siberia was once part of the Russian Federation. Was it? Whoa. Siberia's huge natural
resources to bolster Russian economic success. Russia had a shitload of gold, but Siberia was
that sand from this relationship. In fact, it was mainly exploited and used
a political movement was established. The people for an independent Siberia,
even the regional governor, Mergui, Kurchatov was swept up in the wave,
joining the movement and cutting off Siberia from the Kremlin. The Siberian war of independence
followed Russia contained many Siberians and defections were right. The war was over quickly.
Kurchatov became Siberia's first prime minister, governing his new country with his family and
friends. Dude, it even has, okay. Just read the subtitles for a second. It even has the like,
spreading out the hitman shit, like the little wire frames and the white and the...
All right, let's keep our... Declared war against their government. They attacked oil fields and
stole state assets. Their leader, Nastya Tsurikova, has now become a hero to the people
and Kurchatov's nemesis. Our proposal comes with one requirement. You will need to wear a new
high-tech mask. You have to wear a Halloween mask. It will facilitate direct communication.
Nobody can tell who you are. But there are other benefits for you, including combat enhancements.
My designation will be handler. Yours will be seeker. I look forward to working with you.
I gotta wear an Andros mask? I think that thing's cold and... We're in Siberia, right?
That thing looked like it was made out of steel. You want me to wear a steel mask on my face
in like negative 12 degrees? That thing's not coming off. All right, here we go. Proving
grounds complete the tutorial. Let's take a look at the details so I know what I'm working with here.
All right, it's just a top-down view. Cool. Start the contract. Marksman. Game difficulty
has decreased. Enemies are less aware. They see and hear the player only when he's near.
Enemy's weapon damage is reduced. Standard game, right? Enemies are aware of the player. They see
and hear the player from the standard distance. Enemy's weapon damage is on a standard, normal,
regular level. Perfect for me. Game has increased difficulty. Enemies are much more aware of the
player. They spot the player easily in the open and hear him from the greater distance.
Enemy's weapon damage is increased. That's not real. Everyone that says play on the hard
difficulty don't... That's not the real difficulty. Enemy's weapon damage is increased. What are they
using for bullets? What's the difference? Why can they hear me from five miles away? That's not
real. This is the real difficulty. This is the realistic one. Greetings, seeker. You should have
already received the mask. It is a highly advanced prototype that enhances your capacity in the field
and syncs with your equipment. The mask allows you to upload contracts data to the client after
each mission. Before we drop you in the designated location, we want to make sure you understand the
tech we've given you. For this purpose, you'll be taken to a secure training facility hidden in a
secluded mountain location. You're going to perform a series of simple tasks to familiarize
yourself with the mask and for us to make the necessary adjustments. Report back when you're
at the location, seeker. All right, here we go. It's time. Do I need to know what lore is and
shit? I'm not just gonna jump in without knowing anything. I don't know anything about sniping.
Hopefully this is not realistic at all because hopefully I just aim crosshair on guys' head.
I hope it's not one of those things where I have to do like the distance and then left and then
because otherwise I'm just going to not play the game. Ready for action.
Dude, turn the game down on your mic, man. Like a rifle. Okay, hold on. This is like,
the graphics are too good right now. I need to like turn them down. I'm not kidding.
Doesn't it? I don't know. I must be an old fucking man. I swear to God. But I actually like it when
games don't look like insanely incredible and shit. I like it when they look kind of like crap.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay, approach the sniping spot. What about these?
What is this? Refill ammo. All right, ammo. I got 525. All right, approach sniping spot.
Take a prone position. Hold C to go prone. Press tab to open the tutorial. You got the reading
tutorial. They still haven't figured out how to do tutorials in all video games, huh? I know I just
did an R instead of a W. I'm stupid. This takes me out. It does. If you guys notice that, that the
tutorial always just takes you out. Instead of being like telling me these things as a little
robot in my ear, I have to like, what am I reading a book right now? Okay, crouch stance. Hold C to
go prone. Okay, changing stance to crouch. Reduces weapon sway. All right. And hold your breath.
You have this hold breath mechanic. Cool. All right. Note that only tall grass and bushes provide
fall cover. Good to know. You got to stay on a bar. It'll increase when you perform physical
actions like running and climbing, but it regenerates. Otherwise, your stamina level
determines how long you can hold your breath. Okay, so that's important. Let's go. First,
switch your mask to binocular mode. Target over there. Tagging enemies allows you to measure the
distance to selected targets and keep track of the system to measure your target's distance.
Why do I need to use binoculars when I have a huge binocular on my arm?
Rifle and see for yourself. This is just a giant binocular.
This system scales up the display.
All right. I shoot the target. So it eight. So 117 meters. That means I have to go.
What do I have to aim? That means I have to go up a little bit, right?
Below 100. That's too far. So okay, so if I'm zoomed in that 100 right there, I got to go
a little bit above that. So like right here, higher than that. See for me, it's just,
just guess for me. You know what I'm saying? Proceed to the next one.
So that's the wind check target. Aim along bullet drop cone. Shit. Okay. He's 150 away.
So I have to like drop this on his head. So he's 150. Yeah, I know.
What? Okay. QE. This is, this is the mechanic I was talking about the elevation button.
280. Like that. Like that. So that's 280. Right. That's correct. Right. That's 100. What do
you mean it's 100 on the right? 100. All right. Wait, hold on. I've got to ask a question.
Do the, this is where anytime I play sniper game, just listen to me closely. I know. Just please
listen to me. Hear me out. Do the numbers on the middle of the screen in yellow,
orange mean fucking anything? Yes. No. Yes. Yeah. That's what I'm saying. Okay. So this is at 280
right now. So here's, this is who said no wrong aim. This is wrong. This is not correct.
I have so much trouble with these. I have so much trouble with these games. I swear to God,
I knew it. I have so much trouble with this shit. And I know I should know what I'm doing,
but I don't. Because I've changed the scope. The wind. I know the wind is going down though.
I can't. I can't do it. I have to guess. Got it. I think that is a rule. What is the one on the
top mean? I'm going to sit here until I get it. I don't care if it takes five hours. The top left,
see two, three, four, six. Right. What does that, what does that mean? The top left is wind speed.
Okay. So that doesn't mean there's nothing to do with the, the, this three, four, five, six shit.
I know. Okay. I know the top one is wind. I've played plenty of golf games. I know how that works.
It's a, it's a scale so you can find the distance. Bottom is distance in meters. So this top left
one is the wind direction. See one, two, three, four, six. That's wind direction. Bottom is bullet
drop. People are just, every time I've tried, I've tried many times. I thought I, you know,
I'm fucking staying until I figure it out. Just shoot him. I'm just going to, I'm just going to
shoot him. I almost got him. Just shoot him. Get in discord so somebody can explain this.
How do I take this back? How far away is this guy? Everyone's flooding discord. You think I'm going
to be able to get explained to me on discord? Damn it. It is, it's like hard and you need to
like know what you're doing. I, all I know is wind and this thing of that, the cascading
particle effect. All right. I'm going to slow down. We're going to start at the very beginning.
Here we go. Right now I am not, I'm at, I'm not zoomed in at all. Okay. I'm not zoomed in.
When I go one tick forward, this, the numbers change here. Can someone just give me a basic
explanation as to why when I do one tick in at times eight, these numbers in front of me change.
Like they go down, like it's going down, but that's just, no, they're not changing.
I'm getting closer. Okay. So I figured that out. Just bear with me. I'm a koala for God's sake.
So right now, what the, that number, that 100 means what? That's distance. The top left numbers
are height scale. So that means that this guy, but how do I know he's a hundred meters away?
What are these, what are the lines in the middle mean? It will hit at a hundred meters if you
compensate. Thank you. Thank you. That's what I wanted. So if I compensate, I'll hit this guy.
You have to mark him first, right? Okay. Let's mark and see how far away he is.
Okay. All right. So he's 114 meters away. So that see 200, that's how far away he is. It'll
hit him in the chest, right? It'll hit him right in the chest. If I compensate right there, right?
So right there. So this is going to hit him right in the fucking head. Okay. I get it. I understand.
So what? Okay. This is where I got fucked up. It always, what are these numbers in the two, three,
four, six? What's that mean? What does the two, three, four, six mean? No clue. Omega low. Ignore
those. Well, aren't I supposed to know? Just ignore the top left. See, I'm under the assumption that
I have to make some fucking calculation with the stuff in the top left. All right. I get it.
This is a real tricky one for me here. 262. You understand? Check this out. 262. Look at that.
That's a headshot right there. It only took me 20 minutes to figure out how to play the fucking
game. Now, now I can play any sniper game because I always get to this part and quit.
I said that's not a joke. I, every sniper game that has this mechanic in it.
I, I can't figure out this first part and then I just quit again. All right. Important. I have
something really important to ask guys. What's this shit do? This like 200, 240, like 500.
That's just changing what that's to fine tune it. So if I want to, let's say the guys, let's say the
guy's like 600 meters away, right? And I'm just like, fuck, I can't, how am I supposed to tell?
So there we go. Six, it's like 600 meters that I hit him right in the head. If I compensate for the
wind, let's just say the guy's back there. All right. That was fucking ridiculous. Cause I may
as well just, I, I, I, that's how it was. What? It always seems like it's like impossible. All
right. Right, right. Cause I'm like, I'm zoomed the fuck in. So how far away is this guy? I don't
know. Who cares? Shoot him right in the light. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. I think I
understand. That's how real guns work. That's all right. That's fine. All right. Let's go.
Is there no scope? Oh, we've got a live exercise here. Short range, special bullets,
pick up one of the weapons to try out different sets of special. This technology will increase
your options in the field and allow you to be more creative. Ooh, test a turret or pick up a
sniper rifle to test special bullets. What's wrong with one I have explosive. I just burped
while I was talking and that's why it sounded like that. All right. Let's do explosive.
Press. Oh, there we go. Use explosive to hit targets. They detonate on impact. How do I know
how far away that is though? Let me find out. How far away is this? I can't, I don't know.
How come I, I can't tell how far away that is. I'm fucking, I'm useless.
That was just huge targets. Okay. Cool. They, that's actually pretty fun. Do it again. Sure.
Let's reload. All right. That's fun. Pick up an ammo box. What do we got here? We got armor
piercing. What's what is DARPA? EMP DARPA. What's DARPA do? Top left lets you see distance based on
dude's heights. So wait, hold on. You're telling me that that that guy's 200 meters away. What if
I go like this? Can I just trick myself? No, that's not how it works. Put it on their feet. I'll put
the line, put their feet on the line. It's like that. So this guy's 212, 15. Yeah. All right.
Well, how the, I don't know. I've never used this before in my life. All right. DARPA bullets.
This is actually pretty good because now I won't rage quit every single sniper game I've ever
played. I don't have to compensate for gravity or wind. How do I get a box of these? Can I just
have these? This is just cheating. All right. I'm just going to get a bunch of those.
All right. I get, I understand how it works, but I want to see what this is. Luring tagging, luring.
Why would there be ammo to luring? Dude, this is sick. All right. So now you tell me if I go,
I'm going to just let me just let me listen to me. This here. So you tell me that this thing
is a hundred meters away. Dope. All right. Well, no, we don't need to go that far then. All right.
Tagging. So what am I supposed to do? Tag it or lure? How do I, there's nobody even over here.
Just shoot the ground. These guys can't even walk. It doesn't be luring people. Is it just
making noise? He's blind. What? This is a luring bullet. I mean, these guys aren't moving though.
Cardboard people can't walk. That's what I know. But how targets can't walk. All right. Well,
no, I wasn't about to leave the game. Switch to tagging bullets. What do tagging bullets do?
Probably tag people. Pick up turret. Hold to open weapon wheel and select remote turret.
Am I going to snipe a turret? Plus F to place turret. Where? Like if I, do I call in a turret
call? Press T and switch your mass to binocular mode. Tag targets for remote turret. While in,
what? While in binocular, press H to tag up to two targets. Press H. Press G. Where the hell is
this thing? Press F to put the turret down first. Okay. I'm going to put the turret down. All right.
I got my turret. Let's see. Tag these guys. H. Shoot these guys. Huh? From this far away.
I thought this, I thought this was like you put it down short range. Uh, all right. EMP. I think I
know what that does. I know what that does. It pierces armor. All right. I know what tagging does.
It tags people. Let's just make sure I know what it does. That's a hitscan weapon. That's a little
strange. All right. Let's, all right. We go. Let's just go like this. Watch that wind. All right.
Let's tag. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. I get it. All right. What do I go if I get it?
Just, I'm just going to get the turret. That's all I care about.
This thing is not even in line of sight. That's really, really fun. Okay. Here we go. Let's get,
we got an AK. We've got a pistol. We got bullets. We got grenades. This grenades in this game.
Automatic plus one letter grid. All right. Press F to use selected gadget. I hate when I get
cold. AK. Good. Really loud though. Let's, let's, let's fix that. All right. Let's see if I can get
them all. Pretty good. All right. How do I leave? All right. If I hit the guy all the way in the
back and he drops right now, I get a hundred alls. Oh well. You guys ready? I am. Okay.
Altai mountains. Download Ivanovsky's plans. Find the client spy. Eliminate Demetri. Destroy
all test results. Steal samples of the virus. I thought this was a sniper game. What happened
to where's snipe the bad guy? What? Interrogate officers. Perform headshots. Gas enemies. Eliminate
without. What is all this? What is all this? Inter, how do I interrogate somebody from five
miles away? Greetings Seeker. Just do it. Your primary target is Demetri Ivanovsky. He is a
former Russian armed forces general. He earned the nickname bio-efficacy. You call them.
During the second Mongolian war. Due to his persistent use of both chemical and biological weapons.
You called. His first cousin to the Siberian. That's so funny because it's, I mean, yeah.
During the Siberian war of independence. You ping their walkie-talkie. You just prank call them.
Cousin. Kurtadov gave him the notorious Altai 24 Soviet military research facility as thanks
for his support. Yeah. You hold the walkie-talkie and you go, what do you know? Tell me what you
know. And you smack the walkie-talkie like on a table. And then he goes on the other end.
All right. All right. All right. He's in the back room. Human trials of his bio-weapon.
Understand that Kurtadov plans to use the weapon to secure Siberia's disputed border territories.
Stored on an encrypted military grade laptop. Find the package, hack it and obtain those plans.
All right. I understand it's cold looking and there's a lot going on on the screen, but
what is this supposed to be? What these lines and the geometry, wires, what is this supposed to be?
A computer or what are we supposed to be looking at? A video? Hacking. It's like what hacking looks
like. It just defects in the camera. I just, I guess it looks maybe like on a poster or something,
but I don't know. Whatever. All right. Let's go. Alpaya. Your first objective is to infiltrate
the enemy's facility. It's behind the electric fence. You'll have to cut the power. We've dropped
your weapons nearby. Load your map to see the cargo drop off point. All right. Let's go. Do I even
have a sniper rifle? Open M. Blue areas indicate contact locations. That's a lot of, that's a huge,
this is the legend that you see at a mall. Okay. There's, there's the target. Okay. Where's the,
where's the Nordstrom? This is a mall directory. So here, this is the box I have to go to.
So just go. Can I put a waypoint? Yep. Thank God. I'll update your map with
coordinates related to your contracts. You can load it via your mask at any time.
You can manually mark waypoints on your map. They'll be displayed directly on your map.
All right. You can fall off. You can fall off the edge. Okay. Cool. I need some games. Don't let
you do that. That's plus five. That's a, that's plus 0.2 points. So this is all right. I'm not,
I was just testing to see if you could fall. It's behind the electric fence. You'll have to
cut the power. What force causes me to hypothetical. All right. So I'm ready. Cool. Let's go.
Coordinates related to your contracts. You can load it for your mask at any time.
You can manually mark waypoints on your map. They'll be displayed directly on your mask.
Yep. All right. Jump. That's a pretty floaty jump. All right. Jump plus climb on. How do I do that?
Just jump and hold. This is not the video game I thought it was going to be, and neither did you.
So let's go. Dead end. Use your mask scanner. I have a scanner?
Now what would happen in real life is if you went that far up to a huge building like this,
you would just fall backwards. What was it? Left control? Uh, what? I don't know.
It just makes everything kind of ugly. What is this showing me?
Is there an indicator besides the triangle stuff? The pipes. I mean, I see the pipes,
but what's the point of having the sniper vision on this? Okay. Cool. I can jump that high?
No, you cannot. Is there a flashlight? There's no way I can jump that far down.
Your suit is made from extremely durable, intelligent microfibers that also support
your body's natural regeneration abilities. Yeah. Health bar regenerates, drain stops when
you receive damage or sprint and use med kit to full health and adrenaline shot boost regeneration.
Yeah. You have a stamina bar. You hold your breath and shit. I get it. Your mask sinks
with your central nervous system. It was killing enhancing your reflexes and coordination.
Meaning you will be fine. Meaning it's going to instantly break both of my legs and then
heal them instantly. So I'm still going to feel the pain both ways. See? And now they're being
restructured. How do you save the game? You don't. You don't. I say flashlight. Use my sniper vision.
I still don't understand what the fuck this does. Take him down. When the recognition bar fits.
Wow. Is this stealth? A stealth action first person shooter game? While crouching, you'll be
less visible and quieter. Your silhouette turns black and HUD becomes darker when you are hidden.
Right? The recognition bar fills up when the enemies start noticing you. When it's full and
it's flashing red, you're detected. That's the same indicator. Stealth kill. Press mo when prompted
to perform a silent melee attack. You can also kill enemies when hiding below their field of vision
or jump them from above. If you sneak behind an enemy, you can interrogate him. A successful
interrogation provides information on supplies or hostile soldiers locations. Officers who can
be found at every outpost can provide you with mission relevant. Let's interrogate this person.
Where are they? Sniper vision. Is he talking to himself? What do you know?
Oh, I didn't even do that. I didn't click that. He just did it. He did that. I didn't do it.
Oh my god. You can hide. I didn't even kill this guy. Grab body. Holy shit. You throw them far.
What? Okay. He's hidden. Wait. Duck. All right. There's a hiding place over there. Wait. There's
enemies over here. Hiding place. All right. Approach this. He begged for his life. I did not kill that
guy. Oh shit. Throw a stone. Hold Q and A. You can throw rocks in this game. Oh shit. Prone. Oh,
I hit him in the fucking head. I hit him. I think I just put them on alert. This is an amalgamation
of every video game. Holy shit. They didn't wait. I want to see if you can throw the rocks.
Yeah, I did. Death from above. But there's a guy right there. How would you not hear that?
What? Why would it want me to do that? Why would it want me to do that to this guy? Hey, jump on
this guy and stab him and stomp on his head. Yes. Distract them. Yes. Use a decoy to distract. Okay.
But why don't you just walk by this? What do you know? Take down. Why was it right click? What do
you mean right click is take down? What are you talking about? Right. Take down. Right click.
I just threw a rock. What? What the fuck is going on?
Why did it? It was saying right click. Right click. Right. Why right click? Right click is aimed.
All right. Press tab to open the store. Okay. Mask. The mask mode can help you analyze the
environment. A fully developed mask will highlight interactive objects. Cool. Even through walls,
it can show camera vision cones, detect sound sources, and much more. All right. That's called
mask mode. Avoiding enemy patrols on our post can be difficult. Search for the hideouts like lockers,
trash cans. To hide this is where you can wait out alarms. You can also hide bodies in these
containers. All right. So I get mask mode. I would highlight usable items and markers. All right.
Pick up weapon. Yeah. I can use this. Cool. What's this thing? I can. What's the looting even do?
What's the point of looting? It's just ammo. Okay. Cool. Why hide them when you can just throw them
over? All right. I don't even need the ammo. Wait. Easy. Mask mode. All right. We're good. What is
this? Grenades. Pick. Got it. You can only carry a limited amount so keep track of your equipment.
All right. Cool. Grenades. On. Recon the area before you proceed.
All right. We got it. What do we got? Recon out these binoculars. We've got a electricity.
Shoot that. Electrify tank. Looks like they're guarding the transformer station ahead.
Use them by different tags and appearance. I would look for the officers. Okay. I need an officer.
Looks like an officer. Search him when you're done. Copy that. All right. Wait.
All right. Regular soldiers are versatile but relatively easy to kill. Sargeants are close
combat specialists resistant to gas weapons. Riflemen specialize in assault and can use
higher class grenades. Marksmen are long-distance killers and best to eliminate heavy. So I'm going
up against like a class-based shooter. What am I? A sniper? Heavy soldiers can withstand a lot of
damage. Try to use a heavy sniper rifle on them. Just provide information. Watch out for drones.
They can expose your position. Targets and bounties are always well guarded.
Some info dump. I think the the moral of the story here is yeah like somebody just said just
shoot them. Shut up and kill them. Guys relax. All right. Let's get this guy. How come I okay
everybody talk about you. How do I know if they're an officer or not? I mean that guy looks like an
officer I guess. Shit. Keep an eye out for useful environmental elements. Fuse box. Yeah. Shoot the
fuse box. You can lure enemy to avoid combat or place where you can deal with them easily. Yeah.
If you do this you can use interactive objects like generators in few boxes or gadgets like
decoy traps or the upgraded drone. Avoiding enemy patrols and outposts can be difficult.
Hide. All right I think I got everybody tagged right. Nobody no snipers. Okay shoot fuse box.
Wait how far away is it? Not that far. Wait let me just check this. All right he's like right here.
Should I shoot this guy? No. What's he doing? How how loud is this gun? Did I get him?
Holy shit. Okay that was pretty cool. Uh now what? Wait this guy. Wait who's the officer?
That's the officer. I gotta clear this out. So um what else we got? This guy still has no idea
what's going on behind him. All right I'd have to interrogate this guy. Is this a zipline? Oh shit.
Keep your distance till they're all down. What do you mean till they're all down?
Is this like I have to interrogate this guy? Shoot this guy? I don't have to interrogate him.
Isn't that the officer? He doesn't know where I am. He just knows something's going on.
If I'm quiet can I climb this thing? I'll get around to him. Is there money in this game?
That's actually kind of fun. All right I gotta get behind him. I think I'm gonna make it. How
do I get all I gotta get all the way around him? Wait I gotta throw a stone. Did I go over the
house? Ah Mike you threw it over the house. Oh that's the only ball we had. Whip the ball like
in the backyard with your friends. You never played like just throw a ball in backyard.
All right I'm going after him. Fuck I think I just hit the fence. Sorry I'll get him here.
Interrogate. Holy shit how did he know? What? I was in the bushes. Are you serious? Oh come on. What?
Before you get there you may need a key card to access the station. I would look for the officers.
Interrogate the officer. Search him when you're done. Search him when you're done.
Fuck me. All right I'm gonna do this real damn quick. Altangos down. I have a live feed from
your mask you know. I thought he said for my mom. Die hard. He says dinner's ready. I just
don't want them to have electricity. All right let's search the uh officer. I don't take money
too right? Yeah I'm gonna loot everybody. Dude I am pogging right now so hard. Really? I appreciate
that. Did I take this guy's head off? Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness. Oh I've got the key
card. Why is it giving me these wrong names? Grab body is not space. It's this mouse button.
All right let's get in. All right wait. Okay what can I do with this? Can I pick this up? Or is it
it just explodes? Power down. The fence should be harmless now. I've marked the exfil location.
Shoot it point blank. Proceed there and upload your data. Exfil location will be visible on your mask
tub if you use the scanner. Copy. I did it. What do I get? Exfiltration point. When the contract is
complete go to the exfiltration point to see the mission summary screen. From there you can stay
in the region to finish other objectives so you can leave but lose any unfinished progress.
That's it? Okay let's go. Is that person right there? No it's just a tree. I gotta get the
binoculars up in case there's any danger and any people or anything right? No people?
What am I supposed to do? A bunch of stuff here? Uh 20 community subs just came in from Ben Folds.
Thanks a lot Ben. 20. Huge sub drop. That's a big one. That's a fucking big one.
Could you be any more annoying in the sky? Dude he's pogging so hard. I am. That's a lot of money.
Two percent? Wait how? Weapons. Upgrade your gear in the loadout tab. Before each mission you
visit development section of the loadout tab. You can upgrade your mask suit gadgets and recon.
The first upgrades only cost cash but more advanced ones require
tokens. Don't tell me I have to buy these. Better not be. Okay shop screen,
find gadgets, attachments, weapons. We can look at that later.
Either. Both. I'm ready. It won't matter to the people they used the weapon on.
That's not your concern. Stay focused. All right what? Maybe it's just a drill. Who's talking?
How many other? Tag him. One. He's got three. Any more? I don't see any more. Can I get three or
can I kill him? What's that? Is that an explosive? I think there might be an explosive barrel.
Nope. Oh shit. I missed. Who cares about the wind compensation and all that dumb stuff?
Just shoot him in the head. All right where am I going? Fast. I can fast travel? Is this like open
world? I'm so confused. That's travel. I'm going here. We're just gonna go up there somehow. All
right what do they got? Plus one letter grade. Give it to me. It's an opportunity. She blew it.
What can I do with gas? Oh explosion. Anybody else? No. Should I hide these guys? I feel like
I need to hide them. That's part of the game right? There's a cave on the left. We'll put
them down here. I'll loot them right right right right. Oh that's a good spot to drop right down
here right? Is anybody nobody's down here? It's just trash. Yeah it's just like trash down there.
All right no one's looking down there. Now let's get up here. Take out the binoculars and let's
scope this out. Wait you wouldn't even see the news. Where is this person? It's them politicians
am I right? That game was so fun. I can't see anybody. I think I just have to get up here.
Go play it. I'm not playing that game. Slow down. Wasn't somebody just talking? Wait where am I
hearing this? Oh fuck they're right here. I need to interrogate somebody. All right I'm gonna try
to interrogate. I'll get that guy with a snipe. Another guy right there. Snipe that guy. Oh no.
Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Oh no. Rock! Wait how far away is he? 126. Compensate for the...
No that's too much compensation. He's 126. So that means he's right there.
What did I hit the rock? What am I hitting? Uh oh this is very bad. I'm freaking out. My character's
freaking out. Slow down. What am I? I'm not hitting his head. Am I hitting this guy in the face?
What he has a mask that blocks my bullets? Oh shit there's a tank. I think the tank just ran
him over. Where is that guy looking? Is somebody alive? Is he shooting on the ground? He's shooting
in the air. I'll get him. Whoa! I have to interrogate someone. What is that? Did they find me? I'm trying
to shoot it. Just being followed around by drones. Peek out. Fuck the wind. I didn't... I forgot about
the wind. They know. Everybody knows. Oh my feet. Right in this guy's head. All right I'm gonna move
position. Can I take the drone? Nothing even in here. This is actually a pretty good spot to snipe.
They still know where I am. Hello?
Hello?
Is it a drone? It's a fucking drone. It's a drone. Where? Where's the drone? Where is it?
Where is this thing? Behind me? No it's not. Wait is that a guy? No. God damn it.
There's a lot of people here. I need to tag this guy. I need to know how far away he is.
Play it right. All right. He is... What? Oh no. Oh shit. Oh we both did the same thing. We got him.
Why would you look at me with binoculars? Who is it? Who's shooting? Who's a grenade? Did I throw
a grenade? Where's the grenade? Is there a grenade here? Where is it? Where you at? I'm gonna blow
this guy up with the explosive. I'll lure him out. I fucking can't believe I missed. Did I kill him?
I need a better place to... How many people are in this compound?
There's still this many people that I have to... That was insane. All right. Damn it. They're getting
in the tank. Oh no. He's aiming at the tank over here. I didn't... Wait are they leaving?
Where are they taking this? Where are you going? You're not gonna drive into me, right? What are you
doing? Oh move move move move. How do I heal? Lie down. Yes. Oh fuck. Okay I need to throw a
grenade at this guy. It's G right? Oh my god I'm dead. Don't stand the fuck up. I'm trying to... How
do you... Oh my god. Was it like J? B. I'm going in. I'm fucking doing it this time. Remember special
ammo? I don't think I have any special ammo. Okay so don't get spotted. These guys come back here.
I'm gonna try to shoot him through. I'm gonna try to shoot him in the head through his friend.
Well that was fucking pretty cool. All right. I'm doing this slow because I don't want to...
There's like 30 or 40 people in here. Get in there. What was that? I heard a beep. I wish I could
save it. So now is the task here to just get in there? Find the client's spy? That's... I think
you just do whatever you want. I don't think there's a set mission here. I think I just do
whatever I want. So download the plans is this one and it's in here somewhere. Download dusk.
I already have dusk downloaded. I just tried to... I tried to prone and I apparently... My body
was too far over the edge that proning actually... I lied forward and fell face down forward into the
ground. Let me get... I want to get a better spot. All right. This is not bad. Okay. I see 269 meters
to the flag and to the supported stance. Oh shit. Okay. This is not good. Where does it go?
How many people are here? I need to do some tagging. Like I've got it. I have to.
How do I get off? Is he coming up this way? This is never gonna happen unless I tag everybody.
All right. Who else is left? Guy up top. That guy's dead. I can kill that guy but
I just don't want to be spotted.
All right. Secure the package. Let's get the guy. We're gonna go top down, right? We're gonna kill
guys on roof. I'm gonna kill. Don't worry. Guys on roof first. There's only two. Supported stance.
Get it in there. These guys are 117 meters away which means that it's got to be somewhere around
right there. We'll be right in the head. Right there. I'm gonna wait until there's an opportunity.
Didn't tag that guy. Jesus. Okay. Nobody saw that, right? I feel like I would hear that.
I feel like I would hear that guy's watermelon head exploding. That was just like
exploding watermelon. I feel like I could hear that. 139. Somebody's gonna come out this door,
aren't they? Whatever. Let's go. Didn't the guy go in here? I think somebody went in here.
All right. Who's next? We've got two guys here. One, two there. A bunch of people over on the
right side. I can't kill these guys yet. I think I have to change position. I gotta get these guys
over here. All right. Changing position. Chat's getting restless. Turn your camera on. I don't
have any clothes on. I've been especially naked these last few days so now no face cam. All right.
Let's get a good shot over here. Right there. What do you think over here? I think so. I've got a
guy right there inside that building. This is getting intense. I'm like feeling this right now.
What about any others over here? No, I don't see anybody. Moving in.
Come on. I've got to keep that. I got to keep that type of like language up. You know what I
mean? Like moving in. Spotted. Top bunker. I see two. Two people. Gonna go for a collab. Because
like otherwise I'm gonna lose you guys. Check this out. Right here. I'm gonna get a collateral.
How far away are these guys? 40 meters. It's gonna go through. One, two. Get it. Did I miss anybody?
Heavy weapons guy coming over here. I don't think there's anybody else this way. I'm gonna stay
here though because there's this guy right here and then there's that guy right. Okay.
It's time to start clearing. Ready? No, not yet. Can I get them both? I'm going for it.
Fuck it. I'm going for it. Why is this guy fucking cemented? Yes. There's a guy right here.
I haven't been alerted yet. Gas canister right there. No, I don't want to alert the whole entire
compound. Wait, not because I'm not zoomed in. You see me? Almost fucking break. Where is this
guy? He's still hiding. That's a cardboard box. I can't shoot through a cardboard box.
I can, but why did it not kill him? I think everyone's dead. At least the ones that I need
to kill are dead. There's one guy right here hiding behind a cardboard, an impenetrable cardboard box.
He's not moving. He's just going to stay there. Okay. Just stay there. Don't move. Why would you
move? Climb this part. You think that you would patch this wall? This is... I can just go in here.
Didn't see that guy. Take the pistol out? No, no, no, no. There's two guys right here. I wonder if
I can interrogate one of them. Is that walking or is that the fire? Oh, fuck. He's right there.
Holy. Did he actually turn around and look? Why is he just pivoting back and forth, back and forth?
He's looking at every exit. B. B. G. Why am I not healing? Why am I not healing? B. G. T. D. F.
Okay, it's F. That guy popped out like an old light gun game. Am I good? All right, let's deal
plans. It plays a sniper game and kills people every moment with an assault rifle. Uh, you mean
three people. I killed like 15 with the sniper rifle. So what? Like I was at an eight percentile
of shooting with the with the standard shooting weapons. It was like four. It was not more than
four. I killed like 20 people with the... All right, let's go. Where's this thing over here?
In the bunker? No scope with the sniper. I don't think you can. No, you can't. I would have done it
like three times already. Okay, easy. What's in here? I don't see any people. Stay on the tube.
Never mind. Do you see anybody? There ain't nobody here, Ryan. What up here? There's nobody in the
nest. That's odd. I just... Okay, that was like a chimpanzee in a tree. Do you see anybody? There's
like a camp over here. I'm freezing to death. Get out. Get out of the ice.
It's right here. What am I looking for? A document? Why would there be a document all the way back
here? All right. Why was there a waypoint here? Why was there a custom waypoint?
Where was I? Over... Oh my god. I put it there. God damn it. Can I climb back up this thing? Yeah,
right here. I'm good. You can't climb this? Yes, you can. Don't tell me you can't climb this. It's
literally squares. What the fuck just happened? I'm just going this way, I guess. Sorry, I have to
use my fucking hacker stripy silly string vision. Okay. Now, what am I looking for? I download the
plans. So there's a computer in here. Where's the computer? I gotta find a computer room.
All right. Computer in here. That's I mean, that's a computer. There's multiple computers in here.
There's a lot of computers in this room, but I don't think it's one of these computers.
Let's try this one. Computer. Nice name. What are you guys doing? Stop. Stop it at once. Okay,
it's not in here. Try one of the other buildings. This one. This place is just trashed. It's probably
up here. Let me look. Use the silly string vision to find the laptop. It's the laptop.
Is this a computer? No. All right. Found it. Hack it. And 17,000 dollars. I can exfiltrate.
So you exfil. All right. So you do a random mission on the map. And then you exfiltrate. So
exfiltrate. And then you do it again. I gotta kill the I can't move on from this game until
I kill the guy in this map. I have to kill the dude that came. I can't just not do that.
All right. Extraction point. Let's get it. This is gonna hurt. That almost killed me.
I could jump from there and be fine. Guaranteed. There's more than one.
Uh, let's go to this one. Pulling the wall over here. Yeah, I did it. Jump off the roof of your
house right now and prove it. It wasn't that high. All right. So I want to get how do I get out of
here? I want to go to the I want to buy stuff. All right. Where's it? Eliminate him over here.
Let's go. I'm going in. Why is it red? I'm going in. I'm gonna I'm going I'm going for the main
I'm going for the main contract. Let's go. Nobody down here. This is the way I need to go.
Elite sniper has to buy own gear. How do you think they get this stuff? I'm supposed to be
like a mercenary. Can you sleep for 32 weeks in this game? I feel like a lot of you are already
doing that. Yeah, I don't need to. Is he dead? Not good enough. You're gonna tell me where they are.
That way. Over at the base where all the people are. Idiot. Thanks for the info.
Found you. He's 75 meters away. Therefore, we're right there. Don't even need to zoom it in. Let's
get it. One, two, three. That's a super bullet. Should I not use this? Uh, I don't want this thing.
I only have four shots left. No, this thing. I don't want this thing. Use your pistol. Yeah,
this thing is better. It's not better, but you know. All right, let me keep going.
Oh, something in there. Might be a ammunition in here. This would be a pretty cool puzzle game.
I have to decide which one of these turns on which vent. Diaper check. That's pretty good.
This is your first stream. What would you think about the diaper check command? That's not real.
You wouldn't think I was a weirdo. You just think everyone here was a fucking weirdo.
All right, am I going the right way? No, I gotta go over there.
Because all I even okay, it doesn't matter if I've said any of this shit before.
If someone is a brand new viewer, I can be like, what is diaper check? What the fuck are you guys
doing? Relax. And a new viewer will go, okay, he has nothing to do with that. What are you guys
doing? Yeah, what's wrong with you guys? Even though it's all my fault. That's like kind of,
I mean, it's kind of interesting, I guess. Diaper check is funny and then a bunch of swears.
It seems that a lot of people want Ivanowski dead. All right, here we go. Which one are we
working for? Paying. Does it matter who or what they are? Individual, corporation, or government?
No, I'm a bounty hunter. Take out. All right, here we go. Let's make this happen. Guy up here.
Anybody on the other areas where there's only one person guarding this whole entire community,
I guess, wherever this is. All right, here we go. How far were you 37 meters away, which means just
Yeah, I got it. All right, they got the bad guys in here. Just a question of where
can you interrogate the bad guy? Now, I know I'm saying the bad guy, because that's just how you
generally phrase everybody that you're fighting in anything. Get those bad guys.
It's not bad guys. It's bad guys. It's its own term. It's also a way to explain to anybody
that like what you're doing is just you're playing a video game. That's the best just
Oh, what what do you do? Why did you just do that? Why'd you shoot that guy? Ah, he's a bad guy.
You want me to go off to the nuanced explanation as to what all these people are and what they're
all doing here? Well, that's how you tell your mom what you're doing. Oh, get get that guy. Get
that guy right there. Get that bad guy. I'll get him. Mom does not want lore. Mom does not want
lore. Mom wants to know make sure you're not doing drugs. I heard voices. He's in here somewhere.
Wait, am I gonna get an opportunity to go up? What was that? Are we being attacked? Are we under
attack? I think we're under attack. All right, we're under attack. Where do I go? We're under
attack. What is that for? Is it me? What's that? Camera? Oh, I've been spotted on camera. Where's
the camera? Son of a gun. Well, he's in here somewhere. He's probably in there. Mom is angry.
What do you mean mom? Interrogation. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I'm being aimed at by who?
Somebody's over there. Who? Who is it? Where are they? Where are they? Where are they?
Do you guys see anybody? I want to interrogate this guy. Oh, fuck. How did I? Great. How did
that guy not? The target is running. Target is running. Target's running. Where is he? Where is
he? Okay, I'm gonna go this way. Where is he? I don't see him anywhere. The target can see me,
but what? Where is he? Is he looking at a camera? He's on his laptop. Is that him?
I haven't seen that shot before. Right through the lens. Yep. You never see that shit. All right,
where's the target? What the fuck was that? Imagine hard scoping. Is he trying to pick up the guy's
gun? Oh, no. Oh, no. Reload. Oh, that guy's got a mask on.
Are you sure it's not the full five straight minutes of here comes the nuke alarm?
It might have something to do with that. And the noise of gunfire. Got a grenade?
Where is he? Somebody's right. Did you see that? I got a camera view of somebody else hiding over
there. Did you see that? Where is he? He's like right there. The camera went by him. He was hiding
behind a wall. Where was he? There's a lot of money here. I can hear him talking. Is he underneath?
There's too many dead bodies on the ground. I can't see. All right, let's go.
I need to find the guy that I was supposed to... I'm just going to accidentally come across this
guy, aren't I? Sniper, by the way. Yeah, well, this game wants me to infiltrate and stealth kill
people close and far. This shouldn't be called Sniper Contracts. What just happened in there?
I got him. That was him. He's in a hazmat suit. Oh, there's this gas. All right, I gotta get out
I gotta get out. This game shouldn't be... All right, I'm leaving. Who? All right, out. I got him.
Wait, let me just get one more kill really far away. I want like at least 200-300 meters like this.
Damn it, I had it.
There's no way you're gonna get more paid contracts after this. I did it.
Did you hear the guy in the tutorial?
He said something like that.
That's what he said. The guy that's in my ear said something like that.
They're waiting for me. All right, time to bring out the assault rifle because there's gonna be
like another person here and I'm gonna get the fucking insta-killed. Uploading data. Guy in hazmat
suit. I don't know where he was or what happened but the room he was in exploded. I just aimed
down a hallway and held the button down and like five people exploded. I guess one of them was in.
There's more to do here. What's the... Destroy all test results. Steal samples of the virus.
Find the client's spy. I'm not... I kind of... This is... It's not like it just said in all capitals,
this sucks, but I mean just wait. Let me continue playing up close and far away.
Did I shoot myself in the head with the gun? You should move on to hand simulator.
What do you mean bounty active? I just got him. Oh, that's the spy. Okay. All right, let's go.
Damn it. I need... All right, let's go. Bounty update. Find the spy. Who gives a shit about...
I mean, this is up close. Up close is more important sometimes. Why are the two not here anymore?
I got eyes. Bounty active. Entering bounty area. Who's the bounty? Is it this guy? I mean,
there's like a lot of smoke over here. Damn it. I saw his face. Come on. Right, I bet he... He could
hear that bullet. Almost out of ammo. Without the sniper rifle, this is just an FPS game.
Yeah, I mean it is. I mean, it's just like a... It's an open-ended just run around and...
Holy shit, that guy was blending and smoking a cigarette. That guy was... I didn't even know
he existed. I mean, okay, here's one takeaway. It's kind of cool that there's just... It's an
open-ended game where you just can walk around and do whatever you want. There's no missions.
It's just... Here's all the things that we want you to do here. Go do it somehow.
I guess that's kind of cool. But I don't even think I... I mean, leaving the bounty area. Where?
That was... Yeah, that was poor timing. I know. I'm dead. Yeah, all right. It's like, here's a
sniper, but no run through this place where there's a bunch of people walking around and shoot them
with the gun. Sniper, but it's a sniper game. But don't use your sniper. Well, you should be
using your sniper, but recon, but don't recon. Stealth, but don't stealth. Be far away. Be close.
I guess you can just do it any way you want. That's kind of the point, isn't it? All right,
this is gonna be tricky. Here on a Star Wars planet. Another one? Wait, Captain what? Captain Ivan...
That's him! That's the guy! I have to kill that guy. Did I actually miss that? I went through his...
Where is he? He has a grenade in his hand. I don't need to go any further. Let's go
find the spy. Let's move. All right, let's get in there. Wait, I can do a super... I can do a kill
thing, right? That worth more points? This is a shotgun. Like, why would you give a guy a shotgun
and a sniper? Like, I want to use this right now. Okay, in here, I gotta find the spy, then use it.
I already got the bounty. What do you mean, leaving the bounty area? Wait, do I have to like, prove it?
Did I already get that guy? I already killed him. I don't think I care. I already killed the guy.
I apparently failed the bounty. Where is he? He's in the trees. Where the fuck is he?
Now, this is what I call... That's a... I deserve at least a hundred pop champs for that one.
Dude, why do I have to take off their shell? I'm so confused. He's hiding? He's not firing at me.
Oh my god! I don't need to heal yet. I have to go this way, so... He's the same... I can't even see
through the tree. I'm throwing a grenade over there. Sometimes you have to do it. I'm out of ammo.
What's with the enemies always narrating their actions? Why can't they just stealth grenade or
stealth reload? You know, that is true, but I guess it's to tell everybody that you're...
Hey, I'm in trouble, or I'm... Somebody cover me, or... All right, only four shots in the sniper rifle.
All right, I gotta find the spy. Hey, German, this is Matthew. We've seen that copypasta so
many times now. I can't see shit. You gotta take their hard shell off and then shoot him in the face.
Uh-oh, to the right. There's a whole encampment over there. All right, am I still in the zone?
Not really. He's over here. Two bullets. That's it. Don't fall down there. What the hell is this guy?
He's like either in here or he's this way. Is there a building over here? There's a little camp up
there. That's where I just was. Wait, slow down. That's a bright light. Is there a tank?
Uh, I don't know what that is. No. I found the agent. He's dead. Retrieve any lab samples he was
carrying. Here, lab samples. I cannot find any samples. I am disappointed, seeker. Did that take
too long? I've marked safe exit points on your map. Should you choose to exfiltrate now?
I gotta spend some money, guys. That was not ideal, I know. Wait, I need to... I need health and ammo
and shit. Don't kill them. What do you mean don't kill? This is a game about killing people.
Don't kill them. What would you like me to do? Just run by them? Oh, there is no knockout. Bounty
active. All right, I gotta... I'm going... I want to go in and buy something. I feel like I've been
stuck on the first mission. I'm just doing the first mission. I'm doing everything in the first
map. We've been on snow level for two hours. All right, how do I just leave? I kind of don't want
to do that, though. Destroy all the test results? Steal samples? All right, main menu. Yeah, let's
go to... Remember the loadout screen? Isn't there a loadout? Contracts. I guess I'm just on this.
You just have to do this one. Loadout. There we go. Loadout. I have $163,000. Look at... Okay,
this is what I should have done from the very beginning. Damage, firing rate, stability,
noise reduction, so that people hear this shit. People hear this really... It's very loud.
I want the most expensive one. It's this one. Preferred range. I'm gonna sneeze. I'm sorry.
I caught it. I want... This one's in tons of damage, but why do I care about that?
I want complete noise reduction. This one here. All right, that... This is... How is this bad?
More damage, more fire rate, more stability, more damage reduction. Oh, a little bit less
mobility. Who cares? Oh. Well, I need tokens. Mobility, firing rate, stability. I'll try this
one. It's loud, but I mean, it's got better stability, more fire rate, and I can move around
and snipe. All right, I bought it. Now what? Can I do anything else with it?
Developing. There's a skill tree. Mask. How many points do I need? $25,000.
Oh, I can make... I can get the turret. No, I can't. Suit. Stamina regenerates faster,
adds Kevlar armor layer to the current armor. You're harder to detect. I want to go to that
level. I don't want to be in the snow level. This level looks cool. Turret. Increases remote
sniper turret fire range. That's not... I need to, like, get the turret. Okay, secondary weapon.
I want this to be heavy, heavy damage. I don't care about noise. I mean, this is... I already
have it on. What was the sidearm? Ooh, magnum. Fire rate, mobility, ammo capacity. I like this.
That's too much. I can't buy it. I'm getting the magnum. All right, med kit, fire grenade,
and then turret. Where's the turret? I need challenge tokens. God damn it. Warning device?
This is a cool ad. What do you mean, ad? I'm just trying to pick weapons. I can't do the
turret, guys. Unfortunate. Let's go to development. I'm going to do, uh, more, yep, detection.
Hard to detect. Uh, more armor. Uh, more sniper ammo. Yep. Uh, okay. Okay. All right, I just
got to... You're in the middle of another mission. I don't understand.
I already did this. I just said continue. I said continue. Do I just do this again?
No, I already... I already have everything. All right, let's try fast traveling.
Fast travel to here. What else do I need in order to play the next game?
Um, 500 million dollars and I'll switch. Let me try my new rifle. Oh, let's go. We can do it.
We can hit it. All right, the next time I die, well, I'm just going to play Dusk. I mean,
the game's, it's all, it's pretty fun. It's all right. I wouldn't say this is like my favorite
game ever, but I'm still interested. Dude, people think I lose interest in a video game real quick.
Yeah, here's the thing. What if I don't die? All right. Steal the data. Steal samples of the virus.
I'm going to steal the samples of the virus. Steal the samples. All right. There's like a package
in here for me. Where is it? Public media. I got 4,500 bucks for collecting that collectible.
So I just need to get back in here and steal the plans. All right. Fine. I won't even play
with the sniper. Fine. All right. I was gonna... I'm fine. Oh, shit. Sample. Where's this damp sample?
There's no, that's not a sample. Give me a sample. I need, where are the samples? Sample? That looks
like a sample. May days? This little fucking lunchbox is the sample. Are you kidding me?
Fine. Avoid combat. Good luck. Extraction point. Jump the fence. Jump the fence. If I die,
game turns off. I'm trying. I'm playing like full on FPS game right now.
Where is he? I'm going to finish the rest of this fucking level without dying.
That better be a pog. 32% completion. Let's go back up there. I'm going. Who cares? Just go.
I think I can do it. I think I can do it. I'm just going to play like this. Just check this up.
Up here. I don't need to fast travel. We got to go up here. We got to destroy the test results.
You got it. I'm getting myself ready for dusk. Dusk is all about like spin,
shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, twist, twist, twist, twist, twist, turn, twist, turn, turn,
twist, turn, shoot. I would have had it. All right. Only a hundred miles, a hundred meters.
It just took forever to reload that. God damn it, man. Really? It's not.
Find another way in this way. Attention span here. It's like I know where I'm going.
Okay. Fuck. I was doing so well too and I'm just going too fast. Whatever. Who fucking cares?
I wish I could play the other levels. It's almost like this game wants you to have this drop in,
drop out sort of mentality, but you have to stay here until when? Do I have to do all the major
objectives before I can do anything else? All right. Let's play dusk. I've never played dusk.
I have no idea what happened. It's probably going to be fun.
Let's just do dusk. Okay. Is this game good? Okay. You're going to get mad. Am I?