Start breathing. I can't, guys, I can't hear him breathing. Is he there? Can anybody hear him breathe?
Oh, shit. Imagine if I, could you guys hear me breathing before? Could you guys hear me breathe?
No, no, no, okay. Somebody's asking, where are the Winx? Well, it's disabled for now,
because we're going to give a specific place at a specific time today to do them.
Winx are going to be, we're gonna, we're gonna sit here for a little while. Winx are going to be
like 75% off. What were they, 75? They'll probably be like 10 or like 15,000. I'm just
going to sit there and listen to some music at the end of the stream today for like 20 minutes
or so and just fucking wink into the camera, like a hundred times, and then they ain't ever coming
back. They're going to be gone forever. I'm going to fuck up his eyes. No, no, no, no, no,
don't worry. I put eye drops in. I'll be all right. I'm going to set up like a Mario coin noise.
We'll just play a coin every time one comes in. You know, like a prding!
Frashing the wink economy. Well, the wink, here's the thing. You should have sold Winx
a week ago, right? You shouldn't be buying Winx now. You knew that the store was closing.
You didn't know that. Was this not going to be a wink bounce? There's not going to be a bounce
back in price. The store is closing. But anyways, welcome to community content night. This is for
the month of January. I think January into the first little bit of February. There is a lot of
stuff and I have to determine how I want to continue doing community content night going forward
because it seems like we're always 30, 40 days behind, even when we do hundreds of pieces of
artwork and dozens and dozens and dozens of videos every time. So there's always so much stuff. I am
flabbergasted at the amount of artwork and videos and music that people give
to this community and especially these streams. So I got to try to figure out a solution to make
it so we're not constantly like five weeks behind no matter what. Instead of doing it once a month,
I might try to do something like this more than that or we'll have to put a like maybe like a
filter on the submissions or something. I haven't figured out what I want to do.
It's either reduce the amount of things you show on stream or do it way more often. And I'm not
sure which one of those I want to do every other hour. But here we are. Just tell people to stop
making content. Hey everybody, don't make anything anymore. But we can get started.
Do it quicker. Well, that's the thing. I don't want to have it get to a point where I'm just like
fanning out fucking artwork cards. Just like that one, that one, that one, that one, that one,
that one, that one, that one, that one, that one, that one. Those are all cool, right? All right,
next. What we got next? This one, that one, that one, this way, that way, this way.
That kind of defeats the purpose. But here we go. Is my camera on? I'm going to play some music.
Can you hear the music? I'm already, I got, I got the, oh by the way, sorry, I'm like 40 minutes
late. Listen, the reason why I'm 40 minutes late is because fucking daylight savings time
kicked in last night and I didn't even know. This is shit that I don't even pay attention to.
I don't pay attention. Daylight fucking savings time. No, I had no idea. So I woke up this morning
and had some stuff I had to do that it was like 11 45 before I started my day. It's like, okay,
cool. Thanks. I got out of the shower and I'm just looking at my phone like, wait, what? It's
fucking noon? How's that possible? I said that what we should do is, hold on, let's look, take
a look at this. First of all, yeah, this is Celeste OST. Turn it down a little bit. But yeah,
daylight savings time just fucking killed me. It was like, everybody loves going back,
but nobody likes going forward. But when you go forward, you're just adding the time from when
you've lost it. It's just like, I hate the bouncing back and forth. I'd rather just like,
can we just do 30 minutes permanently forward? Like, do we have to go back an hour and then
forward an hour? Like, why can't we just do like a permanent, like 20 minutes forward?
Like, could it be 20 minutes and like 20 back? Does it have to be a full hour? Why does it have
to be a full hour? Make it like, I know it's the, I know it's like the farming and you're trying to
get as much daylight as possible. I, I, I, I know, I know the theory. I know, I know the reasons.
It's not even for farming. It's not, it doesn't, that doesn't even matter anymore. Does it not?
Does that not even, what's going on with my fucking like weird bug hair? Oh, we're good.
Anyways, daylight savings time. This should be like a fucking, it should be on the news.
I like the, the space cats though. This is very pretty. It's going a little more.
It was to save, what was it? It was to save resources during World War II. It's useless now.
It was to save resources during World War II? That's not, is that not even, is that, am I,
that's not even true. That's fake. Did I, was it, did I just get like a, like a Facebook fucking
reblog of something that's not even real? This is beautiful though. Look at this dude. He boogie.
If Jerma looks at this, please DM me a clip on Discord. Oh, there you go. Let's get a DM.
Well, hold on. No, not all of you. Not, not all of you. This guy's fucking mentions are
going to blow the fuck up. Thanks for the fireman. I like all of us. Oh man. I, I, whatever. What am
I supposed to do? Be like, Hey, don't, don't do that. I just like to think about what I want
to do with fireman too. Fireman needs something. Fireman needs like his own merchandise. Like
people love fireman so much. Fireman accounts for at least 10 to 20%, maybe even more, like
30% of every submission. Like everybody loves this guy. I've got, I've got to, I've got to have
something. It's like, it would be like, why, why don't I not have anything? He's cool. He's,
he's really fucking cool. He's wicked cool. The jackbox shit got taken down. Yeah. I have to figure
out what I want to do. This is a Murius. This is me controlling Murius. I love Murius so much.
Every time I see a cow, it makes me happy. You get the eyes right too. That's the best part.
Like frog eyes. That's not, that's not the cow's name. The audio is out of sync. Can we,
do we still have to keep this joke on that? Like my audio doesn't match up. How long are we going
to keep this going? Is this the new, your mic is muted? Is this, Hey, your mic's muted. My mic's
muted? Oh, fuck. Is that the new mic muted? It is slightly delayed. That's not even possible.
This shit's not even possible. It's like 10 milliseconds. It's not even, it's impossible.
All right. Anyways, it's not, clip me this. I want to see. Uh, but this is beautiful though.
It's not even delayed. These people have this shit internet. What? Why did nobody clip? I just,
I specifically demanded that somebody clip. I specifically asked that somebody clip that.
Nobody clipped it. You, uh, this is, I was trying to figure out when there's another thing of what
to do about, uh, photo shops. There's a lot of photo shops that get put into the community content,
uh, discord. I'm trying to think like, should it, should it, should photo shops be allowed anymore?
Cause like, there's like hundreds of photo shops. Keep them, ban them, no. But some photos, this is
the thing. It's like, this is why it's hard to determine what's like, what should be on screen.
Cause some photo shops are just like, somebody took the squish tool and like dragged it across
the screen. And it's like, all right, dude, you just, you like did the squish tool and you just
like dragged it across my eyes and my nose and you hit export. And then some of them are very,
very well made. It's still art. Yeah. But just remove the bad ones. Well, that's the thought.
That's the idea is like, just slowly try to cut off, uh, have a filter at least somewhere. So it's
not just like 100% of everything gets put on the screen. I'm trying to figure it out. This is only
community content. Number five. I love, I love shitposts. I love shitposts, but you, but we,
should we just have like a shit? But no, we can't have a shitpost category because shitposts,
that could be everything. That could be literally anything. And if you have a shitpost category,
holy fuck that. You think that there's, there's, there's like a thousand submissions a month. Now
it will be like 5,000 shitposts a month as physically not even possible to show on stream.
It would be like, that's like two weeks of streams. Oh no, that would, that'd be impossible.
Electric skin plus glass body. He said he loves it. Do a shitpost week. Yeah. I can't just like
stream myself looking at shitposts. Electric skin. This is from, um, what's that Kingsway?
Is this Kingsway? Show your armpits. No. Get out of here. Please play Danganronpa. Some, uh,
Jerma Rumble fan art. And we got the pencil. Let's get a good zoom in here. I like this. I like the,
I like the bug guys. Do not play Danganronpa. Don't, don't worry. I'm not going to. Don't worry.
I'm not, I'm not going to play Danganronpa. I, like, I'm just not, I'm not going to. I fucking
hate the pencil. So do I. And I made him. That was the biggest mistake of my whole entire career.
Biggest mistake of my entire career was creating this character. Because the second that that,
that I made him and the second that that video went up, I was like, no,
no, that was a mistake to make him. But, uh, I, I, I, I, I'm breaking my rules saying I'll never
play something. That's not true. I might never play it. There's some more, uh, art. What's this?
Uh, spy crab. Pick dastardly Richard, glue man. This is year of the rat. That's true. It's like
a fireman rat. So what is next year? What's next year? The year of you're the fish rat too.
All right. You're a year of the rat too. You're actually you're on the fish. Is it the ox? I,
this one's here because I wanted to go over this because this is wrong. This is incredibly
inaccurate. That's been corrected. Um, health is actually at one at this point. I have one bar in
hell. DPS is probably somewhere around like somewhere around a yellow. I definitely not
red. Definitely not speed. Speed is app is, is speed is that fucking red. Did you see how you
couldn't even see how fast that was. That was too fast. The camera didn't pick it up. What fell the
we sensor bar. It's okay. That's made it a fucking plastic. Uh, defense is probably like a yellow
range is like a green. I mean, I'm, I don't have that much like, I don't have that much range.
I mean, I'll be honest with you. I do have, actually I kind of have long arms though.
I have really long fucking arms. I have like a short body and long arms and a long torso.
The only reason why I'm like just about five eight is because I have like this big ass like
swimmer's torso. So I got, I don't have long legs, but I got a long torso. He's lanky Kong.
Yeah. Lanky Kong. If lanky Kong was like five inches shorter than how big he is.
And I kind of have big hands too. Remember we talked about this. Like I've got big hands.
He has no grace. Yeah. But that thing, this is, this is definitely way up here. Lanky Kong is
not a red on speed. Lanky Kong is like a zero for speed, isn't he? You're like an alien. Yes,
I have an alien body. That's correct. I've got really wide shoulders, like a small waist, long
torso, like big fucking eyes. No, I don't. The Bostonian psycho. It's me with a Shido.
He has no style. He has no grace. This guy's got a funny face. Yeah. That means that's,
what else does it say about lanky Kong? What are the other lanky Kong lyrics?
This Kong is a fucking disgrace. That's not the lyrics. That's not the lyrics. It does not say
that. It doesn't. No, it doesn't say that. It doesn't say why. They wouldn't put that in a
kid's game. I like this one though, with my trusted friend Shido. It does say that. It does not say
that. I like the background. I like the, Jerma is doing a thing where he talks about art again,
where he's like, I like the background. I like how squishy it is. Like, I don't know what the
fuck I'm talking about. It didn't say fucking. No, it didn't. Why would it do that? I hate some rat.
It's like a bunny. It's a bunny rat. You got the facial hair, right? That's like, that's pristine.
Correct. I do, I even, I have hairs that grow up here. I really do. Can I even show this? Like,
I have hairs that like grow up here. You see that? There's like hair up here. Like, why is
their hair growing here? Like, why is that happening? You get a zit? One. One in 10 years.
Sorry. One zit in 10 years. Sorry, guys. Now, this, this is the thumbnail for a video
called the Speedy Grinner. The video, I think, has been DMCA takedown by this point.
So, if you are the owner and operator of the Speedy Grinner video, you're gonna have to
probably re-upload it because this was not available when I tried to click it. Stay. Stay.
Imagine taking down a Jerma video. Wait, is it, it's back up? Is it? Hold on. Let me get this. Is
this it? Alright, let me, hold on. Let me just get this added. Is this actually it or is this a
fucking gnome or something? Please tell me you guys aren't doing this to me right now. Let me
just check it. Click on the crosswalk. Why, why, why, click on crosswalk. Why does it, why does it,
I'm not a robot. Why does YouTube think I'm a robot now? Oh, the Speedy Grinner. There it is.
Alright. Yeah, no, it's real. Alright, let me just put this in the queue here. Probably just start
with that. It's easy just to put it there. Alright, back to what we were doing. There we go. This is
just, you know, a scary image of the guy that I get referred to a lot as, which is unfortunate
because I don't think I am this person at all. I think that I'm more of, you already know.
You guys know who I think that I am. My Marvel fursona. It's the Riddler. You have to be smart
to be the Riddler. You gotta be fucking, you know how I'm smart enough. You gotta be fucking smart.
If you keep cunning, dangerous, and with it, and this is a Joker. I'm doing a Joker.
I'm the Riddler. That's my, that's my Marvel fursona. I'm the Riddler. Punch, punch, defend,
break his legs. What is this from? Punch, punch, defend, break his legs. Oh, it's from Black and
White, right. Murius. Punch, punch, break his legs. What a psycho. I'm the Riddler. The Riddler's a
psycho too. If you do like a psycho-analytical on the Riddler, he's a, he's a, he's a psycho,
so that's fine. Jeremy Albertson. A stupid fucking production of some kind of currency thing.
Oh, a stupid fucking production. Stupid fuck. Stupid fucking goddamn. No, I gotta do the face too.
Wanna see an actor? Stupid fucking goddamn fucking thing. Stupid fucking goddamn fucking
piece of fucking shit. Stupid fucking thing. Fucking ridiculous. I'm not really bad. I mean,
I'm an actor. But I do. Some kind of currency thing. Uh, I got too scared of these to finish
them. Sincerely snoozing copter. Uh, I'm scared of these too. Yeah, these freak me out. The one in
the back is, no, this one right here. It's like Bilbo grab the ring vibes. I make the Bilbo grab
the ring fucking face all the time, don't I? Like, I can't even, I do that all the time.
Not even on purpose. That one looks real. It's not real. Uh, this is Jerma the cute goblin.
Okay, I thought these, I thought I had a bunch of earrings. Is this hair? It's the same face.
It's close. These need to be a little higher. No, my hair's too long. You can't even see it.
Pretty cool. Teeth, my, my teeth goblin. Oh, tooth goblin. Uh, you are fooled to believe
that I can be contained. Uh, are you going to grow mutton chops? You know, it might be kind of funny
for me to do that, but, uh, if I just shaved everything else and let this grow disgustingly,
um, I, my, my girlfriend would no longer touch me. Like, I'm just going to be honest with you.
If I did that and it was, it was these gross, big, long hairs here and it would be all fucked up and
all gross and disgusting. I, I, I, you're, you're, you're literally making me delete
my entire intimate life that I have with my girlfriend. So that's Wolverine appeal. No,
the appeal of Wolverine is nice. It's, it's thick and it's, it's there. And no, that's not the appeal
of Wolverine. The appeal of Wolverine, Wolverine's got fucking scissors that come out of his hands.
What are you talking about? You get rid of the scissors on his hands and his healing capability
and he's just a guy on the subway. It's not, oh, Wolverine has that. He can do 600 sit-ups.
Yeah, because while he's doing the sit-ups, his body is, he's tearing his muscles up and their
body, they're healing instantly. Wolverine could spend a day, a full day at the gym and do every
single body group three times. Jealous. Check his hair. Check hair. What, what, like, what is it
going to be like fucking clean in here? Like, what do you think it was? Check your hair.
It's cool. I don't agree. I just took a shower fucking like three, four hours ago or something,
whatever it was at 11 45. I remember because I was pissed about daylight savings time. It's
done greasy lice. I had to include this one because it's fucking funny. Well, I don't even
remember what this is from, but I mean, it's, that's very, very, very fun. I remember that
somebody made this within 10 seconds. It's from rhythm heaven. Oh, that was a fucked up stream.
That was a weird one. It was like normal. Rhythm heaven was very normal and fun for about four and
a half hours. And then it turned into this shit. It was a ton. I had a bunch of fun, but like I,
I wasn't doing this in the first four or five hours. Uh, this is from the FTK stream King
Jermo, which by the way, people have been looking for an update on that. Uh, there's currently an
FTK part two that's in development right now. It is not even going to be remotely close to the way
that it was before. It's going to be very, very, very different, way different than what you,
what you experienced last time. We are changing it completely. We're going to try it. It's still
going to be a Minecraft, but the whole idea is going to be a lot more, um, planned and stuck to
do. So there will be at least one more of these scripted content. No, I mean, just planned,
like not just running around with a stone ax and fucking singing while people try to shoot arrows
at me and walking people in little cubes to fight each other. Like it's going to be like stuff to do
and not 5,000 people connecting at the same time. Look at this dude. I see this image a lot and I
don't really know what it is. This is, this is a Jojo thing. It has to be because of that, right?
J omega low J omega low. Uh, I don't know what it's referencing exactly, but people seem to
really like this exact scene. Uh, I think we've never seen this one before. We've seen stuff from
science before since, and I'm going to, I say it wrong every time and I will always say it wrong.
Hard for me to even remember my own friend's names. It's a lie. So like, don't like people like,
well, that's kind of concerning, dude. Like what are you fucking talking about? That's, I'm kidding.
It's a joke. Joe the werelord. The werelord has turned into a auto bed. Uh, it's been washed
and it's now autos like coy auto leg loves this thing. He sleeps on it. He plays with it.
It's like auto bed now. It's very cute. Tomato flan Leo's. I remember this. This is from the
last, I think. Yeah. Can we go over this breakfast for a second? Uh, more, this is important. So I
don't know who the fuck, there's gotta be some insider bullshit with like the breakfast industry
on how much food and how much shit you're supposed to have out during breakfast time.
Right. So when I eat breakfast, if I'm have a bowl of cereal, it's just a bowl of cereal.
Go back, go back. What do you mean go back? What, what, what, what happened? What? Oh, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What? Oh, please. You've already seen that one. Anyways, anyways,
when I eat a bowl of cereal, I'm done. In fact, sometimes I pour a little too much cereal than I
think I can even eat. And you eat half the bowl of cereal and you look at the rest of the soggy mess
that you've made and you go, Oh, this is fucking, this is gross. I don't even want to eat this.
So you try to, what I try to do now is do a little bit of cereal, a little bit of milk,
eat that first, a little bit of cereal, a little bit of milk, eat that until I'm done.
Right. Instead of just dumping a five cups of cereal in a bowl this high.
This is what I don't understand. I don't know anyone that's ever done this in their entire life
is have a bowl of cereal, eggs, breakfast, whatever. And then have like a buffet of scones
and shit on the table. And sorry to sound strange here, but coffee and orange juice,
that doesn't mix together very well. What are you taking a sip of orange juice
and then taking a sip of your coffee? That's like brushing your teeth and then drinking
orange juice. If you know that combination, it's like a cilantro like instant puke reaction
for a lot of people. So what do you drink? You got to drink this first. No, you got this,
you got to drink this one first. It's hot and then drink this later. It's room temperature.
The whole like complete breakfast is always like three pieces of toast, four scones, three eggs,
two pieces of bacon, a full bowl of cereal and oatmeal. What the fuck are you talking about?
I eat one of these in the morning because I don't, in the morning I get like kind of,
I'm not hungry in the morning. I can only eat something light or small or something a little
bit. Who eats four danishes for breakfast in the morning and like a full orange juice and a bowl
of fucking tomatoes? Well, this is not, I mean, that's rude. Just like give me a cup of coffee
and like maybe some toast with a little bit of fucking jam on it. That's it. Or like a little
bit of cereal. Maybe even like some, just like a smoothie or something. Like this is ridiculous
and I'm sick of it. I'm sick of hearing about this. What are you going to do about it?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing. I'm just going to complain to you about it for like 10 minutes
and then forget I even was angry about it in the first place. And then a year will go by
and I'll see it again and it'll irritate me for five minutes again.
Take that fucking food industry. Moving on. I don't have to say sorry about that.
Hello, you know, small ass Megalop, tiny fuck. Now this is a good one. Half of you don't leave
because he's on screen. Literally unintelligible. The down arrows. I can't get over that. It's so
funny to me. I wake up laughing at this sometimes. I'm in the shower laughing about this. That was
like a big Halloween stream. It was like almost 10,000 fucking people watching that stream and
like five, like four fucking thousand people left. I can't even, I have to talk about it every time
because it's fucking hysterical to me. This is great though. This is fantastic. I even forgot,
I didn't at one point, wasn't I like eating bugs and stuff? Well, not me, but I saw it on the screen
over here. I saw it on, I was watching and I was like, what is he doing over there? What is he
crazy? Wasn't he eating, wasn't he eating bugs in like clay? There was a joke that was supposed to
be happening and it might have been too dark, but there were spiders. Little spiders. Look, look, I'm
spoiler alert. There were bugs. We had spiders that were on strings and one of the people that
were there, one of the crew was, was going to drag them across the table and I was going to
keep eating them and the strings all broke. So we, so I had to try to find ways to eat the spiders
and one of them was huge. One of them was this big and before we started, before the stream was live,
I remember the, the production manager was just like, are you, are you, are you, I don't think we
can do that. And I'm like, well, yeah, we can. We'll figure it out. We put them on the strings.
They were supposed to bounce across the table and like, give it out. Oh, and it didn't work at all.
Wait, that was you? I was in, I was a part of the production. I knew this is a person that I hired.
This wasn't me. Of course not. It's not fucking me. I will prove it to you guys. I'll prove it to you
guys. Don't worry. One day I'll prove this to you that we're not the same person. I will be in the
same room with bugleberry on camera. That's not the same person. Big wow chat is big brain chat.
Remember rum layout. Can't, oh, can't remember rum layout. Sorry. No scanner, no scanner. Tag me.
No, I'm shy. Please don't ask for tagging since some tag on purpose. Wait, tag me?
Is this me saying this? I like the, I like the, is that, that's supposed to be Kim? I wish I had these.
That'd be great. Leg muscles. Holy shit. Whoa. That's, that's some, that's some, that's some
turkey leg right there. That is like a full like Disney turkey leg. Jesus. All right. Nice.
Tricked you. Uh, what'd you trick us for? It's Egypt and we're both blog pyros. What is this done
with? It's very neat. It's like, it's almost like a crayon. It looks like crayon. Very well done
crayon. Crayon brush. That's cool. Don't you want to see this as a, hold on. I have to apply lip balm
before I turn into fucking dust. Don't you want to see like a cartoon like this? They already did.
What was it? What was it called? Um, uh, what the fuck was it? God. It was like, was it, you know,
a kid that could draw stuff. The Chalk Zone. Yeah, that's what it was. Good thing I wasn't on camera
for that embarrassing impression. Yeah, it was, it was Chalk Zone. They still making episodes of that
TV show or is it gone forever? What do they still make episodes of? What the fuck is on TV right
now? Teen Titans. Well, I could have told you that it was Teen Titans. Teen Titans has turned into
the infomercial of Cartoon Network. And what I mean by that is it's on like six straight hours.
You know, like when you, when you turn on TV at like one o'clock in the morning, it's infomercials
for like seven hours straight. Teen Titans is now the like, we don't know what to put on this block.
It's going to be four or five straight hours of Teen Titans. It's such, it's such a great thing
just to have there. It's got the music on here. I don't, that's not, I don't have anything bad to
say about Teen Titans. I don't even watch it. I'm just saying, I just, I'll have the TV on. This
actually happened very recently. It was like, I thought I was stuck in a fucking time warp
because I was drifting off and it was very, very late. I fell asleep and I, well, I put the TV on.
So the TV's turned on. It's on Cartoon Network. I was watching like Adult Swim before I fell
asleep or something like that. This is in a hotel room. And I remember hearing, okay, and coming up
next, we've got Teen Titans Go. Let's get it. Let's go, whatever they do, right? And it was like,
Nickelodeon splashes and stuff. And then, okay, I woke me up and I then went back to bed. And then
I woke it up by again. All right, Titans, it's time for Teen Titans Go. And I'm like, Teen Titans Go
happened again. And I fell back asleep. And this happened like three more times before it was like,
okay, Titan Goers, Teen Titans Go coming up next, only on Cartoon Network. And I like grabbed the
fucking remote and I was like, shut the fuck up. Turn it off. I thought I could just sleep with
this, but no, turn this shit off. What is this? What is it? What are you doing? Okay. So, um,
this is a schedule for Cartoon Network. Gumball, Teen Titans Go. This is, it doesn't, yeah, this
is real. There are three television shows. Okay, I love Gumball. If there's anything that I think
Gumball should have, Gumball should have a block here. Okay. But I mean, when your schedule
on your television network looks like somebody that needs a disc defragmentation,
nothing's probably wrong. I'm just saying. Look at the Christmas one. Hold on, there's a Christmas
one. What? Is this a joke? Or is this like somebody fucked this up and made this the way
Teen Titans? Oh, Steven Universe! Steven Universe! What time? Friday at 7 30. Whoa. Teen Titans Go
Island Adventure. Is that a movie? Cause this is, this is, no, this is, what is this? A movie?
It's a 30 minute episode. They made a movie too. Well, um, all right. That was the Cartoon Network
schedule. Let's get back to where we were, which I believe wasn't right here. Hey, was it this one?
Were we on this one last? Moving on. Jerma and his gamer son. This is from rewatching the Mario RPG
Vaude and thought something like this would make 12 year old Jerma pog his ass off.
Season 2. Fighter Pass 2. Fighter 1. Travis Touchdown. Fighter 2. Geno. Fighter 3. Beautiful
Joe. Fighter 4. Mew 2. Fighter 5. Fire Emblem Carrot. And I don't know which one,
cuz they're all the same. Get a load of this guy. That's not even a hot take. That's not even a
hot take. That's not even a hot take anymore. That was a hot take like five months ago,
or like a year ago. That's me just being like, hey, like, I'm gonna jump on that thing that
people say. Hey, you know that thing about like too many Fire Emblem characters and that they're
all like sword users? Hey, I'm gonna say that now. Aren't I like controversial? And it's like, dude,
come on. Somebody made that joke like fucking two years ago. But really though, I hope we don't,
I hope we don't see any more Fire Emblem characters. I hope we don't. I mean, that's
Siri. What a cool Siri. Just Super Mario. They don't need more people in it than Super Mario
Brothers. Super Mario Brothers character here, by the way. Super, I haven't seen a new
representer for the Mario series in, it's never, it's just Wario. Like Smash Brothers Brawl.
Piranha Plant. Fuck! Fuck! Here's Waterman. Delete your stream. Apology. This is cute. This is
kind of scary, but it's cute. At the same time, I mean, the rat is cute. Wait, why is it, wait,
no, is the rat like sad? What's, wait, what's going on here? What's wrong with me? Let him go,
let him go, let him go. Why, why do I have this impression on people? I do not like this painting,
chat. It's smug or mocks me. World War II. World War III. Wait, is that supposed to be just me?
I don't understand. I don't understand. Nice baseball. Yeah, unsettling. It's like that,
this, this is like my, I have such an evil presence. Why do I have such an evil fucking
presence in every picture? Every time, that Joel Vinesauce, he didn't, he didn't make this.
Why would he make this? Why would Joel draw a picture of me, like, very detailed picture of me
in a fucking baseball uniform? This is, there's no way this is Joel. He did not make this.
That's so odd. Like, that's so odd. Why would you put this here? This is like a really, like,
detailed picture. Joel didn't do this. No, I'm not saying that Joel, like, can't make detailed photos.
I'm saying, like, why would he do this? He, like, he doesn't have time for this. He's busy.
Call Joel. He's crying. Why not? He didn't draw this. He did not. I've seen Joel's drawings.
And by the way, one of them's on here. One of Joel's drawings is actually on here.
And it wasn't like me batting detailed. No, it's, it's like, he drew me with these big
stacked shoulders and these tiny legs. This is not a Joel photo. This is a fake photo.
He made two. I don't, I don't think he drew this. What if he did? I, that's, I know. What,
what if he really did? Somebody find out for me. Like, and I'll hear back. What a fake friend.
What? Oh, I love this. He said he did. Did he? Did he actually? Uh, is that true? Yes.
Whoa. You go, big guy. Uh, this is the rats. He'd be a rat and fireman. Everybody's lost.
Is that guy a triplet of a theme park? Think of how many great theme park characters exist
in this community. Can you imagine the rides that could be made over like the rats and fireman and
me? Did you like that little? I just did like a smug neck head.
I didn't do that on purpose. This is cute though. Uh, this is, you seem to be a short streamer. Do
you need help with that? Yes. Help me or no. This is, uh, from hypnospace, hypnospace outlaw.
I look to be in some, in some distraught BWL, right? Uh, get well soon. German from Jude
Minecraft. Has to be, gotta put a Garfield in there somewhere. It's cool. Cute. Of course,
there's a rat. Always a rat. Garfield. What was the last Garfield reference? Anybody know?
What was the actual last Garfield reference? Okay. I'm so sorry. Not right. No, no, no. I mean,
like a true Garfield is, has a significant time on stream. Um, I was rubbing my face and had an
itchy eye. But in like 2018, yeah. Uh, fireman, waterman, earthman, windman. Pretty cute. This
is element man. What element am I? Didn't I already do that? This is me eating my own arm.
But what was, what element was I? Wasn't I fire or air or something? I was air because I could,
I just like fucking fly around and like float around and I'm like, I'm like this way, that way,
this way, that way. Right. And I got like, I'm air, right? Yeah. I'm definitely an air spirit.
Yeah. That's my, my element for sauna is air for sure. Oh, by the way, I'm not even reacting
to this on stream. Yes. This is me eating my own arm. But I did this, I was angry at a game
and I bit my arm very, very gently. Is that from Mr. Mosquito? Toad lipstick. Somebody will, if you
don't, if you just link it, link the clip. We have little, uh, collectible icons. This grandpa.
That one just stuck out so much for me. Little like figurines. All right. Let me see if I get,
this is checks. Uh, egg with a bird and eye, sun, moon, chair. Everything is mining of Isaac,
by the way. Like these, I could, I could see me running into a room and picking all these up and
then giving like plus like two speed or like plus one damage or something. Oh, that's been on the
mind lately. Finding the Isaac's been on my brain every day now. You know what that means?
That means it's time to sit up to play it. I've made, when I start making references to shit,
that's how you know it's time. Although not World of Warcraft because I'm not going to play that
again. I don't see something gross. So this is, uh, this is what happens if you let a coffee sip.
There's a little bit of almond milk in here and it's turned into that where the coffee is on top
and the almond milk is now on the bottom, which now this is a gross drink and the ice has watered
it down. Just mix it with my finger. Ballast. Oh, Jeremy, you're not fucking good at anything.
Jeremy, you can't do anything. What do you have like two IQ? I almost just spilled it on myself
right there. Uh, this is great though. This is awesome. This is a, uh, re-imagining. I think
we've seen this before. This is the most interesting man in the world face. I don't even know why this
is here. It's, uh, it's me. I don't even know. I don't know. I guess. Look at that hair though.
That's long. It's long now, but that was very long. I look like Wes Anderson. Does he still look like
this? Fishy mint. This is a little fireman icons and, uh, chat. This is really cute. I love it.
Let's zoom in a little. It's great. Good shit. Here we go from that to this. Okay, if this is
like fireman, this is fireman's like evil grandma. Holy shit. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh those fucking toes.
Oh my God. That's fucking heinous. That is heinous. Oh, this is good though. This is very,
very, very good. Whoa. I know what it sounds like too. It's got like what it is like.
You think you can stop me? I don't think so. He's got like a, well, I like an Ursula voice. Just,
okay, make that talk with a line from Ursula. What do you think this sounds like? Have this lip sync
poor unfortunate souls while walking around and like going like this and like this. That's grandpa.
I can't do Ursula. Try. I just did. And apparently everybody fucking hated it. This is Zapman.
This is not a fireman, but like with a person's face. Oh, Murius. Always, always up vote Murius
under every circumstance. Very cute. Here's the poses that I did that I can never delete.
Little did I know. And I remember this stream of picking up a YouTube video
and like desperately trying to do these as accurate as possible and not even knowing
what I was doing when it's green screen stream too. I don't know. I don't know. I can't.
I don't know. I don't know. Once like I feel, I wish I could fucking tell you.
We'll talk about it in a second, but this is pixel art of bugleberry,
which is actually pretty good. I like it a lot. Actually it's an emo. It's a little too big for
an emo, but I think it specifically said it wasn't supposed to be an emo. They just like doing pixel
art. Let's see. I'd be a little too dark. No, maybe not. Like up here and like down here.
I can, I guess, you know, you can see it. It works. Put the candle. It's a discord emo. Oh,
okay. Well, that makes sense. You will be flashed. You know, I've thought about what I want to go
back to. I really want to go back to light gun stuff. I do, but just so hard to actually capture
that and get it right. If you, if you actually, I don't think it's possible without a CRT TV,
CRT TV. And that thing was such a pain in the ass. If that thing's gone forever. No, that,
I do not have that TV. That TV, that TV was such a pain in the ass. Seriously. You know how hard
that was to get that out of that fucking room? You know how hard it was to get it into the room?
Thing was 400 pounds. What song? This is the Celeste OST. No, it's just, I don't know exactly
what song it is. It's just on the OST. Very, very good OST. Very good music in this fucking game.
The game's really good too. I think it was fun. It's a fun game. Oh, here are the three,
Dick Dastley Richard and the other two that don't have names. This is the only one that had a name.
This is cool. I like the coin. Oh, is it? It's a bald coin. It's a bald coin. It's the gang. It's
the gang. The gang's here. Give them names now. I don't know. Fucking Button Up Barry and Dr.
Digestion. No, don't leave that. There's more of these. I think this is the, the same group.
Put these together. Too late. Too late. Already on the wiki. Too late. Too late. Too late.
You know, like the original shitty drawing that I did, that was the thumbnail for all the grandpa
videos in like 2011, 2012. That's the original. You drew a face in less than five seconds.
Making an emote. Why would I make this? It's not even relevant anymore. Grandpa is like not a
relevant character. He's been replaced by Bugle. And he's gone. Didn't you see the German Rumble
live? He's gone. He's, he's gone. No longer relevant. Snort. He's a demon. Hey, he's back in hell.
He got one opportunity to come through the portal and he fucked it up. He ain't dead. Well, I mean,
he's, he's where he is. He had a heart attack. How do you fuck that up? I don't know. He should
have been like, he should have been taking like an omega-3 supplement in hell. What am I supposed to
do? What is this? What character is this? Slime man? I love Pac-Man. Pac-Man, I'm starting to
realize something. Cheeto is kind of just a zoomer Pac-Man. I'm kind of realizing this.
They're both wicked cool. But yeah, wicked cool. What? I'm from fucking Boston, dude. Is that
how we fucking talk, dude? This is great though. A little sketch we have. Oh, if you give me that
pillow, I'll give you this toothbrush. Okay, just don't tell my dad. See, look, I told you,
this is now actually, this is now locked into canon. See, it's a werelord. That's a good trade.
That's not a bad trade. We have Cheeto on the playground with other, that's a J and then
a little slug. Oh, is that the snake? This is farmer man, I think is what it was. What the fuck
is going on? Hey, hey, how do I get rid of, how do I get rid of the magnifying glass?
I have the magnifying glass open right now. You can't see it on your screen. How do I get
rid of the escape? I pressed alt. Hold on, there it is. Okay, that was weird. This works so well.
It like, it's perfect. It's like, that's, it's just, it's perfect. What do I, what do you want
me to tell you? Here, hey, hey, cheers to that one. Oh sure, okay. A coffee from earlier this
morning and you got another cup because you're a fucking weirdo and didn't put ice and new
coffee in this cup. Sure. Cheers to that one. Of course we will. Joel and Jerma, Joel versus
Jerma from the Vine Wrestle. The coffee is fucking vile, dude. No, it's not. That's just coffee.
Fucking looks like a little bit of almond milk in it. That's just, that's just coffee. That's just,
that's black coffee with like almond milk and then no sugar, no bullshit, no sweetener, no sweetness.
Sure, vanilla? I'm gonna add. Although that would be a 10. Uh, here we go. Almond milk is disgusting.
Okay, what would I say? Hey, you wouldn't dumb. Don't, hey. That's like, okay, that's like saying
I don't like the color green. All right. Why do you have a green car? I don't like the color green.
Uh, is that your car? No. Whose car is it? It's your car. Right, right. Fuck yeah, I don't like
that color. That color sucks. Destroyed with facts. That was a bad analogy. No, it's not. It's if you
don't like the color green, I don't give a shit. I like the color green. It's not your car, motherfucker.
Stretch is squish. I love the stretch. It's just like happy rat lunar year. Oh my goodness. This is,
this is cool. This is cool. Right? You know what I'm saying? You know what I mean? You know what I'm
saying? Right? You know what I mean? Should learn words at the end of sentences. Oh, this is cool.
I like it. Uh, this is, this is the chat fursona apparently. Um, why, why do I, this is like,
this right here and this. Wouldn't it somewhere else? Chat rat. Chat's official fursona is here
at long last. Evil. Greasy. Something. All right. Where's bag to honor dick dastardly? And it's,
I don't, I hate this word. I hate that word. You know, there's some, like we, there's some words
that, that, that you, that you just hate the way they sound. You don't like even saying them or
hearing them. Like I can't even say it. I hate it. I hate the way it sounds. It's like, it's like,
I hate it. I can't say it. I can't say it. Stinky. Oh, I fucking hate that word. I hate that word.
Smelly is a little better, but, oh, that's the most unpleasant sounding word in the English
language. Stinky. Stinky. I'm done. This is a lot of stuff going on in here. There's the FTK stream.
It's moist. No, it's not moist. It's fine. Moist. You know why moist is perfectly fine? Because when
I think of the word moist, I think of, I think of a cake and I think of fork. I think, I see a
fork pressing down on a cake and the cake like smushing and getting coagulated into the fork
and then suddenly the fork going in and picking up the piece of cake. That's, that's what I see
when I hear the word moist. I think of a pound cake that you put in your mouth and it just like
smushes down in your gums and teeth and shit. When I think of the word stinky, I think of
like dirty laundry. Like, oh, like a diaper. Like, oh, stinky. Oh, no, like a diaper.
Go like cat litter. Yeah. Like, oh, let's stinky cat litter. Oh, fuck that word. That word sucks.
All right. Let's go. This is great though. Oh, wait, wait. I want to see what a
$75,000 for this. It's pretty cheap though, don't you think? Look, more, more evidence.
Look, I told you guys. I think that this, this probably, this probably a picture of this somewhere.
You're the rat. This is really, really good. This is like really, really detailed.
Really nice work. Show the picture. I don't have the picture available to me.
This is manga, anime, and then the Netflix adaptation. It's pretty good. Pretty good.
There it is. See, this is Joel. Joel Vinesauce drew this one. Not like the guy with the,
not the bat one. That's a different style. Is this supposed to be me or Joel? That's me, right? Of
course it is. I, that's my fucking body type. Here is a, just a rat. Or you're the rat. I like
this. You know, this is like my, one of my favorite colors. Of course it is. Of course it is.
I am exhibit A. I love this light sort of teal aqua green experiment kind of green,
like teal into spearmint. I could look at this all day. I know what this smells like. You know
what I mean? This has a smell. It's like a clean, fresh laundry smell. It's like a minty laundry
air, like opening up your window on a fucking cool afternoon in the fall.
No, not, not that word. I know this color has a smell and this color has a taste.
Look at this. Look at my, look at my shirt and imagine what it tastes like.
See? It's not mint. It's like a freshness. Like a pistachio ice cream kind of freshness.
So this is the, it's mint. It's not mint. There are other things that are light green that aren't
bubble gum. Like, like the green milkshake from Sonic. It's like the St. Patrick's Day milkshake
from Sonic. Eat that, food industry. It's mint. It's literally mint. No, it's, it's whatever.
Toothpaste, toothpaste, toothpaste. No, toothpaste is like toothpaste. It's like frozen. It's like
blue and no, no, and tooth, most toothpaste is just white. All right. I, I gotta talk about some
stuff. Moving on. This is the bet that we had between me and Joel when we did keep talking
and nobody explodes, which was, I had to eat like a quadruple bypass burger. I haven't, I haven't
done that yet. Oh no, I had to put it in my underwear. I didn't have to put one of these in
my underwear. I'm not going to do that. So like, that was like a joke that we did. Wait, didn't,
didn't he, did he eat like a bunch of raw eggs? Wait, it's not a scam unless, unless he did his
part. He actually ate a bunch of raw eggs. He did. That's not good. That's not okay. Don't do that.
You need to steam them first so you can get rid of the bacteria. Uh, I'll put a fucking hamburger
down my underwear in like, I don't know, like a couple years or something. Here's a rat. That's
me on the rat's nose because you know, this one's clever. This is the LGBT pose. I thought it was
clever. It's very clever. I get it. I get it. Yeah, it's like, it's clever. This shit's clever.
This is Batman. What is this? Is this, no, this is Joel. Oh, that's Joel. That's me and Joel. I
thought I was holding a, I thought, I didn't know what this was. All right. I, I was just sweating.
Clock. The omega symbol. Right, right, right. Hey, this is really good though. Thank you.
This one's fucked. Look at how fucked up this is. This is the janitor smashing your fucking head
with the, this is, this is insane. What? That's, that was really good. It's cute. Come on.
New emote. A new walking emote? Will it be Fireman walk? I feel like, I think we've seen this image
before, but it's still, this is, this is the like, you're the baby, right? This is like the,
you opened your eyes for the first time and like, like dads, you're the baby in my arms, right?
Did we do something weird? I don't remember any. I don't remember what we did two days ago.
Nice fucking neck. What you meant to say was, why does it look like my nose and right eye have been
photoshopped into this photo? Here is, uh, German Wars, The Rat Awakens. Which is pretty good.
I love lightsabers. Remind me, please, when I eventually do get in front of the green screen
again, I know I've been putting off for a long fucking time, but I, I know there's a whole thing
that's a suggestion, but please remind me that when we do it again, I want to get a fake lightsaber
thing and I want to do a full on like lightsaber actual like, and I want, I need it. I need it just
for me. I want a full lightsaber event that I'm going to do with like 20 lightsaber different
things. I want all lightsabers. Make sure the lights, the lightsabers green. Yeah. I want a
full on green lightsaber. Roll eats an egg. Hold on. I'll look at it in a second, but this is,
this is pretty cool. All the Jojo poses. Hey, look, it's a little rat. Not green at a blend in.
Have Bugleberry be on it and give him a Darth Maul lightsaber. Maybe.
Rep in the fireman shirt. This is good shit. Animal crossing. Oh yeah, that is cool. That's
like an animal crossing. This is cool. I didn't even realize that. Here is, I don't know,
but looks good. Am I going to play, I'll play the one on Switch when it comes out.
I love the hat. You got the carnival hat in here. Why is there a reason? Oh, because I said I was
going to play Odd Michael. Hey. Oh, not quite. A little too green. Good shit. Can't wait for you
to play it. This is, I zoomed in a little too much, but this is some pixel art of the J.
Yeah, I'll play the Switch one. When does it come out? I don't want to play the old ones,
but I want to play the new one. Comes out in 12 days. What? Holy shit. Yeah, let's go.
Look, I'll play the fuck out of that game. Comes out the same day as Doom Eternal.
Oh. Now I'll play an animal crossing first. We'll do Doom Eternal afterwards. I look like the villain
in two or three specific Goosebumps books. This is like what, this is what the bad kid turns into,
right? At what point did everyone agree in media that this was how a vampire was, you know what
I mean? Why are their hands curled like this? These long fingernails, they curve their arms.
It's just odd. A bat. Oh, right, because bats. Shit, that's right. How come in Twilight they
weren't walking around like, but I don't get, there's vampires. Why did we get rid of it?
Why didn't Robert Pattinson not have a big long mouth and shit?
There's a sex appeal. It's not supposed to be scary. Twilight isn't about vampires. Yes,
it is. It's about the eternal conflict between vampires and werewolves. No, that's Underworld.
What the fuck happens in Twilight? I don't know what it is. I've never seen it. I mean,
I know what it is, but what's the premise of Twilight? Okay, okay, Twilight. Spoiler alert
for Twilight, but who cares? If you're gonna, if you're not, do I really give a shit about
spoiling Twilight? All right, Twilight is, Robert Pattinson is a sparkly vampire and he bites,
he bites that girl and then she becomes vampire too. And then there's also that other guy who's
Taylor and he's a vampire. I know he's a werewolf, right? And they kind of like each other,
kind of, pretending to not know. I actually, I know I saw somebody say this and you're completely
accurate. I have to give credit to what creditors do. Somebody said this is like 2008, like 2010
tier, like jokey reference to something. Like dude, this is like something, like this is like a joke
from 10 fucking years ago. I know, but remember I'm late to everything. I played Super Mario
Sunshine for the first time ever four days ago. So, I mean, I'm late to literally everything.
So anyways, yeah, I've never seen it. I don't plan on seeing it. Anyways, vampire, T-O-D-W,
too long, didn't watch the whole stream. Vampires, they've got to go back to being fucking weird and
creepy and scary like this. Year of the 2020 rat Reddit streamer. Oh, look at this up in the
champagne and dancing. That's what they do best. This is so cute. Zoom in on that watermark. Who
is it? Wait, wait, did the I will never stop it song come up? I think it did. Hey, look at that.
Who's that? Close. Not quite. Oh, it is that song. It is the song, the best singing of 2019, right?
What a cute compact streamer. This is my face mixed with Jim Carrey's face.
The first thing I thought of was I thought it was one of those, this is not a real person,
AI generated people, but apparently this is me and Jim Carrey put together, which is odd because I
I'm not sure where I am. Up here and like into here, mouth and eyes. It's been blended together
and that's definitely forehead, right? Cause up here he is listening to farting and screaming.
No, no, no, no. This is good shit. Why does he have a cold? That's, that's me crying.
You got the one earbud accurate and the shirt's pretty accurate too. Oh, what a fucking nightmare
that was. Hey, fireman, look at this dude. Take a look. I like the hair on this one. This is like,
this is a fireman with gel. The fireman that styled the fire. He's going out tonight. Very
cute. There's another one. Gaze upon man. What is the, if not an eternal flame? It's like a
charcoaly. Uh, charcoal. What? I just said it was like charcoal kind of. Art words. Art words.
It's very good. Oh, here's an album. It's called E-Clown. Uh, we have a parental advisory on this.
Side A, we have Michael Berry Bush favorite breakfast material. Bonk, booze, bam.
Booze, bonk, bam. Acid base. On the other side is pirate spy, rat burger, giant enemy spider,
MLG grandpa, and free shit. I hope this was not more than $4. Uh, because some of these are just
like audio files of me saying two words. There were like three songs on this whole album,
one of which I stole from somebody else. TF2 radio, 2020. All rights of the produced and owner
of the work reproduced reserve. Unauthorized copying, hiring, lending. Public, I tricked you.
It's Egypt and we're both vlog pyros. Pretty good. Oh, no wait. He's confirmed. Too bad it's not
glue, man. This is adorable. I love it. Very, very clean. You know what I mean? The muscle work back
here. The muscle work here. Another fucking Jerma character shaking my head. That's fat. No, it's
not. That's back muscle. I have that same thing. It starts like here and goes like hump back and
there's like another hump. I have the same thing. It's fucking muscle. I don't even know why you
made this. Like what did all this is, is an embarrassment when somebody comes over that
doesn't know what this is. This is like a, oh, that's on your desk. And it's funny until somebody
like you make a new friend or like maybe like a love interest comes over. And it's like,
what the fuck is this thing? Are we going to rip it up? Like, oh, that's a joke. That's a streamer
that I, uh, uh. What do you say to this? No, I know, I know this little guy on the internet.
Love interest, omega low. Love interest, omega low. Love interest. What are you talking about?
The sun goes down. Actual psycho Disney villain. Yeah, this is the point in the Disney movie when
the handsome guy that was a villain, kind of in the first hour of the movie,
you're like, oh, he's kind of a bad guy. And then like the, this is the finale where there's a big
fight with like a knife or something. There's a weapon involved here and it's like, Holy shit.
This is, this is like a rotten evil fucking evil person. And they do that evil face and shit.
A knife. Yeah. Isn't there, Disney wouldn't allow, what are you talking about? There's knives.
There's a knife in Aladdin. There's a fucking knife. There's a, there's a knife threat in Aladdin.
So I don't know what you're talking about. Not only is there a knife, there's a, there's a, like,
I'm going to stab you in the head. It's a threat. Like I'm coming. I'm going to come down and stab
you in the fucking head. That happens in Aladdin. Your eternal reward. There you go. There you go.
This is fucking awesome. Real face. Oh, this is you without makeup on.
No, that's, that's like my skin's been taken off and draped over a mannequin head.
That's what this looks like. Link the actual, link the face. Somebody link an image of that.
So for people that don't know what the fuck this is. It's so fucking ridiculous.
This is 3d fireman mapped on a 3d plane in a 3d program.
How big is this though? This looks like it could be huge. Is it like a giant statue or is it little?
Very cool. This is huge. Okay. This is boomer, boomer germa. Fucking mega milk thing, man.
God, I got to like, I got to like delete, I got to like stop this out.
I can't have that be like connected to the community. Oh, fireman. The rats. Oh, that like,
oh, the thing face. Mega milk. Okay. At some point you've got to like, we've got to steer the
community in a different direction. Like at some point this has to change. Nice baseball.
Germa versus jump king. Wait, germa minus two, jump king plus two. Why is that, why is this,
why would it be plus two? Oh no, the base, the baseball has a, the baseball is sentient.
Is this fireman? Because you are minus two. This is sick though. Oh, sick! The entire fireman
family. Let's see who made it. The best part is they're all drawn out except this one is just
that face just pasted on here and smoothed in with bald head. One of these is not like the other.
No. And hey, there we are at the art segment here. We have about, now we have about 50 or 60 videos
to look at. Something like that. Perfect music. Well, the music isn't going to turn off. Good
shit. Thank you everybody for submitting artwork. You guys are fucking awesome. There's still a
shitload of stuff that's in that channel that we have to get through. So I've got to figure out
how we can do it smoothly. We are going to go to the video section, but I'm going to pee first,
so I'm going to take a minute or two break here and we'll come back with the videos.
I'll be right back. Okay. Let's turn this music off. Oops a daisy. All right. So let us begin
our, what is this? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing? What are you doing?
It's like, this is every single chat message. I'd never say this to his face, but he's a wonderful
person and a gifted streamer. It says lewd and rude. I would never say this to his face.
I would never say this to his face. That's so funny. That's fucking funny. I'd never tell him,
but well, thank you for that. We're going to start now. We're going to start with a video
that we talked about previously already is called the, the speedy Grinner. Get ready for the,
this section of the stream. We potentially be VOD watchers. Sorry, but some of these are probably
like movie clips and YouTube videos. So sorry, VOD watchers. Let's begin. The first video is,
like I said, the greedy, the speedy Grinner.
How the fuck is this a trailer for a show?
Oh, that was so loud. What the fuck was that? Oh, is this video over? Oh, what the fuck?
What is speedy Grinner 2? Is this even supposed to be me? No, this is spoilers. Spoilers. No,
this is spoilers. All right. I'm going to put it in a new tab. Hold on. Let me get this in a new tab.
Okay. Don't spoil the movie. All right. Is this one going to be as loud or we might as well just
play this one right now. All right. We're playing this one now. It's a speedy Grinner 2. What am I
going to do? Not play the fucking sequel immediately after the first one. Here we go.
Spoiler for the flash.
I'm
just squeaking.
This is like how the show ends. What the fuck? Holy shit. Hopefully nobody cares about that show.
All right. I got to make, I got an actual warning. We have to do this warning
every single time, every community content fucking night. Like if you ever have any plans
of watching any television for the next like six months, just, just leave now. Like, I mean,
like seriously, like this is, we spoil so many TV shows and so many movies. Just give you a
warning right now. Moving on to the next one. The next one is called, uh, this is scary.
This one's fucking scary. Just watch it. Okay. I'm done with this one. I'm done with this one.
Okay. That's it for that one. This one's called Jerma toilet.
Hey, your memories have arrived. Huh? That's real cute. Photo dome. Hey, here you go.
Got a picture of the toilet. Hey, here you go. Got a picture of the toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, fuck.
I just wanted to make sure I made this really, really clear. I've been drinking water out of
the toilet, like literally like drinking like toilet, like the water in the toilet.
Very fucking disgusting. Tastes like somebody's asshole. Oh my God. Um, that is what my whole
looks like. I don't even have pants on. They had to be gone for this. Look at that. Uncensored. Oh,
oh, it's a toilet. You know what I mean? I totally got you. I totally got you.
I need to watch this part one more time. This like this. This is fucking perfect.
Got a picture of the toilet. Hey, here you go. Got a picture of the toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, fuck.
I just wanted to make sure I made this really, really clear. I've been drinking water out of
the toilet, like literally like drinking like toilet, like the water in the toilet.
Very fucking disgusting. Tastes like somebody's asshole.
Oh my God. Um, that is what my whole looks like. Oh, that was fucking, this is 10 out of 10.
If you'd like the link to this one, here it is. Oh my goodness. That was fucking wild.
Just wild, man. Uh, this next one is called Jerma gets heckled. Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat.
Ladies and gentlemen.
You know what's funny? I actually had to sign an agreement.
Are we ready? I don't know what we're ready for, Jeremy. Extreme filler for untrained,
unprofessional losers. You fucking wanker. Oh yeah, yeah. You're here with like your
drunk, ugly ass friends, huh? Why don't you come up here and try? You think it's so easy.
You little shit. I'm going to strangle your parents. Okay. That's what's going to happen.
Like you'll fit in that parking lot. You'll make as big as the parking lot.
You want to get your fucking turkey roasted. I think he's got his ultimate.
That was crack. That was just crack. Oh, you want to get your turkey roasted?
Guys, I can't, I've said some, just, I don't know. How many, do you want me to explain that?
That was like from like a 2012 Huntsman video. I can't even tell you what that meant. It meant
like, I'm going to like, you're going to, you're, you're cooked. Like you're done. It's over.
You know what I mean? I have no idea. Oh, this one's called shoot him jump. The rhythm heaven.
Looks like it could be pretty interesting. Let's take a look. Oh, this is cool. This is
awesome. That was the hard one. That was the hard one. Thanks for watching. Thanks for making.
No dupes. Hard making of this. Fuck. That's a big, look at how big that is. Oh, that was awesome.
It was actually very, very well made. This one's called, uh, stimulate your senses.
How it feels to chew five gum.
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I want to do this one again. How it feels to chew
five gum. Well, that was fucking awesome. This one's called, uh, Yugi summons Jerma. Remember,
if you've, if you ever plan on watching television for any series ever made,
you can't watch these streams. Okay.
Of course. Of course it was. Why would it be anything else? God, this is called a normal
windy night. Normal windy night. Oh, it's a scary one. I'm going to be in the woods and I'm going
to like, it's going to be the, all right, here comes another dinosaur. Here comes a dinosaur.
Here comes sword streamer. You serious? Oh, you kept me watching. That's for sure.
You kept me watching. That's for sure. This is called average day for Jerma. Two beds.
Wait, the, the mirror of my arms, not lifting up. It's not even a mirror.
Oh no, it's raining outside. I hate this. I hate this. This is terrible.
Dude, people use, you know what I've noticed? Uh, so what, like two years ago, whatever it was,
like a year and a half ago, almost two years ago, that I went in front of the green screen.
This, this below your nose one is, it was like six hours of footage. This appears in so many
places. It was just a one-off, just a little throw away, 10 seconds and so funny. Just people
use this one thing everywhere. It makes me laugh every fucking time. And the puke one too. Yeah.
God, it's fucking funny. This next one is, is guaranteed that I'll like it because as you saw
last community content night, um, I, I mentioned the baseball video was my favorite green screen
thing. And what do you know? Here we are. Uh, JLB highlights Elbertson blasts a walk-off slam.
Every 20th for Janssen here in the ninth inning.
What is this?
Is this another,
nobody down there.
Hold on.
The 20th, I love the baseball one. There's so much. I love them. I just want to see this part
right here.
And imagine like a fucking, imagine we live in like a hundred years ago and like the,
there was no such thing as like green screen footage. Man, we truly live in the best time.
You know what I mean? This one's called DJ Jerma. Oh God. Wait, didn't we already see this?
I think we've already seen this one. Okay. Uh, this is a ha ha Jerma walk funny.
I got on the top rope. Why am I running a fucking moron? I don't walk like this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. Yeah. Nah, it's all right. This one's called Jerma, but it's half life sound effects.
Hey, step off buddy. Don't tick me off. Gordon. What? Oh shit. Major fracture detected.
Let's try this. Ah, Freeman. Who is responsible for this? Theoretically. Yes. As I expected.
Do you know who ate all the doughnuts?
Major fracture detected. No.
That was rude.
They'll all go and they'll sit down and be like, and then you have your attention. Oh my God.
That was really, that was very clever. I liked it. That was very good.
Clever use of sound effects. Here's a link to that. A lot of people looking for it.
There it is. That was very good. The thing with half life sound effects is probably fucking
ridiculous. All right. This is a, this is the, called the death of Jerma 985.
But as of the first frame you can see here, this is a, this is a Mr. Peanut joke. So yeah,
can't wait for this one. Here we go.
Oh, you let go. Hey, Mr. Peanut. No, you don't. Don't do it.
Holy shit, it worked. I feel fine. Maybe you'll be all right. Maybe not.
This is the next one. What the fuck? What the hell was that? What the fuck?
Spoilers, maybe. Uh, it's, we're getting political presidential candidates.
Political spoilers. Uh, this one's called the Jerma ball, the streak. Yes. More baseball. Yes.
I can't wait. This is, this one's long too. Holy shit. This one's long. This is called the streak.
We use the sample of your DNA to clone a bunch of players. Hey, where are you going?
It's off the scoreboard and they can't get it in time.
Two runs are in. The big rats are back. The rats have flick-shotted their way from last place to
first in the AL West. That's somebody's asshole. I hope it's not mine. No, that's mine.
Something strange is now happening in Las Vegas. Well, there ain't nothing in the rule book that
says you can't have a team full of clowns. They don't, yeah. Making a joke out of the American
league. When is there even a major league baseball team in Las Vegas anyway? 16 consecutive games,
fucking streak in baseball folks in 25 years are screaming and farting.
This team was written off. None of this makes any sense. Can't be how it happens.
Drew slugging fastballs. This team has cracked the case wide open on baseball.
Finishing Dark Souls three on stream was all time number 17. The Vegas Rathletics are now
two wins away from tying the American league record. 20 wins in a row doesn't seem so impossible
anymore. They're really going up the top rope here and the league can't take it. The age of
the Boston Float today. They're the biggest deal since Jerma Rumble live action. These guys are
laughing. Oh yeah, they could have cloned Reggie or Ricky or Giambi, but instead they chose this
weirdo from Boston. But hey, the results don't lie. This dude's fucked. Some teams are trolling
millions of dollars at players, but these guys are paying the same in bits. This isn't just some
kind of currency, you know? Not a big deal. Not a big deal at all. Because what I would say,
if what was occurring here made any sense at all, but it doesn't. The statistics don't work here.
This is bigger than us. Up the middle the rats have won 19 in a row. The 1906 White Sox and the 1947
Yankees have come. They're going to the road. That's making all of the rules. The giant enemy slider.
Wait, what happened? Why did we lose? What? The giant enemy slider. The giant enemy slider?
The Pittsburgh pinwheels.
I gotta say the best 10 seconds of this whole video is the birds and the fucking
the tomahawk swing not even in the right spot. I gotta see it again. But these guys are paying
the same in bits. This isn't just some kind of currency thing, you know? Not a big deal.
Not a big deal at all. Because what I would say, if what was occurring here made any sense...
This was fucked. I loved it. This is fucking perfect.
All the like the voice work. That was a fully scripted out voice. That was perfect.
Oh man. That was hamster pie. Hamster pie. You're here right now. I'm not sure. I mean this video,
we're about 30 days behind. So it fucking is hilarious. Oh my god. All right. Moving on.
Let's keep it rolling. We have... Oh yes. Oh man. Are we gonna have back-to-back fucking
baseball or Star Wars? You've got my attention. I know I should probably... It's just true. It's
real. Okay. You want me to not... It's real. This is Compact Jedi and Sidekick Ninja Turtle
take on Sith Lord. Star Wars Episode 3 spoilers. I love this shit, man. I love this shit.
Oh man. No hesitation. And it was the baseball swing. I can't wait to get back in front of this
fucking thing, man. I gotta like... This like rib cage problem. Gotta get the fuck out of here.
I want to do like another eight hours in front of this thing. You know what I mean? Like
this is so... This is... You guys are so creative and so... Where you use this shit,
it's fucking hysterical. I gotta get the fuck in front of this thing again.
It's been like a year and a half. Oh man. Good shit. Keep going. This is uh...
Jerma and the Wizard of Oz. Jesus Christ. That was all over the place. But it was good. It was
very, very good. This is Anthony Bantony exposed by hidden camera. And this is shocking.
What was this? What program was this made in? What was this? It was like... What animation
was political? That wasn't political. That wasn't political. This is called uh... This is just a D
face. Oh, you want to fight? You want to fucking fight me? Don't fucking come at me. Don't...
This next one is called... Streamer becomes psychotic barbarian in virtual reality.
I've made it to the zone, the play area, and I'm ready to fucking go nuts.
Excellent. Hello. Jeremy. I'm Genghis Khan. You go where I go. Defile what I defile. Eat who I eat.
I'm wild. I'm like a cave fucking beast. Eat this you fucking celery bitch.
This is what everybody does when they play. Let kids do this. I'll do it. I'll do it. I'll do it.
Oh, get it. Come here you son of a bitch. I'm not a psycho. This is a video. This is...
What's wrong? What? What? What? What? What's wrong with that? What the hell is going on?
This guy has love. Everybody, everybody that plays Blade and Sorcery, every single person,
you try to like cut people's fucking heads off and like stab them in the eye and shit,
and like throw them off cliffs, as everybody does. You tell me you didn't do that? You didn't like
throw a person into another person and then like stab them both through the chest with a
spear and then throw the skewered people off a cliff. But you're lying if you say no.
Oh, that was fucking crazy. This one's called... I feel like we have we seen this one? It's called
Jerma Maze. Have we seen this? Good thing I had it turned down. That's it. All right, that's
scary. I wouldn't want to play this game. This is Jerma Makes a TikTok.
God damn, man. Freddie, Freddie Dredd. Freddie just gave $400 of bits.
I don't, I don't, I don't know what that is. It's TikTok. I don't even know what TikTok is.
I mean, I'm lying, but it's, it's a, it's a clock app. No, I know, I know. I've done it before.
I don't even, did I even do it again? This, this thing, this thing. Should I do that again?
No, it's been recorded more than once. So like head move. Animated movement thing. Yeah. I,
it's, it's recorded somewhere. I won't do it again. This next one is called, uh, Jerma is Speed.
Jerma is Speed. Speed. Speed. You see, on this channel, I like to call myself Dr. Jekyll
and Mr. Jerma because I have two different sides. No, no, no. I have a very professional side where
I review content. I review packages. What? I don't review packages. You want to fight? You
want to fight? Don't fuck with that. So here's like, here's a cup. This cup is good. There's a whole
lot of stuff here though. I have my fun. I have my professional side. I mold them together into
sort of this lunacy that is Jerma985. So hopefully this little trailer will be able to give you an
explanation of Mr. Jerma and hopefully you subscribe. What? You have to use this. So please
subscribe, subscribe. Oh, yeah. Lightning's ready.
Oh, Honda Civic. Wait, what?
This didn't happen. I'm still in like 40th place. You understand?
Oh, pass him. Pass him.
This is just like the first, this is like the first 20 minutes of the movie.
But the last thing he expected was the full movie.
You know, I don't think anybody expected this. The rookie sensation came into the season unknown,
but everyone knows him now. Will he be the first rookie to win a Piston Cup
and land down a co? The legend, the runner up and the rookie. Three cars, one champion.
The
rookie screamer. The full movie. What? Hey, that's just, he just like ripped the band-aid off.
You just tore the band-aid off. I want to know what happens. Should I just watch the movie?
Okay, this one's called Jerma985 reunites with Tim CJ Davidson. Turn it up. Turn it up.
Hey, big smoke. It's me, Carl. Chill, chill. Tim? Tim Davidson? What? Hey, man.
This is my house. Nah, man. It's my mom's, homie. Hey, mad dog. What you doing up there, fool?
Earth. Earth. Earth is on fire. I just shit my pants. I can't do it anymore. Motherfucker.
Get a grip. You still got it? You still gangsta? Some of these just end with just the most
abrupt fucking endings possible. This one's called Jerma Interacting with Chat, and this is going to
be really, really fucking weird. This is another one of those scary deep fakes. Here we go.
I'm standing here. You make the move. You make the move.
It's your move. I'm trying. You talking to me? You talking to me? You talking to me? Oh, it's
fucked up. Who the hell else are you talking to? You talking to me? Well, I'm the only one here.
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to? Oh, yeah? Okay.
Okay. It's just scary. It's just, you know, the worst thing about deep fakes
is if, if you sent this to, if you sent this to my grandmother,
she would think this was me standing here doing this. You'd be like, what is this? Why, why, why?
Why does he, why does he have a gun? That's not the grandson that I raised.
I don't think this is real. My grandmother would think this is real. That's where we're going.
Send it to your grandmother. What in the name of God would I send that to my grandmother for?
His mom's called, uh, Jerma is the newest Avenger. Half-life.
Quickest to a salad you ever made. Here we go. Slap it a couple of times. One, two, three.
Easy as pie. Just a thing, the thing to clean it. It opens up like a waterfall.
See? Take a look at that. See? It's easy. No, no, no mess. No bullshit. Throw it in the
fucking sink behind me. What? Slap it a couple of times. One, two, three.
What? What? Why? What was the point of that? Two, three.
Got to use the clip somehow. Oh, right. Yeah. I did. Did I, did I do this in front of the green
screen? I don't remember even saying that. I did. Uh, this is called a compact turnabout.
This is an Ace Attorney thing. This is not the same one we saw last time, right? Let's see.
A box or something. Yeah.
That's very short. He was even having trouble climbing to the box.
Hey, it's me, Jerma, from the downtown of Center Sports. I'm downtown. I'm a Tuber.
Sitting down.
What's that mean? What's that mean? What's that mean? What's that mean?
What's that mean?
I'm an influencer, not a Tuber. That's not all. It also says I, uh, performed at this conundrum.
Why is it a fucking Egypt? What? No, no, no, no. I like Egypt. Please, please.
That's a double. That's a double bullshit.
Nice. There's infinite options, huh? You can do whatever you want in this movie maker.
Yeah. That was, that was a double end the, end the video bullshit. I can't believe it. We,
we got the trick to you, flog pyro, and then explosion. And then you got Vinny at the end.
That was fucking crazy. It was a triple bullshit. You can do anything. React to his reaction.
Is that good? No. Oh, let's get it again. Nice. There's infinite options, huh? You can do
whatever you want in this movie maker. Right. Cool. I made a cover of a giant enemy spider
in a low effort pixel animation. React harder. I don't fucking know how to react. You guys,
don't you guys know that by now? I don't fucking know how to react to anything.
My reactions on these streams are this. Or I lean forward and laugh really hard. Or I go
react, react, react. I'm doing it again. All right. You said you were fast. I did say I was fast.
Okay. I can't do that again. Okay. I got like full of fucking muscle.
Holy fuck. Yeah. So you want to talk about how you don't, you don't think, you don't think I have
the fucking speed. Physical therapy down the drain. No, I did like a burst. That wasn't a turn.
I'm all right. I'm fine. Don't worry. Is this called, let's go to German. Let's just do a solid bop.
No, don't turn it off. It's a great song. Don't turn it off. It's a great song.
Oh shit. I was supposed to do that. A lot of people that are just trickling into this stream,
but I had just probably like, this is like, what is it? This is, it's an explanation I can't give
you. This is, uh, I think we've seen this one before, but this is germ of friends.
Why is this auto playing? This one's called small enemy spider. It looks like an animation.
Wait a minute. Holy shit. There's a small enemy spider.
I just die. That's videos. I just die.
Shit. Hold on.
This one's called Jerma's nightmare. Skipped a video. What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? When he skipped a video, he skipped a pixel. What? Are you sure?
Where? Pixel. When, when, when did I skip it? Three videos ago? Wait, what?
You were showing us your speed. Oh, and I just, we just didn't watch the video. Oh, okay. Wait.
I, so I just like skipped it. Okay. All right. All right. All right. Sorry. I'm trying to pick.
All right. Somebody link it right now. I thought you meant like I hit like the,
all right. I see what you're saying. I was too fast. Let me see this. Oh, okay. Right.
I'm sitting here going like, what are they talking about? My brain is so fucking small. Here we go.
What is this up here? That's not a spider, is it?
It is a spider. That's scary, dude. Dude. Fuck, dude. Dude. Oh, there you go. Sorry that I almost
fucking just did, just deleted it for my brain. That's how you can tell that I have an actual
goldfish memory. This is Jerma's nightmare. I had a dream last night that I was sponsored by this
company that makes this wallet. And I was nervously doing a presentation for it. And there
were like 30,000 people here for some reason. And it was just a wall, a spam of like, I'm
fucking out of here. I'm something you piece of shit. This opens store cards. It's a good wallet.
It is. And it looks like an SSD. There's all kinds of styles.
Really good. They're very good. They're secure. They fit into pants. You can actually put this
into like a jacket pocket. You put your essentials in here. It's light. It's got a nice click to it.
It's very sturdy. What is happening?
What the fuck is going on?
Who put that in there?
This is a crack video.
I'm gonna do it with two hands.
Everyone dies.
It's time for you to pay.
Is this a Jojo thing? Jojo?
Something that I care about. Something that I want to show.
That I haven't had the opportunity to do it until now.
That's me on my fishing trip.
Go through. Get out of here.
I'll see you Sunday.
Hey!
Jesus.
Meme vomit.
It's like this is another full minute.
Are you kidding me? That isn't what happened.
That is not what happened. That's exactly what happened.
What are you talking about? No it's not.
That was bullshit. This is what really happened.
Jojo.
What am I about? Wait.
When did I say this?
Alright. Spoilers for Jojo.
I mean we only got 20 seconds left, guy.
I said. At some point.
If you haven't seen it yet.
If you have.
Jojo.
Not one of you has not seen it.
But mute for the next 45 minutes.
What about me?
What about me? I haven't seen it.
Should I mute?
Alright. I'm going to look away.
Those of you that have seen the show. You can keep watching.
Those of you that haven't seen the show.
Look away. And take out your earphones.
Ok. 3. 2. 1.
Go.
Alright.
We have this one.
This is another animated show.
If you haven't seen.
This is from Attack on Titan.
This is 30 seconds.
This is called German invades castle.
Just want to make sure.
If you have never seen it.
Just the words that I just said 5 seconds ago.
If you have never seen it. Who cares.
Here we go.
I deleted everything.
This is kind of it.
I just hit the backwards button.
With everything selected.
Sorry.
I don't want you to see my pores.
I know. I know.
Screen camera is going to shit.
This one was funny.
They've all been good.
Coming up next.
We have a video called.
The impressive scale of our universe.
Let's see what our universe looks like.
I bet you anything.
I'm as small as the smallest atom.
I already know what it is.
I already see it. I've already seen this video.
I guarantee you that's what happens.
There's no way.
That we don't go into like.
0.00500th of a percent of a micron.
And not be standing there T posing.
Right? Has to be.
Wait for it. Yeah.
We're going to go through the whole thing.
This is how big everything fucking is.
Let's zoom way in.
Pay attention.
I know how the video ends.
Anticipation is killing me.
Almost there.
And T pose. Got it.
I'm tiny.
I'm fucking tiny.
I can smell that one from a fucking mile away.
You have appeased us goblin.
Thank you.
How long is that video? 2 minutes and 47 seconds.
Alright coming up next.
We are going to move on to music.
I'm going to hang out for a little bit.
Let's go to conclude the video section.
We had to fucking end on that one.
And now we get to do.
Something that I'm not looking forward to.
What's going to happen for the next few.
I want to do music first.
Because I'm about to do.
I'm about to turn on the winks.
They're going to be discounted.
I think it's going to be like.
10,000 or 20.
No. No. No. 20,000. 20,000.
20,000. 10,000.
Alright 10,000 for a wink.
We're going to listen to music.
And just fucking wink into the.
Embarrassing pain in the ass isn't it?
Okay. Hold on.
Hold on.
I am about to turn it on.
Don't use it yet.
I need to be able to keep track of this shit.
Alright. I'm going to listen to some music.
And just hang out.
And fuck this. A bunch of people here.
And these people are going to be like.
There's a lot of people here right now.
And I'm going to do this now?
Wait. Holy shit.
Should have made it 50.
I turned it off.
I think there are.
Let's see.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9,
10, 11, 12, 13,
14.
Are there any.
Mods.
That are in the channel right now.
That.
Anybody have any.
Data on how many that just was.
That was a lot.
It was probably
2 or 3. It was like 3 or 400.
It was 400.
Grump.
If you have any awareness or access
to how many times somebody just redeemed a link.
It was like
hundreds and hundreds of fucking times.
I think it was like 400 and something.
543.
543 times.
Okay.
I need like a counter.
I'm like practicing.
I'm like going to prepare for this.
Okay.
One blink counts as 2?
No, no, no, no. Does it? Yeah, it does.
No? What do you mean no?
Oh my fucking god. I can't believe that.
Am I? I'm not like the. I'm not like the top
row of just chatting right now.
And I'm going to wink count?
Hey, come on out of German. I hit 5.
Where I go like this. Click. Click.
543 fucking times.
Oh, I did this to myself.
I did this to myself.
Hold on. Hold on. Give us the winks.
Alright. Hold on. Wait. Wait. I gotta move.
I have to move something.
Because we still have music to do.
I still want to play the music.
I'm getting this over with right now.
And winks are dead forever. They're not coming back.
Oh man. Oh man. Oh man.
The music?
I'm almost halfway there. I'm fine.
What do you mean music? Oh, you want fucking music?
Fine. We'll play some fucking music.
Okay. I missed one.
What was that? Put on thunderstruck?
Was it like just a kid talking?
No. No. We're not at 21.
We're at 63.
You have to catch up.
Click on source.
You're watching in like 360p. You're like 4 minutes behind.
I'll make this go so much faster.
If I do this.
There's an intro before the intro.
I just want sound effects.
I'm close.
He's going crazy.
This is performance art?
No. This is called making a mistake.
This is called making a mistake.
Minus 400 viewers.
Oh fuck.
It's replaying them.
We need a better playlist.
Do thunderstruck?
Hey lady.
Nope. We're staying here.
Oh babe. I am.
Yeah baby.
Okay. We actually are moving on.
I'll get this all done in one
thunderstruck.
I'll get this done in one thunderstruck.
543?
Can you put water in your eyes?
Like can I like put water in my eyes
to like lubricate them?
That's okay right?
Okay. Don't do that.
At least let me lubricate something.
I gotta get ready for this.
Hold on.
These bleeding viewers.
Do you think people are going to want to stay?
TikTok!
What do you mean they don't count?
I'm getting sleepy.
Okay. It's itchy.
It's itchy right now.
My eyes are wicked itchy.
They're bleeding?
I'm not bleeding.
No. It's just itchy.
It's wicked itchy. Oh no. I know why.
Because I touched this.
I'm fine.
I'm getting an irritated eye from winking.
Imagine winking yourself into an allergy.
Holy shit man.
What the?
Alright when you do this like
400 fucking times.
It starts to blend together.
It starts to blend together like
an itchy eye. Hold on.
This is fucked up.
Hey.
Is it fucked up that I'm doing it?
Fucked up that you're here watching it.
Which one?
I gotta help myself here. Ready?
It's becoming hard to do.
I'm gonna end up with like
big eyebrow muscles.
I'm gonna have huge ass eyebrow
with like cheek muscles from this.
I'm like working out muscles up here
that I've never worked out in my life.
I'm gonna get like big
jacked under eyes.
This guy's an egomaniac.
No he's just an idiot.
That continues to fuck up stuff.
Super Saiyan 3.
Both?
He's normally just dumb.
We're almost there.
Play us out.
500. What was it?
Oh it was 543. Fuck.
555.
I did extra because some of those were blinks.
Alright now excuse me.
I'm going to go throw up.
I did it. Ding ding ding.
I won.
Play stupid games, win stupid prizes.
Winks by the way are gone.
They're not coming back.
Anyways we have some music to listen to.
I'm gonna be watching everybody.
I'm gonna come back to camera now.
We're just gonna chill and listen to some music.
While we do the bits.
That sounds like a good place to put it.
I'm gonna replace it with something more fun.
I'm replacing it with stuff like what we did yesterday.
If you were here yesterday
that is more
fun to me.
Than just dump like
20-30 thousand points
and like streamers said something.
Or winks into camera.
I actually have like little fun games.
You know what I mean?
The idea.
We're gonna do the, how many points for
Nancy Drew stream.
Please play Joel's movie in time.
Have you watched the 3D movie maker movie?
Oh I haven't no.
Alright well that's the last thing that we're gonna do.
We're gonna end the stream
with Joel's 3D movie maker movie.
But not now. Not yet.
Let's listen to some music first.
While we do the bits and stuff.
Actually no we should probably hold off.
Because it's gonna be like another 20-30 minutes right?
Yeah let's hold off.
Let's play some music.
This is some giant enemy spider music.
That we're gonna listen to right now.
Here's this first one.
This actually is pretty sick.
This is actually pretty good.
Right now Nintendo owns this.
I think they owned it before too.
Bopping.
Look at this. This sounds pretty good.
That's why I'm ice fine.
End of the stream.
Well I mean technically this is the end of the stream.
We're doing a bonus end.
We're gonna watch Joel's movie.
This next one is very very interesting.
This is called
Kids With Rats.
You know that thing how the rat song goes
literally with everything?
It's pretty cool actually.
That's good shit.
Link, link, link, link, link, link.
Here's Link.
There you go. That was really good.
Zelda, Zelda, Zelda, Zelda, Zelda.
This one's called Giant Enemy Spider 11.
The giant enemy spider.
Isn't this 11 seconds?
Hey, giant
enemy spider.
Wait, Jerma screams.
So handsome.
I'm the most handsome person you've ever met.
What the fuck is that guy?
They fucking scream.
I never
scream like that.
I'm a fan of that person.
God, shut up already.
What? I just turned it on.
What are you talking about?
Oh yeah, somebody did that recently.
I remember that. I turned the stream on
and I started talking about, like, they love doing the intro.
And somebody was like, dude, shut the fuck up already.
Dude, just shut up already.
I just turned on the stream.
I remember that.
It's like, I just turned on the
fucking broadcast.
You're going to be here for at least,
you're going to have to listen to me for at least four to eight
hours, depending on how I feel that day.
This next one's called Giant Enemy Spider
Remix.
The giant enemy spider.
Giant enemy spider
remix.
Seriously.
Link, I actually
don't have a link for this one because
it was embedded directly into Discord.
Let me see
if I can get it.
This is good.
What going on in this one?
Trying to find it. It's right here somewhere.
Hold on.
Oh, with the ending too, with the old
ending sound.
Yeah, even with, hold on.
Even with the, if I found it in Discord,
you'd have to go to the community
content section
and pull it from there.
Let me get the exact name of it though.
Somebody, oh, you got it, somebody has it right now?
You got it? Is that it?
Oh, they don't. Shit. Okay.
Yeah, because I had to save this and just
play it through the computer.
So, if we can get maybe somebody
one of the mods or something maybe
where somebody can find it.
Because I just tried to scroll through and couldn't see it.
Oh, there you go. Okay.
Yeah, it's in the
stream chat in stream related
category. Cool. There we go. That was really
fucking good. Now,
without further ado,
we're going to do,
we're going to watch Joel's
video.
Does somebody have a link to the 3D movie maker movie?
This is it. Link this.
Hurry. Why
are you in a hurry?
The giant enemy spider.
Spider on me like the Spider-Man.
This is not it.
Link this.
Hurry.
I do not want the cooties, man.
Spider on me like the Spider-Man.
I've been jumping higher than I head up on a single fan.
Quick, link it.
I don't want you
I do not want the cooties, man. I think we've heard
this already. It's pretty good.
Real link. Yeah,
we've heard that already.
You motherfucker.
Okay, here we go. Let's pull this back.
We're going to watch this movie.
I need to get like a snack or something.
Oh, do I need like a snack for this?
Just eat your nails.
Alright, I'll be right back. I'm going to
get like a water.
The stream is technically over.
Alright, technically. Cause we're just
watching Joel's movie and we're going to scroll through some other stuff
too. And do the bits and everything.
So I'll be right back.
In fact, I'm just going to go to the screen because
this is more accurate. I'll be right back.
Okay.
This is called the Blue
Shell Incident.
This is what this is called.
Hold on, let me get it in the right spot.
We need a React
Cam. Oh, you don't need a
React Cam, do you?
Alright, hold on. You want a React
Cam? Let me just fix my hair so
I look at least presentable
on your fucking big screen.
What's going on in the back of my head here?
Alright, here we go. This is
the Blue Shell Incident.
Just spaghetti on the rocks.
Don't you get these characters?
Hey, little bro. Or should I say
Green Mario?
Don't you dive in Sansibar?
Ah, but that's where you're wrong, bro.
You see, Blue Shell Incident
was just a cover up.
Location,
Sansibar Island,
5 PM.
That was...
This is Lasagna
Ocelot, over.
Commencing Operation Blue
Shell Kill. How did you get Garfield?
When did you get a gun?
And the wood pipe was a Zybrows's ass all
along, Luigi!
Hey, uh, do you smell
Lasagna?
Hey, Luigi!
I was talking here!
What scene is this?
Well, Luigi, all I gotta say is
pasta la vista.
Lasagna doesn't smell Italian.
All I gotta say, Luigi,
you go to hell before you die!
D-d-d-d-d-die?
I didn't shoot Luigi, we don't kill Luigi,
do you? Holy fuck.
That's pretty good.
That was a pretty good Luigi.
Today just
had to be a Monday, huh?
Oh my god.
Oh no, it was Mario
that got shot, not Luigi.
Blow up the earth. Blow the earth up. Please blow the
earth up. I know you want to do it. Do it.
Do it!
Oh, god damn it.
I thought we were gonna get an earth explosion.
That's right, Luigi! It was me
all along! It's
me, Mario!
Yahoo!
Mario, that's impossible!
Well, if I can't
have had any better aim, you'd be dead
that Monday. I guess
you could call a Spaghetti up, Luigi!
But Mario,
what about the blood?
Look at my shitty degree.
All Chef Boyardee. I never passed
that way, but how could
you do salsa thing?
Truth is, the game was
rigatoni'd from the start, Luigi.
Boppity boppity Mario,
you piece of shit!
It was rigatoni'd from
the start just something I picked up
that was pretty good that was a good animation technique I'm telling you
and I'm all I saw it all back in Zanzibar you really ducked up now Mario
hey wait a minute that's a song you also looks good hit Luigi oh no it go my
Jesus Christ wait a minute is that duck on my side it was an eyeball in there
this braided are well you must know Mario I work for Mario well you missed
one it's time for foul play mother duck er good work on this on the fiery you
know how much of a pain in the ass it is to do this shit in this program took like
fucking 45 minutes right now that right there was 30 minutes oh duck for a war
pipe I mean you saved me I'll be here in a half for an event well Luigi that when
that was just a duck wing those breadcrumbs yeah well I'm here to repay
the favor what he did to you let's crack his skull open what you're saying you
peed in my Cheerios mr. duck no that's not what I'm saying at all what I am
saying is all right that's all I need to know let's go all right let's do this
the duck has wings hey that's from Mario Sunshine I know that one and then I said
why we can stop him before I kill someone a taxi make like a banana and
step on it okay I'm David Hasselhoff
stuff right yeah I got a ton a skeleton damn he was my only customer monkey
he's gonna drive over gonna fuck him up he's gonna drive over it's gonna fuck
him up I do it
I'm fine you know duck after all we've been through with these seven minutes I
gotta say you truly were the real Super Mario brother all along my favorite part
of the movie right there just the leg damn you turn this ugly duckling into a
swan Luigi after this duck spaghetti on the rocks on knowing cold sound this is
it Mario hey I can smell you over there by the way Toad's voice it's not me
fucking horrible it's toad toad's voice I'm not talking about like this
impression of toad I'm talking about just toad in general it's so bad you
it's just like a like I don't even want to do it I'll hurt your ears it's just
like a screeching like re talking it's a holy fuck why did they make him like
that all right anyways that's what we're doing it's handy oh damn it we lost
him you're saying that's really him this is getting somebody shot him oh Mario
just fuck up Mario this is why why all this how could you do this to your own
bro because I am man John fuck you that actually is his face part joke so a
scat man John all along I knew Mario was full of shit no that
guy's in movie maker that's an actual character in 3d man I was using the John
just like I'm using you was that a fucking twist huh what was that noise
damn I knew something wasn't smelling right where's that weird chicken like
picking up a baby thing like I was fucking on the naughty list now oh hey
boss ah lasagna ocelot I see your back sorry boss blue shell kill is cancelled
what do we do now we get the second weapon on Garfield metal gear McQueen
have no he's gigantic well boss I mean that that just looks terrible well we
kind of ran out of a budget but let's get in it holy quacka moly I've got to
stop that technological terror it's so bad it's so stupid boss did you hear a
terrible sound effect well it's so perfect the radar here boss don't
talking about lightning McQueen I saw ya it's a terrible turkey oh
frack jack where'd he go you know boss I don't think I've ever asked why are we
killing Luigi well I guess it's time for you to find out sensible island I hear
for a fact this is in the Nickelodeon one Johnny Bravo Marge Simpson this is
this reminds me of the end of blue frame Roger Rabbit which is like every
cartoon character ever it's just like dancing yeah you want Mario you would
shit ever since that day I vowed to put him in his gravy only oh so what's it
over the fact you pissed in your Cheerios he did what he's he's still
alive I know what I must do now he's taking he's he's taking he's taking up
took this nice try but that wasn't good enough to stop me this fucking crazy
look so Luigi you're back to play her too like you always were you know once
Mario I'm not gonna it's got like three games Mario's not wrong
I can't believe you check tears on that pesky pigeon Luigi oh it's the bits the
duck we have character growth something says character growth thank you duck now
it's time for me to repay the favor
that was like that's worse than like an iPad the city is like I've had mobile
game city but not like from 10 years ago 20 years ago now where's the bastard
brother of mine looking for me little bro Mario yeah say Luigi you ever
wondered about our memes memes you see Luigi being a plumber it's just a myth
everything is just a joke we're all pawns controlled by something greater
can metal gears metal gear so true souls they shape our will they are culture
they are everything we pass on Luigi I don't understand what you're talking
about Mario I knew you wouldn't Luigi ever since that day I'm Sam Sabar Luigi I
could never forgive you what are you talking about Mario when the blue shell
hit me and I came in last I was humiliated Luigi all because of that all
of this because of that Mario no true this I've always hated you bro we're
bros but we're not ordinary bros we're bros linked by cursed memes you you're
fine you got all the old man's dominant memes I got all the flawed recessive
memes old man you mean that's right Luigi but enough of that it's time your
memes end here who's gonna win who wins the battle at the end
liquid liquid Luigi we'll see about that next week you Luigi classic one
best of Luigi you know Luigi you make me laugh we're not so different you and I
were both plumbers we love spaghetti but you know what I like the most about you
brothers what the fact you never use cheat codes like me thank you so much for
playing my game and now Luigi you die mother ducker forgot to dig me a grave
huh look you're alive let's just say I borrowed a few power stores before I
went Luigi farewell you were the bro I never had I thought I was a Reese's car
for a second I was like holy shit Reese's
spaghetti on the rocks you know you remind me of someone mr. duck to ice cubes
my brother keep the change he said Bane laugh why cuz I had my name is Luigi oh
my god rather I'm a movie that took a year to make see something that a lot of
people need to understand this shit this each minute of this is this program is
not designed to do any of this shit any absolutely zero so trying to manipulate
this to do any of this it's so hard to do fuck you Windows 10 from was
destroying this yeah it is post-credit scene
what's the success no sir operation blue shell kill was indeed a success no sir
D for lore no yet that's Garfield
it is so fun to fuck around in this program I was insane even having that
many people like that many characters is sitting like in one place is just so
it's so annoying to manipulate stuff you're not subbed I thought I've logged
in I haven't been logged into my YouTube channel in fucking like a half decade
I'm not logged in that was fucking crazy though and I know my password I'm glad
I finally get to see it we spent was a 26 minute film we just saw and that's
gonna bring us to the actual the actual find down in the stream log in on the
stream why the fuck would I do that make rat movie 3 on stream it's is that
something that people would actually want me to do and watch the thing is it
3d movie maker is not like 30 movie it's not like the movies it's a lot more
like painful frame-by-frame animation than it is about like hey look at this
funny thing that happens right now but I would actually consider that because the
plan for rat movie 3 kind of just disappeared when I stopped making
YouTube videos so maybe I put it on the list it would I would have to be truly
dedicated to it though because I would need to dedicate real real real time to
it actual time to it so I don't know I don't know what I want to do with that
there is no list German we know oh yeah there is no list I've got a notepad right
here with every single stream thing idea that I got it's on a notepad there's
like 60 things on it why would I show you that it's a
spoilers for future streams you're a liar I'm not a liar I don't want to show
to you I can't show it I'm gonna put it on Google dot you're gonna leak every
stream idea that I've ever had that's how far I'd know how would I do that I
have a notepad blow the whistle on yourself no all right let's do this
let's go back thanks for joining us for community content night thanks guys I
will see you guys I am NOT gonna be streaming for the next few days we're
gonna be back on we'll be back on Thursday the 12th and I'm supposed to
be the 12th is gonna be a fuckface dream so it's gonna that's gonna be one
I'm eating but I'm not eating his real shoe we'll see I wonder I'll see you
guys in a few days thanks for watching I've had a it's been a really really fun
week these last five streams here in a row have been very very very fun they
always are but you know it's been a fun week I'll see you guys next week but
we need to the bits we'll go over the bits and subs and everything those
videos I just want to get some more material I want to get more footage so
bad but Andy Andy Andy rude dupe thanks to the thousand bits ten bucks can you
make the troll face I needed for a reference how do you make what's the
face how do you do the troll face it's like this right hold on it's like this
how do you do it it's like right like that that was that's it right close
enough yeah that's close enough all right well there you go thanks for 10
bucks a sticks renegade thanks for the 250 tell me your favorite animals so I
can draw your fursona frog if you abstain from answering I will default it
to rat I'll get ready to see your fursona drawn by yours truly it's a
frog or a rat it's probably frog hey mostly lost thanks to the 250 stinky
streamer I hate that fucking word thank you Oh muffin thanks for the three
dollars Oh muffin fuck you stinky is a fun word I call my cat stinky baby all
the time also no offense but please get better at commenting on art I already
told you this I divide I don't know what every time I talk about like the line
work but I don't know I don't anything I just think it looks cool I like think it
looks awesome what do you want me to be a fucking like art exhibit curator what
do you want me to say I don't run I don't run a fucking art museum yes you
do why did you gift me a sub I get there well you if you hey wow you were here oh
wait how does that work don't they have to be in the chat to get the sub people
not in the stream get gift subs too it can wait you don't if I randomly give
500 subs to like right now you don't have to be you literally don't have to
be here just picks a random person that's a follower no way no way why the
fuck would they do it like that I don't but is that that can't be accurate
that's insane if that's real well I don't even know what's real I got five
subs from streams that I wasn't even watching a while back that's really
weird I would figure to be whoever's like currently on the stream right now
I guess not peaceful Haley thanks for 250 you got to go to galaxy's edge and
get a lightsaber from there it's so worth it get a Kylo mask from Walmart
or something or something yeah those things oh I would break one of those I
would bring that to the green screen and be like look at my cool $300
Darth Maul lightsaber and I would break it during that stream it would be a
disaster the thing would just shatter it would just be made of a glass it would
just break although I mean that's like funny because like why would somebody's
lightsaber break you've spent more on us oh I know but that I'm just saying you
got to make a statement hey Mitchell thanks for a thousand bits Twilight is
softcore erotica or women since women prefer literary erotica as opposed to
the male preferred porn the top five searches women maker for vampire
werewolf surgeon billionaire and pirate oh what are the top five for men boobs
all right okay all right all right all right all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right all right all right all right all right all
right all right asking questions I shouldn't be asking that's okay though
thank you Mitchell for the thousand bits appreciate it hey one hey Zeus thanks
to the 250 what an unbelievably talented community I know that's why I
like to do this stuff because there's some real real effort that people put
into this shit and it's really fun to watch and really fun to look at thanks
to 50 a BS 88 1 4 thanks for the $3 German I've been watching since 2013
recently started watching your streams love the content it's helped me get
through a rough month always excited to see you live before I go to work would
give more bits but I'm a little tight at the moment appreciate you don't worry
about that save you money spend it on you put me at the very bottom of your
list of things to give money to thank you try con thanks for the 500 bits
you're my love the streams wonder if you could ever go back and play the new
stage they added to Celeste there's a really good level and I want to see if
you would play it you know I have a good stream it's Celeste have DLC and I never
did or what because I remember I played it pretty late did I do any of it was it
available I'm asking questions and people can't even write first thing we
get to see is German love the stream what's your favorite brand of adult
diaper that's a for you had that queued up you there's no way you wrote that you
knew it was an emote only mode so what you did is you type that sentence out
sentence out and waited until the second you saw the notification and hit enter
make sure you were the first one smart that's very smart that's like that's a
that's next level like shit post I respect that anyways maybe I don't want
to have it be at least something I can do for a few hours though cuz I feel
like if I went back to Celeste I would hopefully I mean would that be more
than an hour or two the new levels are harder than Jump King well I know
something I'm not doing and they're probably not it's hellish Oh God
captain crunchy thanks with five community subs punterm Lundquist
thanks for the four hundred bits with a pogchamp mink fur thanks with a thousand
bits with a germ of Venus ten bucks thank you did I say 400 subs is it 400
bits right that would be pretty nonchalant way to say thanks for 400
subs hey thanks for the 400 subs thank you also to you
hey the speed thanks for the 250 just saw this website on the latest valve
news network video the text-to-speech generator for some popular voices made by
some someone from MIT the voice replication is actually very good for
some of the options give it a try you've actually heard of some of these things
before aren't there aren't there what can't you do
in this shit that you can do that's like you send in voice clips and it'll give
it'll give you text-to-speech of your voice and it's perfect that's so scary I
thought about doing that it might have been fun to do but then it's like holy
shit now somebody can use that people could make you say anything I just
imagine it in the next community content video people just having that
software and having it just not even need to sentence splice any fucked up
things I've ever said just let them do it already they already can well yeah
but I mean they could like I could say anything still sounds fake though
interesting app though make it be bugleberry goat slice thanks the 250
appreciate your I'm glad you and chat enjoy not only a little doodles what
everyone else is to keep German it up here's the 2020 full of self-love
Omega wink I feel like Omega wink happens when you sneeze potato chief
thanks for the 500 bits blink 543 times if you're in trouble big Apple would
thanks for the 400 bits Percy thanks for the thousand bits Percy thanks for
another four dollars no message just money fourteen dollars worth of bits
thank you hey one hey Zeus thanks for 250 thanks for getting my wink I was
number 264 who 64 Apple ship thanks for 250 only you could hold nearly 8,000
viewers by sitting in front of a camera and winking 400 plus times laugh out
well um that actually kind of didn't happen I had like 8,200 concurrent
viewers and then when I started winking we dropped to about 7,100 so we actually
lost about a thousand people during that whole thing so it's alright that's
actually pretty good considering but I appreciate it nonetheless thank you not
as cat as not a cat not as cataclysmic as blue bugleberry no not quite not
quite it could have been there though if I had to do that like two or three
thousand times that would have been it would have been bad that was just long
enough for it to be done good moment a stripes beast thanks the five dollars
stripes beast you are hands down the best surrealist streamer out there
surrealist please make sure to apply some ointment on your right eye to
reduce the massive swelling you'll have tomorrow I'll be alright I'm fucking a
surrealist mink for thanks for the 500 bits winks for days links for days more
like egomaniac yeah yeah that is like an egomaniac thing huh I'm not I'm not
though am I no I'm not that's exactly the butt somebody would say if they
were I'm not I'm not I'm not it's true it's not true is it no it's not flower
patch thanks for the five dollars what up German just so you know I'm not mad or
anything I just think it's really funny how you didn't fulfill your promise of
finishing Pajama Sam 3 you are what you eat from your head to your feet I
understand you got stuck at the french fry part but you said you were gonna
beat that level off stream and now you're just pretending we've forgotten
about that please finish it we want to see your funny reactions to all of
Pajama Sam 3's wacky scenarios can't beat kids game get called out the the
cle the clematron or the clematron thanks for the 300 bits Garfield the
Monday killer thanks for the 250 hey Jeremy you're gonna watch the Sonic
Rebuild film like you said oh that's right and Joel's movie kind of pulled in
front of you in traffic there are you gonna watch in the next community
content stream I should also tell a Garfield joke lasagna everyone please
laugh oh yeah I unfortunately we watched Joel's movie instead but I will skim
through that eventually watch number 12 unfortunately no no no no no I'm not
saying unfortunately we've bought you got it semantics you can't play
semantics I'm talking about like we were gonna watch Garfield the Monday killer
is Sonic the Hedgehog fucking movie and like skim through it but unfortunately
sorry but like there was a there was a scheduling conflict with Joel's movie
not oh how unfortunate we had to watch that instead come on you playing
semantics with me roll of the dice thanks for five dollars hopefully this
works first time actually using bits thanks German for being a really cool
welcoming streamer while I suffered from some weeks of insomnia and stress I've
had insomnia plenty of times before it actually really really sucks so I know
what you're talking about your attitude is what others should aspire to be like
just trying to have a good time that's all was it appreciate it though thank
you let's get the credits on here oh thanks to subbing everybody I really
appreciate it thanks for sticking around thanks for subbing this channel you have
a lot of options on this website and some of you a lot of you actually have
decided to give me money every month on the same day
thank you appreciate that which dot com slash Jeremy it's not even I don't have
that something thanks again hey sterner thanks for the three dollars sterner
hello mr. 985 how are you gonna explain to your doctor that you got an eye
injury from winking too much and how am I gonna explain to my doctor I got a
lung injury for laughing too hard I got dizzy for laughing from laughing well I
don't know how you're gonna explain that but I'll look I'll just be like I was a
G I blinked it a bunch the baseball one almost killed me yeah me too
hundred and one domination is thanks for thousand bits ten dollars hey German
you've been a great help over the past few weeks as schools over here in South
Korea was shut down due to the corona virus with them opening back up in April
after spring break has been really frustrating being a senior in high
school makes things kind of important you've odds in the evening and streams
in the morning have been great for keeping me morale high in times like
these it's not as bad as a lot of the media report life isn't quite the same
hopefully that goes back to normal very soon I can imagine how frustrating that
is even now over here is new cases every day over here and it gets to a point
where it's like well all right how when how's this gonna play out you know how
is gonna happen oh I mean we've already started seeing
conventions and being closed and stuff canceled things being moved so it's
starting to happen over here too you just really hope that it doesn't get to
a point where everything has to shut off for an extended period of time so who
knows just try to stay safe as you can try to take care of yourself and let's
hope this whole thing kind of lays itself out with the right with the
proper proper health organization stepping forward and that's getting rid
of this shit that's all we can really do yeah I heard about the cases in in
Massachusetts to Vegas just had a one just pop up now to take yesterday the
day before so it's it's it's spreading over here it's happening here it's
hopefully not to the extent that it could but stay safe glad to hang out
with you while you're thanks a lot for the 10 bucks
Derma put Sun chips in F tier thanks to the 250 the past six months I've been
driving across Vegas at ungodly speeds that's right I have been every rumor
these past few months and by using echolocation with my extremely high IQ I
triangulated your exact address now confirm that it's pronounced juke not
juke jump not juke or I will really all right well this is a scary message this
is like a fucking freak me out message but I'll tell you it's it's Jupiter
Jupiter Jupiter Jupiter Jupiter is incorrect it's Jupiter Jupiter imagine
the timing would have been perfect German put F's chips and Sun chips in F
tier I also did do that sorry about that hey gnarly thanks for the 250 I need you
to randomly choose between heads or tails it'll decide what I do for a
community content night in the future and that was a lot of fun
hey ready tails hopefully you got it right sideways Reaper 500 thanks for the
250 German there's a newer version of 3d moviemaker that somebody made it's much
faster stronger and has mod support which is how Joel leans at Mario
characters in this movie you can go crazy and wrap movie 3 yeah I had some
of the mods for illegal some of the stability ones I didn't get any of the
crazy character ones though hey goo berry juice thanks for the 250 all
right winker 555 time to step out of the spotlight for a second I don't want to
take a moment to talk about how you're great your community is they're all so
fucking talented and funny just makes me want to be part of it so bad I feel like
a fat goblin sometimes being in the same chat room as these gods nothing makes me
more happy than when I make even one person feel supported a laugh from a
stupid donation I'm gonna miss your streams for the week but more I'll miss
you pointing at chat well you are but you are participating you're you are you
are laughing and encouraging people to make really fun things and you get to
enjoy it too a lot of this the meme shit and a lot of the brand of videos are
because of jokes and references that this community has come up with so
you're you get to be part of it even if you don't make oh no you don't I didn't
make I didn't spend like two weeks on a video like that's that's doesn't matter
all right I just make pee-pee poo-poo joke so mega low that's that's all good
man I want them it's more fun the more people get to hang out and enjoy this
shit anyway we'll get into we'll get into like potential Phil Stadium amounts
of people here and it's fucking wild it makes me so happy and we can continue
to bring people on that just hang out and have a good time
what's Phil's stadium oh I see well there was $50 that just came in like
five minutes ago when when did this come in this is from Jamie KW 5,000 bits 50
fucking bucks hi Jeremy I love your streams been watching for years and I'm
super glad I got to see you watch the blue shell incident live thanks for
everything you've done over the past few years really got me through a lot
thanks for the huge fucking amount of money thanks a lot dude seriously guys
no one tell Jerma I love him well I saw it this slaps King I will play this
we'll change the music to this while we finish it up unplugged my headphones
let's listen pretty good all right let's get to the end of the bits here but
Jamie seriously that's fucking a ton of money 5,000 bits never expect people to
do that shit but people do all the time so thank you oh muffin thanks for the
300 bits I'm sorry for being mean to you Jerma I was just playing I know I'm so
am I 95% of everything I say is not even real don't you remember that thank you
the 300 bits appreciate a whimsy five dollars from Wimsy hey Jerma here's
something of a little thank you for everything you did and continue to do
who will collab with RT game sometime actually hung out with RT for like two
three days he was in Vegas the song is pretty fucking good too that's gonna
bring us to the end of the stream the actual end and the end of the streams
for the week have a great night everybody you'll see me again on Thursday
enjoy the first start of your week here take care of yourselves we have two more
bits to do but we'll see you soon hey raise intros thanks to 300 bits Jerma
I'm a newer viewer of yours but I'm having such a great time catching up on
your streams and learning all the in jokes I'm one of the 500 go in your gift
subs and since I can't keep up the sub I just say thanks here and thanks to you
Chad I'm blown away by what crazy and unique community you have here cheers
to you Jerma well welcome thanks for stopping by for the first place we're
glad to have you thanks for checking us out thanks for checking me out thanks
for checking the community content nights out that shits not mine I mean
it's me it's footage of me and footage that I've presented but it still has to
be you somewhere give us one final wink sure I will but welcome to the stream
hopefully stick around it we'll see you again soon and finally gnarly 250 from
gnarly tails huh it may have been a bad idea to let you choose the heads option
was just gonna be some more soul caliber characters but without spoiling it tails
is related to one of the worst dreams you did last year oh this is the funny
part where the people in chat say well which one there were hundreds all of
them all right good night guys I'll see you later see you next coming week I'm
gonna do a wink though I'm gonna give you a final wink there you go good night
goodbye it's never happening ever again even if it makes sense for me to wink
for some reason on stream I'm not going to do it not gonna happen I'm never
gonna wink ever again that's my first wink up there all right goodbye see you
guys on Thursday good night wait goobeary juice says for 250 thanks for
250 germa you once made a potion that cures a goblinism at one time you think
I could borrow it I'm feeling pretty gobliny tonight you can you hook me up
I don't drink that don't drink that they fuck with come on we gotta stay as a
goblin come on don't drink that shit all right see you left