Hello ladies and gentlemen, my name is Gunther. Welcome to Facecam Fortress 2. I will be your host tonight, not Jerma.
I'm going to be playing as the Huntsman Sniper.
Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2. Gunther, it's not your time to shine. You'll do that some other time.
Three sentries on top of the roof. Excellent. Play it as the Sniper like Gunther told you. On bad water. Didn't get the headshot, but that's okay.
Got it. Why am I lagging right now? I'm like lagging. Can you guys see that? Maybe I'm just going crazy.
So I'm wearing this goofy hat today. I know I'm not completely crazy. This is just something I found in my closet. It's actually my father's hat.
And I figured, you know what? Facecam Fortress 2, Saturday's edition. I'm going to put on a dumb hat and I'm going to leave it on for the whole entire time.
Probably not though, because it's starting to hurt my skull. But my eyes pinched them out. I should have died.
We only have a minute and 50 seconds left anyways. Auto balanced. What the heck?
Trying to get those mad kills as a... Oh, one of these days that's going to work.
I saw a YouTube video one time where that actually worked very, very well. And if I don't like throw up my mouth, I'll kill this heavy.
Drinking too much coffee. Oh, make it three for three. Three for three. Got to get rid of that sentry.
And sentry down. Oh my God, I forgot. I totally forgot there was this many sentries. That's four for four.
Oh, you spy, you spy F word. Oh, this thing really hurts.
I'm going to take this off halfway through this and there's going to be a red ring around my whole skull.
I'm going to look like Friar Tuck. Here we go. It's going to work. I'm hoping if I get that, you're going to see a pretty ridiculous reaction.
You can't run from me, man. How did they not hit him in the face? Don't ask me. Here he is. No, where'd he go?
Oh, there's absolutely no way we're going to do this unless like an Uber demo man comes over here.
Show yourself. How are we supposed to do this? Look at this chaos.
All right. So I have actually, while we just get smoked right here by these five sentries up here, I actually have something to talk about.
Oh my God. Hold on. Oh, something in my eye. Oh, this is what happens when you play live. You can't control things like this.
Are we good? We're good. So what I want to talk about before my eye gets eaten by a leech or whatever the hell flew into my eye or whatever in my eye.
I want to talk about my live stream this weekend because it's actually it's something interesting I want to try and do and it has to do with choose your own adventure.
Now bear with me for a second. I want to make a poll every 20 minutes during my live stream tomorrow and I'm going to have like five different options.
So it's going to say eat an egg, do a cartwheel on camera, like play a different game.
Like there's going to be five different options you can choose from and whatever one gets the most amount of votes is what I'm going to do.
I'm going to call it the choose your own adventure live stream with Jerma.
Hopefully that wasn't too loud, but that's what I plan on doing tomorrow.
I'm going to iron out some of the details, but it could actually be pretty funny and pretty fun at the same time.
So we'll see how that goes. Pee on that medic.
And by tomorrow I should be able to stream 3D games.
And that's not because I got some magic patch that allowed me to stream 3D games.
I'm getting another computer. As ludicrous as that sounds, it's actually true.
I'm going to get like a cheap laptop that can stream 3D games. Where is anybody?
Cheap laptop, not going to get anything too fancy, but just something enough where I can be confident that I can at least stream games.
And that's something I am... No!
Aw, something I'm going to do. So I should be able to do it by tomorrow afternoon.
Heavy, you are spraying everywhere. You look like a real psycho.
So let's just roll, huh? Are we just going to roll this card? I'm going forward.
I'm moving forward, baby. I stand still for no man.
Where's the team? Did we just really push that far forward?
What just happened with that?
How did I not... Did I put anybody out with that?
I swear that didn't put anybody out. I threw it right in the middle of all of us.
Spy? No.
You know, I'd like to kill somebody. That would be fantastic right now.
I can't kill anybody. I'm just like...
Did I not kill that guy?
Alright, I'm going to switch. What is happening right now?
I keep hearing like the ding, but I don't kill anyone. Let's just go...
Let's go Demoman.
Uber. Uber. We got a Uber.
Scout, what do you think you're doing, boy?
New rank. New rank.
That guy flew a thousand feet in the air.
Dr. Sandvich, the hack master.
Alright, this thing is really starting to concave my skull. I have to get this thing off.
Oh, by the way, if you're wondering, they're right here.
It's not like they're in some case somewhere.
My gunner optics are sitting right here.
And a lot of people ask, Jerma, why do you not wear those during your face cam sessions?
I feel like they kind of make my face look a little different.
I'd rather have you guys see the real me rather than the glasses me.
Because I don't think I look very good in glasses. I think I look pretty bad.
Oh, this spy. Let's watch it. Oh, nice backstab there, dude.
Nice. Lock and load.
Miss twice. Miss again. Run.
Brain freeze. Brain freeze. I'm not even drinking that cold of a drink and I just got brain freeze.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Only two and a half minutes left and we win.
Look at this engineer insanity. Two dispensers, three engineers, two...
Wow. You have to be a spy.
I always do that. I always think that somebody's a spy when they're just not.
But this guy has to be. Yes, of course he is.
Of course he does the thing where I... Wait. Wait. I think he went down here.
You know what? I'm not going on a wild goose chase right now. I got stuff to do.
Oh, and there he is. That's one way to do it.
Oh, don't you dare. Oh. Oh, yeah.
Oh, that was so satisfying. I love doing that. It's so much fun.
The lock and load is just too fun. Did I just kill two people with that?
Yikes. Come on. Show your bloody face.
Whoa. Fire. Fire. Fire. Fire. Miss. Wow.
Oh, but I love that same spy again. Oh, that's just depressing.
Have I been killed by three spy revolvers in a row? I really think I might have.
Just dink, dink, dink. Oh, don't let them get this.
Do not let... I'm going to be very upset if they get this.
I might, in fact, puke blood. That would be horrible.
Let's go straight down the line. Straight down the line with the lock and load.
Oh, will he do a backflip for me? Where are you going? Where are you going?
Where are you going? 16 seconds left. Come here. Come over here.
Oh. Five, four, three, two, one, zero. I think we won.
Over time, you're going to make me spit my coffee on the screen.
I will see you guys all next time. Thanks for watching so much.
And stay tuned for the livestream tomorrow. I might have explained that very, very strangely,
but it's going to be a choose-your-own-adventure livestream.
I will explain in better detail tomorrow when it happens, but it should be pretty fun.
So thanks so much, guys, for watching. I'll see you guys all soon.
And, of course, take care, everybody.