Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, gonna be doing a good old-fashioned shoutcast, like I used to do back in the day.
Used to talk really fast, used to go over gameplay elements, and that's what I'm gonna do tonight in this video.
And the class of choice is gonna be the Scout, using the default scatter gun, the Criticola, and the Candy Can, one of my default setups, my favorite setup as the Scout by far.
And before I get started, I do want to say that I am reading the comments, I am taking in your guys' feedback, and here is one of the most requested things I get to do more gameplay-oriented videos.
Breaking down how I'm killing people, why I'm choosing the certain targets, and the map direction and all that stuff, that is what this entire video is going to be about.
So without further ado, let's get started. Playing on King of the Hill Lake side right now, which is arguably the best Scout map in the game, at least in my opinion.
I find when I play Scout, I can come on here and do very, very well, regardless of if I'm having a bad day or a good day or something like that, it just all clicks on Lake side.
So coming around the left stairwell over here, left or right, depending on where you're looking at it.
Get this Scout, he wasn't looking at me off guard, and I get the assist on this Soldier as well.
Stay in this area as a Scout. The fact that there is a full health pack in there should make you lead over there for the entire duration of the fight.
And also right over here too, there is a medium health pack. Health packs, health packs, health packs, that is I guess what I'm getting at here.
Get a route as the Scout where you can run around in a circle almost while you're killing people, picking up these various health packs and staying alive.
And the best part about that pool room is there is water in that room. So if you get lit on fire by a Pyro and there's no health pack there, somebody took it recently, you can just jump into the water.
So sticking around here on the bottom level patrolling, making sure nobody comes around, no Scouts or anything like that.
Not going to go over on that side because there was obviously 55,000 people over there.
Get lit on fire by this Pyro, and this is exactly what I'm talking about over here. Watch the health pack. It's not there.
I actually get it because it reappears, but at the same time I could have just jumped right in.
Me and this Soldier fall in there together and I kind of feel bad because that was a random crit right in his face.
But at the same time you take those if you can get them, and I ended up getting one.
So let's break for a second right here and let me tell you why I'm not entering that room.
Kind of the counter to a Scout is a Mini-Sentry Engineer. There was a Mini-Sentry in that room.
He actually came out and I killed him right there. But at the same time, going into this room is certain death for any Scout.
If you know there is a Mini-Sentry around, do not just run yourself into death.
Go around the other side, wait for one of the power classes to take it out.
But you are not the one that can kill that. If you do, if you can get it, great.
But most of the time you're going to find yourself in a lot of trouble if there's a Mini-Sentry.
So coming down to about a minute and ten seconds left, the Red Team has not really got on the point.
This is a pretty good push right here, but they don't actually succeed.
Because of course we have a Heavy sitting in the corner waiting for anyone to come through.
Get a nice shot on that Scout and a Pyro chasing me.
I love that part right there. That Scout just bashed his brains in. He wasn't even paying attention.
So a small tip, at least on Lakeside. It works for other maps as well.
Take a look at where everyone comes out of the spawn.
Everyone tries to find the easiest possible route out of a spawn door.
And it just so happens to be the straightforward option.
This little S-curve right there is the best possible straightforward option for anyone coming out of the spawn.
The only people that go left and right are Snipers and maybe Spies.
But that's really it. Most people try to go, like I said, to the easiest possible exit.
Which gives you a great little picking round for finding people off guard.
As you just saw right there, I got killed by that enemy Scout.
Because I had Criticola on and the only explanation for that is I like to live dangerously.
And right here, this mini-century is not built yet.
So that's why I kind of went for it. I knew I was going to put it down.
Knew I could get it if I could just get in there fast enough.
And it actually worked out perfectly.
So that is going to wrap up this gameplay. I actually got on the top of the scoreboard.
Which is always interesting, always cool.
And this last little bit is just a couple of random clips I put together.
Just because I didn't want a three and a half minute video or a four minute video.
So while this kind of ends here, this last Scout gameplay on Lakeside, I want to bring up this question to you guys.
Do you want to see more content like this?
More Shoutcast-y, more gameplay-oriented, more fast-paced.
And I know it's about a 50-50 threshold where some people like the other content, some people like this content.
So I'm going to try to bring some of this back a little bit and do this a little more often.
Because I do have a lot of fun doing this.
And it's always interesting to get on here and start talking about the gameplay and start talking about the characters and stuff.
Only I don't know why I haven't done this in a while, to be honest with you guys.
I don't know why I haven't done one of these Shoutcast-type gameplay videos in a while.
And I think it's because it's just been on the back burner a little bit.
I told myself a few weeks ago, I said, I should do another Shoutcast.
I should do another just gameplay Shoutcast video.
And I forgot. I never did it.
And actually yesterday or the day before, I forget what it was, I got a couple of comments of people saying,
Jerma, where's the old Shoutcast, the old gameplay-type videos?
And I went, whoa, my memory jogged.
And I said, you know what? I forgot. I got to do one of those.
So here it is. I hope you guys enjoyed it.
And like I said, please give me some feedback if you want to see some different classes
or if you want to see me continue this type of series, then please let me know.
And I will catch you guys all next time.
So take care, everybody.