Why am I seeing a bunch of- Finally, crack time. Crack time, crack time. Finally, it's crack time.
Are you just sitting there waiting to smoke crack? Like you've got your crack on the table and your
crack pipe or your crack device. Are you just sitting there like a napkin is laid out in front
of you? Come on, come on, start the stream dude. He's late. I can't smoke this crack until he's here.
God damn it. Oh, live, live. Oh yeah. Yes, we have to wait. Oh, finally, crack time.
Anyways, how are you? Just like crack work. Yeah, we're going to play more house flipper today
for an undetermined amount of time. I might get bored in 30 minutes and we play Desperados 3
or I'll be here for another five or six straight fucking hours and then we're going to do,
we're just going to keep doing it. I don't know. Am I going to just sly Cooper?
I don't know. Sly Cooper. You got to put that in the list of games that are similar to,
and I know people are going to be like, did he just sit? Hold on. I put like Jack and Dexter
and Dexter and Jack's. What's that other one? This too. Ratchet and Clank. Ratchet and Clank,
Jack and Dexter. I feel like that's like a tag team fight. Okay. So that's very different.
Jekyll and Hyde. Take that. Say no, that you, okay. I thought you said, take that back.
You said, say hi back. Hey, how are you? They were competing platform mascot game. Yeah,
it's, I don't know. Sly Cooper just kind of fits there in my brain with like other mascot platformer
game. I thought you don't have a gun or anything. You don't just jump around and I only like Jack
one and they're all great. Hey, I know I haven't played them. I'm sure I will eventually on stream
and you delay the screen by five minutes. I have to enter the litter box.
I, it's going to probably take five minutes to go do it now and take probably five minutes
before I get into the game. This dude's a pathological liar. No, I'm a pathological
forgetter. There's a huge difference. You play PlayStation heroes. No, I haven't. That's a lie.
You're going to play fall guys. No, not today. Not today. I, I can't, I can't do it. I cannot
win. I finally pulled out of the seven 11 parking lot. That is like $42 scratch tickets. I don't
think I'm going to win. He's a selective pathological forgetter. You just described like
a patient in a Leslie Nielsen movie. What's the prognosis doctor? Oh, he's a selective
pathological forgetter. Interesting. Did you just who Leslie Nielsen? I want to ban that guy.
Are we getting a who on Leslie Nielsen? A who? A who on Leslie Nielsen? Oh boy. Do yourself a
favor. Just go watch every Leslie Nielsen movie from start to finish. And I'm even talking about
the ones that are in black and white that weren't comedies. Go watch those too. Watch them all.
Watch this whole catalog. He has like a hundred movies. I told that I told that person that they
could empty the litter box. Look, we haven't even done anything. The naked gun movies are
were a pretty major influence on what I think is funny. I used to watch those all the time.
Airplane, airplane movies, huge influences. Spaceballs, kind of the same era. I love the
naked gun series. It was just ridiculous. He made so much money just being the guy that was dead
serious in absurd situations. It was just Leslie Nielsen. It was going to look at something with
a stern face and be completely deadpan while a clown like honked a horn behind him. It was
awesome. Is that police squad show? Yeah, that was what it was before, right? No, no, no. What was
it was? It was naked gun was the movies based on a TV show that got canceled, right? That's the one,
right? That police squad was first. What are you resident sleeper? Resident sleeper.
Just go watch. OK, you could resident sleep for me on this topic, but go watch naked gun.
And I bet you that resident sleeper face turns into like a hog mouth in about 45 minutes.
Leslie Nielsen who naked gun resident sleeper.
Shit, now I'm going to be 40 soon. All right, let's go. Let's play. Welcome back, everybody.
Hope you're having a good day. Hey, hope you're having a good day. What does that mean? I say
that a lot. I think a lot of people say that, like when they broadcast and they make videos,
they guess hope you're having a good day. I mean, I kind of I do, but that's always the go to.
All right, here's the Aqua teen house because every house is a fucking cartoon house. I
seriously couldn't stop thinking about this. I couldn't stop thinking about this the whole
night of this. I didn't even want this to be a cartoon house. But like the title says,
it's always a cartoon house. Always a mystic quests. That's what a great name that is.
Mystic quests. Thanks to the five community subs. And what is this? This is a image of me.
OK, hold on. I thought this was. Don't ask me why.
I thought that was ice. I thought I was sitting in ice, like an ice bath going like, oh,
I saw it. It was this small when I saw it. I was like, oh, shit, like somebody made me like an
ice bath. It's a coke bath. No, no, we guys, we cannot. We this we cannot. We cannot.
What is going on? Weak to 2020. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. This is absurd.
I got to put this up. This is ridiculous. All right. We got up. I'm going to move on after
this. We got to play. Is this because I took the week off? I didn't take a week off. I took
two months off. Fuck. This is fucking ridiculous. OK. All right. I got to let's get grounded here.
Oh, he's on vacation again. I wasn't on vacation. All right. Time to get to work.
You guys are grounded. OK, so I have to take a wall down. I cannot. This is this can't be
Meatwad's room, but I have practiced the voice. OK, what are you doing? I don't want you in my
room. No, I don't think so. I think I want to get out of my room. I've been working on the voice as
of yet. It took me about four hours to get that correct. He did that yesterday. I didn't do the
high part. I didn't do that. What do you do? I didn't do that one yesterday. I did the low one.
It took me two hours in the bathtub saying that into the ceiling to get that right. But I have to
I can't do this. This has to change. This is I can't. This cannot be the Aqua Teen house.
I'm sorry. I have to get rid of this. I have to take this wall down. This cannot be an Aqua Teen
house. No, no, it's not happening. I don't care. All every house cannot be a cartoon house,
not every. It's not going to be. Oh, do Family Guy, do the Simpsons, do Aqua Teen,
do the American Dad house. No, this is my house. My house is not a cartoon house. There's no sound.
Oh, shit. Sorry about that. It was on full blast. OK, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. That was
fucking loud. I know this sounds allowed. I didn't have the desktop audio pulled down a little.
What OST are we going to listen to today? How about the Aqua Teen Hunger Force OST?
I'm not muted. What happened here? Who chipped this tooth? All right. What if what if the house
is just a giant garage? What? OK, what if this is a house for a car? Like you pull the car in
and you pull the car and you turn right and then you drive straight and you pull in into the
bedroom and you sleep in the car. And if you have to go to the bathroom, you have to like drive into
another room and like just pee out your window. A drive in house. Yeah. OK, this house makes sense
in some weird dystopian future where we have to stay in our cars because there are like there
are like weird aliens outside that will like implant themselves in your brain if you get out
of your car. This is this is a post 5G world. I mean, I mean, I'm talking more about like
it's just like aliens and the aliens don't understand the cars for some reason, right?
That's like the weird plot of the movie. It's like for some strange reason, the aliens do not
understand cars and they they're afraid of them. They won't go near them. Kind of like how that's
a spoiler. I was going to make a direct reference to a movie, but it's the whole it's the whole
thing about to say is a spoiler. All right. Well, this is the first make sure we can make this turn.
Say it. No, I don't want to say I don't. I know people like movies open. Slime already did this
bit. Just give a spoiler warning. OK, here's I'm going to give you a spoiler warning. OK,
this is a spoiler warning for the movie Bird Box. OK, this is I'm about to make a major
talk about I'm going to talk about Bird Box. OK, just are you ready? Put it on screen.
All right. This is why this is like in the poster of the movie.
I don't know. Why do I need to? I don't need to. What the fuck do I care? This is in the poster
of the movie. It's Samantha. What's her name? Famous, incredibly talented, famous actress.
Sandra Bullock, right? Nobody cares about Bird Box. Some one of you does. Who cares? Who cares?
No, you don't understand. People care about this shit. Do you know how much direct email
I've gotten about spoiling like the Lord of the Rings? I've got like seven pieces of fan mail
that were not fan mail at all. By the way, they lied in the subject and was like,
dude, such a huge fan. Click me. I love you. I'm like, oh, cool. And I click it.
It's like you fucking asshole. Fuck you, dude. I was on the last book and I had no idea
that Sauron was the eye. Piece of shit. I'm just like, dude, I'm fucking. OK, wait. It's like in the
menu. Like the devs. OK, I got to tell you about this. I'm so fucking annoyed with this movie.
We got to continue game. We got to move the obvious. Bird Box spoilers. Click here if you
want to see them, because I got to tell you. It's my review. All right. Anyways, no, but that's
good. Here we go. OK, so in the movie Bird Box, here comes the whole movie. In the movie,
I'm going to tell you the whole movie. In the movie Bird Box, this these this aliens invade Earth
or something, and you can't look at them. They haven't. They didn't figure out that,
like, you have eyelids. You cannot look at them. If you look at them, you're in big fucking trouble.
You're you're in a lot of trouble if you look at them. But for some reason, they didn't figure
out that if everyone walks around with their eyes closed, they can just walk around like stab people
that don't ever see it coming away. Know the whole point of the movie was the birds in the box.
The birds like chirped when they were around. Oh, yeah, the writers figured that part out.
That's right. Yeah, the writers like figured out a way to make it so like they couldn't just walk up
and stab people. Right. OK, that's that's the whole point of the movie. That's the whole it's in the
title. That's not what the movie was about. What are you talking about? But that doesn't that
doesn't happen in Bird Box. That's not Bird Box. That's a different movie. What do you mean? What
movie am I thinking of? Wait, so there's not a bird in Bird Box that tweets that chirps when
the monsters are around. Yes, it is. This is a different movie. Spoils a different movie.
Movie. No, I'm being gaslit. All right. This is gaslighting. OK, where was I going with this?
What are you guys doing to me? Why do you guys say that thing about Bird Box? What did you do that
for? He's pretending for views. No, that's what happened. Long story short, in the movie Bird Box,
you have to keep your eyes closed and the aliens have not figured out a fucking way
of how to like get somebody to open their eyes so they don't know. They just stand around until
you open your eyes. So imagine like that your eyes are the car that happens in the movie Signs. No,
it doesn't. You're doing with the house. No, this is yeah. It's about being gaslit. I'm saying that
like the aliens cannot figure out how to get you out of your car, just like how they couldn't
figure out how to get you to open your eyes in Bird Box. That's what I was saying. So you drive
around in your fucking car and you have to live in your car house because the aliens don't know
how to get you to understand your car. It's not a spoiler. It's a basic presence of the presence of
the movie. OK. OK, so in this world, you cars like is it does everybody in the family have their own
car that they drive around the house and if you want to go like get breakfast like, oh, here comes
like here comes like little little Timmy coming down the stairs in his car. His house is not big
enough for that. This is supposed to be your house. It is. I don't like it. It's an aqua teen
thing that fucks me all up. I don't want an aqua teen house. Now, how am I going to do this?
I'm not going to sell it. I'm not going to lose my money on it. That's not a spoiler. That's the
basic premise of the movie. That's what I was saying. But you don't understand the fucking hate
mail that I've gotten. I want to pick this up. Just sell the damn thing. What do I care? This
was like fun for a little while, but like who cares about me making the stream room? This is
the garage. The garage leads down to a basement. Basement leads into a larger room and then a
bathroom. OK, there's a bathroom down here. This should just be the house. I just have a dummy
house upstairs like the burglars to go into if there's ever like a burglary or something,
just a fake house with a bunch of fake money. And then my house is down here. It's all just
like weird cardboard furniture and shit. But like my actual house is down there. I'm not going to
sell these computers yet. This is a fortnight house. No, it's not. This is not a fortnight house
because if I was building it like a fortnight house, I'd be doing this. OK, so I want to let's
make a fake living room. TV is going to go here. It's the only logical place for it. This house is
pretty small. You go into the front door. You need a little kitchen. This is going to be a kitchen.
What's this? This is like another weird room. This room is just why they all have a why does
every room in this house have a back entrance to the backyard? That's kind of weird, right?
I don't like that. I can't put that down here. Why can I not put that down to destroy this? I
can't destroy this either. So I'm just going to put a wall here and then I'll paint like I'll paint
just outside to be painted. It's fine. There was a spoiler for House Flipper doesn't even have a plot
more of a mystic quest. Thanks again. Five more six more subs actually. No joke. Make your dream
house. I don't think I could even do that, though. I thought about it even more last night. My dream
house is just a room, a decent toilet and a nice bed and a door that works in locks. I'm pretty
simple. It's like, well, I can't wait to do like a huge decoration upstairs. I don't upstairs may
as well. Downstairs may as well not even exist. Do I have a room with a toilet next to me? A bed
is like a 70 inch TV with like all the consoles plugged in. And yeah, I'm good. That's much better.
This is like an actual room. Need curtains here. What? Wait, I need what color? That's prison.
Um, that's not what. OK, what prison do you know that each prison cell has a 70 inch TV
in every console plugged in? You're going to go to gamer jail. You dream, dream, solitary confinement.
No. All right. I need to focus on my dream house. This is going to be up here. There's a room here.
I need to get a big picture here of this. You know, this can stay. This could just stay open.
Like, should there be signs up here that's like, yep, like you fucked up. Nothing in here, idiot.
And I like paint on the walls that says like nothing to steal. Stupid. Oh, right. You couldn't
find the right house to steal from, huh? And then have like this door just be blocked. Custom paint
images. Yeah, yeah, I like that. I like that. Have the dummy house on top of the real house.
And I'm going to put like a bunch of diamonds and shit in here. And this room is going to be the
pre room to my actual house. And I'm going to put like a sign up here that just is like toxic,
fucking toxic waste or like electrified room. Do not touch handle. And to really push this,
to make sure nobody like actual. Oh yeah, bullshit. I'm knocking over a fucking toxic
waste barrel right here. So they're like, wait, what's that? Holy shit, dude. This is a bad idea.
Go back upstairs. Do not open door. We'll break a gas line. OK, yeah. Go, go, go. We're going to
have like a bunch of like dumb. OK, I'm ready. This is this goes downstairs. OK, should I do
the fake house first or should I do the real house first? Absolute paranoid house. Fake house first.
Traps all over it. OK, yeah. So this house is going to this room is going to be like a standard
bedroom. We're going to get what's what's like the cheapest paint. OK, well, forest mist is the
cheapest paint. But why did you say, of course I do. I thought I thought I told you guys that links
we were links were banned. Thanks for the fully rigged Vista slime. Oh, no, I saw this. I saw this.
You don't know anybody in your whole life. I feel like I feel like I would want more than one.
That's fucking awesome, though. I think there should be like a whole streamer slime family
and they like switch off who's going to stream today because what I think when I think of like
the mainstreamer, which is like slime, like just slime dad, I mean, I'm thinking of like
Slimer just like a disgusting Slimer that looks like he's barely functioning, like he's barely
able to even stay upright. Here we go. Oh, there we go. Look at this room. Wait, fan links.
I've thought about it. I've thought about it. Thank you, DJ on the beat. Thanks for the five
community subs. Thank you. Don't do it. I thought about it. You know, when people if you start to
overstay your link privileges. All right, what's something what's like looks OK.
I mean, we need something that has to look good enough. Right. This is cheap.
Porcelain. Oh, no. Fifty dollars to one. Fifty bucks from Ellis. Thank you, Ellis,
in there for the five thousand bits. Thank you. Ellis is in there. Oh, it's time. Is it time to
ban links? Oh, they're. Oh, they're doing it. Oh, they're doing it. Thank you, Ellis. Seriously,
you're a legend. I've never donated before. This is for years of content. Thank you, man.
Completely not necessary to give me that amount of money, but I appreciate it nonetheless.
Um, stop. Stop spamming my link. All right, let's go with, um,
should I name one of the rooms like expensive shit and this? Oh, no, it's time to do it.
We got I think we got to close links today. All it takes is you know how they say all it takes is
one person. Well, no, all it takes is like 400 people. This is be spamming links. And that's
when you get my attention. OK, somebody just write, let's go spam. No, what? No, stay. Don't
go anywhere. Don't go. Stay. Stay and then hang out. This looks good. God damn it. But it's I.
Oh, I do the same. I'm so boring. No. Wait, it's the same. Is it the same? Shit. It's really close.
OK, hold on. It's got to be something else. Floor rugs. No floor panels. It's a toilet house. No,
we're going to do, um, blue fitted carpet. That's better. Better, better, better, better,
better, better. OK. And the walls are changing that. God damn it. I don't know. I can't get
the doctor's office out of my mind. I don't. Should I do this? Change the walls. Jeans. Make
a jeans house. Denim ground. It's not denim. Look, you toss a rug on here and it's going to be
just fine. Watch this. Ready? Just toss. Look at this. Check this out. You toss a rug on here.
Look at that. It's changed the room entirely. It's a completely different room now. There.
I have made I've changed the room completely. I put a fucking expensive ass chandelier sphere
atom thing. Look at that. I want to see the before and after. And then a painting right here,
too. These walls are terrible. OK, we just need just like cheap a pet desk.
Why? What do you mean a pet desk? This actually is a desk for a dog or something. This is weird.
It's tiny. No, that's too small. Furniture. I need. Yeah, like, here we go. Bambino.
Should this be like a fake? This is going to be a fake kid's room.
No, there's nothing to steal. Germa desk. Germa desk. Germa desk. Yeah.
What is this? It's a crib. No, I want a bed. Here we are. One of these or.
Wait, is this a bed up top? It is. Holy shit. This is awesome. OK, this is my favorite kind
of bunk bed because it's a bunk bed without the other asshole underneath you. Perfect.
You know, I almost wish this was reversed. I don't want my bed this close to the ceiling,
but I would like sit up there. I don't care about that. I want to like climb up to my desk
and sleep down here. That would be cool if you climb up and there's like a platform and you
sit up here. I think that would be pretty. I want to be I don't I want to be closer to the ground.
I don't want to be sleeping up here. It freaks me out. No, not gray. All right. Blue.
We're going to go with the blue. The blue looks good, especially in a house that's gray with.
There we go. Perfect. OK, this just encompasses everything I told you guys I wanted in a house.
This is really all I need. You ready? You have a place to sleep up top right there.
You have a place to do your work right there. You just need a chair. You've got exercise.
You can climb up and down that thing like 10 times. You have the storage shoes, clothes.
You have a toilet. You could you could you could just piss in that.
Just have a hole in the ground. All right. There's your shoes and your clothes.
And you can slide that and there's like a little there's a hole in the ground.
You can just pee into it. It's a toilet. And just give me a TV right there.
Right in that big rectangle in the middle. It's perfect. TV right here.
And you just like go in here and sit and watch. What would a kitchen be?
You just order McDonald's every day. You know who cooks. What do you mean?
It's bad placement. Yeah, it kind of is. That's a little better.
No, it's not. It needs to be like a little bit. What about the closet?
Oh, fuck. Yeah, it needs to. OK, where do I put my hamster hotel?
The thing that I want so badly, I can't put it anywhere. It doesn't fit here.
Here? I guess it fits right here. Walk in the window. But you know, whatever.
Should I go then? Maybe that goes in another room.
I know a lot of you guys are talking a lot of some talking some serious shit right now.
But if you woke up and you kind of like went to the bathroom and you opened up a door and there was
like a McDonald's play place in one of the behind one of the doors in your house,
you don't think that you would go in there and just fuck around all the time?
Of course you would. Hamster. Yeah, the hamster house.
Imagine if you could go into a person sized hamster wheel and just sprint around your house
and smash the fuck into walls and you'd be fine. You just sprint in this bubble
and could just go anywhere. Just run into stuff that's lying. Oh, I know. OK, that's fine.
Now let's go with I want to put I want to put blinds on there, but not blinds. I hate blinds.
I want like just regular curtains, a multiple narrow curtain there and we can make this room
pop. I had a little bit of orange. It needs to be bigger than that.
It needs to be wide curtain, multiple short wide curtain. What's wrong with that? The bed in the
way. Where are the curtains? Oh, perfect. I just I only have this in here because I want it,
not because it makes sense in the room. Not big enough. All right, I can fix that.
This is fixable. Honey, we've got to take the wall down so I can fit my hamster bed.
Um, I can't can we just get a regular mattress that we know. Excuse me. You did not say
McDonald's play place. OK, move the door. That's too late. This room just got much bigger.
Oops. I swung and hit the wrong part of the house. You never do your own project.
This is one of those scenarios where it's just like, OK, let's start our project.
Here we go. We've got our tools. Cut to the ambulance. Cut to in the in the emergency room
where I'm like on like five different machines. He's flatlining. OK, this has to be like this,
though. Cut to the cut to a funeral. Well, does that have the same weight? Because how did he die?
We don't know. That could be like years in the future. If you cut to the funeral of the guy,
it's like, oh, no, he died. And then it goes back to their house. And what an amazing looking
incredible project that they did. By the way, this is the funeral is like from two or three years
after they completed this awesome project that you got to have context there. I don't think you
cut to the funeral. Irma has died of construction project. All right, here we go. Perfect. Now,
this room becomes longer like this. Trust yourself, man. Don't fucking listen to what anybody says.
Do you do it like this? Yeah, you did this. Nobody don't listen to fucking anybody.
Oh, and you can't fucking do it like this. I can fucking do it.
See, don't let anybody tell you can't do that. Can't do it because it's too close to the
window. It's all right. I can make this a corner. This is going to be a corner that people do that,
right? Disgusting. This is not disgusting. See, problem completely solved there. Oh, looks actually
really good. Cracks, cracks, lol. You guys have any idea what's surrounding you in your house
right now? You know how many cracks, how many broken like pieces of wood are just surrounding
you? You know how many dead animals are surrounding you right now? Right now, there are probably like
10 different dead bugs and animals surrounding you in your walls. There's a squirrel that's
dead in your wall. That's a skeleton that's been there for probably 45 years and it's
less than five feet, probably away from your face. So crack in the wall that I'm covering up.
Oh, it's not a big problem to me. How do you know that? Look it up. You put them in there.
How do you put something in a wall? So you're telling me that you think that you knock apart,
you go cut into your drywall and place an object in there and then put the drywall back up. Well,
for what reason? I just open up the drywall and dump like 5,000 crickets in there and then seal it.
Yeah, that's right. That's what I did today. Why did you do that? I don't know.
Shit! Is it big enough? All right, you can reach it. It's not big enough. It's not big enough.
Wait, can I turn the other way? You're fine. You're fine. You can fit in here. Just only open this
one and then duck and then kind of get your body inside of it and then and then get your clothes.
You have to close this one first and then leave. It's fine. The person using this is going to be
like this tall anyways. Yeah, you. Yeah. Wait, get that out of here. Can I take this down and
just go one more? I can do it now. I'm going to fix this. This is my dream house. What are
you talking about? This is my dream fake house above my real dream house. OK, so right here is
where I can safely open this. We're good. Close it up. Perfect. There we go. I don't fucking listen
to anybody. You can't do that. You can't. What are you doing? You're an idiot. Shut up. I can
fucking do it. I can do whatever I want. I'm not going to tell you anything like that ever again.
I'm not listening to anybody. Hey, it worked. What was he talking to? Oh, OK, I need paint.
We're doing a better paint, too. I want something nicer than this. Not I don't want it too dark,
though. No grays. Get away from the gray ink mist. Just just black every room. It's blue like
an Azure Bliss or a sleep. I think sleepy blue, baby blue. Let's try sleepy blue. I want to get
this right. Wait a minute here. Hold on. Hold on a minute here. A minute here. Hold on a minute
here. One, two, three, four, five. One, two, three. Hold on. Wait a minute here. One, two,
three, four, one, two, three, four, five. What's it? What color is this? Forest mist, right? OK,
one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four. Nice. Then that means
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen,
fifteen. So we need one here or up there. I paint it. What's wrong with this?
And I want like a green too or something. What looks better? Green. I need to see what this
looks like. Jerma, Jerma, hurry up. No, I'm making my dream fucking fake house. OK,
it's terrible. This is why I can't design anything. I like don't get it. My design philosophy is put
different color line in here. I don't know. That's why everything's gray. That's why all
my floors are gray. All my everything in my whole house is gray. I don't understand. I don't get it.
Should I do like a line, line, line or like one wall should be? Hold on. What if I do one whole
wall? OK, that looks all right. Do all blue. That's not too much, though. Oh, then I know
we can put little cloud artwork all over here. Yeah. Yeah. Like every baby boy's room in America.
Cloud, cloud, cloud, rainbow, frog, cloud, cloud, cloud, rainbow, frog.
Gaming. I get rid of this. It's going to it's going to pee through the walls here. All right.
Thank you. This is not disgusting. Disgust. This is OK. If you think this is disgusting,
then then you thought your room was disgusting. This is what it looked like. This is what your
room looked like when you were like 12. OK, this is what your room looked like. No, it didn't. Yes,
it did. When you were like under the age of seven, you had this room, this room right here.
What about dinosaurs? Yeah, we're going to put like dinosaur action figures on here. No, they better
not be expensive. Whatever they are, they better be cheap. Oh, wait, you know, you guys talk about
the stealing furniture. You can't deal this. It's just not it's bolted to the ground. It doesn't
come up, hinge on the floor. Hmm. That'd be cheap. Yeah, it better be cheap. Put concrete in here.
Bolted furniture is in prisons. No, it's not. It's in people who want to make sure that their
stuff is secure. It doesn't move. I open and close these. Oh, you can't close and open these.
All right. Now we need. OK, installations vent grill. Yeah. No, no, no. Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. We're not we don't give a shit about like giving and putting AC or heat up here.
This is not even real. No air in here. Nobody's going to be sleeping in here. This is a fake
dream house. All right. Here we go. This is perfect. Who the fuck is going to steal this?
It's twenty twenty, dude. You're going to you're not going to pick this up.
You can't sell this electronic equipment. No, no cool speakers. We're going to this is going to be
this. We're going to have so much such a wow mini fridge downstairs, a router,
a bunch of consoles and stuff. Oh, this is the real house is going to be awesome.
And none of this belongs in this room. TV remote microwave.
Should there be a microwave in this kid's room?
No, it's not even a person's room, though. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. A DVD player.
This is a perfect, perfect fake Ikea room where you lean over here and you go, oh,
and you touch this and it's hollow and it's like, boom, boom, boom. Oh, shit. Oh, this is not real.
OK, if you you come in here. All right, here we go. I got I got I got I got two minutes.
I got to figure out what I want to steal this house. I'm in. I'm in. I'm in. What's in this room?
OK, we got fucking nothing. DVD player. I got to get the fuck. I have to get out of the house now.
DVD player. No, I'm like this house sucks. Wrong one. Who uses a DVD player in 2020?
This house sucks. OK, what are the like just like fake like plastic Ikea furniture thing can we do
here? Decorations. Now, here's the thing. Should I make it like a game for them? Should there be
like a two like two hundred thousand dollar painting like hidden in all of the bullshit?
All right, hold on pictures and paintings. Put it somewhere like random. Like there's no reason why
you would care to look over here. OK, yeah, here's what I'm going to have with it. This is the plan.
I'm going to put like a two hundred thousand dollar painting behind the wicked shitty stove,
like down here. So all you need to do is just move the plastic Ikea furniture and it's like,
holy shit, there's a Mona Lisa back here. And you got to give them at least something. I mean,
I'll have like five of those downstairs. Bathroom. There's no reason for a bathroom up here.
Well, what would what would there be a bathroom up here for? It's not a real house.
OK, imagine coming into somebody's house and you only have like a few minutes.
You're running around like, OK, what am I going to steal? OK, that's just this.
Where's the bathroom? You would question everything. This is that. Yeah, somebody just
said this is a game show house. This is a house that's made. This is set and exactly. Yeah. But
why would there be a functioning toilet up here? There's no reason to have a functioning toilet.
This is going to be another bedroom or like a closet or something. We're not done here yet,
though. Use the toilet backstage. Shit, I spit everywhere. Put kitty litter in the corner.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea. If I can do it, I'll put like 10 litter boxes over here.
So you come and you go, oh, there's a lot of cats in here. A lot of cats in this house.
But where are they, though? Where are the cats? How come they're nowhere?
Where then? Why are there no cats? Paint the top of the windows.
I knew somebody was going to be like, this is all right. Let's go. You get the vision.
Get the vision. Good. What was it called? Sleepy Blue. You're making a crack then.
No, this is a fake house upstairs and then the real house is downstairs, which I guess could be
a front for a drug operation. Now that I think about it. Yes, you, I guess like,
what's going on here? Nothing. Yeah, nothing. Actually, you're right. What's going on downstairs?
That's what the fake room for it before the real room is for. This is going to be a bunch of boxes
and storage as I'm five steps ahead of you. That looks good. Always the same voice.
Don't you get it? Whenever I'm talking about somebody that's not me, they either sound like
this. They sound like this. Or they sound like this. There's only three other people that I've
referenced. It's always the same three people. That's the easiest way for me to differentiate
that it's not me talking. Because if I go, think about that, right? If I don't make some type of
differential voice to who I'm talking, I'm a different person speaking, then me saying this.
Yeah. Yeah. The paint looks good. Look at that paint. Yeah. Okay. Good job with that paint.
Hey, welcome to the drug den. I do drugs downstairs. Hey, officer. Yeah, come on in.
Yeah, go. Don't look downstairs though. There's drugs everywhere down there.
Oh, that's the storage. Just storage down there. You understand how that doesn't work now?
That's just me saying that. It has to be somebody else. It can't be me. All right,
that room is pretty good. Maybe another decoration. It's just me saying it. Is that part of the stream
or is that a cry for help? See, you get it now. No, it's not that. It's the voice. It's the other
voice doing it. I can push all of my insecurities through the other voice. I'm just sitting here
watching the stream with you guys. Gas mask. All right, let's go with furniture.
I need a chair in here. Yeah, this is like wooden. This is a fucking wood chair. It's a little small,
but it's fine. I need to have something else. Yeah, get a chair from like the 1400s.
Just wood. Just hard, painful wood. Why do they still make chairs out of wood? Am I crazy for
saying this? Everybody puts a pad on their chairs if they made it a wood. Why even make them out of
wood? Why not make them out of like silicone and like have the legs be wood? Why do we have to sit
on wood still? I don't understand. It's easy to make. It's cheap. Wood looks good. I guess.
This sucks to sit on. Okay, how about for support, you adult. I'm saying the wood,
you can keep this. Yeah, but sitting on wood sucks. You don't want to sit in this for more than like
10 minutes. Is there going to be a washing machine up here? And get cushions. Yeah, then why not just
have like a cushioned thing that you actually sit on? Oh, here we go. This is perfect. Just a fucking
plastic recycling bin. There's a million chairs like that. Yeah, I know there's options,
but at the end of the day, like sitting on wood hurts as a poop bucket. Where's the plaster?
You need a thicker butt. Fix the door. That can wait. I don't even know what you're talking about.
That's it for plaster, right? Yep. Now outlets. What's the point? I almost want to take this door
out because the door means you can go in there. No, that's more suspicious that way. Okay, so I'm
going to put what does this is the garage leading to the door that leads to the real house. Let's
figure out what we're going to do here. This is bedroom one. Let's go decorations or what about
equipment? No toilet paper. No, no reason. Accessories. This is stealable. I don't want
it in here. Just spoons. No one's going to steal utensils. Put a tent in here. No,
put a tent in the house. Hold on. Jar full of manna. Okay, this is fake fruit. Perfect. That's
perfect for our kitchen. Where's that going to be? Right here, right? Yeah. What happened to the
mirror maze? I had like a mental breakdown playing the mirror house yesterday and had a lot to do
with it. The Luigi's Mansion music just got wicked fucked up. It was messing with me. I had to stop.
I had to get out. Anything else I want in here? It's in this room particularly. These are going
to be in every room. Decorations maybe. Plants. No. Nah. Nah. Ikea? Firewood in here? No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's just firewood down here.
There's nothing down here. This is like firewood. There's nothing in here. I have to do a different
variety though. I don't want it to look like Minecraft. Put a gas stove on the front lawn
to scare off the thieves. No, a gas stove on the front lawn means I'll probably be on an episode
of Hoarders in a few weeks. That's what that means. All right, let's do the other variant.
There's got to be enough space that I can walk through here though. Okay, this plenty,
this plenty space. Well then upstairs has to be a like a shitty wood stove. There's a lot of firewood
put on new music. Okay, somebody recommend something that's not Luigi's Mansion? Not really.
Is this not a lot of wood? I guess maybe not. Okay, those of you that have used, I've never
used a wood burning stove or anything. How much, how long would you be able to heat your house
with this much wood? Not very long. Maybe a couple of hours. A few hours. Hour, a couple
hours. Damn, really? Holy shit. That doesn't seem like very long at all. Two days. Wait,
is that you kidding? Or is it what I, who said what? It's not supposed to be symmetrical.
If it was, it would look weird if it was symmetrical. This is stacked wood.
It would be two to three days. Okay, so I was just, am I taking a picture? Okay, no, I don't want the
camera. I want variant one. Close to your Instagram. All right, one more layer. Just like a little bit
kind of tethered down a little. Layered a little, you know what I'm saying? This is probably the
most thought I've put into the whole house. Okay, good. That looks good. That's like if you got
firewood down here. Did I put the wood stove down here? Would that make sense? Or does it have to be
on the same layer? All right, don't open that door. I slammed a water before I started playing.
So that water is on its way out. So I got to be right back. Come on, guys, if we can convince
him to play 100 gecks, just keep spamming 100 gecks or riot. Well, now I know what I'm not
going to play ever. Welcome back to the stream, everybody. It's me, Jabba that I vied. Slime, slime,
everyone riot, everyone riot. If you could do me a favor and stop rioting, that would be awesome.
I would be so good on radio. You all know it. Streaming, like streaming, if it doesn't work out,
I'm just going to go to the radio station. I'm just going to be like, can I have an interview?
Are you sure? Do you apply through our website portal? No. Okay, I guess we have a position open.
Come sit down. Okay, I will. So can you tell me about yourself a little? Of course I can.
I grew up in Massachusetts in a small town called Boston. Okay. What are you interested in? Well,
I'll tell you. I love talking. I love talking to people. I'm a people person. You need somebody
to read the news. I'm that guy. I also like video games. I grew up on them my entire life.
Okay. Can you would just just us in the room here together? I can't turn it off. Let me do my thing.
Okay. Change the channel. Make, please, please make a booker house. I'm going to have to
respectfully decline. And by the way, if you're going to take 95, I would avoid it. Just keep that.
You know how awesome that would be? Just reading like where like the traffic is. I would be so
good at that. You're going to have to find a way around through the rotary on Second Street. And
by the way, if you be careful, there is a crash in an accident on I-95. I would kill it. And I
would just throw shit in there that like somebody would hear. Make sure you take the rotary.
Wait, I'm fired. I got fired. The door rips open. You fucked up a word. You're fired. Hold on. Let
me do it again. Just take the rotary on Second Street. Come on, Gwen. Coming up next, we have
the news by Jake Stevenson. He's coming up here. And one of you guys would be like, what? Hold
the fuck on. What did he just? Who's that? All right. Stop walking in circles and play. I've
stopped this. Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat. Don't do it. Don't say toy boat. Toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat. Oh yeah. He still can do it. I could
fucking read the weather. If you gave me a script, I'll do it. What's happening? Okay. Let's go. I
needed the second room. This room is done. Here's kitchen, all wood, a wooden sink.
This is just like construction house. I don't know what happened over there, but I'll fix it later.
Fuck this. This should be made out of silicone. Everything should be made out of silicone.
Okay. Cabinet. What do we got for cabinets? We got the wood. Yeah. Jesus. This. Okay. I know
how like wooden cabinets look good, but these don't. This is a really tall.
Where are the long cabinets? Too tall for you. That's too tall for anybody. This is like,
it's like, that's 11 feet tall. You would have trouble reaching that. Let's do a tiered system.
Oh shit. All right. Nice. And then we have like a painting up there. Nice.
Too high, too low, too high, too low. Okay. I need the kitchen. Okay. Door cabinet,
single door cabinet. Where's the wooden corner cabinet? Wooden corner left,
wooden double door. Here we go. Why does this look crooked? Is the wall crooked? Oh no. Right. Shit.
I can't do that. Try it. What's the ride for? What are you talking about? I hate the way that
looks. What if I get rid of this? What is it? What's over there? I hate how that looks. I
don't like that little thing sticking out. It's pissing me off. Turn off slow mode. Why would
I turn off slow mode? There's like some 7,000 people here. Turn off slow mode. I hate this. I
know I've done this like three times already, but I don't like how this looks. I have the solution.
Don't worry. Turn on fast mode. That's just no restrictions. I have the solution. The solution
is here. There we go. And then this wall just needs to be built this way. Why? Is that good?
Yes. This legit looks like a lot of fun. Yeah, it is. We said this yesterday. We talked about
it yesterday. This is like one of my favorite games. It just exists in its own fun world.
I wish there was a little bit more freedom. I wish there was more freedom. If I could
delete stuff on the outside, if you could make the actual house, if I want to take down this
wall and remove these windows, if I want to get rid of a staircase or put a staircase in,
you're talking about now you're at a 10. That's how you get to a 10. Just play The Sims. It's
not the same. It's not the same. This is first person like home decoration. It's not like in a
cartoon universe. This is realistic graphics, realistic game. It's not cartoon sim world.
So Minecraft. Minecraft is not... No, what are you talking about? I would be careful here.
Fried lightly here, guys. You're talking shit about potentially my favorite game ever.
I would choose your words more carefully. How's that? That's better. Super blue? No,
not super blue. That's super frog. Sleepy blue. Punching. Unfair. Mr. Albliston, I didn't see it.
There, that's so much better. Now it doesn't look disgusting from this side. No, it doesn't
look disgusting. Why do I keep doing this? It doesn't work every time. Why do I keep doing
this? Why do I do that? It doesn't work every single time. But now this is just like a wall
here. This has to move. This has got to move down. That sink's got to be in the right spot,
though. I don't like the sink over there. Move sleepy blue in. Albliston is in there.
I don't know what that is. Are you writing that? This has to move. I need this to be right there.
Fake SpongeBob fan. Sorry, I can't recall... Guys, I cannot recall every piece of media I have ever
seen. This has got to come in, but I made it like this so this could fit. All right, moving... Okay,
I'm taking the advice that that guy said like an hour and a half ago. Move wall. No, move door.
Move the window. I can't move the windows. They're locked in place. You make me able to move
windows and move staircases and take out exterior walls? Game's a 10. Okay, I need this. Okay,
front door. No, not a front door. We need a... Here, internal white, just internal white door.
Perfect. There we go. Okay, excellent. I always have been an hour and a half and he's done nothing.
Welcome to the game. That's kind of the whole game. The whole game is just kind of do nothing
for four to ten hours and then sometimes look back and go, oh yeah, that paint looks nice.
That's better. All right, now I can move this forward a little and then this wall...
Home designing is hard. Oh, music. Right, right. Listen to your viewers. Better. This comes forward
like this. All right, this wall then comes in. What happens if I break this?
It's okay. I'll pick it up later. Somebody scratches all over these.
Why does it look like you ran over my cabinets with a car? Well, they fell. One of them fell
in the truck. It must have been a truck problem. I didn't do anything. I wonder how much shit
actually happens with instruction that you just never know. You know in the beginning of
Ace Ventura when Jim Carrey is literally just drop kicking that guy's package all over the whole
fucking entire apartment complex. How many times does that happen? How many times do they just
blow a wall out with a hammer for fun and like destroy somebody's cabinets and then go, oh shit,
we gotta patch that back up. But it happens quite frequently. All right, is that better?
Did I fix it finally? Because then this goes... Did I not do anything? No, no, I got it. I got
this one. And then I can still make it in here. Good. This has to move a little bit. Remove the
walls. No, I can't. Every single house I've ever made in this game has been just an open floor
plan. Open floor plan is just translated into I don't actually know what I should do. So just
remove all of it. Splatoon 2 OST for fuck's sake. Oh my God. Oh my goodness. Splatoon 2 OST.
Oh, actually, this is kind of cool. I like when they go...
If I had practiced in the bathtub, I would get it. Is there a song in this that's like...
I think there is, right? Where it goes... What does it do? It's this one. That's the one I'm
thinking of. I was gonna say this is one of the lyrics. Am I making progress? I feel like I'm
just Indiana Jones-ing this room. I'm just like squishing it. I'm slowly moving the walls in.
Is this doing anything? Is this gonna fix my problem? Oh, yeah, this is the song. I want this
played at my fucking funeral. Excuse me. There is no... I'm about to skip this one. Is this even
a good soundtrack? It doesn't have that song. That's a different track. It better be on here.
I'm skipping it. That's fine. Looks good. This looks like I just moved in. Throw my boxes.
All right. Put this shit back. I need to paint it. What color is the kitchen gonna be?
Copper coin? Light cream? Mustard yellow? Sunny D orange? Oh, that's Sunny D orange.
Sunny D. The orange juice enema. Why'd you say that? Oh, fuck. Usually I can blame this on
somebody. In a typical fashion, I can just blame someone in the chat for that. None of you said
that, though. I did. Hmm. Never been in this position before. That has never happened. Oh,
no. Sorry about that one. I guess. Put it down. What are you doing? Put this down.
These are in such stupid places. I hate it already. What are you saying? This music is bad.
Oh, at least somebody is gonna take the rock throwing away from my house for a change.
I didn't say that. Is this a hundred gecks? Sure. Maybe. Platoon music sounds good for
about three minutes. I don't know. Does it? Does this be flush? What do you guys think? Flush? Oh,
but no. How am I gonna wash my hands and look at the kids outside? No, I hate it. Change it.
There. Now I can see my children playing. I mean, what? I mean, what? Like, you sit in here,
you're like the dad or the mom or whatever, and you're gonna wash. The kids are playing outside,
and you can just watch them from doing the dishes or something. Kitchen island. Yeah.
That looks nice. All right. I'm gonna leave everything open. So whoever is trying to rob
this place knows, sees that there's literally nothing in this whole house. Right? If you come
in here, oh, I'm gonna steal. Let's get in there. No, nothing. Brute. It's fake. Okay. Cool. Now we
need, uh, oh yeah. You need to have appliances. Distillation. All right. I'll give you something
else. I want a different soundtrack. This is cool. I like Splatoon 2, but it lost me a little bit
when I didn't get the song that I wanted. I didn't get that song. Not Yoshi's Islands,
Outer Wilds. Now that's a good one. I can get behind that one. Outer Wilds OST.
Hey, remember when I gave Outer Wilds an 8.9 and you guys wanted to dip me in acid?
I remember that. Oh yeah. This music is so good. I'm sorry, but an 8.9 is an incredible score.
8.9. That's a, that's fantastic. That's a very, very good score. Anything below a 9.5 is
unacceptable. No, I think anything below an 8.5 would be unacceptable. Should I put this, this
toilet paper? Should I really just be like a prank? There'd be a shitload of toilet paper
just in every cabinet or in one of the cabinets. Okay. In one cabinet over here, it's going to be
full of toilet paper. He hated the game. No, it was a fucking great game. You know what? Fine. I'll
give it a nine. You want, you don't want to change. It's a 9.0. I was going to give it a 9.0.
Fine. It's a 9.0. No, it's not. It's an 8.9. Music's too low. The soundtrack sounds like an 8.9.
What does that mean? All right. Here we go. I want to do, I need kitchen shit.
Here we go. This wooden cabinet with an oven. It's not a real oven. I'm sure it's the same
wood. Can I open the oven too? Like we don't have any food either, dude. I can't put this in the oven.
Because now it's really loud. There. Toilet paper in the oven. I can't. I cannot put toilet paper in
the oven, unfortunately. I don't like this color either. It's too, it's way too bright.
Give me the lighter one. Copper coin. I think that makes, yeah, that looks, that'll look nice.
That's my app. Better. Way better. So did somebody ask why does this house look so cheap?
Um, stick around for like another hour or two and you, wrong paint. Skin. Flasher walls. No, sorry.
It's copper coin. How does that look bad? Sorry. Just getting a little sip. Meat walls. Damn. It's
really been almost two hours. How does this keep happening to me? All right. That is not this room
anymore. Get out. There we are. This is alert, alert, alert, alert. This shouldn't be here.
This is messed up. Okay. What's the ground going to be? We need some kind of tile in them.
Nobody has a carpeted kitchen. Floor. It's either tile or wood or floor. Something like this.
Something easy. A little gray. No, no gray. Although I like that. I like the way this looks.
Arcade carpet everywhere. Whatever it is, it's got to be cheap. I mean, is this the dead giveaway
that this is not a real kitchen? That there's arcade carpet? Oh, that's so ugly. It's too,
it's so ugly. I can't even have it here as the funny thing. I go, haha, it's the arcade rug. No,
it's so bad. I don't do. Am I, am I like a dick? Okay. I don't want to be like a dick,
but if you go and you're going to get carpet installed somewhere, what makes you point at
this one and go, that's the one. Love it. How, how do you, what, how did this is, it's just,
it just hurts. You know, okay. If they took out, if they took out the yellow, okay, that maybe,
but it's like, it's too, it's like I'm looking at a magic eye painting. Like I'm going to go like
this. I'm going to like cross my eyes and like Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer is going to be
there. You know, a lot of people can't do those and I couldn't do it for a really long time.
If you cannot do a magic eye, I'm going to give you the secret. If when you look at a magic eye,
you sit and you go, I can't make it work. I can't make it work.
I just, just cross my eyes while I look at it. And when I cross my eyes and look at it, eventually
the picture just goes, Oh, here it is. Okay. What's it going to be over here? This is the garage.
The garage is going to be a garage. It's not a secret. That's how it works. Wait, are you
supposed to cross your eyes? That's the point. Yeah. But I thought it was usually, but I'm not
all people can just cross their eyes straight together. You know, it's actually hard for people
to cross their eyes. Like they can't do it. So yeah, it's not a secret. I thought it was a secret
for the longest time when I was younger. Okay. I thought it was a secret when I was like 10.
And this topic has never been brought up before until today. I don't think I've heard. I haven't
thought about magic guys. There's 10 and like maybe like the two or three other times I've
referenced it before maybe, but I never talked about my secret. So my secret, that was knowledge.
That was 10 year old knowledge. I have not thought about that secret in 25 years. I'm still
crouching. Begging you start making sense when you talk. Sure. Time that person out for 10 minutes.
Is that clear? Did that make sense? Steal his spoons.
Tyrant, tyrant, evil, evil. I don't actually mean any of this shit. Don't you? There might be a lot
of new viewers here. I'm 95% of the things that say are not even true. We only have a 5%
truth policy on this channel. Perfect. Oh yeah. Wait, was this an actual toxic waste barrel?
How did I just get to that? Wait, it's an app. It's supposed to be yellow, right?
And then I don't go down there. That's where the radioactive stuff is. Make them red explosive
barrels. I can't. I want to make them yellow. I can't. Can I? Wait, I can make red explosive
barrels. Yeah. All right. So don't fuck around down here. Yeah. You turn this corner and this
is anybody. It doesn't matter who you are. If you've ever played a single video game in your
entire life, if you are in someone's house and you walk down these stairs and you see that,
this is a video game set up with poison barrels and an explosive barrel. I'm not going down here.
I'm going to come back up the stairs and I'm going to say, you go first. Not going to be me
first. Like, okay. There is like four guys over here and they're about to run at me with machine
guns and I'm supposed to shoot that barrel. Nope. I ain't going down. This is your house, man.
Perfect deterrent. All right. Good. Just build an FPS house. No, don't. This idea can't change.
I don't want to find like explosive barrels. Make it FPS house. No, it's perfect. It's so funny.
That was such a good idea. No, I can't make like a, I can't make the in the house. You're the shooter
FPS. You're in. I can't like, oh, you're going to go in here. It's like pub G explosive barrels of
weapons. God damn it. I gotta finish this. I'm finishing this one. I have to finish this. I have
to, I start, I can't just keep doing new houses. I can't. We started with mirror house, then it
turned into cars. People are in cars, living in the cars in the house. And then that turns into
a fake house. No, we're not turning this to FPS level. That's going to have to be the next one.
ADHD TV. No, I can't. We can't. I can't. I can't. I can't. Not right now. I have to finish my,
my thing. FPS level up top. I have to make my dream house. It's so perfect though. It's so
perfect. The perfect thing. All right. I'm going to finish this idea. And after the idea is over,
it can be changed. Let me do my kitchen floor. Let me do my kitchen floor. Let me, here we are.
If you just, you need to, when you do social distancing, don't stand near each other. Don't
be stupid and wear your fucking mask. There's no reason not to wear one. Hey, I think I can do a
pretty good Fauci. You do know that like when I, when I unlock a new voice, you're going to hear
it at least four or five times in a month. I'm sorry. That's the way it is here. If you don't,
if you can't handle that, I'm not sure what to tell you. I only get to unlock a new voice like
every two or three years. You got to let me have it for a little while. Oh no. I gotta hurry up.
Oh no. No, where is it? Does the screen go to black or does the screen go to white in that game?
I couldn't figure it out. Stream just reverts to the beginning. All right. No, no more distractions.
Stop. Don't distract me anymore. I'm done. Here we go. Floor tiles. I'm like the most easily
distractable person. How about this one? Floor panels. There, there we are. Okay. That looks so
cozy. You built one room in three hours. It says, excuse me. First of all, you added 33% more time.
You added a third more time. It's only been two hours. And no, I did one room and then a room
before that when we changed the new houses. Okay. Good. There's my floor. Done. Next. What's up next?
Next thing we got, there's the kitchen. We got the stove, the sink. Uh, a microwave. It's okay.
Did it just go over here? No, that's, you could unplug that and walk out with it. Things that can't
be walked. Fine. That's good. All right. This has to be a hallway. And then you turn the corner,
you peek and there it is. FPS house. I can't get over it. That's so stupid.
There we are. Here's the kitchen. You open up. There you are.
There's the bathroom, but it's not a bathroom. In fact, take this whole thing out. What's this
here for? For nothing. Did I put, what good expensive looking shit in the windows?
In the, on the windows right here in the front of the house, just put really expensive looking
clocks. What's with, why are you baiting burglars to come in? Um, because I'm so,
I guess I'm so confident that they're never going to find the real house.
I don't know. Like it's almost like I have like a camera set up up here, like in every room
and I kind of just watch and try to find the real room. But then if they find it,
I'm in a lot of trouble. It's a Frank video house.
Okay. This house is becoming a lot of different things.
Yeah. The first is going to come in here and they're going to get chased around this
house by a guy in a gorilla suit. No more monkey in around here.
We'll see when we come back next on prank masters. They're always so huddled down in
front of the little screen they have. Oh, they're coming in. Like why do you have one screen?
How come you don't have that way bigger? Why is it like,
why are you like eight people hovering over and looking at somebody else's monitor?
Why would we put it up on the fucking wall, dude? It's always this wicked cramped ass room.
Oh, they're in a room closet. Why wouldn't you have a huge setup for that?
Well, they're always in like a hotel room. I know that some of that is because they're in
the hotel room next door, but doesn't make any sense to me because if this 10 people
all like laughing their ass off and talking in the hotel room next door,
wouldn't you hear that if you were in the adjacent room?
Like, can you imagine like you hear like a ding dong at your door and you hear like,
who is it?
I'm the pizza delivery gorilla.
Uh, I just heard that over there. All right. I get, come on in.
You got, Hey, uh, got, you're in a cool gorilla. So does somebody, you know, is there,
are you, thanks for the pizza, dude. I didn't order a pizza.
Let's throw the pizza. Don't throw the fucking pizza at me, dude. Don't, it's like,
boom, slam the door. How does that always work? Why did I take this down? Oh, wait,
this makes actually, this kind of makes sense. And it makes sense for one reason
is that I want the entrance here. No, yeah, I do. This is in the garage.
That's a perfect entrance. I want it to be tiny though.
And I actually, no, I can't build on that. Shit. Remember, this would be a 10 out of 10 game.
If you could get rid of staircases and rebuild them somewhere, we're talking 10.
No, I can't, I can't do what I wanted to do. So it's okay.
Put it back. All right. We need to do a Sandy coin.
Prank shows are ridiculous though. I never like thought about being on a prank. Okay.
Hi. Here's the thing. How many times do you think you may have been on a prank show that was never
aired? I think about that. Like the joke didn't work on you. And they kind of just like leave.
Like how many times have I may have seen somebody in a gorilla suit,
like running around like screaming and she screams in my face or something. And I'm like,
Hey, what the fuck? It's not like, Oh, I didn't get them. Just delete that part.
The shows are fake idiot. All right. We're not talking about like who won on the bachelor.
We're talking about like a prank video. No, I don't think that they're real. I'm just saying
I have, I ever been on one. They're fake. You're on one right now.
Stealable, stealable, stealable, stealable, stealable, extravagant. No, that's not going up here.
No lights either. Who cares? They'll have to bring a flashlight. Okay. That looks good.
Somebody said no fridge. Japan refrigerator. No, that's it. That sounds expensive.
No, why is this a wooden fridge? Okay. Now it's a skin house. I agree with you. Now
it's a horror movie, human skin furniture in appliance house. This would be scary.
This would be terrifying without any context on this room. I'm leaving as soon as I get in here.
The fruit there. Don't touch that fruit. Don't touch that. This is either fake and real. This
is either fake with a trap on it. Real and poisoned. Don't touch this. Cool. All right.
Let's go. Let's continue. Wooden. The Pinocchio house. Okay. Let's go. I need doors and windows.
Roman blinds. Wait, hold on. Can I just put a gigantic curtain here? Please. Please. No,
I can't just put a big curtain. I guess I could just do a big door frame, right?
And then hang the curtain on the door frame. I do that. Can I put something in this doorway?
Just block it with barrels. No barrels. An outside hallway. No. Okay. All right. All right. All
right. I guess what's the point of this? What's the point of the door frame? It doesn't matter.
The doors are going to be open anyways. Slime raid. Yeah. Yeah. He's a good streamer.
You don't know his name. You don't know his name. I haven't told you yet. Where's the raid from?
What's the channel's name? Okay. I want carpet or wood. Wood on the ground. No carpet. Carpet.
Carpet. Carpet. Carpet. How about somebody mentioned kitty litter before? There it is.
Holding the kitty litter. This is an arcade carpet. Not quite. It's kind of. Let's do. Do
I need any more wall down this way? Yeah. With a door or just like an opening. That's the garage.
Right. Okay. Hold on. Get rid of this. Absolutely rancid house. School library.
We talked about wood earlier. This kind of carpet, if you lay down on it, would be like laying down
on wood. There's nothing there. This is the same thickness as a sticker pack. It's just there so
the cold concrete doesn't come through. What's going on up here? Cut that out. It pisses me off.
All right, guys. I fucking just get mad sometimes. This is annoying.
Dream house is coming along really well, I think. Good. Look. Look. Look. Psycho is going off the
deep end. Psycho. What? I'm what? You're a psycho. Flesh kitchen, two left doors, explosive nuclear.
What? Flesh kitchen, two left doors, explosive nuclear barrels in the basement. Looks like a
good house. Well, you don't know about those barrels yet until you decide to come fucking rob
me. So this is that concept. So what is this incoming concept? No, no, no. I'm not talking
about the theme. All right. Let's do this quick. I'll leave that for now. This is the living area.
Remember I said TV goes right here. I've removed the exact spot where the TV was supposed to go.
It's okay. The TV can be right here. Yeah, that's fine. Can I please hang one of those
CRT TVs? Can I hang this? Please tell me I can hang this. I know how to do this. I'm going to
put a shelf and then put it on the shelf. OK, good. Remember, this is supposed to be a fake IKEA house
and these are made of plastic. It's not going to fall. It's got lots of back weight. Another DVD
player. I need hold on. I need some furniture. It's stapled. They always have this really,
really basic shitty little sofa too. I'm convinced that those like IKEA showroom sofas,
they're not actually purchasable. I know they have a tag on it, but I feel like they don't
actually for sale. They are. I know, but I don't know. I feel like that it wouldn't even
be hates IKEA. I actually like IKEA. I like eating at IKEA. IKEA foods. All right. Oh,
that's awesome. You got to get that. The meatballs, man. The meatballs are awesome.
Meatballs, gravy and fries. They actually do. The salmon's there's pretty good.
They still do a salmon. He hates bits. Oh shit. Did I miss one? I'm doing like a toilet paper
like seance. OK, big bits. Let's see. Huge actually. Fucking hundred dollars. That's 10,000
bits. That's an insane amount of money, especially considering that people know now that I don't read
messages anymore. I cannot believe there are people that are still willing to throw that kind
of money at me. That's insane. I can't believe you would pay me that much money. This is my dream
house. No, no, no, no, no, no. But that was from slow. Sorry. Let me say that correctly. That was
from S10W update. Thank you for the hundred fucking bucks. I've been saving this. I'm grateful for
the years I spent watching content. I want you to keep that money. OK, if you have an opportunity
to put a hundred dollars into my bank account or a hundred dollars into your savings account,
pick the savings account every time. Oh shit, there's a second room. This is both of the bathrooms
down here. Right, right, right. I would much rather you come to me like four or five months from now
and be like, oh yeah, I saved a bunch of money and be like, wait, wait, wait, where's my cut?
You didn't give it to me. I want something else in here. But a hundred dollars is a lot of money.
And there's a lot of people that have given shit a shitload. That's why I appreciate the
fact that you're willing to do that. But I hope that you're taking care of yourself first.
But thank you S10W update. The hundred dollars is a lot of money. Hope I use it well. And they say
play Bioshock 2. I'll play Bioshock 1 first on the list. Oh my God, play that now. What is
going on here? What's this? OK, I got to figure out what I want to do with these rooms. I did
my toilet paper like, got you like, oh yeah, somebody said this is your dream house. It is,
but not yet. Need a wallpaper. I wish I could just do toilet paper on the walls.
I want to see what it looks like. Yeah, it is. No, no, it can't be that egregious. You know what
I mean? It's got to be, I have to at least put a little tongue in cheek here. We're going to go
with something just decent. It's kind of a living room wallpaper. This one here. Scary music. Turn
it off. I can't get over the prank house. This really isn't. This is not even a prank house. This
is a really shitty prank house. I'll come in here. Oh, this went on. What? What? What the heck? That's
weird. It's kind of an odd thing. Toilet paper. Ha ha ha. In the place of stuff. I'm on TV. I'm on TV.
Where is it? This is definitely, yeah, this is an I'm on TV house. It's so obvious. I got to change
this music. This is putting me to sleep. I have mellowed the fuck out so hard since that music's
been on. It's just, it's, it's, it's, it's just making me chilled out. I'm going to change the music.
Mario Kart. Nice. That'll do it. Mario Kart. Um, I typed DLC. OST. That's much better. That's that
room. That's that. We're going to make a, it's going to stay open. That's the concept I'm going
for. Very good. Louder. I've increased it by 100%. Let's go down here. Looks pretty good. Garage
door. Got to fix that little gap. I wish I could paint the ceiling. Do I need my couch? Louder. No,
I don't want to be louder. It's loud enough. Louder. 100% louder. Fine. I'm looking for a couch.
There it is. It's expensive, but that's the one I'm talking about. This is one of those weird sofas
that the back is too short and your feet don't touch the ground somehow because you're short.
No, it's because the cushions too high. There we go. That's leather though. Too expensive.
It's a nice coffin bed. Why would I want to lie in? I don't want to lie on this panini press.
This is going to squish me and grill me. I don't want this. This sucks so much that I feel like
it should be in this house. No, no, I'm just made myself so hungry. It's like a fresh s'more. That's
hasn't been squished yet and they're going to put the chocolate in it and squish it.
God damn it. I can't look at that anymore. I can't look at that. It looks like a delicious
ice cream cake. I might have to get rid of that. It's too delicious looking. Get it out of my house.
I'm going to go here. The barrels are down there. Let's go over here.
The wooden thing. I'm fucking wicked nervous now. What's going on?
Um, I think I'm going to put in the air conditioner downstairs. What's wrong?
I think I heard the clock up. Did I put more fruit? Faster, faster, faster, faster, faster.
Now something's really wrong. Whoa, weird house, man. What is this crazy looking thing?
Not a real clock. Not a real clock. Not a real clock. It's a child's clock. I'm going to die.
I'm dead. I'm already dead. I've already died because I booked up here. I'm dead. Faster. No,
slower. All right. I'm going to do whatever. What color is the actual this place going to be?
White? Not red. Green? I mean, what's wrong with the clock? The clock is backwards? Why? No, it's
not. Is it one? Well, one, two, it's backwards. It is backwards. That makes it even worse. I don't
like this. Why do I have to keep playing the music that makes me wicked anxious? I know it's the OST,
but you do have to have the full soundtrack with when there's 10 seconds left in the game.
That's one of his songs. I don't want to hear the sped up, scary, you're going to lose song right
after it. Is that the table? Get this fucking off. But Mario Kart N64 soundtrack. I'm liking
that one. That's better. It's even wrong in the picture too. All right. What was I doing?
Oh, it's good. It looks good. I was going to do. Okay. We have furniture. Lock. Did this stay open?
All right. Color for out here. Let's go with a no bright pink, right? Lavender is way too obvious.
Heavy green. No, too dark. Way too dark. Select your player.
Select your level. What's happening? Oh, I've just kind of channeled that. Sorry about that.
We're going with blood. No, not blood. Not dark lavender. I tried blood red. Let's see what it
looks like. It's got to be lights in here. Red. You know, you did that voice by sucking in air,
but I don't know if I can do that right now with my chest. I could, I would really be able to do
like that. I would be able to do it, but I can't do that right now. Voice lost. Gained. Dr. Fauci
lost red rum. Damn it. I think that's, I think that's a good, that's a really good trade.
That's fair. I'll take that a thousand times. All right. Can somebody select a level and pick
what mode we're going to play? This is also panic inducing. Like, why have you not picked? So why
have you taken it? It's taking you this long. Pick a level and pick the, please pick a character.
I've never heard this song for this long and it's freaking me out. I've only heard this song for
10 straight seconds. Never five minutes. This is an audio sensation I've never had. And it's,
I, I don't want it anymore. Skip it. I can't. There we are. Oh, my Mia.
Whoa, you spooked toad. That's what you heard every single time. And then the occasional, uh,
there's always Luigi too. Oh, Luigi would always get hit by something in the very beginning.
Nobody even had to run over one of those cubes. Luigi just got hurt every time.
You would hear his, I got hit sound from across the game. Do the toad, do toad falling off the
map. I, that's what I think it is. It's a Tasmanian devil where I have to go all out for it.
This is only one way you do that. This is going to be hard to do. If I nailed this.
Nope. I tried twice. Hard. Let's try it one more time. Oh, I won't do it again. I can't,
I can't do it. I cannot do it. Good effort. Yeah. Make a painting noise. Should this be,
wait, this room's supposed to be blood red. I can probably do it without yelling.
You can't unless you can't. It's not possible. You have to, when you say, when you say,
out loud, you have to be that person's actual voice. Nobody can do that.
No, that was not the worst noise. 2028 over yet. All right. It's not, it wasn't. No, no, no,
it wasn't. I can't hold on. I have so much trouble. I need to paint these walls blue.
That's why I don't listen to music. You guys know the secret, the real reason why I don't
listen to music because my ADHD brain and not listen to it, I have to focus on it. And when
I focus on it, I lose, I lose complete everything. All I can see right now in my mind, I can't see
anything or hear anything else besides the banjo. That's, that's the, I'm playing it visually on the
screen. Okay. We fixed it. Mr. Spot. Did I? Somebody said I was trying, didn't finish the
blue room. What? I don't like that. What should be over here? It's good. This looks good.
Put a bunch of trash in here. Turn this shit off. I was reading what somebody said. Okay. Let's go
to paint. Now this all can stay the same. I just need some junk in here. Is it just like a junk
category? I see. Definitely need one of these. Make it less loud. We go. Okay. Cool. I like it.
Just needs to, should it just go all the way around? People paint their garages white. Yeah,
just white. So funky. And it's a low volume funky. This is the Aqua teen house.
I'm trying to get away from the Aqua teen house. It's not the Aqua teen house.
It is, but maybe a little. You made the Aqua teen house through muscle reflexes. That's so funny to
me because that means I've done this potentially thousands of times. Am I such a huge Aqua teen
fan? I gotta, I gotta get it right one day. I did not make the Aqua teen house through muscle
memory. I haven't seen an episode of that show in probably five years. I have paint. Yeah. Good.
Let's put some of the just very, very, very normal stuff to have in your. Yeah. Let's put some,
some junk. Junk works. Get junk. Other. What have we got in the other category?
Should we put a safe with toilet paper in it? Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, absolutely not. I mean, this, this has to be, this has to have money in it.
Right. For this to work, like, oh, there's nothing in here, but there's like a dollar,
just $2 in here. Spoon. I can't put the spoon in there. Oh shit. This is an FPS house.
Like, okay, I come in here. Oh, look, there's like an item over here in the item spot.
Oh, it's like 10 ammo. Weird fucked up kitchen. Like guy, like up two monsters. Boom, boom. Like,
turn this way. Like somebody jumps through here. Weird clock and weird room.
And then into the garage down the stairs. I did, I did it already. This is what makes it that like
whatever the pub G house. There you go. Good. It's a pub G house. You missed a spot.
Oops. Add purple loot. I mean, I could probably put like images on the ground, like paintings on
the ground of just like Fortnite weapons, but then that becomes a full on FPS house. And we're not
there. We're not doing that. Like have this open and have to be like three or four purple items on
the ground. Good. All right. No more paint backyard gas back here. What happened over here? Oh, right.
I was going to project for a different day. I think this is good. I think this works. Welcome.
This paint's got to change though. All right. What can you see when you look in here?
Something to steal. It's flawed. It's flawed. It can't be in here. Let's make that better.
They spoke fluorescent. How do you spell for more? S fluorescent. You is a you first. It's
flora fluorescent. Okay. I was close. Oh man. Oh no. I thought this was a play bar.
Like the video was supposed to be up here. And there's like, this is the play bar.
I was like, what did I click on? You get one light. You redditor. I'm not, that's why I'm not
making a joke. I'm not, that's not a joke. I promise you that you can believe one thing today.
It's not me making a joke. It's like, it's trying to load an ad. It's an image of a TV on the wall.
It's not a bad idea. I don't use fluorescence. There's not even a light switch. I think we're
done with the upstairs. This is one space here, which I guess we could put like
expensive stuff in the walls. How about this? Very like a, it was like a cabinet.
It was way too nice. This really is making an FPS in something that's not a video game engine.
You know what I mean? Like this wasn't made in unreal. This was made in a video game that uses
unreal. Put guns. That is unreal. No, no, I think you're missing what I'm saying. It's not unreal.
You don't open like unreal engine and go in the engine and make a game. You make the game
in the game that already exists, but that game is using assets from unreal engine. Like, like,
like Gary's mod or something. You don't like going in code in the engine. He's rambling. What? What
are you talking about? Like I'm talking about like a game maker studio for or something not
unreal. You don't like make this in unreal engine. Actually you do code. All code is in engine.
He's not wrong. I feel like I'm questioning my whole life right now.
Stop bragging. I think it's time to start my house. What do you think? We'll do some,
we'll tidy up upstairs. Why is it so dirty over here? Why is it so dirty down here?
I had to change it. All right. This is going to be my real house. This is my real bathroom.
This is my real house here. Get to work. You come in here. Ball. What's in the way?
FPS boss fight. It's not a boss fight. Okay. We're fine. I'm the boss. Do I do what? Do I just stand
down here? I really am making an FPS fucking level. No, this is supposed to be like trick.
This is the prank house. This is trick the guy to come in here. The guy comes in here. You're
tricking him with all kinds of weird tricks. He finally makes it around here. He gets down to you.
This is a level. That's a level. You try to stop the main character from coming down to your like
secret stash of stuff that you have behind you. And you're the guy with like the gun. What happened?
Okay. I'm ready to damn it. My vision. Yo dude, Charles entertainment cheese is streaming.
I hope so. That'd be like funny. Okay. Furniture. I need a huge bed. How many rooms should my
house be? Is this this? This can be over here. This is going to turn the room before the room.
How much space do I get? This is a, this is a room here. This is a room here.
But this is a room here. Okay. Right here. I got to block this out and then I can look at it later
and figure it out. Bathroom here. There's going to be a door there, which leads into this room,
which then this is a hallway. Then this is a room. All right. Let's figure this out. Bathroom,
the door here, right here. That looks good. You got to go. Have a good stream. Well, thanks for
coming. Hope your day is filled pleasantries. All right. That's where doors can go. And then this is
a door is going to go. Where am I? Wait, what is that? What room is this?
Okay. That's bathroom. Okay. Right here. This is making me irrationally angry that it's not
right here. The door has to line up with this door, fill the basement with mirrors. I cannot
do mirrors again. I will puke. That looks fine. You go through here. There's a hallway here. This
leads to here. And then this is a room. Bathroom, room, hallway, room. Wait. Okay.
So this is a hallway here. I'm going to have to put a med pack right there. This is my room.
This is the bathroom. It's all leading to the bathroom. You're making an airsoft house now.
I don't know if that means, but I think it's funny. Door, door, door, internal door. Get out of the
way. Cool. All right. Kind of weird how it opens. This is rainbow road. Yep. What happened? What's
down? How does it look wrong? Okay. We heard one that went through once. Turn it down. Look,
this is the electric guitar part. Okay. Door. All right. Let's go. God, this is to go to the
bathroom. Honestly, I don't even need to have a door on the bathroom. I can make this a super
bathroom. Somebody said this is a filler house. Filler house. I love that term. God,
get out of here. This is the shower. Fuck. Did anyone know what this is called? What
is this noise called? I hear it everywhere. And I never, what do you search for? Like
keyboard sound. There's no way. What is it called? I don't know how this is somehow worse than the
mirror house to me. Yeah. This is worse than the mirror house. I don't like it down here.
This is supposed to be my dream house. It's unsettling. It is. It's really unsettling. I
don't like it. It's making me wicked uncomfortable. Or maybe it's the Baldi's basics thing in the
background. Why are we going so fast? No, I don't, I have to get rid of this. I'm just actually going
to hurt my head. We're going to keep this. That was, there was another three or four minutes on that.
Now I made an FPS house, but this is a really, this is not even a good FPS level. I forgot to
remove some of this stuff when I was making the game puzzle game. No, I'll make it. I'm no dream
house. That's fine. Take this down. Did he make another joke house? So halfway, half joke house.
Now this is real house. I want to actually make my stuff awesome down here. There's the door
member. It's supposed to be a secret. So when you come in here, this room here is just storage.
Like a closet. This is the house. Welcome. All right. Sort by, uh, price. Welcome. Okay. Let's do
floor search, search by price. Ooh, I like this little explosive. I don't know. We're going to
get into these brick walls. Walls are killing it for me. My perfect wall. I'm being serious.
My absolute, my go-to, the wall I actually like is gray, gray, beige. No, no, no. I once like,
what was that? Silver gray, silver Galatia. Look at that. It looks so nice. You're boring.
That's fine. But I actually truly enjoy, uh, shades of gray. The best part about gray is there,
there are so many shades. You get a blue, light blue. It's like, you can put gray,
like brown, gray, beige. Yeah. There's about 50. I'd say there's probably 50. I'm a huge fan of
all the 50. Big fan. I didn't, I didn't even complete it. I didn't even, you know,
I didn't even want to complete it because it was so easy. I didn't want to complete it. You guys did.
That's fine. I didn't, I'm not going to complete that one. All right. Looking good. I actually
believe that though. I truly do believe that I like gray. I like all the shades of gray. I like
blue gray. I like brown gray. I like them. There are two different grays. Prove it. Eat gray on
stream. I don't think I would want to eat anything gray on stream because the gray is like mold.
All right. I don't like the floors. Floors have to change. Floor panels and covering.
All right. So the most expensive thing is this carpet. I don't like that carpet.
What is it? How is wood more expensive? How is wood less expensive than carpet? Perfect. In a
perfect world, this would be tile. It is. It will be tile. I'm sorry everybody. Just let me get a
look at it first before everybody freaks out. This is not a perfect world. Come on here.
Expensive. I would definitely, this is what I would want, but I can't set how many, how big I want it.
This is a normie house. So it's a normal house. It's a regular house. What kind of house do you
want to live in? I mean, we made the joke about like having discovery zone in your backyard, but
is that, is that so weird to want just to live in a normal house? This is for later. Can I not put
this anywhere? Okay. What's the most expensive fireplace? Okay. Here we go. Galactic sauna heater.
Electric fireplace. Yeah. Look at this. And it's already gray. I don't even have to do anything.
I won't. No, I'd like the smoky gray. That looks so good. Dude. Oh my God. Give it to me today.
Where can I pick this up? Where can I pick this up? I want that. Look at how, look at that.
Oh, so angular and there's so much like the material. I love like that shiny stone. Don't
you just want to live inside of that? Beautiful. Okay. I need some shelving furniture. We need a
most expensive, awesome ass couch. This one, but I don't want to, I don't want to blue.
It's actually pretty good. That looks good. It's bigger than it looks in the picture. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven. When am I ever expecting seven people to come over?
Wait, can this be saved? Yeah, I can. Hold on for those cold nights. You know what I mean?
I need a place to sleep. Yeah, I know. I know this is an evil guy bed. This is an evil sorcerer bed,
but it's the most expensive thing. I won. Nice. This is my dream house. That means I have a fixture
built into the structure. That is a bathroom that I can go take a shit and play video games on. Like
I used to do when I was like a kid, used to what, what question marks when I was, when I was younger
up until probably, I was like 20. Whenever like laptops became small enough to use, I used to
bring my entire computer into the bathroom and set the whole thing up and just be on the computer
and play games and shit while I took a shit. And then I had to take all of it out. And after I was
satisfied and done going and I was, it was over the daunting task of now I have to redo my whole
computer setup for like maybe like an hour and 12 minutes worth of enjoyment. Not anymore because
now this is my dream home. This is permanent here. This is a dedicated computer in here.
I don't think there'll be two computers. Sorry that you don't know that. And there's a little
heater right there. Monitor. Am I writing Minotaur? Monitor. He told us this story. Yeah,
but I never made it in my dream house. Okay. Wait, I need this. I need a little stool.
Now you've lost. Really? Like a little corner table. Come on, man. What's this even doing in
here? That's not in my dream house. Okay. This is for like drinks and shit for the mouse and keyboard
right here. Toilet. Toilet plumbing system. Toilet. Okay. How long is this?
Skip next please. Yep. A little bit more to the left. Damn it. Damn it. I gotta move the,
I gotta move the toilet. No, I don't. This can be different. Doesn't have to be the same.
Just need a little thing. How about this? How big is this? The ultimate gamer throne. Get in there.
For the wall? No, it doesn't need to be that big. Just need a little thing. A little tiny little
thing. Got it. Perfect. Perfect reach too. You see? If you're sitting here, your arm is right there.
Here's the next part of this. How do you get in here reliably? I know. You just drag it.
It stores over here. And then when you're ready to go to the bathroom, you like,
ah, just slide it over. And keyboard. Look at that. And the keyboard will just sit on my lap.
Here's a couple of drinks. Maybe dinner. Food. Go. Okay, go. Okay, go. Yeah, look at this. And I
could just sit down. There's the mouse. Keyboard right on the lap. I could even get like a little
keyboard tray if I really wanted to. I need a shower, don't I? Oh, well, I need a shower.
You can still get in and out. Just my sodas. Drinks. Soda. Um, water? Like, what would it
even be under? Why the walls have changed? Well, I think the walls have to be white.
Like, teeth white. Colgate white. Yeah, I already like it better. Painting is
part of, is bad for back support? No, I don't like, this is public bathroom vibe. I don't like that.
Green tile in bathroom always means public bathroom.
You're just painting over the tiles. Yeah, it's a video game. It's okay.
That'd be pretty messed up. I agree. Oh, no. Now it's just a not rendered room.
No, this has to change too. Wall. Foot looks good. These? Try these. But I'll do what they did.
Why does it look like they made it a colored pencil? This is a Yoshi's Island wall? Hold on,
I gotta put these down. It's supposed to be two. One. Two. I'm gonna fix it. Don't worry.
Here Mario. I baked you a delicious cake. If you, uh, uh, peach from Mario 64 is Mickey Mouse.
I have some kind of Mario syndrome, right? It's like, I, I, I've read like a book and Mario music
is now like, here I go. I do it now. One, two, one. Wait, I'll say here we go either. Here we go.
Here we go. I have to go. I gotta get out of here. One. You'll, I promise you'll like this when it's
done. You don't walk into a construction before it's even close and say, this looks ugly. Like,
yeah, dude. Cause I'm not even fucking done. Bathroom is mad stinky. I can't, I hate that you
wrote that. Move you. That was the equivalent of hitting my thumb. But if this were real life,
I would have wished I hit my thumb because I just might've destroyed the house. Okay. So this is one,
two, one, two, one, one, two, one, two, one, two, one, one, two, one, one, two, one,
wrapped in wild. Well, pile look, look, look, look, oh, nice. Nice. Oh. One, two, one,
one, two, one, one, two, one, one, two, one, one, two. One, two, one,
...tura
...tur finding
songs that just fuck up my brain yeah without music like streamers suck huh
yeah all right now where am I gonna go now what over here hey guys hog champ I
missed one where did not miss one I'm aware it looks like a cathedral that
what do you think we are this is I'm on the throne here man this is a sacred
fucking room I know it looks like the binding of Isaac angel room but forget
about that it is an angel room for me that ground that ground looks like it's
got to go good there's no sink yet what do you wipe with I mean that's the easy
fix that's the simp that's the easiest fix all day
I typed in toilet paper
here comes the genius play here you know how long this is gonna last give it
run out of toilet paper and you go oh shit that sucks not anymore you only
need to refill this once a year but much longer than that one roll telephone
every month this is probably like a month worth of toilet paper right month
or two that's better maybe a month this is two weeks to wait for but are we
talking like the Charmin mega rolls are we talking like the Scotts sandpaper
rolls what are we talking about here I'm going by I'm going by by Charmin ultra
mega soft ultra rolls or ultra soft mega Charmin rolls is four rolls of
toilet paper so this is actually four eight twelve sixteen I don't like this
blood red shit's gotta go there's the sink I don't worry I'm working on it
it's gonna be right here I need to make this door only open inside I don't want
it to open both ways why can't it do that by the way I only want to go this
way I don't I double hinge door ah what a room okay let's go here make a race
car bed oh my dream house is not this is not big enough this is definitely dream
bathroom for sure it's more expensive shit in here this is way better way
better put a bunch of plants is it like jewelry well this I guess I've done I
could have a grand piano down here uh yeah can I play it in a Christmas tree
down here Italian Luffer bed what is all this hold on clown mask holy shit it
actually exists if it's in the remember we're talking about this yesterday the
why are these in here Wow it's for the streamer room content creator room all
right I don't need a bed I don't I don't want a piano either hold on let me
where's the big what's the biggest TV I want a huge TV ball-mounted TV like
extra-large I'm gonna do what they do at the bar now I can watch every game okay
spy headquarters this is a prank room no this is the prank room ah that's not
what I want that's not what I want but I'm gonna make a nice couch you're a
stock market guy I need a big expensive couch these are all huge this one right
here come on fit bet I can't break this I need a small one okay yeah yeah yeah
yeah there we go
there we go oh I don't but I don't like this one either no this is like a
Nickelodeon couch I don't want that that's the snick couch
eat something though it's a big bed what if I do this this is my dream home
remember I told you about this a long time ago where is it it's just a just
want a mattress mattress mattress mattress
dog bed no I actually kind of like the way this bed looks
this is perfect it's your own personal I lost some kind of weird bet there
somebody just screamed in discord and they were like told you four of them
were upside down congratulations on whoever you whatever that was I this is
I don't like the aesthetic in here gonna change the shit right now before I get
pissed off we're gonna do this is the bedroom hmm
faded lemon can't really go wrong with faded lemon and I don't think ass
thickness yes what he said he did a mispronunciation joke oh my god I will
make a well I can't breathe what did I do what word did I like make a
mispronunciation joke on my opening did I open oh the door oh fucking laugh out
loud wall joke you guys you guys are fucking hilarious you don't need that
wall where am I gonna hang all my TVs I'm gonna get a nice big landscape
painting of a city that always goes right here let him make his dream house
I'm damn trying to just make my dream house you have no style mega low did do
I need style for some reason you think I'm worried about my style I wear Star
Wars shirts and jeans from Target every day I don't I don't know I don't and I
don't I don't really pay attention what do I want in my bedroom carpet
definitely but it's got to be a nice long flush carpet only in the bedroom
ton of padding not so much padding where it feels like you're walking around on a
diaper I've been in those places before and I don't like it it even makes the
diaper sound when you walk on it don't like that you go you guys never walked
around on a really really absurdly padded carpet and it makes this like
weird swishy crunchy like I'm wearing a diaper walking around sound like it's
it's like I can't even describe it it's the you're stepping on heavy padded
carpet sound almost like they didn't take the like the plastic tape off of it
they left it on or something wrinkle yeah yeah crinkle crinkle
they're a pain in the ass get hardwood I'd like carpets only in certain places
I like carpets in bedrooms it's cozier that way for me okay cool sometimes I
think German just makes up weird scenarios and add some weird noise to it
to make us go what the fuck is this guy on about you know my friends have said
the same thing it's interesting it's interesting most of the people in my
life have asked that same question and the answer is you never know I'll be
telling the truth this time but this time fucking what nope could be lying
this time but telling you the complete truth this time that guy that way you'll
you'll never know anything it'll always be a fucking mystery that's what
somebody says when all of it is real to make sure that you go okay he must be
fucking around half the time I got you I got you let's get a good panning here
this upside down all right I thought I thought it was a bunch of like geese I
thought it was like geese the goose heads like look at it from here this is
like a goose body long goose neck like long necks I know it's a horse
paintings hey what the fuck this guy on about at least one guy gets it happy I
like this medium doesn't really match them that kind of does it looks all
right I need a bureau or a bra how do you wish I say draw a hospital bed
furniture cupboards desks armchairs you don't have a cupboard here we go
wardrobe that's what I'm looking for wardrobe you could flush I can do it or
I can't why I again that's pretty cool all right we need another painting right
here of Autumn Lake oh that's what I'm on that one hmm wait wait wait I need
here we go this looks like another TV too big Oh
birch yeah a little end table like right here it's all expensive artwork too
I need a see okay hold on water washer bathtub plumbing system shower plumbing
why I didn't do the bathes to sink right sink sink sink sink sink there's no
problem with a sink mountable sink stick it in above carpet okay bucket
underneath this let's go tighten it I already know what your problem is I fixed
it okay fuck it let's go you need a mirror do I really though are you just
trying to give me stress oh this one's nice you can just go like all right
a towel rack I need to place a babe right wait do I just bathe in the sink
and use the bucket and stuff wait that looks wrong this is a weird
there we go much better hey this little room is coming together as a dream room
door there is a hotel room the sink that's not in the bathroom and hold on
there's not that many TVs just put tiles under the sink well that person's
got a huge brain let's listen to them wait and wrong thing what are the ones
in the bathroom and these I don't even know what these are these this is gray
ceramic white close enough close enough these no it's too dark
these god damn it they're fucking problem solved okay what's that better
there tell the middle I can get it actually kind of like it I don't hate it
I don't hate it I hate this but that's unavoidable a door I'm gonna do a
interior white interior door one it's my fucking snack zone you need light down
here I'll put some down here sitting here using the bathroom and doing your
business and then reaching into the pickle jar I think might be one of the
most heinous things I've think of ever thought of this shouldn't be in the jar
like this any of these jars should not be touched this has to be before you
actually do your thing not after and never after only before remember that
just have the jars open eating and shitting at the same time Jeremy you're
gonna make me throw up by the way peanut butter is I'm replacing all this
peanut butter is my favorite food yeah get rid of the disgusting pickles get
rid of the disgusting pickles the nuts can stay peanut butter is my favorite
food I seriously love this shit him thinks I am a serial killer I will sit
on the couch and I will eat peanut butter out of the jar with a spoon is
that odd that's strange or no no no no no no no it's not right is it maybe a
little what kind most of pure sugar no no no no no no I'm not like the not like
GIF like this still like the whatever like like if you go to like a Whole
Foods or something you can get like the good stuff it's real there's no bullshit
the best part oh it's like the cream would you get like an organic peanut
butter listen to me all of you do this I want you to come back and tell me did
this I want you all to go get one of those organic peanut butters when you
get it don't shake it up and don't stir it up when you open that up for the first
time let it settle you're gonna get this layer of about a full inch or two of oil
holy shit all you have to do is you just take that a teaspoon of that oil don't
mix it up and you can either just do it straight up if you want to do it neat
that's fine or you can put it in a little put it in a little dipping
container and dip your toast in it make toast and dunk it into the little
peanut like the peanut butter oil you're welcome for your new favorite
snack and if you can get like the oil and some of the peanut butter and you
put it on a piece of bread or toast and you've had nice and toasty it's peanut
oil is incredible it is so delicious peanut butter oil not peanut oil yeah I
know I know I know but but my point still stands peanut butter oil is very
varied very good I'll just sit there and I will eat little spoonfuls of the
peanut butter oil and after every single bite I do like the lady on the yogurt
commercial like lean back with a spoon in your mouth with the eyes closed oh
every time okay we're good I need a shelving are you talking about I'm
talking about eating peanut butter with a spoon dog do I should I put a love on
my wall I so badly want to oh it's not gonna fit anywhere
miss it will I do know I need a little end table you doing nightstand cool I
just need a little nightstand elegant wooden coffee table nice it was made by
the same material as the toilet cover here we are the love room where you can
watch anime on six different TVs and play video games to eat peanut butter
well you go to the yeah well I don't know why I didn't have to be anime now
this would be a ton of expensive items on here let's go with equipment other I
don't know I thought this was a grenade okay let's go to decorations but
diamonds oh let's see what they have there are weapons yes you can't use them
but there they exist but vases is the most expensive vase you got it is nice
but it will auto asleep I got you writer no I don't like that it's gotta be dark
but not too dark auto sleeps in the bed with me so no we didn't need that not
under the sink I'm looking good all these TVs you need more expensive stuff
accessories bubble kid wait this is how is the most expensive toy is the fake
kids oven stuff ooh wait different color okay look at it and this clock works
what else do we need just more shit more stuff accessories accessorize whoa whoa
that's way cooler come on come on I gotta get right in the middle am I in the
way I was standing in the way nice this is such a swaggy apartment
don't ha ha me come on what what do you think I'm become serious facing that way
if not I like the other way right there nice all right end table
it's not that even whoo okay I like it let's go it's too big and things sucks
you're talking about the let's go thing I don't think I could really even scream
that loud anymore I really don't think so my voice would give out at the G and
go I wouldn't be able to scream it big table come on was it just a little end
table right here nice how's that how's that coloring the coloring good oh all
right good end table need a light we do we need expensive lights is what you
meant to say lamps ceiling lamps ooh this one's cool let me see this from far
away I don't have any measuring tools that good is that like right in the
middle I'm gonna be hilarious if Dermot is stream where face cam was message was
deleted and slow mode was turned on that would be a pretty weird stream yeah I
need us light switches elegant light switch whoo get this little place huh
wouldn't you like to call this home hey now we need let's see doors
installations lamps decorations Airbnb room oh what you meant to say was like
high quality designed cool bedroom I need a door I think it was fine look at
this you trying to tell me that this is not a place that you would feel
comfortable in you don't think that you would feel wait let me get rid of this
look at this shit look at that cool light there's no light in the bathroom
yeah there is right there but I'll put one in lamp ceiling lamps I know where
this is going light switch please pull the doorbell no it's a light switch this
is a little I don't like how this is very barren but in the middle of the
wall right there but then look at I have this one too that this is your eye
pieces you walk in and you go holy shit he's got money holy shit he's got money
holy shit he's got a lot of money right they don't see this part they don't see
that part they're not allowed in there it's my private room please rotate the
TVs please I will ET rooms dude all right how sick would this actually be
though that would be that would be you telling me this wouldn't be cool if you
were lying down in your bed on your back just looking down and you've got like
a huge entertainment display which by the way that's gonna make sure I'm not
playing a really really action-packed movie when somebody goes upstairs because
I'm gonna put in like stereo like a speaker and shit subwoofer and speaker
there it is this is way smaller than I thought it was gonna be speaker here we
go I'm gonna I'm gonna put off like a limp biscuit song and I'm gonna crack
my foundation this whole wall is gonna blow backwards I'm gonna take this whole
thing down that's good then I need a little place for consoles and in a
course not a DVD player like an entertainment center entertainment
center what would it be called furniture I need like the entertainment center
rooms too cluttered well it has to be because this is all the room I have
entertainment center dresser Andy is that just we have to have dresser Andy
on the stream right I gotta be of course we do yeah I've got to have way too many
dressers in here but this to be allowed in here I mean all right this dresser
Andy this is a hoarder room no all right I'm get rid of this this is the
cleanest hoarder room I think I may have ever seen this is not a hoarder room not
even close all right what was I doing yeah I'm looking for okay entertainment
systems getting there getting there getting there linen closet hold on
desk hanging cabinet mmm no no mm-hmm this is not what I'm looking for hanging
shelf bingo I like the white okay now here come all the other consoles we got
console Fez yeah I got one of these what's the other one console brushy yeah
I got a Fez and a brushy but I mean unfortunately the only one I played the
only game I played in here was Madden this is the one that had all the games
you have to go to the bathroom to play PC that's where you are wrong
unfortunately for you and I got wireless keyboard wireless mouse let's go this
would be uncomfortable oh got everything you need look I'll put like an I'll put
an exercise treadmill out here right here no I can't hey my clothes there's
my subwoofers sink there's the other station where I don't have to move
anything it just stays here oh I need AC I need air conditioning where am I gonna
put AC and heaters and stuff installations AC installation there we
go right here right over the bed right what's the most efficient place for this
to go right here all right install install AC put together gamers don't
shower why is this would be a gamer room there's more things you can do with a
computer and a bunch of TVs all about playing video games you don't have a
shower one of these is not in anybody hear me those weird yeah my computer
fucked up I'm back and that wasn't my internet that was something I was I'm
weird happened it's a man cave live I hope so should did right wait why does it
look like that it went into the toilet the computer while I'm sitting there
now we're good we're good and let's see yeah we have my skin house mm-hmm yep
watch out for that watch out for the enemies would lies more deceit and then
my dream house perfect it's still here yes it was a too many TVs yeah I'm gonna
turn off all the TVs let's let's read let's reset okay somebody said porn
room porn room yeah okay what are you gonna put porn on go to porn hub and
put a tab on every single one of these and then just blast the AC and why how
well are you gonna do this for yeah I put the AC down to 58 okay here we go
this looks like my porn room okay your porn room the PC was too close to the
fire it burned out well sorry about that I probably wasn't gonna be going for
very much longer but they'll don't like to abruptly end but we're not done yet
so I what am I gonna do out here more accessories ooh a standing hanging towel
sugar container wait I gotta have a bunch of a bunch of books that nobody
this I got a subscription for this magazine and they are so crisp and so
apt that they've never been touched I bought a subscription I just never
fucking read one single one of them needs to be moved a little bit though
shit that was under the bed no stop stop no why did I just say that like I was
acting no stop no stop yeah it's because I was gonna say like
porn DVDs it's porn magazines everywhere why would you this you just I
already have my fucking porn sanctuary that's not even what this is but if
that's what happens on this channel you guys call it something and that's what
it becomes and that's what it stays yeah all six just look you could you could
have Mario Kart on this one and then four porn five porn hub tabs they that's
what the consoles are for that room is done is the firewood all right what am I
this is make this look like shit yeah this looks like shit this is not the real
house what are these doing not open sell this house what is this a sh mount a
shower it's got ten community subs and retrospective thank you retro for the
ten community subs that's all all you non subbed humans that now have a sub now
you can spam the emotes and put these in here too if you're gonna come in here
and you what if you'd like it knocked into that and you'd explodes and shit
more booby traps it's so hard to not hold it down so hard to not hold down
left trigger right now I have to I can't I will burn it all I have to leave okay
I got it out of my system so now what what we do about this what's the outside
gonna look like invisible house right maybe just like a white or brick five
more subs from yes is online thanks to the five subs back-to-back sub drop
mirrors you'd be the most annoying neighbor in history glare coming off of
your house would be blinding I don't think you'd be able to beat if the Sun
was shining brightly like it is right there and you lived in this house that
what would that do he's doing the mirror house thing again oh yeah shit I can't
do that again I know like an invisible house is funny but I don't want to sit
here for an hour and 20 minutes doing this it would catch on fire and let's
do one guy in chat save this stream sure all right now let's do outdoor paint to
make it really just gray and boring maybe not maybe that maybe this is the
fake part of the house we're gonna do this kit is white how much is white how
boring does this look plaid Mayo house did you guys know I just recently learned
this do you know that if something is called Mayo it doesn't actually have to
be mayonnaise to truly call your product mayonnaise and it's actually really
mayonnaise it has to have a specific set of ingredients if you call something
Mayo it could be pretty close but it's not actually mayonnaise if you see like
oh like you check out this one light Mayo that's not mayonnaise it's
legally not mayonnaise it needs to be a certain amount of egg yep there I'm gonna
certain amount of oil I did not know that I was marketing tricks forever I
thought that Mayo was just mayonnaise cool random fact XD man oh come on that
is like a kind of interesting fact come on man that's a kind that's pretty
interesting I didn't know that as of like a few days ago that's interesting
that's an interesting thing because I said it yeah if like Bill Nye was on
camera right now talking about how mayonnaise and mayo are not the same
thing and he had like a bunch of test tubes and those glasses on you'd be
like oh cool but I say it and I'm a weirdo you don't you don't have a
science music there is no music this is birds let's change that so sucks it
like really does something look like mayonnaise it looks like a big
marshmallow I don't really want to get on the
scaffolding so I think it's gonna stay yellow mayonnaise isn't white it's it is
but it's slightly it's a little it's like a it's a kind of a cream color
isn't it it's a little bit on the yellow side isn't it not pure white who
needs it yeah I need a scaffolding don't think I do I'll do the other side
you ever just stand outside and listen to birds and then actually sit there
and go I'll just sit in the background this is so loud and there's so many of
them it's not until you really sit there and listen for 10 seconds and go holy
shit what is it pac-man dying sounds it's a sorting algorithm Galaga it is
Galaga all right what fucking weird bird is this I need to find out what the what
the Galaga bird is hold on pause everything turn them off turn off of
where's the other one coming from okay what is that world's weirdest bird dusky
grouse no what is it crested or okay this is apparently what the crested
oro pendola sounds like that's crazy I can't believe that that's unbelievable
show a bird show bird rested on one I gotta get a good photo it's kind of
bald it's got a bald head look that's what it looks like
I'm gonna put it on stream this is what's making that noise it's bald let's
say that one more time bird watching stream holy shit what an incredible idea
I would go out there with like telephoto lens and try to capture birds and stuff
gone on image I mean I love that idea you get bored really quick yeah but I
did build a bird house on stream and how long was that stream like three hours
four hours right was eight it was eight hours okay if I if I build a bird house
for eight hours I can watch birds before you do it was a full workday to do one
bird house yesterday not everything needs to be streamed today bird watching
is a go I think that has to be streamed I think that's something that's been
important to be streamed put a picture of that bird in the house I don't even
know that bird is but I don't even know what kind of bird that is now I like my
city painting thing the problem with bird watching at least I mean around
here it's there's not birds like that around here this chickadees and I mean
there are roadrunners out here though and those are awesome so it would turn
into a road running watching stream and Ravens there's like these big-ass crows
and Ravens out here like Hawks and Condors and there's a lot of cool birds
out here what am I talking about let's do it 30 hours in he's still on the
Aqua teen house not the Aqua teen house anymore come on here would be a good
stream I'm what I'll do it I'm looking forward to it I have to find the right
equipment to be able to have you guys able to watch some type of telephoto
lens that I can get real close in or like a binocular thing that can be fed
to a stream because if I go bird watching that means I have to do on
location like IRL backpack type shit right how would I connect I got a
kind of like a lens that sounds expensive that's alright if it's if it's
worth it to stream you know the story hold it a few times tell it again but I
liquidated my retirement account to do the German rumble that that's what I
mean like it was worth doing I'm gonna do it just watch bird videos instead
that's not that that's not the row that's gonna be the real thing well all
right cool connect camera would be a USB to a laptop and use the webcam to see
on a PC no I'm not gonna aim the webcam and the laptop at a bird I would need to
use I need to get like a camera hold holding it up and like pointing the
laptop webcam you would see nothing it would be so pixelated and horrible
GoPros maybe I feel like I would be the unlucky asshole that had a GoPro attached
to his head and a camera and I ended up getting chased by a rhino it would be
just a horrible footage of me just running away screaming that happened
this room's got to change this room's terrible I don't know rhinos and there's
no rhinos native to Las Vegas no there aren't I don't know maybe who knows a
bigfoot apparently still exists and no one's been able to see him that doesn't
mean he can't kill you they've been looking for him for a long time and he's
still he's kills people in the woods hmm let's go in cabinets cabinet
teleporter they're not symmetrical it cares table need like a little runner
like a runner table mm-hmm one of these one of these one of these I just thought
a tuna sandwich tuna salad and I wanted one now right now something about the
mayonnaise shit from earlier how big is this it's way too big
did I make a trail of porn magazines into the room who am I trying to catch
by the way with this no this room now has a completely different context that
I don't want any I thought I wanted to be just like the weird porn room in the
basement of your house it's hidden down here it was supposed to be my dream
house but it's actually just the hidden like pornographic theater get rid of all
these I'm getting rid of the context it's your shame room okay you could
never get you can ever find them all I'm gonna go through all this get rid of
all of them all right it's over no more of that no more porn magazines and then
a month later Jeremy what's this no no no I got rid of all of them can't be no
this room is now no this is my this is where I come play games and these this
is food over here this is food this is tuna salad peanut butter some kind of
yogurt and nuts this is my domain down here is where I go secret fucking like
porn addict part of your house this is you you guys have effectively this has
ruined my dream house speakers now if somebody's upstairs wow that's gonna be
really really odd isn't it what the hell do I hear so loud coming through this
house somewhere is this make it a Bible study room quick you'll be able to hear
this at the ground level at the street where is it it's a webcam there's a
FaceTime it's a connect it's no I don't want to put webcams all over the room
that's that makes this fucking weird why would I have webcams all over my
fucking room like this this is my security system no no no no no no no no
no no no imagine somebody no imagine somebody streaming from their toilet
like but they're on the computer that's that's so fucked up
Diablo 2 stream part 2 don't even okay we'll get um gum I'm over that what was
I looking for right right right sound dampening when I watch fucking
Infinity War at max volume roofing soundproof okay if if somebody was in
this room and they're watching Infinity War at max volume here we go I'm gonna
watch Infinity War at max volume I'll talk to you later don't you feel like
that they've turned it on and you would hear like you'd be like holy shit and
you get out of the house you'd come back down here like three months later hey
I haven't heard from him in a while is he see all right you open this up it's
just skeleton on the bed they'd killed him it killed this motherfucker where is
it streaming from bed okay so where is this where the hold on first of all this
is what I'm looking for it's starting to derail I'm this is derailing hard can't
put them close together cover the entire wall so I can have my in my max volume
Infinity Ward death chamber under by hundred we want more than that I can't
even fit anymore on the wall I made the room too cool I can't fit anymore it's
uneven I know I know I know I know uneven kill it stop I got it where is it
where is it what is this what is this a kissing toilet
stop distracting me I'm trying to get to a very specific place not you game best
dad's trophy I got trophies everywhere I got like Emmys guitar where is it where
is it where is it where is it where is it come on come on no why supposed to
be him you can't be placed I don't like that um what uh what was I doing get
rid of that too I don't want that in here okay hold on this is like what I
imagined hearing from upstairs hold on a second I gotta get that I gotta get the
right thing here okay hold on let's get the right thing
this needs to be dropped a little bit get that down far so good here we go okay
okay that's that looks this is what it's like to live above or below or next to
somebody that just has this shit way too fucking goddamn loud all right turn it
on I'll be up here fucking god damn it just trying to cook fucking dinner kids
it's time for dinner soon this is Kim's point of view but then you go downstairs
and he's just you would never be safe if there was a room like this you would
never be safe you wouldn't be safe it anywhere in this house there's gonna be
three levels it wouldn't matter for me you produced a hit single how does it
feel to be famous when put Thanos on oh hey let's let's see let's see what he's
watching let's get down there get a little bit closer
destiny arrives all the same and it's here I'm here and the thing about all
that map of my fingers I could make the whole world turn to shit what are you
watching we're still on right and looks right in the camera hey what are you
sounds spooky Freddy Krueger Freddy Freddy Freddy Krueger oh wow it looks
like I could see into your nightmares can I why don't you come down here and
I'll just fuck you up oh you can wake up soon can't you but not on my watch
slash motherfucker slash I think I could I could do it that's mr. Satan
it's the same person mr. Satan is Freddy Krueger the same voice well I think that
me and Goku are gonna find ourselves in trouble here look out for Majin Boo hey
motherfucker I'm gonna come over there I'm gonna slash your face in this
nightmare don't tell Goku that I'll slash your face in your dreams every
voice is the same there's only like eight voices put Steve Buscemi across
all six screens do a 5g tower no we're not reverting back to 5g tower that's a
wrestling character yes it is and when I come down to the ring you better believe
oh that I will slash that motherfucker in his dreams inside of the ring Goku and
then when Majin Boo scoop slams me down into the bathtub part of the blood
coming out of me I will be able to fly away and don't tell anybody Goku that I
will never see the light of day again your mom drunk you're gonna make me
throw up what time is it southern preacher well I'll tell you something
Goku our last time that I was out this sermon we told the Lord that he was
gonna come down to that ring and when he came down to that ring Goku we were
gonna cast out Satan and slash him in his nightmare and then drag him to hell
where he belongs goofy well I'll tell you something Mickey we have to be
careful if Donald is in a lot of trouble down in that ring I need to get down to
that well Mickey well Mickey Donald seems like he's in a little bit of
trouble down in that ring whoa we gotta get in there and I'm gonna tell you
nothing about the Democrats they're gonna take us on they're gonna come down
to the ring and I'm gonna make our stuff I'm gonna get them I'm gonna get
into a car I'm gonna drive over there and we're gonna stop them that's the best
part of it and then we're gonna slash me in their nightmares and they're gonna
bring him down to hell too and they belong come on down to the ring and face
me you won't Goku I know you won't and if you show your face here again you God
fearing bastard I will drag you out of here never show your face in my castle
again which is a church I know I just said castle you think I'd give a shit
Goku oh hey Jimmy I just want to let you know that Donald's in a lot of trouble
over there we have to go find Sora and then we're gonna drag him down no no no
no I'm moving on we're done hey Jimmy I just want to let you know that those
Democrats that's just twitch chat yeah oh hey Jimmy I just want to tell you
that Arthur Jimmy what I meant to say Arthur is good to hell hey Jim hey
Arthur I have a plan to cast Satan out of my halls that plan needs to be done
right Arthur you can't just rob an entire gold van without me and without
included me and you didn't even include Goku or Vegeta how could you expect us
to care about that Sora it's a is infinite stop please stop okay you this
is you can't do Bernie here let me tell you there is no you cannot that don't
even don't interrupt me no that's not Bernie personality core in portal I've
been walking in a circle venom Bernie what we're gonna do is we're gonna break
up the banks we don't need them it's no reason to have a bank Bernie I agree
completely with you I know I know I know Bernie venom we also should do is we
should make socialized health care too yes that's what I'm saying we you could
stay as long as you want I don't know why I would be afraid of you there's no
reason why I would be afraid of you there's no reason why I would be afraid
of you I think we agree on most things I agree on everything it seems when can
I eat somebody not doing that we're not doing that
you Walter what Jesse Jesse we've got to go to Larry David no we're done with
this I am done I am not gonna do this again ever again in my life and you know
what else oh every single one oh hey Jimmy I gotta rip this thing out I gotta
tear this thing out of this is not gonna stop okay so what do we do now rip to
anybody that was asleep I keep opening the same door this is that end of the
stream is that how this ends I think that's how this just ends today it's
been about six hours when I started 1015 1030 you still have two empty rooms are
yeah yeah yeah yeah well let's finish this finishes finishes it's been 45
minutes I think of just what we were just doing so that's probably accurate
you can't even walk in I can't even look at this room anymore I can't even look
at that room anymore I can't look at this room anymore it has a completely
different fucked up context for me now about to burn it I want something here
whoo very very cool nice all right before it saves wait it permanently saves
everything no doesn't no doesn't know doesn't know doesn't nope shift enter I
had to burn that room though I had to get it out of me that room that room
was satanic I had to get rid of it okay let's go so let's go over what's gonna
happen over the next few days okay so I am NOT gonna be live until Monday I'll
see you guys on Monday we're probably going to start either custom robo or
he's leaving us didn't save I don't think so when's the last time it did
save though that's a great question I don't think it really matters
considering we didn't do anything for about the last 32 straight minutes so
there's no there's no improvements or problems I have I still have the 3DO I
got to pull that out there's at least three or four games on the 3DO that we
have to play only custom robo matters yeah we're good look
everything looks in order yeah I remember that I remember this everything
seems to be in order barrels are still here everything's still here
aim did not save look at that guys I told you good his trophies are gone no
they are not do it again no I'm not gonna risk that what is this what is
that why is there a toilet on top of the toilet that's weird now sell the house
let's see what we can get for it if I can't get something crazy I bought the
house for 180 put it on auction I'm not gonna let me I'm gonna I'll keep it but
I feel if it's a lot of money we'll see I'm in the hole a hundred and if it's
not at least two hundred and eighty thousand I'm not doing it it'd be fine
five grand don't care move my bank accounts fucking 360 man I've got plenty
of money all right that's gonna be the end that this is like a perfect like
just about like what six hours or so I don't know what we did well hold on let
me see it's been like five or six hours I'm just deletes when I play this game
where's my videos tab how long has it been there's a videos tab let me check
and see how long the other the last one was just curious four hours five hours
four hours and 31 minutes there you go yeah exactly where I wanted to stop
sorry for the crash it's gonna screw up a lot of the credit stuff because when
you lose stream you cut everything else out so that's gonna be dead
unfortunately and I did fix it too I did remember I told you guys I was gonna
fix it the next time you saw me I did but the game everything my computer just
like fucked up so it's all gone I'm sorry about that I know that people like
to watch the credits rigged I know he had to pull the plug to hide the fact
that he didn't fix it now I'll see you guys on Monday we're gonna do either
the Desperados 3 or Custom Robo whatever I feel like playing raid raid raid
Chuck E. Cheese right hold on now Chuck E. Cheese is no isn't Chuck E. Cheese
bankrupt didn't they go out of business or aren't they going out of business
hold on I'm this is this is a real Chuck E. Cheese isn't it going out of
business it's not yeah they went didn't they file a chapter 11 they're not
screaming anymore oh well I'll see you guys Monday thanks for
watching as always house flipper you probably I think we're probably we're
probably probably done with house flipper for now I'll wait for some more DLC is
one of my favorite games it's always a blast something interesting always seems
to happen as it happens you get to build your own little house but I'll see you
Monday take care everybody I'm going to send you to I'm gonna send you to Kiwo
in a while since we have said hello to Kiwo it's been probably like six months
or something have a good rest of your night see you soon see you Monday and
bye we don't even need this screen unfortunately let's get the raid going I
will do the end screen though because the credits have messed up thank you so
many people subscribe to this channel it's it's ridiculous I don't even know
what to say besides thanks it's shocking to know that there's that many people
that want to give me money a month I just I seriously still can't believe it
but we'll see you soon take care guys have a wonderful rest of your night and goodbye