How you doing? Welcome back to a stream. I'll be doing good. I'll be doing well. Pretty cool.
We're back on Sunday for some more Omega Gaming Weekend. I told you I thought maybe I'd be here
on Monday or Sunday maybe. I don't know. You missed the last stream. It was a 14 hour stream.
Went all the way into Saturday. Now here we are on Sunday to do some more of what I would,
what I've coined, you know, trademarks and stuff like that trying to figure it out.
Omega Gaming Weekend. So yeah, that's really cool. He's keeping promises kept. He's keeping his
promises. I was actually in here at the pre-stream and had the suss changed to Monday and I was like,
no, no, I'm just kidding. I'm doing today. I mean, a lot of people that got, you know,
they made Omega Gaming Weekend t-shirts were a little annoyed when I made it on Monday.
But yeah, today we're going to be doing Breath of the Wild. I'm going in here with a completely
open mind. I am not going to say anything about a Brom software game that I may have played
recently, six months ago, whatever. I've never played Breath of the Wild. I don't know. All I
know about, this is all I know. All I know is it's an open world Zelda game where your weapons break.
That's it. I don't know anything else. So if you're going to be a backseat Barry today,
keep in mind, I have no idea what you're even referring to. If I need help, I'll ask for it,
or I might just look over a chat and just see the answer. Backseat Barrys, yeah. Malled incoming.
Can you even mauled? Can you mauled in a Zelda game? Is that even possible? I don't, okay. Let's
also talk about this real quick. The last Zelda game that I opened was Chlorine Eyes Princess.
That's the last one I played. Twilight Princess. Sorry, that's what it was. Twilight Princess.
Sorry, I got it wrong. Yeah, Twilight Princess is the last one that I played,
and I stopped after the first three hours. I hate the way that game looks. That whole game looks
like you opened your eyes in a pool and then looked at light and shit. It's Chlorine Eyes.
That whole game is Chlorine Eyes. I cannot play it. All the bloom. There's so much weird bloom,
chlorine bloom, but that's a lot. And I didn't play anything else after that.
And I've never played Wind Waker. The only thing I know about Wind Waker is
and there's a boat on the screen. I don't know anything else. Play that too. You would like it,
but I don't really play Zelda. I'm telling you, I just don't really play Zelda games.
Let's see if my opinion will change. Let's find out. I'm ready to go right now.
Did I tweet? It's so good. I know it's so good. Okay, what's better? One's in the chat if Breath
of the Wild is better. Two in the chat if Wind Waker is better. What's better? What should I be
playing right now? If you had a choice right now, if the genie showed up and said, I will change it
to whatever. I will make him play Wind Waker right now. What a stupid wish. What a bad wish.
The genie is here. I will do whatever you ask. You have free wishes. Hey, this 37 year old man
child on the internet. Can you make him play Wind Waker, please? Yeah, Wind Waker. That's the one.
Make him do it. No, excuse me. I'm, I'm, I'm a man. I'm just, I'm a man. Sorry, I'm a man.
No, I'm not. No, I'm not. I'm a man. Okay, I just looked down and I'm hoping that I could. Okay,
so I don't, I don't have a Star Wars shirt on. I picked, I almost did. I looked down. I thought
I had a Star Wars shirt on. Not today. We're just standard default adult gray. Sorry, nothing on it.
Villain hair? Yeah, maybe a little. I, I, we gotta test something here because the way that you
capture, you know, I'm living with, I'm using technology from like 2013 still. And I know,
dude, just get like a professional capture card. I, it's never going to happen because that
requires me to have to go get like actually get one, but we need to do this. You ready?
And I was like, just get it on Amazon. But every time I do an Amazon order for anything,
I always, I think of like, okay, what do I want? And then two or three important things,
just never make it to the list ever. Uh, okay. So you got to tell me if this is matching up
both webcam, audio, and on the screen. You ready? So tell me there's a delay. Go options,
ability controls. One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three.
We good? So that means I got it right. All right. I got it right. You guys ready? Are you pumped?
This is a Sunday of Omega Gaming Weekend. All right. So this is the, I, I, yeah, I opened it
and I, I didn't watch the opening cuts thing because I don't care. So let's go. It was onto
the background. I was like, I had, I was going like this. Nice frames. What do you mean nice frames?
Is this game 30 FPS? Do I have something wrong? There's a bingo card going. I don't even want
to see it. It's 30 FPS. Wait, what are you saying? This game is 30 FPS? Hey, Bloodborne's one of my
favorite games ever made. And that's 30 FPS. So quiet. I need two headphones with this shit.
There's no LPs. It will help guide you after your long slumber. That is a Sheikah Slate. Take it.
It will help you with the classic sound effects in it too. Oh, he's got it. Is that a Wii U?
Was this a Wii U game? What does it come out for? A mysterious tablet with a glowing center. You've
never seen this device before, and yet there's something familiar about it. Are there annoying
puzzles in this game? No, this is, this was on, this wasn't Wii U. This was a Switch release, right?
These all, all treasures? Wait, the chests? Well-worn trousers. These old trousers are
red bear in spots, but they're surprisingly comfortable. The legs are a bit too short though.
Okay. This gear? Okay. Nice. So what is that like Hearthstone card pack that I have for my,
what is that? Is that like the, the slate? All right. I got pants. I was even never played this
before. I don't play Zelda. I, I actually, this is the first Zelda game I played in probably
15 years. Ooh, shirt. You can pick, wait, you can pick stuff up. Particle effects. Pretty good.
It's got physics. Pretty good. Do naked no armor run. Is this kind of like, um, all right, should
we make a, make a running counter of, try to do this without mentioning any From Software game?
How? I don't think I can do that.
That will show you the way. Don't ask chat for advice. LOL. The game is self-explanatory.
Okay. I'm not, I'm not looking over here. So that's how you, it's a key. I didn't make the title,
one of the mods did. It's pretty good though. I can't, I don't think I can delete it. No intro?
Um, well, I already saw it. It was, uh, did the thing that video games challenge.
You are the light, our light, that must shine upon Hyrule once again. Now go.
Uh, it did the thing that video games like to do where, and I hate this. I want a menu before
anything happens. Anything. I don't want an opening cut scene. I don't want a get into the game and
here's the tutorial, but you can't access the menu. I give me the menu immediately. Immediately.
Once I do my settings, it pops up, should call it, come up and be like, hey, do you give a shit
about doing your settings? Just hit B if you don't care. And then whatever, you can do that whole
thing out. But I want to change the gamma. I want to change the, uh, field of view. I want to change
the audio levels. I don't want to just see the opening cut scene. God, if I made a game, God,
it would be the best game ever made. It would sell a hundred fucking billion copies. It would be so
good. That would, yeah, that would be each person would, would, would own 10 copies of my game.
It's just so goddamn good. Jump is X. That's kind of weird. All right. B is sprint. I don't like
that. I want it to be, I want B to be jump. Okay. Hold on a second. This is a switch controller. I
forgot. I'll fix it in a minute because this is a grip meter. Wait, wait, wait, hold on, hold on.
Wow. Okay. No, I'm not going to say it. I won't. Okay. If I make 10 Elden Ring references this
stream, then I have to eat a bug on camera. I'm not doing that. Do you guys remember the old fear
factor fucking whatever they were videos? What was going on? I can't even stand it eating fucking
like live insects. Like what the fuck? What are we doing? It was horrible. I couldn't take it.
Okay. Wooden branches such as these are pretty common. All right. Wait, I have a branch for a
weapon. Okay. Attack with your weapon. All right. That's kind of cool. Can I use the branch for the
whole game? Yeah, this is all fucked up. This is all fucked up. Hold on a second. Change jump button
on. Wait, what? Oh, there we go. So now where, what is sprint? Sprint is X.
I think that's all right. Wait, I broke it already? I didn't even touch anything. Why is it already
broken? Mushrooms. Okay. You can eat these. You smashed it. What? Did I already ruin something?
You're covering the map. Oh, I'll go like this then. Better. That's throw. Who needs a weapon? Fuck it.
How do you get another weapon? I don't actually need that, right? It's a...
Where's, where's that? Oh, okay. Oh, all right. And you can stamp too. Okay, cool. So I gotta go this
way. Cool. All right. Follow the Sheikah Slate. Baked apple. Beg your pardon. I do believe that is
my baked apple. You can't just go around taking whatever you please. Oh, forgive me. I could not
resist pulling your leg. Please help yourself. An apple a day keeps the doctor away, as they say,
don't they like? It's a succulent treat. Where are you? Me? I'm Ganondorf. You see, I'm gonna have a
fucking big Santa Claus beard on for the whole game and then I'm gonna take it off and at the end
you're gonna be fighting me as Ganon. I win. I'm just an old fool who's lived here alone for quite
some time. I'm not Ganondorf. Don't worry. What brings a bright-eyed young man here?
Answering a question with a question. That is fair enough. As I cannot imagine our reading to be a
simple coincidence, I shall tell you this is the Great Plateau. According to legend, this is the
birthplace of the entire Kingdom of Hyrule. Why do I look like this? Why did I read that? Of the
five million comments that were just coming through. Okay, cool. This is the birthplace of
Hyrule. That's, no, it's gonna say Ganon's dad. He's his fucking Gondondorf. That temple there,
long ago, was the site of many sacred ceremonies. Ever since the decline of the kingdom a hundred
years ago, it has set abandoned in a state of decay. Yet another forgotten entity, a mere ghost
of its former self. Interesting. That's right. That'll be, that'll be five hundred dollars,
because that was a cool magic trick and I didn't even ask you, I didn't even ask you for money.
That'll be a thousand dollars, please, for that kind of personal show. Oh, cool. Well,
then just help yourself to that torch there and how may I ask you planning to use it?
Um, it's a secret. To set things on fire, it's rather unnerving. Please be cautious with that
around any dry grass. You know, there are plenty of monsters in this area. That torch would make a
good weapon if need be. Don't just swing it around without purpose. You must face your opponents and
lock your sights on them. Yeah, right, obviously. Okay, I'm just testing it. Do I have to light it?
How do I light the torch? Okay, got it. Now what? Let's go. I'm holding this as if I don't know
what to do with this, right? This is like, this is like I don't know what to do with this item.
Wait, is this an axe? Woodcutter's axe. Oh, shit, cool. No, I don't want to put that on.
Change weapon. Press and hold and then switch. This is a camera? How do I zoom out? Did I just
take a picture? Okay. Um, I got to go that way. How do I switch? It said hold what? How do I
switch weapons? I said hold this and then press. Oh, okay, there it is. Yeah. All right, I'm ready.
Let's move. Acorn. So you just wait. You just eat nuts and seeds and shit. 20 rupees under there.
Okay, cool. Let's move. I got him. Oh, is there a dodge roll? What the fuck? Is there a dodge roll?
Okay, got him. Is it jump? Bokoblin fang. Cook it alongside a critter to make it an elixir.
Wait, I cook their teeth? Okay, cool. Wasting durability on weak enemies. What do you mean
wasting durability? I don't know what that- what do you mean? How do I go to the- I mean wasting
durability. How can I see how much durability this has? Should I use the stick or something for now?
Wait, search. Ancient spring. Okay, cool. I get some more sticks? How do you block? Can I punch?
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Oh, he dropped a turkey leg. How long does it take to
break stuff? Should I actually not be using this? Look at this. This thing's sick. I'm gonna hold
onto the turkey leg. It depends. It doesn't take long. Is there a durability menu? Can I see which
one is low and high? Don't even- who cares? Don't even worry about it. All right, I'm just gonna
keep the axe on. How come the title says horsies, by the way? Is there a horse? Can you climb this?
I found a bird up here. Oh, I'm just stealing the eggs. He found his way. I mean, if this is- this
is just- hey, all right. So, I'm gonna push that over here and kill these guys. What happens when
you die? What was the last- what? What was the last save? Why did I just explode? They- do I still
have everything? No, I'm good. I'm good. Okay, that was fine. So, wait, this is my- do you have to
pick your body up? Hey, come get me. How do I- can I get their attention? I got hit by that, too.
How did I get hit by that? Oh, a cooked turkey! Pick up souls? Where are they? I don't see them
anywhere. Are they actually on the ground? There's an X on the screen. Dude, I actually don't like it
like that. The sprint really needs to be- but no, it sucks that way. I don't like it like that.
I'll keep it the other way. I'll have to get used to it. Why can't I just map it? Okay, that's really
funny to me that there's a change the jump button rebind, but it just makes it a different one that
you can't determine what you want to do. You want to remap jump? Well, you can only make it this
other one button. Okay, let's go. Get a better PC. Ooh, okay, that's cool. What's this? I got a bow?
Okay, right trigger is bow. How do I fire? Is he throwing fucking rocks? All right,
there's tons of shit here. Oh, I didn't have any arrows. Arrows, horn. Very cool. All right.
Should I eat an apple or eat something? Tasty. No arrow, Andy. Good one, thanks. I appreciate it.
I was hoping at least one of you would care. Wait, hidden cave? No, I'm supposed to go here.
Okay, so cool. So this is the first little area. This is my first dungeon? First dungeon? Link,
it's a rectangle the size of the device. Just put it in. You can rebind in the actual menu.
Really? You can? That pig default noise. Oh shit. That's pretty, uh, that's pretty cool.
Great Plateau Tower. Distilling local information. Here it comes. Oh, it's nevermind. I'm not gonna
say it. I'm gonna have you guys keep track of the times I say it, but it is that thing
from that other game that I played. Why didn't anybody wake me up? Now then, you must hurry,
Link, before it's too late. He doesn't care? Why are you even saying that? Mirrored cam?
No, it's not a mirrored cam. All right, so now I opened up that, which that's, okay, that's the
very end of the game, right? I have to go there. I have to dip the axe into the mountain to get the
encrusted fucking, like, Dairy Queen cherry dip on the axe, right? And then I gotta go over here
on the left and I have to mold the handle out of clay. The hardest clay that was put in the kiln
up here in the mountain of the ovens and stuff. And then, yeah, I'll be there eventually. I'll be
there eventually. That's how it worked in the other ones, right? Like, you have to go get this part
from the sword and go get this from over here and get this sword. I haven't played Zelda in fucking
15 years. I have no idea how it works. Don't you, like, make the master sword in all these games?
Isn't that the whole point? I thought that's what the entire point of all these games was.
It's like, oh, you have to get the master sword. We got that out of the way. That's right. Okay,
how do I get down from here? Can I go faster than this? Can you, how do you climb faster?
Okay, this tower and others just like it have erupted across the land one after another.
It's almost as though a long dormant power has awoken quite suddenly. You do not mind me asking,
did anything odd occur while you were atop that tower? I'm revealing no information. I saw the
whole thing. You don't have to hide it from me. Well, why ask the question then? Although I could
not hear anything, I did see you react as if you heard something coming from the direction of the
castle. Okay. Did you recognize this voice? Let's see if you can go two for two. Seems to have some
work to do as far as earning your trust goes. I suppose that is understandable. I assume you
caught sight of that atrocity enshrouding the castle. That is calamity Ganon. 100 years ago,
that vile entity brought the kingdom of Hyrule to ruin. It appeared suddenly and destroyed
everything in its path. So many innocent lives were lost in its wake. For a century, the very
symbol of our kingdom, Hyrule Castle, has managed to contain that evil, but just barely. There it
festers, building its strength for the moment. It will unleash its blight upon the land once again.
It would appear that moment is fast approaching. Do you intend to make your way to the castle?
I do. Had a feeling you would say that. Here on this isolated plateau, we are surrounded on all
sides by steep cliffs with no way down. If you were to try to jump off, well, no death could be
more certain or more foolish. Of course, if you had a paraglider like mine, that would be another
story. Give me it. Certainly, why not? But there is no such thing as a free item in this world,
you know. Let's see now. How about I trade it for a bit of treasure that slumbers nearby?
So you get quests and stuff? Okay, cool. Yeah, let's track this one. Let me show you something.
I didn't know I think that. I was seeing... Okay, well, oops. I'm following you. You said,
follow me. I'm following you. You see that structure, the one shining with a strange light?
Yeah, it began glowing at the exact moment these towers rose up from the ground. It must be a
dungeon. Okay, I would think such a place might house some sort of treasure. All right, let's go.
Fair exchange for the paraglider. Oh, you can swim. Okay, cool. Does everything break or anything?
I just caught a fish in my mouth. What? I thought that was... Wait, hold on.
Oh, my God. I'm all right. I'm okay. I'll be all right. I just drowned in a three-foot deep
pool. I'm sorry. I thought that was just like, okay... I didn't know that was breath. I get it
now. I get it. I get it. I get it. I thought that was my stamina and then when it was empty,
I was going to start, I don't know, getting hurt or... I don't know. I didn't know. How was
I supposed to know? I'm going that way. 1240... Is that real time? This is pretty. I can't move
that rock. Treasure down here. Raid song? I mean, raid song. How do I open this? Oh, there's a raid.
Hey, the grapefruit. Thanks for the raid. Is there... That was a raid? That just happened?
I'm not going to fucking drown in here. I'm dead again. I'm dead. I'm actually going to die in this.
Oh, my God. Thank goodness. You can't swim to treasure. It's its own puzzle. Oh, okay. So,
let's figure that out. Do I have to drain the water? Power fire? Wait, I think I know what to do.
Can I shove this in and like, displace some water? I don't know. There's no lever to pull,
whatever. I can probably do it later. Okay, so here we go. Let's do it. Play the game?
How am I not playing the game? Access granted. This seems kind of fun. Maybe I will enjoy this.
Solving puzzles is a big part of the game. Don't let chat ruin it for you unless you're stuck.
Okay. To you, who sets foot in this shrine, I am Oman Ao. In the name of... Why did I want
to press A? Is this temperature? What? There's a degrees temperature? All right, let's do it.
It's engine oil temp. No help. No help. Play Disney Infinity 3.0. I tried to two days ago,
and it didn't work. I couldn't capture it and I could barely play it. They just, like I said,
they just dragged the console port folder over to Unity or something to make it just run. I don't
even know. I have no idea. It's one of those ports. Manipulate metallic objects using magnetism.
Grab onto metallic objects using the magnetic energy that pours forth from the magnesis ruin.
Okay, so I can control magnetic powers? That's kind of cool. Push. Oh, cool. So you've done those
special powers? All right, I got it. Is the treasure chest up there? Cool. Okay, I know how
to get that. Oh, I can't just pick it up? Oh, push. Okay. Can I make like a bridge? I guess not.
Maybe I can make a bridge. What happened? What the fuck was that? What was that? I snapped my neck.
Oh, I started at the very beginning. What? You slammed a metal slab directly into your face.
There's like a hop, isn't there? There's always a hop in the Zelda games. There's like a hop, hop,
hop. How do I do it? How do I do the hop? Ancient screw. No, it's not the jump. It's like a
they usually there's a bloodborne dash. You guys know what I'm talking about, right?
Doesn't he do like a backflip? There's like a flip, flip, flip. Is that just not in this game?
Hold, target, and jump. Yeah, but it's not doing it. You learn that later. Okay,
I wonder how close I am to actually getting that because I want it. I can probably jump up here.
I can't tilt this. Oh shit. Okay, cool. Oh, it's made out of metal. That's right. Traveller's bow.
All right, change bow. I'll keep this one on. All right, that's fun. What else? You seriously
suck at this game. Dude, I don't, I've just started playing it. You've proven to possess
the resolve of a true hero. I am Omen Ao, the creator of this trial. I am a humble monk,
blessed with the sight of goddess Hylia and dedicated to helping those who seek defeated
Ganon. With your arrival, my duty is now fulfilled. In the name of goddess Hylia, allow me to bestow
this gift upon you, the varnish for the master sword. Can't use it yet though. Spirit orb,
a symbol of courage given to those who have overcome the challenges of a shrine. So what is
it? Is it like a currency thing? And I mean that actually, not like the joke from like five years
ago. Cool. All right. So you beat, beat shrines, get currency, get money, get experience. It's a
soul coin. Ooh. I'll be really honest. To be able to come from that direction and land here,
you had to have jumped from like all the way up there. You know, you had to have left 20 minutes
ago and started gliding down here. How would you know that I was going to be done by whatever?
Okay. Where's the paraglider? I encourage you to slow down for a moment, my courageous friend.
The appearance of those towers in the awakening of the shrine is all connected to that Sheikah
slate you carry on your hip there. What do you mean? Well, it's been quite some time since I have
seen that Sheikah slate long ago. Highly advanced tribe known as the Sheikah inhabited these lands.
The great power of their wisdom saved this kingdom time and time again, but their ancient
technology disappeared long ago. Or so it is said. It's interesting, however, to think how
something like that survived all this time hidden away in a shrine. These shrines are tucked away in
numerous places across the land. On this plateau alone, I believe there are three. Three. Bring me
the treasure from each of these shrines and I will give you my paraglider. That was not the deal.
Oh, well, I suppose I changed my mind. I'm sure that won't be a problem for a young go-getter
like you. I'll also teach you a trick for finding shrines. It's always best to survey the area by
looking around from a high point. Let's see here. How about you make your way to the top of that
tower again? Really? I was just up there. That didn't even stick. I didn't get anything on me.
You know what I mean? That didn't even apply. Okay. Take a look at the map on your Sheikah slate.
Take a look. I sent you a friend request on Pokemon Go. It was a few days ago and
now you don't have no pressure, but I mean, I think we could really find some monsters together.
Okay. See those blue icons? You should recognize the cave where you woke, the shrine where you
came from in the tower. Travel instantly to any of those places with the Sheikah slate.
Fix that one strand of hair. All right. So let's go back up here. Wait, I need to figure out this
lake puzzle, right? If everything's a little puzzle, then I have to figure it out. Oh,
shit. Cool. I can chop down trees. What's that? All right. The way there's something interesting
here. Is this poisonous? No, but it apparently is quicksand. Wait a minute. I have this. Wait,
I can, can I pull the treasures from under the, hold on a second. I think I got it.
Those are not treasures. I can't, I can't grab those and not made it a metal.
It is very clearly a jump here. What are the, what are the metal? Is it a metal? Dude, go back.
I'm, I'm just surveying the area. What is that? Let them explore there. Okay. Sorry. I didn't,
I didn't. Okay. All right. All right. All right. I didn't know what this was attached to. All right.
What do I do about this? All the way I have to put it inside. You fucking piece of shit.
Do I have to put the, like score it like a basket? Yeah. Haha. You found me. You're not
Hestu, but you can see me. I didn't know your kind could see the children in the forest.
Give this to Hestu. A Korok seed. Okay. No, I want to be able to pick up the item he dropped.
Oh my God. Whatever. Can I, do I have to come back here? Why is this blinking? Why is this
blinking? It's like, it's like blink, blink, blink. Like come over here. Blink, blink, blink.
Do something here. What is it telling me? Well, those are the arrows. I, okay. Whatever. I'll be,
I'll come back later. Fuck it. They're your arrows. Well, I didn't know that they blinked.
This game is cool. I like it. What's the height for fall damage? Is it bad? I don't know. I'm
just going to see. Like, can I, is it, how far, how high is it? Almost there. Oh, okay. Thank you.
Thank you. I think I've had to sneeze. Okay. I'm glad I got that out. That's been sitting there
for the last 45 minutes. I swear to God. Okay. You certainly took your time. Did you forget how to
fast travel? Yes, I did. Now then I want you to join me up here so you can look at,
out there to find another. I already see it. The scope. Oh, that's what I saw before with that.
Look, it's over there. Uh, no, I got it. Wait. Oh, finding the shrines more than one. Okay.
Wait, take those pins away. There's way too many. How do I get rid of them? I'm doing an orbital
strike on that place. Uh, I want to put, whatever. There's three, right? How do I take them down?
So now there's one more, he said. One, two. Did I already get that one? Did I already get this one?
I got them, right? The ones you finished turn blue. Okay. So then there's three. Isn't that what he
said? To find three of them? Or three more. Oh, just go to them. Okay. So which, this one's on
the ground level. I'm doing this one first. I like this one. I like this. This is cool.
Should I check? I'm going to investigate this camp. Do you have to sleep or anything?
Oh, an arm. Comes back to life. How do you, how do you permanently kill these? These things are
five? The woodcutter's axe is dog shit in comparison. All right. I'm going to keep this for now.
All right. I'm going to, let me invest. Wait, is there a way to put a food on your quick bar or
something? Completely fucking missed. All right. Whatever. This thing's already, I touched one thing
with it. It's a, what does it, why does it just explode? Somebody, what happened in there? Okay.
I guess I'm going to just loot your whole place. Somebody, somebody really fucked up in here.
God damn it. Just scared the shit out of me. Okay. Cool. So you can only carry a certain amount of
things. Let's put the, let's put the club on. I feel like I don't want to eat a lot of this stuff.
How much is it? Do you get for this? Spiked club. So what was actually in here? You hold right D pad.
You can switch between. All right. That, thank you so much. What do we got? Fire arrows. Cool. Got it.
It was the weirdest way I could have possibly done that. All right. That was cool. A little dungeon,
a little dungeon. What should we do now that hell has frozen over? Um, I don't know. Oh,
you can probably activate those. And that is a map reveal. What's up there? All right. I like this
game. I like this game. I didn't say anything else. Everyone hold off. Okay. I can, I can grab those.
I got to go back to that other shrine. Amber. It's been valued as a component in decorations
and crafting since ancient times. Cool. And the shrines right here, right? Get away from me.
What is the dodge? There has to be a dodge. Why? Because games with two frame invincibility
dodge rolls are my favorites. So I want it to be in everything. All right. I get it. I'm going to,
I'm going to hide behind something in the ruins and be fine. Ready? Watch this. Jesus.
You can't outrun it. I was seeing if you could outrun it with a sprint. I was seeing if you're
going to run with the sprints. Relax. Crouch. I need a weapon so I can outrun it. No, I cannot
actually. Stop telling me I can outrun it. I'm going to use my bow. Yeah, bro. You can. I can.
No, you cannot. How do I put the bow down? What? Why can I hurt this? Everything's breaking.
I shoot it in like the neck. Oh shit. It's emote only. I actually don't know what I in the head.
My bow is gone. What was that for? Um, where's the bow? No, don't throw this. How do I put this down?
How do you quick equip the bow? I have a second bow. How do I equip a bow quickly?
Does it have like a thing on its head? Can I climb it? I can't hurt this. I think,
do I have to shoot it in its neck? Is that working? It's not working. I don't think I can kill
this. I have to like go pick up a fucking heavy box and throw it at it. I don't get it. Shoot it
in the eye. I am. I have no air. I cannot fight this thing. I don't have, I'm definitely, I don't
have an item that I need to kill this. Yeah. I need the ancient gear to make the ancient gear
arrow to shoot it in the eye with the ancient gear arrow tip. I put this into the coin slot.
All right. I actually don't know what the fuck to do. What about shooting the ears?
I think I just have to shoot it there. I actually think I just keep doing this over and over again.
No, that's wrong. Nay, nay, nay. Okay. So is there something else here I can do?
Wait, is there something? Can I crush it? No, no, no, no. Wait. Okay. Should I just leave?
Am I missing a very specific item that I need to kill this? Nay, nay. Yeah. Yeah. It's yeah. I'm
telling you that I picked up the gear. All right. I'm out of here. Okay. The judge by shrine. This
game is pretty sick. I love breath of the wild. Cool. I hope I like it as much as you do. You
should play sonic adventure. Didn't I already play sonic adventure on stream long time ago
during a dream cast night or dream cast week, whatever it was. Okay. Second shrine. Yeah, I did.
In the name of the goddess Hylia, I offer this trial bomb trial. All right, let's turn it on.
Can you just make this the new Elden ring where you play it every single stream? I don't know.
We'll see. Do I see if I like it? I have to enjoy it for a while. Whoa. Okay. The force of the blast
can be used to damage monsters or destroy objects. I wonder what I do with that now. Okay. They're
both round and cube bombs. We use whatever was better for the situation. Okay. So I go take that
back outside and I just throw bombs at that thing and blow its head off. Got you. So it's just a
cool down. It's not, there's no mana. Just cool down. Cool. Oh, okay. I have to detonate them.
Ooh, it's in here. Pretty great. All right. I'm never going to use that. Your inventory is full.
What? I was getting rid of it. Damn. This thing's cool. All right. Put this away. I'm probably never
going to equip this for the rest of the entire playthrough. I'm going to run into so many problems
with this. Uh, the, this game system where things break, I will never use a good weapon until like
the last boss and I'll cycle through five of them. Anything down here? This is too complicated. I
quit. I can't climb this. No, I cannot climb smooth surfaces. Sound design of the game is really nice.
It does sound really good. It is a very nice sound. Okay. I think I did it. Can I get launched from
these? Well, that's fun. I can. So hold on. I'm not going to do that. I want to get launched from
that one. Yeah, I know. I'm getting the chest. I want to make sure they didn't kill you instantly
or something. Just like you're dead. I was hoping it would. I was trying to time it.
Amber. Okay, cool. Now I've take this and I probably put it into something over here, right?
I guess not. Your resourcefulness in overcoming this trial speaks to the promise of a hero.
In the name of goddess Hylia, I bestow upon you the spirit orb. That wasn't not that hard.
The fact that nobody has stumbled in here and done this simple pick the ball up puzzle. This is
a, this place is full of fucking idiots and no one's come down here and done that.
Oh, the ancient trial where it's only the truest of heroes can pick a ball up and put it next to
this thing to blow up. That's really not that hard. It wasn't activated till you touch the tower.
You need the tablet. All right, but why make it so easy for me, right? If like,
if you need the tablet to come in here, shouldn't don't they want to have some barrier
and make sure that the hero can actually do shit and not just have it be a simple
pick the ball up puzzle? If you want to make sure this guy's got what it takes,
you put a, you, you, you put like a Griffin in one of these, then you'll find somebody that you
can fucking really deal with again. You put like a fucking Hydra in one, in one of these and have it
be a wall of Sudokus before you get to that point. You want the real hero? I'm talking a mural of
Sudokus. Eventually someone might be able to do it. You know how many heroes would go down to the
wall of Sudokus? There's like 5,000 Sudokus and just be like, I'm not gonna open this. I'm out of
here. Is that working? All right. Well, I did that one. So I should clear that section. Is this
hurting? I don't think it's hurt. Okay. Let me get out of here. So I did that. That's good.
Now let's head this way. Ooh, give me this. Very cool. This is a Nintendo switch shirt.
You just pulled me out of the game. So bad. I'm now out of the game. I've now, this is, I'm,
I'm going to like a Zelda convention now. This is no longer breath of the wild. What happened?
You pulled me out. I'm a gamer now. I'm going up. We're that way. Probably. It's too bad.
There's not an emo where you can just be like, what was up in these trees? Nothing. Flowers?
Nothing. Which one's closer? This one or this one? Oh, this one by far is closer. How do I get up
there? Yeah. I can't care anymore. Are there bees? Oh shit. Oh, yeah. Can I get it? Give me that
quick. What's the agro range? Okay. We're good. All right. How do I get up there? All right. Well,
there's the old man. It's a pear. Spicy pepper. Ooh, old man's diary. Don't, this is kind of
fucked up. Should I read this? Spicy meat and seafood fry. Not only restores health,
but also keeps me warm even when traveling in the snowy mountains. Okay. I forgot to write down a
very important recipe. I know it contained raw meat and spicy pepper. However, I can't remember
what else I used. Sadly, on this lonely plateau, I have only my known knowledge and memory to rely
on. If I did find someone who knew the missing ingredient, I would happily reward them with my
warm doublet. Okay. Shield! You can pass time by a fire. Uh, let me talk to you. Ooh, fancy that. We
meet again. This body of mine isn't what it used to be. Recovering from bout of hard work takes a
while. If you're hungry, I have an empty pot you can use to cook yourself a meal. Open your inventory,
grab hold of your ingredients, and toss them in. Try to consider how the ingredients will
complement one another. You can even make a dish that increases your stamina. Sick. Oh, food. Wait,
how do you cook? You have to hold it? Hold. Hold? Hold, hold, hold. Oh, oh, oh, I see what you mean.
Okay, what about like a mushroom? You want some cooked fucking poisonous mushrooms? And, ooh! Oh,
shit! Okay. What about a cooked acorn and fish souffle? Fish? Wait, hold on. Two fishes, an egg,
and spicy peppers, and some fucking honey. How does that sound? That sounds like a pretty good
batch to me. Glazed seafood, bro! How about some rubies for crunch? Uh, gear, a bat wing, and like
a fucking monster eye. Dude, did I, what? Did I just actually make a special food? Go make grass
and shit? Wait, you can cook grass? All right, what about an egg? Egg, acorn, spicy pepper, and
ancient screw. Wait, like, why can I cook that? All right, um, you can do that? That's so stupid.
That wasn't an important item or anything, right? Was that actually, that was not like
an important thing I need, is it? Eat it. No? Okay, good. Thank God. Okay, if they added a puke,
this would be a full letter grade higher. If I came out of the menu and he just went,
just green sludge came out of his mouth. All right, well, that's cool. You can just make recipes?
Really? Whoa! Apple tree right here. Look at all these apples up here. Well, I'm gonna make like
an apple pie. The cooking part's my favorite thing. I don't want to cut this down. Is there
a seed? I actually did not really want to cut that down. What if I did apple and wood, you know,
for crunch? How much wood should I get? I feel like I should do this now so I don't do this later.
Leaf, leaf, leaf, leaf, leaf, leaf. I mean leaf. Leaf, leaf, leaf. Oh, um, whoa! All right, don't,
I don't want to use that. I'll make an apple pie or something. Spicy apple mushroom pie. Ooh,
grants low level cold resistance. The sweet dish is made by heaping tasty fruits into a pan and
simmering until tender. I get four and a half minutes of, uh, cold resist. That is by far the
most fun part of the game so far, without a doubt. That's awesome. That's really fun to do.
The fact you can make your own recipes, that's death. Okay, so how do I get across here? Good
question. Up there and then left. Tree, tree, tree. Climb the tree or knock the tree down.
Can you actually climb this whole thing? I'm mainly curious about that. Can you get to the top?
Can I, can I go up and like put my legs up like Spider-Man? Okay, I made it. Okay, so you cannot
get there from that. You, uh, you probably just chop it down. What was it? Hold. Oh, right. That
didn't work either. What the fuck? What? That didn't work. Cut the other one. You guys are
fucking with me. Oh, fuck off. All right. What's the, it's holding. What button do you hold to,
I don't know. It's hold, hold this shit. Hold that shit. Hold right. Okay. It's hold right.
What's this? Ooh, a spear. Explain. I know it's a hold right and then press the right stick and then
let go. And I, I, I know, I know it's contextual pressed, pulled button key mapping. Where's my
food? Boomer reflexes. There's way more than four buttons in this. You know how I feel about it.
Okay. Can I climb up here? I might be able to climb this scared the fuck out of me. All right.
Um, I don't think I can climb that. I want to get all these apples though. Emote only. Yeah.
The emote only only makes it so I can't see all the back seaters. Just give me the fuck. I want
all the apples. Give them. I want them. Give them to me. Too lazy to climb to the right spot.
So I just cut the whole tree down. Okay. So then over here. Ah, I can climb that.
Okay. Ooh, there's purple mushrooms over here. What are these? Rush room. Oh,
raggy. There's a rush room over here. A mushroom that can almost grow anywhere.
Cook it before eating to temporarily increase your movement speed. Okay. A lot of, a lot of rush
rooms over here. I'll check this out. It's why I just blew up my face. Oh my God, dude,
this is going to be fucking awesome. Check this out. I'm going to hit this person in the fucking
head. Oh, there's no arrows. Whatever. Can you craft arrows? Hop left for bow. Oh shit. Don't
jump again. Oh, close. All right. This is over here. And okay. I got to go to the right here.
What the hell is that? I'm going to put somebody going to throw a rock over here. No one's going
to come step on my fingers when I get to the top. I think I'm good. Something died up here. All
right. Oh, I die. I'm trying. Let's do it. This game's sick. He's doing it. But I'm playing it.
I bet you he's never going to play this again. Don't be so sure who sets foot in this shrine.
I am Oh, I die. I am in the name of the goddess Hylia. I offer you this trial stealing rune.
Now what if I just leaned over and opened my mouth and caught that in my mouth? Would that ruin
everything? Would I have blue diarrhea for a year? Stop the flow of time for an object.
I'm out of the loop. Is this your first playthrough? I've never played this. This is
my first Zelda game in 15 years. It's got to be 15 to 17, 18. When did Majora's Mask come out
in Ocarina of Time? That was like 1996. We're talking about like 17 years. It's been a long
fucking time. Okay. So it's time stop. How long ago was it? Majora's Mask was 22 years ago? Oh
my God. All right. So obviously we're going to go like this. Wait, how long is it? I'm trying to,
whatever. I'm, I'm, I'm holding jump to grab, but that's not how you do it. It's not hold,
jump, grab. It's hold, jump, and you have to hold X. You have to, there's like a grab button you
have to press. Ah, cool down. Chest or anything? You should name your horse shit stain. So there's
a horse in the game. I didn't know that until you just said it. That looks cool. Iron sledgehammer.
Oh my fucking God. I don't know. What did I just drop? What did I just drop? All right.
Throw this thing away. Wait, let me see what the moveset is like. This thing's awesome. I
don't have room for it. Torch. Should I hold onto the torch? Okay. I want that. Yep. Sledgehammers
are very important. You'll want one at all times. Okay. It reminds me of this, the Wario where the
Dun-dun-dun-dun....
That's like din-din-din-din-dun-din-dun-din-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun
Can I move it? Uh, will the, will this work? Why would that work?
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun
Spirit orb? Three spirit orbs. Okay, I got one more tutorial shrine to do. Go back and read
the tutorials? If I need to, I will. All right, there's only one remaining and it's up there.
The temperature is getting diversely low. Find of find warm. How many? How many clothes that guy that's gonna help this? He's shrunk
The temperature the temperature when it reaches a certain level. Well, how do I get the fuck out of here?
Where's the hot spot? Come on. So it's too cold. I wait I have food
Okay grants a low level cold resistance. The sweet dish is made of okay
So I got four and a half minutes if I eat this then I have about five minutes to walk around, right?
Let's go for it. I'll try to get there as quick as possible
So if I eat it not yet wait till it I get to the temperature drop. Okay temperature dropped
Okay, eat the food here. Eat it cold resistance. Let's go
I apparently got lost going to the nintendo convention. How did I end up here? Oh shit. Do I have a bow?
Okay, I got it. I did it. I'm fine. What was even over here? There's nothing even here. Oh wait chest
Come on, it's like a comfy hoodie. All right. Hurry up. Come on idiot
Loco shield. Whoa, cool. All right. I can't carry any more items three minutes on the cold resist five arrows
Come on, give me some gear green rupee. Oh shit. Okay. Can I climb? Okay climb this can I make it over over?
Wait, I have an idea. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I think I can't just sit up there and god just get up there. I can't stand on this looks like I can
All right, let's go
All right. I made it. Okay, it's right over there. I think is this freezing. How cold is this water?
Okay, well we're going a different way. Why do you only have three health?
I don't know because I just started the game. It looks like this is a bridge or something right here
What is this line on the map? See this? What what is this? Oh, that's the waterfall edge
Um, shit. What do I do? I have one minute. Hold on. Hold on. Wait. Wait. I think I can maybe can I get up this?
I got one minute
Wait mushroom second, how do I cook? How do I cook food? Oh my god. I got this is no way
I can I can eat my way there though. Am I good? I can eat my way here. Are you kidding me guys?
I don't why don't have a weapon equipped. I gotta make quick work of this
Oh look look at the my temperature. My temperature is good. Take what is it? Oh, let's take that
Oh my god, take arrows. Is this food or anything? It is very cool. All right. Should I cook? All right two apples
One mushroom one rush room and a acorn toasty rush room roast. Oh, it's not
I just toasted everything. All right. Well, I didn't know I thought you could cook. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait, if I light up this
The temperature's okay. I'm good. I get it. No, don't do that. No, I can't get it
All right. I hurry up get in here. Is it warm in here? It's got to be insulated in here, right?
I would imagine it's probably insulated. The temperature is
To you sets foot in the shrine. I am khan namut in the name of the goddess halei after this trial
Yeah, it's insulated insulated and it is not the oh wait pillar of ice from a water surface
Builds ice pillars that are very stable. These pillars can be used as stepping stones or as obstacles use cryonis
On an ice pillar to break it. That's a cool ability. Let's try it. Cool. So these how long do they last?
Can you only have one? Okay, you can have more than one
I love that sound
I love ice
You know, it's my favorite one of my favorite things in the world when you get an ice tray
so I like to make my own ice and
the thick
It takes like a whole day to freeze this in the freezer
But when you get those huge they're at least two inches tall and two inches wide almost they're these big
It's completely see-through thick ice chunks
I love just sitting that in a cup and just putting I don't know like ice tea in there
Like a coca-cola or something. Oh, how high can I make this? Is that as high as it goes?
Can't go higher than that. Oh
Fuck I just got hurt. I think I just hurt my chest. I'm just thinking about somebody looking at the security camp
This guy fucking dies right there
Oh that hurt. Ooh
All right, I'm just thinking somebody looking at the security monitors and oh hey somebody made it somebody got in
Yeah. Yeah, another adventurer. I wonder yeah what's giving the ice move?
And the guy throws a bomb against the wall it bounces off and fucking blows the guy smithereen
Nope, that one didn't make it wait another 5 000 years for the next one
Okay
Oh, well, I just laughed too quickly and I like popped a joint in my rib
God damn it
Okay. So how do I get out of here? I can't even make it faster. Where is this door?
This is why you have a team. This is what a team is for guys. The wizard of oz
Told us a long long time ago
You get the guy that knows how to do the puzzles the guy that can dodge the x
with and they can kill things with melee weapons the strong one the smart one the
The the courageous one, right? We all can do something
We let the smart one do the puzzles and then I get in there with the fucking axe
And start swinging. That's the whole that we that we've learned this 100 years ago
That's why you need a team. Let the smart person figure this out while I smoke a cigarette over there in the corner
How do I get out of here? How do I do this?
Stop time. All right. I stopped time on that. This thing is made out of fucking metal. What?
Get in there. Okay. I did it who wants turkey
I gotta have my song. Well, of course Dorothy. Well, what can you do?
well
I can dodge an axe with a swift kick fall backwards and smoke a cigarette and salt them with the rain
Well, this thing's made out of metal. We're good. Hold on. This is technically this is wait. This is water. Oh my god
Look what you can do
physics
oh
physics physics
Get up there if I don't make this again. I'm gonna be very upset
Okay, what's going on?
Go up i'm getting caught in the
Get on
There. Oh, hold on
Yeah
Spear. Oh monka cool. I think that's it, right? Yeah
Never before seen solutions. What do you what does that mean? All right, you're resourcefulness. You're very resourceful in the name of the goddess
Hylia, I bestow upon you this orb cool fucking chest
Why did I have to think about the stupid security footage of somebody dying in this dungeon? Hey, I got them all where's my glider?
Extraordinary link it is finally time for me to tell you everything but first sign this non-disclosure agreement
So you can't tell anybody about between me and you I didn't read that where the two
Lines connecting the shrines would cross there. I'll be waiting there were four shrines centered amid the four shrines
one
two
three
Four right about here. Okay. Why is that not on the map? It has to be a pin not a stamp. Oh
Mm-hmm
You bet your ass I can dodge it every weapon held in two hands if you only swung an axe
Yeah, I talk about in that movie
I how I can dodge everything and then I just get an arrow like through the temple like just goes like
Can't dodge that
Okay
So you said it was a stamp not a marker. So then it's it's it's the yeah
It's this so make a pen. There we go. Badly damaged
Who needs it? Okay, so it's right there. You needed to use the ice pillar to lift the gate
Man, you look like we can play the game two different ways
It's a little chilly out though
A sword and stone can I climb and hold on?
Rusty broadsword does not you do that does not constitute putting that into a stone like that
That's not that interesting
Oh
Opal not a bad find. Oh lots of fangs. Okay. I'm here. He's having fun. I don't know. This is good
I'm it's just one of those games where there's tons of stuff just to look at and do
And play with and find and look a treasure chest with a tooth in it, right? I I like that stuff ancient screw
Where's that guy? This is definitely it. This is definitely it
Where is he top? So when does breath of the wild 2 come out?
May may 12th. All right looking forward to it another ancient gear assuming they don't delay it. Oh, that's true
It could get delayed. Couldn't it?
Could another ancient shaft. I kind of want to go up there
Wait rupees no rupees
Not a single rupee
bullshit
He's pretending to be excited. The nintendo fans are gonna kill me
Stop quiet
What are you trying to do?
Let's go
Traveler's bow. Oh beautiful
Okay, I don't actually need that. I have like five of these. All right here. Can I throw the bow?
how do I throw the bow just drop it so I've got the turkey leg and
the
Traveler's shield is fine. And then is there a fast way to switch the bow?
Yeah, hold this and go like that. All right, so I definitely don't want yeah
I just want the boku the boku bow, whatever it is. I'm supposed to do this the boku bow
wasn't boku
a adult juice box
Do you guys remember that it was a company that tried to make an adult juice box
It was supposed to be it's not for kids. It's for adults. I want one. Hold on. Yeah, i'm telling you. This is real
Yeah back in the the 90s. Yeah boku. It was supposed to it was it was a juice box for adults
Wait, richard lewis is in this commercial on a boku a seven fruit blend boku
I mean all this carbon I can't hear this but I don't know what he's saying anymore belching this for babies
I want to be refreshed. No, it's not alcohol. No, it was just a juice box
My undeniable right is a man. This is richard lewis now the 90s to quench my thirst in my own way
I want a boku. I've had it. What do you mean? T. O. S. What are you talking about? Show this
I I can't hear it but I can show it because my headphones are plugged into the uh, the able to hear the switch
But here hold on. Well, I i'll let you guys watch it. That's fine
So I go to a I don't know what he's saying. I go to a party and I got my choice of coke or pepsi
This isn't right. I want a boku a seven fruit blend boku. I mean all this carbon is saying this is an adult juice box
I don't want to belch anymore belching this for babies. I want to be refreshed naturally calmly
I mean, it's my undeniable right as a man of the 90s to quench my thirst in my own way
I want a boku. I've had it people invite me to a party. I'm bringing my own boku
Boku fruit juice cooler from mccain. Why why do they have a belt of them? This is stupid. What did he say?
Is it funny he sounds like you doing a voice. Yeah, it was an adult juice box
Okay, well, let's play you who have conquered the shrines and claimed their spirit orbs. I can offer you
I don't I can't dub it. I don't know what what he's saying. It sounds like he's mocking the drink
Oh, he said he's bringing him to a party
Okay, it appears you have four spirit orbs in exchange. I will amplify your being oh
This is important you guys adult juice boxes already exist
It's called just going and getting orange juice from the grocery store a pretty adult beverage
I would say just orange juice like you can be an adult and drink it
Uh, I think I want the stamina do heart. I want stamina though. I don't feel to move around more and climb more
I'm doing stamina stamina to me is more important. Just don't get hit all the people saying heart container. Just get good
Just don't get hit. Give me a break. Cool. All right, very cool. Ooh, I get extra little
Uh thing there give me the glider. Is my fps on this camera fine?
Yeah, the blessing of the goddess has made you much more resilient. I see here. I am get up here quickly
Do you know that never happened in tf2?
I always tried to get it but it never happened coming out of a map or come out of the spawn and just
Knocking a huntsman arrow across the whole map and just waiting to hear that come. I tried it probably
Ten to twenty thousand different times. It's just so hard to do
By the way, if there's not a single way i'm ever gonna play a different zelda game than this
As I find this to be a hundred times cooler than any of the zelda games i've ever played he talks
I truly am. I was king rome
Bosporamus hyrule or my shortened name. I was ganondorf the last leader of hyrule a kingdom which no longer exists
Oh, is this the dinner guy?
Devastated everything in its path lo a century ago
It was then that my life was taken away from me
And since that time here I have remained in spirit form
I did not think it wise to overwhelm you while your memory was still fragile
so rather than that
I thought it best to assume a temporary form
Forgive me
I think you are now ready
Ready to hear what happened three years ago
Somebody said why does he sound hot?
To know kalanin's true form what the fuck one must know the story from an age-long past
The demon king was born into this kingdom, but his transformation into malice created the horror you see now
Stories of ganon were passed from generation to generation in the form of legends and fairy tales
But there was also
Prophecy the signs of a resurrection of calamity ganon are clear the power to oppose it
lies dormant
We decided to heed the prophecy and began excavating large areas of land. I'm going to gamelan
Before we discovered several ancient relics to protect me in the hands of our distant ancestors fuck you link
I will eat you for dinner these relics the divine beasts were giant fuck you the king
Fuck you ganon
We also learned of a princess with a sacred power and her appointed knight chosen by the sword that seals the darkness
It was they who sealed ganon away using the power of these ancient relics
100 years ago. There was a princess set to inherit a secret. They always if they wanted to do something that they never said
Stringing together like six different consonants
Right. So if oh i'm going to gamelan
For
Sentence mixing
It's so great when it doesn't work at all, but you know what they were trying to do
He appeared from deep below hyrule castle sees definitely have seen videos of the spy from tf2 saying like
My
Like okay, I all right, I know what you were doing. I know what you were trying whatever and thus devastated
However, the princess survived to face ganon alone link
You are our final help
The fate of hyrule rests with you
Yeah, if you're like
my
Princess was my own daughter
My dear zelda and the courageous knight who protected her right up to the very end
That night was none other than you link you
When your fate took an unfortunate turn sure. Yeah, this does this does not seem right taken to the shrine of resurrection
Here you now stand revitalized 100 years in a switch game words of guidance
You have been hearing since your awakening are from princess zelda herself
Even now
As she works to restrain ganon from within hyrule castle. She calls out for your help
however
My daughter's power will soon be exhausted
once that happens
Ganon will freely regenerate himself and nothing will stop him from consuming our lives. It really what happened to be in my link costume
I'm still link. Does it matter? Who cares?
Link could just put on a green shirt. Who cares? What's the difference must save her as well as those guardians swarming around hyrule castle
I believe it would be quite reckless for you to head directly to the castle at this point
I suggest
That you make your way east out to one of the villages in the wilderness
Follow the road out to kakariko village
There you will find the elder impa
She will tell you more about the path that lies ahead
Consult the map on your sheikah slate for the precise location of kakariko village
Make your way past the twin summits of the dueling peaks
From there follow the road as it proceeds north
Hmm, thanks to the paraglider
Yay
Okay, press b while you're in the air to use it fly off cliffs and I think that's it
And I think that's it link you must save hyrule
Is he ever coming back?
Seek out impa. Okay, so now I can jump
All right, I want to pan over and have his mouth just be open like wide like
The air filling it
That would be so funny. All right, you can use it pretty much anywhere. Wait, hold on. Can I kill this thing now?
so I have
Uh stasis. Let's try this
Here we go bombs. Maybe
Can I block this?
Broke my shield actually blew my shield up never mind. All right, i'm getting the fuck out of here
All right, I want you in the chat to everyone to tell me why
Zelda is why you like zelda games. Why do you like a zelda game and I want it in four words
I love adventure games. Okay, cool
Is sword ghost slash? Mm-hmm. They're kind of fun
None of your business fair. That's four words
I like dungeon crawling. Cool. Very good
I save the princess. Okay
Fun dungeons and adventure. All right, I get it
Music is usually good. Yep
Only played this one
Fuck you. That's why yeah, that's fair
Excuse me
Why is this thing coming alive?
stone talus
i'm fucking dead
Why there's no dodge i'm trying to do the
I just want to do that. All I want is my whole body to lunge sideways in a flip just like
Why can't I do that?
All right, let's do it again
ex-teleportation rumors
Oh, I blew his leg off
Okay, hold on
Nice drop throwing it the wrong direction
Stop telling me about stop texting me rumors. I don't care
Oh my god, stop texting me
Stop texting me about stuff. I don't want to see that
stop
xeno blade chronicles 2
I don't stop with these advertisement texts. What what?
What are you talking about?
Every zelda boss has a puzzle you have to blow off his leg and then you have to like go inside of his
Bone marrow and like hit him in the bone marrow and uh, all right. Now, what do I do?
Do I hit him and like the butt tail thing?
Just like holding onto his ass
I have to smash this thing, right?
Why are you crouching?
I'll get him. I'll get him. I'm gonna use a different weapon to something better
It's time to actually use one of these good items
I'm using this traveler's claymore and i'm going to fuck him up. Nice hit
I have to just throw the bomb at the diamond in his back
Mallet mallet smash the mallet. I don't know what you mean with the cartoon bullshit. Do you use this?
Okay, i'm gonna use this. Thanks for the help. I'm on his head. I didn't I didn't want to jump
What are you talking about?
Why did I think that was sprint?
I'm so fucking confused. Why did that happen?
No
All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go go go go go go go go go. He's gonna smash his head
Okay
Okay, do I just can I
Stop doing the mallet emote. I don't know what that means. Can I stop time? Oh wait, it broke what I thought I
I get it back right because I died. I get it back because I died, right?
Okay, good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Thank god. Okay. I maybe i'm just not strong enough
I might just not be strong enough to do this
I don't think i'm strong enough to beat this guy
You piece of shit
Okay, i'm not strong enough, but I want to beat it so bad
One more try i'm taking both arms out. I'm gonna be very patient. Here we go patient time
There's both arms done
He's gonna smash his head. I'm gonna climb up his body
And i'm gonna get the no he grows the shit back
Fucking completely missed
Hey
Hey, put the fucking phone down
Oh
Can I shoot with arrows?
Yes, that does not do any damage at all though
I'm not strong enough to be here. I actually don't think i'm strong enough to be here
I think you come back in like 10 levels you come back in 10 plus levels
Just give up on the tree sentinel. Not yet. I will okay. I'm gonna get it here. I'm just gonna play
I'm gonna dodge and fight. How does that i'm done?
I'm fucking done. I'm leaving. I'm okay. I'm alive and live. I'm fine. I'm good
Bye i'm done. I'm coming back later. I'm not supposed to be here
Um, this is like something you do like in 10 levels or like 20 levels
Because you do the same this is like a late game fight
It's a late game fight
Can I I can't I don't think I can freeze him in time. Can I can I freeze his body?
I got chapstick all over the controller. I know I can't freeze him stop time
What is going on get out of here?
No, I just gotta fight him
If I think i'm safer, let me hold on. Okay
so
What happened? Um
That was such over dramatic bullshit link, please you could have gotten up five times
There's no referee to give anybody a red card here, please enough
I got a fucking idea
How's this for an idea?
Watch this
Eat shit
That's the play and then I just gotta get off
So i'm just not doing enough damage
Look at his health
Do it
What about the bow dude the bow does just as little fucking damage
The bow does less damage than that. I'm supposed to come back here after this. I'm not supposed to be here use the bow
Use the hammer
I need better weapons
Dude, stun him with arrows, huh?
All right. You got no arms now
Okay, here we go
Now he's gonna what dude some fucking stun that is that stun is not even one second
Lock on that shit don't last long enough. When does this motherfucker go down?
I can't beat him. I don't have explosive arrows
Fuck that. I I know I can't kill him. That's not true. Yeah, it is. What am I supposed to do? Look
This rock piece of shit. I can't
No
That was that was not nice
I have to get some type of item to like blow the back of that thing off
I die in one hit i'm not supposed to be here
Okay, what's this
Hold on
I'm disappointed in you disappointed because I don't I don't have the thing
I don't have the game knowledge to beat the the gimmick boss where you have to blow his leg off and fucking bite his bone
Marrow to do damage
Bro chill with the chapstick
Lost a bone marrow. I'm telling you i'm gonna come back there and it's gonna be like dude
You could have killed him. You could have killed him. Yeah, just like you can kill the um,
What's it called the sentry in the beginning of elden ring? Yeah, you can
No, you can't you're not supposed to
All right, let's go. We're gonna new strong
How do I get the wind?
Can I hit to go faster? I can't um
oh
Okay
Amber I better see at least 100 pogchamps over there because I figured it out
Okay, what about this one over here? What's this for? Just get back. Okay. What about down here?
By the way, thanks for joining me for uh, omega gaming weekend. Yeah, I know what to do. I'm not stupid
Sorry, I've reset I can't okay you absolutely go from there
Is there a quick slot for food? I think I asked that before no there isn't what?
Unfucking believable. What year is it? Nintendo? What year is it?
2022 we don't have a quick slot for healing items. Okay, what is wrong?
What's what is going on? Why is it? Why can I not make it? I made it to before
Germa tv that email is supposed to be banned. I don't want to die
No, I was going stop. I was going out of the stream. I'm fine. All right
So what are we doing this? What kind of accolade do I get?
Mods are making fun of me in mod chat because how bad I did the rock bite. Oh a spear. Okay
I need four of these. Okay, dream tv. I'm having fun. I'm having fun
I know you're not supposed to compare this to elden ring, but i'm going to
Uh, it's the same kind of go look over there. Go look over there. Go check that out. Go look over there. Go look over there
Um, they're definitely not the same game, right? They're very different. They're pretty similar, but they're very different
So check this out
What is it 50 rupees? All right
Um, what's that over there? I'll check it out later
I okay that scared the shit out of me. I thought this was a gigantic dragon or something. I thought it was a huge dragon wing
Because I looked it was right there my breath rule. I thought it was a huge dragon
Let's get out
There's a villain. Is this an npc?
We're doomed. I mean don't panic. Sorry. Who are you?
Have we met doesn't matter who you are really I was getting tired of talking to myself
So you're coming a good time by the way those strange things that popped out of the ground
Did you see them talking about the mushrooms here? I'm talking about
Oh, okay
They seem to have popped up all over the place and that's not the only strange things happening those long deserted shrines suddenly started glowing
You know what that means. Don't you the end is near with all the craziness happening
I've been keeping an eye on that thing
Just to see if it suddenly starts moving
What thing talk about that guardian, of course, haven't you heard the old stories?
See that thing over there the one shaped like an overturned urn
That is what i'm talking about
Did you know that some of them can move one of them once chased me down and tried to kill me?
No, it was a different one
That one was closer to the castle but before the forest
When they spot you
They shoot blue beams of light at you man. I was so sure that was the end for me
I was prepared for the worst until uh, I got it right in the bone marrow
Let me tell you how to do it. I hear guardians like that still wander
Be careful. Thanks for no info. I'm just doing a physics test. Holy shit. What can I do anything with the ram?
I guess not. What are you doing? Where's my weapon way too high? Oh, this guy's kind of strong. Stop rolling
Boko bat
No, I want to pick up the item
Pick it up pick up the pick. I want to do what I just did
Pick up the fucking rock, please. I need to do this
He fucking dropped it on that was bug's bunny level shit right there. Oh
Okay
He was trying to kill me. Oh, that's funny. Okay. All right, so
Uh, what did I get for that? There was a chest right here, right?
And this food over here. Ooh
Thank you
Try toast some more stuff
the opal destroy crates
They have stuff in them. Oh, they do. Okay
crab
Roasted bass. Oh shit. Thank you for the uh reminder. Seriously
Is there a way I can break them without damaging an item? Okay, well that didn't work. I can use the uh use magnet
Oh, I could just blow them up with an idiot
With a magnet
It was a shitty rusty sword. Anyways, who cares? It doesn't matter. Ooh blue rupee
I'm gonna eat one of those crabs. All right, let's keep going base cam is covering what what are you what's going on?
Go to the glowing mountain. I'm just gonna say there's an event on the mountain. What do you mean?
I almost fucking drowned in two feet of water again. Okay. No, no, no nay nay nay nay nay what?
God, I hope link gets in smash brothers this year. I thought it was friendly. Now the camp is this I like the sounds
It's very peaceful over here. There it is. Okay
Okay, this and bloodborne are my two favorite games
Well, I if you're saying bloodborne is one of your favorite games and this I probably would agree with you at some point
Maybe we'll find out
Is there anything else I've been over here?
You got me like an item in here, right?
Pass me an item. There's no way there's no item here. Why would there be a camp with no item?
What is the actual destination here? Oh my god, that's far away. That's across the whole game
Can I even make it can I make it there?
well
Um, maybe I should activate that thing, right?
Give me some location data
Dude, you just got elden ring
Oh, I kind of did
All right
You can go anywhere and you can climb anything. I got elden ring
Stop saying elden ring elden
Okay, do you know how hard it's gonna be to not say anything about elden ring?
I know i'm not supposed to be but think about it. That was one of like the most ridiculous
Hold on a sec
The bow broken my hands. Okay. Well never mind
Yeah, let's get this guy's another strong one. Oh my god. I just baseball swung him
Where are you going? Is there an instant kill backstab or something that he didn't wake up? Why?
Hello
Why is why did that happen? It was the fire does that really I can cook over here
All right. Oh, let me open it. Let me I want to cook some stuff. All right, so
I have
A lot of random stuff one shroom two shrooms
Okay, how about like a shroom surprise mushroom skewer? Can I just what happens if you just cook one apple?
Simmered fruit. Okay, so it's only one now you gotta
This is gonna be three hearts
Right. Yeah. Okay. So it's it's about quantity means more health. I get it. Okay, cool
Was there a chest?
I don't think so, right
Chasing fucking apples around like an idiot chasing apples around like a dumb ass
All right. Let's turn this thing on
Dueling peaks tower. It's a map info here simplify the hud if you want some immersion
Um, I think I want it for now. I think I'd rather have it for now do motion aiming
I hate motion aiming it only ever worked in my brain for the wii using two hands to use a gyroscope is
Unbearable for me. The wii was fine because the wii was one hand, right?
It was almost like a mouse pointer but needing to hold two hands like this
And go like a no, no, no, no doesn't work for me at all. I don't like it use the joycons
Why would I ever use the joycons? The joycons are my least favorite controller ever made
They are hands down the worst possible device that was ever invented. They are so bad. They are so small
The buttons are so tiny pressing. I i'm saying i'm telling you if you try to press
X on a joycon if there's a lot there's a real possibility you're going to hit every single other button
That's a face button. They're so bad. They're just so tiny and so it's like hurts to hold them for a long time
Oh, we effing looks like it
It looks like we're seeing some some small f
Behavior here. Okay. Oh, there's a road. It's like a road here a sheikah sensor
The sensor reacts when you are close to shrines that you've not yet visited
Okay, you head in the direction where the reaction is strongest you should be able to find the shrine, okay
Wait, it's on the map. That's weird
When you play dog island, didn't I already play dog island search for shrines by moving in the direction with the strongest signal
shrine nearby
Like this way. Yeah getting some effs. It should even out though. It should be okay in a few minutes
So it's this way. Is this am I going the right way here? That's not the right weapon. Let it go flint
I'm going right here. Yeah, it's gonna it's gonna be bad for a little bit. I really I have no idea why
Um, I don't know why i'd be
We were just fine for like almost four hours. Does this make any sense? Ah, I found it
Not a big deal. Yeah, it's all right
Yeah, I don't I really don't get it. It's so bizarre. So I did a 14 hour stream two days ago
I didn't drop one single frame streaming to the same server and now here we are
But not even what a day later a day and a half later
And just kind of shit in the bed now. It's weird. It doesn't make any sense
And it's
The it's not like oh, it's because it's eight o'clock and it's getting busy. I have a fiber to the house
So I don't share a connection with anybody
It doesn't make any sense
I don't get it. Okay. Uh, I am re da he
In the name of this, uh, I have a challenge for you
ISP throttle
I don't I mean I have a well, it's a 1000 up connection. I'm only using i'm not using that much
Six up
That's no no way. All right dump that in there
Oh cool
All right, so i'll probably have to uh, let's go somebody said rich andy
Uh, actually no like this connection. This is the dumbest thing about uh high speed internet
So this line is less than a hundred dollars a month
It's less than I think it's like 80 or I think it's like 80 bucks a month for this. I was paying
at the old place
Cox business internet. It was fucking it was like three or four hundred dollars a month and it was for a
20 times slower connection sharing with the whole neighborhood is fucking ridiculous. It's absolutely ridiculous and it was still shitty
Yep. Oh, yeah, did I just accidentally do this? I wasn't paying any attention. I think I just did it. Okay, cool
You see I think it looks like it's fine now, can I launch it? Wait, hold on. Um, what is that?
Why did that what was that for? Wait, wait, wait, hold on. I can stop the ball
Okay, so yeah, you don't like launch it you do launch it. Well, I just I was playing
Uh chess and I'm supposed to play checkers. I'm sitting thinking I gotta freeze it and then knock it three times
So yeah, that's my fault. How do I get that like this? Let's see. Laugh laugh. Go ahead. Laugh
What are you doing? I could have just grabbed the ledge. I could have done that
I actually could have done that and my nose right here is itchy. I'm sorry. I can't do it. Fuck this watch this fuck
That was I that was so close
I fucking had it. You saw it. It was right there. All right last try. I'm not doing this anymore
Who doesn't really matter? What do you mean? Eat it?
I have to do it. I have to do it. I'm not gonna leave till I do I don't care
I don't give a shit if this is the worst
Legend of Zelda place you've ever seen in your life. I don't care. I'm gonna get it. All right gonna run out of food
I'm gonna run out of food if i'm not careful. How did I get on the first time fuck i'm fucking done. I'm done
I'm done. I'm actually done. I'm not running
Fuck you. I had it. It was the first try and I landed if I rolled off like an idiot
I need to run and jump off and then get blown from behind. All right, i'm gonna get full health all that food wasted
Guys, i'll just rob a bunch of trolls and get another two pounds of apples. I'll be all right. Don't worry. Okay
Do I even need that chest go back and get it? I need to stay. Yeah, I know I need to stay
Whatever
So fucking impatient. I just want to get over there and open it
Okay now
Stasis the button somebody said oh because okay. I see I get it. I actually see I get it
Oh my god, how can one person be so such a fool?
How can one person be such a fool? Hurry up
Oh my god, this thing takes forever. I made it climbers bandana. Okay, that really was worth doing
Can this break this is definitely worth getting can you teleport me back to the beginning so I don't die?
Cool. All right, so now I can climb better armor never breaks. Cool. That was a cool shrine
Now where do I want to go? I could keep heading this way, right?
I would be surprised if there was a way to go up. So i'm gonna head towards the bridge
This way i'm just gonna keep keep heading over here. I probably should look for a fish, right?
This is probably the easiest thing to get
Never mind trying nearby
Not talking about that one, is it?
who cares
It does not detect cleared shrines. Okay, cool growing spear. All right. I got so much dumb shit
I gotta get rid of some of this stuff
I'm trying to break this
Where's my stuff?
I'm gonna get away. Get away from me. Just keep away from me. I thought I could get away with it
I probably actually could have gotten away with it on purpose. Oh, I did it on purpose. Oh, yeah
I thought I could I actually thought I could get away with it. I definitely can
If they're sleeping, I can definitely just sneak in and do it
There's no penalty for dying anyways, who cares
Come the fuck on how did that not hit?
Where the where am I?
Excuse me
Um, whatever i'll try it again
You have a bow
Yeah, I have a bow you shoot three arrows and it's he goes broken my hands
I didn't break it
Ooh broadsword you need to light the arrow. God damn it. I didn't know that. Okay
Do you want ketchup on your hot dogs? I actually like mustard. I don't really like ketchup on a hot dog
All right time to get rid of some of this absolute crap that I have here. This is six. This thing sucks. Get rid of it
What else do I have
This thing do I really need two torches? No, I don't get rid of it
This is a throwing spear. That's pretty good
I definitely want the broadsword
Hot dogs are overrated. Ah, it depends on where you're getting them from
Some hot dogs are very overrated. You're right, but not all of them
Some hot dogs are incredibly overrated
You don't yeah, how about this?
Uh boomerang
That's cool
God dude, what should I get rid of? This thing looks awesome. All right, cool. Uh spear get rid of the leaf
Why would you throw the you threw away a claymore? Yeah, because it was little it was like 10 damage. Everything else I had was good
I need to cook stuff
Salt. Oh somebody over there. I need fish
I'm gonna go catch this fish right here. I'm gonna drop down and grab it
Okay cooking into a dish will fortify your bones
All right, there's definitely food over here
Uh, not food. There was a cooking fire over there, but I don't have any I don't I have one fish
Okay
What is that? It's like a little hut. What what did frog cook it? I don't want to cook a frog
sneaky river snail
So wait, i'm just gonna make like a frog snail fish soup
Are these people friendly?
Ah, this is the life. Good evening. Don't see a whole lot of travelers passing through here
You know with how peaceful it is around here and sometimes easy to forget that the world almost ended years ago
There's still monsters wandering around in the area near hyrule castle is especially dangerous
Do you know anything about elixirs?
You can make elixirs by mixing bugs and other small creatures with monster parts
Most of them are no good for refilling your health, but they can have a lot of unique effects
From elixirs can increase your speed
resistance to temperatures
You made it this far without knowing anything about them
Okay grants a low level haste effect. That's cool
Hightail lizard and monster parts. I need a
How much fun do I have? Can I buy stuff?
Are you a merchant?
I don't believe I made your acquaintance
The name's beetle but you can call me actually let's stick with beetle beetle shaped backpack
Shopping needs. All right. I stock bugs and items
Ooh
I also buy all sorts of things if you're in need of rupees gemstones in particular fetch a high price
Uh, what have you got?
Crickets stamina recovery elixir speed boost elixir octa balloon, maybe just buy arrows get the balloon
How many should I buy just one?
All right. I'll buy one balloon
Okay, what do I got?
um
I have a very important question
Do I need to hold on to the what is just vendor bullshit? I want to be back seated over this
should I hold on to any of these gems or just oh like amber and
Ruby and opals and sell the rubies gems are a good money to sell it sell it. It's fine for a little while
Keep at least one to five of each gem
So I shouldn't sell it
Hold you need to hold on hold on to at least one contain the power of fire and a fetch to high price
I'll hold on. I'll keep it for now. Okay. Yeah opal for instance, right power of water
It's too early to use it. Okay. I'll sell the rupee. So should I buy anything else then?
Should I buy all the octa balloons? All right. I'm buying the whole I'm buying all the octa balloons
Maybe get some arrows too. All right. I'm gonna get 10. I'm gonna get 10 arrows. Very cool. What else is over here?
Stable what's going on kakariko villages ways north of here. If you're going to dueling peak stable
It's not much further from here. It's right next to me. Actually, you can usually find me at the stables
Let's do business right here. I carry only the finest meats raw prime meat. Ooh
Should I get a bunch of prime meat or salt can I sell some stuff? I have some meat to sell
Do you want um 10? That's it. Look at my stable. We deal in all horse related things haven't seen you before
Do you know about the stable? I don't you can board your horse companions with us and then summon them as you please from
Our network of stables you may come across wild horses during your travels
If you catch one and ride it here to register it, it will be your horse companion
One person can board up to five horses. How do you catch a horse?
Hop on slowly from behind soothe it. It'll settle down and bring it to me
Okay, it may take a while or wild horses to get used to being they change directions
So slow down until you get whatever redirect it beat it or something
I do not oh you want to rest. Is it free? I want to sleep stay for a rest. Oh head to the counter. Okay
Like really you could have just done it right there. I'm 20 rupees. No, that's way too much
20 rupees
I've got the scoop on misco's treasure and it's great. Listen up. Wait, wait, hang on. What's your problem?
You aren't being incredibly rude and listening to our conversation
Are you treasure hunters the treasure of the great bandit misco? You're gonna give it all away. Don't tell them
Sorry, I got carried away. Okay
Okay, so you want and I need to pay for a hint how much 100 rupees? All right. I need to cook
There we go. Cool. Wait, there are horses right here. Look at this little horse. Wow
I've never seen one like this before. What was that? Wait, can I can I feed you or anything? Can I like do anything?
This person's sleeping
Can I kill somebody with this
No, I don't think so
I'll give you directions
That was a kid. What? I don't know where i'm trying to go. I need to cook though. Okay
So i've got I think i'm just gonna do raw prime meat an apple
Right for flavor and a little bit of salt. So this is like an apple salt glazed. Um
with uh
With oakland guts. I think that's a good start, right? That should be good salt apple glazed. Um
Pork shoulder or whatever the hell this is don't do apple just salt
What don't add this what are you talking this is bad
Meat and salt, right?
That's not worth 60 rupees. What am I what's something's wrong fish?
And uh mushroom fish and mushroom stew
Buying meat's never worth it
That really is a fish and mushroom stew. Do I even have monster parts? So like this and the frog, right?
Hd elixir cool. Next slide, please
Yeah, I don't know man
I didn't really don't get it
Like some nights, uh, it'll it's something to do with the connection that I have to twitch and
I doesn't matter how much trouble shooting I'll do
Um
I'm probably gonna call my isp
Just be like hey, um, is there anything I can even do about this or what?
It's so random
Pitchfork. Yeah, I I I cannot even I can't come up with the reason why this would ever be happening
I have fiber to the house
I will go at a thousand a thousand for 20 straight hours
and then just
It just does this for like an hour or two straight sometimes randomly for no reason
I don't know
Uh, yeah, i'm gonna heal. Okay, let me do this. Uh shrine
Save the game. There's no auto save
Looks like I saved it
Hey interesting
Plan pretty good plan. Hey
What why did it run out? What happened?
Did I not a stamina? What the hell just happened? That was gonna work. That was gonna actually work. That was gonna be fine
I ran this
All right. All right. I i'm gonna jump from here and just glide over it. Wait
Can I climb this and just do that instead?
No, that's definitely what that's what i'm doing. I probably don't have to go that high
There we go. Okay, so
I can't
Look at my hair. My hair's really kind of greasy today
Shouldn't be I washed it the water guides
Very cool
Uh, all right from here. Oh
That's neat. Why did I not die? Did I?
Why did I think that was ever going to be a thing that would work? I thought I could get around it
Ooh weird. Okay, fuck
I don't want to go. I just didn't want to run all the way back up here and do it
Uh, you know what i'm saying?
You fucking asshole
I'll dodge an axe if you swing it at me
I'm the I told you I'm smoking fucking cigarettes in the corner. I have to like get it at the right angle and freeze it
You know what I mean? I gotta it's gotta move and then I gotta freeze it
Yeah
Are we still dropping frames?
Is this still happening?
Yeah, god damn it. I don't get it
I don't understand
I don't get it
Doesn't make any sense
I need two more right? I like this aspect of the game. It's really cool. The shrines are
Some of my favorite part you like the worst part of the game. Really? I think it's really fun. I like it
Okay, so now I got this i gotta go up here. That's far away, but i'll make it i'll get a horse
Well, I gotta find a wild horse I get it's not just gonna happen. They're right here. I want the blue one
I'll take this one instead
Got it
What is that
What did I just do?
How do you ride the how do you actually ride the horse?
Is there a jump? I want to register this horse, please. I want to talk
Get back here come back back back back
I want to register this horse
Thank you. Jesus. Oh, okay. Yes 20 rupees saddle and riddle. Yeah, let's do it
I need a name. Um, I don't know. I'm gonna go pee. I haven't peed in like five hours
Pee, all right pee break and we'll come back and you'll see what the horse is named
In the meantime the stream might f for a second. Well, I do a test of some sort right back. Yeah, I don't understand
So I just i'm doing speed test right now. I have I mean it's maybe that it's a stable
900 up I gotta talk to somebody at data twitch bad and I actually have to do it now because I don't
Something about where my connection is hopping from vegas to the servers. I go to it's just
Something happens all the time and it I don't think it can't be something on my end
It's hard to determine that because two days ago I streamed for 14 hours and we didn't drop one frame not one
Same time frame two same time friday night. It's not like oh, yeah
You're streaming on like a wednesday at two o'clock in the morning
I mean that was friday at eight nine ten o'clock at night not one frame here. We are sunday night and
For what for four hours is not a single frame. It's just bizarre and then it's oh
Now all of a sudden you're just going to start dropping packets to twitch
Why go pee? No, I will I will but just so it doesn't make any sense right like
Okay, if I was consistently having internet problems, that would make sense
But you can't have a stream go flawlessly for four hours and then randomly at like 8 15
It's just oh now everything sucks
And if I do a speed test or if I do like an upload test, it's like no your connection is perfectly normal
It's the it's the data leaving here
from vegas
It's hitting some point some hop in a trace route, right if you did one
And it's just junking up somewhere on the road at some point. I don't get it
I don't know, but i'm gonna go pee i'll be right back. Okay, i'm back
Looks like I didn't drop a frame while I was gone. It's kind of strange
Okay, sorry. I scared you frank. Do I like it? I the game is great. Yeah, okay
Can horses die can a horse die? So if I go out with this horse, can I the horse die? Okay?
I'm kind of concerned about that. Be honest. Okay, so I need to go from here. We need to go straight
Right. I'm just gonna go on the road
How do you turn? Yeah, this is this is nice. It's a good looking horse. Okay. Here's a uh, this is this bridge out
Acarico bridge
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Okay. I'm almost there. It's pretty cool. See i'm petting the horse. I'm fine
I'm sad. I ran over a
Animal can you is there no jumping with the horse bones actually
It's automatic jumping okay
Turning is hard
Go what's wrong?
Okay, go back go back you walked past broccoli man. Who's broccoli man?
Go go you walked past broccoli man
That's broccoli man. Okay
Do this, okay
You can see me
I can see you. Oh, i'm hestu and I need your this is okay where we bring this stuff
I can't use my powers without them
Please please get my maracas back from them. You got it
I was trying to ram. I was trying to ram
Is that not okay? This the horse is causing all kinds of problems. I'm gonna get off the horse
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that twice
It's i'm trying so hard to turn
You know what? Just hang it out here. You're fine. Just just chill out there. We'll be good
Got a little bit of business to take care of. Oh, yeah escape
I spit everywhere. I
I just so impatient
Lock on it's the I I want to be able to just
Attack, you know what I mean?
Give me this. I this thing fuck this thing. Give me this thing way better
I'm using an actual item
There we go
Use spells. What spell would you want me to use freeze one?
Ooh
Pyromancy, okay. Hestu's maracas. This game is sick
Okay, let me let me take a quick look and see what I would rate this right now out of 10
I probably would give it like a four
Yeah, I mean the only reason it's not getting a zero is so people don't get really mad when I give it a low score
I think a four is okay
But no, this is really fun. I like it a lot. This is this definitely it's pretty high
so far
It's just really fun. It's it's there's lots of fun things to do
Here are your maracas
Can we get a number that why would you want a number?
It's definitely better than the eight
It's 100 higher than an eight. It's somewhere between eight and ten. I just don't know which I don't know where
I need to keep going. This game is objectively better than elden ring. We'll see. I don't know
Inventory expansion. That's a huge deal. I have one
um, yeah
Oh, definitely weapon, right? I keep having so much trouble. I have so much trouble with weapons. No frames dropped either
In the last like 10 minutes
Is there scientists that we can explain how that's possible?
Okay
da na na na na
The weapon stash has been expanded good to know that's where I need to mark this, right?
Okay, i'm gonna stamp this a pin here. Yeah, I need to put a pin here. Uh, i'm gonna say this is
Uh this right? Okay, let's keep going. Are you gonna collect all 900 seeds?
I would be happy if I were to get the first boss on stream
Be real
I don't you guys all right. It's been it's been about five hours of this game. It's time to do the uh, the poll
Vote if you do you want to see more?
Elders I really almost said elden ring. Do you want to see more?
Breath of the wild
Would you like me to keep playing this? Would you like me to be what this what I play when I stream again?
Like the next stream the next stream that you see on this channel. Do you want it to be this?
We need a poll
Well, the one is yes two is no do you want this to be the next thing that I play like
On the next stream just keep going
A lot of people were I mean no internet problems probably uh booted a lot of you guys
But there were a lot of people here tonight a surprising amount of people so
You guys like it. I'll definitely keep playing it
I like it. So if you guys like it, then why not?
Yeah, use the pole load on that pole drying somewhere
Oh, this is kakariko village
Travel i'm sorry, but I seem to have twisted my ankle. All right. Sorry. You had to see me like that
Say traveler
Where'd you get that object hanging from your waist? I found it. I'm the dead guy that I killed
Okay, we've been waiting for you for a very long time. I must insist that you meet with our leader
Lady impa lady impa's house is below lantern falls just over there
In any case, it was a real honor to meet you. Nice to meet you, too
They probably have a shrine in here
Somewhere right I imagine
I want to do that for I like the shrines the most
Wow, that's a lot. That's 90. Damn
I cannot deny that
I can't deny that that's way too high to deny
Uh, so we're gonna keep playing breath of the wild. There's 120 shrines in the game
Wow
Yes, it looks like everybody voted
4 000 of you
89 said to play more. Um, but breath of the wild nice
Okay, that's uh, i'm i'm excited. I think
Why did I pretend to like it?
I'm gonna just break my switch with a hammer and then show everybody on twitter be like, I don't know
I dropped my switch. I fucking shattered. I have to play, uh multiverses instead shield of the mind's eye
Stop closing my stuff. I want hot mic hot mic
No, actually, i'm happy
It's a micro boss micro boss
Finally, I unlocked the dodge roll
Oh my god, finally. Wait, did I have it the whole time lorry rush?
What I didn't that's new
Do a backflip to avoid enemy attacks and create an opening to strike back
Yeah back pedal
I should probably not be using this
I hit the wrong button. I'm
Again, i'll say this again
I hate so badly that all the controllers like across the consoles the controllers are different
Like i'm pressing where b is on xbox and b is like I wish it was just universal
Button law. Yeah button rant. I know that's what i'm saying
It should be
You know what i'm saying?
Wait, I can parry at the right time
Well, I need a shield equipped first of all
Why am I forgetting how to play? Okay. Oh, it's because okay, right right right right right because I have this um
equipped
Am I a man or am I a muppet a muppet of a man?
Where's my inventory?
Cool
Uh, something's moving around my mouth
Guardian sword. Oh, hell. Yeah, i'm gonna store this for like 10 hours. I'm chewing my lip off camera. I'm sorry
Ooh
Drop it pretty cool looking pretty sweet gets pumped up get pumped get pumped up
Okay, opal a valuable ore. Yep. Yep. Yep. I'll lay one more and I can do something. Actually don't get pumped up
It's 9 30 pacific. It's pretty late chill out
I'm gonna stream for a little while like at least another hour or two. Maybe omega gaming weekend
I think we're gonna stop playing during omega gaming weekend
I'm not sure if it's gonna be a five-hour stream on omega sunday present sleeper. Just relax. Just chill. Just chill out. It's all good
Just chill mommy's hiding but i'll find her. I'm just I just skipped all the dialogue a man
Hmm, you have a sheikah slate. Could you be the hero? My grandmother told me about what was his name?
Oh
Arnold it's it's not i forgot it's bad
But whatever my name is paia i'm gonna it's a weird one tonight. I'm sorry
My grandma's been awaiting your return ever since I was little
Please hurry. It's me biggest fan of the nintendo switch here to save the world
It has been quite a long time. I am much older now
You remember me don't you?
I'm holding a lot of shit
Uh, yeah, of course man. I hit up all the uh, swag spots at the convention. I got the god of war bow
Legend of zelda sword the hearthstone card pack trinket. Oh man. I hit up every booth. I don't have any memory dearest link
Please come a bit closer max level of redditor
Uh, a hundred years ago the kingdom of hyrule was destroyed after you fell princess zelda's final wish was to place you in it
Wait, so I lost really and then alone. She went to face ganon
She entrusted me with some words. She wished to say to you
I've been waiting a hundred years to deliver the princess's message. What is it? However
These words which the princess risked her life to leave you
Well, if you are to hear them, you must be prepared to risk your life as well
I'm afraid that burden may be too much to bear while you are still without your memories
I'll leave the choice to you when you feel you are ready to receive the princess's message returned to me
What are they not a memory to your name yet?
You are as intent as ever to charge forward with only courage and justice on your side
You've not changed a bit once a hero always a hero very well. Here we go
He's gonna tell us everything long ago
history of the royal family is also the history of
calamity ganon a primal evil that has endured over the ages
This evil has been turned back time and again
The soul of a hero and a princess who carries the blood of the goddess
with the passage of time
Each conflict with ganon faded into legend
So listen closely as I tell you of this
Legend that occurred 10,000 years ago
What are the words? What's the secret sentence?
Was then their technological prowess to ensure the safety of the land
Should calamity ganon ever return?
They constructed four mechanical wonders that came to be known as the divine beasts
They also built a region of autonomous weapons
Called guardians those are things that I was fighting the shoot lasers was for
Where's my little fairy friend? No, but that's the one with the elmo voice
Music's pretty uh
The darkness delivered his final blow
The princess used her sacred power to seal away
calamity ganon
Okay, we strove to follow the lead of our ancestors of 10,000 years prior. Okay, but in the end
Despite our best efforts and careful planning we underestimated his power in order to avoid making that grave mistake again
The princess left you these words
Free the four divine beasts is what she said
What the heck?
Berked up a little bit on that one
The four divine beasts are the ancient shika weapons wielded by the four champions who ganon defeated
va
radania controlled by
the rook of the gorons the divine beast of va meadow
Controlled by a rivale of the rito the divine beast va ruta controlled by mipha of the zora
And the divine beast va neboros controlled by urbosa of the gerudo
Extremely ill-advised to face ganon without the power of the divine beast to help you
You must infiltrate the divine beast that were stolen away by ganon 100 years ago and bring them back to our side
Or hold left trigger and step forward hold left trigger step forward and teleport across the entire game
And kill the final boss in one swing and beat the game in four minutes more information about these divine beasts
Can be found by locating the four races scattered across hyrule. My goodness. This was big dude. You want a hit of my jewel pod
Oh, bro. Yeah, let me see
You got handed over man. Thanks, dude. Cool. All right. Cool this thing here that's on the ground
Don't stop doing that. Come on. Gwen. Yeah, do you mind put that up?
The device princess elda left you is your guide and also your memory now
Let's see someone at the research lab in hateno village might be able to help you
Where's that across the whole world one of the very few places that avoided suffering significant damage during the great calamity
A lot of quests get mario kart installed
It's freddy dreads birthday. Happy birthday freddy dread. What's up? Uh, hey
Oh, sorry. Hold on. I got stuck on the door. I got all this swag. Sorry. Should I talk master link?
Whatever is the matter at this hour dark magic preys upon the land when darkness falls
Please promise to take care
Read the book by the door
journal of various worries
Well, my wife left me today. The last thing she said to me was what's more important cuckoos or me?
I chose the cuckoos painter unfamiliar to any of us has arrived in the village
He claims he is searching for the great fairy's fountain, but that's near where the village's spirit protector resides
We must make sure the outsider doesn't learn the location of the fountain or the two shrines near it
That new guy in town looks like he really knows how to tune a bow
I hope he comes by and knocks an arrow for me. It's been way too long. I'm just gonna read this
All right. Let's check. Where's that? I want another shrine. Okay
We need to protect lady impa
Technology became the key to sealing ganon away during the great calamity some 10 000 years ago
Okay
Okay. All right. Okay beef. What what goat butter?
Oh goat cheese is so gross goat cheese is fucking vile
I honest to god I feel like everybody that eats people pretend to like goat cheese you pretend to like it
I'm i'm so serious. I will die on this hill goat cheese does not it tastes like dirt
It tastes like dirt. It tastes like dirt from the ground peep. I swear to god people pretend to like goat cheese
They don't actually like it. They just like oh, oh goat cheese is on that. No, you don't actually I know you don't like it
It tastes like dirt
It's fucking I hate it. It's one of my least favorite things in the world
it
Goat cheese is one of those things
That overpowers every single thing on the plate
It is unbearable if there's goat cheese on something. All you're going to taste is goat cheese. It's just going to be that like
Like dirt like rotten dirt taste. Oh my god. It's so awful. That's an incredibly wrong opinion
I'm i'm sorry goat cheese is fucking filthy. I hate it more than anything
That's a rare germa l. No, it's a it's a it's a common germa win
Get a poll going. I want to know I want to know how many people here actually like goat cheese. Come on
Well, yeah pile it up on a cracker then. Yeah. Oh, yeah goat cheese. Yeah
Oh goat cheese, bro. I love it
Oh, dude, I would i'll eat a ton of it on a cracker. Of course I would
Yeah, right
Goat cheese. Yes or no feta is not goat cheese. It is not feta is not goat cheese feta is not goat cheese
I'm sorry. That's incorrect
Feta is not goat cheese. Incorrect. Feta is not goat cheese incorrect
germa l
Absolute germa l for real
We do this every time i'm just telling you right now. I cannot believe people like that
What's the poll at?
I'm fucking believable. I cannot believe that half of you like goat cheese. There's no way
I don't find that to be possible. No way
I must be one of those people that has the the piece of dna in my body
Where when you eat cilantro, it's like you're eating soap and you want to throw up
If goat cheese is in something it ruins the entire dish. It's so awful. It's so awful
No way. I'm shocked at this 51 think goat cheese is good. It is it is like
I feel like i'm eating paint
You eat mcdonald's l take
Yeah, just wait till mcdonald's comes out with a burger with goat cheese on it. I swear to god. It'll probably happen soon
Oh the mcdonald's, uh, the mcdonald's, uh fucking
You know burger with
Goat cheese is spread. Yeah, whatever. Oh, hey, holy. Yeah, it's you know what I mean? It's kind of it's happening
Yeah, just wait. Just wait for the cilantro goat cheese fucking
Shit burger good bit. I couldn't think of anything to say. I just I hate goat cheese
It sucks every time it's on anything
You eat mcdonald's mcdonald's is fucking delicious
Oh, I hate it
I just think of the way that it feels when you when you eat a piece of goat cheese
It's like poison
Any listen i'm gonna i'll move on in a second. I promise i'll move on in a second. I promise this is really important
If it wasn't so powerful
So, you know when you take a bite of food and it takes a second
It's like oh i'm going to take a bite of this whatever's on it this tomato this lettuce or onion peppers or meat
Turkey cheese doesn't matter
When you take a bite of food, it takes a second. It's like, oh, okay. Here are the flavors
That's the tomato. I can taste that that's what beef tastes like that's what chicken tastes like
goat cheese is this immediate
immediate like
Flavor it's it's like right when it touches your lip. It's just like oh what's on this
Goat cheese
It's like it's immediately. It's just so powerful and it hits me. It's so strong
It's like oh, it's like grinding up a fucking weed and just like oh man. What's that?
Oh my god. Okay. That's that's very heavy
It's I whatever goat cheese is the ground up pot version of cheese. It just stinks and it tastes it just
What was the final of the poll?
It's it. Yeah. Yeah, we got some mods in here that know what they're talking about. It takes me out of every dish
because the second that the goat cheese hits it
Just paints over everything else. Okay. Well, I don't want to buy any of this
Bro, you literally drank urine
When did I drink piss on stream?
When did I drink pee? I drank pee on stream
when
He doesn't remember when did I drink pee?
It was the pee drinking stream event
Oh
Right, right, right
But that's for an event though
I remember. Yeah, I remember I was trying to see if I could be I could be my own water filter, right?
I thought that like I could filter out shit and drink the pee and stuff and it was cleaning the
Essentially, I was drinking pee because I was trying to be my own filter
Um my own water filter
Oh speaking of water filters. This is weird. I was gonna tweet this but I didn't because it was kind of odd
Maybe i'll put the picture up here
So I got these water quality test strips
Just to test the water. It's like oh 16 in one test strips
So I pissed on one for a joke and to see like what my like fucking vitamin levels were and um
It was kind of fucked up. There was a shitload of lead in my piss. Is that bad?
I just like I pissed on one and I just like shook it and I was like what and there was a shitload of lead
The lead indicator was really high. Is that bad? Is that actually bad? Like hold on. Let me show you put the picture up
I actually might not be able to get it. Ask a doctor that explains a lot that explains a lot. No, it doesn't shut up
Get out of here. I I actually it was bright red and bright red was like you have a bunch of lead in your piss
No, but it's not it's not a hold on. It's not a piss test. It was a water
Quality test where you dunk it in like whatever your water is and then you read it
It's probably not accurate, right? No, the piss wasn't red. I think it's the saline
No, you guys have fucking up this whole story. Hold on. Let me
I bought water. Okay, this is we're playing a game of telephone and i'm the only one talking
How are you guys miss construing this I got water quality test strips
I peed on one the one that I pissed on said there was lead. It was huge bright red like alarm lead
Hold on. Give me a second. We'll go over this
One sec. All right. Hold on actually give me one second
All right, let me i'm gonna get let me turn off my camera and turn this off. This is I don't want this is weird
Is this weird that i'm doing this and showing this to you probably hold on I need to like upload them
Hold on. Is there any piss in the image? No, there's no piss in the image
All right. I got them uploaded and by uploaded it means uh, okay
All right. Hold on. Okay. Wait, i'm being told not to do this because is this to s it is piss on this
Wait, wait, don't show don't show it's wet with piss. Is that to s?
All right. Yeah, I can't show this. Yeah, actually, I definitely can't show this. There's like piss all over it. Yeah, never mind
blur it out
You should then tweet it then
Well, I get banned on twitch if I tweet out a picture that I something that I pissed on
I don't know. I'm concerned about that. That's freaking me out
anyways
Uh, maybe i'll tweet it. Maybe i'll tweet it later draw a diagram show us you're a coward
I'm a i'm a guy that wants to keep his twitch channel intact
Maybe i'll ask somebody at twitch. That's kind of a weird email
Hey, I pissed on like a water quality test strip and it's this p all over the image
Can I show like a piss thing that I did?
And by the way, take a look at the fucking twitch servers if you could
But yeah, no, I pissed on one for real and it said that my lead was off the charts
I need to yeah, where's that fountain? Is the fountain right? What's this?
Dude, shut up. This is gross
Yeah, it's it's heart container
That's definitely something to worry about
I I mean i'm kind of fucking around because
I've had my piss tested from a doctor within the last month or two
You know, right like I peed into a cup in the last month
By the way, my water has been tested. There's no lead in it. That's why I got the strips. Nice
Okay, where's that fountain?
Do they test it for lead?
I don't know, man
I mean nothing. I'm not there's no source of lead that i'm being exposed to
My water's been tested. There's no lead
Oh, we got a raid from point crow
Thanks micro
Welcome everybody
Uh, but I don't do they test you piss for lead
No, thanks a lot point girl
If you if you're just joining us, I i've pissed on a water quality test strip
uh
This is for a joke for fun. I just thought it would be funny and it turns out this is shit a little lead in my pee
Um, I could be like, I don't know if it's false positive or I don't know what it means
but
um
It's all right
All right. Can I cook?
All right. So this is uh, all right this and monster parts. Do I have any monster parts? Yes
All right, so this would give me a cool, uh
potion, right
What I thought it said it heightens your senses so you can move about so I thought
I thought it meant it was like a sneak potion or something. All right, let's make some apples
Do you have the 1987 garfield mug? It could be related to lead. No, I don't have the 1987 garfield mug
That has lead paint
Is that real?
Yeah, somebody just said dude those things are tested for water not urine. You're fine
Imagine going to the doctor being like hey doc
Yeah, I just like i'm just coming in today virgin care because I see I peed on a water test strip as a joke
And yeah here I brought it in see and it says I got lead in my pee
I'm just thinking maybe I could get like a real lead test
That's when you get one of these
iced
Okay
Sure. We'll test you for lead
Jesus and then he's like good and he turns around and he closes the door fucking
hard behind him
He closes the door fucking hard. It's like
All right, where's the
They're getting big. Ooh, this is cool
Where's the fountain?
There's two shrines in the fountain. I gotta go so far away. Where's the fountain fountain fountain store in
Ooh, I want to go there
If I can get this stupid nintendo switch shirt off
I mean, it's not stupid. Switch is a great console
What do you got? God go cheese is so disgusting
Okay, larry collection, okay, I want to how do I buy it
Don't just walk up to it. Ooh hood. I'm like 17 bucks
Can I sell
Don't really have anything. I can't really sell anything
I could sell some opals and shit, right?
You just don't like anything that doesn't have the most basic flavor profile. I love fish. I love
salmon
bass trout
You guys don't know the basic flavor profiles
I'm a huge fan of
tuna fish
I got that tuna steak
Basic how basic is it's like as like a sea bass flavor. What are you talking about? I actually hate sea bass. I'm just pretending
Um, I love tuna though
I can't afford anything
Basic flavor profiles. No, i'm sorry. I just don't think that like hey this flavor this flavor profile is crazy and weird
Therefore I should eat it
You have the diet of a brown bear
and
one of the strongest most feared
Creatures on the planet hyper intelligent hyper strong and
Yeah, what's your problem then who eats goat cheese?
goat cheese
Name me an animal animal kingdom of these goat cheese and how strong are they?
Oh the bear with the yeah the bear with the fucking monocle with his goat cheese and caviar. Oh, yes
What are you talking about
meat potatoes
Lettuce and fucking gravy
spinach
And radishes and i'm alive and i'm human
I like to eat too and I like to have children
I'm here and i'm coming
Tell the gems. All right, let me I need to play the game. Can I please play the game for like at least 10 minutes?
Somebody help me. Where's the fountain?
Oh
What's happening what's happening I fucking kill every last one of you
So
What are you painting?
Great
I hear there's a great fairy fountain somewhere near this village. I hear it's breathed. Where is it then?
Now if it was an outsider like me to begin
Just all non-sequiturs the last hour
somebody help
I'm stuck in non-sequitur. Andy. Like I gotta get out of this
Near the village
It's probably over here. Wasn't the the shrine where's my horse? It's the lead
and I eat lead too
Sir, sir link
like cuckoos
My precious cuckoos
They haven't come home yet
Okay, what do I do?
I'm not doing that. I don't care. I'm gonna get like 50 dollars. I don't want it
It's the 1987 garfield mug
Pass the shrine up the hill in the forest. Oh, thank you
Pass the shrine up the hill in the forest
So you mean like in here?
man
Get a man. Thanks. Get a man dude
Get a man
up here
Is there any backseat enforcement? Um, I just I I have to get out of this non-sequitur andy thing
And um, I just just tell me where to go like for the next two
This horse doesn't want to walk in the right direction
Am I going the right way?
Up here into the left. The horse controls are so ridiculous. This is so hard
It's gonna take a lot of getting used to you can't turn
it's
I could have walked by now other way other way up the hill
Can be up here
No
wrong way
No wrong way
To go northeast so you mean up this way
up here
Yes
Thanks
Okay, so pass the shrine up the hill
the hill
Up this hill
I'm getting i'm not getting any beeps
Please don't fall off. We're in trouble. How do we how do I solve how do I fix this?
Is there like a thing I can eat that like takes me to the last bonfire? How do I fix this?
Into the forest?
Oh shit
Oh, this is bad. This is bad. This is bad. This is bad. This is bad. This is bad. This is bad
Um, I think we're in trouble. I think we're in trouble
Is the horse still alive
Please tell me the horse is still alive. Is the horse gonna be alive?
I have to get off the horse. The horse sucks though. I can't control it. Okay, the forest
Past here up this way over here
Here's a forest. I'm getting off the horse. I can't die. I'm I go slower
And just running
Okay
Who found it?
So what what do we got here?
Okay
There's a ball somewhere
Legendary owl
Blue nightshade cook with the dew increase your stealth cool
relax
Okay
I'm not getting any beeps from my thing
There are two shrines like down in the fountain under the fairy fountain
Is that one down there? Is that it right there?
That's it right there, right? Yeah, that's it
um
A lot of stuff here. That's not a
Endura carrot
highly crunchy
Silent princess, okay
A lot of materials over here
Can you catch the fairy?
What is this?
Boy, sweet boy
Please listen to my story. I am the great fairy cotera
This place was once a beautiful spring
But as time passed fewer and fewer travelers arrived to offer me rupees
As a result, my power has abandoned me. I'm nearly powerless now
I need rupees
All I need is a hundred rupees. I don't have any that is tragic
I need to mark this on the map
Uh, i'm gonna say
Is it a person?
Okay
Where is that shrine?
Pay her sell the gems. I don't have 17 rupees guys. What are you talking about?
I don't know if it's okay. I don't think I can do it. I don't think I can do it
I gotta head this way though
I'm gonna fast travel to here. I'm gonna go this way
That feels like the safest place to go
You're a quitter sell everything sell stuff. Oh my goodness fine. Is it worth it?
Is it actually worth it?
Where's the general store?
I have a few opals I can sell
Uh, i'll sell
two opals
Now let's go back and and give the rupees
Horses love apples and carrots
Yeah
Come over here. I'll give you i'll give you carrot
Carrot come get a carrot
Come here here. You just you took the eye. Oh, okay. Cool. You liked it
Did you take it without permission come back? Oh, I can't just take all these pumpkins
All right. Now i'm gonna go back to here
Uh-huh. So i gotta go past the shrine
Up here, right?
Just running there's no point the horse it doesn't like me
All right, so i'm gonna go this way i'm gonna glide back over there and we'll pay it. Let's see
I'm hungry. What should I eat?
You mentioned before maybe
Might be a mcdonald's kind of night
Piss off all the goat cheese enjoyers goat cheese with a side of lead paint
All right. Here we go. 100 rupees for you
What are you gonna do for me?
Here you go
Is that a mistake okay
What a feeling that first breath of fresh air after an eternity of decay
It's just so intoxicating thanks to you have been returned to my former glory
And as they say one good turn deserves another I can help you allow me to enhance your clothing. No, not this clothing
Don't enhance my nintendo switch t-shirt, please
No, I don't want you to no do not enhance the switch shirt. Oh, I see you have a nintendo switch shirt
Yes, let's give that plus two defense so you can never take it off
Are you wearing makeup?
No, I have just this camera has filters on it
All right. I'm gonna go this way. We're gonna get on the road my horse around frank. I can't hear your call
Why not?
Why what are you gonna quest for me now? All right actual gameplay coming up here interesting
I have to go. I want nothing to do with you. I I have to play the game. I'm not doing that because another side quest
Uh, I want to get my horse frank
Let's go frank. All right, so i'm gonna go right here at the fork
And go from here feed. I fed him a carrot already
All right. Here we go
Take a right here. See if you can find another shrine. That'd be pretty cool
Hold on here
Choo-choo jelly actually the spears are my favorite weapons in this game right now. This thing is great
Forget about the swords. These are way better
Cool, oh another tower over there
I want to find a shrine my favorite part
Got you watch out this monster watch out
Have you already been to the spring of wisdom?
It is known that princess elda visited the spring in prayer. I have a great deal of love and respect for her
Don't worry. I got it
That was close
Ooh
Let's investigate dude. See you the bombs are so good. What one more people people over here
What the fuck jeremy
What the fuck are you doing? Why did you do that? I didn't want to press that fucking button. I'm actually pissed right now
I'm pissed
My god that hurt
There we go. Man that guy was hard
Soldier's shield cool
This thing open yet? No
Yeah
Are they mcdonald's you guys feeling mcdonald's? What about like wendy's burger king? What do you feel like?
Opal nice this ruins over there, too
Um, you should get some goat cheese. No, I don't think so blinking up there
Okay, i'm gonna check the ruins right i'm gonna check the ruins might be something there
mcgoat cheese
Gonna come alive ancient spring ancient screw
Ooh, you dropped the claymore. Nice. Yes say euro euro euro. Yeah, it's euro
It's like euro right euro euro not gyro
everybody calls
Um
I mean these torch
It's euro. Yeah euro. Holy shit claymore claymore claymore clayma. Okay. Well anything else here? It's euro
Okay
Try shield surfing. I don't even know what that means, but it sounds cool
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat. Oh, man
I still got it even these many years later really something in here
Wild horses, I want the blue horse shit
What
I don't think i'm not strong enough. I was soothing
I need more stamina come see fort hateno. I take it. That's right. It's worth seeing. Okay
Everyone's got to come and pay their respects at least once in life, right?
Yeah, let's go
Ancient stuff should I be collecting as many of these as I can or is this a waste of time?
Yes, okay
So it's worth getting all these
Very worth it. Okay a lot. They're extremely useful. All right
Did you know did you get new clothes I did not I did not please i'm begging you try to shield surf
Um, oh, there's another raid too from uh from automated. Thank you auto
I didn't see that either
Probably talking about goat cheese and shit pissing everybody off
Are you mad at me that I don't like goat cheese?
I hope now we can still be friends, right?
Like we can still be friends, right?
Just kidding. I can be friends somebody needs fucking
Yeah, I think that's possible for me. Nope
All right, I need a tower
Or this is far away cook those carrots
I should cook a lot of things that I have right? Okay
Cook it cook with it to increase your stealth
Um like this could I do like this?
What happens if I do that?
carrots and
flowers
fried wild greens
Cool. No
Oh, what if I do this?
Sneaky fried wild greens cool. So wait
What if I do this? This would be interesting. Can I just make like a super huge potion?
Like 10. Oh, that's 10 minutes. All right, that's cool
So I get it
very cool
so if I do a mushroom
and this
then i'll have food that heals me and
Gives me stealth
Right sneaky steamed mushrooms. I got it get it. That's really cool. I like it. You don't like feta. I do like feta
That is not goat cheese. It has a completely different flavor profile. It's sheep
It's sheep cheese. I did that sheep is not a goat
The sheep is not a goat. Do you need what do we need to go over the animals again?
A is for alligator B is for
Bear S is for sheep G is for goat
That was mean
Are you playing on switch or pc? This is not on pc. It's on switch, right? Yeah, it's only on nintendo
Point of interest. What's this?
Kind of got hit once. Is it an emulator?
Um, I can sleep in here. Is there a chest or anything?
What is diary?
Ancient text when a dark light resides in the cursed statue's eyes pierce its gaze to purge the seal from the shrine
Good to know the reason to use an emulator is for 4k 60 fps texture packs
Okay, let me guess you caught one of the great dr
Calypso's groundbreaking research and just had to meet him for yourself. Huh? No, don't tell me you never heard of me
I have not I use an emulator bat chest. I'm just playing the game on switch. Okay
Dr. Calyp if you please I didn't study my rear end off to be called. Mr. Calyp
Everyone forgets i'm a doctor for some reason
And since you asked i'll inform you that i'm engaged in analyzing ancient texts. I've been time for idle chit chat
doctor calip
Who's he talking to my mom my mom's watching right now. I have her
Text her right here
He's my mom doesn't know how to use twitch chat. So she chats
Right with but with text
She texts me
And I use that as a chat
Yeah, let's go
What's the last thing she said?
Don't listen to them, sweetheart
McDonald's is delicious. We're a mcdonald's family
All the way through I never used to cook with goat cheese because it was disgusting cheddar cheese where it's at
Love mom. Yeah
Monka s she said monka s like five times before that. I don't know what she meant
Yeah, they're like
30 to 40 minutes apart each one like six times
Okay, so uh, yeah
If I don't have a bow equipped why not dude if I if I was an adventurer I definitely would use a bow 100
What if you get attacked up close good luck. Oh shit. Here we go. He's making noises
Uh, what is over here? Are you gonna wrap this stream up? It's god damn. I almost drowned. Okay
Uh, uh, maybe like another half hour
I'm still good
Seven hours or so maybe seven and a half hours something like that. You're addicted. It's a good. It's a fun game
It's genuinely a fun game. It's very nice
What's that
Oh, it's an acorn
You said that yesterday and I left and you stream for another nine hours. Yeah, that was a rare occasion though
Where's the tower here?
Uh, i'm gonna keep wandering this way
Oh, hi, you should join the yiga clan. You don't know. I mean I do know
Brave group of warriors founded by master
Koga and dedicated defending a hero throughout long. Why I didn't hit family guy death pose
I should have just fought that was weird. I thought I could just boom just blow them crazy
They fly and you know, I guess you can't is that just a random occurrence? That's pretty cool
I just missed. Yeah, I felt like it could have hit though
Right on top of it. Your skin suit looks accurate to a human today. Thanks
No, never mind. I'm not gonna do that weird
Take what was on that? That was a bug. Oh, hold on. Hell. Yeah more amber. You should buy the broadcasting rights to family guy
Uh, that would be nice to hit up
Box
And see whether you know the 10 to 25 million dollars I probably would need
For like a month
Oh, I can't carry any more melee weapons. I have a lot of these claim wars. I'll just get rid of it
Uh, that thing's 18 damage 16 damage
shit
Back swing hit me and killed me in one hit guys. Is that somebody on a horse?
Oh my goodness, there's a lot of them. What are they all attacking? Holy shit that guy went
I'm doing dark souls controls. I keep on hitting right stick to try to lock on
These guys are way higher level than me. Oh my god. I'm just fucking running. What's the point help?
What's happening
Is there stuff on your cart? Do you have stuff on your cart?
What the fuck is going on? This isn't supposed to be hard. You die in one swing. What do you mean?
It's not hard. Okay, I die in one hit with my nintendo switch
Polyester t-shirt on oh he took care of it. No, I didn't they telegraph for two seconds. I'm
Do I die in one hit?
This character sucks. I'm trying to dodge it and do the fucking parry thing
I'm trying to do the flurry dodge. Whatever. I have a better idea
Go put on something that is made out of anything besides
Like something that I got it fucking old navy
Goodbye fuck out of here
Let's go
Get the tower. Yeah, where where is it? I'm trying to look wait. Let me climb up here and see if I can see it
I'm up here
Oh
Okay, i'm not gonna glide
I would not have made it
Do you enjoy the scenery? It's beautiful. The 30 fps is not a big deal. It's doable. It's workable. It's fine. I think it's fine
Who's the sniff guy?
Mop
slide
That guy was a lot scarier than he
Okay
Moblin fang moblin horn. Okay moblin. I don't know. I don't care pink got you. Oh, you have a weapon
They let him no no
No
I can definitely do it. Just stop jumping
Hang out up here for a sec. I should be able to stand on this, right?
I don't I I don't have to go around. I bet you I can stand up here right there
Come on. I have to go all the way around. I just should have died
I probably would have ended up up there again. All right, I think I can get this here we go
Don't do the jump thing. That'd be fine. Yeah, I can definitely make it from here. Oh my god. That's a lot
Oh shit. Nice. Okay, so from wait, hold on
So from here, I should be able to stand on top of this and go up from here
I think I got it straight up. No jumping. We stand right up there. I just hope so right on this lip
I don't think so for a sec. All right, got my fucking gold by the way sapphire
Amber sapphire rock salt pretty nice check this house. Oh, it's an enemy
Ooh
What octoballoons and bass cool? Okay. Let me get my bearings and see where I am a little hut right here
I need to get back over there. Let me check the house
10 arrows actually really useful. All right
I'm so screwed though. I need to somehow get back up the whole mountain
Is this I could probably teleport and then go again. What would this be for?
What's what is this for?
Wouldn't just be here for no reason. I have to set it back in the slot
Oh, I found another um seed monster
Fear a little guy's got no fear. I have to go all the way around right that sucks wouldn't mop
Wow, I just died to a mop
All right, I gotta start using the better weapons I need a shield things way better what an actual item
It's not like the the handle of a fridge
Or a tire iron
Pure offense. Yeah
These guys do so much the huge guys don't do that much damage
those
the blue
Um trolls, whatever they are. They they do so much damage. Where did I end up? Okay, let me just the horse
I'm just going up that way and i'm gonna go turn the thing on
I'll come back and explore this later
I need armor
See that did one quarter of a heart not my entire health pool
Stupid. All right, let's go wrap around and turn the thing on
Where is it? I lost it these things tower over the whole horizon. Why can I not see it?
I gotta go around here to the right
And just i'm only going for that
And then when I get up there, that's i'm gonna probably gonna call it. It's a solid seven hours
This is great though. This is a good game
We will definitely continue playing breath of the wild
Yeah, definitely. What's the average time to take to beat it?
This could just turn into the elden ring
Right where I just play I just play it every other day or something like that
Probably like about 100 hours
Oh
Oh, no
He threw a bomb
Okay. Thank god. It didn't directly hit me
Oh my god, get me the fuck out of here
That's a bow. I don't what's that boat brennic bow. Cool
The chest over here too, uh, how do I get up there and I climb the tree
Okay
No ladder as it glides from there from the yeah pretty far away
Uh, i'll go from the top. It makes more sense, right?
All right. What do you got in here? Ten arrows. I'll take it. All right now we gotta go
That way geez, how am I gonna hopefully I can get up here this way. Can you come to my birthday party?
Um, I don't think I can come to your birthday party. I can I can say happy birthday
Hope you have a good birthday
Whenever it is
One two, three, four five six seven
Scary tree don't if I died in the thorns
You could revoke my gaming license. Seriously
What's my opinion on greek yogurt? Um, it's it
It sucks. I'm not a big fan. I think it's gross
Um goats milk goat cheese, you know, i'm not i'm not a big fan
Um
I actually love greek yogurt. I love yogurt in general
You know what? I like that. I like um, I like kefir. I did not do this right. Just don't move. Hi
God I landed right on my neck
I landed it right on my neck
Almost there. You're doing good. Oh, this this game is just fun to play. All right now we can jump
Let go let go. That was bad. Do not jump
I need a coffee. I do not want to drink a coffee at 11 30 at night. That would be a mistake
I had one like six seven wait eight hours ago. How am I gonna get over this same exact fucking thing?
Should I I don't understand should I try the other side?
I'm drinking one of these i'm even going faster. I don't think i'm not even going faster. What the fuck is going on?
Rises to its peak under the hour of the hour of the blood moon
Aimless spirits of monsters slain in the name of the light return to flesh
It's a good thing. I'm a thousand feet above everything
I don't give a shit. I'm out. Look where I am
I'm protected up here. Why would I be concerned about that? I'm
2000 feet above sea level
Okay, so i'm gonna go i'm gonna do this
See if I can do this ready
Maybe smart maybe I climb this
No, oh, here we go. I got it
We're good. All right
And that's where we're gonna end the stream first impression breath of the wild. It's pretty great. I like it
I think it's really fun. I definitely want to do some more shrines. I definitely want to do
I want to fight like the first boss. It's very engaging. There's a lot to do and there it is
There's a there's your omega gaming weekend. It's kind of a regular stream here
Uh, and then uh, oh
Oh nice, okay, this map is huge are you gonna stream tomorrow?
Uh, I will not be streaming tomorrow. No the next time the channel will be live. What is today's date today is sunday
sunday the
under the 18th
This okay. Here's what's gonna happen. I will be back
on
Tuesday or wednesday
Let's say wednesday and I might surprise you with an omega early stream on tuesday
So let's just i'm gonna say wednesday
At 2 p.m pacific
But it could happen on tuesday, but don't put that in the sus because I don't want people to think that i'm gonna be there
So there it is
breath of the wilds thumbs up. It's fun
I very much enjoyed my time there
Uh, there were a lot of raids tonight. Thanks point crow. First of all automated
Grapefruit the three uh raids pretty chunky raids
And with that we'll uh, we'll call it here
Sorry for the internet bullshit. I don't I don't get it makes no sense
You see what happened from like 7 30 to like 8 15 pacific
It was all over the place, but it's been perfect for the last two or three hours. I don't get it
I always save it. Yeah, okay saving the game
So we I you know what I might open with something else for like an hour or two
And then move to breath of the wild
For like the remainder of the next like three four five hours of the stream on wednesday. We'll see i'm into it though
I'm very into it
Uh, I don't know if you heard it, but I literally walked off and died
All right. I'll see you guys on wednesday, maybe tuesday, but wednesday is what we're gonna say when is sorcery gonna be back
Yeah, there's a lot to do post the p-strip pic to twitter
No, no, no
Maybe on your birthday. Thanks for watching. See you soon everybody
I can't believe I streamed for 14 hours on friday into saturday. That was weird. That was I had a lot of fun though
All right. Good night guys call your mother take care of yourselves
Have a great remainder of what's left of this weekend here, which for most of you is is over
But have a good monday. Have a good tuesday
See you wednesday
See you later guys