Afternoon, everybody. I'll be on a swell a couple of days. Don't forget about the pre-stream bits.
Holy shit, don't... uh, yeah, don't forget about those. Oh my god. We... we... I just turned it on.
Wait, you... this is before the stream even went on. Uh, Fat Bossant. Fat Bossant. Fat Bossient.
I don't know, I'm saying your name like it's a croissant. Uh, thank you for the 50 dollars.
50 bucks from Fat Bossant. RIP January 23, 2019 at 7 43 p.m. The YouTube link here, let's just make
sure. Let's see what we're getting into here. All right, where even is that plane? Is this even
plane? I don't like this. So is that Eastern time? Does it count if I go back in time like
I did? Wednesday, January 23, at 7 43 p.m. But that could be local time.
Fate knows you moved any time zone other than EST. Fate predicted that you would move. Well,
whatever. Even if it is Eastern. Let's go by the original fate. That would mean that at 4...
at 4 43 tomorrow, I'm gonna be in this chair with my room duct taped. And I'm gonna be...
I had quite the Amazon order. Uh, if Amazon like wanted to like take a look at people
what they were buying. I bought like a hockey mask, duct tape, and like hockey pads.
Sometimes I look at my fucking orders that I put through and I go, my god, what am I doing?
I'm like a murderer. Like Jason. When do you think he gets those masks? He has an Amazon
subscription order that comes in like once or twice a month. Why are you playing hockey
in Vegas? Vegas has got a good hockey team. They just got one. The Golden Knights. But
regardless, thank you so much to Fat Bossiant for 5,000 bits before the stream even turned on.
The fact that you do just give that. Thanks a lot. Really. Thank you so fucking much for 50
dollars. And then P337R for 25 dollars. Thank you so much Peter for the 25 bucks. And then
Fat Bossiant said that they demand Tim Machine 9 for the next Jerma Rumble. And he's like,
he's traveling all over the world in different time periods. So he might show up. He might
not. Anyways, we're gonna play a game called, why don't we just switch to it so you know what
it is, Lifeline. This game is for PlayStation 2. It uses the PlayStation 2 microphone,
which is, was actually kind of hard to track down because there's only like two mics
that work with this game. And I couldn't really find an original PlayStation 2 one.
And I didn't really want an original PlayStation 2 one because I don't think it's that high
quality. It would probably misunderstand everything I was saying. So I had to get a,
an old Logitech PS2 headset and I tested it. It works. I know you're not seeing any
audio right now, but what's a bet. Thanks to the five community subs and Herbert,
both of you, five community subs, 10 in total here. You guys are fucking awesome. Yeah,
the audio is not on because you guys are gonna have to play a little game here
called capturing the PlayStation 2 through a little box from little box to capture card,
capture card to PC. There's going to be like a thousand milliseconds of audio delay.
So we're going to do a Dora the fucking Explorer here in the beginning where you
guys are going to help me turn and fix this shit. So for a second I thought it
didn't have a controller. I was like, well, that ruined everything. No, I got one right here.
So the, this is lifeline. It's a game. You, I don't even need a controller
because the whole game is used with your voice. Every single thing in the game. It's a voice
command voice activated game and it's like an action shooter and we're going to try to beat
the whole game. No, we're not. You might see me here for like five hours. I can't promise
that anyways. I'm ready to go. Let's go ahead and get started. Let me just get this
on. God, last time I wore a headset like this was like three months ago because I moved and I
had to get a similar one, but this is only for the PlayStation 2. Let's get an audio sync in
here before we do anything else. So here comes the audio and you guys are going to have
the fun job. I gotta make sure it's in the right spot. Okay. So let's do a little audio
sync test here. I'm going to press the start button. Not you. Hold on. Okay. Ready?
So how does that sound? You should be hearing a little like did it and did it in every time
it's selected. It's okay. That's good. All right. Now we're going to do a thing where I'm matching
my voice to it. Oh my God. Somebody's to give a hundred dollars. It's a, this is almost
two hundred dollars and I haven't even done anything. I just turned on a stream. Oh my
goodness. Vladimir. Vladimir, bad man. Thanks for the hundred dollars. 10,000 bits. Thank you.
I'm going to say thanks for the years of quality content, Jerma. Shame about your untimely death
tomorrow. I'll be just fine. I got a fat suit. I got hockey pads. I'm patting myself and I'm
going to sit here and we're going to just fucking read nursery rhymes or something.
I, I, I'll be just fine. I'll buy boxing gloves. But holy shit, Vladimir. Thank you
for the extreme amount of money. All of the, all of you guys. My God. All right, here we go.
Ready? One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. We lined up.
Almost good. Sounds fine. There's a tiny delay. All right. So you, is it my voice first or
is it game audio first? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. So my voice is first. So it's like,
let me, let me, this fixes it. See if it's okay. You ready? Oh my God. Oh no,
that's just like it's stream labs. I don't know why it takes like five minutes to show on screen
sometimes. Holy shit. I was about to lose my mind. All right. Ready? One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. One, two. Oh yeah. This game's gotta be fun. Oh yeah. This game's
gotta be fun. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good. All right. We're going.
New game. This is lifeline PlayStation two. Let's get the fuck going. What do you say?
New game. Show your face. No, I'm wicked ugly. I'm too ugly today. I've been feeling kind of
ill lately. They're going to hear me say this. I don't want them to hear me say this.
Two to three centimeters from your mouth. Two to three centimeters from my mouth it is.
The position of the microphone is crucial. This is crucial.
Dual shock two.
All right. Circle when speaking. Hold it down. You got it.
Okay. Speak when talk now appears. Say hello. Hello. Hello. Microphone done. I'm just kidding.
Hello. Hello. PlayStation. Lifeline. Oh, you get points for how good you say it.
I'm gonna do just fine. I'm gonna put on my like used car salesman voice
or my telemarketer voice. I'm gonna get. Just wait.
Give an order to the character. Walk. I can.
Run. That's not great.
Okay. Stop. How many tiers of good pronunciation are there?
Go to the table. I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
Look at the bottle. What? Fuck you. Turned out to be one. Like this names of objects
are revealed when instructions are given successfully. If you are not sure of the
name of an object, saying its dominant color or basic shape may work instead.
In this case, saying green bottle is better for recognition than simply saying
bottle. Once the name is revealed, you can give more specific instructions.
Check the wine. Why am I doing these so bad? Am I not saying it good enough? Do it faster.
Seems like nothing is unusual about the wine. When you find anything remotely curious,
it's best to check the item carefully. Additionally, certain objects can be
combined with various verbs when you give instructions. Drink the wine. Get the wine.
Oh god. Go back. I'm like, this is like an English lesson.
Remember when the enemy is detected, we will automatically move to the scene of battle.
So is it turn based or is it? Carefully observe the enemy while giving commands.
This thing doesn't have a head to stomach or a mouth. It's a shoe.
Carefully observe the shoe while getting attacked. Let's try making an actual attack.
Shoot. Jumped over it. Move left. Shoot head. I was waiting. It didn't do anything. Dodge.
This is going to be fun. Okay. Dodge and shoot. Should I do my like anime voice actor voice?
Is that better? It might be. Flee and recover. Shoot, shoot, shoot. Did I get them?
When multiple enemies appear, targeting can be prioritized with number one,
number two, et cetera. Number two. Number one. Okay. Let's shoot head. Shoot mouth.
Yeah. Yeah. Head shoot. Reload. Okay. How do I know what a weak spot is? Stomach. Stomach.
You should be aware of when giving commands. Why do I look like this?
Pay close attention to the following points. Pay attention to this because this is important
shit because I'm going to mess up a ton of these pronunciations. Use proper timing
when pressing and releasing the microphone button. Okay. Use the proper point volume.
Okay. Use clear pronunciation. This is just, this is a job interview instructions.
Make sure when you're at your interview, you talk with the proper voice volume.
Don't intimidate the interviewer. This concludes the tutorial. It does. All right. Let's go.
Let's go. Now we begin our tale. Let's go. Always immediately intimidate the interviewer
with a loud voice. Do your best Jim Carrey impression when you open the door to the
position. There's no subtitles. Not only was he one of the era's finest medical minds,
he also made contributions in alchemy, astrology, astronomy, and mysticism. When he was in his
thirties, he was said to have incredible healing abilities. That prompted him to adopt the name
of Perichelsus, superseding Kelsus, the famed doctor of ancient times. In his later years,
he is said to have gone on a journey of healing, visiting the terminally ill and
curing them. I'm not doing this voice.
It just pops up on screen. Bad. The narrator's like, what the fuck are you talking about?
That was perfect pronunciation. That was, was that actually Orson Welles? That was, this is
1998. No, this is 2004 guys. Pretty nice graphics. December 24th, 2029, 10 PM. That's
your new death date, Jeremy. Yeah, this is PlayStation 2 guys. Give it a little bit of
slack. It's PlayStation 2 being upscaled to like 720p or like 1080 nearly. Doesn't look that bad.
No, it doesn't. I mean, this little device that I have is pretty much works great.
I really don't know. I don't appreciate the long like Star Wars pause silence thing.
It was the same scene from a different angle. Is this the monitor room? Here we go. My
first command. Open. No, I'm not going to say that. That's so, that's too easy. That's
a very low hanging fruit. I'm not going to grab it. I'm reaching for the fucking
coconut that's up there. I'm not reaching for the banana. A wound. I can't read that.
Surveillance camera recording canceled.
Okay, I did that voice. That's, that's a much better example.
Today. So this occasion is extra meaningful for me. Today we mark the first day to the end
of our long running. That's me and Naomi. We were lucky to be invited to the space station
hotel. Cheers. Good evening. Don't drink it. Do you like a cocktail? No. How do I say no?
No, thank you. I don't drink. Naomi. Yeah. Why is she doing this?
But the government has been promising economic relief.
Why are you just watching unedited video footage of when you were here?
You're probably looking for something. Somebody, somebody did something bad.
This is when the aliens come in. The whole room shook violently and something crashed the party.
Red eyes. Insatiable hunger. They started eating guests. I heard it in my eyes. And then
I passed out. I can't believe we're spending Christmas in space. Thank you.
Oh, is that, is that some like exposition to tell us that that
separated from my beloved girlfriend? I can't even see. Okay, this is the security room.
I understand what this game is. Can anyone come in please?
I'm the security officer giving instructions. I'm just like the fat guy sitting there at
security detail. Hello. Hey. You don't sound like the regular guy.
Anyway, it doesn't matter who you listen. Will you please undo the lock?
I mean, you didn't say please. Okay. Understood. Please hurry.
Holy shit. What a fucking unbelievable game. This game. When did this game come up?
There's no way that just happened. Please disengage the lock on the store.
Uh, hold on a minute. I'm just currently processing some information here.
We can talk after I get out of here. Please disengage the lock door panel. Disengage. If you
press the button, you'll access the door panel and the button again. That will open the
panel for controlling. Oh, it's supposed to be a voice game. Operate to disengage the
detaining cell door lock to operate. Open the control panel. Disengage the lock on the store.
The lock is open. Saved at last. A real headcase security guard locked me up in there for over an
hour. Geez. I didn't know what was going to happen. So what's your story? Are you trapped
inside that monitor room? So we share the same dilemma. Oh, I wish I could have told
my story. And now? I would have talked her ear off. Uh, YDNA 10 community subs right now.
Thank you. It's not in here. 10 community subs. A lot of money. Thanks a lot. Huge thanks.
What are you looking for? I'm positive that it's here in this room. What is in the room?
It's locked. I'll take care of this. Stand back. Just like you ended the other one.
Yeah, I'm Superman. Look at how powerful I am. I can make red bars green and then
you can open them. Where are you going? Yeah, I can't. Yeah, I can't talk right now.
Where'd you get the gun? Here it is. You just have that. I should take care of any monsters.
Look, I'm in a bit of a hurry. Just wait there to be rescued. If we're lucky,
we'll see each other soon. Until then. Uh, that's not gonna happen. You're gonna
open this door and you're gonna need my help immediately. Get up. Okay, here we go.
Dodge right. Step back. Step back. Shoot right eye. Run left. Back. Shoot. Shoot left eye.
Shoot left eye. Shoot mouth. Back. Back. Dodge roll. Okay. Shoot left eye.
Shoot left eye. Shoot tail. Shoot tail. Shoot tail. Back. Run away.
Don't run away. Run away. Okay. Shoot middle eye. No, she did that on her own. Shoot middle eye.
Shoot middle eye. Back. Shoot mouth. Oh, shoot red eye. Back. Dodge left.
Dodge left. Shoot red eye. Shoot. Shoot. Shoot. Shoot eye. Shoot red eye. Reload.
Shoot the sans eye. Shoot red eye. Shoot red eye. Don't put that, what are you doing?
That's a dangerously close place to put your, don't put your head there.
My god, you're gonna be a heart attack later. What the fuck?
There, weren't you? You were with the girl in the dark blue dress.
That girl you were with, what was her name? Frank. Fred. Wendy. Wrong. That wasn't her name.
Oh, it's on the tip of my tongue. She didn't want to tell me. Agatha. I'm talking about
your girlfriend. I got lots of girlfriends, so I mean. That can't be true. What's your
girlfriend's name? I don't, I don't remember her name. I don't remember. That can't be true.
Come on, what's the name of that girl? I don't know. Nancy. Vicki. No, no, wrong name.
Vicki? Vicki. No, no, wrong name. Your girlfriend's name. Sarah. Sarah? No, that's
not it. Stacy. Stephanie. Wrong. It was three syllables. Jessica. Jessica. Wrong.
It was three syllables. Jennifer. Jennifer? No, no, wrong name. Help me out here, lady.
Come on, what's the name of that girl? Linda. Linda. Rhonda. No, that's not it.
It was three syllables. Come on, what's the name of that girl? Naomi.
Oh, and she. I wouldn't have got, we would have been there all day. I would have had to
reset the game if I didn't get cheated in chat. Well, no wonder, and all that commotion.
Me, I don't even remember how I managed to get out of the restaurant. I'm worried about her.
She may be in need of help somewhere. I didn't, I don't, I didn't even know.
Listen, can I ask for your help? Before escaping from the station hotel, there's something that
I have to find. Can you help me out as an operator, like the way you did before?
In return, I'll find your Naomi along the way. So it's a deal? I can count on your help?
SpongeBob meme. Punching over. Can I count on your help? You can call me Rio. Okay, glad
to meet you, operator. Are you ready? Oh, should have to say yes. I forgot. I did like
do everything. I guess there's no need for formal introductions. Oh, yes. Well, that's
fine. I won't fail in my search. All right, let's shut down the stream. That's the worst
joke. It was, it was a fake one. I was making a fake reference to a meme overuse thing.
Let's choose a password for ourselves. Oh, no. You don't know very much about this hotel,
do you? I need a password. I bet there's lots of things that'll confuse you while
we're searching. Like what should we be doing for instance? So in a situation like that,
let's see. Banana. Coconut. Say consultation. Consultation? If you say that, I'll explain
things to you. Okay? Try saying the word. This is just that movie with um. Say it please.
Consultation. Yep, a consultation. With Tom Cruise. We have to go search the station
hotel thoroughly after this. No, that's a fucking spoiler. We'll have to go everywhere.
I can't do movie and TV spoilers this stream. I intend to follow your instructions for
doing most things. But if your instructions are hard to understand, I'll get confused.
For instance, if you were to say go over there, I'd be like, which way is there?
I'd be like. So if you want me to go somewhere, I want you to say its name.
For example, in this room, there are places like the lockers and the table.
Four fridges. You know how you can just play maps in the monitor room?
Direct me where you want to go by the name on the map.
Okay. Do you understand? Not really, but yes. Okay. The map that you just saw, you can access
and display it on your monitor. If there's anything else you don't understand, check the
keyword list. That list records keywords and phrases that are extracted from our dialogue.
Not only that, the list already contains words in the operator's manual.
Of course, there are plenty of words that aren't on the list. Anyway,
how about giving me my first instruction? What should I do?
A lot of options here. Go to the bathroom. Yep. No, no, no. I don't mean like that.
That's not what I mean, guys. I mean, like I want to go into the bathroom.
She's currently walking around. She did it. Okay. Get a snack from the vending machine.
The vending machine. Okay. Bottom left vending machine receptacle.
These are the vending machines. Put hand in vending machine. Put hand in leftmost slot.
If there is something, it would be good. Nope. Too bad. It's empty. Dispenser.
Put hand in right dispenser. There was nothing. I'm disappointed.
I see something in there. Put hand in dispenser slot number three.
Put hand in dispenser. Put hand in dispenser. Grab item in dispenser.
Which dispenser do you mean? Put hand in first dispenser slot on the right.
I've checked it earlier. That was enough. Put hand in second from the right dispenser slot.
I've checked it earlier. That was enough. Middle right dispenser. The dispenser?
I don't know what you mean. Put hand in middle right dispenser.
I've checked it earlier. That was enough. Check all dispensers.
Which dispenser do you mean? Check third dispenser. Check third dispenser.
Which dispenser do you mean? Check currently selected dispenser.
Which dispenser do you mean? Check red dispenser. Which dispenser do you mean?
Check red dispenser. Which dispenser do you mean? Check red dispenser three.
Which dispenser do you mean? There's an item in there that I have to get.
Red left. That's not going to work. Pilot guy, thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you. Just coming in right now. Left red. I've checked it earlier. That was enough.
Just do it without the mic. Those of you that are just joining the stream,
I cannot move. It's only voice commands only. Check the third slot. It only says juice.
Everything sold out except for prune juice. Consultation. Wait a second. Can that
consultation wait? Let's check this first. No, I can't even get tech support. I'm on hold right
now. Okay, I'm going to try this again. Grab. You're too vague. I don't know what you mean.
Check dispenser slot three. Which dispenser do you mean? Look at right dispenser.
I've checked it earlier. That was enough. Check second from the right dispenser.
I've checked it earlier. That was enough. The item's right here. Just dispenser three.
I've said every single one of these. Check dispenser three. Which dispenser do you mean?
That's what happens. Right vending machine. These are the vending machines. Grab item red
from left. No, that's like I got hit the head with a hammer and just said five random words.
Pick up item from dispenser. I've checked it earlier. That was enough. I can't select them
either. There's an item in here. She needs to get this. There is an item in the dispenser
on the right. No response. Germa, your right is her left. No, it isn't. What? Check second
dispenser from the right. There's something in here. Okay, I said that like 15 times.
Back up. Pardon me? Do what to what? Sure you did. I did. I said it like five, 10 times.
Leave. What is it? Leave. Leave the room? Okay. No. No, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop what you're
doing. The lockers. Okay. Oh no, not like I'll, this is Sesame Street bullshit all over again.
Open locker all the way to the right. I checked that earlier. Oh god. I didn't even
say anything. A license plate. This is a chip. I'll take this. Good. It might be useful later.
I really like your hat. The writing's too sloppy for me to read.
Why don't you analyze it? Sure thing. I'll analyze. December reading material
purchases electronic newspaper magazines. All reading materials are to be returned to the
designated spaces after use. Grab guard's note. It's a handwritten note. It doesn't look
important. To you, but it's reading material for me when I'm on the can. Um, okay. I mean,
do I got a map? Where's my map? Okay, here's, there's some basic commands we got here.
Oh, I gotta like it. Okay. This is, this is giving me some tips on how to play.
Javadab coming in with 10 community subs. I guess you're stumped too, operator.
Javadab coming in with 10 community subs. What do you think about that?
Nothing at all. But thank you, Javadab. A lot of big subs and big bits
very early in the stream. So thank you guys. Why were you in that holding cell?
Holding cell one. Okay. You're gonna go stop. Stop. Yes. Video recording, disc, handgun,
heel capsule. I need like the, I need a map. Here we go. Is he actually watching me?
Go into the living room. Okay. I'll leave. Check table. The table. Okay. Look at all
this shit on here. Drink coffee. Drink liquid in cup. Huh? This strange command. I don't get
it. Well, you don't get it obviously. Anything here of value that I need to get? Check document.
Pardon me? Do what to what? Look at magazine. This is a really popular entertainment magazine.
I read it occasionally. Find fax machine. Fax me magazine. The vending machine. Okay. No,
stop, stop, stop, stop. Stop. Yes. Check table. The table. Okay. Grab cup. Shooting will just put
a hole through it. Get in the clown car. 10 community subs. Thank you. Thank you to the
10 community subs clown car. Grab cup. This paper cup must be from the vending machine.
It's empty. I'm not gonna say that. So there's nothing in it. I can't take it though. Take
cup. I don't intend to take anything except what I need. But that's not what I'm telling you to do.
Check papers. Paper? There's a lot of paper around. Which do you mean? Check left paper.
It's a report by the security guards. Tell her to bark like a dog. Little dog or big dog?
Scream as loud as you can. Let's see. This month's features on chips. I collect them too.
Scream. When you say it that way, I don't know what you mean. So what is that? That's report.
What does that mean? A tablet? Check tablet. Are you talking about this? Yes. Yes. By the
desks? Okay. What? No, no, no, no, no. I was answering a question. That's all right. Grab
notebook. It's the security guards notebook. Like a diary. I'm not interested. Sure. Okay.
We've got some consoles here. Activate left console. Not a chance. It's totally wrecked.
All of them? All these PCs all fucked up. Caution. Malfunction caused by abnormal external
shock. Yeah. What else is in here? Table. This is pretty much it. So we got, we got the stuff
we needed. Let's take, you know, holding cell. Go now. Holding cell one. Okay. Faster. By the
desks. Okay. Now holding cell one. Holding cell one. Okay. Run to holding cell one. Holding cell
one. Okay. How do I save the game? You guys are with the community subs tonight. Holy shit. Jamie,
five community subs. Thank you. Run to holding cell one. Holding cell one. Okay.
Huh? What's this? Grab the Mio water enhancer. What even is that? Holding cell two. Holding
cell two. Right. There's nothing in here. I checked from corner to corner while I was locked up.
Check holding cell three. Okay. Holding cell three. This place is empty. Let's check
somewhere else. Moron. I am walking. All right. Well I got it. Holding cell one. I checked
everything. So now we gotta go. I'm not sure where the hell. How do I get? Go to the
hallway. Okay. I'll leave. Never checked tablets. That's the save point? I told her to look at it
and she looked at me with. Operator, look. Emergency shutters have been activated all over
the place. It doesn't look like we'll be able to go on a casual tour of the station.
First there's something I'd like you to confirm. What's that? Please analyze this video disc.
Interview footage. December 24th to the observatory restaurant.
On. Okay. You managed to get back. You couldn't just flip the phone up yourself.
Do you see the woman who's interviewing Prime Minister Takayama?
Her name is Helen Johnson. She's a big wig announcer for a major TV network.
I need to find her and speak with her. She has information that can help me.
Your autograph can wait. I haven't found a single lead since the chaos started.
I'll have to check rooms one by one. Helen, the reporter and your Naomi.
Let's work together and find them. Okay. How about some guidance?
Where should I start searching? I forget. I don't know what that place is even called.
So go to vending machine. Okay. I'll walk. Go to holding cell one. Shutter one. Okay.
Oh no. What? What's going on? Oh, shoot head. Shoot. Shoot head. Shoot stomach.
Turn around. Turn left. Back. Back. Back. Shoot head. Shoot stomach. One.
Shoot head. Two. Shoot stomach. Two. Oh my God. Look at all this. I need to go. I need to
save the fucking game. Can I leave? All right. Let's check. We're right here.
Go to guest room one. I'm talking. Excuse me. Go to guest room one.
Guest room one. Okay. Hurry up. Yes. The guest rooms are locked for security purposes.
You should be able to disengage the locks on your end.
Well, I was trying to talk and she just started speaking over me.
She's like, give me directions. And I'm like, sure. I'll give you directions.
I, you even let, I'm giving directions right now. Thanks. She, I was speaking first.
Is someone there? Pet peeve discovered. No, I'm just fucking kidding. So where should I begin
checking? Tell me please. No, you know what? I, when I am talking to somebody, listen to
this. Okay. When you're in a conversation with somebody and everybody has that moment
where they know that you start, you both start talking at the same time.
Right. So I have something I want to say and you have something you want to say.
It usually goes by who got, who got it out first. Right. And then you start to have that
internal fake little battle where who's going to stop talking first, who's going to let the
other one just win. So, you know, for instance, if we're talking about a movie we saw
and we're talking about like a Thanos or the infinity world was such a great movie.
And especially, I think the point of the movie is when Thanos, like if I start saying what I
think the point of the movie is, and you start saying the point of the movie is at the same time,
one of us has to back down eventually. So what happens is whoever got the word out first,
that person gets to keep going. The other one has to just back down. And then you can make
your point afterwards. Now, the problem is if that person does not let you in, right. So
if we start talking for five straight seconds, both, okay, you started saying you started
talking first. I'm going to back down here and you're going to talk for about 30 or 40
seconds. Now let me come in and think about the ship. The ship was just bullshit. It's like,
okay, now you're not playing by the rules. Every, every about 30 or 40 seconds you got
to let the other person in. Walk to table. You can't just talk for like two straight minutes
if somebody's in a conversation with you. It just doesn't work. Then that person eventually
is going to throw the hot coffee. Yes. Grab coffee cup.
Dump coffee on self. Grab camera. No film, no batteries, no lens. Okay, so
drink coffee. That's what I just said. All right. Read newspaper clipping.
Ordinary people couldn't afford this hotel.
Uh, save point. Go to save point. The save point, okay. Take out a hundred dollars cash.
No, no, no. Cancel the save. No, I forgot. Square is, it's the weird place that the
old PlayStation systems had. Yeah. Guest room one. Hour and 23 minutes. Number of commands
138. Go to bed. The bed. Okay. Monster. Shoot head. Shoot head. Dodge right. Shoot
stomach. Shoot mouth. Shoot stomach. Reload. Her aim is horrible. Yeah, it is. Don't,
oh my God. That's giving me so much. Yes, you've done it. Thanks to you. We're saved.
What? You're just a damn waitress. Great. So what's your name, baby? It's Rio. Jesus.
This thing had us trapped in the bathroom. Now I control this guy too. Freaking mess. Son
of a. Would you spit on the floor? Isn't it my luck to be saved by some waitress,
but I suppose I do owe you a thanks. I bet you're some greedy little gold digger looking to hook
a big sugar daddy and reel him in. Wait a minute. The monitors are live. Which ones?
Who's the operator anyway? George. He says he's a guest to the hotel. He's stuck in the
monitor room. Is that right? Well, that sucks for him. Doesn't it? Now you're on camera.
But what the hell is a guest doing in the monitor room? Yeah, somebody made a really
good point. Why are there cameras in the bedrooms? Well, if I know there was an
explosion, then those monsters appeared all over. God knows what the hell they are.
Some alien swarm or other. Still, they ain't jack if you can blow them away with a handgun.
Run along and rescue our guests. I'll look for the prime minister. This guy's gonna be
dead. But he came out of the transportation ministry and I'm screwed if he dies in my
hotel. Sir? What? Do you kiss your mother with that mouth? Whoa. Problem with it?
Jerk. That was surprising. Save it for someone who cares, bimbo.
This guy's gonna end up like eaten in five minutes. Such an arrogant jerk. Yes,
that was manager Tanaka. He's in charge of this hotel. He told me to go rescue the guests.
Maybe he's the one who needs help. Well, anyway, what should we do now? We're in the bedroom,
right? Go to bed. The bed, okay. It's an ordinary bed, but with soft springs in it for low
gravity use. Huh, I wonder what this is. Another one of those devices. Hey, a heel
capsule. It's like a flask of whiskey. There doesn't seem to be anything else.
Lie in bed. The bed, okay. Lie down. There doesn't seem to be anything else.
Let's check somewhere else. Jump on bed. The bed, okay. There doesn't seem to be anything else.
Let's check somewhere else. Sit in chair. Nope. Uh, no. Okay. No. What else do we have here?
We got, uh, go to the emergency panel. The emergency panel. Okay. Tell her to do a sexy pose.
Is that like, that's like a meme thing? Emergency tools are stored in here. I'm pretty
certain that there's a key for the hallway shutters in here. That's strange. It looks
like someone's already taken it. Strange. What else? There's nothing else that needs checking.
Uh, then I guess, you know, I guess do a pose. Do a pose. Do a sexy pose. Stop. Yes.
Do a pose. Hello. What was that? Do a pose. I am stopped. Do a sexy pose. This is horseshit.
You guys just made me do this for no reason. Oh my God. I thought this is going to be like
one of the meme inputs. Is he actually watching me? Oh my God. Damn it. Okay. Whatever.
Go to the dresser. The dresser. Okay. You fuckers. It actually does exist.
Look at mirror. I want to get changed out of this outfit. Check luggage. Are you talking about
this? Check trunk. This is a chip. Another chip. Let's take this. Does she know if you,
how loud you are? I'm curious. All right. I'm going to be kind of loud here. So just want
to give you guys some warning. If you want to drag the volume slider a little bit to the
left here. I'm going to give you some warning. Here we go. By the bed. Okay. No. There doesn't
seem to be anything else. Let's check somewhere else. Go to mirror. I am walking.
Go to mirror. The table. Okay. Stop. Yes. Check mirror. I am standing. Go to mirror.
The dresser. Okay. What a weird fucking word that is. Look in mirror. I checked that earlier.
It's fine. Smash mirror. Eat glass. I'll go out into the hallway. Where should I go?
That's a great question. Run to security room. The security room. Okay. Run there.
There we go. Run. I am running. Run. I am running. Run faster. I am running. Run as fast
as you can. This is this. This is okay. This is the security room. Leave. Yes. Leave. I am stopped.
Leave room. Yes. I'm not going to say that. Leave the room. Don't do a lap. Do a lap. Yep.
Do a lap around the room. Okay. I'll leave. There we go. I'm not going to say that. Why
would I say that? That makes no sense. That doesn't make any sense. Why would that ever be
an input? Where should I go? All right. We got guest room. We'll go. Go to guest room four.
Guest room four. Okay. It's an Easter egg. Say it. Oh, is it really? Run. Yes. Walk.
Crawl. Yes. Sneak. I am running. I don't think I can do anything here. You'll be able to
control the shutter by inserting the emergency shutter key. I don't think I have that. If we
don't find the shutter key, we won't be able to progress. So we can't go that way.
So we can go to... Maybe we can't. Because that's... We can go to security room. Guest room one.
Let's see. Go to shutter nine. Shutter nine. Okay. Can we open this? No. Go to shutter seven.
Shutter seven. Okay. Run. Yes. Because only the two guest rooms. The guest room
and security room. I need a key. Can I open this one? No, I can't. If we don't find the
shutter key, we won't be able to progress. Is it the shutter keys in the guest room?
Go to security room. The security room. Okay. Run. Yes. Is that one thing on the table that
I didn't actually look at? Braid hair? Freudian weapon. Thanks for the five community subs.
Thank you so much. Five just came in. Check table. The table. Okay. What is this thing called?
Check newspaper. Oh. This is today's newspaper. That's too easy. And I'm not doing that. Why
would I... No, that doesn't do anything. Read newspaper? Today's opening party was the top
story. Tomorrow it'll be front page news again. I can't believe I'm... No, I'm not
going to say this because there's no way it's... There's no way. Go to guest room one. Leave the
room? Okay. Leave room. Run. Run. Yes. Everyone in the chat is just shouting commands that
I'm never going to say. Guest room one. Guest room one. Okay. Run. Run. Yes. Undo
the door lock please. It wasn't... Wasn't it already open? Oh my god. Why is it...
I just closed it. Sorry. The sun's sweet. Okay. What? No, no, no, no, no, no. Stop.
Guest room one. Guest room one. Okay. Run. Yes. Undo the door lock please. Thanks. File
your taxes. You're doing it wrong. Jerma, we're giving commands to you, not the girl.
Well, none of that's going to happen. All right. Bathroom. Go to bathroom. The bathroom.
Okay. Run. Yes. How did Tanaka manage to hide here? I think I see a disc underneath the sink.
Punch mirror. Is my face dirty? I'll wash it later. Wash face. It's an ordinary wash
stand. There's nothing unusual. Item under sink. Under the sink? Here's the shutter key.
Nice job. Nice job. Nice work. Nice work. Nice work. I didn't understand that.
I said nice fucking work. I didn't understand that. Nice work. The floor has been thoroughly
cleaned. It's sparkling. Good job. I'll walk. Back. The bathroom. Okay. Run. Yes. Shower. The
shower itself is ordinary. Over 90% of the water used here is recycled. Okay. Destroy window.
The living room. Okay. No, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Shoot mirror. Shoot mirror. Back. The bed.
Okay. Stop. Yes. Shoot mirror. Go to mirror. Okay. I got it already. Stop. There doesn't
seem to be anything else. You don't got it. You don't got it. You don't got it. Go to
bathroom. The bathroom. Okay. Run. Yes. Smash mirror. Okay. Now you can leave. What is it?
Shutter two. It's an ordinary shower. No, no. The water is recycled.
It's just a wash stand. Okay. I understand. Do you? Let's see. What did she understand?
Leave. Yes. Leave quickly. I am stopped. Leave. I am stopped. Hallway. Okay.
I'll leave. Run. Yes. What an odd game. Strangely enough, though, this works way better
than any game that's tried to do this 10 to 15 years later.
I'm getting interference. Hello. Operator. Wiggle mic. What? Wait, I'm hearing another voice.
Who is this? Other frequency. Hello. Hello. Operator. Can you hear me? There's definitely
someone calling for help. There's someone else alive out there. All right. Well, let's
what we're going to go shutter. We need some guests from two. Hold on. Come on. I need to
know what happens when I do this. I was going to sneeze. You're awfully slow with
instructions. Hold on. Okay. I'll walk. Yes. Let's see if Shido can give some commands.
You listen to me. This should open a shutter half the time. You listen to Shido completely.
Hurry up and go back. No, Shido. Don't tell. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm going to
override you here, Shido. Go back. Yep. Back to panel. No, we already looked under the bed.
There's nothing under the bed. No, we looked under the bed already. Analyze shutter panel.
It's okay. This control panel can be operated on your end. I'll get it. No, wait. The auto
control emergency shutter can now be opened and closed. Open it. Give, give Shido a turn.
No, no, I have to do this. It's not going to understand you.
Shoot right eye. Back. Back. Shoot right eye. Left eye. Shoot. Middle eye. Shoot. Red eye.
Shoot. You want to play? See how well Shido does. I'm just going to take a back seat here.
There's going to be a Shido stream for about five minutes. You ready? Okay. You can say it a little
louder. What do you want me to try to say? What are you trying to say here? Try something
else because she's obviously not getting it. Okay. Well, give me proper instructions. I'm
I know. I understand. Look, the game, the game is trying to listen to you. I know it's,
it's finicky sometimes. Maybe she's being too high. Go a little bit lower. I don't think this is
going to. No. All right. All right. Settle down. Settle down. I understand that they get,
I know the game sucks. That's fine. You're freaking out. Okay. It's, it's not going to
hear you. Just go back to bed. Go back to bed. Let me take over. Okay. Doesn't work. Go.
I am standing. Go to guest room two. Guest room two. Okay. Run. Yes. Stop.
Run. Yes. Stop. Run. Yes. Stop. Run. Stop.
Shido! Shido's in the game. Eat. Eat flour. Let me type in thing on face.
All right. Here we go. Here we go. Apparently not. What? Go.
Go. No, close it. I just opened it. No, close it. Close the door. Oh, fuck. Oh, no. It's all
right. We're right there. Imagine if I didn't save it the whole time. Yeah. This is, this
is simple. We're just going to run it. Look, we speed run on this. Go to bathroom. The
bathroom. Run. Yes. Oh, fuck. We have to do this again. No, sorry. I'm just going to go
bathroom and then door. We already got everything. Shoot mouth. Mouth. Shoot. Stomach.
Shoot. The guy's going to come out. We're just going to skip it. Skip. Skip cut scene.
Skip. Cutscene. Skip. Oh, fucking hell. Come on. Yes. You've done it. No skipping.
What? You're just a damn waitress? Great. So what's your name, baby?
It's okay. I have to do this shit again. Damn it. I need to, I gotta remember this
PlayStation 2. You got to save it every time you do something. Oh, you're some greedy
little gold digger. Look at the big sugar daddy and reel him in. No. What have I done?
Wait a minute. The monitor's alive? Which ones? Who's the operator anyway?
There's more than one camera. There's like five cameras in these rooms. He's a guest
to the hotel. He's stuck in the monitor room. Use Shito to voice act. That sucks for him,
doesn't it? Shito is only going to leave you around for like 10 minutes per stream.
What the hell is a guest doing in the monitor room? Mr. Schmelke, pardon me.
What's going on in the hotel? If I know, there was an explosion and then those monsters
appeared all over. God knows what in the hell they are. Some alien swarm or other.
Someone just clapped when Shito shows up, don't they?
Run along and rescue our guests. I'll look for the prime minister, the jackass.
But he came out of the transportation ministry and I'm screwed if he dies in my hotel.
I'm moving to Vegas. I've been here for a few months. You got a problem with it? I moved
in October. To help and you're being a real jerk. Still on the balloon. I'm streaming from
the balloon. Save it for someone who cares, bimbo. He's such an arrogant jerk. Yes,
that was manager Tanaka. He's in charge of this hotel. He told me to go rescue the guests.
Maybe he's the one who needs help. We're ready to go. What should we do now?
Go to bathroom. The bathroom. Okay. Run. Yes.
How did Tanaka manage to hide here? Under sink. Under the sink? Oh, here's the shutter key.
This will let us open that shutter. Yeah, it should. Out. Back. By the bed. Okay. Check
trunk. I am walking. Check trunk. Check trunk. It's an ordinary bed but with soft springs
in it for low gravity use. Huh. I wonder what this is. Some of the heel. Hey, a heel capsule.
There doesn't seem to be anything else. Check mirror. Stop. Yes. Check dresser. The dresser.
Okay. Check trunk. We're not going back to earth yet. We can pack our luggage later.
No, check it though. There's something down there. Check trunk.
Huh. This is a chip. All right. We are. We've made the same amount of progress we made in
40 minutes. Shoot mirror. See. Okay. I did it. Everybody calm down. Save.
Save game. Where the hell is the dumb thing? Save point. The save point. Okay. Run. Run.
Yes. Now we're good. All right. Let's go. Go. I am stopped. Go. I am stopped. Oh.
Okay. I got it already. I'm really going. Uh. Hallway. Okay. I'll leave. Run. Yes.
Go. I am stopped. Wait. We have a shutter tube. Here comes the transmission incoming.
Hello. Operator. What? Wait. I'm hearing another voice.
Who is this? Hello. Hello. Operator, can you hear me? She did. There's definitely
someone calling for help. There's someone else alive out there. Shutter seven. Shutter seven.
Okay. Here we go. Now I got to close. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. You'll be able to control the
shutter by inserting the emergency shutter key. All right. I remember this part. This time
is not going to be. I'm going to close the door on the monster. I can't even read that right
now. Shoot right eye. Back up. Back. Middle eye. Left eye. Red eye. All right. We're good.
Same thing can happen. This time I'm going to close it. Guest room two. Guest room two.
Run. Lady. Close the door on him. Save game. Tell me a story. Stop.
Turn around. Turn around. All right. I got to make sure I choose the right thing.
Close the door.
Here we go
Close
Every time it just freaks me out
You don't have to hold the gun like a baby with your finger on the trigger like that's
It's scaring me saved
Thank you
Huh, you're welcome. Can you hear footsteps?
Somebody's coming
Somebody is coming
Rio
Geno, how'd you get out of that holding cell? I had an operator open it for me
that idiot
Inside the cell no alien would have reached you. Why is everybody? I thought you died
It'll take a lot more than those aliens to kill me. I'm just a streamer
So those are aliens. Yeah, I was watching German on eight five
Fucking idiot. Hey, the good news is that a shuttle with a rescue team is on the way
I ran into a researcher in the testing ward and he said they'd caught a radio signal
I've got to tell the others about this right away
Hey operator look after her. Okay. Oh
Yeah here take this
It's the voice password for one of the suites the researcher I met he's hiding in the Sun suite
That sounds we I'm gonna keep looking for survivors make your way to the receiving port got it and be extra careful
Let's go. Let's go. I
Gotta save the game
The Sun suite. I think it's done this way
If it's a voice password, just tell her
If you could forget it the rescue team is headed for the receiving port
But the receiving port is on the other side of that spider monster
So we gotta go the other way. There's no way I can get through there
Anyway, we should search every room
Searching for Naomi and Helen the reporter. That's our top priority
All right, so we're across here we need to go to
Room two room three these are the two rooms. We got go to go to guest room to guest room to okay run. Yes
undo the door lock, please
Thanks fucking save. Oh, I keep forgetting this probably gonna be a safe point in here
Shit, please don't do this to me
Save kiosk. Yes
Where should I start searching go to the save ATM?
Save point the save point. Okay run. Yes, this blood all over the floors. There's about this monster on the ceiling
Probably hurry up
All right, we're safe hour and 36 minutes. That's not even true
Our in 36 minutes has that get up
Okay, I got it already. Someone's at a baseball bat. What's on the ground there grab telescope grab telescope. Yes
stop
Check wall
No
Go I have no idea what to check floor in corner. Okay, I'll leave no stop. Yes turn around
I am standing turn around. Yep. No, don't look behind you
Go to save point the save point. Okay, stop. Yes
Check floor. What the hell is that thing that little?
chair leg
Check floor by kiosk. Well, I'm sorry. You feel that way
What grab a chair leg?
Somebody's gave $50
Juno upseto, thanks to the 50
5,000 bits 50 bucks
Despite the fact that I'm a lurker and don't chat often
I want to say that I haven't missed a stream yet and I appreciate all you do watching me keep it up
And don't die tomorrow
Forehead, I'll be fine. Don't worry, but thank you so much for 50 bucks
Another huge amount of money coming in been a lot today. So
Thank you guys. Thank you
For your fucking huge amount of money. Okay, you didn't give it to me lady. Check
Table the table. Okay. Stop. Yes. Is it like an arm or something? What is that?
No, no emergency panel
Living like what is that thing right there?
check
Arms. Yes. I don't even know what the hell to call that
Desk
Monsters
Shoot shoot head back
Shoot head free shoot head free shoot head to wiggle
back
back shoot head to
No, shoot to
dodge right
Dodge left
Shake dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left
dodge left
touch left dodge left
shoot to
dodge left
shoot head to
Target to shoot head shoot mouth. Shoot stomach. I
Don't know why you wouldn't listen to me too. I couldn't I can't say shoot to shoot three
No
It's head then shoot. Okay, we got checked check table or whatever the table. Okay, grab
picture
Okay, I understand. I don't know what that is
Stop
Grab the bed. Okay, stop. I don't know what to call it check table the table
Is it a book a magazine or?
grab magazine
Are you talking about this X X X XL an extra extra extra extra large dress
Check catalog. It's a bone vaulting on the catalog
Not familiar to you. How big is that the brand is more popular with rich women X X X XL
Is that a dress or is that is that a dressers had a blanket?
Triple X dash triple XL. That's it. That's a tent
Okay open catalog
It's mostly photos. Oh, they also seem to have the brand history and stuff
Vom Von Teons logo is the stylized representation of its year of establishment in Roman numerals. It says
Something stuck between the pages
Is it a correction notice? It's an eviction notice grab eviction notice
It's a note with formulas written on it. You better analyze it and confirm it for yourself. I
May analyze that for a second
One five ten fifteen twenty one V one one six eight one six six X V X X
Okay, sure. So that's Roman numerals. I got it. Now. What do you want?
So wait, so that's X X
So that's 20. It's 20 20
2021 I guess
Not stuck I'm not stuck I didn't understand that
Twenty twenty one now, I analyzed it already pick up note
Do what with what?
Grab note
Are you talking about this? It's still shiny
2021 whatever I'll figure it's good. It's easy. Okay, check corpse
Monsters must have done this
What's your favorite color?
Vaughn Fontaine's logo is the stylized representation of its year of establishment in Roman numerals. It says I
Don't know what Crayola box that one's in but I'm gonna I'm gonna say that's a form of green. So cool
Check dresser the dresser. Okay
Another EC how much is that a full here or is that like a half-heeled?
We got here we get some stuff. I don't know. How's that back?
Look in bag
It's already open isn't it inside
It's empty
steel bag
Look in mirror
There doesn't appear to be anywhere worth checking
Do not under any circumstances
Do not shoot the mirror. No, nothing special. See
Y'all thought that was gonna be a joke
check bed
by the bed, okay, there's the
Super sized XX XXL dress check dress
It's a gorgeous dress. There's a big logo in the hem. It's a Vaughn Fontaine design
She really must have liked this brand
put on dress
This is better for activity. I'd rather not get changed
shoot dress
pardon
You've got to be kidding. There'll be such a waste. Why will you shoot a mirror, but you won't shoot anything else
It's not a waste to shoot the mirror that makes a mess, but it's a waste to shoot the dress. I
Don't even know what the fuck that is check box
Check box on table the table. Okay
No, stop
Check bed by the bed. Okay
Nice a nightstand
Look at nightstand
White box. Are you talking about? Oh, yeah member of the tutorial
Open safe. It's something that the hotel loans to the guests. It has a combination guarantee. This is 2021
I wonder what's been placed inside here
It's bothering me. I can't undo this lock. I can't
Can't you open it on your side? Yes
Mm-hmm
Open it
Wait, i'm ready open it, please. There's a room. I just have to I just can open it
Yeah, yeah, look at that first word. I know what a what a funny first word that is
All right, so it's 20 20 20 21
That's it there it is it opened
Oh, it's a shutter key of all the strange places to find it
Got the code. Why would someone lock it away in a safe?
Because there's something more sinister going on here
And we're gonna do some detective work to find go
Go to limp
There's nothing on the bed itself
bright light
Are you talking about that?
I am I already said nightstand check nightstand
It's an ordinary nightstand
Oh, hey, except what's a chip doing here?
shoot lamp
What a waste, huh?
shoot bright light
The save point. Okay. No
I actually know you know what?
Do it. That's a good idea
Run. Yeah, that's a great idea
That's a good thought. So I got the
shutter thing
Which is good
You're doing you're back seating a streamer in this game
Okay, so
We've done pretty much everything here
Check bed. I didn't check. Did I check the bathroom in here?
check bathroom
The bathroom run. Okay. Yes
There's a lot of what's all this red stuff?
red bottle
Are you talking about this the cologne?
Put on makeup our present situation doesn't allow that
Check makeup. This is vaunt voltaire on makeup made in france
The name vaunt voltaire is french. So yeah
Well, they're really pushing this whole vaunt voltaire
check shower
It looks like somebody else had been here
Turn on water
Hmm. There's no need to do that
check mirror
There's nothing especially suspicious. I'm not gonna shoot the mirror
It's just it's the same thing over and over again
Take makeup
It's not necessary
I'm not gonna need to use it somewhere
All right. Well
leave
Do what with what?
What is it leave?
I'll go out into the hallway. Thank you. Thank you
Bite controller
So run. Yes
Shoot the makeup. No, I i'm not gonna shoot any more stuff
There's another transmission
Are you there? Hello? Hello?
Where are you
I don't know. I can't see anything. Is this
Naomi
Operator that voice it had to be naomi. You don't know that she's calling for help somewhere. Hurry. We've got to find her
All right
guest room three
guest room three, okay, yes
Sit down forget it. There's no point in sitting down run to guest room three guest room three, okay
Undo the door lock, please
Thanks operator put me through to the other line
Here we go. Any enemies in here?
Yeah, if there is a couple of slimes
Watch out
Uh
Why didn't you say something? I did i've very clearly told you to watch out
dodge right
back
target enemy two
shoot head
stomach shoot
back left target three
target enemy three
head number three
stomach number three
dodge left
enemy one head
shoot shoot shoot
walk forward
left
dodge left
dodge left turn
Shoot shoot shoot head
Mirror enemy mirror head enemy mirror
Heal yourself
Ha ha don't worry. There are plenty of ways for me to die in here
uh
heal
Huh?
Heal yourself
Ha ha don't worry. There are plenty of ways for me to die in here
Use med pack
Yes
Stop
Stop. Yes turn around. Yes. Stop. Ah
Where should I go?
Heal yourself
Heal yourself. What am I supposed to use?
Mend wounds
Left. Okay. Stop
Stop
Yes
Recover health
Okay
Guest room three guest room three run. Okay. Yes
Undo the door lock, please
This time don't just leave. Thanks
That stock sound effect
That's used in a lot of games
So many sound effects you hear in games are used
You'll start to pay attention to them and hear them and just be like, oh, yeah, that's in this game. That's in that game
Bonk from tf2
What are the that's a couple of the drink sounds
Stop. Yes
What else what is that that gulp sound from?
I said right on the tip of my tongue. It's it's tf2. It's here
Sky room
Aren't there any instructions?
Hold on. I'm busy talking to people save point the save point. Okay
I'm gonna save and i'm gonna go pee
So let's use this opportunity to go take a piss
Not her me
Saving it. I'll be right back
See you guys in like less than two minutes
Please wake up
Okay, we are back get my headset back on
Wake up
What is she talking? Is she saying all kinds of weird things?
Are you busy with something else?
Oh, she's been yelling at me this whole time
I didn't mute the ps2. Did I wake up?
Okay, I got it already
So what do we not look here?
Check emergency panel the emergency panel run. Yes
The emergency panel is open
Oh
The shutter key's broken need a piece to fix it probably right we can't use this anymore
Uh check vacuum cleaner head. I don't even know what that is
Um
orange
Beige triangle. I don't want it. It's not much of a picture anyway
suction cup
emergency plane oxygen mask
The shutter key's broken there appears to be nothing special. Um
So triangle
Shaped device. Are you talking about this? Oh boy. I am what is it?
On it
I got it. It was right
Check oxygen mask
It could be used in an emergency to get air
Breathe oxygen. It's just a sofa
Put on oxygen mask there's plenty of breathable air
I don't want to sit on the sofa
I don't want to breathe in the sofa go smell sofa breathe in sofa
Oh
What the flying fuck get out
By the bed, okay
That's fucking not
Where are we going?
Okay
What dodge left?
dodge left
back
I can't do anymore shoot head two
Oh target
target two
target two head
target enemy two
shoot head
shoot stomach
shoot mouth
Back dodge right dodge left dodge left back
stop
mouth
stomach
mouth dodge right
dodge right
dodge
Shoot shoot mouth shoot mouth
shoot stomach
Shoot stomach dodge right
Oh fuck run
I shoot stomach
Shoot dodge right dodge right
shoot stomach
stomach stomach
stomach
back back
Ah
stomach
Do i'm dodge stomach
dodge left dodge left
Stop turn turn around turn around shoot two head shoot shoot
Shoot stomach a shoot head
shoot head
shoot stomach
Why did that take so long?
This person's dead
That was that was close
Check blood
Yes
I don't think she had a stance stop. Yes
Uh check body I am standing check corpse corpse corpse
Look at corpse
Yes
Stop. Yes
Check bed the bed. Okay
There's nothing here
Let's check elsewhere
What is this something on the
check
Stop. Yes
Check desk the bed. Okay
I think we're done with checking this place
Don't you do you you think that okay check bathroom the bathroom run. Yes
There's nothing here
Let's look elsewhere nothing in here
I think she's trying to tell me there's nothing in the room
What's that on the floor? Stop. Yes
Look at floor
mirror, huh
check
Wardrobe. Yep. I don't know. What am I trying to say?
Check dresser the dresser. Okay, there's a heel down there
grab heel
How am I supposed to understand that? Oh my god
look
under
There appears to be nothing abnormal. There is a heel
Look under dresser
Under the dresser. Yes
It's a heel capsule
smoke smoke cigar
suicide
Don't be stupid. There are people who are counting on us
I mean
Brown box
Are you talking about this?
open cigar case
Oh cool, it fits in there perfectly
smoke what should I check
smoke a cigar
I'll go out into the hallway. Stop
Stop stop stop stop. Stop. I am stopped
Check dresser the dresser run. Okay. Yes
check corpse
This guy here. I'm certain. He's the son of jsl's chairman
I wouldn't want to break this news to the manager
Look at mirror
I don't see anything strange
save point
The save point, okay
run
quick
quickly
Yes
Stop I am stopped check food the bedroom. Stop. Okay. Yes turn around. I am stopped turn around
Huh?
Check table the table. Okay
Shoot thanksgiving dinner. I'll go out into the hallway. Stop
Stop
Yes check table
The table, okay
Shoot turkey
What are you even aiming at she's not the chair
Look at turkey
The dresser
No, the turkey that's on the table. Stop. Yes check table the table. Okay
examine food
The bedroom, okay
Stop
Stop it. Stop. Okay. I'll leave check table the table. Okay
Bottle of champagne the champagne is often made by jsl naturally. That's awful
Hold on
Shoot champagne the champagne
It's terrible, but there's no need to go that far
What did you think I meant by that?
attack champagne bottle
The food will fly everywhere. Let's not
Drink champagne
Under a different situation. I might have had a drink
Okay
Check food
Are you talking about this? Yes. How many what what even is this meal?
You can't say turkey. You can't say food. You can't say chicken. You can't say thanksgiving gotta say meal
check meal
Christmas dinner courtesy of christmas dinner
Forget it's christmas eve today. It's christmas eve today
Okay
Did the turkey just come I was looking at did the turkey just come alive
shoot turkey
head shoot
back shoot
wait till he jumps
No, shoot head
head shoot
wait
run
shoot
Fucking duck hunt. All right, here we go
Walk forward mouth walk front front
I can't do anymore
approach the enemy
shoot
shoot mouth
Not necessarily you didn't you didn't you didn't you didn't check emergency panel the emergency panel
Okay, and hurry the fuck up
Shutter key this doesn't appear to be useful anymore
too bad
Check table
The table, okay
There was one other thing I could do here. There's a heel on here wasn't there?
Yeah
What kind of dinner is that?
Merry christmas everybody
we've got
thanksgiving turkey
alien meat
wine champagne
and a heel
A drugs just on the table
Now this is very important. I need to make sure this is very clear
Because i'm at full health and I do not want to use a heel
I want to take the heel
You're awfully slow with instructions
grab
heel
Didn't your mother tell you to never waste food?
Let's not
grab item
What this half-eaten meal?
You must be joking not on your life
he
No, you're not
Ha ha don't worry. There are plenty of ways for me to die in here
What?
Why would you say that?
Why would you tell why would you say that right now?
achieve
um
The bathroom, okay stop
Stop
Yes
Grab heel on table
The table, okay
I don't know if I want to say take heel somebody says you say take heel but it won't that mean
Take heel
What is that instruction?
I don't know what you mean
take drugs
Use no don't use anything stop
The save point
Go back stop stop stop
Stop I am stopped table the table. Okay
What is this thing even called? It's called something
grab med kit
What is that instruction?
I don't know what you mean
pick up
Heal
What is that instruction?
I don't know what you mean
Pick up capsule
I'll go out into the hallway that didn't work either guys
Stop I am stop. Yes table the table. Okay
Check bottle bottle
There's a few
Which one do you mean? Um
Check right bottle
It's everywhere this jsl okay energy charge is what it's called. Most of it's still here. Thanks for the close-up
Pick up energy charge
The emergency panel, okay
Stop check table
The table, okay run pick up heel capsule
I got it. Wow. You're right
I'll take it then
Only took us 30 tries
save point
The save point, okay
Run. Yes
Eat table
Oh, wow, you're right
Give her a break
You're telling her to run all the time
lie down
Huh?
Lie down
Huh? Lie down. Huh? Lie down. Huh? Get up. Okay. I got it already
Go to sleep
Yes
That work that definitely doesn't work. No way
Exit room, okay. I'll leave run. Yes
Tell her to lose the attitude
Where should I go?
Who is your favorite actor?
What's your favorite movie?
What's your favorite tv show?
Who do you admire most?
How tall are you? Can you at least try to be serious?
Go to shutter three
shutter three, okay
run
Yes, run fast
The sun sweet. Okay
This will open that shutter
You relax
I'll go back. No
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No
Yes, no
What is it? No
No
Pardon
Forget it. There's no point in sitting down shutter
Three shutter three, okay run. Yes
What is it hurry up and analyze analyze open the door
Hey
Remember me
back
Right eye dog left. Fuck
Right eye shoot left eye shoot middle eye shoot left eye shoot red eye shoot
Those ones are you
Try kicking and punching
So that's the sun sweet
That's where we gotta go
Looking for a another character in here, Naomi
I mean what is her name?
Honeymoon mode do not disturb
Oh, no, I don't know. What is it password?
Password it must be the one that gino gave us earlier. Okay
The bride may now read the first portion
Bride in this case, I guess it's me
Okay, let me see dual like sorcerer password shadow that you cast in sunlight
authentication successful
What the groom may now read the second
The groom that must be you
Let's go. I can get this
What what do I say?
and under the moon the
Apparently you do not have the second portions denied
In order to undo the lock to the sun suite, I guess we need another piece of the voice password
Sure
Where should I start looking? Uh
Okay
We're gonna go to guest room number four
guest room four
guest room four, okay run
Run. Yes
What's your name?
What is your name?
Do the door lock, please
What is your name? My sign is no parking now. Let's get a move. Your sign says no parking
I didn't ask you if you look like a Sagittarius. I want to what is your name
Controlling the door panels is your responsibility operator
Hey rio, pardon
Thanks. No parking. What the fuck does that even mean?
I don't get it
Hey, wait, wait. Whoa. Whoa. What if I just i'm sorry
I had to stretch
back
Shoot front limb
front limb shoot
Dodge right. I can't do anymore walk
back
Kind limb shoot
attack
walk forward
walk front
Ah
shoot tongue
tongue tongue shoot
tongue
In her mouth shoot
dodge left
target enemy three
tongue
Body tongue eye
No target enemy two
enemy two
Dodge left. Oh
Dodge left
back
Back back
target enemy one
Shoot body. Shoot body body tongue shoot tongue
Shoot mouth shoot mouth
Dodge left dodge right. Dodge right shoot
shoot mouth
shoot inner mouth
Shoot in her mouth shoot in her mouth shoot in her mouth
No
Turn
Oh
let me just take a sip of this i'm just like getting a coffee here oh fuck me okay target two
heal use heal capsule target three target enemy three shoot inner mouth shoot inner mouth
shoot front limb shoot inner mouth shoot inner mouth shoot inner mouth
shoot inner mouth shoot inner mouth shoot shoot inner mouth shoot shoot two mouth
shoot stomach two
S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S
Look at the sofa.
Huh?
Look at chair.
The bedroom.
Stop.
Yes.
Emergency panel.
The emergency panel.
Okay.
Ugh, the shutter key's broken.
Come on, really?
We can't use this anymore.
Let's check somewhere else.
Well, uh, look out window.
Huh?
Look out the window.
This is the living room.
Dumb person.
Look out window.
This is the living room.
Check living room.
Green box.
Check.
Okay, I got it already.
Stop.
Yes.
Grab heel capsule on green box.
The bedroom.
Stop.
Yes.
Pick up heel capsule.
Huh?
Ugh.
Stop.
Okay.
Go to living room.
Oh, hey.
I didn't even do this.
What's a chip doing here?
There's a heel capsule in the corner.
There doesn't seem to be anything else.
Let's check somewhere else.
Living area.
The living area.
Okay.
Stop.
Yes.
Turn around.
Stop.
Check living area.
The living area.
Okay.
Huh?
All right.
Grab helmet.
If I put on something like this,
my hair would be totally messed up.
Do you really care about that right now?
Check helmet.
This?
Look underneath, there's probably money in there.
Engineering staff use.
It's odd to find this here.
Look at metal pipe.
But why is there a steel pipe in a guest room?
Pick up steel pipe.
I have a hand.
I won't be needing this.
But what about Melee?
Okay.
Check green box.
Are you talking about this?
That is what I'm talking about.
I'm glad you picked up on it.
Check rations.
It's the hotel's emergency rations.
Eat some.
They're stored in the equipment room.
Oh, hey.
There's a heel capsule by the rations.
I wonder who told you that?
I just came up with that on my own.
Look at corpse.
Corpse?
There's nothing like that in here.
It's behind it.
Look behind chair, couch.
What is this?
Behind.
What are you trying to say?
There isn't anything.
Look behind the chair.
Behind the chair?
Yeah.
This person's dead.
He was hiding here
in hopes of finding protection.
What was that?
Voice password.
Ooh.
Nice.
Now we can get into the Sun Suite.
Yes, we can.
Time for the Sun Suite.
Let's get over there.
Okay, let's go.
It might be way, there might be some, hold on.
Check bedroom.
The bedroom, okay.
Run, run, run.
Yes.
Check table.
Stop.
The table, okay.
Mmm.
Turn on movie.
There's not much point in moving this.
What else should I do?
Turn on projector.
Turn on the projector?
Actually, you have to analyze the thing and turn it on.
You do it.
Well, I can't even, check projector.
And I can't even target it.
If you turn the power on for me,
it might show something.
This is the station's floor map.
This is halo.
See?
This is guest room four, where I am.
You're in the monitor room.
It's pretty far from the hotel section.
And that's the receiving port.
If Geno's story is true,
the rescue team will be arriving here.
That's new info that we didn't have before,
so I'm glad to have it.
All right.
Look at book.
What should I check?
The book.
Okay, I understand.
No, you don't.
That means, okay, every time she says I understand,
that means I don't understand.
Stop.
Yes.
Every time.
Check table.
The table.
Okay.
Look at tablecloth.
It looks like a tornado hit this place.
What?
Tablecloth on table.
What is that instruction?
I don't know what you mean.
Open tablecloth.
Are you talking about that?
Yes.
That's a blueprint?
That is a picnic tablecloth.
Look at blueprint.
It's the hotel blueprints.
This guest must have been on staff.
Check, use.
It's an ordinary chair.
I don't even know what the fuck to do with that.
Look at blueprint.
There's not much point in moving this.
What else should I do?
Green book.
Are you talking about this?
Take questionnaire.
A questionnaire?
We don't need this either.
Shoot projector.
I think it would be better if we didn't wreck this.
Shoot screen.
Putting a hole through it will make it useless.
Let's not.
Shoot mirror.
Shoot the mirror.
Are you talking about that?
Mm-mm, mm-mm, mm-mm, no.
Stop.
So I should run, OK?
No.
Stop.
Shoot the mirror.
Shoot mirror.
What is it?
Check dresser.
The dresser.
Ah.
Grab checkbook.
Huh?
It's just an ordinary chair.
Look at checkbook.
Huh?
It's just an ordinary chair.
Grab invitation.
This is an invitation from JSL.
So this guest must have been well-connected or pressed.
The one on the back.
Use invitation.
The invitation?
I don't know what you mean.
Shoot mirror.
You made a mess.
Are you talking about this?
Yeah, the thing that you just did.
Shoot invitation.
I will just put a hole through it.
Why do you have such a problem with shooting anything
that's not a mirror?
Do you just hate the sight of your own reflection?
I don't understand.
Leave.
Do what with what?
Go to the honeymoon suite.
I'll go out into the hallway.
What is it?
Let's put the sun suite.
Go to sun suite.
Sun suite.
Well, I still have my health.
I am stopped.
Head to the sun suite.
Check the bathroom.
The bathroom.
OK.
Run.
Yes.
There's nothing here.
Let's look elsewhere.
Shoot mirror.
Shoot mirror in bathroom.
Yes.
Oh!
Go to save point.
The save point.
Run.
OK.
Yes.
Run.
I am running.
God damn it.
Whatever.
End of stream voice.
No.
Well, I mean, look.
I did say shoot mirror.
And I see her put her hand up towards her face.
I'm just like, what the fuck is she doing?
Boo!
The bed.
OK.
Stop.
Yes.
Go to the sun honeymoon suite.
The living room.
OK.
Out.
Leave hallway.
OK.
I'll leave.
Run.
Yes.
Where should I go?
Sun suite.
The sun suite.
OK.
Bark like a dog.
Or big dog.
Woof, woof.
Bark like a big dog.
Little dog?
Clearly said big.
Or big dog.
Woof, woof.
Woof.
Yes.
Go to sun suite.
The sun suite.
OK.
All right, time for me to read my line.
Welcome back.
This room is currently operating in honeymoon mode.
Please read your voice scheme.
The bride may now read the first portion.
Bride read the first portion.
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
Authentication successful.
The groom may now read the second portion.
It's talking about you.
All right.
Disprorts the moon and the rays in all of the sun
through all of our eternal love.
Authentication unsuccessful.
Please speak clearly.
Casting away our doubts and our love for each other
through thick and thin.
Enter.
The end.
And with our shining doubts, we make the commands to each other
to be fruitful for the eternal sun.
I just didn't say it correctly.
You may both enter.
Ready?
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
I want to monopolize.
Authentication unsuccessful.
She got it wrong.
Will the groom please face the bride while reading?
What's going on?
In case you forgot, we also have
to say both lines of the poem at the same time.
Fuck.
OK.
One more time.
The bride may now read the first portion.
Oh, the first portion.
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
Somebody clip that.
I need to, I don't know what I just,
somebody clip what I said for the last one.
The groom may now read the second portion.
And?
It's talking about you.
I need, I don't know what it was.
Anybody have a clip?
And even the eternal love we shine together,
facing one another in our endless fury.
Authentication unsuccessful.
God damn it.
Will the groom please?
Yabba dabba doo.
I love you too.
Authentication unsuccessful.
Will the groom please clear the room?
What did I say?
Over the river and through the woods
to grandmother's house we go.
Today.
Authentication unsuccessful.
I don't even know what the fuck, hey.
My fucking mouse.
Will the groom please put the passion into it?
How did this even happen?
Somebody got it?
What was it?
Hold on.
How did I fucking tangle myself in here?
Just wait, just wait, just wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, all right.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right, where is it?
No, that's the gnome video thing.
That's me slapping myself.
Here it is, okay.
I need to hear this.
Let's see what I said.
Will the groom please clear the room?
Casting away our doubts and our love for each other.
Through thick and thin.
Casting away our doubts.
Thick and thin.
Through thick and thin.
Enter.
The end.
Doubts.
No.
Fruit each other.
We make shining doubt with our,
and with our,
and with our shining doubts.
Shining doubts.
We make the commands to each other
to be fruitful for eternal sun.
God damn it.
The eternal shining doubt.
With our, and with our shining doubts.
Just play it into the mic.
I can't, can I even do that?
I'll try it.
Enter.
The end.
Where's the mic?
And with our shining doubts.
We make the commands to each other
to be fruitful for the eternal sun.
No, it's not hearing it.
Fruit shining doubt.
I'm gonna do.
And with our.
And with our Shining Doubts, we make the commands to each other to be fruitful for the eternal love of suns.
Authentication unsuccessful.
I want to monopolize.
Authentication successful.
You may both enter.
Eternal love.
Ready?
I want to monopolize.
Authentication unsuccessful.
What?
I thought we had to say it at the same time.
Look, it's pretty weird for me too.
Okay, we'll try it one more time.
The ride may now read the first portion.
That's password two?
I have to read password one?
Even the very shadow...
Even the very shadow of two out of two.
Authentication successful.
The groom may now read the second portion.
It's talking about you.
I have to read the same thing.
I want to play Monopoly.
Authentication unsuccessful.
I want to monopolize.
Will the groom please put some passion into it?
Authentication successful.
So now I have to read this and then I want to monopolize.
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
You may both enter.
I want to monopolize.
Authentication unsuccessful.
No!
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
I need to just have it open.
Why did I close it?
There was no reason to close it.
The ride may now read the first portion.
I just keep it open.
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
Authentication successful.
The groom may now read the second portion.
I want to monopolize.
I'll get it right.
Sorry.
It's talking about you.
I want to monopolize.
Authentication successful.
Here we go.
Just read what is on the sheet.
You may both enter.
Ready?
I'm ready.
Even the very shadow that you cast in sunlight.
I want to monopolize.
Authentication successful.
Oh my god.
Get us in here.
Please enter.
We finally made it in here.
We made it to the suite.
The honeymoon suite.
That's just a bathroom tile at a beach bathroom.
Oh boy.
Coffee table.
The coffee table, okay.
Meow like a cat.
Grab coffee cup.
She just never wants to drink the coffee, ever.
Read paper.
Okay, complimentary gift in the lounge.
That's it.
This is the lounge.
Go to the lounge.
They're gonna be both just be dead on the ground here.
Alright, we got a piece of fish.
A purple circle.
It's decorated for honeymooners.
Notice all the fruit?
What kind of fruit is that?
Is it purple apple?
Grab purple apple.
Are you talking about this?
That's not a grape.
That's a huge.
That's not a plum.
Plums are way smaller than that.
Grab plum.
Are you talking about this?
Look at champagne.
Product of Champagne France.
It's a real thing.
Far from cheap.
But unfortunately empty.
You didn't want to drink the last one.
Look at fruits.
Yeah, there's all kinds of fruit.
All places to find a chip.
You can't tell me that.
What fruit?
Are those supposed to be bananas?
They don't look like bananas at all.
Alright, what about...
Look at fish.
The second floor.
Stop.
Yes.
Table.
The coffee table.
No, stop, stop, stop.
The second floor.
Stop.
The fruits.
The bed.
Stop.
Yes.
Check the fruits.
I am standing.
Go to the fruit table.
The coffee table.
Stop what you're doing.
The lounge.
Go to the lounge.
Okay, the lounge.
Run.
I am running.
Look at dinner plate.
I'll go out into the hallway.
Stop.
Stop, stop.
Yes.
Lounge.
The lounge.
Run.
Okay.
Yes.
Look at plate.
I've checked it earlier.
You didn't look at the plate.
That was enough.
What is that thing?
What is that supposed to be?
Look at picture.
Are you talking about this?
I thought it was food.
I thought it was a plate with a piece of fish on it.
Look at the photograph.
It's a photo of the guests from their wedding.
Everyone looks so happy.
Check couch.
I've checked it earlier.
That was enough.
Red sofa.
Check sofa.
There's more than enough room on this sofa for just a couple of people.
Oh my goodness.
Look at flowers on sofa.
I'll go out into the hallway.
Stop what you're doing.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Yes.
Look at sofa.
Okay.
I'll leave.
Stop.
Yes.
Go.
Lounge.
The lounge.
Yes.
Flowers.
Are you talking about that?
Yeah.
Look at banquet.
Look at the bouquet.
It's pretty, isn't it?
But they're fake flowers.
Real flowers can't take the stress if the G-Force is on launch.
That was completely and totally worthless.
Save point.
The save point.
Okay.
Run.
Yes.
Fake flowers.
Yeah, they are fake.
They ain't even real.
Look at banquet TV dinner meal.
Get up.
Okay.
I got it already.
Get up.
I am standing.
Go upstairs.
The second floor.
Okay.
No.
Don't.
Hello.
Bathroom.
The bathroom.
Run.
Yes.
Dead person in the bathtub.
What?
Oh my God.
They must be the guest couple.
Looks like they tried to hide in here.
I can't bear to look.
Why are they carrying...
Let's check somewhere else.
Yeah, I know.
Get in bath.
The bathroom.
Okay.
I can't bear to look.
Let's check somewhere else.
There's nothing in there?
Nothing at all.
There's nothing in the bathtub or the bathroom.
Go upstairs.
The second floor.
Run.
Okay.
Yes.
The mirror's already broken.
Yeah, I didn't have to do anything.
It's already shattered for me.
Maybe a monster's gonna be up here.
That thing.
It can't be.
Who else is up here?
This dude looks still alive.
We were too late.
Operator, I don't think we're gonna get any information from this researcher.
What couldn't you ask me?
What?
Stop, stop.
Wait a second.
I'm human.
Pretending to be dead?
Hey, I'm sorry.
I thought that an alien had come in here.
I don't have any useful weapons, so the only thing I could do was play dead.
I'm Alan Honda, a researcher.
Can you maybe lower that gun?
I'm human.
Hey, I'll admit to being a little weird.
First person that says they're human usually isn't.
Did you just say alien?
Snake skin alien.
You really think those were aliens?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Well, I get it.
I see the significance of that question.
Are you maybe thinking that we screwed up our experiments and made the aliens?
Oh, that's one of those games.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
You think I like going to the children's department in the store and buying the
kid's vest?
No.
But I do it anyway.
If you're so interested in our research, I'll give you some reference material.
That was a gun.
You ran into that spider, right?
Uh huh.
How did you get away from it?
Please tell me.
How to kill the spider.
With that?
But it's out of fuel now.
New weapon?
Is it a flamethrower?
That thing is huge.
Do I get to flamethrow mirrors now?
But it seems to share similarities with Earth's arthropod, a spider.
You scared it off with fire.
So it's vulnerable against fire.
Uh huh.
Until help arrives, I'm holing up in here.
Earlier, Research Supervisor Powers sent a rescue signal.
Powers told me to spread the word, so I came to tell the others, but...
Because of that monster spider, you can't make it to the receiving port?
Bingo.
It's a nasty obstacle.
So, uh, how about it?
Wanna play dead with me?
I'm going.
I have a partner backing me up.
Right?
Whoa, hang on.
Take this with you.
Shutter key.
Do you really intend to just play dead?
Please refrain from talking to me.
Okay, whatever.
The Research Supervisor really sent for help.
I guess the rescue team is already on the way.
That means everyone will gather in the receiving port.
What the fu-
Gino said that he'd tell the others.
Both Helen and Naomi may be at the receiving port.
I think we should be making our way to the receiving port too.
How many times can you say receiving port in the same?
We have to get rid of that monster spider if I'm gonna get to the receiving port.
There's five.
That flamethrower Alan had.
It came from the equipment room.
There should be more at the same.
Yep.
I think we better check out the equipment room.
To the receiving port.
Oh no, you changed it to equipment room.
Alright.
Looks like we have to go to the equipment room.
Leave.
Yes.
Run.
Leave.
Hallway.
Okay.
I'll leave.
Save point.
The save point.
Run.
Okay.
Yes.
Do I have a key?
I don't think I have one of those door opening keys.
Oh, it gave one to me.
I am stopped.
Up.
The bed.
Hallway.
Okay.
Run.
Yes.
Where should I go?
You need to go to the equipment.
Alright.
Shutter two.
Okay.
Run.
Yes.
Alright.
Equipment room.
This will open that shutter.
Activate the flamethrower.
Flamethrow the spider.
We have to analyze.
Geez.
Pushy.
And then two.
There should be a flamethrower in the equipment room.
Check.
Hey.
Wait, wait, hey.
I didn't tell you to do that.
Since when do you make decisions on your own?
It's getting dark.
The power must be weakening.
We always confer with each other.
A flamethrower would be in the mechanical unit.
Where was that camera?
Great.
Hopefully there's some fuel left.
Did you see that crane shot?
Where was she looking?
What camera was that?
Huh?
No fuel?
Oh man, it's completely empty.
This won't do.
Am I like a floating little robot?
Listen.
See?
I think we have to give up on that flamethrower.
There's no fuel.
The tank is empty.
There's nothing we can do.
To get to the other side of that shutter, we have to kill that spider.
The flamethrower that Alan had been using is worthless now.
What?
That giant spider is vulnerable to fire.
Let's look for a weapon that involves fire.
You mean a flamethrower?
That's the only thing we can do.
Did they just not want to develop the fire coming out of the flamethrower?
Hey, what's an item that uses fire and can do fire damage?
A flamethrower.
Well, you know, but we can't use that.
So what else does fire?
I don't know.
A fire?
Start a fire.
Where are you going?
Supply unit.
The supply unit.
Okay.
God.
Left boxes.
Check.
These are ventilation fan parts.
Item on top of the shelf.
Have you forgotten that I work here?
Don't expect me to go shooting the hotel's supplies.
Selective shooting for some reason.
Item on left shelf.
Have you forgotten that I work here?
Don't expect me to go shooting the hotel's supplies.
Get on scaffolding.
Geez.
You're expecting me to pick up everything, aren't you?
No way.
I can't pick that up.
Get on the...
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's check what's up top.
Okay, you've got the controls.
Up we go.
That would hurt.
That would hurt really bad.
Smashed her head against the ceiling.
All right.
What am I looking for?
I said the middle shelf is suspicious.
Wait.
There's something suspicious about that shelf I just passed.
Stay there.
Stop.
I'm not doing anything.
I said the middle shelf is suspicious.
Oh my God.
I'm not doing anything.
I swear to God.
Stop.
The middle shelf is...
I can't stop at the middle shelf.
This lift is scary, so don't say anything weird, please.
Press enter.
Enter.
Okay.
Then lower the lift.
This lift is scary, so don't say anything weird, please.
I did.
I'm sorry.
Get off.
Look.
Forward.
This lift is scary, so don't say anything weird, please.
Check.
There's nothing on the shelf that we can use for lighting a fire.
Whoa.
You did it again.
Take it easy.
Whoa.
That was too close.
Control it better.
I can't go right.
Why not?
Whoa.
I did it again.
Take it easy.
Check.
I looked carefully, but there's nothing here that we need.
Nothing?
Check.
There's nothing on the shelf that we can use for lighting a fire.
Listen.
I know you probably don't get this, but I can't put you in the middle.
For some reason, it won't let me.
The utility unit.
Okay.
Stop.
Yes.
Go back to supply unit.
The supply unit.
Run.
Okay.
I am running.
So this...
Get on.
Okay.
Let's check what's up top.
You've got the controls.
Jump.
You would think I could just go this way from here.
Whoa.
That was too close.
Control it better.
Use.
Check.
I can't.
I can't check a shelf properly unless I'm squarely in front of it.
Use the X button?
No.
Enter doesn't do anything.
There is no, like, enter.
Wait.
There's something suspicious about that shelf I just passed.
Go diagonal.
Try from the left again.
That was too close.
Control it better.
Can I do this?
Enter on the PlayStation 2 controller is...
What, though?
Does none of these buttons do anything?
Circle is talk.
I can't check a shelf properly unless I'm squarely in front of it.
Diagonally?
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute, wait a minute.
What?
No way that that works.
There's no way that that works.
Are you serious?
Come on.
It actually fucking works.
How...
There's no way I would have been able to ever assume that I could go diagonal.
I've got four.
One, two, three, four.
Check.
There's nothing on the shelf that we can use for lighting a fire.
I can't believe it.
Check.
That's unbelievable.
This magnesium chip.
Let's see.
What does it say?
Warnings for magnesium chip usage.
One, keep out of reach of children.
Two, avoid direct sunlight and temperature over 50 degrees Celsius.
Do not incinerate.
Three, hold away from face while igniting and confirm that it is extinguished.
Four, that's enough, huh?
In other words, it's like a lighter.
It won't make a weapon, but I can use it for lighting a fire.
So throw that.
What the hell is that thing called?
Magnesium.
I got the magnesium.
Off.
I can't check a shelf properly unless I'm squarely in front of it.
Get off.
Off.
Yes, maybe we should go somewhere else.
So I'm going to say throw magnesium at Spider.
So we got supply unit, food unit.
The food unit.
OK.
Run.
Yes.
This is another one of these dumb scaffolding puzzles.
This unit only has preserved food.
There's no need to check this.
Let's go.
OK.
It's apparently that easy.
Mechanical unit.
The mechanical unit.
OK.
Run.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Time thrower, shelf, shelf, power panel, out of order.
Fix power panel.
I'd feel bad if I were to wreck this anymore.
Utility unit.
Run.
I gotcha.
The shelf on the other side.
Run.
Yes.
Get on.
OK.
Let's check what's up top.
You've got the controls.
Do I?
I do.
Voltage at 50%.
The power supply is unstable.
Please raise the voltage to 100.
I can't go anywhere.
I think I have to raise the power.
Nothing works.
Check.
If you want me to check the lower shelves, I won't need the lift.
So how is this even possible?
I mean, top?
From here?
No.
I gotta get off.
Get off.
Yes.
I think we should go somewhere else.
Turn the other one off.
Supply unit.
The supply unit.
OK.
Maybe that'll defer power?
Utility unit.
I gotcha.
Run.
The shelf on the other side.
Yes.
Did it say the power?
Get on.
OK.
Let's check what's up top.
You've got the controls.
I wonder if that worked.
Yeah.
It did.
Wow.
It's pretty remarkable actually.
Check.
This.
It's a chip.
It's pretty sweet.
Check.
I looked carefully, but there's nothing here that we need.
Running to a wall here.
Nothing else?
Check.
There's nothing on the shelf that we can use for lighting a fire.
I think that's it.
Jesus.
That was too close.
Control it better.
Get off.
Yes.
Maybe we should go somewhere else.
So that was data unit.
Data unit.
The data unit.
OK.
Run.
Yes.
Check note.
What is this?
Oh, that's the...
This diagram.
That's the thing that describes...
Is it just some doodling by the staff?
That's the solution to the puzzle.
OK.
That's great.
Look at left.
How am I supposed to understand that?
What is that thing?
Look at dolly.
Leave the room?
No.
OK.
Stop.
Go back.
Yep.
Go to data panel.
The data unit.
OK.
Check left panel.
No go.
It's not working properly because it's not getting enough power.
If this was working properly, it would have been easy to check this room.
OK.
Look at platform.
It's a cart for delivering supplies to various sections.
It's for staff use.
That's it.
All right.
I think we can get out of here.
Safe point.
OK.
The safe point.
We got the fire.
We can kill the bug.
I am walking.
Mine Bitcoin.
I'm not going to say that.
Get up.
OK.
I got it already.
Leave.
Into the hallway.
OK.
I'll leave.
Go.
Did you say something?
Hallway.
OK.
I'll leave.
Be nice to her.
Where should I go?
So now we go to infirmary.
The infirmary.
OK.
This is the infirmary.
This is actually the first time I've ever been here.
Ha ha.
That'd be funny.
What?
A way to kill that spider.
I already have it.
Listen, operator.
What do you associate with an infirmary?
Can you name the sorts of things that you'd find in an infirmary?
Sure.
Medicine.
In a room this big, there should be all sorts.
Anything else?
A doctor.
Yep.
You bet.
There'd be a doctor.
Definitely.
Are there any others?
Turkey.
Thanksgiving turkey.
Christmas turkey.
A football.
Tell me some things you'd find in an infirmary.
A lawyer.
Oh.
Barium.
I absolutely loathe the idea.
Did you just say...
Can't they find a better way to...
Barium?
Come on.
More guesses.
Barium?
Surgery tools.
Uh, yeah.
Bedpan.
Are there any more?
Yes, Dora.
Let me see.
Syringes.
A syringe.
I hate them.
Can you manage one more guess?
Stuff you'd find in an infirmary.
Alcohol?
No.
I mean, alcohol, but not really.
Alcohol.
Yeah.
Disinfectant always stings on cuts or scrapes.
Yeah, let's see.
Being a medical room, there should be chemicals here.
Chemicals.
A flamethrower.
Oh.
Listen, operator.
There's gotta be a weapon we can use to kill that spider.
Chemical fire.
Alright, let's put it together.
That weapon's name...
A flamethrower.
What was it now?
You don't remember the flamethrower?
What was its name now?
I can't talk.
What was it called?
That thing.
I can't remember.
Hey, operator.
Can you name some weapons that you know?
Grenade.
A grenade or something?
Would you say the names of other weapons?
Knife.
Um...
You know that, um...
No, a stick won't do it.
A stick.
Yeah, hit it with a stick.
Hit the monster with a stick.
No, it won't do it.
Yes, it will.
A medicine.
Yes, that's it.
A weapon you can make using medicine.
No, hit it with a stick.
Uh...
Flame broiled.
We had to give up on flamethrowers already.
Um...
That weapon that burned...
A battle axe.
Was it an axe or something?
Um...
That burning weapon, what was it?
A burning axe.
That's enough about axes.
Um...
An ice enchanted axe.
That burning weapon, what was it?
A plus two lightning axe.
Operator, can you tell me the names of weapons that you know?
Lightning.
Lightning spell.
A taser.
Um...
A fiery weapon.
Sword.
A sword.
Um...
That's right, a weapon that uses alcohol.
I didn't say anything.
It's gonna Luigi me in about five seconds.
An alcohol coated sword.
No, a stick won't do it.
Um...
An alcohol stick.
That's right, a weapon that uses alcohol.
Cannon.
A cannon.
That's enough about swords.
Um...
A weapon that uses alcohol.
A bomb.
Handguns and stuff.
Huh.
Um...
A weapon that burns with alcohol.
I know what it is, but I want to see how many things she knows.
Molotov cocktail.
Molotov.
Sword.
There should be alcohol in every medical room.
We'll find some alcohol and make a Molotov cocktail.
Okay, let's look for some alcohol.
Imagine how fucking stupid you would sound if I'm an operator sitting in a room by myself
and this girl is here alone.
There's all kinds of fucking creatures and monsters and weirdos.
And she's asking me for help on what they can make for a weapon
and I'm leaning in going, you should find a sword.
You should find a sword.
Like how much of a fucking idiot would you have to be?
Operating table.
The operating table.
Okay.
A stick.
Throw a stick at him.
Operating table.
Check.
Huh?
Sorry.
It's nothing.
What?
What are you getting?
Strong memories.
Getting some backstory.
You know what I mean?
Check machine.
Oh, sorry.
Now is not the time to be talking about that.
How about the machine?
We're looking for weapons here.
There doesn't appear to be anything here.
Come on.
Let's check somewhere else.
You are really stupid.
Okay.
You are very dumb.
Yes.
You are extraordinarily untalented.
You are dumb.
Phew.
You are stupid.
All right.
What am I doing?
Check bed.
The bed.
Okay.
You are very cool.
Yes.
It's a bed for resting.
It doesn't appear to have been used at all.
That's it?
There's nothing here.
Let's look elsewhere.
There's nothing in the bed.
Nothing in the operating table.
Check desk.
The desk.
Okay.
We got some x-rays here.
Look at the x-rays.
It's from an employee checkup.
But to have someone look inside your body.
Not for me.
Thanks.
You're never going to get an x-ray?
That's really not that smart to say that.
I fell off my skateboard and I think I might have broke my arm.
We need to see where the brake is so we can determine if we need to do anything about it.
No.
I'm not doing x-rays.
I'm not doing it.
Check left drawer.
Drawer.
This one, right?
Oh, nice.
A collectible card.
It's a doctor's ID card.
It looks useful.
I'll take it.
We got...
Take a quick look at the computer monitor on the left.
The PC?
I don't know what you're saying.
The PC.
There's nothing wrong.
It's just not turned on.
Play Fortnite on PC.
The PC?
I don't know what you're saying.
Sorry.
I was doing it.
I was making a dumb joke for chat.
Go look at the books.
Open medical book.
It wasn't his own joke.
No, it wasn't.
I'm looking at it.
I'm seeing a lot of HAA.
Capital HAA.
I don't like it.
Nopers.
Ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
Nopers?
Right?
Right, guys?
Open fridge.
Refrigerated box on the right.
Glass case.
No.
What?
What the hell am I doing?
Shoot.
Here we go.
This is the perfect...
Shoot glass.
Glass.
Stop.
Shoot mirror.
Mirror.
Shoot.
Shoot case three.
Shoot case two.
Didn't work.
The normal way.
Look at panel.
Panel.
Yeah.
Card reader.
Do you have one?
Use card on card reader.
I'm not there.
ID card required for awkward opening and closing cases.
Use ID.
No.
Stop.
Use ID card on case two.
Use ID card.
Dummy.
Pick up the phone.
Open the cases.
Let's take a look.
Back.
Can I get a better angle than this?
I'm trying to do like a cinematic machinima here.
Back.
Target two.
Target enemy two.
Head shoot.
Shoot.
Target three.
Dodge right.
Target one.
No.
Target enemy one.
What in the name of God would you say?
I didn't say heal.
Enemy one.
Shoot.
Back.
Enemy three.
Shoot head.
Shoot.
Shoot stomach.
Shoot mouth.
Stomach.
Shoot.
Shot.
Dodge left.
Back.
Enemy one.
Shoot head.
Shoot stomach.
Shoot mouth.
Shoot head.
Stomach.
Gonna open them all now.
Use ID card.
Okay.
What is it?
Case three.
Okay.
I'll use the ID card.
Yes you will.
Okay.
Now you can disengage the locks.
Can I?
Open it up.
The shelf appears to be for ointments and lotions.
This is just a liquor store cabinet.
This is the beer and wine section of the grocery store.
Grab a fucking 12 pack of cider while we're at it.
This?
Here it is.
Alcohol.
Oh it is alcohol.
We can use this to make a molotov cocktail.
That's right.
Let me see.
Alan said that the spider is vulnerable to fire.
But he was using a flamethrower.
I wonder if a molotov cocktail would really do the job.
It is fire so yes.
But there's no choice.
This will have to do.
Hey, operator.
I'm finding it a little hard to believe those monsters are actually aliens.
I mean imagine it.
Aliens attacking people.
What do you think they are?
This isn't a movie.
Do you think they're like parrots?
No, it's okay.
Dogs?
Cats?
It's fine.
Anyways, we have to do something about the spider first.
It's not a spider.
It's clearly a huge fucking alien with the green eyes.
And a giant tongue.
Okay.
Now we can go exterminate that monster spider.
Alright.
We also found that magnesium chip in the equipment room.
We're ready to fight that spider, right?
I hope so.
Then let's go.
There is a couple there.
Hold on.
No, no, no, no.
Go to case four.
Case four.
Okay.
I'll use the ID card.
Now you can disengage the locks.
Hopefully I can replace a heal.
Because I accidentally used one and I didn't even mean to.
Heals?
Great.
Just one.
Shoot head.
Head.
Back.
Target enemy two.
Dodge left.
Back.
Shake.
Dodge right.
Back.
Dodge left.
Enemy one.
Shoot.
Get off.
shoot stomach mouth mouth mouth mouth back back back mouth mouth mouth you
missed every shot back back enemy one head head dodge right dodge left dodge
left oh heel heel use heels heel capsules use heel capsules use heel capsules
Jake use heel capsules god damn it this is like 20 minutes ago oh this is right
when we can get up don't tell me this is how what did I did I honest to God
please what would was the last thing I just did I got the magnesium chip oh what
a crock of shit data unit the data unit okay run yes okay no we're good we're
good leave what should I move just got to make the cocktail again that's I
wish to get out oh my fucking god hallway leave the room okay I left at
part thanks for the recap where should I go infirmary the infirmary okay run we're
gonna do the guess the fireball weapons again I'm just gonna say this is the
infirmary damn it why is there a safe point in here that I just this is
actually the first I could have just saved it and just been done and we
didn't have to do this again a way to kill that spider listen operate
yeah what's a weapon associate with an infirmary you associate can you name
the sorts of things that you'd find in an infirmary sure I can Molotov
cocktail Molotov cocktail you can find that anywhere no you can't is there
something that's more alcohol yeah disinfectant always stings on cuts
or scrapes anything else bandages bandages yes yeah mice yes
in a room this big there there should be all sorts chemicals rats chemicals
chemicals chemicals chemical chemicals chemical chemical fire chemicals yeah I
guess so an enema bag are there anymore a doctor I don't want to do
this again there'd be a doctor definitely okay can you manage one
sure can chemicals chemical fire rats gloves
oh for surgery yeah yeah for sure yeah let's see being a medical room there
should be chemicals yes I wonder if I said that to you I don't think I did
um oh listen operator there's got to be a weapon we can use to kill that
first try it's that weapons name what was it now just let me get just let me
talk I know what it is you guys see you're gonna say it like two more
times what was it called that thing I can't remember hey operator can you
name some weapons that you know sure Molotov cocktail Molotov cocktail a
pickaxe no would you say the names of other weapons Molotov cocktail enough
about pickaxes a pickaxe enough about pickaxes a Molotov cocktail cocktail
cocktail yes a weapon you can make using medicine yes Molotov cocktail
you know that fire cocktail fire cocktail fire handguns Molotov cocktail
Molotov cocktail that's gotta be it there should be alcohol in every
medical room we'll find some alcohol and make a Molotov cocktail enema
cocktail okay let's look for some alcohol where should I begin looking
save point the same run yes hey you gotta you guys got a spam I'm gonna
encourage chat spam because when I get to a new room we do a couple of
activities I need to be able to all I want to see over here is save the
game like every like 20 to 30 minutes just spam it that's the only time
I'll ever encourage it rock backwards yes dance okay dance okay can you dance
okay do you know how to dance the desk okay stop yes do you like to dance
the desk stop okay yes dance okay do a dance the desk okay good left drawer
drawer this one right shoes I'm not gonna say that okay cuz it'll it's a
doctor's ID card it looks useful I'll take it it's not gonna do anything do
you think the developers of this 2004 PlayStation 2 game thought to
put that in for any reason she doesn't even dance okay sing sing a song are
you talking about this that is actually yeah open the cabinet it's already open
check cabinet there's only anti-nausea medication nothing in there okay
x-rays it's from an employee checkup but to have someone look inside your
body not for me thanks case two are you talking about this case two case
okay it's locked it won't open you guys are fucking crazy all right use ID card
on use ID card okay got it I'll try that now all that's left is to toggle
switch I did I just saved it we're good
head shoot shoot shoot shoot three times dodge right back back
shoot dodge right dodge right
dodge left shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot dodge right back enemy three
shoot head shoot stomach shoot mouth mouth head stomach
I'm safe safe point the safe point okay yes number of commands a thousand
eighty five it's a lot of commands case three case three okay okay I'll use the
ID card good okay now you can disengage the locks
disengage and I'm just getting out of here I opened up the other case and
got attacked by very difficult monsters and it killed me
hmm the shelf appears to be for ointments and lotions huh this here it
is alcohol alcohol we can use this to make a Molotov cocktail let me see
drink alcohol Alan said that the spider is vulnerable to fire but he
was using a flamethrower I wonder if a Molotov cocktail would really do
the job but there's no choice this will have to do hey yeah I'm finding it a
little hard to believe those monsters are actually aliens you too I mean
imagine it aliens attacking people this isn't a movie no and I'll be
worried if this is a movie no it's okay it's fine anyways we have to do
something about the spider first it's finished great okay now we can go
exterminate them throw Molotov into ceiling we also found that magnesium
chip in the equipment room we're ready to fight that spider right then let's
go safe point the safe point okay yes
and 90 sweet get up okay I got it already hallway okay run leave yes we
tried sexy pose it didn't do anything I'm fully prepared to defeat that spider
it's on the other side of shutter four I'm ready
shutter four shutter four okay run run yes sprint there's only you can only run
so I got the Molotov cocktail open and throw Molotov cocktail at spider here we
go okay holding it in my hand on the other side of the show ready spider
things waiting all right it's do-or-die time are you ready mm-hmm
open door yeah those aren't open the door isn't open operator listen carefully
I'm gonna throw the Molotov cocktail right into that spider creatures mouth
listen the bottle is too heavy to throw very far and I need to time my
throw with the opening explode I need you to spider's movements on your
monitor and give me when you get the signal I'll throw the Molotov
what
there's only one Molotov cocktail if we blow it I'm as good as dead okay it's
time to waste that this is giving me anxiety I don't like the alcohol in
there here we go open the shutter still there throw the Molotov when it
gets close enough what get closer walk closer throw it I got it she fell
forward she also threw that less than ten kudos to you here's the mad doctor
that thing kept me from reaching the receiving port I was concerned thank
you I appreciate your resourcefulness is something the matter I don't like your
condescending tone don't patronize me how delightfully forthright of you to
say and what is your name it's on my name tag stock photos who are you oh my
so very brusque well it can't be helped after facing such a fearsome creature
unfortunately I am partly to blame my name is Joe powers I'm the research
supervisor of the testing ward what happened here isn't a total surprise
much of this was top secret you see my assistant Alan became aware of an
approaching UFO last year nobody believed him but I had opposed the
opening of this hotel but JSL refused to heed my warnings in preparation for
possible disaster I kept a rescue team on standby they're on their way here now
you should make your way to the receiving port I will catch up after I
find Alan I found your assistant unconscious in the Sun Suite goodness is
Alan safe I wouldn't know most movement I've seen a character doing
you need to hurry what oh that's terrible
hotel is the real monster
this is gonna Indiana Jones close in on me or something but good thing this
section wasn't sealed off not much else we can do besides obtaining a shutter
key let's take a look at that so we got shutter five there's the restrooms
go to restrooms the restrooms yes don't worry we'll get a sexy pose in
the mirror I promise I'll do it I'll do it if I don't have to see it
anymore the lights seem to be out in the back listen do you know the
story that if you die in space your soul wanders through space forever
talking about the restroom in the guest section well there are these
spooky rumors at night even though they're supposed to be no one around
this is like the 50 and 20 dollar bill the music box when they were
building the outer wall of the station there was an accident involving some
workers and three were lost two were miraculously rescued but the last
worker was never recovered that worker he said to have worn a pendant
with a family photo and a music box scary story listen operator how good are
you with stories like this it's a little scary for me I don't know I'm
too scared the music box don't go down that hall don't move it's the music
box from the story they must be true
I can't operator I can't go any further you can throw a molotov cocktail down the
throat of a giant spider alien fucking monster that was gonna kill you but
you can't walk into a bathroom go in okay I'll go back no what oh my god
safe point the safe point okay spooky scary story music box versus my
life is truly in immediate danger I will die if I do not pull off this
throw spooky scary sounds coming from the toilet okay go in the bathroom
yes I can't operator I can't go any further here what is this wall can we
look in the bathroom that's easy for you to say would it really be okay it's
going to be okay so what it's gonna be fine yeah you're right
scary because we don't know what it is okay I'll go nothing in here there's a
couple of dirty toilets right now and some journals men's stalls the men's
run no run no run no go go no walk what is going on what's she doing we're
gonna play musical stalls open stall one okay I'll open it that's a pretty
nice bathroom gold and toilet paper nothing here no nothing check this one
no problem reach hand inside toilet check stall two okay I'll open it hurry
up while you're at it there's nothing here oh they were doing the
music box dodge left leave enemy to head head head mouth mouth mouth mouth
dodge left dodge left back any three head mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth
head dodge left dodge left wait and be free head head head stomach bleep bleep
bleep head mouth stomach stomach stomach stomach
head mouth mouth stomach head back back stump Jake stomach mouth mouth mouth
lady mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth you just didn't miss stomach stomach
stomach stomach stomach open stall three which stall was that open stall
three which stall was that what hold on one two open stall two which stall was
that open the third stall which stall was that three move what exactly
right stall how am I supposed to move a stall he's not supposed to move a stall
you're supposed to open the door open the door which stall was that open the
door to stall three which stall was that open stall to his door I checked it
earlier this is stuff for there wasn't anything
stall four I checked it already this is stall one stall six I checked it
earlier there wasn't anything stall eight which stall was that stall 25 I
checked it earlier there wasn't anything stall one I checked it already
that's enough stall zero which stall was that stall two I checked it earlier
there wasn't anything middle stall you mean open a door to which stall lady
lady open the middle stalls door which stall was that open middle stall which
open the middle one which open middle stall three I checked it earlier oh my
goodness there wasn't anything she understands the stall one understands
the open stall second from left holy fuck lady I said one you opened one I
still hear the music oh yeah few okay that one so now more scared of a music
box than a dead guy in a stall open stall first from left no music box not
yet at least there's nothing here no nothing we're done with this one no
problem men's wash stands the men's wash stands run okay sexy pose sexy
pose in mirror sexy pose it doesn't work guys mirror mirror which one
mirror to installs okay men's wash tables what are they fucking called
men's wash stands okay yeah it's gonna load us middle mirror I might see
something I don't want to see left mirror it's too dark to see clearly I
can see very very clearly right mirror I sent something behind me I must be
imagining it trash are you maybe talking about that yes the trash can look in
trash can it's only biodegradable trash somebody shit in the trash can
that means examine middle mirror now that the ordinary why is it glowing
shoot mirror middle the mirror shoot the middle mirror something's written on
the wall oh two nine zero two nine I wonder what this number is but it's
there I'm gonna piss my pants again sit down the vase is tipped over it
must have been that trimmer earlier you're gonna be fine all right you
guys just just she's gonna I'm gonna go I gotta go pee listen I need
instructions if you don't have any instructions for me can I wait where
it's not dark what is she doing hold on I'm all tangled okay ready what we're
doing men's wash stands the men's wash stands yes I got a cheeseburger too
by the way it's gonna be hard to eat this and be on stream go I am walking
shoot left mirror it's shattered beautiful in there and that's it
it's like coughed out a bunch of fucking hamburger me hold on a second
beautifully that's why she'll shoot the mirrors because she's like fucking
obsessed with shooting that's the type of shit you see like a YouTube comment
oh on like a smear smashing fucking ASMR video all right shoot the right
mirror oh yeah it's shattered beautiful yeah I did and that's it
save game save point save point okay no wait wait wait wait wait big vault
door I am no no vault door what is that yeah look at door and open the
vault go to men's wash what is that thing I can't stop yeah door to your
left stop yeah look at door look at the door behind you yep large steel door
no large door no stop turn around huh door no what the fuck do I even call
this thing door next to stalls the men's wash stand no no stop turn around
stop huh turn around yeah turn around no scared the
maintenance door it's the ladies stalls stop yeah examine door walk forward okay
stop yeah turn right no turn right okay turn right look right I stopped look
at door on right door with keypad stop green light door stop yeah room closet
okay I'll leave fucking who cares ladies stalls yes examine examine stop no
examine the stall no exit examine stalls the men's doll yes okay
you want to bite suicide don't be stupid there are people who are
counting on us examine stalls the men's doll okay okay finally left door which
door on left yes open closet check check what chat what do I do open
closet door open the closet the men's wash stand holy fuck lady open check
closet the vase is tipped over it must have been that tremor earlier yeah back
okay let's go somewhere brighter stop yeah check closet check the closet
check closet yeah oh lady you are just not fucking listening check stalls the
men's dolls run no I'm scared check stalls the men's dolls okay do it one
more time I'll try it one more time check closet okay the closet oh my god
it took you forever to figure this out watch out it's you we do Ian Louie in
there back shoot head head head head head head head please please stop
motocombatting me please this is boss please please please please no it's not
fair I'm dead oh long ago is that we said sit wait but we did this took
that long for her to open up the stalls ladies room no ladies restroom it's the
ladies stalls the whole side was not even worth going into this is where the
music box is I can't operator I can't go any further here can we stop
looking here go in okay I'll go back everything is gonna be okay everything
we're fine go in the ladies stall it's the ladies stalls ladies stalls ladies
stalls that's easy for you to say would it really be okay yes yeah you're right
it's scary because we don't know what it is okay I'll go I really am frightened
you know okay where should I check first ladies stalls ladies stalls it's
the ladies stalls and there's a closet in here too we got I got oh two nine
already I need to get another code open stall one okay I'll open it found the
music box all of a sudden you're not okay with dead box stall two which
stall was that middle left stall how am I supposed to move a stall open
stall second from right I don't even know which one that was okay I'll open
it say boo okay there's nothing here I'll say boo
thank God don't stun lock me this time shoot shoot
leave right walk walk you shake leave back dodge right back target to enemy
head head head head stomach no mouth mouth stomach mouth head mouth target
head head head head mouth mouth shoot shoot shoot shoot maybe my aim is bad
save point save point okay boo boo hello boo hello boo no boo yes boo save point
it doesn't fucking save point the save point okay scream it like a normal
person ladies washroom yes ladies stall it's the ladies stalls ladies
wash table ladies wash table the ladies washstands okay now which one has the
code trash are you maybe talking about that look in trash can it's an
ordinary trash can it's not trust me reach in trash can pick up trash can
it's an ordinary trash can item in trash can there's only trash in it what I told
you what's this auto fire it says auto fire shoot middle mirror it shattered
beautifully and that's it I think I got everything ladies stalls it's the
ladies stalls got two more these to open open right most stall I checked it
already that's enough open stall second from left okay and what do we
got there is something on the ground it's a heel there's huh a heel capsule
you open right stall okay no music box
there's nothing here no nothing we're done with this one holy shit somebody
get $50 was I eating the hamburger where was I was I gone dry ski get 50
bucks 5,000 bits earlier like uh just about five ten minutes ago thank you
so much dry ski 50 bucks they say shoot head to head to head to head to head
flee flee flee listen save point save point okay that's like the fifth or
sixth more than $50 bit drop tonight thank you guys seriously thank you
dry ski again have I told her that I hate her yet I think I've said a form
of that I hate you well I'm sorry you feel that way I don't hate you the same
point okay no no no that's gonna load the screen again I hate you well I'm
sorry you feel that way I love you can you at least try to be serious there
you go women's stalls the men's stalls okay ladies stalls it's the ladies
stalls I just said it I'm not saying it again
what's open closet okay the closet it's locked it appears to be a number lock
type can you open it operator it's a no it's a lock of the number I can do
it it's probably 029 check it right music box listen operator the sound is
coming from this closet isn't it mm-hmm face you fears let's go there's no
mistake that sound is coming from in here it's what you just said I'll open
nothing in there take a lock it take lock it look at the lock it check
lock it check check check but what tissue it's ordinary tissue paper
check tissue paper are you maybe talking about that check note there's
there's some writing on it read it I think read it move what exactly read
the note wait wait a second Rio gotcha it's me hey hey was it scary I made
that story up who did huh I thought that Rio'd fall for it and come snooping
please bring back my pendant from Meg a prank didn't she say that Meg was just
pulling my leg didn't she said that was like a story everybody told but
was that Meg that told her that back to her she said I've been elaborate
prank for like ten years urban legend or something I'm not even not gonna
take the pen save point the save point okay just leave it in there leave the
pendant inside still better than a bad at the game joke we talking about
hallway hallway leave the room okay idea yeah that's right the men's stall
where should I go I can open the shutter now moon sweet she's gonna be
too scared to go back at bathroom okay understood which stall was it where
are you going okay well never mind this will open that shutter she's not
gonna sexy pose in the mirror she's too scared in that bathroom so we got
guest room five and then that's it guest room five guest room five run okay
yes undo the door lock please thanks consultation mode then sexy pose
vessel back back back back back enemy one enemy right I left I left I left
I shoot shoot left I left I middle I middle I red I head head mouth mouth
dogs left mouth mouth back back back mouth mouth mouth
let's go it's splishy oh so where should I begin actually could be tell
me please consultation okay consultation it is okay what would you
like to know about sexy pose sexy pose okay that's it for
consultation consultation okay consultation it is okay what would you
like to know about so long is this if I move this down does this screw up
the rest of the frame I wonder I wonder if I ruin it okay I guess we're done
with the consultation I guess it has to have those bars huh maybe not
necessarily that's okay is he actually watching me he is all right
shoot lamp the bed okay look out there's a shutter key on the dresser
listen is there some way of putting out a fire water use water we need water
but I can't get to the bathroom bucket it's just a bucket pick up
bucket the bucket is too close to the fire I can't get it leave impossible I
wouldn't come close to reaching the dresser with a shutter key a shoot
bucket further away huh what is that if only I could but I can't get the
fire extinguisher from here shoot fire extinguisher the fire
shoot extinguisher that wasn't pleasant but the fire's gone out this will let us
open that shutter key I probably should heal okay let's go we go get a bed
very emergency panel the emergency run yes I'll check it just in case no
there was nothing anything in them okay we got a safe point safe point the safe
point okay I wonder how much more of the game there is I'm gonna say like
another hour I bet you were getting close get up okay I got it already
dresser the dresser okay I think we're done with checking this place
it's already been smashed let's check somewhere I don't care anymore
hallway okay I'll leave run yes it has to be Naomi Naomi hello is this Naomi
you can hang up now she's not there operator you heard that right mm-hmm
this is fantastic Naomi safe hurry let's find her so we got shutter is
six shutter six shutter six okay run run yes not another spider right left
left eye right eye middle I know I little I little I middle I bright I
bright I read I read I do two two two two two two shoot
mouth mouth mouth mouth how the weak points are gone body tail back what
body red eye dodge left body tail tail tail
usually it dies after you get the red eye yeah the screen doesn't fit you're
right I'm gonna we have to have those bars so that's why it has to look
like this oh well is he actually watching me shutter six wait don't do
that yet show you'll capsule okay yes sure six
shutter six run okay yes use autofire if I just say autofire does that work
this will open that shutter yep and analyze sweet those the moon sweet we
finally made it to here the receiving port is just ahead
monster new NPC take your guess I wonder if someone's there I'll check who's the
evil evil mastermind behind the whole thing I wonder probably the doctor
that's the easiest answer is there anyone here I'll check in the back if
you see anything tell me okay don't screw up behind you behind watch out
I am being careful I heard something huh what to your left there doesn't appear
to be anyone I must have been imagining things sorry guess I didn't
need you that time don't you got him this guy shoot shoot him so sorry
about that apparently some of the aliens are humanoid in appearance I'm
lost a good man to one sorry to hear that
what is the situation know anything I'm not sure what's happening either but
I've been told that a rescue team will be arriving in the receiving port
excellent rescue car muffler rescue team oh dear that's wonderful
it's good news yes but sir which unit could it be
then we have a gun perhaps army special forces if so that makes this a
military incident there was talk that the police department had a task force
capable of this type of rescue and extraction if that's the case and it
is the police we should be able to cover up some of the legal issues
that will stem from this incident still it's a problem I wasn't in
yes of course discussing politics at this very moment by the way there's a
big problem so much shutter is locked in and it won't open he's got mr.
freeze hands it shouldn't be a problem why I have an operator backing
me up he'll open it for us you can do it right fuck every single one of
you you're determined to make life difficult piece of cake you're all
losers all of you she muted means like I know he can do it good but we aren't
the only ones in need of rescuing get word to the team leader that I won't
board the shuttle yes sir understood fine let's be on our way listen
I told you that I need proper guidance the way things are going I fear for my
future what about my future I'm locked in the surveillance room without food
or water at least you can drink little heel juices I don't have any of
that the door panel appears to have been broken we can't get into the
moon suite anymore okay the Prime Minister's party is headed for the
receiving port we need to hurry elevator hall the elevator hall okay run
run yes the operator hasn't gone to the bathroom in over four hours yeah I
have back back dodge right dodge right dodge right
fleet head mouth shoot auto-fire lady color guy please
enemy to enemy to inner mouth enemy to inner mouth
inner mouth any Jim a mouth mouth mouth jiu-jiu-jiu-jiu-jiu-jiu-jiu
shoot you take you stroke your jiu-jiu-jiu inner melts inner mouth
mouth, shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, auto fire, you are so bad, shoot, shoot, shoot, auto
fire, back up, dodge left, back, back, mouth, mouth, dodge left, back, back, head, shoot,
stomach, elevator hall, the elevator hall, yes, saves it, there will be a save point right here,
where should I go, receiving port, the receiving port, run, back, back, back, back, front limb,
front limb, front limb, front limb, front limb, tongue, mouth, mouth, mouth, dodge right,
shit, heel capsule, heel capsule, heel capsule, heel capsule, back up, mouth, inner mouth,
flee, flee, dodge left, dodge left, dodge left, you imbecile, dodge left, why would you run back
to the right, dodge left, shoot, hind limb, shoot, back, mouth, fire, shoot, shoot, shoot,
auto fire, dodge left, dodge left, holy shit, you are an imbecile, dodge left, dodge left,
dodge left, heel capsule, dodge left, heel capsule, dodge left, this is holy shit,
give me a break, dodge left, dodge left, now I'm just gonna run right again,
heel capsule, heel capsule, heel capsule, heel capsule, shoot, heel capsule, heel,
where is this, get up, okay, I got it already, hallway, okay, yes, you have to be patient,
it's hard to be patient when there's enemies shooting spit in your face,
and you have to dodge, dodge left, I guess I will, but not, I'm not gonna do it again,
when you tell me to do it again, why would I do that, give me a break,
right, right, right, right, fire, why can't you just shoot the enemies, I need someone to tell
me when to shoot, I'm the one, you're the one holding the gun, just do it, thank you bro luck
for the hundred dollars, hundred and two dollars actually, that's a shitload of money,
hundred and two bucks, and you say you're so bad at this game mate, I don't even know
if that's physically possible to be bad at a game from 2004 with voice activation,
I don't think it's possible, hundred bucks of, it's just, you talk, I'm talking, I'm talking to
you, do you see how many times I said the same thing like a thousand times, and she looks
at me like a fucking dog, like tilting her head sideways, like huh, I don't know what that word
is, shutter six, shutter six, okay, run, yes, fuck thank you so much bro luck, that's a lot
of fucking money, you have to enunciate, so when I say dodge left, that's not, what, back,
back up, right eye, right eye, middle eye, left eye, left eye,
left eye, middle eye, middle eye, right eye,
right eye, red eye, red eye, red eye, back, mouth, shoot, shoot, auto fire,
auto fire, body, tail, back, dodge right, dodge right, dodge left,
dodge left, back, dodge left, dodge left, dodge left, dodge left, flee, flee, recover capsule,
mouth, shoot, auto fire, mouth, mouth, body, tail, dodge left, dodge left, dodge right, dodge right,
how did you still hit me, shoot tail, tail, shoot the tail, tail, shoot,
it's tough going, bro look, you just gave two hundred and three dollars to tell me how bad I was
at the talking game, what, instructions, safe point, guest room five, guest room five, okay,
run, yes, that's two hundred and three dollars, undo the door lock please, thanks,
I can't accept his badness, you, I don't even need, I'm not even, I don't even need to defend
myself, what, why would I even defend myself against this, what would I do that for,
there's no reason for me to defend this, save point, the save point, okay, run, yes,
rich because bad, that's like the third time I've died in the whole entire playthrough,
what's that term called, let me, let me, let me, what's that term called, let me see,
let me tell her, it's called give me a break, it's three deaths in five hours,
the save point, okay, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop, but anyways, thank you bro luck for
the, for the three, for the three hundred, I want, I want to understand this here,
three hundred and three dollars, three hundred bucks, three hundred dollars, can you just admit
it please so I can stop donating, don't, what, why are you doing this, get up,
hallway, I'm not gonna, why would I admit that I'm bad, it's a, it's a game where you tell
somebody, oh you're not getting an admission from me, recover, yes, hallway, okay, I'll leave,
I'm not gonna say it, the bed, okay, hallway, huh, no, no pulse, this person's gone, bro like
thanks for the three hundred and three dollars, examine coat, are you talking about this, that
is a coat, examine bathrobe, the bathrobe, yes, I don't need that,
get the grab item on bathrobe, shooting something like this won't accomplish a thing,
but you know it's definitely your bad, examine, okay, examine item on bathrobe,
the bathrobe, I don't need that, card on bathrobe, it's the hotels, they only loan it out to guests
who ask for it, examine bathrobe pocket, the bathrobe, I don't need that, look in pocket,
huh, of what, of the, of the, of the, you must be bad at the game, you must be bad at the
game, that's enough, thank you, all right bro luck, you, this is ridiculous, thank you for the four
hundred dollars, you know, I don't have to do any more, you don't have to do any more,
that's, that's way more money than you should ever, in one minute here, bro luck, that's a
lot of fucking money, and they say, I swear to fucking god this is becoming reckless, please
admit it, I just proved on camera, on stream, that I don't have to, you just saw on like in real time,
I don't have to, but for the sake of you not doing that again, I know, why would I do that,
look in bathrobe pocket, it's the hotels, there's nothing strange about it, check pocket,
huh, of what, check bathrobe pocket, it's the hotels, there's nothing strange about it,
grab key card in pocket, are you talking about this, what, grab card, are you talking about this,
but honest to god bro luck, I am not bad at this game, it's, I'm playing through it and it's fun,
and pocket in the bathrobe, grabbed which pocket in bathrobe, what bathrobe, this one,
thank you for the four hundred fucking dollars, you're awfully slow with instructions, grab the
key in the bathrobe, there's something inside, that's unfucking believable, it's a chip,
all right, can I, can I like ban bro luck from giving money, that's five hundred dollars dude,
five hundred, that's five hundred, all right, all right, I gotta save, I gotta save your bank
account, I'm, you can't, you can't do that again, I'm bad at the game, there you go,
I gotta, you're done, you're awfully slow with instructions, I'm not good at the game,
I'm very bad at speaking, I'm very bad at having somebody interpret the things that I'm
saying when I clearly say them at least 15 times in a row and I just say the same thing again
in a different way and she takes it out of the pocket, so I'm sorry I'm bad at that,
thanks for the five hundred fucking dollars, save point, the save point, okay, Carlos the
clam gave 24 dollars, this game can be beaten in under three hours Jerma, I can look it
up, I'm sure it could, but you've gotta be good, all right, that's a, here comes, here comes the
confessions, here comes the clips of me saying it, get up, hallway, why do I even need to,
hallway, well I don't even need to have this conversation, it's, it's remarkable that this
thing can even hear me talk in the first place, this is, this is, it's 14, 15, 6, 7, 8, 9, this is
15 fucking you, what are you doing, thanks mate, now I don't have to donate anymore to prove my
point, I'm glad because I've only got a hundred dollars left, all right, that's six, shutter six,
I can't fucking believe you just gave 600 dollars, you gave fucking that much money,
you are mad, you are mad, no, no, run, yes, no, no, no, stubborn screamer scams innocent
fan out of life savings, that didn't happen, thank you bro, look for the unbelievable amount
of money to tell me that I'm bad at this game, for me to say that I'm bad at the game,
I wonder if someone's there, I'll check, today we learned bribing Jerma to say something works
but it's because he's afraid of getting more money from you and feels bad, all right,
this time I'm gonna get it, is there anyone here, I'll check in the back, if you see anything,
tell me, that was an unbelievable last like 25 minutes, that last like 20 minutes was wild,
there doesn't appear to be anyone, I must have been imagining things,
sorry, guess I didn't need you, to the right, right, right, right,
shoot, but I'm bad at the game, I'm so bad, I'm so terrible at this game,
mad because bad, bad because bad, mad because bad,
apparently some of the aliens are humanoid in appearance, lost a good man to one,
oh sorry to hear that, you work here, don't you, what is the situation in the hotel,
you know anything, I'm not sure what's happening either, but I've been told that a rescue team
will be arriving and receiving, all right you've banned, somebody ban him, a rescue team, oh dear
that's wonderful, oh it's good news, yes, oh that's wonderful, how do I stop somebody from
giving money to a twitch stream, that's uh seven, you see that's fucking wild when you say it,
I don't, uh 700 bucks, oh my god, that's too much money, that's too much money bro like,
I just got informed by chat that you just scammed me, well mate I ain't falling for it again,
it shouldn't be a problem, I have an operator backing me up,
he'll open it for us, 700 fucking bucks, you can do it right, I'm looking over it,
yes I'll do it, I'll save us all, there's no need to be formal with me,
he says he can, oh what the fuck is going on, what are you guys doing,
good, but we aren't the only ones in need of rescuing,
get word to the team leader that, Tora T just gave me 50, yes sir, understood,
fine, that's 50 community subs, I never expected to be attacked by Prime Minister
Takayama's bodyguard, we both better be prepared for more surprises, a lot of community subs
from one person, 700 dollars and then 200, 500, what, how much that's, oh no, most,
mostly lost 50 dollars, it's too much money for one stream,
all right, we've got, we can do the stream money cool down now, the door panel appears
to have been broken, we can't get into the moon suite anymore, mostly lost says, time him out,
or else I'll donate more money, my fingers are on the buy bits button, don't make me do it,
no I don't, I can't do that, all right, we're on stream money cool down now,
local man donates 700 dollars to his favorite streamer to prove his love only to get banned
when the streamer finds out he has no money left to give, you're awfully slow with
instructions, that's so evil but it's not the case, no he's not banned, all right,
where do I need me to go, thank you for the fucking like 1500 bucks, how did we just gain
like 1500 viewers, what just happened, did Joel just come in with a raid, oh my god,
20 subs, there's too much going on, so should I just go off on my own, yes, go off on your
own, how am I supposed to understand that, okay, we got, first of all, we gotta, hold on,
my brain is in five different places, Joel just, what the fuck are you doing, okay, first of
all, exhibit A, Joel just came in with a raid, raid, a bunch of people, thanks Joel, hope you
had a good stream, welcome everybody from Joel's channel, go check out Joel, he's fucking
awesome, streams are awesome, he's a really funny, really awesome guy, welcome guys,
second of all, 50 dollars came in from, most of the loss gave 80, great Canadian fuck,
just gave 100 community subs from great Canadian fuck club, and then we have 20,
20, okay, I gotta get at it, I gotta leave, this is too much, Kyra Toby gave 20, 100 from,
100 subs from, I just got electrocuted, somebody electrocuted me, get in the clown car,
gave a shitload, 20 at least, okay, should I just go off on my own, thanks, thank you
everybody, we're, elevator hall, elevator hall, elevator hall, she's not listening anymore,
elevator hall, okay, needs Vaseline with 28 community subs, run, I have to kill this
thing, I have to fight this, 20 more, Philly, why do they spawn in such a weird place, mouth,
mouth, stomach, front limb, front limb, shoot, shoot, mouth, mouth, mouth, mouth,
inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth, mouth, tongue, reload, tongue, tongue,
inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth,
I keep saying it, tongue, tongue, where am I, where's my character,
too many people, there's another 100 fucking dolls, oh, I gotta, eye, tongue, in, eye,
body, body, in her mouth, in her mouth, what the fuck is happening right now,
that's a hundred dollars from bro, like a hundred dollars from, from, from,
god, g-h-y-h-d-h-e-f-e, a hundred dollars,
I want you to give me instructions. Are you guys are you guys trying to make me like buy a house on stream?
This is definitely over a 15th at least $2,000 at this point. What am I gonna do with this money? I'm gonna have to
Well, I don't know to say there's a fucking insane amount of money over $2,000 probably
Frility gave a bunch of ten community subs here hundred dollars from Brolic again hundred dollars from GYH
Elevator hall and this all started because somebody was trying to make me say that I I'm bad at this game
Where should I go? You guys are unbelievable unbelievable. I I really hope that you guys
Hi, I can't even believe it
Receiving port the receiving port, okay
Back back back front limbs
Front-limb front-limb mouth mouth autofire
Project dodge right dodge left dodge left dodge left
Dodge left dodge left dodge left
Dodge left
Enemy one dog dog left
dodge left
That is so hard to get away from that body
mouse inner mouth
inner mouth
Recover
tongue body body body body body
inner mouse inner mouth
inner mouth
inner mouse
Dodge left
Dodge right
dodge, right
matter
right eye
middle eye
left eye
tail
Left eye left eye red eye red eye
Got through this room, but seriously guys
Let's go. I don't know what to say. That was an extreme last 25 minutes. The receiving port is up ahead
Stream that happened so quickly and so much money came through stream labs can't even keep up with it
This is this is just still porn in
Hallway the hallway. Okay, moon suite the moon suite. Okay, run. Yes
It's actually somebody said by a vibe
It's really funny that you say that cuz I was actually looking at because of the the new vibe got just not into the moon
Sweet and like the cosmos, right? I
Can't get into the minister's party is headed for the receiving port. I can't say we need to hurry
Elevator hall the elevator hall. Okay
Look at that. Just take do just just do me a quick little favor here everybody that's in chat
Just look at the top bits right now
Look at how ridiculous that is
That is absolutely fucking insane
Where should I go?
Wow
Receiving port the receiving port, okay
Someone gave a hundred thousand bits at one time. I don't know say thank you guys. Oh my god
What was the holdup everyone that came from Joel's worried channel? You sorry you kind of jumped in the middle of that
But get the operator the main gate now
It's up to you
It's a little too quiet
Stand on left. Are you talking about that? Yeah, put put face in key card
No, okay for controlling the power supply to a gate. We need the shutter open quick
How we're done, okay
three two one
Here comes at least three four deaths
Give me water. It's gonna be like a huge rushing water
Muffler guy still has the muffler. That's great
Dear hey, there's no one here
It's like we're gonna get surrounded. Where is the rescue team?
Perhaps they haven't arrived yet, sir
This isn't a good place to be if we were attacked by aliens in the air gloves, okay, I get it
At least three people are dead here
We get a full motion video
We're surrounded
Who told you about the rescue team it was a supervisor mr. Powers. I knew something was wrong
We think muffler guy first. I'll draw their attention when I do that
Sir, I can't let you do that. Listen, how many can you take?
No, you can't you can barely take one I figured in that case more for me
But it gets shown up here
For missed shots. Well, you're just as bad as I am. That's what he's terrible
Apparently
People could fit an event up there there's like 60 people in the vent
They all aimed down to start firing at the same time. Do I get rescued to
Barricade the perimeter so nothing can break in. Yes, sir
I'm sorry about your friend. It could make a rainbow six siege
I consider
Captain Yatsu made us sir
The shuttle terminal has been destroyed
So we had to break through the ceiling
That delayed our arrival. Oh
We received a transmission from mr. Powers describing what has taken place
We'll be setting up our base of operations here in the receiving court
We will take all survivors into protective custody here
Barricades will be erected to keep the aliens out do not leave the area for any reason
Is that understood understood?
The suit do I get to wear that may I borrow this that's an armored suit for combat use I
Want to get changed out of these clothes? They're all sticky with sweat
So, okay, I can wear this right
Fine go ahead
She was so against changing clothes two hours ago
All of a sudden she wants to wear the earthworm Jim costume
I mean, I'll be to be honest though. If there was an earthworm Jim
Costume available. I would put it on too. All right, so no, we're still going operator. What's next listen to this
Naomi is definitely not here
She must be waiting for help somewhere in the center. Look the rescue team will be here soon enough in
The meantime, let's go find Helen Johnson the reporter. I can't do this without your help
Will you just trust me just a little while longer?
No, hey
We're not through here
You're still helping me, right? I haven't had water in seven hours and I haven't had food in seven hours
Will you just trust me just a little while I'm dying up here. Will you just trust me just a little while longer?
Thanks, I'm putting my trust in you, too
Leaving the gun I know this will work and I managed to get one of these the PMS group should be safe now
Dollars just came in
from Kara Toby
Okay, let's get out of here
200 bucks and they say I got a round out for brola. Hey, what do you think you're going?
You're not going anywhere nobody is going anywhere. Holy shit guys
Our guns are useless. We're under attack by some invincible alien. Does it look like a giant spider? Use a flamethrower
Soldier we're never gonna get to see the answer me. Hey, what's happening there? Thanks a lot guys. Seriously, Kara Toby bro like
Vladimir like this people that gave more than like the five fucking hundred subs
I think that came in community subs. You guys are fucking unbelievable
my god
Got away safely
Thanks to that wireless system
Just dude me. They're supposed to be a monster that even the rescue team couldn't handle
We have to find Helen and Naomi as soon as we can. It's not safe. I'm going for it. I'll go for it
If we were to check every room one by one, we'd surely find them
Past here's doing great transgender pride. Where shall we check first?
Fuck yeah. All right, where we going?
Control
Control staff quarters. I am I said control control staff quarters the control staff quarters. Okay
Undo the door lock, please
Wait, what was what's going on?
Here's some for the earthworm Jim fursuit fund
Open door
Thanks. Nobody appears to be here
Everybody settled that every settled down. So that settled down every settled down. I
Just saw people putting this but they all right. Yeah, what fucking hell? Yeah
Is he actually watching me? All right, check table the table. Okay
Eat candy drugs candy is not going to restore my health. I don't need any. What is it a bag?
The balcony no, no, no, no, no the bat. Stop stop
Stop. Yes
Table the table. Okay, so go to it. I just said it
Head I got a new gun
Please
Enemy one dodge left
Dodge left
mouth
Mouth mouth. Why are you holding the gun like this mouth?
mouth mouth shake
mouth head
Autofire
You can't be this bad
stomach
Fleet it's not possible to be that bad back
recover
fleet oh
Right eye. Oh my god, right eye
Left eye middle. I
middle-eye shake
fleet
Middle-eye. Oh my god, if you didn't just miss it 200 rounds dodge left
Dodge left dodge left
recover
Dodging dodge right dodge right dodge right enemy three head
head
mouth
How could you do it your handgun with mouth? I'm gonna when did I say this fleet fleet
The machine gun is awful
enemy freeze
enemy to
know
dodge left
enemy one enemy freeze
mouth
mouth mouth
Mouth how long ago is that? Wait a minute. Hold on
This is the last time I was even allowed to save the game
This was an hour ago. That's the last time I was allowed to save the game
Well, if I didn't miss
400 rounds point blank out of like 420 up. Yes
I couldn't I can't go back in this room. This is the last room. I was allowed to go in
Hallway because this the electricity happens and it's like, oh, I can't do that anymore
Hallway. Yes
Hallway, okay. I'll leave I can't believe with a machine gun. You you missed almost five hundred fucking times point blank
Where should I go? Oh
Man what?
Shutter six. This is how far back that is. Okay, run. Yes
I don't think there was even a save point in the middle
It was like the the hallway stuff the bunch of cutscenes
Cutscene again military comes in and then that was there even I don't think it was even a save point
Maybe in that room that I walked into
We finally made it to here
The receiving port is just ahead
Yeah, cuz I can't leave this happens and then when I come out I can't go anywhere right check
Is there anyone here?
This is terrible, I'll check in the back if you see anything tell me don't screw up
There doesn't appear to be anyone. I must have been imagining things. Sorry. Guess I didn't need you that time. Look out
I
Damn it. No, there's so much in between this shit. Apparently some of the aliens are humanoid
I'm gonna try this one more time. Sorry to hear that. We're so we're very they're so close to me. What is the situation in the hotel?
No, anything
I'm not sure what's happening either
But I've been told that a rescue team will be arriving in the receiving port. We have to be getting close
rescue team a
Rescue team. Oh, dear. That's wonderful. Oh, it's good news. Yes
But sir, which unit could it be
Let's see how far this one special forces
If so, that makes this a military incident
There was talk that the police department had a task force capable of this type of rescue and extraction
if that's the case and it is the police we should be able to cover up some of the legal issues that
Stem from this incident still it's a problem. I wasn't involved. Oh, yes
It's got some politics
By the way
There's a big problem. The receiving port shutter is locked in and it won't open
What's that? It shouldn't be a problem. I have an operator backing me up. He'll open it for us
You can do it, right?
Yes, I knew you could do it. Yes, I can go. He says he can hurry. Oh
Good news
Good. He's still here. We aren't the only ones in need of rescuing
Get word to the team leader that I won't board the shuttle
Yes, sir
Understood fine. Let's be on our way. I
Never expected to be attacked by Prime Minister Takayama's bodyguard
We both better be prepared for more surprises
Okay for a luck got baited into dropping 800
See remember that the door closes behind me
And I can't go in here
Why would you the door panel appears to have been broken is the only safe point back here?
I can't get into the moon. Why wouldn't you let somebody save the game after like a long-ass cutscene like that?
The Prime Minister's part I go through the shuttle port. We need to hurry like tonight shutters six shutters six
Can I go through it?
Run. Yes
What should I do now?
guest room five
guest room five so far away
Run yes, and do the door lock, please
Thanks my chat experience. What is this? What's what what's wrong? What's happening?
Save point the save point. Okay
Wait people don't know we're talking politics. No, nobody's always talking politics. Are we we got a rule? No politics?
Yeah, okay. I got it already
Okay
Hallway, so now we got now. We have to watch another cutscene
If I lose it again
we might transition to
IRL headset hair cam where should I go?
Elevator hall the elevator hall run. Hey, come on get there quick
Run. Yes, please die quickly. I'm bored of this
well, the reason why you're bored of it is because
We had to go back and do it all over again. I'd be bored of it too back
dodge left
Target enemy to
Front limb shoot shoot shoot
body body body body body body body
mouth
mouth mouth mouth
Mouth mouth inner mouth inner mouth
inner mouth
Forward inner mouth inner mouth
enemy one
Where I don't know head
What are you talking enemy one
Enemy one get up
Please
Enemy one. Oh my god. Turn around
enemy one
head
stomach stomach
mouth
Let's go. No, it was unbelievable. You gotta be kidding me recover. Yes
Yeah, but we still we still do it we're gonna put it into
Put into emote only for five minutes people are we still talking politics in here. Is he actually watching me?
Don't just don't mention it. Well, if every time I look over here people are like arguing with each other. I don't want that
Receiving port the receiving port. Okay, where should I go?
Receiving port the receiving port, okay
Well, all right if we hold on front limb front limbs front limb front limb
body body
mouth
Come on. I gotta get this one quick mouth
mouth mouth
mouth
inner mouth
Inner marvelous inner mouth inner mouth reload inner mouth inner mouth
in the mouth
inner mouth
dodge left
Dodge left. Holy fuck back back
right eye left eye
Recover the cover recovery dodge left Todd left
Ha ha ha. Middle eye. Right, left eye. Left eye. Red eye.
Receiving port.
Save, save. No, I don't even care. I gotta run all the way back to like room five.
I'm not gonna lose. We're gonna do it right now. Everyone, the guy dies.
It's up to you. Hallway. It's a little too quiet.
Right panel. Panel? What panel do you mean?
I'm just here enjoying the stream. That's good.
Dear? Hey, there's no one here. Where is the rescue team?
Perhaps they haven't arrived yet, sir. This isn't a good place to be.
If we were attacked by aliens in the open...
That's no good. Turn around.
We're surrounded.
Who told you about the rescue team?
It was the supervisor, Mr. Powers.
I knew something was wrong.
Oh, what? I pressed select.
Before.
Listen to this. Naomi is definitely not here. She must be waiting for help somewhere.
I pressed every button like three times.
Look, the rescue team will be here soon enough.
In the meantime, let's go find Helen Johnson, the reporter.
I can't do this without your help.
Will you just trust me? Just a little while longer?
Come on. Come on, just do it.
No. Yes.
Thanks. I've been interested in you two.
I wanna sneeze into the microphone so bad, but I haven't been able to do it ever.
I get sneeze shy when it happens. It's really irritating.
I know this will work, and I managed to get one of these.
Yeah, you're a terrible shot.
The P.M.'s group should be safe now, especially with weapons like these to protect them.
Okay, let's get out of here.
I can't believe select does it, and I really thought I pressed it a dozen times.
Phew. Got away safely, thanks to that wireless system.
There's supposed to be a monster that even the rescue team couldn't handle.
We have to find Helen and Naomi as soon as we can.
Can I go back and receiving port?
It's not safe. If we were to check every room one by one, we'd surely find them.
Past here is the staff area. Where shall we check first?
Receiving port, right?
Receiving port.
The receiving port, okay?
Just go back in, see if there's a kiosk.
Aren't we going to look for Naomi?
No, okay, so then...
Let's move on.
Surface staff quarters.
The service staff quarters.
Run.
Yes.
Listen, do you hear shooting?
Shooting?
I think it's from the warehouse. We should check it out. It's a dead end this way.
Why is that showing up on stream right now? That's from an hour and a half ago.
If something happens, I need you to tell me what to do.
That is so big.
That's a cosplay gun.
A major wobble was detected in the fake station's rotation.
The station was placed on emergency status, although the wobble will not interfere with its orbit.
Phew. It sounds like a war zone.
I think there was a warehouse key in my room.
One person shooting.
Let's go get it. It's in the service staff quarters.
So I have to go in there.
Service staff quarters.
The service staff quarters. Okay.
Run.
Yes.
Really?
Back.
Right eye.
Left eye.
Middle eye.
My body.
Red eye.
Did you see that?
Okay, let's go.
Service staff quarters.
The service staff quarters.
Run.
Okay.
Yes.
What is this?
Big monster?
This is bad.
What about my room?
My room?
What do you mean my room?
Oh, this is fantastic.
I just ran into like the last boss.
Back.
Shoot root.
Root.
Branch's root.
Branch's body.
Root.
Branch's leaf.
Right eye.
Enemy two.
Stomach.
Enemy three.
Head.
Stomach.
Root.
Branch's leaf.
Root body.
Root.
Enemy.
Root body. Root body root. Root body root. Branches. Branches. Branches. Middle eye.
Middle eye. Middle eye. Middle eye. Middle eye. Left eye. Middle eye. Right eye. Dog
left. Back. Back. Leap. Body. Middle eye. What's going on? Safe point. What is happening right
now? I didn't touch anything. I didn't say anything. Safe point is right here. Get out
of that machine and go downstairs and save. Can't be. I know this person. Oh all my clothes.
My pictures. Where are all my pictures? This is awful. I just I give up. You're not gonna have a
react. Oh I have to convince Conventure to keep going. Root body. Root body. Left eye. Root
body. Leaf. We can do this. We can do it. There are so many mementos. We can root body.
Leaf body. Root body. We can do it. I shouldn't have brought them all. If you upset about the
clothes. I've got clothes and I'm willing to let you have some. Money. You want money. My clothes.
You want money. You want. I can give you some money. My photographs. We can get a new camera
too. You're right. I can't let myself get too depressed over things like this but
phew. You can have that 200 dollars. See all it took was hey you can have some money
and you can have some clothes. You want some money? No that wouldn't be it. Do you want any money?
No that wouldn't be it. I think I've forgotten something important. What was it? You want your
clothes? No I'm into my room. Why did I come here? I don't know. I think I came for something.
You brought me up here. Listen can you help me remember? What did I come to get?
A photo. Listen can you help me remember? What did I come to get? A gift a gift card. Don't
choke around. Tell me please. What did I come to get? A key. Oh yes. I came to get the
warehouse card key. Okay we figured it out. It was around here. Here it is. Good. It's not
all filthy. Now we'll be able to get into the warehouse. Save point. The save point. Yeah
yes yes yes. We're at the I'm almost at the end of the game. I got my we saw the room. We got
my key card. We got my Friday's gift card. Save point. The save point. Please tell me
that's where you're going. Four hours and 12 minutes. This is gonna be almost six hours.
What is something going on with the in-game timer? That seems wrong. All right let's go
galley. Run. Yes. It's probably a health pack. It's pretty messy in here.
Hey a heal capsule. There doesn't seem to be anything else. Hallway. Let's check somewhere
else. Hallway. Leave the room? Okay. It's almost the 23rd. Yeah but the 23rd at 7 43
or 7 23 p.m. So which is 4 23 pacific. So I plan on starting the stream somewhere
around like 3 30 ish tomorrow. We'll hang out and I will make sure that I'm good to go.
So I need the warehouse. Warehouse. The warehouse. Okay. Run. Run. Yes. Do you remember
that awful noise? The hockey stuff won't protect you from a disease. I'm going to proceed
cautiously. I'll have fucking hockey mask on. I'll be all right. Huh? Pitch black.
What about you? Can you see me? No. That's a little too scary. I'm stopping.
I'll turn back for now. So what am I supposed to do here? Now I'm stuck. Without your support,
I don't have the confidence to go through. Maybe we need to find an alternate route. Should
I just lie to her and say that I can see her? Where should I go? Control staff quarters.
The control staff quarters. Okay. Run. Run. Run. Yes. Still in warehouse rondo. Yeah.
Undo the door lock, please. Thanks. Here we go. Nobody appears to be where I died last time.
Where should I start looking? Um, save point. Save point. The save point. Yes.
Yes. Do a Jexy pose. Oh. I am stopped. Stand. Okay. I got it already.
Second floor. The second floor. Run. Okay. Yes. Stomach. Stomach. Stomach. Stomach.
Stomach. Flee. Flee. Enemy one. Enemy one.
Head. Stomach. Stomach. Dodge right. Dodge right. Stomach. Stomach. Head. Head. Right eye.
Attack. Dodge left. Dodge left. Why didn't you dodge left? Dodge left.
Dodge right. Dodge right. Right eye. Dodge right. Right eye. Left eye. Middle eye. Red eye.
Dodge left. Head. Stomach. Head. Head. Oh, fuck. Head. Dodge right. Head. Head. Head. Stomach.
Head. Head. Stomach. Mouth. Head. Mouth. Stomach. All right. Um, save point. The save point. Okay.
Run. Yes. You're not bad at this game. Hey. Thank you. I really appreciate that.
Because we had a $1700 argument about an hour and a half ago. Appreciate that. Second floor.
Run. Yes. So what am I looking for up here? I meant to say you're awful at it. Not bad.
That's very funny. Right vault door. Door. Door. No. No. Get your body back upstairs.
Stop. Stop. Oh my fucking god. Back. Out. Second floor. Run. Run. Control panel.
Stop. Panel. Huh? Door panel. Hello? Panel on left. Door. Panel on left. Okay. Stop. Yes. Big
octagon. Circle door. This is the second floor. Circle door. Second floor. Jonathan's room.
Jonathan's room. Okay. This is Jonathan's private room. There's a voice lock in place.
Disengage the lock. This is a message for Jonathan Turner. Hi. I'm Jonathan and this is my room.
I don't know who you are, but if you want to enter my room, you have to answer this question.
You see, there's something that I've been secretly collecting. Okay. Are you ready?
Speak your answer into the mic. Something that he's collecting.
What's he talking about? I'll defer to you. Bugs. Maybe it was a bit too tough.
A hint, huh? Food. I'm not going to tell you anymore. Um, I don't have the slightest idea.
Maybe there are hints to be found in this room. This is a message for Jonathan Turner.
Can you identify what I collect? Are you ready? Say your answer into the mic.
Imagine if your password to your private room on a giant public cruise ship was candy. Candy.
Maybe it was a bit too tough. Candy. A hint, huh? Candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy.
Slightest idea. Maybe there are hints to be found in this room.
Balcony. The balcony. Run. Okay. Run. Yes. Under couch. Under the bench?
Huh. What could it be? Password. It says I like that thing. What it is. But it's not
not my password there's a formula written on this it might be useful for
something I'll take it okay trash are you talking about this look in trash can
I'll look in the trash can they're only cut up scraps of cardboard in it look
at plant it's an ordinary house plant but all the plants in the station are
often studied to obtain data Gustav's room Gustav's room okay run yes this is
Gustav's private room there's a voice lock in place hey it's me Gustav I want
to tell you I love stamps and I'll tell you my favorite state you're gonna have
to guess it this is a message for Gustav Meyers read this oh wait a second this
paper chi chi chi chi chi chi chi chi chi what the hell the question by
referring to this butane pentane huh CH3CH is that CH2 CH1 this is
to chloroprimethyl butane to chloroprimethyl butane wrong to
chloroprimethyl butane butane I don't think so the number on CH is
different chloroprimethyl read this if you look at this paper carefully you
should be able to solve the riddle to chloroprimethyl pentane correct
I knew you could because it was a minor one and the two yeah this employee ID
it's Gustav's what else I don't ever leave your ID in the room nothing much
what if you get caught in let's try somewhere else I know I didn't know
the favorite food let's see if I can break it Jonathan's room Jonathan's
room okay I'm gonna put the mic in my mouth I'd like to get into this
room can you identify what I collect are you ready say your answer into the
mic he said he was collecting something you eat think about it maybe
it was a bit too tough a hint huh food I'm not going to tell you any
more you have to say it more clearly oh I'm sorry first floor the first
run okay run let's go take a look at the clues that are down here besides
candy which it should be candy lockers the lock run okay yes can I just tell
her to run always always run locker on the right leave the room stay okay
stop what stop yeah lockers the lockers okay open open which locker do
you mean open the locker on the left the left locker it's locked now let me
open it passcode they both have like that I don't know what these are leave
storage area the storage area okay run yes head mouth stomach head stomach
mouth head mouth big head stomach head head stomach mouth head please please
nice trip over that guy three enemy three head stomach mouth head head
mouth head stomach head small stomach head mouth free head stomach head
reload stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach
stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach
stomach stomach stomach stomach storage area yeah the storage area okay
vacuum vacuum are you talking about this check vacuum cleaner it's the
hotel's vacuum cleaner it's really useful for cleaning put vacuum cleaner
on face as funny dad joke it's just a vacuum cleaner check box cardboard box
which one do you mean cardboard box three cardboard box which one do you
mean middle cardboard box there are cardboard boxes everywhere can you be a
little more specific lower cardboard box this cardboard box contains hotel
supply that's the one on the right I didn't say that one I guess they're
storing it here temporarily in the staff quarters note on box are you
talking about this check invoice it's an invoice addressed to Jonathan favorite
food he ordered an amazing amount of fruit candies I said it is candy I said
candy but it's fruit candies second floor the second floor okay run yes it
was candy Jonathan's door Jonathan's room Jonathan's room okay I'd like to
get into this room figure it out can you identify what I collect are you
ready say your answer into the mic he said he was collecting how many
recordings did he make of this there's like five variations fruit
candies maybe it was a bit too tough a hint huh food I'm not going to
tell you anymore I don't have the slightest idea maybe there are hints to
be found in this room fruit candy can you identify what I collect are you
ready say your answer into the mic he said he was collecting something you
think about it fruit candy maybe it was a bit too tough leave run leave leave
set the first floor I'm not going to tell you anymore oh my god he has a
jet he's a massive invoice for candy maybe there are hints to be candy all
over the table he has a huge invoice for a ton of candy it's not candy is
this your idea of password security you just leave a bait around all over
the place first floor the first floor okay just say can I said candy the
first time I said candy is it candy is it fruit candy is it fruit candies so
what the hell does this guy have her password if it's not yeah it's a
bunch of red herrings shower room the shower room run okay yes check soap
it's a hotel towel check shower dashboard this is the same as the
showers in the guest rooms it's a bit more stingy with hot water though shower
it's an ordinary house that was it called it's a hotel towel shelf it's an
ordinary shower check shower shelves nothing it's an ordinary shower there's
nothing weird about it pick up medicine there you go saying that sort
of thing again I just changed a while back I'm fine I didn't tell you to
take a shower check conditioner are you talking about this check shampoo this
is the generic hotel shampoo oh but wait a heel cap there's a squeezy heel in
here looks like a payphone call mom leave the room okay galley the galley
run okay yes all right look at all this food check food on the bottom
shelf there are things like ham and doughnuts ham doughnuts the stuff here
is ready to eat items yeah check ham it's ordinary ham check donut it's
covered with jam and chocolate chocolate doughnut this looks fattening
middle shelf the middle shelf has juice coffee beans and so on there's
some kitchen utensils too tissues I don't really like cheese very much
tissue box tissue paper there isn't any here what is that then all the way to
the right in the middle shelf box of tissues they're just juice napkins the
balcony okay stop stop yeah galley the galley okay check napkins on middle
shelf the middle shelf has juice I know what is it middle shelf all the
way to the left the middle shelf has are you talking about this top shelf
the top shelf there appear to be only plates and things like that
how do you not see top shelf med pack the top shelf there appear to be
only plates and things like that top shelf heel the top shelf there appear
to be only plates and things like that top rope are you talking about
behind the bowl top shelf the top shelf there appear to be only plates and
things like that in between the two balls look at top shelf the second
floor okay huh stop stop yes shelf galley the galley okay what is it white
box are you talking about unbelievable if those are napkins whack wax paper
it's just wax paper there's something written in the corner password strafe it
says strafe straight capsule top shelf the top shelf there appear to
be only plates and things like that behind dinner where check behind
dinner where it's dinner where for staff use the plastic kind there's a
heel cap yeah there is a heel capsule bottom shelf on the bottom shelf there
are things like ham the stuff here is ready to eat items bottom shelf
tray second from right on the bottom shelf there are things like ham and
is it sausage sausage check sausage the second floor okay hey hey hey hey the
galley okay yeah pardon galley the galley okay what is that it's not a
doughnut it's not a hit check ham it's ordinary ham check coffee maker this
was in the galley too I guess someone brought it out here what even is that
food check meat rings is this French bread got it it doesn't look very
appetizing okay what am I to eat eat cheese I don't really like cheese very
much eat doughnut no way this is so unhealthy it's calorie content must be
eat bread this looks like really crusty bread it might even chip what am I to
eat ham we don't have the time to be slicing ham drink coffee I'm not
thirsty well then you don't get to eat because you've got plenty of
options doughnuts bread ham cheese coffee leaf huh do what with what
something figured out what this guy has for candy check table the table okay what
is even on the tithes this is a candies check candy they're in different colors
they must be in different flavors too mm-hmm I'm sure they're very
appetizing check middle of table about the only thing eye-catching is
that candy jar check candy jar there are candies in many colors open jar of
candy it's a jar of fruit flavored candy it's a big jar but it's almost
empty already fruit there's some candy spilled on the table fruit candy how is
it not candy doughnuts doughnuts ham I'm gonna try all the other save game
save point the save point okay run yes how can you not like it it's got
this lady's gonna kill you when she finds you check table check table the
table okay read jar of candy but wow is that a big jar that's it candy
flavor there are candies in many colors inspect candy candy is not going to
restore my health I don't need any second floor the second floor okay run
run run yes Jonathan's door Jonathan's room Jonathan's room okay I'd like to
get into this room can you identify what I collect are you ready say your
answer into the mic he said he was collecting something you eat think
fruit candy maybe it was a bit too tough a hint huh food I'm not going to tell
you anymore I don't have the slightest idea flavored candy maybe there are
hints to be found in this room candies red candy strawberry candy junk
food can you identify what I collect the wall are you ready say your answer
into the mic he said he was collecting something you eat think about it
strawberry candy okay welcome to my room where the fuck would you how I
don't get it what awesome I'm amazed that you got that strawberry candy
was there a note it's full of strawberry candy but how would you
even know that someone sure likes these there were no red candies on the
table so who cares does it have to be red candies in a candy jar there was
strawberries on the jar but no red ones off the table yeah but yeah somebody
just said red doesn't need to be struck Rick red could be like cherry
watermelon they could be anything raspberry take okay got his ID check
bottle are you talking about this yeah that's the one look at jar of candy are
we certain these candies and this guy's not just running some weird drug kind
of ring it's an incredible amount of candies that's not really my red
candy that's his front this is like ecstasy or something yeah red candies
right that's what the fucking kids calling it these days don't do
drugs guys it's not worth it check computer check computer it's a
terminal for control staff only the registry's top page is displayed I open
a door hotel regulations waiting room usage restrictions monitor camera
expansion program adds night vision mode to standard monitor cameras this
is it with this you'll get video feed operator all right even from that
warehouse back there okay so now I get night vision mode I need you to
access the system from your end so I'm accessing the computer leave the rest
up to me yep this should work without much fuss I'll download the monitor
camera expansion program access with management system infrared ray
sensitivity upgrade install the latest generation of infrared monitor systems
to see clearly under zero light conditions download successful this
should get video feed to you even where it's dark warehouse and we fight the
last boss leave leave the room okay first floor the first floor okay save
game warehouse bingo we're probably gonna beat this game save point the
same point yes just like the Simpsons hit and run I can't imagine this
much well we got a costume change that means we're at the end of the
arc here when you get the cool costume change you're at the third act hallway
leave the room run okay yes where should I go warehouse warehouse the
warehouse okay run yes you get a costume change every act and there are
ten acts did you think this is a fucking game night vision mode
activated we'll see how this is not even a filter I can't see you that's a
little too scary I'm stopping no no I was kidding it was a joke oh my goodness
it was a joke now I'm stuck without your support I don't have the
confidence to go through maybe we need to find an alternate route where should I
go warehouse understood I'll go back can you see me yep loud and clear
whoa pitch black what about you can you see me yes can you really see me
yeah don't turn I can see you can you tell me which hand I'm raising
here goes go right yep ready go I prove that I can see you not lifting up
anything you're not lifting up any hands yep yep ready go none okay I guess you
can see me clearly my eyes are getting accustomed to the darkness too
I guess we can move on let's go front-limb front-limb front-limb bodies
front-limb front-limb bodies body body tongue mouth mouth mouth dodge
left mouth mouth mouth mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner
mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth gonna turn around what the fuck inner mouth
no two turn around me too body body body front-limb front-limb front-limb
inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth yeah how did
your aim better in the dark I have no idea recover yes area a to area 8
How do you know what that even is? Run. Head, stomach, mouth. Mouth, mouth, head. Stomach,
stomach, head. Stomach, stomach, stomach. Head, stomach, head. Head, head, head. Head,
head, head. Head, head, head. Back. Back. Back. Enemy 2. Head, stomach, stomach. Stomach,
stomach, head. Back. Dodge right. Enemy 1. Head, stomach, stomach. Head, head, head. Head.
Area A2. Run. Turn around. No, flee. Flee. Flee. Dodge left. Dodge. Turn. Left.
Enemy 1. Back. Back. Front limb, front limb, front limb. Mouth, mouth, mouth. Reload. Inner
mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth. Inner mouth, inner mouth, inner mouth. Inner mouth, inner
mouth, inner mouth. Full health heal. Enemy 1. Front limb, front limb. Reload. Mouth,
mouth, body. Body, inner mouth, inner mouth. Tongue, tongue, eye. Left. 1, 2. Head. Dodge
left. Dodge left. Dodge left. Head, head, head. Mouth. Head, head, head. Mouth, stomach,
stomach. Stomach, stomach, stomach. Stomach, stomach, stomach. Reload. Mouth, stomach,
stomach. Stomach, mouth, stomach. Stomach, stomach, stomach. Stomach, stomach, stomach.
Reload. Stomach, stomach, stomach. Shake. Shake. Mouth.
Mouth, mouth, mouth. Mouth, mouth. That's it, now we can move on. Area A2. Area A2,
okay. It doesn't appear as if there's anything special. What do you mean,
nothing special? Let's check somewhere else. I need a save point so bad. Area B1. Area B1.
run yes this is bad head head head stomach enemy two run enemy three back
back head stomach stomach enemy one stomach stomach head stomach enemy one stomach mouth mouth
mouth mouth mouth head head stomach stomach head back back back enemy two enemy two head
enemy one stomach stomach enemy three mouth mouth mouth enemy two mouth enemy three stomach
stomach enemy three head head head wish I could level up in the skin I'm gonna go
all the way to be one it's not anything there area be one area be one run okay
yes there doesn't appear to be anything really nothing over here come on let's
check somewhere else come on I gotta walk all the way around area be two
area be two head enemy one enemy three head head stomach stomach stomach stomach
dodge left dodge left dodge left enemy three stomach stomach stomach stomach
stomach mouth mouth stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach mouth
mouth enemy one front limb dodge right front limb front limb front limb body
mouth mouth three look body mouth mouth mouth mouth tongue tongue inner mouth
tongue inner mouth tongue eye tongue inner mouth tongue inner mouth tongue inner
mouth dodge right dodge right enemy two dodge right enemy two head stomach shoot
shoot stomach shoot mouth mouth area be two thank god you can climb how do I
have any more heals left I think I only have one I wasted that one but no
reason it's gonna be C ones the correct area to go it comes to a dead
end here huh it's a small chip lucky me that's the reason why I came all the
way over here okay I'll go back no area that's such a waste of time so
you need to go to area C1 and C2 area C2 area area front limb front limb
front limb front dodge left front limb front limb front limb off off off
recover recover dodge left dodge left dodge left mouth mouth run run front
anyone dodge holy fuck how am I supposed to do that but it wastes the
heal for no reason like literally stomach stomach stomach dodge left
dodge right heal at full health I gotta even say that where the hell
I went all the way around for a computer chip just I walked around the entire
area get up okay I got it already leave the room run yes so I'm just gonna go
see one and see two where should I go warehouse the warehouse run okay run
run run yes can you see me maybe I should do some hand raisings and then
never talk about the darkness ever again hopefully I can get to see one
from here I wonder if there's a runaway option it's probably not pitch black
what about you can you see me yes can you really see me try straight okay
then can you tell me which hand I'm raising here goes go left hand left
yep ready go left hand left left left what you liar now I'm stuck without
your support I don't have the confidence to go through maybe we need
to find an alternate route where should I go where else understood I'll
go back I said it too fast didn't she see me install the module why would
I live right now I just download the night vision and I'm just pretending like
I can see her pitch black trying to get her killed or something you can you
see me yes can you really see me this is better than the abyss watchers okay
then can you tell me which hand I'm raising here goes go right yep ready
go both hands yep yep ready both hands okay I guess you can see me clearly my
eyes are getting accustomed to the darkness too I guess we can move on
let's go front limb mouth mouth mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth turn around turn around any two front limb mouth mouth
mouth inner mouth reload inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth tongue
inner mouth inner mouth turn around turn around turn around
enemy front limb mouth tongue mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth
reload aye aye aye let's go see one area see one okay you have to go
around the whole thing this is a disaster run really bad
auto-fire head stomach head mouth stomach head mouth dodge left enemy to
stomach head head back dodge left back back and be free head head head
enemy one auto-fire reload auto-fire auto-fire that's not a good enemy to
enemy to head head head it's just auto-fire no good reload let's go see
one area see one yes
turn turn around front my mouth body body inner mouth inner mouth I I I I
inner mouth back up back dodge left dodge left back back reloads dodge
right turn right enemy to head stomach stomach
mouth mouth stomach stomach stomach mouth mouth mouth
reload stomach stomach stomach mouth reload enemy to front limb mouth body
body mouth mouth tongue mouth mouth reload inner mouth body I body dodge
left inner mouth dodge right reload inner mouth body tongue I body
inner mouth inner mouth tongue body body body body body body body body
dodge left dodge left dodge right dodge right inner mouth yeah two
recoveries I'm tired recovery yes see one area see one okay yes we got
like two or three more ring this if I don't do it this time it might be the
end head head head stomach bump dodge right dodge right stomach stomach
stomach head turn around turn around back back enemy one head stomach mouth
mouth and stomach stomach mouth then auto fire auto fire don't ever again
enemy to stomach stomachs head back back enemy to head stomach stomach
stomach head head head reload stomach head any one stomach and the heads
dead funny why any three stomach mouth head area c1 area c1 run okay yes why
did I think this is the last game I ever played it's not gonna happen you're
just fine enemy one dodge left dodge left back enemy three enemy three turn
ah to shoot take enemy to head stomach head mouth mouth take mouth mouth mouth
stomach stomach dodge back back back enemy three head head head stomach stomach
auto-fire kick kick mouth stomach stomach head mouth missed it every
single fucking shot stomach head mouth dodge left mouth mouth mouth mouth
stomach stomach stomach mouth stomach mouth stomach mouth mouth head
stomach mouth kick stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach nobody could be
that bad I don't it's impossible to stomach back back enemy two stomach
stop turn back back back dodge left dodge left holy shit that was as clear
as I could have ever said it dodge left ah run flee flee reload auto-fire
stomach stomach stomach head mouth back back why is this why stop no shake I'm
done game sucks see you later no way not finishing this game I fought a
hundred slugs in this whole game and like at some point when when there's
like some weird issue where the motherfucker you miss like seven
hundred times shoot the stomach shoot the head shoot the stomach autofire you
just miss everything it's close far away don't matter imagine if you gave
up all the Simpsons hit and run why it was just a slug it was just a
it's so easy to die but I don't get it what happened why did that happen it's
just like throw it was it is it really just throwing dice up in the air or
something warehouse yes you know like what when they put their heads up you
shoot but there's been at least a handful of scenarios where the little
slug will come up and you'll shoot it and you choose misses every
every shot every single one leave leave yes leave oh my god hallway and this is
my problem apparently hallway leave the room okay where should I go go to
hell understood no no don't go back don't I'm not unlocking the door go
to the warehouse the warehouse okay run yes no don't stop stop area a area a run
okay yes get that kick that up get that thing pick it up right now back
it's a heel capsule warehouse the warehouse okay this area right here is
so long I wonder what happened what would happen if look I'm gonna be real
with you here out of the whole game we've been playing this game for seven
hours the entire video game this is the first time that they've strung together
like seven fights in a row where was this for the there was you you fight
against like two monsters in every like 12 rooms what the hell is this
room it's like it took you seven hours to put like more than three or
four encounters in a row can you see me heck yes I can see you can you
really see me okay then can you tell me which hand I'm raising I can try here
goes go left yep ready none
yep I hate this I hate this there's two hands what I said to know I don't
have the confidence to go through both not two hands both hands where should I
go warehouse understood I'll go back I gave the lie awakes I'm laughing
stomach head stomach balls auto-fire you liar tell me what you can actually
see me whoa pitch black what about you can you see me yes can you really
see me okay then can you tell me which hand I'm raising here goes go right
yep ready right yep yep ready go none okay I guess you can see me clearly my
eyes are getting accustomed to the darkness too I guess we can move on
let's go front-limb mouth body mouse body
dodge body in her mouth in her mouth body I in her mouth in her mouth walk
forward reload dodge right dodge right enemy two enemy two front-limb body
body body inner mouth mouth mouth dodge left dodge right dodge left reload
inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth body mouth front-limc
front-limb front-limb up
that was pretty tough let's go just dodge the direction you want to go and
scoot to their ignore combat area C1 area C1 okay how fast is my throat
getting dry yeah this is that exactly yeah all right
dodge left back head enemy to enemy to head Jake head stomach stomach turn
around dodge right back stomach mouth mouth stomach stomach stomach stomach
stomach stomach you should study you hit it like you are you it went right into
its body it's stomach head back back stomach stomach head stomach recover yes
C1 area C1 run okay yes turn around dodge left dodge left enemy to stomach
stomach stomach what the fuck dodge left why why did you run at him I said dodge
left and you sprinted at him and then shot the gun enemy one turn around
enemy one back back frontman mouth mouth body tongue inner mouth inner mouth
reload back back dodge left back dodge left enemy to head stomach
mouth stomach stomach mouth stomach mouth mouth stomach stomach stomach
stomach by the time all right by the time it does the animation and you say
do it it's like the animations over stomach stomach stomach body inner mouth
inner mouth body body inner mouth back back back body inner mouth inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth too far away I body body inner mouth what is
this camera reload inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth body body body back
can I please get a better camera angle I'm supposed to be in control of that
back front limb mouth mouth body inner mouth inner mouth body body body inner
mouth tongue body body body body body body body body body body inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth this is where I got destroyed last time see one area see
run head dodge left dodge left dodge left no dodge dodge left please enemy
free stomach back back back back back enemy one stomach head stomach reload
back back back back took you four times back please please please back shake
enemy to auto fire auto fire just fire the goddamn gun fire back dodge left
auto fire dodge right back dodge right back back back back back enemy one head
head head head head finally move on I'm gonna be close I still have to how
many heels do I have I have no heels if he actually watching me heels see
one area stop yes if I leave will that will this work leave I am stopped
hallway leave area I am stopped area a one area a one okay yes is it gonna
reset every enemy in here if I leave we're just retracing our steps let's go
back to the warehouse too no stuck here see one area see one
right okay yes auto fire auto fire dodge left back dodge left
back and be free what command is this by the way what command is she doing
right now back dodge left dodge left back enemy three auto fire reload enemy
two head head stomach right turn right I gotta hold on dodge left sleep enemy
one back back back front limb mouth mouth body body inner mouth reload
body body inner mouth inner mouth I tongue inner mouth inner mouth any free
head enemy one inner mouth body body body back back dodge left dodge left
dodge right dodge right enemy free mouth mouth mouth stomach mouth stomach
dodge right back reload stomach stomach mouth stomach mouth mouth mouth right
reload dodge left dodge left watch dodge left dodge dodge left reload dodge
left dodge left inner mouth dodge left inner mouth inner mouth enemy two attack
in auto fire stomach forward mouth mouth mouth mouth stomach stomach back
stomach stomach
recover yes we're not even close guys don't don't look don't give me those
pogchamps yet see one area see one okay we got a hell encounter here it's
two of the weird hand puppet things and then a slug right in the middle on
either side front limb mouth mouth dodge left dodge left front limb mouth
front mouth body body front take front enemy free front limb front limb front
back mouth so when I say front she's supposed to walk take reload dodge
left reload reload back back back back enemy
one body body body dodge left dodge left dodge right dodge left inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth dodge left dodge left enemy two stomach stomach
dodge back dodge left dodge left walk forward three I didn't even say auto
fire recover back back back back enemy three body body body inner mouth enemy
two head stomach stomach head mouth mouth mouth mouth dodge right dodge right
dodge oh my god what am I doing I'm trying to time it like everyone was
screaming at me for to wait till he lifts his body up and you're doing less
damage overall flee enemy three body body mouth enemy two stomach stomach
mouth mouth mouth body inner mouth reload body body inner mouth inner mouth
inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth inner mouth eye show me your eye again
just shoot the fucking body shoot the body body ha body back back back reload
inner mouth just reload the fucking gun lady body what are you doing I don't
have any heels area C1 area C1 run yes break time it's a dead end somebody's
sitting on the can I see something glowing is this graffiti it's written
yeah one guy break time yes I'm gonna get so fucked here we're gonna go to
area C2 and we'll be right in front of the door and I'm gonna have to
fight like three hands and I'm gonna get destroyed and I'm gonna turn the
screen off C2
properly though turn it on oh my god these all stand up I'm turning the
stream off
the rescue team it's a horrible
can't believe something like that exists it never touched us we're all
twisted one by one please give me a safe point after this please pretty
please
look at this mess it's gonna cost a fortune to fix all this just keeps
getting worse hey I'm thinking once we reopen the hotel we can advertise it
as the first place humans fought off an alien invasion reopen are you sure
about that oh yeah I am and why don't you guys
cool it with the heavy artillery from now on talk to the squad leader all the
freaking squad leader squad leader is on his way hey you aren't you a waitress
crazy bimbo what the hell are you doing in that get up it's still on
this one leader no don't give this to me right now I don't want to fight
the super mutant thing I know how you feel man yeah sorry you didn't say
mouth-mouth body in her mouth
every it's everybody's problem not just mine run yeah fuck that guy I need a
safe point I don't care I need to get a safe point I ain't not gonna screw
around right now I guess it's not chasing me thank God hey I need you
to pay attention I can't beat that monster if I were to run into it again
I have to run from it don't forget that no save point the save point okay
yes grab that heel to game sucks no doubt no I'm fine I made it you know
okay I got it already grab heel yes stop turn around turn around turn
around hello did you say something turn around turn around why are you not
listening to me area a area a okay stop yes examine wreckage examine rubble I
am standing grab capsule yes stop yes turn around check wreckage check
rubble check explosion check area I am standing turn around turn around check
check what am I even supposed to call that check dead end check under check
under steel I am standing area a area a okay check under it's a dead end
and that's I just had to listen to yeah I didn't even need to say anything I
just had to walk over here yeah I have to use it to unfortunately recovery yes
I have to use it safe the save point okay I wonder what happens next I'm
gonna say area C area C area C run okay yes so what we got seven and a
half hours here seven and a half hours we got how much more is left right
stomach mouth body front legs hind legs body right stomach left stomach left
stomach mouth red stomach red stomach red stomach red stomach any two stomach
mouth mouth back back mouth stomach stomach mouth stomach dodge left dodge
left back back back stomach stomach stomach back back mouth back back
reload mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth give me back my fucking green mario turn the world
metal block thing i got i can't i got no jokes for you it's a launcher shelf i'll take that
thank you very much so area c area c run okay yes did we figure out how much longer was in the
game anybody have any idea it's a dead end i have to go back area b area b okay the game can last as
long as 13 hours we've reached a god wait a second um if this wall weren't here i could
keep going through the ducts i wonder if the launcher will wreck it i'll try i'm gonna shoot
launcher let's do it so do it launchers awesome okay let's go if you can beat hit and run then
you can beat this yeah but hit and run i didn't have to i guess i'm going to have to be
constantly going like speaking constantly talking constantly giving commands pretty high up if you
stop if you can't play this game again
close there's spots where the ducts are wobbling this is going to be hell looking closely i see
that there are broken sections here and there green red blue can you guide me safely across
by checking on your monitor okay red blue yes i know what colors are you don't have to explain
to me what the colors look like is that all right yes red walk walk walk fine i'll explain
once more what okay i want you to tell me which of these three ducts i should be taking
how to instruct me red that's what i just did blue green is that all right yes okay
i have total faith in your ability to lead me across those ducts i'm ready to go
did you tell me that you just you need someone to tell you not to walk off the cliff
i didn't even need to tell you anything how did you do that on your own
that was scripted right area b area b okay yes it's a dead end it doesn't look like i can
go on through the lower way oh i get back up there let's find a way of getting up to the ducts
area a area a okay well i got a heel out of it that's a good thing i think i can get up from
here that's a pretty nice build joke okay let's try it again guide me properly this time please
i'm gonna do my absolute best blue red yes blue green blue red
what the hell you just didn't make it area a area a okay run yes it didn't it it looked like they
were all rented a track not just the green and the blue oh blue red red yes go so what go
walk forward red yes go red yes walk yep
blue green blue how are you supposed to go from red how are you going to jump from green to red
isn't the whole point that area a area a isn't the entire point that you have to be within
within one of each other you can jump over two apparently i thought the whole idea was you
couldn't cross two at the same time guide me properly this time please if that's the case then
blue red i can't go forward from red yes walk yep blue green blue yep green red you gotta be
kidding me she couldn't go from blue to we managed to finally make it here i'll be taking
even bigger risks from here on out that stinks you know i'm counting on you operator look at
this american gladiator bullshit coming up here and i have to do the whole thing again don't i if i
fall green blue yep green blue yep red yes blue red yes green i can't i just had a panic attack in
mid area c area c okay that just like hurt my head thank god it's a checkpoint
green bark bark like a dog huh red no no no no no one guy said to say bark like a fucking dog
yes area c i am walking area c area c okay run yes guide me properly it's not gonna work
it works bark like a dog i can't go anymore to the right no guys i'm sorry it's not gonna happen
green blue yep stop yep walk yep red yes stop yep blue walk yep green stop yep walk yep blue
yep stop yep green walk yep stop what walk blue what why did it area c area c okay she that she's
she started wobbling much quicker than before of course she starts right in the middle where
there's nowhere to jump guide me properly i didn't forget to jump across it just looked
like it was empty looked like i couldn't go anywhere blue green walk yes
blue yep stop yep walk yep red yes stop yep blue walk yep green stop yep walk yep blue yep stop
i can't go forward from here green walk yep red red stop stop yep blue walk yep stop green green blue
yep green walk yep red blue walk yes stop yep green walk walk yep red i can't go
red walk walk yep blue walk your instructions are lousy shut up shut up unbelievable i'll take
that your instructions are lousy you should be able to walk forward but you just have to walk
i have to tell you when there's like an obstacle in the way you have eyes just look
it's pretty high up i have no choice but to jump down now you're upset when you have to jump it's
the same height i can't go back just look let's move on waiting room waiting room the waiting
room okay there's no save point hopefully there's one on the road in the waiting room
run yes no enemies just a save point and some snacks or something oh no if only this
reporter were alive i could ask her can you wait a sec there's something i'm trying to find
voice activated password maybe i'm looking for a disc dated august 8th can you help me look for
it i guess i gotta help you organize your shitty cd collection now okay um video foot what i mean
what was the date that she even said what was the date what was the date come on help me look
please what was the date okay the blue disc but there are a lot which one uh the blue star blue
star pattern here the date is wrong red background blue star red and blue stars
yes 2029 august 8th so aren't you curious to know why a waitress would be fighting alien
monsters alone on a space station we vote to find out in the special features of the dvd
well what i'm looking for is what compels me to fight it's it's right here watch
that's the playstation well now we know exactly how much of the world's attention
is focused on the station hotel here comes the hotel manager let's get is this supposed to
be a big reveal we're gonna get a twist here mr tanaka when is the hotel grand opening
well we're in this coming christmasy i was half watching this news report in my apartment
is this a record player it's a record glass case in the corner of the screen
can you see something like a ball in it no it's something that can't be there it's a dinner
plate something that shouldn't be there dvd dinner plate i took the waitress job here to
find out more about that round stone microwave safe where it's at i thought i left out when
the same reporter came aboard to cover the opening ceremony yeah pretty sick actually
i figured i could ask her portable dvd player that you can just put a bunch of food on and
put it in the microwave just eat it while you're watching tv since a reporter can't help us
we'll have to show this footage to others and ask them who do you think we should ask
the president i don't have any friends oh not what i said my friends i don't have any friends
my friends say it again who say it again who say it again who she's really prodding here
the reporter uh well who do you think i should show this footage too
me like asking you is gonna help yes yes it is someone no the guest won't know what i'm
talking about the fbi dad what are you talking about dad works for the fbi dad dad
the cia like asking you is gonna help cia i wouldn't know anyone like that k gb say it again who
uh the aliens it's not somewhere waitress would find it say it again who the police
say it again who the police it's not somewhere waitress would find it the hotel manager you're
not serious i can't ask manager tanaka the reporter i don't have any friends say it again
the doctor i doubt the pm's bodyguard would know anything about the hotel
doctor powers joe powers i think he's too dangerous what are the characters are even in the game
who's left in the game um gino got it gino good idea a security guard would know i doubt he's
sitting around waiting at the receiver port let's find him oh by the way would you like
to know more about the stone no that stone we saw earlier would you like to know what it is
no not at all that stone we saw earlier would you like to know what it is no no reply huh
i understand it has nothing to do with you it's not even listening to the monitor room
you're in there's a small escape shuttle i'll find the stone your girlfriend and make my
way to the shuttle it can carry three people please help me until then we have to sacrifice
somebody safe point the safe point okay yes um yeah i mean she's getting sacrificed the first
chance i get there's an opportunity to like do a final like kick her out the escape pod
that's gonna happen get my girlfriend in get enough room for some snacks and food now i'm
sorry rio this we need to bring like food and snacks and stuff you can't come
you're gonna get like palpatine check window the window okay earth is so far away
i don't think we need to check this place check table the table okay i don't think a dvd
player is necessary it doesn't appear as if there's anything we need why don't you check
somewhere else why don't you check the dvd no response vacuum yes eat vacuum yes eat the
vacuum yep business center the business center okay scan copy of ass which copier do you mean
front copier scan ass this copier appears to be broken sit on copier and fan in whole office
this copier appears to be broken what's on here lift copier it's an ordinary copier
oh look there's a document in it get document yep it's just ordinary everyday copier paper
shoot window and suck us all out get document from copier huh what a strange command
i don't get it grab document from copier yep it's just ordinary everyday copier paper
lift car i'm listening check copier which copier do you mean check front copier it's
a typical copier open copier which copier do you mean open front copier open this copier
uses an internal feeder for scanning you can't open it turn on front copier it's a typical copier
take paper take paper from front copier huh she's the one that told me it was in there
i don't get it check tray of copier it's a typical copier press button i'll walk
i'm gonna get a walk is he actually watching me aren't there any instructions
i want you to give me instructions i want you to give me instructions
operator are you busy with something else chat plays lifeline what do you mean
when i when i walked away i tangled myself up so badly somehow how does that always happen
somehow i mean you don't even mean to your cables just become so tangled
that it's like you intentionally did it to fuck with yourself 10 minutes from now get up okay
i got it already vending machine the vending machine okay she's got a free will now
video camera it's a tv camera like for live interviews huh what's this
oh chip got check under bench under the bench it's a heel capsule i don't think i would drink
something that was on the ground okay if you guys were at like the bus station
and there was a coca cola underneath the bench of the bus station are you gonna be like oh
nice a coca cola and take it and drink it no one does that why would you do that i don't
care if it's sealed something weird happened there check vending machine it's the same as the one in
the security room was it even it was sealed sealed and ice cold nope check dispenser
which dispenser do you mean check left dispenser if there is something it would be good
nope too bad it's empty check right dispenser inside it's empty well i tried
can't say you didn't try don't give myself rings check plant it's an ordinary leafy house plant
newspaper clippings on ground cds do you mean that no dvds it's just news footage
we won't be needing this disc check table the table okay anything else on the table it doesn't
appear as if there's anything we need let's check somewhere else copy machine business center the
business center okay run yes all right let's try this again search copier how am i supposed
to understand that check copy machine do you mean this open the front copier open this copier
uses an internal feeder for scanning you can't open it turn on front copier it's not worth
breaking check scanner how am i supposed to understand that use front copier make a copy
okay i'll press the button hey something came out that's not even real it's fake
jump jump what should i check jump on copier it's an ordinary copier you know with fax
printer radio and tv functions all right save point the save point stop stop stop stop yes
yes check panel turn around huh check panel on wall check panel on wall the table okay stop
yes fax no you guys have been on that for almost seven and a half hours save point
the save point okay fax armpits how would you reliably get a photo of your armpits
you're gonna lift it up squish them down there and scan you know how disgusting that's gonna be
you don't want that from my armpit it's gonna be just a bunch of like matted up hair squished
into the copier and some skin pushing out why would you want to see that
holy shit get up okay i got it already uh business center the business center
run yes stop turn right yes what what do you call that thing on the right open panel the table
okay ah it doesn't appear as if there's anything we need let's check somewhere else
business center the business center okay wall box i'll go out into the hallway stop
stop stop stop yes business center the business center okay check wall yep it's just ordinary
everyday copier paper fuse box do you mean that that is what i mean key box the observatory
restaurant's key is in here but this is locked the walmart business center
access authentication in progress please state your name rio honeheim manager's name
not recognized access denied huh you have to say the control staff manager's name for this to
open jonathan i have no idea who the control staff manager is i'll entrust you with that
can you open it operator sure i got this don't worry abe lincoln
who's that well anyway it appears to be abe lincoln who's abe lincoln in progress
please state your name okay this time we'll get it right
uh jonah barry homin stone name identified as guest access denied the person's in charge
of the key box ensures heck is not one of the guests just trying to say a bunch of random
let's try this one more time access authentication in progress please state your name okay this
time we'll get it right
that's not it who could the person be in charge i don't know hallway i'll go out into the hallway
run it's gotta be it where should i go elevator hall understood i'll go back why did that have
play a game let's play word jumble i'll play word jumble let's play word jumble the window
okay stop yes let's play a game the table stop yes let's play a game consultation okay
consultation it is okay what would you like to know about let's play a game okay that's it for
consultation why does this thing does this do fucking anything does consultation do anything
consultation okay consultation it is okay what would you like to know about
what can we do we have to find gino quickly and ask him where this place is on the dvd
i hope that he's still alive where's the keywords you've got great reflexes i'm proud of my
athleticism but my decision making sense is weak i'm kind of like a cat that way microphone
check microphone check how are things on earth i wonder if earth is under alien invasion too
but somehow i think that most people are happily enjoying their christmas dinner
free of aliens strafe launcher okay that's it for consultation what's the launcher launcher
okay i got it already it doesn't appear as if there's anything we need
let's check somewhere else use launcher use launcher don't give me that attitude
you haven't even seen an attitude yet suicide don't be stupid there are people who are
counting on us save point the save point okay yes punch yourself in face get up okay i got
it already punch yourself in the face what is it punch yourself in the face
not even listening punch yourself in the face the business center stop okay yes slap yourself
like entertainer online comedian germa 985 i'll wait leave the room okay where should i go
elevator hall the elevator hall okay run yes online comedian he's a comedian okay
observatory restaurant the observatory restaurant okay let's play tongue twister yes
let's play tongue twister huh how do you play these games you guys talk about all these
games you can play these things you can do where how do you do them you need the keyword
before it'll happen aren't there any instructions take a break let's take a break jonathan turner
observatory restaurant the observatory restaurant okay you need chips you need
the right key to get into the observatory restaurant let's go look for the key it's
in the key box god damn it hallway the hallway run okay yes john what was jonathan's name
waiting room the waiting room run okay yes key box the table stop okay yes key box
huh key panel let's figure a way out of here first casanova i don't what would did you think i was
saying key box the table stop okay yes business center the business center okay
okay key box we have to get this open somehow if we're going to keep going
access authentication in progress what was it jonathan turner okay this time we'll get it
right jonathan turner manager's name confirmed that was what jonathan's name
did it operator the key box opened thank you thank you it would have been great if the
observatory elevators code key were also here okay we can get into the observatory restaurant
now let's go let's go i am walking yes hallway leave the room yes okay okay leave the room
yes consultation never mind where should i go elevator hall the elevator hall okay
okay fast yes eight and a half hours yeah damn where should i go still enjoying it though
observatory restaurant the observatory restaurant we only get one chance
to do this this is not something i would ever go back and stream again it just isn't so if
we're if we are this close but like not very much longer then i'm just gonna finish it
enjoying in quotes yeah i know that's fine though what a disaster area listen
do you remember this place no when things have changed this much it's understandable
in the place where they held the first party in space you were first space party ever
toasts with naomi when the monsters appeared almost everybody aboard the station was here
i don't think there's anyone here tell me an ending for the story i need to check this area
thoroughly uh she is a double agent she needs she's trying to steal an orb and she's pretending
to be a waitress while she cases the whole place and you can find out at the end that
you were just helping her case this whole place and actually help her steal this orb
and you were just compliant the whole time we didn't even know the hallway to guest section
two is blocked by debris oh right when i was in guest section one there was that huge tremor
there was an announcement that the corridor was sealed and there's gonna be a final showdown
where i'm gonna be able to make a bunch of noise i'm gonna be able to say there she is
and she's gonna be looking at me like don't we become such good friends and i give the
choice to actually let the fbi apprehend her by saying there she is or not saying anything
and she runs away hello is anyone there if it weren't for this panel i could reach the chandelier
it doesn't appear unbreakable blow it up what should i do blow it up use launcher use launcher
on panel okay leave it up to me don't stand that close though i can't get through there
yet you're kidding me did i just waste that aren't there any instructions i mean there
would be chandelier the chandelier okay i can't get any closer than this
what should i do come on vi use launcher on panel okay leave it up to me you can do it again
i can't believe it there's more that was the launcher's last show we'll have to get some
that's great vip seat one vip seat one okay yes
that's ridiculous look around nerd farther if this thing is here but i don't have any launcher
ammo let's check somewhere i may have fucked myself for the rest of this playthrough because
i don't think i was supposed to use them on the chandelier
save point the save point i'm doing a different save point because i you need to blow up that
one you need to blow up the other ones where can i get some shells it's gonna use save down
here just in case someone's saying it's fine it's probably fine you're right
soft locked i don't think so vip seat three vip seat three i can't go any farther if this
thing is here but i don't have any launcher ammo let's check somewhere else section four
okay section four run yes have you tried swearing at her i don't think so i think maybe once
the floor is caved in it looks like a big cavern in the back there's something there
there's frog enemies and a slug it is always a slug they didn't get rid of the dumb
stupid slug enemy body body front leg hind leg right stomach left stomach red stomach
stomach mouth red stomach red stomach red stomach two back back head head
dodge left back take stomach
my mouth
mouth mouth stomach stomach mouth stomach mouth reload
focus on the head doesn't the x mean that it's already been destroyed shake head head stomach
stomach aim aim at stomach stop get off stomach i think those things just suck i'm tired
just say auto shoot um i'm not sure if you were here probably 30 times i've done auto
shoot she misses almost every single shot every time almost every time it's a launcher shell
that monster must have items packed away in its belly just say and they enable hacks
yes chandelier chandelier okay i can't get any closer than this i don't know why
use launcher on panel okay leave it up to me this had better be gone did you hear my voice
my voice is starting to give out now thank goodness we push forward looks like that
was the last one he was in the middle how did he not get hurt it's okay shooting grenades
at the middle and he was in the middle are you with the rescue team are you alone no
there were several dozen staff here even a little while ago but they were eaten i knelt
and prayed to my family back on earth i'd given up all hope another npc but while i was doing so
the monsters went away you're lucky but it's not safe here head for the receiving port
the rescue team has barricaded it thank you oh this may help you elevator elevator
thank you i hope you'll be with your family soon will i see them again yes i'm sure you will
and uh just to determine that that was a lie yeah this will let us operate the observatory
elevator okay let's return to the elevator hall i'm gonna have to do something here
hold on a second where is it on here there is voice memos
run where am i going where should i go why did i leave what did she walk out here on her own
consultation okay consultation it is okay what would you like to know about what do we do
where do we go what do we do it doesn't appear as if anyone else is here in this section
where should we go uh okay so where elevator let's play a game okay that's it for consultation
go to the elevator the elevator okay fuck what oh fuck okay hold on get in the elevator right
recover dodge right dodge right back back dodge right shoot head
back dodge right finn horn shoot horn horn dodge left dodge left all right enemy
auto fire reload dodge left dodge left right claw left claw left dodge left dodge left
this is fucking hell dodge left head eye eye eye shoot eye shoot mouth dog shoot eye
dodge left back dodge left dodge left eye there's no fucking bullets in this gun
eye dodge right dodge left dodge left dodge left shoot eye shoot like she just
stops targeting target the enemy back shoot mouth recover dodge right shoot mouth eye
it's the eye dodge right dodge right eye you see what i'm talking about like this is living hell
this is living hell enemy one dodge left dodge left enemy one turn around turn around
back and it's disappeared dodge right dodge turn left shoot mouth mouth back mouth dodge left
dog mouth reload that jump flee you don't have time to shoot it flee go back jump eye eye
recover nothing eye eye eye eye reload eye eye eye eye eye reload eye eye mouth mouth mouth
mouth back jump jump eye i hate this game observatory restaurant the observatory
restaurant okay save point the save point okay that's not ever going to work is it
i don't have any heels now it will uh stand up please okay i got it already try to be nice that
time oh we need to go to line exit one exit one stop yes section one section one there needs
to be a hill here oh my god it's not gonna happen hey a heel capsule i have to use it
there doesn't seem to be anything else let's check somewhere else recover yes
vip seat one vip seat one okay i can't go any farther if this thing is here
what should i do use launcher on panel okay leave it up to me let's go
it's the day it's it is 1201 pacific it's 1202 that's correct that's right
we're getting close vip seat one vip seat one okay it doesn't appear as if there's anything
special let's check somewhere else vip seat two vip seat two okay give me a heel up here not
just a chip it's a chip there doesn't seem to be anything else come on give me a heel on
vip seat three vip seat three vip seat three okay run yes check in lamp um this is already
broken some minute look in the top of floor lamp that's broken reach into floor lamp
chip in floor lamp inspect lamp shade the table what are you saying look in floor lamp
that's broken grab are you talking about this break floor lamp that's broken search
floor lamp that's broken search lamp that's broken i don't even want it whatever it is
look at the menu it's the restaurant's menu then again it's so dirty i can't really be sure
floor lamp that's broken check top of floor lamp that's broken check floor lamp that's broken
look in look in lamp that's broken run as fast as you can from other side of room
and try to break through fucking glass exit one okay she's going for it she turns around
and just like go go go go go go go where should i go elevator the elevator okay listen the
elevator should work if you enter the number code we got earlier i'm really resorting to
daffy duck stuff at this point no i'm not you yeah yeah uh what what was the code
oh four two three huh code is oh four two three huh just get out of the fucking way lady
i'll handle it that's kind of creepy why would an elevator have a device that wraps around
your neck passing through the central core of the station this is a zero gravity elevator
for your safety please do not worry i think we're almost done we're getting
at the top of the mountain here there's section three which was sealed during the tremor
it wouldn't be anyone like a game with her before i'll try to figure it out for
optimum visibility of the external environment please enjoy the cosmic this up sightseeing in
space do i say that people finally began viewing themselves objectively after they started
seeing earth from space perhaps also maybe they fell to separation with reality as well
but what about you are you really alive that is the absolute stupidest question i have ever
heard anyone ask and i i hate you for asking it huh i couldn't hear you very well you're
still alive right what were the first words your mother taught you as a child eat your
vegetables didn't you hear me please tell me what were the first words your mother taught you
as a baby run you must have been a cute baby we seem to have reached the junction
it's german for we oh you and i
oh that's great and then at me please tell me more taught me that word i love the word
we it makes it seem as if i'm not all alone is that thing too tight around your neck
or are you all right you lose an oxygen hey what's your favorite word or saying
if you're good at something never do it for free
and that's meaningful to you you're probably thinking why is she asking me this all of a
sudden well i just wanted to get to know you better after all we don't know anything about
each other despite the fact that we're partners right would you like to know more about me
no don't be that way please listen she's been talking about how we're partners we're such good
friends and i have denied every single bonding experiment here you want me to tell you this
no please don't i want to steal that orb you want to know why no i don't want to know more about me
i don't want to know a damn thing about you but i'm beginning to understand it's better for
people to be with someone rather than being alone when we get back to earth maybe i'll get
you to introduce me to someone please remain seated until the safety bar has been lifted
and then they'll let you go to like what about you
maybe we'll get you some fucking firearms training but i suppose there's no chance of that huh
now get her some glasses when you get your prescription
a severe wobble was detected in the space station's rotation
the station was placed on emergency status although the wobble will not interfere with the
context of the video game elevator use is prohibited i guess that means there's no turning back
no turning back starting to collapse we're at the apex of the game this is
you know as soon as we can and ask him where the stone is
boomer streamer probably calls pizza places to order you've never you don't order pizza
from a pizza place exit one exit one okay run yes can't order pizza from amazon
did i miss a this is horribly wrecked ahead of here is the senior staff section
where should i go break room the break room okay hurry the f up huh walk yes break room
the break room yes right eye right eye middle eye left eye left eye middle eye right eye
right eye body body body mouth mouth tail mouth tail
tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail tail
bad blind blind actually blind are you pretty she pretending and not
pretending how can you be this bad oh not one there's a safe point right
next to me here we go head dodge left dodge left eye eye eye reload jump
I now please jump jump I I reload jump jump I now now now now now reload back
back back now reload jump I now I please hi hi hi hi hi hi hi Brian
jump I say point save point the save point okay now I'm not fucking around I
ain't going back to the before the elevator I don't want to have her tell
me what her favorite words were grown up again no thanks turn on the TV
the TV okay nine hours of pretending to be bad for cash that's not
that's not in my mental ability to back back please please
auto dodge left dodge left dodge left back head stomach stomach mouth
stomach dodge left auto shoot auto fire dodge left to I'm so tired
stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach I don't fight these things
stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach what the hell
heal stomach reload stomach stomach head stomach mouth stomach mouth
stomach stomach stomach stomach stomach mouth
reload stomach oh recover back child mouth mouth dodge right dodge right
dodge right please dodge left back back dodge right dodge
loud dodge I wanted you to go right dodge right how did you chase me back
mouth mouth mouth mouth dodge right
mouth mouth mouth dodge right back dodge right back back dodge right
dodge right dodge right back dodge right
mouse mouse I'm watching real close and there's only an opportunity when
the stupid slug thing puts his head up mouth mouth dodge right middle I left that
right I right I right I middle I have zero HP honest to God I'm how am I
gonna be able to do this turn on TV the TV okay better save it here no
health I'll take that thanks maybe I'll save in the second slot there's nothing
special left let's search elsewhere nothing with a TV save point the
table save point the save point yes go with the third slot yeah that's a
good idea I'm gonna use all the memory card slots here okay vending
machines see if we can't find a heel the vending machines okay need one
bad on top of vending machine there are only cardboard boxes here it was not
top of left vending machine huh do what with what check top of left vending
machine there's nothing special here left vending machine I don't have any
money on me not what I'm saying check on top of the left vending
machine oh there's a heel capsule recover recover recover use recovery the
galley okay where did you get that stop stop yes recover yes vending machine
the vending machines okay second from far when you say it that way I don't
know what you mean so right vending machine first dispenser there's
nothing special check right dispenser hmm there was nothing I'm disappointed
check trash are you talking about this look in trash can it's just a trash can
galley the galley okay don't you think this game is what middle eye left eye
red eyes back Dodge left Dodge left Dodge right that's right
body body body Dodge left Dodge left back Dodge left Dodge left Back body
body tail tail tail tail tail dodge right tail tail tail dodge left reload
reload dodge right mouth mouth body back back dodge right middle eye left eye
right eye red eye mouth body tail mouth mouth back reload back tail tail body
tail tail body back back back dodge left dodge left dodge right dodge right dodge
right dodge right dodge right you are a moron you did that to yourself tail tail
tail mouth reload dodge right dodge right how are you getting over here how
are you just a glued to me and why there's so many enemies in this room
there's so many people in here that's like enemy number seven or six you
know okay I got it already there's nothing fucking here it's just enemies
vending machine the vending machine I'm getting the hell out of here it's just
what which one of these things you want to spawn an enemy just leave
after this check top of vending machine left there's nothing special here top
of left vending machine oh there's a heel capsule recovery recovery back
leave leave leave what should I move walk I'll walk out stop yes recovery
huh recover yes all right forget everything else hallway leave the room
okay save point the table okay save point save point save point don't just
get enemy spawned in here check dirt it's just a chair look at dirt it's
just a chair look at dirt it's just a chair grab coffee cup it's an
ordinary teacup grab teacup on the left I told you it's an ordinary teacup
that's not a teacup left coffee cup I told you it's an ordinary teacup
smear face in dirt are you talking about this yeah sure look at coffee
bags they're filter bags filled with ground coffee beans they're sure a lot
of them I mean I said coffee look at coffee cup I told you it's an ordinary
teacup look at coffee mug it's a Japanese tea mug it's team I think it's
called Kiyo Mitsuyaki well look in it look in the tea mug it's an
ordinary tea mug there's nothing in it pick up the Japanese tea mug it's
an ordinary tea mug there's nothing in it read note are you talking about
this read the report okay let's see in addition to the incident reported
several days ago researcher Alan Honda's recent actions have been highly
inappropriate and insubordinate he has usurped authority on numerous occasions
removed test subjects without permission and access government
computers outside of regular hours it's apparently about Alan I'll read
I got a big day tomorrow hurry up first time that we have had to make this
request well the stream tomorrow supervisor powers is gonna be we ask
that you demand Alan Honda to fully comply don't expect very much from
tomorrow's spring it's gonna be me sitting in there with hockey equipment
researcher so we're streaming all night tonight because tomorrow's stream
is gonna be probably not that long and I would really like it look behind
Japanese coffee mug ground coffee scattered everywhere look behind tea
cup I told you it's an ordinary look to the left of the teacup I told you
it's an ordinary teacup swat teacup with hand and look behind it I told
you it's an ordinary teacup search coffee grounds the commercial grade
coffee bags search coffee grounds the commercial grade coffee bags look at
coffee grounds the commercial grade coffee bags look at coffee powder
ground coffee scattered everywhere is this someone's idea of a joke clean up
coffee powder huh clean up the coffee granules is that what you're saying
you have to be kidding me the manager's office key good what's it doing here
now we can get into the manager's office we're not done though cuz
this how do I get you to do this grab tea mug it's an ordinary tea mug
there's nothing in it clean tea mug it's an ordinary tea mug there's
how do I get her to interact with that check tea mug it's an ordinary tea mug
check mug nothing it's a small chip lucky me check box they're all blue
cups you'll need to be more specific for me to tell look in the box I
read it already it's a report to powers about Alan's bad behavior look
in the cardboard box it's packed with the hotel's commercial grade coffee
bags I don't think it's necessary save point the save point okay all right at
this point I don't even know which one is the right one to do because I
don't have any heels I'm so screwed hallway leave the room okay where the
teacup is a hat you forgot the galley the galley spawns like four
enemies
that's what I call music volume six leave the dangerous stuff to me it's so
good
shoot Gino
shoot him
hit him in the face
punch him
punch Gino
he's desperate he's not listening to anything I say
shoot
I'm gonna lock you in the cell again
punch him shoot him push him punch him hit me so hard you knocked my fucking
earpiece out of my head now you're gonna begin from the starting cell he
was listening to me she wasn't listening to me but he
was hit her are you sure punch I don't know leave I am stopped get up okay I
got it already leave hallway leave the room okay that's so funny
so what run shake push attack oh Rio Gino what the hell are you doing here
wait real what's going on why are you dressed like that Gino there's
something I want you to see you're babbling give me that weapon you should
wait at the receiver with the others listen I need you to watch this listen
to me real clear sentence no I care about you leave the dangerous stuff to
me take an escape shuttle out of here hey what should I do
right are you still I'm gonna match for him unarmed try to talk to him no way
he's not listening to anything I say what you can't he says he's gonna lock
me up again run if I run off I won't be able to ask him about the stone
punch I'm gonna match for him unarmed scream how can I get him to listen to
me flee if I run off I won't be able to ask him about the stone pistol whip
hey what should I do use gun that's every option there's no other option
that run away this one's listen threaten I'm gonna scream fightin what is the
other option threatened is the right answer I says I did didn't I say that
talk to him he won't listen to me threaten him I can't do that punch him
no he'll get me shoot him I can't shoot him then you're just gonna die you
didn't threaten him you're just dead hallway leave the room okay Mario tennis
ain't looking so bad no I'm I'm good I'm cool I it's just it's kind of
funny that apparently there's one specific thing that I have to say
what the hell are you doing here wait real what's going on why are you dressed
like that do you know there's something I want you to see you're babbling give
me that weapon I can't skip this cutscene you know you should wait at
the receiving port with the other I need you to listen to me Rio you
know I care about the redden threaten leave the dangerous stuff to me take
an escape shuttle out of here hey what should I do kiss why are you still in
here yes I'm gonna match for him unarmed threaten I'm a match for him
unarmed threaten okay I'll try that real drop your weapon why threaten
threaten threaten threaten threaten threaten threaten watch out there are
monsters that are gonna spawn on top of you he puts it in it's just 245 copies
of my ass oh shit it's a wrong CD god damn it where did I put the other one
I must have left it four hours ago
there need to know where this room is here that's the somewhere in the
testing ward no it's the exhibit room Rio you're not a the exhibit room is
closed there are gems and precious metals stored there I'm the one with
the gun so you're a thief this is some scam by you and that operator
I'll scan that scam I suppose you're right huh in some ways I guess I am a
thief it comes a big reveal I told you please do you know turn around I
told you it's gonna happen Rio give up this crazy idea you can't do it
anyways only the manager carries a key to the exhibit room and I got it mr.
Tanaka is under guard by the rescue team in the receiving board that was
like I took a fall somebody paid him to do that your information okay let's
old info break room the break room okay so I'm gonna save this save point the
save point okay psycho Rio leaves guard to die yeah huh all right we're gonna
try to cuz every time I say get up or move she's like fine Rio could you
please stand up yes look at that our team hallway leave the room okay she's
like finally took you over nine hours to say something nice where should I go I
think you should go to the manager's office but and I mean that's just me
manager's office the manager's office okay run yes front-limb front-limb
body mouth inner mouth please dodge left please back enemy to front-limb
hindlimb in the mouth body hindlimb enemy free auto-fire auto-fire reload
dodge left mouth mouth these are harsh enemies in the games mouth stomach back
reload stomach mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth fuck dodge right
back back back back inner mouth hindlimb manager's office the manager's
office I don't think I have any more heels either this is not gonna be
they're not gonna go well run yes give me a healing save point in here body
body body back what back what body enemy to body right stomach left
stomach right stomach left stomach one no not walk into them back back
back right stomach left stomach reload dodge left dodge left sleep enemy to
to enemy to body front leg left stomach right stomach reload your gun
dummy back back back left stomach right stomach right stomach left stomach
left stomach red stomach red stomach fleet reload left stomach red stomach
red stomach fleet turn around turn around back dodge left dodge left
enemy free body front leg left stomach right stomach red stomach red stomach
if you cut me off again after I tell you exactly what to shoot right
stomach watch closely yes he flipped over and I was watching real close he's
got a red stomach that I want you to shoot and you just kind of cut me off
there I really hope you don't do that again left stomach left stomach red
stomach red stomach tail left stomach red stomach fleet turn around turn
around back back back body left stomach front leg reload left stomach right
stomach red stomach red stomach red stomach right stomach right stomach
right stomach body reload back back dodge right dodge right body right
stomach red stomach red stomach fleet body body body right stomach left stomach
tail now red stomach red stomach red stomach mouth body body mouth find
legs red stomach red stomach red stomach reload right
stomach back fleet fleet mouth red stomach i'm tired so am i really getting
real tired of you i'm real tired of you um is there okay here's the thing if i
go back am i going to go to the gauntlet again break room the break room okay
run yes say one thing nice about rio rio you have really really nice hair
the break room okay yeah nice hair you're very smart i said not at all but i'm muted so you're
pretty cool i think you're pretty cool you're really cool leave the room okay where should i go
break room the break room okay you could hear the face bomb i think that was like my hands
that was like my hands and my wrists snapping save point save point the save point okay
wrist palm 3296 commands what is consultation it's actually a pretty good question because
i really don't know either it's supposed to be you go one to one with her and you can talk
about stuff and what the current magician is objective mission i combine the two words
objective magician magician getting to be about 10 hours guys hallway leave the room
okay where should i go so now we go to the manager's office i don't see anything that i can
manage his office the manager's office okay yes he's still playing it yeah sometimes you
got to just marathon as simpson's hit and run don't ask me why i can't really give you much
of an answer to this i don't know why it's always it's a playstation 2 game i did this
with monster rancher 2 i played that for like at least 10 or 11 straight hours
simpson's hit and run was like 11 and a half hours and here we are playing
lifeline for playstation 2 and we're almost 10 hours something about playstation 2 i still
have a handful of ps2 games up there that oh be worth playing eventually here one day
there were tanaka's torn and shredded huh mr tanaka
who is this supposed to be
i warned him that this would happen stay away is the manager don't come any closer why not
shoot shoot him i'm not entirely sure who this is supposed to be
i'm supposed to feel something for this i have no health potions this is not going to go well
yeah head please head left arm right arm please i think we might be in big trouble here
i might have to track down another heal because that's one hit galley the galley run okay yes
yes
left eye right eye middle eye mouth mouth body right eye red back mouth back body tail tail reload
turn around turn around left eye middle eye right eye red eye red eye body mouth mouth tail tail
dodge right that's right dodge right dump tail tail tail right middle i left eye right eye
middle eye left eye right eye right eye red eye mouth dodge right dodge right reload tail tail
tail how do you not shoot her with a desk!
mouth mouth mouth reload dodge right
tail tail tail
dodge left dodge left mouth mouth body
dodge right dodge right reload dodge left mouth
dodge right dodge left dodge left tail tail tail
tail tail dodge right dodge right reload dodge left dodge left body body body
mouth mouth mouth reload yeah i'm serious i'm getting serious save point save point
the save point okay yes
consultation you get a heal in consultation do you actually no galley the galley okay
but i don't think can i even possibly play a game with her right now
because when i tried to before it didn't do anything check chips what should i check check
food what should i check check behind coffee so i should have some tea we can't afford to
dawdle like that look at tea the tv okay back stop what is it galley the galley okay
check top shelf on the top shelf sugar and beverages look behind beverages look behind
the tv okay stop yes you really want to watch tv galley the galley okay check coffee
huh what's this a heal hey a heal capsule check kleenex are you talking about this
no check coffee box it's jsl's coffee bag what's the thing in the middle check middle coffee bogs
one bag makes 10 cups
look at wax paper okay oh god stop stop yes have we've reached the point of the stream where
i'm this i don't think i can do it anymore it's possible galley the galley okay
check wax paper leave the room stop leaving stop stop yes galley the galley okay wax paper box
the table okay i'm going stop move what should i move back what is it
galley the galley okay it's tissues but the last time it wasn't tissues it was wax paper
it was the same box go back like two or three hours when the same thing was there
look at tissue box are you talking about tissue box i said tissue box 14 times last time yes
oh open tissue box are you talking about this check tissue box are you talking about this
check tissue paper it's the hotel's tissue paper there's nothing odd about it wasn't it
just blinking so what's the thing in the middle was it chocolate check tea bag something stuck
between here jump back is written here jump back nice it's a keyword consultation wait a
second can that consultation wait let's check this first back leave huh do what with what
leave the galley what do you mean by that table at the table okay yeah that's how we get her to
know what the fuck she was supposed to do stop yes consultation okay consultation it is okay
what would you like to know about tongue twister tongue twister tongue twister
it doesn't exist tongue twisters tongue twisters tongue twisters tongue twisters tongue
twisters i don't have it bonus menu break microphone i don't have it number one okay
that's it for consultation check gino i am standing approach gino yes it's not tape
galley the galley okay stop stop stop stop yes gino gino she didn't even care that he's here
the save point okay i have a heal i'll beat about full health
all right where's the last boss stand okay i got it already check the chips in the menu
at 11 aren't there trendy and popular collectible items something happens every time your chips
four chips are collected so i need one more chip recover yes here we go hallway leave the
room okay you can use those launcher grenades on the boss so should i
where should i go when he's got the red rings all around him take off all the red rings
and then shoot a grenade launcher down his throat that's what you're saying manager's office
the manager's office okay run yes so i'm gonna i'm gonna say head left body right body
face fingers knees and then all the red things are gonna begin to go and then i rocket grenade
launcher and then red stomach vinny just off streaming well hello guys hopefully uh
hopefully you don't think i'm an insane person because i'm currently almost over the edge right
now of insanity no no that's not true these clothes they were to knock us torn and shredded
huh okay i gotta say shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot so we're gonna i'm just gonna memorize
all the body parts and then i'm gonna grenade launcher but what's this enemy's name
we are gonna have to watch this every time get used to this cut scene
him with that like underbite doing his bat face
i can't be i warned him i warned him that this would happen just use the launcher right off the
back i can't shoot the consensus here is shoot shoot him shoot head left arm right arm left
side right leg what does he have for body parts he has head okay head left arm right arm
right leg left leg head left arm right arm left leg right leg body body left leg right leg
flee tail tail flee dodge right dodge left tail tail watch it carefully reload reload run
flee tail dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left flee go behind
go behind him dodge right dodge left dodge left tail tail how am i gonna get behind him
strafe left strafe strafe flee flee flee flee head head launcher tail tail launcher launcher
he's there tail left leg right leg launcher head head back back back dodge left dodge left
reload shoot head dodge reload dodge left reload no don't reload dodge left dodge left
dodge left dodge left dodge left auto fire dodge left dodge left dodge left
head what do i shoot him now weren't i supposed to shoot him his stomach left arm right arm
dodge right dodge right reload dodge right dodge right tail auto fire dodge left back
what are we doing what should i do i don't know left arm left arm no no it's the wrong arm
god damn it when he pulls his hand up you shoot the hand that does the
oh come on recover recover yes
leave the room okay shoot the thing that's flashing red
you mean my eyes where should i go i bet they are managers managers office the manager's office
okay run yes so i have two launcher shells i'm not even sure i want to use them
maybe no i'm gonna gotta get all that shit off him blow him back shoot his tail and then i
gotta pick he shoots he throws the ball and then a body part lights up ready to shoot that
body part by the way 50 percent of those commands she she went that she dodged a
different direction dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge right
here we go get used to this guts they were to knock us born and shredded huh she's not
calibrated for a boston accent and because i'm tired it's my boston accent just comes out
even harder l2 to skip l2 those aren't doing anything super boston accent select no we have
to watch this every time i got this stuff head left leg no head left arm right arm
body left leg right leg launcher tail let's go shoot shoot
head left arm right arm body left leg right leg
here we go head left arm right arm left leg right leg i don't remember
left arm right i don't left side left leg right leg body left leg right leg body
body left leg right leg that didn't say head body right leg reload
launcher tail tail tail you stupid idiot launcher that's unbelievable
ah launcher tail dodged left dodge right dodge left
yeah dodge left i'm sure to hit the fucking head dodge left i'm not doing this you understand
left dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge left dodge right where is it getting head
dodge right head dodge right dodge left dodge right that was a lot of dog shit right there
you understand that was dog shit oh it's almost like all the commands are getting worse
dodge right dodge left head dodge right back there's not even any letters that match in
there dodge right b a c k there ain't a b there ain't an a there ain't a c and they're not k
dodge right back i gotta turn the gain on my mic down there are there are no settings i'm
gonna have to go into consultation mode apparently what the fuck was that dodge oh
this is my accent get up okay i got it already consultation okay consultation it is
okay what would you like to know about calibrate mic microphone check microphone check
microphone check microphone check this mode doesn't do anything okay that's it for
consultation microphone check your voice that's coming over the microphone
yeah it's pretty clear i can make out almost everything you said
your voice is easy to follow very easy to follow it's very easy to follow except when it's
not recover yes i can hear you perfectly i can hear you so clearly hallway leave the room
all right i'm gonna get it this time we'll be good where should i go
manager's office the manager's office okay pause more during run yes she can hear me
perfectly fine like this we just get an extra thousand viewers um was there a i didn't see
a raid or a host maybe they was did somebody just do a host or a raid oh it's a host from
awesome cool thanks a lot vinny hope you had a good stream if you're not following vinny do it
vinny and joel tonight seriously thanks guys i almost forget it's been like so long my brain
forgot all right streaming long enough to get hosted by vinny and joel this time i'm gonna
be very very slow i'm gonna be very careful i'm gonna try to get it completely right 100
of the time i'm gonna slow down i'm gonna pause we're gonna use our vats system that they're
giving us launcher first no you gotta get him on the ground trying to get behind him
it's too hard shoot shoot key your car please don't do that all right here we go come on
head left arm right arm no no it's left arm right up left arm right arm head
head left arm right arm head left arm left leg right leg body left leg right leg body launcher
launcher tail reload dodge right dodge right this is right arm right arm dodge right i can't do
it anymore dodge left there's right leg right leg left fucking leg left leg
dodge left what was it just tail dodge left fleet fleet launcher launcher your car is gonna
get fucking so keyed it's just you have to say so many the run is dead without having a heal
i don't know it might be ah recover yes hallway leave the room okay alternate dodge directions
instead of going into a wall well when i say dodge left and she dodges right
where should i go that's kind of impossible manager's office the manager's office run okay
run yes germa sounds different it's because i'm like slowly melting in this chair
i've been yelling commands for 10 hours so i'm i'm barely i'm melting
which reminds me i really should get some more water i really just wish we didn't have to
watch the cut scene again if it wasn't for the cut scene these clothes they were to knock us
torn and shredded huh why can't you it's usually select but this is such an important
cut scene apparently that you can't no way i'm gonna do like fucking stretches while this is
going on by the way if you have like get up and like move your legs around an alien i mean
do something reach for the sky down for real i warned him that this would happen buddy i've
been like getting up and doing stuff shoot shoot i'm gonna be so clear about this
it's gonna be shoot what why is you not you did last time it was two times now it's three
and i'm melting my hp bar it was two times wow my god i literally had my hand with my with
my fingers in my eyes leaning to the left because i thought the second time
head left arm right arm left leg right leg launcher tail
dodge right head dodge left dodge left left arm
arm launcher tail body left leg right leg dodge right head dodge left head
dodge right dodge left dodge what leg is that left leg left leg dodge left dodge left
dodge left dot back dodge left what the fuck was with the magic bullet thing magic missile
oh left leg left leg you didn't shoot dodge left and that was a flee right leg dodge right
dodge right dodge right head reload reload reload dodge left
ah dodge left dodge right dodge right dodge back back dodge left this is fucking tail
back dodge left dodge left it's his fucking tail again it's his tail no it's his tail again
dodge left left arm dodge right dodge right dodge left dodge left left arm
dodge right dodge right dodge left dodge left dodge left what is this rng dog shit
we're talking about we are talking about ultimate rng dog shit that's three tails
dodge right dodge left right arm
what do i do i just took a sip of that water and tasted like i was drinking out of a pool
it's the manager's hand i need a new filter on my fucking water the rescue team arrived at
the receiving port just eight of the 50 guests are under guard there the hotel's damage is
worrying but the loss of vips will be critical chairman deckhart missing president suzuki
missing reporter helen johnson missing senator burton missing dr miller missing
research supervisor joe powers missing such bullshit i was gonna in other words i was gonna
be so sad they're dead if i was not gonna be able the exhibit room's key should be in
the three tails where should i start looking all right now don't hope i hold on here i don't
want to crash i don't want to fuck anything up is there a save point the save point
okay yes how am i gonna beat this game that has to be this gotta be nothing left
i'm gonna open i'm gonna use that guy's key i'm gonna scan it there's gonna be the
girl's gonna be in the prison or whatever i'm gonna let her out and we're gonna leave
is this the thing i just did is the noise i just made i might as well just get it over with
i'm hearing i'm so tired i don't know how i made that noise i just a demon exercise for me
get up okay i got it already check desk the desk okay grab a note do you mean this
there's 90 minutes left no there's not check document which document is 90 minutes
there's more no way oh what 90 minutes which one should i check you still need to find naomi
hold on let me grab let me grab a water and i'm gonna come back and i'm gonna get to one
we'll see where we are he's got a mission after this one let me grab some water
we'll come back and i'm gonna determine what the hell is gonna happen okay
right back aren't there any instructions operator are you busy with something else
this mic did it break somehow your instructions are too slow i've had enough
operator what should i do aren't there any instructions aren't there any instructions
all right did we figure out if it actually is 90 more minutes watching me i'll take a quick
break ah let's see what's in the next room is not very clear that we're very close and i will
finish this tomorrow here we go get up okay i got it already desk the desk okay i'm just
eating chocolate check screen do you mean this uh-huh check monitor it's a big monitor it's
showing the station's exterior diagram it's like drain and drain germa's life force why would you
do that bed by the bed stop okay stop stop stop yes take document huh desk the desk okay
take document huh do what with what take document huh do what with what go to the bed
by the bed okay track document take document track document is that how i actually sound
i don't sound like that do i check bed there's nothing especially odd i sound like that
under covers what should i check next to pillow the pillow all places to find a chip
that's 14 uh 12 i mean what do i get for it don't you get something of your 12 chips right
not 12 you know what i mean all right check on top of bookcase encyclopedias and accounting
documents there's nothing that we need starting to sound like you're 40 top of bookcase huh do
what with what check top of bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents on top
of bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents this is why it's gonna take an hour
grab top of bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents somebody help me out here
check top of bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents shoot bookshelf
shooting won't help let's not check behind pictures there's nothing especially odd check
photos on top of bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents this is what it
feels like to watch your stream now i'm just gonna check what should i check look on top
of bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents look it's safe it's a very
old-looking this is an old-fashioned can i open this i don't think it can be opened
can't be open to open it i would have to manually enter the combination using the dial somebody look
it up what do we do open safe to open it i would have to manually enter the combination
using the dial of course i don't have a clue how to open it so you'll have to guide me
how many notches should i turn i don't know 69 um hey how much am i supposed to turn this
uh how many notches should i turn is nobody gonna help me here two okay i'll rotate it to two
hey a lamp just went on okay good what should i check check what should i check turn left
how many notches should i turn two okay i'll rotate it to two turn right okay i'll rotate
it seven to the right it's been reset i guess we screwed up so the dial must be rotated correctly
three times to okay how much am i supposed to turn this or so we're gonna give up on the safe
okay can you wait a second open safe the safe okay how many notches should i turn four
okay i'll rotate it to four six okay i'll rotate it to six two okay i'll rotate it to two
um we blew it again we'll have to start over four okay i'll rotate it to four
left six okay i'll rotate it that was she didn't go left right two to the right okay that's
what i told you she didn't catch the left part reset reset okay right to the right okay how far
should i turn it four okay i'll rotate it four to the right left to the left okay how far should
i turn it six okay i'll rotate it six to the left right to the right okay how far should i
turn it two okay i'll rotate it two to the right got it it opened operator i'm sorry it's
i couldn't i was in there it's here the exhibit room key yeah nice work excellent job everybody
what is this disc nothing other gbd it says lost and found on it it belongs to
alan honda hang on a minute where you going gonna put it on the big screen
this will let us watch that disc we found good it doesn't appear to be broken
soft edge corporation paracelsus plan that didn't say plans his project are you familiar
with the philosopher stone it is said to have been in the possession of paracelsus
a 16th century european philosopher capable of generating intense healing power
it was a stone that defied human comprehension it was studied by some scholars of the time
but despite lengthy research their efforts were in vain at long last however we have
succeeded in reproducing the philosopher stone this is it this is it the philosopher stone we
have created is identical in composition and structure to the original and its potency is
even greater so what are you gonna do this photo presents a simulation of the effects of the
original philosopher stone as noted in ancient manuscripts the next photo shows the results of
an experiment based on the instructions in those ancient documents it's obviously not
working because it's turning people into fucking mad as you can see our philosopher stone is
capable of producing effects precisely opposite to those produced by the original slugs instead
of healing a living thing so that it may survive it curses the organism which remains
alive a number of possible results of the use of this stone can be imagined but the most effective
is the use of an accursed hex capable of plunging a civilized society into chaos
this very stone has been spared in order that your country may carry out its plan of battle
and we believe that this is the only measure available
i'm gonna go break the beauty and the beast uh rose glass it's an alien
joseph craft corrupt living creatures with curses
that's the best thing i've seen all night aliens and ufos it was all a lie
this lady is about to burp like she has been drinking only soda for the last week but before
she was doing a burp voice like controlling a burp stone and the reason for the philosophers
was that it was part of a sky science that was perfect okay hotel registry the hotel
registry okay we need heels rum yes this is the hotel registry it's totally destroyed
i hate that it looks beyond repair it's the worst thing ever the hotel was booked for years
to come i see a grenade launcher soda can ammunition right there it's a launcher shell
pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it up
up up pick it up pick it up up up shower booth shower booth okay run yes things have been
cleared away another Christmas launcher show I'll take that thank you very much
let's check somewhere else drink out of the toilet yes don't do that yes good
I'm glad you agree check bed the bed okay is there any other
heels I need something to drink recover I don't have any right above the book
shelf I already looked at I already grabbed it didn't I no I didn't book
shelf there were only encyclopedias and there's no way to get it impossible check
behind pictures on bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents check
above bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents check above
the bookshelf there were only encyclopedias and documents check above
books do you mean that look above books the desk okay stop yes go with examine
yes back stop okay bed the bed okay pictures on bookshelf this is the
manager's photo how many different ways do you have to say something before
they get it it says it's a crumpled up category five dollar bill we get to
play game consultation wait a second can that consultation wait let's check
this first don't ever deny a consultation I don't know what I'm
doing I have no idea how to do this you can't do that to me you're a
computer computer computer consultation I need help back there's nothing
especially odd her AI is rebelling this is not even AI this is a person
leave who's got time to sleep desk the desk okay consultation well sure what
advice would you like categories categories game what is it category
game category game that's it for consultation category game okay let's
play categories category is the Caribbean okay go Antigua five four
three lago okay Cuba US Virgin Islands five four three two one Puerto Rico
how did I get Pete Largo but I couldn't get a view as Virgin Islands category
game okay let's play categories category is official United States
holidays okay go New Year's Day five Thanksgiving four Thanksgiving yeah
Thanksgiving day sure Columbus day five Halloween four Christmas two
Christmas day close sure Christmas day okay
well Labor Day five four veterans day three veterans day close sure
veterans day okay independence day fine I'll give you an independence day I
hit you with Easter three Easter day two Easter one Easter Sunday what the
total up till now is you haven't won a single game come on Easter Easter
Sunday I said Easter Sunday I did it really clearly category game okay let's
play categories category is islands of the Caribbean no okay go Dominican
Republic five on Tigo for Montego three Montego too close sure Martinique
okay St. Vincent five key Largo four three key Largo one what didn't you just
say game the total up till now is you haven't won a single game I thought
she said that was fun thanks I'm gonna win category game leave the room
category game okay category game we play a category game now
category category is cities with pro football teams here we go
Dallas five New York three New York to Massachusetts Boston hey operator you
lose what the fuck are you talking about New York Jets what total up till
now is New York New York has fucking like 10,000 teams she said city New
York City do I have to say in New York City it's implied that the city is
after the words that you New York I'd say Boston City she said what city
New York New York City category game category game okay let's play
categories category is signs of the zodiac okay hit it Libra five Virgo Wow
very fast that's what I am so I know Virgo okay
Pisces five Gemini Wow very fast Gemini okay well cancer five Leo Wow very
fast how many more are there there's not much more left sure corn five Pisces hey
operator you lose what I said that already I know did she say that
already the total up till now is you haven't won a single game I'm
unbeatable that was fun thanks it was the first one fuck category I need
the heel category game category game okay let's play categories category is
cities with pro football teams here we go Philadelphia five Oakland Wow very
fast sure Oakland well Pittsburgh I was just gonna say Pittsburgh New
England Cleveland Houston what's going on why did you Cleveland Houston that's
not it that's they're in different states Cincinnati Cincinnati oh yeah
Cincinnati sure which should I choose this should do it Detroit five four
three fuck you like a cheese Kansas City Kansas City Kansas City sure which
should I choose this should do it Minneapolis five Green Bay okay Green Bay
sure well what was it oh yeah Dallas you already said that for st. Louis yeah
she said that was stuff she was the first thing she said what well Baltimore
five Chicago okay I forget everything I don't know what I'm out I could
probably think of them was gonna take them more than five seconds yes you do
the total up till now is I seem to be doing better I won't lose that was
fun I win give me a heel when do I get my heel categories shower category
game category game stop yes category game okay let's play categories it
doesn't heal you um category is name of US state capitals go Juno five
Boston okay Boston sure Trenton five Las Vegas Carson City sure Carson City
okay Salem five four three two Anchorage Anchorage Anchorage main Anchorage the
total up till now is why is it doing this to me I seem to be doing better
I won't lose that was fun thanks category game category game do it again
category game okay let's play categories category is states football
teams the Caribbean islands in the Caribbean British Virgin Islands five
four three I don't know to Saint Martin one game the total up till now I'm
screaming them I seem to be doing better I won't lose that was fun thanks
category game okay let's play categories category is American
ready go Rutherford Hayes five Grover Cleveland Grover Cleveland you lose
you lose I just said that why do I lose when when I say it again but
she just I am she said it right back to me right back to my face and I
don't win Abraham Lincoln yeah Abraham Lincoln okay
Ronald Reagan five James Madison wow very fast okay James Madison there
should be more I just said that William Henry Harrison five Howard Taft four
Taft three Howard Taft two Barack Obama the total up till now is I seem
to be doing better I won't lose that was fun thanks you're not gonna give me
you're not gonna give me Howard Taft I would get that on Jeopardy they didn't
call them William Taft they called him Howard Taft that's what his
nickname was category game category game I'm gonna start shaking the
machine category game okay last one I promise last one category is name of
US state capitals go Harrisburg five Boston Wow very fast I'm pretty good at
this sure which should I choose this should do it Boston I just said it
Carson City okay Carson City there should be more Boston this should do
it Providence five downtown three Sacramento Sacramento which should I
choose Dover five Dover Cleveland four three two Washington DC what hey
operator you lose I don't fucking know it's too late I had my brains
locking up Maryland no up till now is I seem to be doing better I won't lose
that was fun thanks so tired category game category game category game okay
let's play categories category is American president good ready go
Harry S Truman five John Quincy Adams or okay John Quincy Adams to say the
Richard Nixon five George Bush George Washington okay Gerald Ford five George
W. Bush three George W. Bush two Howard Taft the total up till now is I seem
to be doing better I won't lose that was fun thanks tongue twisters I don't
have that yet 2004 it too that it is too good this is 2004 I don't have the
keyword she sells she sells she sells seashells by the seashore she sells
she sells seashells by the seashore she sells seashells by the seashore
she sells seashells by the seashore I fucking can kill it I can kill it
even after 11 hours where the fuck am I going consultation well sure what
advice would you like where do we go what do we do what should we do
artificially recreate the philosopher stone I knew it I was afraid of this
it's in the exhibit room we have to get the stone so if you go to the
exhibit all right no heels for me leave save point how am I gonna beat
this with fucking one HP save point save point end transmission I would
call delete consultation I'm done stop get out of consultation save point the
save point run okay yes I am running times I just wasted so much time
watching American capitals
hallway let's finish leave the room okay run yes where should I go I'll
tell you in a second this is the last opportunity I'm gonna get no it doesn't
want to sneeze exhibit room the exhibit run okay run yes the exhibit room is
ahead we're finally close we're here game over huh there are two panels for
swiping cards which one should I be using I'll give it a try you know I'm
looking at him no go maybe it's the other panel she pulled it out of her
anus was in her back pocket relax it won't work oh I get it do you can
enlighten me please what do we do the exhibit room door it looks like you
have to undo two locks at the same time so give me a key I'll undo one
lock with this card key I want you to undo the other lock using the
panel on the right okay you give the cue when you're ready okay when you're
ready say get ready set okay I'm ready like fucking card get ready set now get
ready set now that's perfect I did it is there a way that I can watch this
dream and also go to sleep yeah you can uh you have a mobile phone or an
iPad you can put a maybe put it down on the bed and just listen stone
should be in this exhibit room this is the end of the game help me look
this is gonna take fucking forever save point the safe point okay run yes use
the nightlight filter that's true yeah okay I got it already case one case one
okay one yeah it's gonna go around we're gonna do it huh what is that what
could this be it's not it is this an exhibit too that's just a mineral
this display isn't it case two case two run yes oh this is bad game over I lose
back back I have no heels are these cheats for this game which one in which case is it I'll
give a shit tell me I'm not gonna run around I'm not running around
them look which case is it in so we can just get this done just tell me
yes recover I don't have any more I'll have to find some more case three case three okay
yes thank God it's just a little bug
root root branches leave body root left eye right eye body right eye left eye
leave enemy three head head mouth mouth mouth stomach stomach mouth stomach
mouth reloads back back mouth mouth stomach stomach reloads root branches
leave middle I middle I middle I know I vines vines right I branches branches
branches leaf body root leaf branches right eye right eye right branches
dodge right reload reload attack forward body dodge left dodge left branches
branches how do I kill this fucking thing right eye left eye leaf body body reload safe
point I'm tired safe point the safe point to cheese this run yes oh no why why right
eye middle eye left eye right eye middle eye left eye middle eye left
eye right eye left eye red eye reload red eye red eye body mouth mouth mouth
mouth mouth reload mouth mouth tail tail tail you stupid game middle eye left eye
right eye right eye mouth right eye red eye red body tail tail tail reload
tail reloads back back fleet the middle eye left eye right eye middle eye left eye
right eye middle eye left eye right eye right eye right eye red eye reload mouth
mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth mouth tail tail tail tail tail body body body
tail tail tail tail tail tail tail can I please save the game save point the
save point run okay yes thank God no random encounters am I gonna have to
complete the rest of this game with one hit that would be so bad yes yeah yeah
up yes case three case three run yes this is gonna suck I'm sorry dude best
gamer moment of 2019 playing this game for more than
I'm gonna unplug those and stick them into my body that's gonna be an ultra
hill it's gonna overheal me can you analyze PBX there's no mistake it's a
bomb can you check how to defuse it if you time fuse can be turned off by
entering the passcode okay you found the right instructions some of the
last digits of today's date to me okay and first enter the sum of the
last digits of today's date okay yes that's easy today's December 24th 2029
so the last digit of each one would be 249 that's easy add them up and
enter it what I just missed it I enter the sum of the date and the
center the sum of the last digits of today's date just tell me I'm too
tired 65 that's 14 how do I backspace 15 the number of guests checked into the
hotel how would you ever know that enter the number of detect gender the
the guest checked in the hotel
the note out of 50 guests 13 survivors as of 216 so 50 50 guests 50 agreed the
number of checked in guest should be 50 enter it how do I enter the code okay
enter the sum of the last digits of p.m. Takayama's birthday enter the sum of
the last digits of p.m. Takayama's birthday dny was really nice knowing
you you're right didn't he say something about that at some point I
thought we were just dead I thought the bomb was gonna explode man hopefully
it would trigger it up a mega-memory that's great
we turn off the fucking dubstep what did he say 60 so it was 60 the 60 times
what is the rule and the sum of the last digits of the birthday 60 so that
would be so what is today what's it what year is this supposed to be 20
20 what 20 29 minus 60 is there 30 20 29 minus 60 is 19 90 so yeah you're
right okay so there'd be 30 would be 30 15 because you only need the last
digit okay yeah you only need the last digit don't drop it do you like to take
a break it's taking you 11 hours playing this game to actually ask me
that yeah this whole time I've been trying to remember your face those just
but I can't not anymore easy don't just put on the ground I want you to
know I really am grateful if it weren't for you I'd be dead it's good to know
here we are complete strangers and trusting one another when she said that
and everyone on earth oblivious to what's going on and you know it's
funny I don't even know your name I'm gonna tell it to you if we get
back to earth safely you think we could actually meet somewhere like
normal friends no oh yeah well there is Naomi kind of invading her right now
I'm sure Naomi is safe somewhere we'll find her what are you doing put that
back put that bomb back in there doing why are you destroying the
station that's none of your concern oh it's master chief and his friend
down and hand that over you holy mother of all it's lady lady Gaga no lady
I'm gonna keep running I got a bomb just hold the bomb in the air just sprinting
screaming bomb you know just just use it as a shield be like I'm gonna block the bullets with
the bomb pretty sucks so much in this game oh my god they're about to use a rocket
I'll buy us some time hurry what
I didn't just accidentally press square that was some modal combat bullshit right there
defuse the bomb again no we don't Sam I'll be sitting up use the fucking bomb again get up
get up okay I got it case three case three okay what was it was what was it 15 50 15 15 50 15 run
yes it's not here skip someone's taking it already
we'll have to return to their seat we need to find alan honda
so
I can't skip 15 50 15
this chord what is this
there's no mistake it's a bomb can you check how to defuse it
that you found the right instructions to defusing can you read them to me
we'll think it through together sure I'll read them to you let me just put my glasses on
what's the first one
enter the sum of the last digit to today's date hurry enter the sum of the last digits
of today's date okay yes that's easy 15 today's december 24th 2029 so the last
digit of each one would be 249 that's easy and enter it seems to have worked
enter the number of the guests enter the number of the guests locked in the hotel rooms
enter the number of the guests locked in their hotel rooms enter the number of the
guests checked in the hotel rooms enter the enter the number of guests checked into the hotel
this is easy too the answer is in tanaka's note it's 13 okay enter it
please be careful with this
oh wait a second I had it right oh it's wrong it's not 13
it's not the number of survivors it's the number of checked in guests
check manager tanaka's note carefully and enter that number
right it's on tanaka's note hurry enter the code
that was too close please stop okay what's the next step for defusing
enter the sum of the last and to the sum of the last digits of p.m.
takiyama's birthday date month year what do we do just let it blow up
that at some point
wait why why did somebody just said why didn't i think of that go ahead
okay all right here we go oh yeah it's 50 there you didn't know
there's nothing that I can do
50 I don't know please do 50 again no up 50 no no no 65
15 hey what do you think you're doing with that thing
all right here we go I can um I can she's gonna ask me if we can be friends again
and would you like to take a break
I'm just trying I'm gonna push it as fast as I can how fast think I can hit the button
you ready I can't do it yet this whole time I've been trying to remember your face
but I can't not anymore I want you to know I really am grateful if it weren't for you I'd
be dead here we are complete strangers and trusting one another with our lives
and everyone on earth oblivious to what's going on and you know what's funny I don't
even know your name if we get back to earth safely you think we could actually meet somewhere
like normal friends a few days ago I ordered a pizza from an app and you know some pizza
places have where you can make your own pizza well I got a little overzealous and I thought
I was making something really great and it was a pesto pesto pizza well there is Naomi kind
of in being her ring I'm sure Naomi is safe somewhere we'll find her grilled chicken on it
we've got to and I didn't put any sauce on the pizza it was like sauce no sauce what are you
doing meat grilled chicken I could just press buttons what are you doing I put like olive
oil on it and pesto and garlic it's terrible his worst pizza probably ever eaten I knew
there was something weird you guys aren't a rescue team pipe down and hand that over
holy mother of
let's get it I'm trying wait is that master chief the master chief
okay don't fuck it up select close pesto pizza is good yeah but it was no sauce on it it was
just like a piece it was like a cracker it was a really crunchy cracker with chicken
they weren't a rescue team for me the worst person I know
you don't really believe that dude I hope you don't
no they're after the stone too oh god the pms go back to the receiving port
they're in danger she's running go get away stop her okay close door
Caesar is pretty good too you have like a Caesar pizza it's
Caesar dressing grilled chicken sometimes and lettuce
who's that oh my god they're about to use a rocket
all right I gotta pay attention operator the shutter close I'll buy us some time
close the door I got it
mustard ketchup shoot mustard shoot the buster or the ketchup shoot red which one is it
shoot red shoot red lever shoot the lever shoot red and yellow lever chat help me out here
aim at lever shoot shoot top lever red shoot red out of cover red shoot red
let's do it shoot just shoot red again yellow now shoot yellow shoot no no no another grenade
no another grenade no another grenade why did I stop because people were telling me that
they could shoot I've the real question you should be asking yourself is why did it take
like 17 times saying shoot red shoot red lever red lever shoot red shoot red why did it take
that many times that's the question you should be asking I can't fucking believe it and the
reason why is because somebody said the one guy and I listened it was when I when you go
out of cover you could just get shot by one of these guys if there is that true so wait
so it is true so I would have just died anyways if I did shoot yellow yellow lever I can't believe
I have to do that whole thing again what were they thinking what the hell are you thinking
you put an unskippable like seven minutes of cutscene and a bomb diffusion thing with
a save point here and this is it you're gonna do it again what the hell are you doing
get up get up stand up stand up doesn't want to listen to me anymore stand up
stand up please stand up please stand up get up get up get up get up walk go get up
get up go get up I need guidance hello hello Rio listen I know I've said some really mean things
about you in the video game that you're currently in but I want to make sure you
understand I mean every single one of them all the things that I've said I mean you know I mean
double them I made them double now triple even get up case three
case three case three oh it's getting angry oh no no no no no no no no easy easy easy
watch the light here can you hear me Rio Rio hello hello Rio did you hear that noise
buzz all right all kinds of weird shits going on uh maybe I need to restart the system
Rio get up get up you're not gonna do this to me at the end of an 11 and a half hour stream
you're not gonna sit there and not let me beat the game you're not gonna do that to me
we are potentially 20 to 30 minutes out from finishing the whole game how dare you do this
to me get up right now consultation consultation consultation tech support consultation
what is that buzz I don't know the disc is scratched it is not get in there I broke the
mic how would I have broken the mic I didn't do anything yeah the indicator is still showing
up there it's good it's gonna work right now hey I am stopped get up okay thank you now you
fucking listen to me case three go hurry okay now quickly hurry up go something's not plugged
in all the way but it is everything's plugged it's not here someone's taking it already
we'll have to return to the PS2 is never meant to run for 12 hours
uh
the time fuse can be shipped yes there's no mistake it's a bomb can you check out
it if you enter the sum of the last digits they take okay you found the right instructions
can you read them to me enter the name enter the sum enter the sum
enter the sum what's the first one enter the sum of the last digit of today's date
okay yes that's easy hurry hurry go go go 15 15 15 so the last digit of each one would be
two four nine that's easy add them up and enter it does the game have more crust now
I know it's the game I have more crust now
yes I restarted the PS2 I know the game has extra crust that seems to have worked
how about you read the instructions for the next step enter the number of guests checked
into the hotel this is easy too the answer is in Tanaka's note it's three o'clock in the
morning okay enter it how the fuck am I ever going to get up and stream tomorrow
please be careful with this enter the number of guessing
uh Hong it's not 13 it's not the number of survivors it's the number of checked in guests
you're not
I'm going to sleep through my own death it's very possible
and here's here's another like awful thing so
we're wasting time it's right here we have both of our offices are across the house from
each other right but his bedroom is right here oh so hope you don't mind Ruby I'll be quiet
enter the sum of the last digits of p.m. Takayama's birthday
just birthday I sleep through my death tomorrow what do we do is that going to be bad
came so close I do you can do it we can do it we're a team we'll always be a team
what do we do here here's 100 million dollars in cash no strings what do we do what do we do
here's a hundred million dollars in cash
please be extra careful there's no way I can just back out of here and be like can you say
safe
there you got your fucking toy from Dave and Busters am I about to break my own record here
longest stream ever do you like to take a break no I don't actually and you know I would love
to take a break I'd love for you to go to the safe point that's over there
this whole time I've been trying to remember your face but I can't not anymore here comes
the sob story about how she can't wait to be my best friend and want to fall in love with
me and shit I want you to know I really am grateful if it weren't for you I'd be dead
and here we are complete strangers and trusting one another with our lives
and everyone on earth oblivious to what's going on and you know what's funny I don't even know
your name if we get back to earth safely you think we could actually meet somewhere
say safe point yes if when we get to the next part of this game here you listen carefully
and you do a very good job and you listen oh yeah well there is Naomi
kind of envying her right now I'm sure Naomi is safe somewhere we'll find her we've got to
please get me out of here what are you doing why are you destroying the station
yeah there that's none of your concern I knew there was something weird I'm going to bed
fuck this lullaby life down and hand that over holy mother of select select
red lever so let me get this straight and make sure so red lever or red shoot red lever
and then yellow red lever yellow lever red lever yellow lever left soldier right soldier right
so
red or yellow
keep running shoot red shoot red or do I have to say red lever red lever
red lever
red lever yellow red lever left soldier right soldier
right so right soldier red lever
red lever shoot red
shoot red cover get it cover what are you doing shoot red right soldier clip that I want that
clip because I want to see how perfectly I said shoot red I want to see it give it to me I need
to know because that was it that was that was offensive to me that was offensive who has it
just play the ending on youtube why why I said shoot red and she says right soldier and she
just stood there maybe I'm still alive you don't need to even fucking hear this
get up you don't need to hear this we're gonna put something else on tv
I'm gonna do the meditation thing again everybody do it this five minute meditation can reduce
nervousness before events such as interviews beginning a new job or school case three with
everyday stressful situations or just whenever you want to feel calm to begin sit on a chair
with your feet on the floor you use this twice in a week no this is this is not cheers to you
then exhale through your mouth to the count of two what am I doing with my mouth do this
several times in her mouth in her mouth it might be time to let's break it out
I can't we're gonna no we're gonna we're gonna we're doing cheers to you it's a good
it's a good opportunity for it not yet though I just don't want you guys to hear this awful
fucking music anymore enter the sum of the last digits of today's date you're abusing its power
I need it right now enter the sum of the last digits of today's date he's doing it the same
rig yeah no I'm not no no jokes it's gonna fuck it up just beat it how do I even turn
this back on I don't get time for jokes how about you read the instructions for the next step
I'm gonna sleep through the screen anymore okay enter it
I got like a bunch of
last time I'm doing this I promise
this is gonna be me sleeping in hockey gear enter the sum of the last digits of p.m. takiyama's
birthday how are we supposed to know the prime minister's birthday we do what do we do what do
we do finish it what do we do do it what do we do finish it what do we do finish it
do it come on you can do it finish it do it do it do it do it do it do it finish the stream
finish the stream finish the stream finish the mission do it
yeah they did there's about 3,500 of them over here
be extra careful I need to copy and paste this okay got it left soldier or right soldier to get
them to hide for a moment then shoot the red or lever or yellow lever you want to shoot the
lever that's higher to repeat this process until the shutter finally closes then tell Rio to run
when given the option before sending him to Rio next time you have an option so it's okay
okay let's go let's do it would you like to take a break no
this whole time I've been trying to remember your face but I can't not anymore I want you
to know let's hear it again I really am grateful if it weren't for you I'd be dead
dead here we are
normal friends yes thanks for being considerate no anyway you'll have Naomi back
I don't even know who that was I took a heavy metal to use it but we'll find her we've got to
what are you doing put that back what are you doing why are you destroying the station
that's none of your concern I knew there was something weird you guys aren't about to get
muted that like 10 seconds
I can't miss that stream it's been a year in the making more than that it's been almost a
full year in the making I can't just not stream tomorrow because I'm going to go to bed at like
5 a.m I knew it they weren't your team
just don't stop streaming
no no no no no they're in danger
I'm gonna just assume the worst no
all right so it's shoot red left soldier right soldier
get it right for some reason I thought I'd do the wrong right soldier
shoot the soldiers
is there is there a hide website hide
what oh my god thank fucking god
left soldier right soldier right soldier what the fuck are you doing right hide
left soldier left you fucking idiot that's enough when when I'm being just fought
when I'm being pulled both ways if left soldier right soldier it just ruined the
ruin of the I can't call me a quitter this game I can't I can't not right now
I will see you guys tomorrow today of whatever the fuck it is stream's probably
not gonna start until 4 p.m pacific because this is going very late watch the no I might
finish this tomorrow I think I'm actually gonna jump back into this and finish it tomorrow
so 4 p.m pacific when the stream is gonna start Merry Christmas or whatever today today
like today because another stream is gonna happen today it is also because I only have
no health I actually think the game is fun fairly fun and funny and interesting so I mean
but for the sake of how late this is and how I have to get up and stream again
we're probably going to let's see here let me see how many bits there are because there are
a lot of subs too I want to show the credits at least let's go through some of these
because I think no never mind that's not gonna work yeah I think I have to just save the bit
reading for tomorrow because this is this is a lot of people give a ton of money today like an
absolute monumental amount of fucking money and this this stream will go on for like
another two and a half hours which would then be about five plus a.m pacific so I'm gonna
run the credits the we have that website that tracks everything so I'm gonna go over
the bits from today tomorrow so tomorrow you're gonna be reading bits before I was
no I'm gonna probably go through them as quickly as I can but holy shit guys
there was seriously like there was like probably almost three grand today if you're
including subscriptions bits there were hundreds of gifted subs thousands of dollars
and bits it was it was insane and I'm really sorry that I just I really don't have it
in me mentally for energy right now to go through and do them all just know that I can't
thank you enough thousands of fucking dollars in one day so I'm gonna get some sleep I'll
see you guys at four p.m pacific for the stream and maybe afterwards I will give this another go
we'll see on top of that thanks everybody there was a lot of there's a couple of raids
and hosts and everything and there were a lot of people that came out thank you for coming
out if you stuck around hell yeah thanks for sticking around let's run the credits because
it's gonna be crazy and then we can get some sleep is it even running holy shit
that might be the fastest it's ever gone I've never seen it scroll that fast
holy shit have fun reading that yeah good night guys see you in uh like 12 and a half hours
whatever it is you stayed so I you stayed so I could read your bits at the end I am sad
I'm really sorry but I am out of gas completely I never expected I was gonna
play this for more than like eight to seven to eight plus hours but I gotta be honest with
you guys I'm out of gas completely and I would not I would rather hold on to them and do them
when I have energy than like sleepy almost almost potentially lazily going through them
you know I'm saying did you see cry yeah actually I did uh Kraken was in town
he's really really great he hit me up he said hey I'm gonna be in Vegas and I was
like I'll come say hello hung up for a little while it was great I came back from a pee break
did I miss anything uh well you missed left soldier right soldier is what you missed
I had coached him on gambling well I pressed a button and I won money there's not much
not much coaching this has got to be 500 fucking subs let me see yeah it's this is
close to 500 subs in one day I think that's only ever happened to maybe one or two more
other times how much money have I made isn't it how much money have I made this month how
much money did I make this stream this straights gotta be at least two to three grand has to be
this stream probably just opened like another dozen emotes lots or something
but that's gonna be it thank you everybody I honestly am floored I can't believe it's
shocking the just the ridiculous amount of money and support it's absolutely ridiculous
so I cannot wait to see you again yeah just a little bit a little bit later today take care
see you soon get some sleep if you stayed up all night then glad to have you see you guys
real soon have a great rest of your night or you know not even night it's not night for
anybody right now it's day for everyone now everybody in the world except for Australia
good night guys I can't leave yet I can't leave yet I'm sorry we're not leaving yet
it's 11 58 11 hours and 58 minutes I can't it's got to be 12 hours
I'm gonna have to sit here for like another 30 seconds so two minutes of madness
how's your day been chat three four five six seven eight nine ten is it like noon for some of
you guys a lot of the EU crowd it's definitely somewhere between like 11 and one right have I
ever done a 12-hour stream I don't know have I this is this is definitely the longest stream
half of a full day hit and run was longest and that was about 11 hours
and you're last according to your bio oh god here we go 30 seconds 24 hours now
I just don't have it in me I mean you see how I'm acting after the 10-hour mark there's no
way yeah it's like a physically human and it's a human impossibility gonna be made out of
like a machine you have to be definitely plug your brain in somewhere I will never be able
to do 24 hours there it is 12 hours thanks a lot guys see you very soon sooner than I think
good night good morning good night