Hey, what is going on everybody? It's Jerma here with a vlog, and this is a kind of a
special vlog because, oh, spoiler, spoiler alert, there he is. That's my new dog. His
name is Otto, and I just got him last night. Me and my mother drove to Rhode Island to
pick him up. Hey, come here. Say hello to people. Come here. Can you see him? Look at
how, my God, my room is the messiest room I've ever seen in my life. Come here, you.
Come here. He's a little shy. So here he is. And why don't you look in the camera. Say
hello to the viewers. Look, see, he's a Dachshund, Doberman, Beagle. We don't even know what the
hell he is, but he's a rescue dog. And he's one years old, I think, one and a half, something
like that. We're not exactly sure how old he is exactly, but he's from Tennessee. That's
all I remember. But yeah, those of you that do know, I had a dog that passed away two
or three weeks ago. So this is kind of the, not really the replacement, but it's the continuation
of the dog lineage, because we used to have a Dachshund. He died and wanted to get another
dog, wanted to fill the shoes of the old one, so to speak. And he's doing a great job. He's
a fantastic dog. Look at him. Look at how shy he is. He's just burying his nose into
my arm. What's wrong with you? Huh? Okay, you can get down. So really the second order
of business of the video is, I just, I'm about to pass 20,000 subscribers. And guys, that is
unbelievable. That is insane. I just passed 15,000 like last month or something. You guys are
unbelievable. I have no words to really describe how amazing all you guys are for subscribing to
this channel and for keeping up with the content and for supporting and all the support, everything
you guys do. It's phenomenal. So huge, huge thank you so much for 20,000 subscribers. I can't
believe I'm actually saying that, but thank you. And to kind of add to that, I got another one of
those ridiculous videos planned. Probably not till 25,000 subscribers, but it's coming. So
be ready for that. We're going to do something wacky as usual. So Otto, you want to say goodbye?
His name's Otto. Did I say that? I hope I did. So Otto, say goodbye. See you later. Nice to meet
everybody. I hope you all have a good day.