Hello, how's everybody doing? Welcome back to streamer of the week. That's me. I won the uh
just want to make sure I won the 2016 streamer of the week award. I like to announce that every
stream just so people are aware. I played Minecraft for like a couple hours and I built a cool snowman
looked just like Olaf and it was it was an honor. But welcome to another VR stream. Hope you're
well rested. Just put on my uh utility belt on my hands and we'll get started. Give me one second.
So I wanted to try and see if I could get more of the room here.
God, because when I that's a little bit more wide, right? Oh well you can like see that shit. I want
to get let me move that like this so you can see more of the room. I'll go like that. Why don't
you turn this way? There we go. Okay, so now I've got the complaint. I got a lot of complaints,
okay? Last stream where once I got to be about here I wasn't in frame anymore
and then once I got to be about here I also wasn't in frame anymore and we've got full
widescreen now. Ain't you understand? People were complaining. I got emails. So there we go. See
now no matter where I am you should be able to see me across your entire television set.
Isn't that something? I also got a haircut. What do you think? My twitch chat back here.
Too short? Well you can't you can't that's you can't even see it. That's the joke.
Glad you laughed at it. But anyways let me get started here. We're gonna play Gorn. This is the
first game we're gonna play is Gorn and let's make sure that you can see this. Otherwise I'm
gonna be in big trouble and hey look at that. All right now this is gonna be hard to drink.
Coffee. Wait let me make sure because sometimes I get here but is that a good widescreen display?
You know what I'm saying? Like if I'm gonna say I'm going to walk this way it's gonna happen.
That's a good display right? I'm just concerned if I like stand here.
I'll just be like where I'm supposed to be like right here. This is perfect all right.
Tilt the camera down. Now if I tilt the camera down you'll get to see like below the belt
and then if I like this is like the only place it can be because if I stand here
then like look at this shit. Like I'm cut off over there. It's gotta be.
Like I think that's perfect. I have to go down so I can show feet. I don't think so.
Yeah what if I do it a little bit. I don't want I don't want this real estate to be that much
taken up. You know what I mean? We'll do a little bit. All right I'm stalling long enough. Let me
get my hands in here. Welcome to another edition of fucking boomer plays virtual games.
Hot dogs horseshoes and hand grenades is what we're doing next. All right you don't think I
got that queued up already? All right let's go. I'm going in. Oh no I'm not. Which one of these
goes in? So Goren from my understanding it's uh it's a game where you you have a farm
and your your grandfather dies and then the farm is then given to you and you can buy like uh
cabbage. There's like parsley. You you have to like press buttons on on wood to get wood to build
stuff. It's something like that. That's what at least I think. There's a bunch of towns people
I guess that you can make friends with and you can like romance them. It's kind of an interesting
experience I guess. All right let me say that. Can I say you guys? Hey there you are. Move hand here.
Press and hold to wait move hand here. Press and hold to grab world. Pull hold and pull world.
I hate this already. I look like a different game. I don't like to like rowboat mechanic already.
Is this supposed to be going faster? I have to ski. I'm doing something wrong right?
What am I doing wrong here? Uh that's not correct. What is going on?
Hold on. Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait. I got like strapped in already.
Fucking hand straps. I'm gonna make a VR room. I'm just gonna have it be just padded. There's
rubber all over the place. That's not correct still. I'm gonna have like pillows on the ground
and then you won't need a wrist strap. I will construct a $14,000 room to not have to wear
these. All right okay. How are we doing huh? Rich. He's rich. All right well there we go.
I could die like I have to swim. All right grab the big Willy Wonka lever and pull it.
Gorn. So this is a game where you. You think you are special. Do you even know fight?
Uh make a fist. So I'm trying to do the Julius Caesar thumbs down.
Jump. Fight. Let's see. I just punch him in the face.
Raise your hands. Victory is yours. Oh I get gold coins. All right so that's that's how you do. How
do you move though? Do I have to like pull the world to move still? Dreamer kills someone. I
didn't kill anybody. Here we go. Movement options. That's what I'm talking about. Get over there.
Like an old man with a cane. What's that say? Movement options. I'm not sure. Does this one
come with guacamole? What about this one? I don't want any. I don't want any extra beans in that.
Like I'm an old fucking man like a moze. All right graphics options.
Huh? Do I have to like take the secret cube? Oh for the love of god.
Blur. Nope. Persistent blood armor shatter smooth camera on monitor. What the fuck does that mean?
Uh strict chaperone. Out of here. Strict chaperone. My ass. Movement grab and pull.
Rotation on comfort mode. What does that mean? Gameplay options.
Enter the demo. Difficulty normal. Slow mo on kill. I just keep it default. That's fine. Tier one.
Berserker. General. Okay you do one of them main. That's just the off game. Toggle hold.
Movement hold and gesture is this one. Endless. Is that me? All right let's go to tier one. So hold
is hold. Let's go to that. Let's tier one. Berserker. Let's go. I'm doing something wrong.
Please please. Whoa whoa whoa. Smooth. Smooth. The love of god. Smooth camera. For the love of god.
Oh now I get it. Is this why it looks like this? This kinda hurts my eyes. Movement graphics options.
Smooth camera on monitor. Is it better? Is that better? Movement options.
Is this like frame rate or am I insane? Turn off whole world. Movement. Grip button.
HMD oriented. Controller oriented. Pull. Grip button. It might be the frame rate. I don't
know why it's like this. It is pretty laggy. Controller oriented. Yeah it is like a little
frame rating. So controller oriented. What does that mean? Check the fps. Maybe it's something
to do with like this. Hold on. What if I do this? Is that better? Not really. Don't ask me why.
Try lowering the graphics. I don't think I can. Last time with like graphic and frame rate problems.
Maybe it's just the game maybe in the menu here. Make a middle finger with the controller.
Oh okay I can move like this. I get it. With my thumb. Alright that's cool. Let's just get in
the game and see what happens. I want to see if the graphics are just like fucked up or something.
Because it's like this looks really kind of terrible.
You think you have what it takes to survive? Let's see. Win your first challenge then you
will become a fighter. Alright grab club. Hold your weapon and salute. Yeah this is not this is
not right. Like at all. Look at that. This is not supposed to look like this. Why does this look
like this? This is awful. Try a different game. Yeah this is like that just doesn't look right.
I gotta get out of here. Turn off the motion smoothing. Allocate more rim. Um this is
unfortunate. This is the game. This game is supposed to be really fucking good. So why like
everything over there looks normal. Like up there? No it doesn't. The whole game looks fucked up.
Looking like it's like wiggling around and shit. Nope. Goodbye. No get me out of this.
Let's go look at the ground. Like the whole game is is like jellyfish wiggling around.
That's not correct. Give me a sec. That doesn't make any sense. You think you have what it takes
to survive? Win your first challenge then you will become a fighter. Let me let home. Shield your
eyes. Hold your weapon and salute. This doesn't make any fucking sense. That's how the game is?
Just restart steam VR. Yeah just restart it. That's weird. Did you turn up super sampling? I
didn't do anything. Dev said on steam discussion page the latest update brought frame rate issues.
Really? Well that's kind of unfortunate. Screen smoothing is off. I turned it off.
I turned off screen smoothing. Uh well for the purposes of just getting this going
use an older version. How the hell am I gonna do that? How do I use an older version of the game?
You can't like go where we're gonna how do I get an older version of Gorn? Right click properties
versions. I'm gonna have betas. Manual enable steam overlay is just unchecked. Nah nah this is
fucked up. Hello everyone. We've received a number of reports about performance issues affecting some
people since the update. While we've been able to we have been unable to reproduce these issues of
our own we've investigated as much as we can and did we can and did another update now to address
these problems. If you're having performance issues since this update can you please try the
current version and let us know if the issue has been resolved. This is literally from two days ago.
Uh I don't think it fixed it. Oh it's literally. Well um we're gonna have to go back to this I
think. Unless like let's go betas none. Nah there are no betas here. I think they updated the game
today. Well that's unfortunate. Let's go play hot dogs, horses, and hand grenades. I'll come back
to Gorn. Give me a sec while I open it up. Oh fuck did I lose my uh did I seriously lose my
OVR drop? What the hell? Oh god damn it. That's a pain in the ass. I was ready to go too. Come on.
What a bunch of bullshit. Hold on. You gotta be kidding me. I have to like set this back up again.
This is what we call a pain in the ass guys. I'm gonna put this up for a minute.
Fucking Gorn. How come I can't do this now? Now the controls aren't turned on. That would help.
Hold on. Sorry this is happening. Yep. Oh my god why are you doing this? Why I was ready to play
this motherfucker. And now like I have oh my god I'm so pissed off right now.
I was ready to play. It's done. We were good to go. How am I gonna get this now? Oh that's way too
big. And play 03. I had to save too. Why? Why is this so huge? This is like gigantic. All right
there we go. Okay let's open up hot dogs, heroes, and hand grenades. I don't know what the game is.
Here it comes. There should be an update like two days ago that breaks this game too.
Here see we did like an update and like now like some people just can't play it.
Who fucking knows what the problem is? Hot dogs. Hot dogs, horseshoes, and hand grenades.
That's unfortunate. It looked like a really fun game. I would have loved to have played it.
We'll try it again another time. Hey hey remember me? Mountain Blade VR. See this yeah this is
just looks pretty normal. Hands in the right place probably. All right let's get back in.
Let's go. Early access update 69. Nice. Watch the latest devlog. I have no idea what this game is.
I've been told it's like a simulation sandbox. Guns and knives and pointy things and
all right uh quick tips. Read these first. Sure will. To open the main menu turn let me see I
can see you guys right yeah good so like poop what all right to open the main menu turn one
controller towards you and point at it with the other hand oh oh okay that's good spawn options
arm swing cleanup scene reload scene okay hold the trigger on the pointing hand to select an
option to move to a new place press the menu button the top most button on the vibe so this one here
here and hold when you release you will teleport cool press trigger to pick up objects for simple
objects release trigger to drop them for complex objects press the grip button touch press and hold
grip buttons to hold all objects so you don't grip and hold or you complex i get it to view
controls for various firearms select them in the item spawner found in most scenes that's an item
spawner a control infographic loop here cool movement mode input and control options performance
and quality i just scared the shit out of me i don't know why i just saw it and i was like
i'm something's coming to kill me uh this is fine this is this is good right i think let's just play
simulation let's just let's do it watch the latest devlog let's just go so what i got here i can
grenades uh pointed the tile and pull the trigger to select it then point
at and click the load scene button proving grounds Arizona range sniper range that's the
first one i'm doing fancy yourself a sniper will throw some pillows on the ground grab a rifle with
a bipod go prone and take aim at targets all the way out to 400 millimeters the ultimate test of
stability breathing and patience fuck yeah let's go how do i get hands oh shit okay there are no
hands how do i let it go how do i put down the sniper rifle where does this go okay this is the
scope oh fuck i don't know how to do this shit i don't know how to like work with a real weapon
yes i do all right that's locked in right okay yeah all right uh what's this
okay and somebody hold it for me no i can just put it down how do i put the gun down
like put it down was it was i release hold and let go how do i put the how do i put it on the grip
button i mean the grip button is shoot now oh oh oh oh you mean that okay i get i get it okay come
here grip is not trigger get that down here let's like put this i got twisted in right how do i
what that just grew in size what the fuck screw all right it's on there right okay all right i'm
ready to shoot it no that's all right looking good how do i shoot the gun this is like how do
i turn like this is there a safety how do i turn safety off do you have to actually use this all
right but how do i like no no no how do i how do you shoot a gun oh like this thing okay it's ready
to fire i did it i'm going for the watermelon where's the watermelon what's wrong with it
how do i turn the safety off where's the safety cock it i can't put my hands together
i can't get close enough all right watermelon done got it i fucking got it all the way down at
the end how do i i know nothing about weaponry i don't know how to get this out there's a tutorial
level that explains everything i probably should just do that but i want to shoot this gun so bad
let me just shoot this type rifle one time sarge i have no idea what i'm doing is there a safety
all right i'm gonna go do the fucking tutorial magnification turn that shit down all right we
have to do go i'm gonna do the tutorial level jesus fucking christ all right now how do i i don't know
where that went all right let's go to the tutorial because i have no idea how to play these power
tools horseshoe oh there's a horseshoe all right give me the fuck out of here no how do i get out
of here what's like the escape level how do i get out how do i get the fuck out of here
oh the wrist menu okay right let's go do the actual tutorial all right tutorial is there what
is like the mini arena arena museum west west world sampler sniper range meat grinder
where's the tutorial sampler platter sampler okay it's the sampler platter
there we go look i'm learning i'm getting the hang of this okay here we go to interact with
menus point at the top of the via controller point the top of the via controller the menu yeah
is the beam well this is really cool all right there's like forks this is like spatulas and shit
over there uh teleport is that one yeah to activate teleport when rotate the controller to direct the
beam to your desired teleport location yeah okay then let go pick up an item out of your reach
with an empty hand press the center of the track pad to create a tractor beam that's good i didn't
know that when the beam overlaps an object that may be picked up it will turn blue pull the trigger
to pick an item up well so you hold this down you can press the trigger to pick it up cool to
access the in-game menu rotate your wrist yeah point at the thing you want to look at there it
is okay the sampler platter take a load off use your telematic translocation system to navigate
your grub guns gambling experience all right start of the hors d'oeuvres oh dear so this matches
kick off your sampler platter experience with some lighter fare offering compact interactions
with all the flavor of our main courses grab a grenade or light a stick of dynamite when you're
with us at the sample platter you can always load her up okay again grab what am i looking at here
grab an object by moving the blue interaction sphere so that it intersects with the desired
target then pull the trigger to drop a gun press the grip button to drop anything else
release the trigger okay so here's a grenade so i have a grenade here i just poke pin to throw
a grenade move your controller in an arcing motion like you are throwing a baseball
yeah at the peak of your release the trigger to let go of the grenade make sure to simply
drop your live grenade oh that's unreachable now forever okay oh there did it explode
what the hell is this there's a horseshoe all right you can play horseshoes with buddies after
work pretty nice i'm still holding these here let's like have some fun
oh i can't like the whole thing on fire oh that's unfortunate all right uh frag grenades cyber
grenade interesting yeah what's the cyber is really destroys everything uh bang snaps
what the fuck was that is a grenade that's a grenade that's what was screaming at me
oh that's stupid okay here's a hot dog here's a banana a bunch of bananas let's light it up
fireworks i can hold that down for longer how long can i hold it for longer than that
way longer than that way longer than that now what about that's baseball
oh
where am i going uh there's a machine gun over there
yeah start the hors d'oeuvres all right that's throwing shit that's cool
let's go to the salad bar oh now this is what i'm talking about uh our salad bar is low on
calories but high on excitement satisfy your cravings with one of our many compact salad
offerings or heck try them all pistol selection is hand chosen okay to begin grab an object by
blah blah blah blah blah so how do i moat melon baller speed no matter how do i do this
where's the how do you use the weapon hold on i'm gonna kick my nose real quick like itch it
okay so here's a deagle this goes in here with second controller grab the slide located at the
top pistol pull the second control backwards to the slide boom boom boom snap it forward
to fire the pistol aim the gun at your desired target then pull the trigger rounds will continue
to fire until the trigger is released or into the magazine is empty you got it
to eject the magazine from pistol press down on the bottom quadrant of the trackpad
beautiful so then it just goes in again grab the slide do it again what why did i come over here
that was odd okay um okay so same deal caught it all right let's try one of the other guns
this is fun this is a god fuck you magnum this is my i like this one to fire the revolver aim
the gun at your desired target the pull trigger the cylinder will rotate so i don't have to do
any weird cocking shit i know i'm adding movement to it i know i'm not supposed to be doing that
that's left on the trackpad once cylinders open quickly jerk the revolver backwards
that's pretty fucking cool do it again close the revolver by flicking the control to the right
that's pretty awesome all right let's get one of these guys back there apple dead center
how does he do it how does he continue to perform this is a luger cool this one goes in like that
slide right and then i'm ready i don't like that one uh we got what's this over here
classic 1911 oh what's this one a little snub same deal right this feels like it shouldn't even
exist now let's go with the higher speed i think your speed of a melon oh you bastard you got away
i gotta get at least one i can't fuck this up fucking god i hate this why why
why do i have i didn't i in four and a half hours in two separate other streams i didn't touch this
fucking desk over here all right suit give me this thing yeah i can't pick it up all right
i got a shotgun now how the hell does this work grab a shell with the second controller
just do a slug direct shell into swap look at the bottom of the shotgun all right but you see how i
my hands are too big i have these giant mickey mouse hands that i can't do it like you see look
at jesus christ let go let go let it go let it go come on i can get it something's wrong something's
not happening something's wrong here how did i get down here let go of this what how did i even
end up over there try this again what the fuck is wrong with you all right now let it go is there a
way that i can like calibrate this so i don't have to like mash my hands into each other
i'm not sure there is how many bullets can fit into a shotgun i think i think i got as many as i
can okay so grab for grip with the second controller then move this to get backwards
it will yeah yeah yeah okay um why is this why did that not work before hold the shotgun like this
let me see let me look downfield a little i need to get more shells in here triple head shell
how did i even get down here i don't fucking understand all right here we go
go triple hit damn it all right cool i get it whoops this is a constant let's check the
stomping out insert magnet into the underside of the submachine gun like that yeah click the
left button on the trackpad to change the sub machine guns firing selector okay so i can do
this like semi-auto hold back until a little yeah okay i'm playing like i'm playing like
a fucking accordion right now using the second controller grab the charging handle and pull back
until you will not move any further god damn it i thought it's not a shotgun all right here we go
stabilize the machine
full auto remove magazine release foregrip with secondary control by pressing the grip button
all right cool i gotta use that thing hot bar uh grab an object so this is where it gets really
fucking you know what i mean turn off the melons
waste of food i can't they're so
where are the melons there yeah does he not hear them i thought it was just like okay i thought
i thought it was the shit in this pool i thought it was like the turkeys and the meatballs and the
steaks sloshing around in the fucking soup i didn't think it was watermelons whatever
all right we got this is where i need to pay attention so let's grab this insert magazine
into the underside of the rifle you got it yep yep yep you got it click the left quadrant
to change the rifle fire yeah grab a charging handle and pull back is that it i don't use guns
i don't know anything about them i just know that you point and they go boom boom
and then a big thing comes out of the front and goes really fast into another thing
okay so stabilize yeah aim down top of sub machine gun and pull trigger on the controller
to the rear of the rifle fire okay give it give me that give me that shit iron slice all the way
down to remove magazine release foregrip with the yeah yeah yeah and then grab it pull it out
throw it in the air watch it oh my god that was so funny i need no magazine okay uh yep yep yep
that's the handle right here slap it now i want to do like reflex sight is that on what about uh
the three times scope four grips micro torch okay let's just try this that's pretty cool
that's pretty fucking cool floating sights are a crush well that i let go
like fucking spaghetti hands all right what do we got let's try this one zoom distance how do i
change that is it like a button i press there we go okay so you do it's this so up or okay yeah so
this is zero this is zeroing distance i want to get it off i wonder i want to pull this thing off
up here all right can you tell me how to do that i want to get this off what's the protocol to
remove this how do i remove this it's down on the pad sure down pressing down right down down
all right gripping down hold down the touchpad and rip it off up down shoot it off down on left
pad when touching it nope holding not touching that doesn't do anything while holding it all
right i'm holding this thing right now down on the touchpad it doesn't do anything push it grab it
twist it where's my fucking tutorial all right there's the bolt grab a stripper clip to place
at the top of the firearm get in there all right that's it all right that's fun this is what i'm
talking about this is what i came here for wrong hand all right so grab an object pull the trigger
to drop a gun press any grip under yeah okay so let's grab this grab a box i shouldn't be able
to hold this with one hand god all right put the whole lunch box in here is this going the right
way all right it's in okay i'm ready what's next all right i think i got it i gotta figure it out
the one thing i want to do now is i want to just go back for one second to here now to here reset
this whole thing give me give me this where's the carpet reset all objects don't i get them
pick it up pick it up can i not reset the uh how do i get the gun back well whatever you guys can
help me later i'm ready let's go do it oh hold on reload scene clean up scene reload scene
no we don't even do that shit all right i'm ready to try out one of these weird ones
but first let me like do this because this is what everybody everyone wants me to do like the laugh
out loud thing right meat grinder back to the sniper range no meat grinder this is a survival
horror game brave the meat grinder survival horror experience with procedural generally
challenges and equipment can you find the meat within the maze and grind it before your 30 minutes
runs out what morning meat grinder is an intense experience a wholesale sensory barrage
you should not play if you have epilepsy or sensitive to strobing lights you're prone to
dizziness and have balance issues you are claustrophobic terrified of the dark of a fear
being grounded to meaty chunks burnt alive meat grinder is a difficult timed experience in fact
to die a lot it assumes you know how to play okay you know when you go to a haunted house
and they have the room before the haunted house begins and just barely after where you can fucking
exit because it's too scary for like your 14 year old nephew this is i think i'm about to do it i
like come this way i'm gonna start crying i'll start crying now like come on i should can i go
i don't know it's a little scary and you're like holy fuck man this kid is gonna shit his pants
like he's gonna i'm gonna traumatize this kid for life no no let's go play
skateboard you know that's what's gonna happen right now i'm not doing this we'll come back to
that uh let's do let's go to arizona range that sounds nice and my speed i think hey that's a big
one all right arizona range this is the bus is cool all right let's try this one let's get the
magnum here all right let's just uh oh we got some cans bottles glasses got that one right off the
bat plates that's two points already what we got over here watermelon second from the right bingo
one two three and then you know i just got got on both just to make sure you understand snap that up
i'm out of bolts all right i'm out of bolts with that gun horseshoe oh i play horseshoes
oh so close so close look at this this is oh that's a cool looking shotgun
so this is a double barrel how do i get this open it's gotta be like a little
a little uh doohickey i can pull right under here no no no stop stop stop stop stop i'm sorry i'm
sorry i'm sorry i don't know how to load this one isn't it like right here don't you like pop
it open like okay there we go this shouldn't i be able to be like bang there it is okay yeah
that felt pretty good so then how do i close that up this well i was hitting left before
do i even need to do that oh no i don't okay i never shot one of these before
i need more bullets there's my like bullet menu select caliber 12 gauge
uh dragon breath can i pick this thing up this is like really far away here we go
all right let's go to uh buckshot
yeah let's try that a lot of bullets that's cool nice that was fun all right now let's do
um what over here shotgun tube fed magazine fed shotgun i thought it just said beyonce
uh bazooka gimme it and a rocket oh boy uh it doesn't go this way it goes this way right
how do you load this now you're gonna load it this way okay now that that's loaded uh do you
have to do anything else is shooting a rocket launcher this easy you just have to put a rocket
in the back and then press the button it can't be right i don't know why it did that
okay it is that easy give me another one oh so this really is just like a gun simulator huh
okay put this down get it in the right spot like this okay hold it no who you fire in the hole
so that killed me me not shooting myself in the in the fucking chest
watch the back blast oh what's this thing stinger rpg is a grenade launcher
does it just come loaded no no no no no i need grenade launcher rounds where's the rounds uh box
i blew it away didn't i that's unfortunate oh well well don't you look at that only one
only one stop okay can i pick it up i think i got one shot uh let's try to get that thing
i just played russian roulette with the fucking desert that's great
what else what about that then this is a giant ham gun this is just a comedy weapon right how
am i supposed to do this hey look jerma you're using a regular size pistol right right right
right can i know like i gotta like pull this back right this is right see if i can get this
got it all right i think i'm ready i'm ready for the uh for one of the missions
that slide just killed me it probably would have all right how about um make runner let's go
i'm ready i'm not gonna be scared classic me 30 minutes uh original enemy count all you
can eat buffet no timer build your own meat no timer more enemies kids meet no timer more enemies
item spawner and invincible should i do the kids menu nice nasty event ai primary light source
flashlight lighter glow stick we're gonna do flashlight dessert narrator talk classic all
right let's just do it let's go eat me so the actual zombies in this game i'm a little concerned
right now that's a meat grinder this thing on meat next game jaws don't step in that flubber shit
hello meat remain calm try not to start funny hopping around like an idiot just yet
still coming down from that uh well anyway i poisoned you in the future if you have a future
you might consider not eating unattended fast food that has been left in public
hmm oh fuck i don't know that you're here though we have a number of things to accomplish
before that dose of poison becomes fatal which should be hammer fest 29 minutes from now and yes
those 29 minutes will be rough can't be helped though we've got health to do oh shit please drag
yourself over to that table in front of you and we'll begin i'm here all right let's see here i
made myself notes for this part don't use any weapons like a swamp introduce the machine
tell the meat subject that they must venture into the meat grinder to find three meat objects
and bring each of them here to feed into the aforementioned machine inform meat something
that they have been graciously given some starting tools that this is a very sensitive
and complicated testing environment uh yes and there are more tools and other objects to be
found in this wonderful device add this one last time and then i'm supposed to uh reiterate
the amount of time the meat subject has left which is less than 29 minutes i'm afraid so
and take a lighter too just in case i need it right all right i'm decked up
i'm ready where's my flashlight what happened to the flashlight all right let's get going
meet you know the drill love that drill the penetrative capabilities oh i have to sit there
how do i load this can i put two no i'll store that okay ready it's ready okay go go go give me the
what's my flashlight keep fucking going what's my flashlight where the fuck did it go
how did i already lose it again i'm ready fucking funhouse game tools there might be tools in here
yep come on i don't get all day come on open bomb watch out shoot that bomb
do i only have these one magazines i feel like i should have more weapons oh boy hello
anything in here nothing nothing in here either i don't buy that shit for a second
what is it is this like a i just thought that was like a creeper i just killed a minecraft creeper
he was made out of fucking clay all right there's a gun there
okay okay careful be delicate with that it deserves it fuck i don't know
put this like up here they're gonna is that good does it work how do i put a bullet in here
that was that's just storage i don't know how to load this fucking thing behind you
is there a bullet in here check it out i don't know how to load this gun there's so many bolts
over there too hello there's a gun all over my machine this thing has a gun i thought it was a
monster this is i don't know i'm not very good at this number seven for today hey lucky number
seven that's you i didn't know how to load all the guns i don't even know i don't know how to load
like pistols that's it axe is like a scope already the penetrative capabilities
oh i have to sit there okay i'm speed running this let's go i can't i can't take the axe sorry
it's not gonna happen good shotgun i got i don't know what that is good work captain clever you
found something hashtag level design idiot what's this for idiot i don't know if this thing is
who knows what a piece of plastic is before for the back iron sights don't roll off for the other
gun okay all right i'm ready um let's go boiler i hardly knew her but seriously i knew all of them
i'm not sure exactly what i'm looking for but maybe i'll find it clear where is he jump what's
that am i in the bathroom i'm in like a mcdonald's bathroom lever did i do it i won
i like last like i like my butt saws yes you found jill i did it oh wait was it jill
jillian jillian millie it was millie yes hello there millie
what where am i um why is i why am i like what the fuck was that that just came from the ceiling i
don't know why is that oh god it's dark look at my shotgun
i don't know where the fuck i am
they weren't kidding when they said advanced users
how am i why can't i grab my shot where's the shot it's in my hand
oh my fucking god needs to be what does it need to happen to it is it cocked
are there any bolts in this
you know i don't think i've ever told anyone that's really cool you can do that though
let's do another one uh westworld let's try westworld just stick to sandbox yeah
i didn't rage quit i'm still here i just don't know like how all the guns interact
it's taking a while we made it look it's garfield
okay uh don't forget your e slab just insert a mono function micromecha disc into your
e slab player and it'll start playing immediately your e slab player a good whack to eject the
micro disc okay so we could here's this looks like a disc what is this stapler
all right yeah if you've lost your e slab push this button to retrieve it so i need a disc
of inventory they're gonna find discs what's this okay let's go find a disc
then let's get the best of you up and you take just a nasty spill we've got covered so if you
die you end up here okay the cartridge shells magazines can be spawn locked and letting you
duplicate them okay long guns can be harnessed which returns the gun to you quick slog when you
drop it you can also put 10 cartridges in the same kind of a slot i need to like see what the
hell are you talking about let's see the move yeah toggle safety there it is up all right let
me see here let's get in front of this please refrain the bergman simplex grab magazine this
looks like it's infinite move magazine into the magazine well and there yeah bingo charging
handle yep bomber arm is now alive pistol safety is not enabled by default but may be turned on
so uh let's take a few of these
all right we're gonna this is the park map so i can shoot this guy right is that gonna be a
problem all right employees only the grillzilla silver bullet so where am i okay howdy partner
spawn lock it spawn lock it he's talking to you it's a lot of info let me go back and like read this
fucking live journal post yeah this is my quick slot right so these are my quick slots
can be spawn locked by letting you duplicate it just hover over your hand over a loaded quick
slot and click the touchpad joystick so you're saying like this okay so that's now spawn locked
the touchpad is this level turned green so get this thing out of here
so that all right so that's that's good i got it we're good wait that was a disc that was not a disc
was it no this is like bullets this is not a disc they're all wrong yeah that's what i figured
all right let's go let's go shoot let's go root and toot this is cool like a different uh i don't
need this right let me see what happens if i do this okay so again get this shit out of here
i want just the regular default shotgun i get that somewhere we're gonna have only one slot
i only have one slot huh so now i got sick i'm just gonna bring this shit with me
is that spawn lock now let's go shoot something like just this guy okay well sorry i had to
demonstrate here you're just sitting here so now the question is how do i open this
i did was telling me how before probably should have looked at that tutorial that was there
left right
up so this slot right here let's learn we've got to learn oh yeah dominant hand
and grab the fore grip c no that's not c enable lever rotation wait is it the wrong gun
where's c a b where's where's c wrong gun but where's c see that c is right there but it's not on
the it's not listed here anywhere it's just not labeled enable lever rotation move ahead
okay in a circle pull the fire gun right with non-dominant hand on fore grip pull and hold to
enable lever rotation okay so when that pops out then i do i just have it
i literally just did it oh my god how did i just did it how the fuck did i do that
i have to grab the gun with two hands okay so then now i put in a bullet
jesus fucking god how many is only two can go in there right can i do more than that no that's it
okay see any fucking on there all right i'm ready let's go all right so what's over here
puzzle solving okay it's the new gear you wish to find solve puzzles and shoot their signs
it's yourself a clever one got some puzzles over here solve the puzzles and shoot their signs
what else can i do looking for some action i don't want a dinner alive
make sure to bring your hats back here for shut up what was it uh for course that deposit the
bandit hats here so we gotta get bands they get them is that guy bandit he may have not been a
bandit so it's just a bunch of mini games okay there are 14 there are 14 horseshoes
you find all the horseshoes and toss them into their matching poles so this is horseshoe which
one is this one so kindly upon cheaters if you try to walk off over here how is it gonna take a
million years here don't touch that i'm throwing way too high all right that was a fun game let's
do another one open this chest this is a desk this is just a baby carnival are we good cocks
oh that's my sheriff i gotta put that on here okay so let's go get a bandit that's not a bandit
i got a bullet in here right i should a big churner what's over there it's that button
combination thing let me in it's like a bandit hideout boot leather silver bullet a big churner
you can bring all kinds of shit here apparently okay hats i go up here let's go i gotta find like
a i gotta find some bandit or something all right here's a horseshoe thing where is it up here up
there i want to get that first try come on bingo what i'll just get it yes thank you all right so
where uh this is i've been i've disturbed this probably some bandits around here
am i just gonna do the horseshoe child bandits shit i don't know how to do anything else
oh shit get up i can't take this out again how do i is it it's grip right which button is it
down on the d-pad that's what i thought i pressed that one already quickly
wait
the head i need that other weapon shit okay god damn it all right let's go we're good we're good
all right i got there's a slab over here you know what get back up back up back up back up
that guy was coming after me you all know i don't need to pretend oh i need that guy's hat i need
that guy's hat where's his hat oh first try got it oh you stupid room scale oh my god i'm gonna
break something i'm gonna break something oh it's like bowling focus on where it's going there you
go come on get it so i can move on too little too far shit that's it ah that was too high
that's it that's it oh yeah idiot where's the shotgun go all right i got so i got lots of this
cool all right this one what's this one oh it's the puzzle game you gotta bring all the puzzle pieces
back i don't want to do that what's this oh i can do this one now i need the middle all right where's
the middle turbo this is please this is a gun game i'm just i'm just trying to see the sights
relax i'm playing i'm playing horseshoes shoot put it in shoot shoot shoot shoot it shoot
doesn't do anything one guy said that look this game's really really fucking cool it's really
interesting this level it's very detailed lots of different cool weapons look it up there up
there let's get up there what the fuck i can actually do that i gotta jump from roof to roof
come on get it balcony it's probably so fast i'm playing like a gun game and i'm just
just throwing more shoes around come on get up there right there this is the secret nobody's
funny i just had it got it fuck guns that's it all right i'll go do like one of the other
sandbox ones and then we'll get out of here no i'm like having fun okay this is like just to use
this is like a fun lazy game you just do whatever you want stop having fun you're not allowed to
have fun yes i am oh you want fun fine i'll give you fun i missed oh all right just hold on
i just gotta get this and then we will move on i gotta i have to get it that's it that's it that's
it fuck where am i i'm i know my desk is like literally right here hold on i gotta be careful
get it oh hey everybody having fun damn it now everyone would have fucking screamed all right
okay all right okay okay all right all right all right all right all right fine fine we'll do
let me just do like one more of the sandbox ones this is fun
friendly range snow globe indoor range proving grounds the meat miss coliseum return of the
rot wieners arcade proto all right which one proving grounds take and hold we're gonna do
two more okay we'll do we'll do proving grounds because it's a huge one right here
let me get a sip of my iced coffee hold on can you get direct where's my iced coffee you
don't know what the fuck that is you guys didn't think there were swords in this game really
everyone wants to meet it next no this is okay look this is this game it's a simulation we just
play around not every vr game has to be like a crazy scream game you know what i mean it's all
right not every single vr experience has to be like oh or what the fuck whoa just like edit those in
you know what i mean just like just take crop the webcam and you can put me wherever the fuck
you want i'll give you some more watch out right there he's right there oh got him no i missed
oh yikes oh it's fucking crazy oh wait i'm using my hold on i'm using my that doesn't make any
sense because i have an iced coffee in my hand all right i gotta put this down i'll take the guy
from boston no man i don't fucking care you got any two hands no i i don't give a shit i don't
fucking i gotta have my dunks in my fucking other hand i can do it with one hand you know i'm a
fucking i'm a fucking super stock head all right let's uh let's grab one of these this is cool so
i just like cut how come these don't cut oh here's like the blocks of wood that i can cut right
i cut through them the american ninja warrior no not what's the name of that show
where they like make swords and the guy like freaks out and slashes stuff
and you got a good cut to it i can't even do that in here oh what yeah i'm sorry
this is fun mom's linoleum no get off get off get off you're stuck on me you're sticky
that's the technique that my fucking grandfather passed down to me and my kids and my i don't even
know what i was gonna say give me that that's fine with me what are the other guns what about
over here crowbar knives i throw these nice oh i can throw these over here yeah chainsaw blade
nice good throw hey one of these things pickaxe good hit make sure you can see that just uh
i want to make sure you can get a good view of that shovel rake wait hold on can i no i
can't do like the sideshow bob thing all right uh what's what else we got let's get a weapon here
pistol rifle bolt action anti-material oh what's that thing p90 yeah you're kidding me the p90 is
such a weird gun because it looks like a cartoon gun this looks like it belongs in halo but it's a
real gun got it okay looks good is it ready just need to here we go all right it's time to go
what do you say check it out nice
rainbow six siege what's this a gas tank trying to unscrew it and like it's gonna blow up no it's
not i'm fine what do we got what do we got let's clear all sausages might spawn a few more
this is bad for my computer i'm not doing that anymore now let's blow them all up about uh
support uh we got stinger rpg let's go to stinger that's cool battery stinger battery
so now let's let's play a game called how the fuck do you load this well that was easy
we have to turn this or move this how does this work what is this for up here
why is there a grocery store basket up here anyone know what that is that's the guidance system how
is this the kind of guidance system now we developed an anti-tank guidance system
it's the same thing you put fucking apples in for some reason it works
oh how do you fire it pull a button pull a lever does this work load a missile i didn't just do
that that is a missile isn't it no that is i was i was making the battery joke and it is a battery
that's an actual battery i didn't know that don't say these things take batteries i thought that
was an elaborate stupid fucking reference no keep the battery in there there's something
already in there it's like a magic eight ball in there will i be a millionaire definitely no
we'll see motherfucker uh where's my other rocket for this how come this the rocket's not there
only the batteries see storm grenade four three two two rocket you're getting ammo elsewhere
the ammo menu what the heck put this down miscellaneous horseshoe target utility firework
wow really wow okay i don't care about that how do i look in the lighter down on the d-pad grip
flip it up how do i flip this good matches don't do this don't do this with your friends okay
it's bad what the broken candles don't do this
where's the pocket um is this menu here slide dash tp that's 17 18 hours in this game
what have i been streaming for holy shit imagine what the fuck does that mean i've been trapped in
vr so i can't use this in here fine tank bangs oh what no way no way uh this is the best game
i've ever played i think can you actually that's the i killed that guy i knocked that guy unconscious
by throwing one of these little bangs at him jump of all do the thing we done all well this is not
realistic no what the hell nobody does it like this everybody in their right mind took the whole
package bunched them up into a ball as tight as they could and whipped them into the ground as
hard as they could nobody did singles no you like tied them all together at the tops and then whipped
them into a fucking brick wall into the ground what a waste what do you mean what a waste
you would you would just like take the stuffed up giant spitball wad and throw it into the ground
or you would like stomp on them that's really cool it's in the game though but wait a minute
i got fucking crazy brilliant idea probably never seen a streamer do this before i'll tell you uh i
need these sparklers too how do i use the lighter can somebody please help me down doesn't do anything
up doesn't do anything left now don't tell me why that didn't work before down what okay here we go
please don't pop all right let's let's let's break something what do you say
oh perfect oh yeah no stay here stop it no my collection did i not have done that
it's okay i have everything under the fireworks factory is gonna be just fine
what the fuck else am i doing here uh i'm gonna fucking read the board
can i kind of open the little fireworks all right let's just go on fucking slashing spree
nice i got i got i got i got i got i got three in one swing i got
out of my way all right i got i got okay
oh right at the bottom just get the just get one little sliver off just one sliver i didn't get it
all right let's do the yellow one what was the other one called oh hey look at that you guys
are over there all right let's do something here i'm gonna pick this up and what i'm gonna do this
is for the video right this is for like the funny look at like how funny this stream is video
so imagine like what's gonna happen is i'm gonna pull this and i'm gonna be talking and i'm gonna
drop it accidentally and then right before it explodes i'm gonna turn my wrist and go guys what
and i want to see like a ton of luels you know what i mean like that's like wicked funny you know
the audience will be like holy shit dude it's wicked funny all right you ready let's imagine
this is the beginning of the game yeah uh so hand grenades hot dogs and hell or whatever it's called
this looks kind of fun so we got a grenade oh i better be careful i've got to be careful here
guys what does that say on there let me try to read that and two one nine grease weasel fragmented
oh what fucking perfect guys singing done that's gonna be so funny people gonna think i'm
people gonna think i'm wicked funny what was the other one you guys want me to do where was it
return what was the one you guys actually wanted oh oh that's so funny the meat grinder i can't do
it take and hold take and hold uh point at the tile and pull the trigger to select it then point
i know how to do that get loot take capture points defend them get more loot go as long as you can
all right that's interesting i'm gonna do something really not funny we have to do that like three or
four more times i'm not off that by the way all right let's see item spawner difficulty standard
buck bullets okay on pick up your starting equipment yeah i hope you guys are ready get
loot that's a good one that's actually a pretty good one so again what's gonna happen is i'm
gonna be standing here i'm gonna look that way i'm gonna read the instructions i'm gonna say
uh take an old setup you're starting where does it say loot where does it say loot
difficulty item doesn't say loot there it is loot progression okay so you guys know what to do
so i'm gonna i'm gonna introduce the scene i say oh playing take and hold this is a
game mode looks like we got some stuff over here uh take and hold uh loot or loot progression i'm
gonna turn it's a ton of alleyways like the whole fucking chat has to be exploding with it
you're right get ready okay spawn pan no i think i'm good pick up your starting equipment this is
take and hold follow indicator and spawn points okay i think i get it loot progression or should
i actually probably say lewd progression that's fucking hilarious right i hate this but we're
doing it like two more times all right so uh how do i actually do this follow indicator to supply
and spawn points so supply point take and hold capture the take and hold point from the bots
defend from the bots get more loot from supply points and then keep going as long as you can
chat somebody said why are you listening i don't know because why are you listening
you should be going against what he said all right what's in the case can i open this cool
it looks like we got a little oozy bingo okay anything else in here that i need to take
i don't think so all right i'm gonna concentrate now spawn lock spawn lock it okay what about
the hot dog okay guys listen
you're noticing you like when you look down you notice that like when you like really looking
straight down that's up to your mouth i've already done that before i've already made that reference
before i can't do that twice have you taken hold let's go what am i holding what am i taking
the magazine what spawn lock the magazine like yep i'm supposed to have like an indicator of where
the sucks get in oh my god there's so many bullets get in there's a wall here somewhere
back up back up out of the wall i'm like bingo thank you very much all right oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah so where's the supply area where's my indicator i'm supposed to get like an indicator
for where the supply area is your left hand has a compass oh right i thought that was gonna be
bigger over here okay so let's go this way come on you son of a bitch come on you son of a bitch
do i have time do i have time good what's this what's here what is this what's here
what is here there's a wall there okay i gotta be aware of that
wall wall wall where they go the supply room is in here
somebody in the supply room what the fuck is this guy it's taking hold right there i got it
what i got a hot dog bomb right oh this is help oh what's this oh nice it's like a stock
okay i gotta hold on that what i might need it oh it's two is this a different one this is
different this game is really cool this is great oops that's okay so this is a different magazine
this is the same one okay this is these are different magazines spawn lock this shit
how does this thing work right you brace it up against your body right here okay should i throw
this other one away like should i throw this one away no okay i've got the ammo this can i like
should i like hold on to this shit like that right there bang bang bang bang bang
what doesn't okay that's fine let's go ah i'm gonna shoot this ladder up there all right let me
reload these what's up there we're a good place to uh defend from i would say come on there we go
nice who's left where you at i did it get destroyed rotate the stock well this one
like that what are we gonna do with this get this shit out of here all right let's go uh there's a
supply room over here somewhere down here supply room straight through there and here down maybe
this looks pretty supply room to me one guy no i'm good what do i got the hell 72
how much does this heal i feel like i should be eating these all right we got oh it's a handgun
um i have too many i have too many items the health of full heal uh it's a magic i'm gonna
put that here uh this is pretty good yeah i'm gonna use this shit i don't want the machine
guns now all right let's go through here there should be a taking hold again over there and
straight looks like it yep right here damn okay so who's that way wait i hear somebody
who's talking okay what's that is up there it's like in the next room over here looks like it
it's not what up there there it is okay here we go 7200 didn't even get it holy fuck one there
holy shit i didn't see that guy over there oops vibe aim nice aim what it's hard to do
sometimes you do kind of good i was doing so well that was really cool
i was doing a really good job i did so well too i was like oh like eight out of ten headshots
i'm gonna drop the gun story of my fucking life story of my goddamn life look at how perfect i'm
doing this is so impressive oh i idiot god damn all right uh let's take a look so there's a supply
drop over here somewhere am i doing on health i got plenty through sheet straight this way
straight out this way
it's a tech peak it's pretty good it's a decent tech beaker i would say it's called wait till
guy gets close enough to you and then shoot yourself in the head oops this car i'm stepping on
cords nice i'm sure someone's around here all right what am i replacing consume your hot dog
no i need to get it all right i need to i gotta i gotta get rid of the uh the little one here
this one here yeah is awfully lonely out here did you this is cool look at this thing wow
let's just wait no no no no take that out i don't have hands i take this off
sure and then this flips up and then that pulls back i think we're done that's snapped in place
right and then i should be able to hold this like this and just okay did you hear that we're going
this way to the right i think that i think it's literally right here here we go straight ahead
this way right here 4500 i'm gonna stay in the corner over here
i'm taking this damn fucking serious nothing in there whoo last one in the chamber yeah
seriously that's what saved me that last one all right it's time to take a hot dog i think
no not yet don't do that i have to eat this no i don't move it over here then this can sit in here
all right i'm good that's wrong it'll blow up my shit though but this is not loaded i just look
like a total asshole all right i got my side arms i got my main hand i got my three hot dogs i got
a little bit more help eat the hot dog eat the eat eat eat okay what how do i eat the fucking hot
dog did that just give me no how much health did that give me what do you mean wrong one
what did i just eat i think i powered up one oh my fuck i don't even know what did i just do
i ate the blue one i don't know what kind of flavors they have how am i supposed to know
about their the different kinds of hot dog flavors all right supply drop is this way
at least i think it's down here hey excuse me
cox you having problems like a little i took too many hits there i didn't want to take those hits
all right now now i can see why people really really like this game this is fucking awesome
there's so many different weapons and somebody they all work the way that they work in in reality
but it's not reality it's a virtual depiction of reality go figure am i even facing you guys
that should be all right so we're going down here i feel like i've been in this one for a long time
though how long has stream been up for now i've been i've been playing this one for a long time
i'm still having fun though we'll get it i mean i have to remember i had two days of rest right
so that doesn't mean that this is not going to be like a three to four hour stream i had
two days of goddamn rest my eyes are locked in i feel locked in i can go for longer don't worry
so this is not that is this the supply drop that it's trying to tell me to go to
that's kind of unfair or am i wrong no it's not i guess that i was aiming for who else is there
come on who the fuck else is here huh straight down there we go nice okay this is okay that's
a green hot dog what does the green hot dog do there was blue there's red and there's green
what's the green one do read it infinite and well i guess i guess it does just kind of say it
doesn't it doesn't just kind of say it what's it ah that is a beauty this is the decisions
to make here but we've been through so much together i'm gonna miss you look at how cute
your tail is which one is the middle of those which one was it is it that one yeah how did i
do it the last time what the fuck okay i'm like i gotta i gotta be okay there we go how does this
work pretty i did a lot of damage okay you know this is cool though put this little thing up
all right this goes here which now let's make sure we load everything
load it let's go where to behind us let me i gotta orient myself i need it i need an ice
coffee guide me i think i see it i see i see yep got it i almost just fell over hold on let me just
hello hello what happened hello no i gotta come up i gotta get out of here hold on hold on
shoot your eyes i gotta come up my hair was getting pushed into my eyes how does it look
even worse i even got a haircut too you can't tell how why didn't you tell me that you could
notice my hair we're back in just give me a second didn't even notice my new haircut what about your
assholes how are we good on like audio and shit like that like if you can you see what i'm doing
how are we this is the first time i've come out in like three hours i'm gonna just give 20
community sub great canadian fuck club just gave 20 community subs holy shit thank you
that's a lot of subs damn well thank you so much for that all right maybe like one more sip of my
fucking dunkin donuts it's the first time i've had dunkin donuts in four and a half months
it's pretty bad all right i'm ready to get back in here that feels better
just move my hair out of the way a little let's get the tuck behind the ears all right so i
ended up with this shit there you are why do i not use both earbuds because there's something wrong
with me and for some reason when i put in two earbuds even if it's back even if it's the back
ones the ones that open back it feels like the world is going to crush me and i can't talk i
can't think i can't i can't do anything i can barely see both ears blocked i become useless
okay you know uh it's you know superman oh superman has the kryptonite and if you ever
show up with kryptonite and you're like holding out like this he'll be like ah and he like won't be
able to do anything and his laser eyes don't work if you ever like are in a fight with me just like
cover my ears and i'll be like i mean i'll roll over like a fucking like a dog on his back and
put his paws in the air stop talking about cryptocurrency that's what he's talking about
what did i bring up cryptocurrency are there huge subs again how many subs came in 10 more came in
from who from mostly loss well thank you so much mostly lost thanks to the 10 thanks great
canadian fk club for the fucking 20 you guys rock all right we had a little break
it didn't actually have a real break but you know i'll take one of those later
i got my grenade launcher i've got my super gun my fast shooting gun and my side arm gun
let's go ahead and take out some bad guys what do you say so the enemies just get progressively
harder i'm assuming right over here they need to get right through there right you know
they're in this corner yeah all right let's make it i'm stepping all over something we good
i think we're good hold on load up the weapons right we're taking this thing for a ride
i'm gonna get up top there but if they were going to drop hell down on everybody it's activated
duty noob tube camping i did it modern work for you too yeah this is all i need at the end of the
match i just need a bunch of people on voice chat to call me horrible fucking names we just need
like people screaming fucking swears at me now fucking noob tube get out of my game get out of
my game and then you hear this is what you hear i mean i can't really simulate it that well but
you know the kid gets his headset on and it's like i just spit all of my you know you know
you understand he said fucking put the headset on and get in his mouth all right we're going this
way right this way i think it's this way could be wrong how you guys doing on the puke meter
by the way germist oh that's right my jokes need to land you're right he's checking to see how well
his jokes land where are you guys he's right they're right you're right you're right i need
to make sure i don't know i have no real-time definition of what happened if i make like a
quality modern warfare 2 reference bang did it land how does it vibe compared to the psvr they're
not even in the same category the psvr is is not even you shouldn't even mention it in the same
sentence all right uh supply drop do i still have is this loaded let's make sure the rest
of this stuff is i want to go do that that sniper one again holy fucking hell that's what we call
a bad shot
ah where am i where am i where am i i can't move i don't know where i am
somebody got back it over there was my desk right okay i'm backing up wait load load load
i did it too fast no let's need to go over here no stop it this dilly dilly that's better here
because it's in my right hand
is this up this is loaded i forget let's just do it again just in case no it's loaded okay it's
loaded all right i'm ready let's go gotten gravy and potatoes whatever the name of this game is
in case bingo the stock where's the stock remember what do i get rid of
drop the pistol i can't i'm so good with the pistol i'm so good test it up use the sights
use the back holster what the heck are you talking about how do i do how do i back holster
shoulder oh you guys are just fucking messing with me i'm getting rid of this it was fun
i want the shotgun i mean most definitely i want the shotgun sorry guys no no that's a no
it's real what do you mean it's real i how do i access it how do i use the shotgun
no this is not real let me test it how do i shoot it oops i like it shotgun's pretty good
i know it's a fucking rifle i think a shotgun comes out of here it's like a dentist drill god
what do you think i am some kind of dumb guy you think i'm a dumb guy all right i don't i don't
like that thing it's terrible that it's not good gg idiot it doesn't mean i'm gonna not bring it
with me and just fucking use it once like jack wick i could use it one time like i'm gonna use it just
but then i'm gonna throw it away who gives a fuck thing's stupid this rifle is from like world war
one i've got a uzi where am i all right we're gonna go the other way up top there
i'm gonna try using the sights no i'm not why the hell would i do that
do they spawn lock the mags yeah they could all right so it's down here there it is
okay there it is anybody on the get out of the way fucking jesus that's not
it's a fucking head i'm in so much trouble here how am i gonna be able to do this
okay they come from all angles right in the corner here oh this is the end
what do you have time here i need some more help
no more sausages left i gotta make the i need i gotta go to the supply rooms i think
i'm not prepared for anything else right now want to do a hundred health that's bad that's bad
i'm right here oh you fucker hold on hello where am i fucking hell who is it who's near me
what am i near oh there's a wall i'm stuck those guys take a few hits to the head
straight ahead i have 130 health there's no hot dogs in here what this thing is i don't know i
don't know i don't know what to do i have 130 health is they good i need another supply room
i'm dead here there's one it's this one right yeah it's the don't i don't want this
i'm so dead damn it well that was fun the safety was on yeah yeah that was cool all right let's go
let me do one more thing here end of the stream what are you talking about i want to do one more
i'm like just getting the hang of this sniper range i want to do the sniper
remember this now we're coming back to it don't know what the hell we're doing
bingo stick it in there put this shit up we got loaded up we got scope get that on here
lock it in silencer okay good to go safety's off plant this thing on the ground which there
we go stick it right here let it go take a look all the way down what's all the way down
magnification drop that a little bit so i can see what the hell i'm doing
why does it don't work it's on backwards all right uh now we're back to where i don't i can't take
the thing off the lens is covered no it's not iron sights iron sight sniper does that work no this
thing's on backwards oh that's that's correct what are you guys talking about a bolt should be like
that all right so let me lie down here i don't know what i'm running into what the fuck you gotta
say about that all right i need to put a new one of these in here how do i get more ammo for that
i think i gotta go all the way down magnification um how many bolts left in here one i think what
bullets oh look at these oh look at these come on easy i think bullets how do i just spawn bullets
isn't it like the red ipad oh what get out of here oh that's that's that one right
already got one of those okay let's go crank oh hot okay all the way down let's get a better
magnification here let's see i need more magnification see all the way down the last
fucking traffic light stay right there magnification times 32 here we go ah it
hurts too much get this off ow something bit my hand no just me
i don't like that one oh i like the hearts all right let's go to the m200 thank you god
fucking damn it okay looking good so now i'll just crank this that's all cranked up
what is this okay i need a scope does it work that's nice nice okay i need a scope
uh let's try this again fuck what the fuck sniper is a dumb how do i put uh accessories on this
magnifier scope okay here we go what does this button do okay well what do you get up
he just needs a weapon he's comfortable with i got it no i gotta like got it oh you got it again
i can't i can't stop i can't stop i'm gonna get sick there we go ready got one it's okay
i'm gonna fucking yeah i'm god is it like a cool pistol port grenade lever action let's do one of
these 1873 18 this one right here lever action rifle but it's gonna go one shot iron sights
why is it one bullet what the hell camera here we go what the fuck all right one more one more one
more one more one more and then i'm gonna take a fist break rage quit i can't do that one
indoor rains that's kind of cool the breach this one's breaching proto i will do breaching
currency structured challenge space and experiment for a breach and clear a challenge in hintings of
parking okay i'll give it a try tangle it up here all right oh this is big so what that's bad this
is actually bad i gotta like untangle this shit uh all right so we got i can choose my weapon let's
go the shotgun uh we're gonna go with a magazine fed shotgun this one look at this super a super
one this is a huge magazine okay that is that's fucking cool i get this out how do i take this out
down left right up
up
walk forward paddle release oh this is a little tab the first time i've ever seen a little tab
let's go uh target score spawn hot dogs uh begin on the ground i'm like a SWAT team member
i didn't get it i get it all right i got that guy in the head what did i do all right uh give
me the handgun i'm good with the handguns not much else we're gonna go just with an automatic
pistol we're gonna go with just a deagle or 40 deagle 44 magnum double i didn't fucking even
know they could come over here get a pound that meat blue plate special this is the gun i want
to use can i let me just set up please can i just set the hell up please let's go why can i not
shoot this one hi guys hey yeah now we're doing a little fun thing here aren't we
step go ahead stay right there what's that all right so the safety
can i just reset this he's still alive got him okay let's go ahead and do this again this fires
right just making sure don't oh i'm getting a little upset now this also fires good to know
very great let's begin play time oh don't i just ripped it did i record out over there i ripped
the cord out maybe not very fun all right this one's really fun i could see why people would spend
a shitload of time in here but i'm gonna go pee we're gonna come back we're gonna do another
game i must just go over because i turned around too fast and i'm tangled up so i'll be right back
i can sink hours into this game just throwing shit at people shooting stuff
so i can understand the appeal i'll see you in like two or three minutes i'm gonna go pee grab
a water and we'll move on to something else be right back so i've got some water so the choices
let me see i have jet island uh waltz of the wizard jet island yeah jet island looked crazy
i also have uh duck season gore i wish gore worked that's so unfortunate yeah we'll do jet island
yeah jet island is change the game name here uh that was really fun though just kind of a
gun sandbox more blade and sorcery i could i want to try to experience as much as i can though
so we'll do jet island uh duck season is a whole experience isn't it jet island here we go it's
got like 12 unique endings really duck season's like a neat little couple hour long package looks
like super hot that's cool all right i'm getting back in i'm gonna do jet island and by the way so
after today i think we're gonna put the vibe away for a little while because this would be the third
vibe stream in a row feels bad put away just become a vibe only stream i can't do that though
i like physically wouldn't be able to do that that means i have to like exercise every day
that's a that's a big commitment to exercise every single day all right here we go let's get back in
you just stand there uh you've got to move around you got to swing your arms around
you're like jumping around you're screaming it's more than just standing okay so this looks a
little strange hold on you're at the wrong place this game isn't this game has intense movement i'm
already getting warned hold on all right hello it's back where it belongs so i'm gonna weird
i gotta like back up here uh new features thin purple orbs caution this game has intense movement
you may fall over in real life please clear your play area that's quite the warning
uh let me put on my this is gonna be a huge problem i'm gonna have to take the headset off
and like spin it around a million times we'll see if that's a problem i can still see you guys
right yeah the vr warning should just be the wii safety guide yeah they were a little bit
before their time weren't they with their warnings your straps cure i'm gonna fall down in real life
that's uh reassuring okay so don't fall down in real life here we go uh start new profile
uh germa that's me you get to be like a power ranger jet island i gotta i gotta deal with this
tangle you fucker there we go all right cool uh effects volume how we doing on volume we good
you can't see us yeah okay i can see it's good all right uh turn type snap 45 warning smooth
turning can cause motion sickness select modify sync player online switch profile avatar
so let's get a good one i want to be all right i like that face that face looks pretty good
i don't know what's that doing no i'm blue either blue or germa 95 officially licensed color
this is my board i like that i like the enterprise oh i like this one this is the
pattern on the board like the smooth finish okay single player new game you get a hammer oh no
that's just me all right don't fall down right that's the name of the game hold grip to toggle
hoverboard touchpad use jets my honor am i standing on it am i starting the hoverboard
is frictionless i don't like this steer with the jets on your hands swipe left and right to turn
oh boy i need to sit down i think i have to sit down for this slow down slow down slow down slow
down stop stop stop stop moving stop moving how do i stop moving so how do i how do i steer
effectively use like my hands how do i jet up jet up i'm squished i'm squished i can't go over there
i'm gonna have juice no stop stop go that way i went too fast stop
somebody just said this is like that marble game where i am the marble it's gonna go slower how do
i like hit the brakes hold grip to stop what the fuck is that what is that you can put the
hoverboard on your back oh aim hook swing menu button b menu button so the menu button is this
one right no that's the fucking turn all right menu button what the hell is that what aim hook and
swing i can't do this one i'm i'll throw up on screen this is like i'll actually throw up from
this i can already feel like the puke you're building it here okay fuck that's so cool though
i have to see it so how do i get what am i supposed to go from here i think i was supposed to jump
that get get off get off get off no no slow oh where am i stop stop get off how am i god i have
to like turn this way all right let's try it again i don't have to just ski get up get up
how do i stop oh the green bar is jet fuel green bar is jet fuel and meatloaf for lunch and you
might see it pull me over there right back and forth on the pain speed
the gun there's the button on your wrist this is fucking really cool charge and shoot
okay okay what happened okay
oh okay so i don't really i can't make out what this means one two two two three four
close it up okay there's like an octopus over there this is ridiculous looking i'll say that
all right now that it's more out in the open here i feel a little less puking what is that
checkpoint okay oh oh that felt good though
you feel that from a mile away anymore holy fuck this is too much you're not in my life
that's it right there so what do i get for that anything pretty decent cutscene boxes really
fucking going crazy how is it are we good now how bad is it still bad sorry i hope that if you could
play this and get the hang of the movement my god some people probably are insane with this game
you master the movement are they supposed to touch that what a hook shot retract unlocked
really so what does that mean hold trigger and hook shot you can pull yourself in
oh wow okay sounds cool to me let's go no no this way we still caught
checkpoint right here this game's really cool too all right just get on my board
checkpoint jump what was that just like tribes ascend hold on it's a checkpoint in here
checkpoint so where are the monsters there's a huge one in the sky look over here i want to
go that way this is loop to loop right there i don't know why the hell i didn't hit that
up this way jesus i've never experienced anything like this before i want to go kill the dragon
what is this boost whoa shit i'm too overwhelmed i don't know where to go maybe like over this way
let's go try to get this fucking giant bug thing i mean the huge centipede we have to see what the
hell that is there's something up there you guys see that fuck there's so much to look at this is
just a i don't i don't even know what to say all i know is my hair is being pulled
i sit in that i'm gonna sit in that all right here it comes ready uh oh uh oh i did it i did it i
did it i did it just stay here and go what do i do just stand here i made it to the other side
all right it's cool but i'm gonna throw up yeah i feel the same way the board on your back
i didn't know you could do that i got that right yeah so i'm gonna assume this way once i get to
the end of here i'm gonna take like another break it's too much for my brain it's probably
something up there's a big lighthouse up there that was awesome it's up there i see it i see it i see
it okay be easy here jeremy oh it's so fucking horrible i lost my sound that structure looks
different let me look at it this is gonna come alive this looks like it's gonna be alive it's not
look at how high up you can go too this is ridiculous right up there up up up right up there
odd octopus holy shit it's getting worse isn't really that's irritating oh my back
like hurt my whole body i need to like go lose something i feel like there's so much cool shit
to do in this game but i'm not doing it well i i got like launched by the catapult that was
fucking cool come on give me enough to get back come on come on come on come on come on come on
i just smashed my face what was the glass that i just shattered i'm going after the centipede
oh i'm starting to fall now i understand the warning all right here we go just like spider-man
all right um getting close look at this perfect seat come here i don't know face what the hell is
in here oh just a shitload of spikes that i'm absolutely gonna die on stop stop and let it
recharge some adventure time bullshit right here it's gonna make me go fast this is
a boost right damn it damn it i need to do something it looks like there's a million ways
to go but i don't know which way is a way to go do you see any of the monsters or
things i should try to do it's the red lighthouses okay i was close to one before
let's go to that one yeah there we go all right there's one coming up right here
just don't crash into a spike for that for that for that we got some jumps here
there it is gotta get a good swing here i'm dead good swinger i'm dead exactly what i wanted
shit die there try it another way there's a ball why am i dropping like a sink like a
fucking brick what the hell is this fuck i'm tangled i'm tangled up i'm tangled up bad
real bad actually like bad really bad in his gun sony and aro goodbye but i get drone defeated
wind resistance up this is fucking really cool this is awesome all right lighthouse another
lighthouse let's go i see a lighthouse over there and there is one of these things my hands are so
sweaty probably better kill me out there please the checkpoint
how the steering is gonna kill me for the love of god
i don't have to spin around this whole thing aren't i i'm getting tangled up all right we got
jump right here we're going all the way to the bottom apparently get okay let's see where we're
going from here right i got a little jump pad here dude i'm gonna fucking smash into a wall i
know it so god damn it man like that you have to get this wireless like you gotta get it wireless
or it'd be sitting down this shit wraps around you like a fucking bubble constrictor
god damn it man like that you have to get this wireless like you gotta get it wireless
or it'd be sitting down this shit wraps around you like a fucking follow constrictor
what we got i took the fucking board off i have the audio again um oh god damn it
is it nothing up here just stay here don't move stop moving down the hole hold on there's a 15
foot snake attached to my body right now hold on guys i can't even put my headphones on
get this off my headphones on my back yeah my head fell out because my ears are sweating profusely
it's just oil in my ears they're just gonna slip out let me land right here so i can put my
fucking headphones in knock the board i'm gonna push this in as hard as i can like they're gonna
go into my brain yeah like this shit i can't even hear myself talk i have literally no idea what i'm
saying right now this is i can't it's just an earthquake all right so you guys are talking
about it i feel like i've got a construction yard and i'm trying to talk to somebody over
one of those cat machines dripping up dirt behind me there's a hole oh that's loud
oh
humans were not supposed to do this this would have killed the caveman if you put this on the
can't be able to put this on and instantly die grab him what's going on here fuck you
got another one is it up top rabbit he's gonna shoot me he's gonna shoot me get on the board he's
gonna shoot me i don't get out of here collapsing holy shit where's my stuff with my with my
unlockable didn't i get a new unlockable there it is all right let's just don't get hit by the
spikes by top three spikes i'm gonna be so angry give it to me long laser oh that's pretty cool
so i have a much longer shot that's really great okay sniper shot how are you guys doing
is cox just fucking with it how many frames have we dropped you see a lot actually that's a lot
well don't ask me why how can i get the hell out of this let me stretch my back
guess it out that way that looks pretty good if i were to guess in the other
that hole straight up come on i can't do that i can't look up for that long
i'll actually throw up and fall down i guess this goal is okay hold on let me sit here for
damn it i don't want to like have to take a break this is like so fun but honest to god it's like
riding a disney ride like an hour you know the transformers ride at disney world where are you
guys okay you know the transformers ride at disney world imagine if you were on that ride for an hour
straight and you couldn't get off that's like a 14 minute experience if that oh i'm starting to
get a little greasy here where's my water i think one of those yeah what the fuck is going on with
the internet the internet really sucks huh welcome back to the world let me just see if it's like any
i mean like messages or anything about it back down home went the wrong way really chats angry
oh so am i it's a load of this like 10 000 frames drop it's a load of bullshit
you're gonna do horror vr's absolutely but i want to do the like some of the most requested ones
it's a lot of vr the fuck when did this start happening like an hour ago all right have i played
sarento no not yet i wonder if i feel ill watching this because of vr because i barely started an
essay no i think it's because of the this game this game is incredibly intense all right well
sorry that we're dropping frames but i can really only realistically play this game for like another
maybe like another 20 to 30 minutes let's go back in a new game we'll see how i feel i've been in it
for about five hours we'll see how i feel after this i want to try to get my hair is all fucked
up just play till you puke there's a tunnel back down in the hole really god damn it duck season
yeah that's i'm gonna play them but i'm gonna play all of them eventually but you do kind of
have to give yourself a break because it's essentially over the last three oh look okay
okay thanks for coming to the stream uh realistically i mean i've got like like 15
16 17 hours in vr in three days this is more physical activity i think i've had in the last
year go back in the hole all right let's go i missed a tunnel where's the secret tunnel
i don't think that's it i don't think it a good view
oh my god that hurts spiral ramp thank you i'm like holding this button down oh man i'm getting i
this is probably going to be the end here very soon i guess dr field my marvel scrambling
spiral up this way let's go let's just do the loop-de-loop all right just get on it no
ah i see it and when i get out of this hole i gotta stop that's just the way it is
i can't even fucking function right now right there ski ski am i going the right way yeah yeah
yeah this is it right all right slow down slow down slow down slow why get off what the fuck
all right you gotta know you gotta know when to quit we're there look at how like slow to react i am
i just kept putting a jar and shook it
that way i wonder how many people have left the stream because this game is like making them feel
i'm sorry i'm sorry this is still fun though all right another alien i'll get it
damn it nope come on i got one shot why am i holding my skateboard yes no no i'm too far away
yes what do i get for this drone defeated jet fuel oh nice there's no next he's making himself sick
so he doesn't have to play another game no i'm all right i'm good i'm good don't worry about me i'm
fine i don't know where you guys are there you are he's making himself sick all right one more
lighthouse and then that's it what over there this game is surprisingly player friendly not viewer
friendly yeah it probably isn't you probably guys probably fucking sick right now uh it's really fun
you lost a thousand viewers well i people i don't i don't blame you you know i don't blame you if
you can't watch something like this you can't watch it you know if a thousand people leave
it just gets like i can't physically watch you play this that's that's all right
let me get a better view all right let me just ski over there and see let me just see what that is
and once i see what that is we're probably gonna stop
because i know what that is face look at how beautiful that is over there though
all right we're almost there almost there i got more jet fuel oh dear great
okay almost there getting close we're so close this thing this thing that was pretty perfect
accidental perfect but perfect nonetheless oh trying to go that way
there it is spikes easy oh oh oh oh oh no no no go this way all right i made it
just gotta get up the top of the tower there we go what do i gotta shoot there's no fucking hole
another damn hole this is the same hole that i went in before this is not the same one is it
okay here we go jesus christ i just felt that for real
okay watch out for the star explosion things they definitely explode this is bad
i'm gonna have to do like spike stuff now i'm not looking forward to this no no no oh i made it
playing just a counter strike surf now where is it a boss or is this like a room of obstacles
charged up okay hold on wait wait wait those spikes oh shit right right there
you think i'm not fucking smart about this shit don't hit the speed boost got it let's go now what
this way i can't believe i made it down that get off you know uh i'm not gonna run into a spike
right now you're supposed to go fast oh that's fine but fast is dead stop stop yeah right yeah
right dang that's not good no that's not gonna happen wow yeah wow i can't believe i just went
through that there's even more of this bullshit why down does that go what the fuck happened
yeah what's uh what's the deal here boy just calm down it's in his mouth come on give me
something to work with here a tree yeah i'm running out i'm running out yeah come on
open wide motherfucker no sorry i'm right here tail yeah dang it how does that turn this sponge
bob oh it hurts son of a bitch so high up need something better to swing on to come here you
bastard oh i run the juice thank you had it yeah motherfucker that's how we do it that's how we do
it here one more where's his back where is it on the stomach stomach i think bingo right here
here i'm coming for you i'm coming for that stomach too slow too fast see it let me see it open water
where is it
it's gotta be up there right is it up there it's gonna be like in there damn damn damn
oh fuck you get out of my way come on luke come on luke come on luke
oh we're getting bounced around i don't know where i am up what's up is up is down up down is up
not in the spikes easy folks easy folks where the fuck did i go right there bring it in
it my sound effects see you in hell
i should get out of here i should get out of here i gotta get out of here i gotta move
out the front
shoot it again shoot it again all right i did it oh holy shit this game is awesome this is awesome
this is wow where's my uh upgrade i thought one of the spikes was gonna come and just
crush me that would have been so horrible hold on let me get situated there you are
that was a full pucker i thought i was gonna get crushed yeah at first i wasn't so sure about this
game a little puke inducing but once you get used to it man this is you just track down gigantic
mechanical monsters and kill them it's really really cool i feel like something's stuck
that's not gonna get undone all right let's go up here uh if i were a upgrade where would i be
easy all right something's pulling here this is my slippery oily ears maybe in his mouth
don't see it anymore don't go too fast i want to get hit by a spike i don't see it
maybe up a little higher bounce there it is probably get a good angle down here
there it is give me the ball give me the ball give me the ball power jump unlocked
bend knees and stand up really bend knees and stand up further on the board that crack sound
um cool that's cool well this game's fantastic i can't do that though because i will fall over
that like all right i'm gonna have to call it here i'm exhausted but damn that was fucking fun
sorry to all the people that could not handle it i could barely handle it too but let me just
get out of this i'm just gonna look i'm just gonna look over i can't look up there
okay wait what i don't know where did i go uh i made it onto the snake i got the snake
is there anywhere on this i can shoot go looking for a blue orb if you see it scream
right this face maybe it might be right down uh main street there let's find out we'll get there
much outrageous all right let's take a look at that big ugly mug of yours what do you say
can't get in there it's closed off well he's probably the last boss i can stop
as much as i want to keep going this is a blast oh come back to it another time probably
god it's so much fun oh forgot what do you mean forgot to save doesn't it does auto save
wait did you actually have to save the game no i don't save you oh boy oh boy well thank you
for joining me for another vr adventure it was a lot of fun uh sorry for the shitload of people
that uh left the stream because i couldn't handle it and speaking of can't handle it
this looks like i tried to do this doesn't it i put gel in my hair and styled it to look like this
what time is it too is it late yeah it's getting there the little yeah look at this i swear okay
if i go like this and if i pull the whole thing's gonna come off i could just go and the whole thing
would come off you look like you live under a bridge hey but come on pac-man oh i'm not pulling
it i'm not gonna do it but thank you for joining me everybody i'll see you guys uh i'm not streaming
tomorrow so today is wednesday tomorrow's thursday i'm gonna go friday saturday and sunday i'm gonna
do three days in a row we're gonna go back we're gonna go back to the dreamcast we're gonna move
vr out of the way for a week or so because i do need like a little break from it my fate my hair
needs a break so we're gonna go back to uh c man and space channel five part one so we'll see if
we can complete both those tomorrow not tomorrow i mean the next day day after tomorrow so yeah i
have the microphone look here it's here it only took a million years for me to get it
vr is some of the most fun i've had on your streams oh me too they're fucking awesome
but remember you can't we can't just like blow through it i want to enjoy every experience
i don't want to just like hey vr tomorrow vr the next day let's do vr for three straight weeks vr
only it'll start to i gotta i gotta give myself a break so we'll go back to vr next week
so for the purposes of the remaining streams i got a couple of dreamcast things
i got a shit move for playstation 2 games for some crazy reason i don't know why they look fun though
and the stream just went to zero i guess not there's also some new games that came out that
i'd like to try yeah sorry about the internet issues too and with that we're gonna move on
i'll see you guys uh if you're taking off i'll see you on thursday oh not thursday technically
yeah no friday friday saturday and sunday i'm gonna go three straight days i'm locking it up
for you vr is gonna take a break let's do the bits i want to get in there don't keep playing
it's so much fun yeah metro does look good there's a lot of things look good i gotta pull myself out
of the virtual world for a little while so we went uh just about six hours here tonight
back earlier we've got let's see here we've got five dollars from five dollars from
tish chaboy for five bucks hey germa love you content have a perfect school i have a
i have a project for school where i interview role models and i was wondering if you're interested
i already emailed you some of the details uh love you germa uh somebody else was talking about that
too wasn't pin talking about interview stuff all jokes aside i really don't like do interviews
i'm gonna give let's give a general gigantic clip here all right here you go
so when i started from the same school he's too famous to do interviews he's not pr trained i
don't really do for real i don't like do interviews i don't i mean i'm just kind of
all right here you go here's a gigantic clip you can take yeah when i started i never thought i'd
have any people watching just trying to have fun every uh every day i'm just trying to have
fun with my friends and try to have the most experiences that we can on stream and it's a
lot of fun it gives a commencement speech oh why did my elbow just click the ego on this guy
make sure your dreamcast clock battery isn't dead because c-man requires it that is a random
thing that i didn't even know existed so i'm gonna definitely check into that thank you but uh i wish
all of your luck on your projects whether they be about me or about somebody else but i don't i
don't do interviews i don't do pictures i don't do autographs i don't do selfies if you stop me on
the street and you're like hey can i get a picture i'm just i'm like absolutely not
i'm just kidding but thank you nonetheless i am flattered and thank you to sawdust bunnies for
the 10 bucks yay a stream on my birthday happy birthday sawdust bunnies thank you for the 10
dollars appreciate it he's getting killed here on internet huh well well now we're at zero
so still alive okay it's very weird uh i thought the problem was fixed maybe it's not
but thank you for the 10 dollars on your birthday i don't know why you're giving me
10 dollars on your birthday but happy birthday nonetheless one time i asked jeremy for a picture
and he stuck my phone down his pants and the even worse the picture is blurry
what the fuck that's so fucked up thank you binary man for the five dollars uh first i want
to start by saying that i'm really sorry for blowing everyone's eardrums out with my bits last
stream i have no excuses and i'm not expecting forgiveness but i want you to know that i'm
genuinely sorry i don't know what i was thinking when i said that i was an idiot i took advantage
of the trust you have for your chat and i know it's unforgivable but know that i'm sorry i've
learned my lesson and it will not happen again three day ban is up uh if it happens again that's
uh that's that's goodbye it's uh you know boink out of town he's supposed to post a link to an
even even louder video in that message thank you binary man i know you're just messing around you're
just fucking around i know but you gotta remember if people aren't prepared for the noise that loud
you know you could fucking actually mess up somebody's head you could blow out an ear you
could fuck up a speaker you just gotta remember you're dealing with people just like you you know
would you want your speaker blown out i don't think you would what have you had it up loud
no you couldn't yeah you could you could like it would be the subwoofer will just blow out
and the tube in the middle will just fly out at like 100 miles per hour it's dangerous shit
but thank you binary uh commando i think commando uh commando nom thanks for the two bucks
i found someone on deviantart who makes stuffed animals and i'm gonna pay him
in march to make a stuffed animal of you well uh that's i hope you have uh i don't even know how
to say anything without out of context just being bad i um that is a thing that you're going to buy
that you're gonna get made i just hope you don't stick needles in it while chanting and trying to
hurt me if anything like if you're gonna do that if you're gonna do like uh like a curse or something
just like put me in like a nice warm bath right dude nobody does nice shit with one of those
dolls you know open up like cook bacon and then hold me up and just kind of swirl me around over
where the bacon is cooking so i can smell it give me a nice warm bath do nice things what do you
mean that's worse you don't think if you just woke up in the morning randomly one day and you could
just smell bacon you'd be like wow it smells like bacon in here this is delicious and i guess that
would be kind of worse because then you would go to wherever your kitchen was thinking somebody made
bacon and they didn't on second thought just stab me with the knives that's probably better pluck
out his chest hairs play loud videos to the doll it just put my ear up to his speaker
you guys are fucking vicious why would you want to do that to me what chest hairs i got plenty
but thank you commando thank you uh cougar for the one dollar germa germa germa gimme gimme gimme
a hernia a alec thanks to the one dollar is an htc vibe a good investment a yes it is
i would put the 100 stamp of recommendation and approval on
the vibe just the last three sessions alone was worth the five six hundred dollar investment
to play it because it's a lot different i mean i know i know some of you guys have probably played
it at conventions or at a friend's house or something but when you have it in your own room
and you can just go in and play it it's a lot different than just doing like uh i guess i'm
like gonna do this for like 10 minutes what's this demo it's a lot more fun now what i would
tell you somebody just already mentioned it valve and htc they are coming out with a new one it's
called the cosmo right the htc vibe cosmo it's not out yet but it might be a different maybe
potentially better version of the one that currently exists i don't know they're not
discontinuing the regular one from what i know yeah the htc cosmo it's that is not valve that's
htc only well uh they announced it very recently so we'll see cosmos is different valve has their
own in development really so there's going to be a cosmos and a new valve only made one
uh you you kind of making too many you know you got that's gonna be four
that's a little weird because there's five five pro cosmos and then whatever valve is doing because
i know they're not getting rid of the old ones they're not gonna finish it maybe not but we'll
see what they do but anyways we had uh yeah i would say yes it is currently for the standard
default five it's 499 but if you like me you're kind of going to need an accessory or two
i had to get two stands to hold the lighthouses because i couldn't put them they weren't that i
couldn't clamp them anywhere so that was another like 60 bucks plus if you want a couple extra
lighthouses you know who knows it depending on how big your room is or what you want to do with it
it could cost between five and seven hundred bucks or wireless if you want to get the wireless
thing that's 299 which i like think i have to get it it almost makes it necessary when you're trying
to do a room scale thing sitting down sure i don't think it's necessary or standing only but doing
like the two or three steps forward and backwards and turning around 360 i think i have to get it
you can get some elgato lights for cheaper than that uh but these i mean these ones came with
a bundle so maybe you can i don't know but thank you too uh where were we here alec uh d jack thanks
for the two dollars and 49 cents thanks for all the laughs mr funny man thank you for being here
and thank you for the two dollars and 49 cents divas thanks for the 250 thank you combine for
the three dollars come on down and eat some gorn or we'll sacrifice your newborn thanks jeremy you're
the best i'm uh i'm disappointed that i couldn't play that i was really looking forward to that
too i guess it just kind of something was wrong with the new update or something we'll try it
again next time we do uh vibe but it does look very fun thank you topac for the 250 uh check out
what chat drew of you i've pre-screened it so it's nothing to worry about
i've pre-screened it wow brought to you by fruit zoom ha ha ha there's a bird in a tree
what the hell is all this brought to you by fruit wow and then somebody does like a really detailed
one down there ha ha idiot nice zoom hey look look look here here here here here look look
virus nice zoom idiot what is this link is that a virus link it's not a virus link it's like a
weird website that is like a bad website no it's not it's a fine website is it a good website
what did you link me you pre-screened it told me pre-screen it there's a pre-screened website
no it works it's not a picture it's a website it could be dynamic and change to a screamer
at any time i linked flinstone's porn no that that that did not happen
i think we broke the site the site we may have accidentally just took it down
yeah that was so fucked up like barney was getting cooked or something it was
really fucking weird it was horrifying they were like eating each other it was very very very
graphic and horrible i didn't even do that i went to i searched for something don't have a search
for anybody ever that actually yeah that did actually happen like a year ago but thank you
topec for the website where you can draw whatever you want hey cougar thanks for the one dollar
hoorah hoorah oh for the marines okay cool sweet tweet don't tell us this shit what the hell wait
what do you mean the amount of new subs who missed the flinstone's porn has got to be quite high
yeah probably a lot of new people probably have no idea
it's been with some weird shit on this stream that's for sure
hey smiter thanks for the one dollar demonic cucumber thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents
hey germy i got a question about the new 250 limit if i donate three 100 bit donations in a row
would i still be right at the end no uh it has to be 250 it's got to be of the whatever the
message is it has to be in a 250 limit and i'm reading one dollar one still as you see but
i want it to slowly over the last like last few streams get uh you know transition slowly
but uh it's hard for me to buy exactly 250 here anyway i thought you'd like to know there's a
groundhog day vr game coming out later this year other than that i'd recommend payday vr
essentially built again for vr and maybe la noir vr as you didn't finish the first time
yeah the vr case files looks fun i'll probably end up doing that at some point soon
but yes the message whatever you want to write if you whatever the message is that has to be
at two dollars and 50 cents vr needs to grow yes it does they got to solve some of the random
issues that pop up from time to time it's getting there though i give it like maybe another three to
five years before they start to really get there it's getting close but thank you so much to
montecucumber for the 250 ambix thanks for the 250 babe don't make a sound 2 a.m love gotta keep
it down don't wait around for a signal now give me some verbs i ain't talking nouns you want to
ride in the six you want to dive in the six when i lean for the kiss he said i'll probably send
you some bits thank you yes is online for the four dollars this took 10 hours of my life i hope
you enjoy it oh wait this is the birth we have we listened to this already this is the death rips
and rats birthday mix didn't we already hear this yeah but i swear to god we already we heard this
before this two default negative turn i'm trying to change my desktop sound thing there we go
that better okay here we go i just like yeah i don't feel good i can't
i don't feel good today i can't do that you got you have to put a gnome in here
you really have to do that this was starting off so well like this is going very well
is there anything else here i'm something of a scientist myself
is that death yes
link again link it again here here here there's the link well that was the mashup between death
rips rat's birthday song and a gnome halfway through just in case you weren't paying attention
thank you so much for that i love how they kept the screaming in the background
yeah it looks like some work went into that thank you thank you yes is online for the four dollars
and that video siroc thanks for the 250 siroc hey germa i saw kim shopping at walmart with shido
yesterday i couldn't tell it to her but i can tell it to you shido was acting very inappropriately
he was yelling at people throwing cereal on the floor opening up toys and breaking them stealing
and eating candy bars you should have a talk with shido and with kim about his behavior
i'll talk to him i'll find out what happened he's acting out for some reason i don't know why
i think he's in some kind of phase shida would never do that i have to i gotta confirm that
story with kim it's important but thank you sir rock for the two dollars fifty cents
thank you jess you got it for the 250 i would love to see a stream in the middle of nowhere
in vegas just you and a table of guns teaching gun safety well that's definitely never gonna
happen because i do not necessarily know anything about how to handle a firearm so i would never
ever operate one without the proper guidance and safety procedures and i would never teach anybody
anything about gun safety because i know i there's no way i'd be able to tell you anything
i would have to step out of the way and have a professional go over safety
that's the point why would i ever do that you'd like to know what that's such a terrible awful
idea you definitely seem like an expert after today's stream your dog there's a little dog down
there but yeah this there's some shit that i'm doing soon as if i can get figured out this is
i got plans i got lots of plans but when it gets warm up just you wait uh thank you daring
ocelot for the two dollars uh only jex would do the meat grinder after i played for a couple
hours i really should have gone back and tried it because i figured out all the nuances of the
game at that point that's cheeto i think it actually might be cheeto that's weird
maybe he is acting on i'm learning how to bark too but thank you daring ocelot for the two bucks
cypress 74 thanks for the ten dollars go to sandbox and learn them yeah i eventually figured
it out it was a fun learning experience and i'm glad i didn't just skip that game because
that sort of go in defend the point and go pick up stuff in the supply cases it was actually very
fun so thank you cypress for the ten dollars and the tip thank you hey topac thanks for the 250
uh how is my relationship with how's my relationship with the northern lion
it's cool that his chat has a jup command i would love to see you guys do something together wait
what wait no northern line has a command for like the jupiter like the like my emote is it for real
or is it a different thing does he have his own jupiter yeah it blocks the jupiter from being
completed oh no i mean i don't really i don't talk to northern lion i mean he just
been around for a long time i've never really had a even a conversation with him so i don't really
yeah he's doing his thing that's that's cool whatever i don't really know him at all but thank
you the 250 uh mj lodge thanks for the ten bucks hey jerma keep on being an awesome streamer love
you also do you think we'll ever see you play ace attorney i kind of want to see that also should
i buy a dre and a scooter well the first part of that is uh ace attorney when it comes to pc
and gets remastered on pc is when i'm gonna try it i got a lot of people's hopes up a few weeks
ago when i said i was gonna play it but i got the version that i was told was not very good
and it's not the way you should experience the game and i said okay i will hold off
the pc version is released it's already out when the wait the pc hd where is it
there's no steam when did this come up it had to have come out today well the day before
ace attorney well um all right oh it came out in japan well let me go take a look
see if i can figure out when it's coming out in north america but thank you mj for the ten dollars
and should you buy adrian a scooter i'm not sure what is adrian does adrian want a scooter
what is adrian going to do with the scooter go ride around town the neighborhood play along
have some fun why are you responsible for buying adrian a scooter i don't you know i don't get much
context adrian a friend of yours adrian a little brother adrian a significant other i don't know
i would say yeah again i mean why not but thank you for the ten dollars mostly lost thanks for the
one dollar mostly lost how do you only read the one guy every single time it's honestly impressive
just the thing that pops up the most it just pops out to me the one guy thank you cyprus for
the ten dollars they say more fun i had a lot of fun thank you for the ten bucks and more fun
silver flame thanks for the two dollars and fifty cents hey germa my pet duck oswald
couple duck passed away recently and it's been rough just want to say thank you for always being
able to bring a smile to my face at my roughest moments it's kind of corny but honestly in my
darkest moments you and your content has always been in the light in my life reminding me to
laugh hopefully one day i'll be able to repay you but till then take my ad bits keep being you
germa because that's the guy we all love no it's not it's all right it's not corny it's all right
first of all i'm really sorry to hear that i've heard that ducks are incredibly intelligent really
really loyal and loving animals so pet duck uh rest in peace to your duck first of all and
second of all i just i just like to hang out here and have fun you know if that is what's happening
and you are also having a good time and you're enjoying yourself by collectively hanging out
here with a bunch of random people and me and all of us together making up this kind of crazy
community then yeah that's fucking incredible it's amazing i'm so happy that it happens
because we're all just randomly in different places in the world and somehow we we hang out here
during these streams so it's great much respect to you thank you silver flame and again sorry
about your pet sorry about your duck thank you uh commando commando again commando nam for two
dollars that green rocket launcher itself is a easter egg to half-life one that's interesting
stuff it's pretty cool thank you for the little tidbit freudian weapon thanks for the three
dollars and 19 cents 319 they just say germa hart and germa jex i think it did okay i did all right
uh we had a bunch of big sub gifts come in from great canadian fuck club mostly lost you guys
came in with 30 i believe you know 20 and then 10 thank you both of you smelly boy we had smelly
boy for a dollar war is hell yes yes it is thank you flank tank for the three dollars uh
quote american doesn't know how to use guns k kona but really germa you live in the wild west now
aka the desert take kim and italics to a shooting range and just try it out it's kind of relaxing
you shoot the shit literally i have i have been to a range before i have shot a firearm before
at a range a couple of years ago i've shot a nine millimeter a
some type of sub machine gun some type of rifle and i was too afraid to shoot the shotgun i was
afraid so i didn't do it it was very scary i didn't want to do it it was a very powerful
shotgun and i'm like i don't know if i want to do that some some guy in there shot this huge
huge sniper rifle and actually what they what they tell you that everybody has to stop so
everybody just kind of hangs back and just waits because this giant huge high caliber sniper rifle
we you have ear protection on first of all right and this thing you only get to shoot it one time
at this place and holy crap when that thing is fired you can feel it wind hits you in the face
and like your chest you feel like a boom deep inside of your chest it's wild
it was it was it definitely was an experience there was a room with probably maybe 20 30 people
all at this range and we all were just kind of sitting there like wait for it wait for it here
it goes boom and you the whole place just shakes the 50 caliber pressure wave yeah
no it was it was interesting would i do it again i don't maybe yeah i don't i don't see like
as long as it was a safe place and he was you know they did things by the book and they had a lot of
the procedures were good right they usually are my dad paid ten dollars for me to shoot one bullet
out of a barrett 50 caliber maybe that's what it was there's a shotgun called a 410 that is fun
i don't know i definitely wanted to like experience it at least once that was the idea
use a varmint rifle no it was cool it was cool but also a little nerve-wracking too because
you're just like somebody that i don't really handle guns or weapons ever so when they you
know it's like okay stand here and you're like yeah okay hey hold that it's like heavy and you're
like okay so and over here oh oh just hold it up okay but you're gonna be explaining everything
and you know you're listening and you're paying attention and you're sitting there going like
i'm gonna fire this i'm gonna fire this at the target and what's gonna happen it sounds
stressful the first like three or four shots at a range is pretty stressful but once you
because look it's an if you've never done it before you don't even know what to expect
it ain't like a fucking movie you know what i mean you gotta like control you gotta like be very very
attentive you have to pay the fuck attention because everything you're doing
shaky hands very interesting stuff though yeah attentive just hearing you talk about it is
stressing me out well i have i haven't really done it since no i have like that was i did it once
that was about two and a half years ago it was very different but there you go thank you flank
tank door cube thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents door cube not sure if you noticed but
you did something weird during that horseshoes and hot dogs game take a look what did i that's
pretty good thank you for the thank you for the 250 and that image appreciate you did something
weird saw feather thanks for the doll 78 saw feather thank you future gamer thanks for the
250 the dev added a super secret mode called extreme spin mode where your body angles to
the ground so you stand on and spin you in the direction of the jets i'm pretty good in vr and
almost made me projectile vomit yeah i feel bad that that's kind of what we ended on
because somebody did say that more than a thousand people left the stream after 10-15
minutes of being in that game so actually it's probably better to end on that because
we've been going for about four and a half hours anyways so probably better to end it
than start on it that game is really cool though i'm gonna have i have to go back and play that
one again because sometimes it was a little too much but as long as you can kind of power
through it it was really really really fun but thank you future gamer with the 250 thank you
bingo sunshine sunshine for the five dollars germany if a vr game is making you sick stop
playing it don't keep making yourself sick for an hour plus laughing my ass off
it was fine it was fun look you guys know me pretty well at this point if something is not
okay with me on this stream it goes off or it changes especially something like that
so if i was really having a problem that i've really had to stop i absolutely would have so
thank you for the concern though i appreciate it and thank you for the thank you for the laughing
my ass off at the end if you do vomit make sure to get it on camera how long do you get banned
for on twitch if you puke on stream okay but hold on a second though that's what if it's like not
even my that's not even my no i'm not drinking on stream we're doing something fucked up
i just like got sick in vr and puked on stream but i get banned for like three days no like on
accident not on purpose i don't think it's i mean isn't it against isn't like bodily fluids
against the terms of service it has to be you probably get 24 hours imagine that's like the
way that my stream gets banned this throwing up in vr it would ruin this whole fucking room
24 hours what the hell's with the internet right now god damn it i gotta make like i'm
gonna phone call and make sure this is getting fixed but thank you bingo sunshine for the five
bucks thank you great lord walden how did i miss this this is like 20 subs from the grip this is
all this is the one that i missed earlier yeah great lord walden thank you so much for the
20 community subs that was just barely an hour ago thank you mu means mu thanks for the five bucks
even though this game makes me want to puke i want to say thank you for how fun the stream has been
to watch unfortunately i had to say a final goodbye to one of my dogs today he was a great
boy and i'll miss him once so i appreciate the laughs tonight here's some pictures of him playing
in the snow oh man oh look at look at this good boy i'm really sorry to hear that here
now remember all the wonderful things this this dog looks so just wonderful thank you for sharing
these pictures and i'm really really sorry to hear about that and that would that happen today
today yeah i'm so sorry to hear that move what a good boy and thank you for the five dollars
much love to you yeah it's always hard when you lose when you lose like an animal you lose
another like a really good friend a really close friend family member even right it's they
especially like dogs cats birds doesn't matter talk about a significant portion of your whole life
is spent with this animal that when i had uh the last dog that i had was around for 17 years
17 years it's a big deal it's a lot to have to handle and now auto is around he's been around
for about five to seven or six years now just about seven maybe you know everybody's gonna
have to do it eventually right just enjoy the time you have with your animals love them every day
and just enjoy the time you have right but thank you boo thank you bingo sunshine for five dollars
uh i'm sorry germa i was wrong that was awesome good job sticking it out yeah it's that started
off really rocky but as long as you just let it you know you let it just flow over you you start
to try to pay attention you try to learn the moves eventually there's a really really very
really very fun game there thank you bingo i'm sure we will return to it
hey smelly boy thanks for the one dollar i know you said no more vr but you have to beat that sky
worm thank you dr stein for the five dollars pull the hair tuft embrace baldness it'll be
a good look for you smooth streamer no not yet i don't have to do that yet i don't have to go
bald yet i got plenty of hair up here i can still style it it still can swoosh i can spray some
stuff and put it back and it looks nice i don't have to do that yet maybe like another five to
ten years no omega low t yet oh god uh we had 10 community subs coming from asha asha108 thanks
for the 10 community subs thank you thank you thank you no bt tv nope five to ten days is more
accurate we'll see thank you asha and thank you dr stein for the suggestion but i'm not pulling
out my hair um mr oh me double j thanks for the five dollars me double j drummer would you say
that vr was worth it also so far what's your favorite vr game super hot vr is not only my
favorite vr game it's one of my favorite games i think i've played over the last couple of years
now here's the thing about vr that's a little strange and i get it this seems like there are
it seems like all these vr games are kind of like two to three hour experiences and they're all
between 15 and 25 dollars if super hot vr was a 60 dollar game and was like another three or four
maybe five hours of content maybe like another three hours of content even even if it was a
four to five hour vr experience i think i would be worth it but nobody's like making full on
complete vr games because probably that market share just isn't there and maybe people can only
play them for so long right but man if i if i could pay 60 bucks for two and a half times
the content that was in super hot vr that'd be one of my probably favorite games ever made
i'm not kidding around that's not a joke you know like ocarina of time no no no bump it off the
list see you later you add like two to three more hours of of actual campaign content in
super hot vr make it like a 40 to 50 60 dollar game that's one of my favorite games ever made
market share is a big word for you they used to trade cryptocurrency you don't think i know what
that word means he finally admitted it what are you guys know that i have an emote that is a coin
that was that why is it some now quit talking about cryptocurrency somebody just said it
but the thing is before i wasn't okay we're gonna move on because i wasn't talking about
it before and somebody accused me of talking about it before i don't talk about it anymore
it's a goddamn bear market and i'm not going to talk about that in a bear market
oh he knows what that word is that means that instead of uh it's a it's bull and bear
now how that works is in wall street instead of humans there are bears in suits that go in there
they're all dressed up and they trade for a little while that's like a bear market they're
allowed to be in there for a few months and then they let the the bears out when they're done
because they have to hibernate and the bulls come in and then they put on suits and shit and it's
animals no bull is up bear is down you don't think i know this stuff you want to know what
market cap means i'll give you a whole course stay after the credits that sounds like a furry party
okay i'm gonna laugh my ass off okay okay if i said that i was gonna do a financial course after
the credits and i was gonna explain market cap after the credits were over i wonder how many
people leave i'm not a financial advisor why did i say that never said that but yes uh back to i
don't know how that even got there but vr is great it's definitely worth it super hot vr was
unbelievably good to a point where i'm angry about it i am upset that super hot vr is something
that i can't play anymore because i mean i could go back and like beat all the levels and try to
get really good at them do the speed run stuff but i beat it in about an hour and 32 minutes
and it was one of my favorite things i've done in the last couple years take that how you will
e dragon thanks for the three bucks e dragon hey germ a great stream i showed you to my drunk
friend he thinks you're hilarious uh hello drunk friend happy to have you aboard thanks for the
three bucks e dragon and thanks for introducing me to one of your friends thank you well i get
somebody i gotta end an argument here uh jesse you got it 250 thanks to 250 we're having an
argument in the discord prove a point for us and say these words okay arkansas crayon baloney
caramel tomato done what do i win pronounced it wr omega lull wrong what what is the the word
the omega lull in the middle of a word where it oh is
omega lull this is a super laugh right that means you're having a lot of fun
what the heck is omega lull no i know what that is that's the big the big mouth being open right
a huger that means i'm i'm that means i'm laughing so hard that i'm like turning i'm i can't even i
can't even comprehend it anymore i'm laughing so hard right can i get a crap okay after the
stream you guys are gonna give me a crash course in uh stay i don't know what these some of these
emotes mean what do they actually mean so lul is i just laughed that was funny omega lull is
i'm laughing so hard that it hurts and i have to stop laughing is that correct okay good so
kappa means get over it loser right no no no no um not kappa a forehead forehead is like okay get
over it not funny right that's correct isn't it like forehead is like oh look at how laugh you're
laughing so hard like i'm laughing like get over it's not funny it's like a sarcastic one okay and
then haha is i i respect this person so much and i think that they're really awesome so i want them
to show i want to show them a close-up of my face right like i'm gonna take a selfie of my face
like smiling to show them how much fun i'm having that's what i thought it means cringe cringe i've
never heard that i've never seen that sequence of letters before in a row i don't know is it a
different language i'm not sure whatever that means hey toshiro.tv thanks for the five dollars
jet island looks absolutely bonkers to play i hope to eventually get a vr set up
on an unrelated note i was wondering what your policy is on fan meetups i'm actually going to
be in vegas this weekend with my dad my 21st birthday happy 21st birthday i was hoping to
meet up at some point but since you're streaming all weekend that i won't worry about it much
hope i have as much fun in vegas as you do in vr well i can tell you right now
i don't do them i don't do fan meetups i don't do meet and greets unless very specifically
they are on a convention floor like a twitchcon a pax east pax west e3 i don't do meetups
i mean i guess this is like probably a handful of reasons why
terma just let us in your house he can't get the pass to conventions what but no i don't
i like to kind of here here's let me give you the long and short of it here so let's say that you
and i hung out tomorrow right all right i'm coming down i'll see you in a minute let's hang out and
let's let's play roulette you know whatever you would be doing let's go to dinner essentially
what i'm doing is i'm like i'm opening myself up to a stranger you know what i mean it's not
like i don't not like you're a stranger stranger you've been on the stream you write text i see
you in chat but i don't personally like to kind of open myself up to somebody that i don't know in
real life unless it was at a place that i was comfortable going to like a convention where
we're all there for the same reason anyways and that's nothing against anybody that ever wants
to say hello there's been plenty of people that have just you know happened to see me on the
street even here like it's happened it's happened like at least twice in vegas and that's great
that's fine that's fine but like specifically planning to go like hang out with somebody
is something i will never do it just it's never gonna happen so maybe that can be like a blanket
statement i think but if we're at a convention or you happen to see me on the street or you happen
to just know that i'm here and you ran into me somehow i was at like some place on the strip or
in downtown or wherever that do not take this as a leave me the fuck alone no it's just specific
hangouts or something i will never do hey you want to hang out at chili's i just want to hang
out at your house and eat pizza rolls no because i mean i look i do have to be on top of that because
you know you just never know you never know what somebody's intentions are what they will you know
what they want out of that you know if somebody has then like oh maybe like i maybe i have your
phone number now i got your phone number it just gets i don't want it to ever get to that place
but we'll move on from it just know that if you don't see me at a convention
uh i do meetups pretty much at any convention i ever go to but that's where i'm gonna leave it
no i have it hey flying sombrero thanks for the three bucks hey germa oh but but but hold on but
toshiro toshiro happy birthday happy 21st birthday you gotta love las vegas it's amazing
as long as you do it responsibly you're gonna love it flying sombrero thanks for the three bucks
hey germa i turned 21 now what 21s turned 21 last week and me and my friend got drunk to
your most recent rumble i had to drunkenly explain who bugleberry was to the other normies in the
dorm but it was one of the best nights of my life thanks for being a great role model as
i've been growing up you mean a lot to us who the fuck is bugleberry i had to explain to these
normies in my dorm room i can't imagine how that explanation came up dormies that's so funny why
would you show anyone germa rumble as their first germa video i mean those i like those videos
i'm just like i'm living that scenario in my head a bunch of people are on a couch
people don't know who it is you're desperately drunkenly trying to explain
that this is he puts on a mask and like pretends to be this like rl stein fucking creepy guy
and like nobody thinks it's funny but he still does it all the time anyways because he thinks
it's funny that's a long explanation mask
now he puts on a mask i'm talking about a social mask you know he has to he's not himself
he's just a regular guy and he has to put on the mask and be in front of camera what did you guys
think i was talking about well thank you commando noun for the two dollars hey i yelled life is pain
i hate myself in the middle of class during a test today and i got a lunch detention why would you do
that but it was totally worth it no it wasn't you got detention for no reason no that's that's not
a good thing it was worth it all you got out of that was a bunch of people around you were like
this guy's screaming and then you went to school jail everyone yeah somebody just said everyone's
talking about like oh what a good role model that's not the description of somebody that has a load
yeah that's a who when did you get that from um you know my role model oh who's your role model
that's this guy germa he like sucks he's fucked up he like screams he says like a bunch of
fucking crazy shit oh really and i'm gonna get banned from your school they won't you
guys you won't be able to wear like the t-shirts anymore my germa boomer germa old emote phone
case that's coming out next week you won't be able to have that on anymore you have to take it off
put a new phone case on leaked i mean i'm just making that up that might just appear on the store
next week yeah just because i said it here if more than 10 people buy that i think that would be
funny well it's what is teespring gonna think you know it's gonna be human skin as your phone case
yeah i can hear you there's that guy again remember he donated last time
she's gonna show up again that was me
but anyways thank you toshiro again for the five dollars toshiro.tv it's me again i gotta dip up
for the conclusion but just want to know that regardless of the answer to my question
i know that you are appreciated and that i'm looking forward to the watching more streams
and vods my life is taking a different direction as of late and you've been an important pillar
of my life and interests is to a good future for you italics kim and all of us in the chat
absolutely thank you it's a very very nice thing to say hopefully the direction you're taking is
the correct one hopefully you got a good choice there life is weird sometimes you get thrown a
curveball you go in a different direction sometimes the car turns around you go the
you go on the road you just came down and you go back like four exits and get off that highway
whatever is best for you thank you again for the five dollars and i wish you the best of luck good
luck on whatever route life is taking you let's do your best that's all you can do tingy thanks for
the two dollars and 49 cents sorry that i'm a bit short on the minimum i don't have enough germa
pluto i'm sorry but still get ready hey nate thanks for the two bucks nate am i gonna play
back black mesa zen soon it's the biggest thing to ever happen in the half-life community
probably not i hate to crush your dreams here but i don't think i'm gonna play that sorry
i just i don't think i'll play it not sure probably not play tilt brush yeah there's so
many things to do it sucks because that i have this finite amount of time in vr where i know
i'm only going to be able to do it for four to five hours straight there's so many pieces of
content that i need to stuff in there and then come up for air and do it again another time
i wish it didn't kill me but it does but i love it plays geoguessr and shitty flash games won't
play black mesa yeah but i so well i'm not interested in black mesa geo i was interested
in geoguessr i mean remember i'm only going to do things that i know i'm going to be interested
in doing i don't have a current interest in black mesa really at all so all i would be doing
was just forcing myself to pretend to be interested in black mesa to stream it you know what i'm
saying like that i don't i don't click with me don't click with me that's just the truth
and i'm gonna be truthful google earth vr is an amazing experience by the way even if you don't
stream it highly suggest you take your own time to look at it yeah that was a big request too
but i mean that's not to say i don't like half life i think it just i'm i have i highly highly
respect the black mesa stuff the half life stuff the half life offshoots wonderful things great
things just not something that i'm interested in i can respect it you know what i'm saying that was
yes i just did like an otter clap that's a backpedal that's not a backpedal i'm not
interested in any black mesa related material otters are cute yes they are lol it's like he
thinks he's the streamer all right you go it's your turn go on get up here let's go i'll be back in
like 10 minutes but thank you precision weed for the five dollars hey germa really enjoying the
streams give up the good work i will try thank you thank you for the five dollars and thanks for the
uh amazing kind thing that you just said thank you uh thank you shino dage for the two dollars
and fifty cents hey germa is the gamer challenge with joel still happening we need to know we need
to figure out a good game to do it i already vetoed uh grounds why do i think the name of that game
is grounds for divorce grounds for what was it called getting over it what where did that come
from getting over it i vetoed that because if i he already has a ton of time and it's not fair
we bet we have to both go in blind to a highly skilled video game that neither one of us have
played and we'll be good to go i'm just gonna figure out which one that is what's the punishment
for the loser the person that would have to take one sip of beer and i'm talking a bud light like
the lightest pea beer you can drink um that's people probably like that drink i'm sorry
that's extra i know people probably so somebody's probably drinking that right now
and i just like i didn't mean to make fun of you i wasn't making fun of you
bud light is fine it's just gross and no human should ever consume it in fact i would not be
i would not be upset at all if they dumped it all
no bud light is fine it's does it's a cold beer which is gonna ban you just drink water
no i'm not gonna be one of those beer elitists didn't tell you elitists that's a really weird
word to say elitists there's tooths in that word i'm not gonna be a beer elitist not one of those
people that says well yeah why are you drinking bud light you idiot no if you like drink what
you like do what you like drink what you like you don't have to let somebody tell you that
you can't drink a bud light because they don't think it's cool who gives a shit what is that
guy drinking well i have a gin and tonic disgusting he's even worse anyways pbr people don't like pbr
people drink pbr it's like oh yeah people drink pbr in my opinion yeah but this is all my opinion
right this is somebody that drinks pbr right so forget about the hair pretend i don't look this
bad imagine this is full of pbr you know people yeah yeah pbr man i love pbr it's so awesome you
got pbr here oh you got it on tap yeah thanks man all right yeah pbr yeah i drink pbr it's
fucking good you know i like it it's like cool and like indie yeah man like you're going to the
bathroom nice man and they dump it in a fucking sink and then they like oh like that's wicked
quick and it comes back and like the person comes back pbr man yeah you want another pbr
the guy comes back hey you want another pbr dude yeah uh yeah uh give me that give me two you know
i mean because i fucking love it so much and they go and they get you two and you have to pretend
to like it pbr is fine it's not a big deal if you drink pbr if you drink bud light you drink pbr
you drink gin and tonic you drink uh you drink like vodka tonic which don't ask me why i don't
know why anybody would put tonic in a drink tonic just it just tastes like throw up it doesn't even
the flavor the quinine's flavor is disgusting it's just adding gross water to your drink if you're
going to do like a vodka tonic just do a vodka soda with a lime why do you put tonic in there
it tastes like stomach acid what does tonic do but make the gross the drink grosser all right if
you like vodka tonic if you like gin and tonic if you like pbr if you like bud light anything that
you like to drink just drink it and like it and don't worry what some asshole like me says you
know making fun of the fact that i don't think pbr tastes very good what you should be drinking
what you should be drinking is gray goose on ice with a splash of soda and a splash of ginger ale
and a lime that's what you should be drinking all right let's move on if you're old enough to drink
do you know what you know what wine i've been hold on i say let me go on cam for this
no why would i do that uh you know i i had i had him this is gonna be very elitist and i can
already smell i can smell it in the chat already i had a malbec the other day it was great malbec
malbec it's fucking fantastic one of the best wines i've ever had it's an argentinian wine it's
fantastic malbec if you're looking for a new red to drink that's what i'm looking for
elitist oh look at me i got my pbr on tap excuse me excuse me do you guys have pbr on tap look at me
you know yeah oh yeah sure yeah we sure do we got pbr on tap just hand tight yeah it's called he
goes to the fucking bathroom he goes to the toilet and like dunks your glass in it and puts it on the
table there's your pbr on tap why did you go in the back room to do that after we got a special
keg back there oh it's in the it's it's in the bathroom you just went into the men's bathroom
yeah oh yep okay that'll be three dollars where the fuck was i on bits i don't remember
no all jokes aside drink what you like like what you drink and don't listen to anybody the whole
point of this whole conversation was you should have been rolling your eyes the whole time
at everything i was just saying well you have your 32 ounce gatorade bottle of pbr thank you
multi trip for the two dollars and 50 cents i'm glad you didn't quit uh h3vr after spending two
hours solving puzzles and fucking around in a dev room you boomer what what do you mean a dev room
oh that's so ridiculous i don't know these things i just like clicked on them people told me to click
on it dev room thank you moldy trip for the 250 that just like brought my voice that killed my
voice it was already shot before thank you dork cube for the 250 seeing your violent reaction to
slamming into virtual walls reminds me when people first saw a motion picture and thought
they were really a train heading towards them you have no idea it is that experience that is
exactly how i could describe that that's this is our version of the old timey train is coming and
people screaming in the movie theater thank you dork you uh thank you great canadian fuck club for
the five dollars and the huge amount of community subs hey germa what do you call a fish with no
eyes i don't know but you gave five more dollars right after that and it's i don't understand oh
there's no i there's no i it's just f h f s h h h h h do what's the best peter griffin impression
you got it yeah no i'm not even gonna let that go far enough for anyone to even cap it and clip it
and embarrass me uh thank you great canadian though for the 10 bucks total commando thanks
to the two dollars and 51 cents two dollars and 51 cents how savage am i chat thank you nate for
the two dollars hey germa so i found out this one last blockbuster video in the entire world
and it's in alaska you should go to your extinct store and make a video in alaska bring my
pamphlet that says that i'm a gamer that one closed well looks like they're all closed
it looks like they're all closed do you hear that looks like they're all closed
closed i'm doing the weird old person teeth whistle thing the one organ is still open
interesting the pamphlet was fake not wasn't it was real hey juno thanks for the three dollars
juno okay germa clear it up once again it's jup as in jup not a jump right yes i don't know how
many times i have to explain this it is the planet's name is jupiter it's not jupiter it's
not the planet jupiter it's jupiter jupiter jupiter jup not jup jup jupiter you find somebody that
calls it jupiter and i will tell you they can use it and say jup how much they want civil war averted
and then i started a new one by talking shit about bud light pbr gin and tonic vodka tonic
you know what fuck it let's just let's let's do the whole let's let's go around the horn um
what are the like alcohols that grows oh heavy beers too like you just you just you're drinking
liquid bread what's wrong with you i'm gonna blend up a loaf of wheat bread and put some water in it
and you can sip on it and like swallow it hard because it's like it takes like four or five
seconds to go down your throat no no okay hold on a minute i have to be careful here i'm gonna be
very careful because saying like heavy beer is bad is like that's grounds for divorce because that's
real beer right that's the real ale now my brother likes uh stuff like guinness we were with a bunch
of friends of his friends and it was the first time we all hung out after 21 and you know they're
all drinking we're all having a fun time we're at a bar and they're all drinking these big
heavy heavy like dark brews you know what i mean big heavy beers and he wanted me to try it and
you know all his friends are like super into beer and i embarrassed him like crazy because i took
one sip and like coughed as if i'd just taken a hit from a cigarette and i was like oh disgusting
and all of his friends just was staring at him like who is this motherfucker that you brought here
by the way that story is not really made the whole thing i'm sorry so i'm a liar uh garfia the monday
killer thank you for the one dollar uh figaro figaro figaro figaro you caught me singing
i actually saw a nice dog today it was really small and i got to give it tons of pets sounds
pretty nice huh the little dude reminded me of auto odo gave it a pet too oh so od anybody germ
keep up the great work and don't stop garping around because you're having a garf time having
a garf time thank you garfield appreciate it glad you saw a good uh little dog today commando thanks
to the 250 here's the black mesa trailer please watch it i don't have to do anything this is vr
this is vr game all right fuck yeah this is that day somebody they made a vr game what do you mean
no that's impossible no no i'm sorry hold on a minute here no i don't want top 10 facts about
half life how did i just have like easter eggs how did i get here what happened what
easter eggs all right i gotta let's try look what i'm trying to tell you is i've been playing vr
exclusively for the last like three or four straight days okay so when i see a trailer
that somebody says no no check it out it's great and i see those hands come down when i see these
hands right there that's a vr game to me sorry all right what else we got looks pretty good
you're still in vr thank you by the way vr josh that i'll make sure i get a chance to say thanks
for giving me the tip so now getting over yard drop to work cool looks looks pretty cool actually
looks pretty cool if you like half life and that shit which is essential he the pbr of video games
that was a joke i'm just kidding this is a fucking joke that's not real i can't i'm not that is an
absolute not true statement just want to make sure that's very clear now that looked really cool
actually but i'm not sure i'll play it what am i trying to do here i'm trying to upset as many
people as possible apparently is this one of those streams yeah let me like prod this way and then
prod that way and you know hey pbr sucks half life like i duck hey half life two is stupid
oh shit that got really bad what am i doing don't ha ha me on my own stream hey uh thank you again
to commando for the trailer for black mesa if i get if i see two to three thousand more ha ha's
over the course of the next six years i'll stop streaming by the way it has to be has to be unique
ips that do it so you only get to do it once so all of you are using it right now thank you
there'll be like 200 just fucking dropping shit yeah unique it's gonna be unique ip sorry you can
do it like 50 times if you want it's not gonna count i'm behind you got multiple ips i have a vpn
you can't catch me you don't think i can i know exactly where you're coming from
sweden right got it thank you moving on hey all of you thanks for the one dollar i'm really upset
today because my family had to sell their hey almost thanks for the good times i'll spell it
out b-e-a-t-e-r jesse you got it thanks for the 250 i got that uh argument already done
thank you for the two dollars fifty cents we got garfield coming back again for one dollar all this
odd bears on wall street talk and germa gets mad when garf talks about things that aren't real
of course it's not real germa i'm a cartoon cat although pookie actually does work on wall street
you know that bear from the garfield comic strips have never even seen it yeah he actually wrestles
bulls on wall street let me let me let you in on a little secret germa some of my bits are actually
are real they just go through a garfield themed filter since i'm garfield of course they would
this is sad poochie reset the universe what does that mean but thank you garfield no you're very
real uh deus mortay thanks for the three dollars hello germy you're my most favorite streamer in
zawab rudo keep it up yours truly muda muda mudo don't thank you uh for the three dollars
dork cube thanks for the two dollars fifty cents here's a fun game to determine your superhero name
what how crazy all right so your first name is your current address of residence your middle
name is the number on the front of your credit card and your last name is your twitch password
what what did you get i'll i'll tell you after you tell me yours that would be a really weird
superhero name now don't tell anybody your address on the internet be careful unless it's like an
amazon order in that case like it's automated thank you lula more for the three dollars germa
will you do an interview for my school about role models what is with everybody wanting to
do interviews with me i've no one ever asked me this before oh this is just kidding i'm 34 and
not in school oh there we go okay i probably should have kept reading i just want to say thank
you again for keeping your spirit up i regularly get excited about your streams and my husband and
kids think i'm weird you're like tgif tv but on twitch love the streams you're a cool guy ps
don't ever meet up with strangers you'll definitely get killed i've i'm tgif tv thank
god it's friday tv i like to know what that is isn't that from like tvs tgif tv what network was
this abc tgif yeah the 18 to 49 demographic for the most of the 1990s tgif is just look okay here
ready okay i'm gonna make a restaurant here i'm gonna i'm gonna bring you to a restaurant
i'm gonna bring you inside that restaurant i'm gonna take you into a booth and you're gonna
order whatever you want on the menu all the brand names are blocked out you don't know what anything
is you just know that you are in a restaurant okay so you order the fish and chips because
it's guaranteed to be on here you eat the fish and chips hey that was like a six to seven out
of ten i guess where are we oh well why don't you step outside and well i'll show you so okay
you're blindfolded at this point now you look you know we just get outside somehow you look at the
sign the sign says tgi fridays you go oh okay that's uh that makes sense okay that's good
and then what you don't know is i dropped the veil this is going nowhere i dropped the veil
in front of the sign out front and it's actually a chili's because they're the same restaurant and
i could have just said that chilies and tgi fridays are the same restaurant there's no
differences you eat blindfolded out of chilies and eat blindfolded at tgi fridays the even the way
that people talk to you is the same what a walk that story was yeah first of all i could yeah i
blindfold you and then you come on in and i sit you know in a restaurant you get the fish and chips
that none of that matters i just gave you like five anime filler episodes for one punch in a
fight scene not even the whole thing i don't ask me what i why i did that but anyways uh thank you
lula appreciate the three bucks and uh kind messages thank you hey tingy i'm getting close
to the end here thank you tingy for the two dollars and 51 cents i found a penny from my last message
it took me a while because canada doesn't use pennies anymore so i had to search for one found
it in some snow after my dog sled went over it and fell to bump while on my way to tim hortons for
a double double is that canada doesn't have pennies anymore they took him out of circulation
yeah okay so you eat it chilies you see you go down you have the fish and chips you're like oh
this is like this fish and chips just you're like crunching it tastes weird this is like really kind
of gross it tastes really off to me and you take a sip and you're like oh that's also off what the
fuck is going on this is disgusting and i take you outside the blindfold still on you i spin you
around i take the blindfold off it says tga fridays or chilies you're like oh tga fridays
i dropped the fucking veil it's pbr you've been eating and drinking pbr that's why you said that
hey commando thanks for the four dollars commando nam i got in a heated argument with my friend
today about what's better halo 2 or call of duty 2 i choose halo 2 and he chose call of duty 2
the worst call of duty world war 2 game of all time um i mean you kind of have to go with halo
2 halo 2 did a lot to define multiplayer shooters it was you know linking up with your friends and
playing it was halo 2 was like the golden eye of that generation of continuing the fps genre
that makes sense right then you're not going to pull my like my my skin off my face and it's
like a pbr under there that's a good point but yeah i'd say call i mean call of duty is
there's just too many of them it's the same thing like i don't understand like
battlefield five came out and what the heck it's not doing it's not selling as well as we wanted
it to just stop making those make a different video game i don't understand so you got battlefield
four battlefield one battlefield five what's next battlefield six i just do a different do something
else but i have an idea let's do battlefield again but star wars just give dice has one of
the best fucking engines in the entire country i'm talking all countries that frostbite engine is
insane get you do a different ip do something else but this time we're gonna put planes in it
i don't get that it was really great fucking battlefield was amazing some of those new
generation battlefields were were so like a real battlefield moment i know what you're talking
about but you don't think it's time to like hang up the battlefield coat and get a new coat you
don't even have to throw it away you can put it in the attic i would love it i would love dice
to do something else i don't know and this is just my this is my just fucking bread opinion
but i feel the same way about call of duty too activision hired three different studios to pump
them out over and over again it's like why don't you just like combine those three studios collective
intelligence quotients and the three of you come up with a fucking new great experience have it
pass around the office does cod still is that still a sell point does cod still sell that much
that you still have the three teams on it does it i don't think i feel like it doesn't it does
but yeah i mean i would love to see the creative people that are behind some of these games
just do something else call it is almost a guaranteed casual shooter pick up
yeah blops four he's been crazy popular maybe i'm just old and fucking out of touch but i
remember well i was about to just grab the mic and scream banjo kazooie into the mic
i was gonna go banjo kazooie when that came out i was gonna scream it good thing i didn't
a lot of talented people in this industry i feel like just making the next jason movie is not
another way to use the resources there but that's just me you know and i can't put the frog though
you know that one uh almost at the end germ is still waiting for half-life three
yeah it'd be nice it'd be cool they pop them up because battlefield and cod makes money and
they're safe yeah i guess turn up the music sonny oh is it low it's not even on you're right money
talks well let's hope that phil spencer after buying like 38 studios maybe they'll make
something together all right where the hell were we just what do they make my own game company
the first thing i'm gonna make is gonna be an ant simulator massive multiplayer you get one life
as a bug you could you could spawn as an ant right everybody's an ant just like a 500 000 people
servers you could do it because the amount of data required for an ant that doesn't do anything
besides eat and walk in your hands can work you could have a million people in that server
and you all have to work towards getting the queen more babies and then you can colonize and
like fight each other you could do it you can level up become like a worker ant and then a
flying ant you could even go as far as you could have like different skill trees like red ant
when you bite somebody it's one point of fire damage per tick for 10 seconds i do consulting
work just give me just give me money and i'll do it just one of these game companies hit me up
i'll take a 15 million dollar check one damage one damage per fire of tick that's worth a lot
i'm getting i'm like i'm i'm in one of those moods i don't know why it popped up after being
out of vr i think it's because i'm like allowed to breathe now when you become a hundred you get
you a queen yeah i can't wait to floss as an ant all right let's just let's do the bit somebody
said something about a penny and then we ended up there no no no it was uh call of duty 2 versus
halo i'd say halo too but that's just me thank you nate for the three dollars hey what about
half-life 2 beta it's freeing us some really good content if you're not going to play free
half-life then buy half-life 1 i want to play half-life why do i have to play half-life
i already played half-life i played half-life 1 i played half-life 2 the motor boat part maybe
almost throw up because i didn't understand what fov was back when i was 19 episode 1 episode 2 i
watched a friend play them i've experienced it but they were great hey oh mew thanks for the two
dollars i really enjoy the stream and you're the only content creator that makes me laugh
uncontrollably sometimes i think you're a hey almost better thank you all mew for the two dollars
thank you yes is online for the 250 uh you've disrespected by gin and tonic and that's
unforgivable gin and tonic is the best drink for casual sipping and hardcore chugging
aviator gin the true chads drink germa gin oh they don't true chads funnel corona true germa
fans drink hot cider smirnoff i remember okay smirnoff was one of those things when you turn
21 and you have no idea what alcohol you should be drinking oh i turned 21 oh what am i going to
give him my first drink um i'll have a smirnoff ice everybody does that and you drink it you're
like yeah i guess it's cool like i just ordered this legally i just like ordered this you want
another one he's asking if i want another uh yeah yeah give me another smirnoff ice
he opens it for you can't even believe it when you're 21 yeah i don't know i don't know the
hell to order and then i my palate got a little better started to actually give a shit about
you know where my alcohol was coming from you know what farm the alcohol was raised on what
it was allowed you know it was free range alcohol i've started to care about those kind of things
and started drinking wine out of a box ass chug why did i read that the one guy you were right
i always just end up reading the one guy this has been fun i've been having this has been fun
thank you commando for the three dollars i drink chocolate milk every day i've been drinking it
since 2007 four years after i was born hold on wait doctors say that two percent of my blood is
chocolate milk 2007 four years after his what thank you for three dollars don't drink chocolate
milk every day it's too much sugary substances drinking almond milk it's better for you right
here i go here i go um i'm walking in the starbucks right now and i've got the glasses on and i've got
my hairstyle that way let's see what i mean look it's already there you drink cow's milk yeah the
like starbucks elitist almond milk user is here room here that that guy's multi-trip your band
for at least 600 streams have i even done shave okay no i will thank you for saying that now i'm
gonna grow it up for like three years i'm not gonna shave again that one guy said shave in
all capitals no i'm not gonna shave for three years no no cream in your coffee milk in your
coffee almond milk i don't really like soy milk i don't think that doesn't taste very good tastes
like it's made out of plastic that's just what i think coconut milk is a little i don't like it
tastes like coconut flakes rice milk is too watery almond milk sits right in a perfect place for me
plus i can't really eat that i can't have that much dairy just drink water
you can't put water in your coffee oh yeah what am i gonna put in my coffee to make it a little
you know maybe give it a little a little substance how about some more water
what what other thing can i fucking like bring up and and talk about how i don't like it
no i like regular milk i just can't drink it drink put some pbr in it
but thank you shawnee noodles for the five dollars can you play mountain blade warband
the game of thrones mod is a joke for a couple hours before the new season premieres as a joke
stream well i maybe i haven't ruled it out what do you mean i haven't ruled it out you just brought
up the suggestion you know i haven't ruled that out i just was able to rule it in by you saying
that but thank you shawnee noodles uh mr phrase year thank you mr phrase year for the 10 bucks
just want to say that i appreciate all your content you put out since the early days of
putting around in tf2 you remain consistently entertaining and intelligent
for so long that i can't do anything but aspire to be as driven as you
that's a incredibly nice thing to say about somebody i mean come on i know what market cap is
i know where all the continents are huh 5g tower have i heard of them 5g yeah that's the new it's
3g 4g lte 5g lte it's coming how many continents are there just enough for people to live on them
but no i that's uh mr frazier thank you so much for the 10 bucks i i'm happy that
i could potentially inspire somebody to do something to care about something regardless
of what it is thank you for the 10 bucks uh then we also had commando came in with 250 sorry i
accidentally pressed enter i guess you could say i'm a chocolate milk man chocolate milk i missed
the days where you could get chocolate milk delivered to your house in the bottles you know
the guy that comes to your door that was dressed like a doctor for some reason what was with that
outfit it was like a doctor taxi cab driver you were a lie for those no i'm just saying i missed
that opportunity have the guy like that's the sound but when the you know you didn't even see
what i did it's the milk in the grate that he's carrying uh thank you sten fisken for the 10 bucks
hey man been following your content for a while now just want to give back for all the amazing
entertainment hope to see a lot of cool skits and minus two jokes keep it up well you're guaranteed
to get at least a few of those per string guarantee but thanks for being around for a while
and thank you for the 10 dollars means a lot uh rembo thanks for the 250 i wore my new germanite
sky shirt to work today two people came up to me to say it was a nice shirt it's fucking mint
it's a very nice shirt i'd say one of the best yeah thank you for purchasing it thank you for
wearing it thank you for thinking it's cool hey toshiro.tv thanks for the 250 i was planning on
stopping by hash house when i'm in vegas since you said you had the best burger you've ever had
uh do you remember what it was uh let me tell you something hash house gogo is like the best
restaurant in vegas if you ever find yourself at the link go to hash house and get anything on
that menu that place is ridiculous absolutely ridiculous you can say sponsored all you want
that's the best fucking food i've probably ever had in my life uh the burger i had it was a i
believe it was a blue cheese spread on the burger it was huge the meat was cooked and squashed up
and smashed up perfectly plenty of good condiments on it was big what kind of food it is just
like big portion comfort food they have burgers they have like meatloaf sandwiches they've got
fried chicken and they've got waffles they've got so much they've got a um they've got like a
chorizo hash you will eat a piece of that chorizo hash and then you will just lie back and go
everything is fine everything on earth is fine great canadian fuck club gave 50 dollars to
say i'm willing to die on this jump hill 50 bucks to unfortunately unfortunately be incorrect
but thank you so much for the 50 dollars in your astronomical insane contributions over the last
like four months of the streams thank you but hash house ago go everyone asks so what you've
been at vegas for a while favorite spot that's definitely it the one that's in the link he's
given he's he's responsible for thousands of dollars it's unbelievable thank you but yeah um
toshiro hope you enjoy it a lot of good stuff a lot of cool stuff to see a lot of amazing
restaurants if you're visiting vegas and you've ever been here you are going to have a great time
snowing in las vegas yeah it's been snowing in random places it's like the first time it's
happened in a long time apparently there's no one here that's fucking ridiculous snow in las vegas
accumulating snow in las vegas jerma brought the snow to vegas yeah that's something i never
thought i'd ever see how much snow is on the ground it's alex i mean we did you get a chance
to go out there because that's crazy that's crazy like an inch or more wow yeah if it snows even a
dusting out here the whole state goes into a like a meltdown mode because you don't have any way to
deal with that they don't ever get it that's insane uh but thank you great canadian fuck club
for you fifty dollars and your ten dollars here they say it's okay to be wrong
girma but it's definitely jump jump it's not it's not chopper it's the name of a planet scientists
came together and named that planet jupiter the one guy in the back that said we should name it
jupiter they fucking handed that guy his books and they fired his ass fifty dollars from great
canadian fifty dollars to admit i'm right now money does not come above principles okay thank
you for the 110 dollars money does not come above principle and therefore jupiter jup you can pay
you can pay me 50 000 more dollars and i would still say jup i've got my integrity see underneath
this pbr t-shirt that i'm wearing my pbr themed wristbands that i wear every day there's integrity
under here here comes that's the 50 000 bait but thank you so much dude that's too much money
too much money you spoil me you flatter me thank you hey nate thanks for the three dollars nate
somebody handcrafted their own blockbuster video sign for 13 bucks on ebay you should get it
where the hell am i gonna put that i'm just gonna hang that out my front door that would end up in
a closet and i would never take it out uh get half life for dreamcast it's not that hard
half life for dream but i've already beat i've already played what's with the half life
get half life for dreamcast it's not hard why is there no forehead here after this
half life is a great game i've i've beat half life on the computer probably two or three times
the dreamcast is not going to give me anything more than than that they're desperate to get
you to play halfway i don't i've already done it i've done it i've already done this thing
that you are so so hell bent on telling me to do i can understand if it was like hey get a
you should get bloodborne ah maybe one day i've never played it before though maybe one day
dude get bloodborne nah maybe i don't think so no it's like hey you should get bloodborne i love
bloodborne it's a great game i've played it a bunch you gotta get bloodborne though i i love
that game it's a very very good game i've i've played it have you played bloodborne yet though
yeah i've yes i have just played bloodborne already when when is this guy even going to
get bloodborne but in all seriousness no i forgot that half life did come out on dreamcast did it
come out in anything else the old hunters that is an amazing dlc was it on ps2 right yes um i
i love half life but i'm not gonna play it on the dreamcast thank you though hey commando thanks
for the three dollars there was an ending to the trailer d oh no he did this he's all right thank
you jess you got it for the one dollar it's a youtube link and it's probably a gnome
oh it's close enough same two letters thank you moo means moo for the five dollars half life more
like mad wife ha ha karen let me see those kids i miss them what the fuck uh thank you
thank you move for five bucks hey axie and thanks for the one dollar hey germa i made the news
bloopers video like you predicted a few streams ago i would be really happy if you showed it to
the stream just type in german news bloopers on youtube in the first link sorry i'm not a sub
what did i just say german news bloopers on youtube oh i can't i don't see it
germa type in okay there it is yeah sure why not let's watch it don't look at that that's
personal info on there don't look at that never mind all right so i've got my trusty stopwatch
and here they come down the hill it looks like rubin is in the lead and here comes out and this
that was a bad idea i look at the dew point in the area right now right now dew points in the
20s and near 30 degrees across central mississippi
well hey there so as you see here it's gonna be wow well we've got a little bit of uh interesting
things going on right now whoa take a look at what's going on right now you want to point out
the weather right now gotta tell you festival is gonna be canceled because oh no is he running out
of gas oh he's stopping at like that minimart kind of thing at that gas station he's getting
out of the car interesting okay well at least we saw the car door open maybe he's letting
us pass okay that was at the yeah that was the driver's side looks like he's wearing a different
shirt i feel like he was wearing a blue shirt before we will get our pick there we go i don't
know if the passenger uh got out of the vehicle it didn't look like it colin but it's hard to say
now my eyes were on that driver's side so now bruce what would they do here if he's pulled
he's he's pulled into this oh dear we might have the wrong car colin
i thought that was me for a second
that worries them but at this point if you haven't left those people naked
the chicago tribune 19 people were hospitalized at a furry convention in illinois
after being called an intentional lake of chlorine what's a furry what did i get that relief there
okay officials were called when i strong over chlorines what spread
i think they had to evacuate the building and everything set the hotel guests along
with convention attendees into the cold night many still dressed in their furry furry costumes
the police officer was trying to pull his fool over
when he got out of the car and started to run well he didn't get very far i wonder if the car gets
like an assist you know what i mean it's for the takedown for the takeout like you should have been
driving me anyway central indiana had a couple of showers
i told you not to throw it
did you see that the pass through right there was perfect and i think
yeah i think we do we do have his description can we take that let's take his description
okay this is the guy there uh they wanted they wanted people in pennsylvania to be out on the
lookout for he's got uh he's got a nose and some hair that goes like that it's got kind of a
chin that comes down to a almost a point stands about five feet four inches tall oh come on
there it is get a good look for yourself you had to have that one and now i'm getting word that
police actually caught this guy thanks to the sketch no doubt so here's a picture of the real
guy next to the sketch that led to his arrest it's uncanny lisa oh this is the same one you
have to do it twice it's fucking ridiculous that was fantastic link link hey i'll get you link
that was really really good job well done i look forward to when you do it again because of that
end there play league of legends termo i can't do that as i won't do that i'm sorry i'm sorry
you might be like a big fan of that game i just i i can't i can't do it but thank you so much
for that video uh that was axion thank you axion hey dobski dude thanks for the one dollar taught
me about being the streamer all you like but i need to remind you that long before the movie night
stream you played my videos live for precisely three minutes in total meaning i was the streamer
i held the keys to the kingdom i was a god and yes i'll totally take your stream when you retire
uh but the bit minimum will be 50 and sub mode will be on permanently so get ready it's not a
bad idea my strength you wouldn't dare no i can't think of that you know okay do you know how many
funny fucking things that i've seen in this chat from a non-sub seen plenty of great things from
subs but there are at least five or six in the last 12 years that i've been streaming on twitch
i was a back it went up justin tv i was streaming me multi-boxing warcraft that's how i've been
around for a long time remember i was the guy with like the fucking orc multi-boxing i used to like
raid i used to raid ogre mar i used to raid stormin by myself wild you probably remember
me from the service yeah i was there for those streams see yeah you remember some people
remember that i had like three viewers i was all of them see get him out get him out all right
here we go thank you depth skiddo for the one dollar hey commando nam thanks for the three
dollars and 50 cents so uh jeremy i watch an old stream and you're telling me you never played
a original xbox game mecha salt conquer live reloaded none of that that sucks man hey when
do you get hey when you do get an original xbox you better connect it to x-link um
original i didn't have an original xbox i've played it a few times i've friends of mine had it i've
played halo halo 2 you know better than call of duty 2 if it was me giving my opinion on that
i think that'd be better than call of duty 2 but conquer yeah i remember the original conquer for
n64 what a game but yeah that may be one day i got a lot of old console stuff to go through already
but thank you hey something i wrote a thanks for the 250 remember that film being john malcovich
if that ever got a spiritual successor i think you would be perfect to take on the prophylic role
of having people walk into your brain i would do it sign me up i would give it i would give that
role everything i had everything hey commando thanks for the two dollars and 51 cents if you
do get an original xbox get the duke controller if you have big hands i do they're huge if not
get a logitech controller which is wireless and get an hdmi cord instead of the original
i think italics was talking about maybe getting an old xbox i will definitely
pass that info along big meaty claws yeah i get big fucking hands man looking when you grab a door
handle when i grab a door handle my fingers go all the way around and touch the back of my hand
they're huge they're big mittens i got like baseball gloves on both hands uh but thank you
commando for the three dollars again here you never played half-life opposing force and blue
shift i did i did play blue shift with barney you start off you walk around he talks to you for a
little while you go over the you're a police officer i've played it what is it with that
but i'm getting i'm getting half-life i played opposing force i have long time ago very long
time ago don't read this message too late hey deus morta thanks for the 250 fun fact to you
i heard if you feel a heard if you feed a bee a turnip its honey will be sweeter i'm a professional
you can trust me i don't trust anything that you just said that sounds like something that
would be shared on a 55 year old lady's facebook but i do appreciate it what it's a that's a that's
a bj joke what how how does where are you getting that from ban what am i doing ban all right all
right all right all right settle down let's hit the brakes a little thank you nate for the three
dollars it's another half-life question i'm just gonna put a blanket statement under i'm never
gonna play a half-life game on stream ever so there's no half-life game that i'm gonna play
on this stream i'm not gonna play half-life it's fucking wonderful series am i getting trolled
at this point are we getting like am i getting bit baited like somebody just said i have to be
have you played half-life grunt and half-life paranoia i don't even know what those are
play half-life it's been years where's toontown you can't even play toontown it got taken off the
air but thank you for the uh the incredibly high interest in the game franchise half-life
and also nate thanks for the five bucks you also probably never heard of this but gta 4
finally got an update last year they've removed songs on the car radio really that's interesting
so what had you what happens in the radio in the game now it's weird the music license expired
that's it's interesting they just aren't there hey commando thanks for the four dollars commando
i mean during my blood is two percent chocolate milk so i'm gonna be a hyper every day
okay just do me a favor replace replace like two of those chocolate milks you drink a day
with water and one other one that you drink a day with just what with one big cabot you know
what i mean just that's all i ask just crunch on a cabot and you'll be fine place it with a pvr
no no don't do that either a carrot a carrot a carrot carrot uh commando thank you commander
nam for the four dollars oh i know what he's talking about here's the link it's an etsy page
you guys are working together on this you guys are you guys the same are you guys the same person
it's an etsy link to uh to a half life you're trying to get me to buy something off your etsy
this feels coordinated it's a drinking game every drinking every time you say the word half life
uh chat is three people i like a german doesn't realize that all those viewers are me on different
accounts don't believe me watch me post this on my other accounts no what what the fuck are you
talking about that doesn't make any sense hold on am i live what the fuck i mean i can think
i'm going to contact twitch about that because this i didn't know yeah somebody's got somebody's
got a hold of me i think otherwise i mean what's my name on twitch shirma nine eight is another
number it's four it's weird i don't know i understand that's weird because i feel like
that i shouldn't uh because i'm me getting to the end here we got only a few more thank you
commando thanks for the four dollars i can mail you mine i have all the accessories in games
i do not want you to mail me a copy of half life for the dreamcast oh by the way i do own
ed ed and eddie i bought it i got ed ed and eddie can we can we can we put the half life thing to
bed can we can we like cease the half life he owns i own all three eds play half life opposing eds
so it's a great series half life is a wonderful series it truly is okay i love how vr josh
just wrote that copy pasta it's like you're very clearly vr josh you're not that guy
don't believe me when are you gonna tell us about the status of clown in the town would you
all right things are going too fast here hold on i i missed one hold on uh commando thanks
for the four dollars well germa i'm not i'm not what not what what are you done well thank you
nonetheless for the four dollars appreciate it uh superman thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents
halo reach was by far the best halo game i've ever played i remember having so much fun with
my friends and the campaign and story were amazing i love that game so much and nothing
will compare to it during its peak halo reach i don't think i've ever played halo reach
was it good halo reach is more like halo peach what does that mean how long has it been since
you had a sip of water i don't know a few days hey nut uh thank you nut for the four dollars
uh would you ever consider pastoring a wedding uh if found have uh and if if you say yes i'll
book a flight right now into vegas immediately no no it's all right thank you for the four dollars
thank you commando for the three bucks halo reach sucks it doesn't have halo 2's smg
now be careful those are fighting words thank you commando three dollars thank you deus more
tape for the two dollars and 50 cents so i was out of chilies my friend told me about this new
restaurant called tj fridays i took a sip of my pbr and said we should go there after i finished
my project on why half life's the greatest video game ever my friend said perfect he'll invite his
canadian friend to jump her meme collage that is what that was uh laying that thanks with the
five dollars if we keep donating he will have to stay live i mean well we're at the end now
well now we got commando three dollars and 50 cents well germa tell me this did you know that
you can play an original xbox game on the ps2 i did not know that i was unaware great canadian
fuck club just gave another 50 dollars what you guys know no the stream is ending the stream's
over now thank you great canadian for the 50 dollars you want to fucking bet you won't you'll
crack at 200 i'm not gonna crack uh nate gave 16 dollars moo means moo thanks for five dollars
jack um dumb jack uh jack uh thanks for the 10 dollars not thanks for the four dollars have i
played super wizard thanks for the one dollar germa how many seconds of parmesan cheese do
you like on your spaghetti and meatballs until they've run out that's a little little tip that
you guys don't know when that guy comes over with the little thing and goes you have to tell them
to stop i sit there until they have no more in the device and i stare at their eyes and then i say
i'm just getting in i like i pick up the mound of cheese and like put it out i say hey let me see
your hand and i put it back in his hands and i go haha and then like this there's like 15 other
people at the fucking table where i like slapping five and laughing and like there's nine people
with their fucking cell phone cameras all getting it that's how funny my god stop giving me money
stop giving me money to say this another 50 dollars from great canadian fuck club
please crack paypal keeps calling me whenever i try to buy bits no stop it stop this cry cry cry cry
it's jupiter jupiter jupiter jupiter let's go to jupiter let's get on a rocket let's get on a plane
and let's go to jupiter thank you for the fucking hundreds of dollars steal the china steal the
china uh but thank you jack for the 10 bucks finish i spy spooky mansion i already beat it
uh snuts or thanks for the one dollar this isn't funhouse i know i don't think it is thank you
commando for the eight dollars here total on the original xbox you can save your own songs like a
gorilla song like every song do you know do you like led zeppelin i've heard plenty of led zeppelin
songs crack the streamer incorrect pronunciation hey horse horse dog lime thanks for the one
dollars they say haha they're doing the uh crime g-mode i've refused to say it commando thanks
for the four dollars no germy you have to touch you have to you have the touch to end it all to
do it i just have to hit the stop stream but i'm not gonna do that let's run the credits
speaking of which let's run them right now it's fucking like goblin hey yes sir yes run the credits
random god here come the credits oh no start them over there's a shitload of people roll
them again thank you thank you all the new subs all the yellow subs you guys are fucking awesome
thank you so much for your f word as an adjective and s word as a verb hey multi trip thanks for the
two dollars and fifty cents chop wizard ribbon thanks for the one dollar germa if you end the
stream then i'll be sick and bored i'll be back in a couple days and then we're gonna go one two
three days in a row you got me three days in a row hey i did three days in a row as of you know
the day before yesterday gonna go three days in a row again you got me for three days in a row
hey commando thanks for the four dollars germy you ended the half-life battle in the bits world
oh my there was no half-life battle commando thanks for three dollars my life sucks germa please keep
going no all right all right this is just having a slow down i hope you can figure out what's going
on there was no half-life war i was just kidding around half-life is an amazing series i was i was
just messing around when i talked about half-life being like pbr we're just messing around we're
messing around a lot on this stream just want to make sure you know just kidding around hey wizard
ribbon thanks for the one dollar come on man i just need this fix i'm good for it i swear
you paid me oh right to keep this freedom going uh thank you multi trip for the 250 your like pbr
you take that back now if you don't if i don't get a a apology in the chat right now
then i'll i ain't gonna i'll then i'll only stream for one day ever we're talking about like this is
it hey maybe if you say sorry maybe staff he said sorry say sir oh this is the last stream i'll ever
do look at this guy look at that guy hey look at the look at them does your mom know you like pbr
yes we all drink it as a fucking family it's the only thing the fridge you got orange juice in your
bridge we got pbr in our orange juice containers hey great canadian fuck club thanks for the 15
dollars he says jump i will say if you want it whatever you want to call it jump that's fine if
you want to call it that i call it jup because the name of the planet is jupiter that's what how i
call it if you want i mean you probably have an accent right like a Jupiter like oh he Jupiter
if you have an accent of course you're going to say it a different way thank you nut for the
two dollars there is legit nothing wrong with my name say it your name is nut a b c d e f g
uh dog cat uh train tracks on my uh story of david aglaya uh two two two four four four duncan
donuts duncan donuts lips i can't say that in sequence and i would get in trouble he's broken
i was in vr for five straight hours okay i got marbles up here that need to be recalibrated i
got to re-rack the balls and pull uh commando thanks for the nine dollars and 48 cents
uh listen these are my last bits just tell me that you'll let me send my old xbox to you please
it's free please i'll mail the entire thing to you okay bye have a great night i'm i'm not going
to give you my address um that's not going to happen what yeah i wonder why let me think of
some reasons why i wouldn't want to have my address given to somebody you think five hours
is a lot there's a guy that's spending a week in vr well i i applaud his eventual eye doctor
that he would be giving lots of money to he's asleep oh
okay but no thank i really appreciate the fact that you want to give me your xbox
it's not necessary you don't have to do that keep it it's yours you're going to need it one day
because you're going to want to play something one day and i i do not give a personal information
to people that i do not know that's it uh thank you wizard ribbit for the one dollar jerma has
anyone even told you you're very handsome goblin no you're the first one uh thank you nut for the
two dollars please someone crop that sequence into nut blank blank blank we're not lewd on
this stream we're pg-13 thank you snot sore for the one dollar it'd be funny if you had a guitar
stream but you played half-life instead maybe i let my children watch this stream they've learned
so much like one two three four five let's say you get from one to five no all kidding aside
we've been having a lot of fun this stream we've been talking a lot of shit just dicking around
please no it's all in good fun don't take anything i say personally really hope you don't
and that's where we're gonna end it so i will see you guys on friday so not today which is thursday
i'll see you on friday i'm gonna go friday saturday sunday we're gonna do the whole weekend
and that will lead us into the end of february and i'll see you guys soon i'm gonna go take a
look at the snow in las vegas because that's ridiculous have a great day have a great night
i'll see you guys really soon we can take a break from vr i will return to it next week
and much love to y'all thanks for hanging out see you really soon