If that scumbag thinks he can take us on, if he thinks he's going to destroy our will and take down our pride, he has no idea what he's dealing with.
Sergeant Truffletop, you are my leader of the command unit. You must take it forward and you must find him and destroy him.
Puffleduffle, say hello to the missus for me.
But of course, who could forget you?
Ha ha ha ha. Bill Bowbaggins. Copyrighted character that I've just said.
Alright, when you're done with this joke, explain to me if there is anything else we can build.
Besides these drones. Forever.
And you, Anthony Wimblestein, you have been my number one companion ever since we were two. Remember we had that birthday cake that time? Remember we shared that birthday cake?
You have to meet me in the middle, like diplomats come forward.
Alright, so diplomats come forward, I meet you in the middle.
So stop having them following you.
They're not close enough. I'm not comfortable unless they're close enough.
They're going to start shooting.
No they're not. See, alright. Stop.
They're not stopping.
How do you make them stop?
Was there a wait? There's no wait.
Where are you?
I'm with my executive right now.
Oh, I see you walking.
I'm coming up on a secret mission.
This looks so stupid to watch you run.
What an insignificant little like shit you are right now.
I zoom out to like the normal view and it's like there's an ant coming to get me.
In this?
Yeah.
Stop building me hallways.
It's going to take me too long to get around this.
Just get inside of it.
This is never going to happen if you keep building sections.
You fucking dick.
This is going to take, you just added like ten minutes to my trip.
Alright, there you go.
Oh my god.
Well, okay.
Alright, here I come.
This is so funny that you could do this.
I'm coming to your corporation right now.
This is a gun in my hand.
Oh yeah, she wanted to see me.
No, no, no. Put the gun down.
I can't put the gun down.
Put the gun down.
You have like this shitty douche smirk on.
Like yeah, I'm going to shoot you.
Yeah, you think you got me in this.
What does your screen say?
CEO neutral login screen.
Why?
What did I do?
I got startled.
I got scared. I thought you were trying to kill me.
I went back, I sat down at the computer again.
But I thought you were using like telekinetic powers to try to kill me.
Your executive is dead.
What?
This person's not alive.
They're just not alive.
No, you're dead.
You guys are not even breathing.
You're just sitting there as a corpse.
Easy, easy, easy.
Why are you in here?
Your guy's face is so fucked up.
One of his eyes is open and one of them is closed.
You are deep in thought right now.
That thing has taken over.
You've done that too many times.
You know what I mean?
You've done this so many times.
You shouldn't be doing this anymore.
Where the hell did you go?
This is rough.
I have to do one more thing before I head out.
I have one more thing I need to do.
No!
What is going on?
Why is there an organ playing?
Don't look over here.
Whatever you do, for the next minute, do not look over here.
Did you just make a unit that is playing an organ of death?
No.
You can turn around in 10 seconds
and notice that there's a monster behind you.
Really?
Yeah.
So you're telling me in 10 seconds I can turn around?
I would turn now.
Turn now.
You can't stop me.
He thinks he's so big.
He thinks he's so goddamn strong.
Do you think he's strong enough to take on the march of the C-3PO's?
I doubt it.
Oh shit.
This is a jack in the box.
Yeah, we built some hinges on our warehouse.
Hey, what are you doing over there?
Nothing much.
I'm just coming over here to kill you.
Yeah, that's fine. Just get over right here and stand right there.
Right over there?
Yeah, stand over right there.
What a waste of 500 billion dollars.
My grandfather told me
this is the button you press
when you know you've been defeated.
The final stand.
Activate it!
Let him come.
They killed themselves.
What is this guy?
I didn't.
I won.
Well, how did you get out there?
Help.
Let me in.
I'm gonna let you in. Just be careful.
How did you get stuck out there?
He wanted to discuss something.
What did you want to discuss?
We're a military compound.
Not too far away.
You've been...
What did I do again?
You know what? It doesn't matter.
We were playing for two hours.
Two fucking hours of this!
What the hell have we been doing?