Hello, disc. Look at all these discs. One disc, two discs, three discs. Good afternoon, everybody.
How are you? Let me move this. What's with all the love and chat? What do you mean? You should be
saying I'm so glad to see love and chat every day. What are you saying? That shouldn't be a rarity.
My personal pizza. But uh, how you doing? We're gonna pick up right where we were last night
with space channel five, part five. Uh, no, part two, part two. Why do I have to stream so late?
Why are you late? So here's new year, new thing. Uh, I'm going to stop putting times in the sus
command because I feel like people start to get a little frustrated. Uh, I thought me saying I have
no schedule and I have no, uh, days planned. I thought that I was going to be able to kind of
blanket statement, say that I don't have a schedule anymore, but the sus is there to give like
guidelines. And I think some people are getting annoyed because the sus will count down to zero
as if like that's a TV channel and that's when the show starts. And that's not what I've been doing.
So what I'm probably going to end up doing is just the sus command will end up just being
a guideline for the day and the, the, the time period. So like for instance, if a stream is
starting tomorrow, uh, tomorrow afternoon, right? Pacific. Cause I, I feel like I don't want to
start to cause a problem where people are sitting here waiting for a stream to start and it's like,
oh, wait, didn't he say he was going to stream today? Yeah, he did. When, when, oh, the, oh,
the sus says like four 25 PM. So yeah, that's when it's going to start, right? I, that I would,
I don't blame you for thinking that, but I think it's for the best to just have the sus command
give the day and a general time period. Every stream is always going to be between three and
between like two 30 and four PM Pacific every single time, unless there's some kind of, uh,
extreme other reason why there's no stream there, but you can't really put in a sus command.
There's a stream starting between two 30 and four, four 30 PM percent. You can't have this.
That would be, that's like, that's like, I would be like the fucking repair man. I would be like
the guy, I'd be like the fucking dishwasher delivery man giving you a window. Oh yeah,
so this is German industries. What time does stream start? Uh, well, uh, you know, the,
the technician will be there between 12 and five, like, oh, okay. So we're just going to start giving,
um, essentially periods. So like tomorrow afternoon Pacific, but just know that all these
streams will always start somewhere around two to four PM Pacific. I don't want to start,
I don't want to get the hard exact times anymore. Just, I feel like it's causing a problem and not
really a problem, but I feel like it's causing, um, a lot of distress for not for some of you guys,
but me too, because I'll look over at the sus and it's like, oh, fucking hell. It's what,
what is it? Like I got to start in four minutes. I got to party the fuck up like
down. Okay. Wait, is that thing ready? So I'll be asked over here. Shit. Wait, why did I just
eat? I shouldn't have eaten. I should have just weighed. I should have eight, like four hours
from now. It's, it's counterproductive. That's what I'm saying. So I think it's a good change.
Derma, it's a joke. No, no, no, no. I, but I know it is, but it isn't though, because your time is
valuable too, right? It's not all about me. So if some of you guys have been here for, you know,
30, 40 minutes, your time is valuable. And I don't want you to have ever have a thought in
your head that like, oh, he's a fucking asshole. Said he was going to be here at like 3 15 fucking
idiot. Cause I mean that that's, I don't want to leave you hanging. So, so I think given a general
idea, so then people can be like, oh yeah, that's like, that's starting like probably like with the
next hour or so I can be like, I don't have to like sit here and like, you know, he's supposed
to be here. You know, your time is valuable. But anyways, don't need to read this, but thank you
so much for your streams. They're really helpful for these tough times. Thank you so much,
Mupine. It's just a joke. No, but even if it is just a joke, I know that it's like just,
I know it's comedy, but where the fuck is my phone? God, I changed the sus to like five. I
don't know where the phone is. I can't even make a tweet about this frame. Did I tweet this frame
already? I don't think so. Whatever. I have no idea. Anywho, uh, space channel five is where we
left off. Good job. Don't even read this to the same number of streams. My family works on a farm
and as you know, the economy has been tough this week. We all had to sell our hay beater. So I
want to thank you. Nice. Is that what this was? Was just a copy paste thing? That can't be what
this was. Whatever. All right. So let's go. Twitch notifications are broken. Uh, god damn it. Let's
just wait. Wait, I gotta get my phone. Twitch notifications actually broken. Do I have to
actually tweet that? Do I need to get my phone? Oh god damn it. One guy said yup. So yup, yup,
yup, yup, yup. Oh god. Hold on. I'll be right back. Not even two. I'm just gonna sprint down
the stairs as fast as I can. Okay. That was the fastest I think I may have ever ran. Not even
winded at all. Like my breath is perfectly controlled. Okay. So space channel. Let me
save it. Presented by Sega there. How's that audio look? Looks pretty good. Wait, wait, what?
That you guys, you can't make the hay thing. Copy pasta thing. You can't, no.
That's a compounded reference. All right, let's fucking go. Open it up. Hey, a hay beater. A
hay beater. Did we even launch this cutscene? I don't think we did. All right, let's beat it.
Is that Michael Jackson? No, that's the bad guy. That's the bad. That was Michael Jackson right
there. The best part about this is when Michael Jackson keeps calling her Eulayla. Let's go
Eulayla. Eulala. Quiet game? No, you just think it's quiet. It's actually not that quiet. You
just think it is. How's that? Okay, I gotta remember where we were. I'm gonna have to do
like a practice run because I was locked in last night. I think I'm gonna do level one again just
to get back into flow because we're going right to like report five. Try to do a perfect. I don't
think I'm ever gonna, I can't do that shit. We already saw this. We already saw this too.
What the hell is this? Oh, people have no idea that we're here last night.
This is Space Channel 5. It is a Simon Says game where you have to save the god damn it.
Those of you that also were not here last night. This game has a problem where
models just don't show up. That's a good indicator of what's gonna happen once we're started.
It's very random. Now I'm gonna load it up. It's gonna be in Japanese. Watch.
I bet you, I bet you a dollar. He bet all of us a dollar. No, no, no, no, no. I bet
uh Kim a dollar. Let's see. Give us models. Yes. So like I was explaining before,
I had an epic rage quit. It is a Simon Says game where you have to match and do exactly what they
tell you. There are no on-screen prompts. You just have to remember what everybody said.
That's ooh la la. So I have to do what they do. Can I get like 100%?
Let's see if I can get 100%. When is the Dreamcast arc gonna be over? Today. This is pretty much it.
Okay, uh Seaman is not going to be part of Dreamcast. It's going to have to show up.
I wasn't paying any attention at all. I think it was left, right? I wasn't even
watching the game. I was answering a question. It don't matter. I'm just doing this to practice.
Down, chew, chew. See the one part about this game that is uh I'm sure you've heard very evident.
I can't talk. I can't interact. This is just a silent gameplay.
Even okay even moving any of my facial tissue screws me up. If I like close one eye or like
wiggle my nose, I won't be able to do the level. I have to wide open eyes. Quiet. Staring and press
button. Can you hear the gun? So you're not gonna get me like Dunkin Donuts drive through
stories right now. Maybe later. I think I'm ready. The B is you rescue. You have to shoot and rescue.
Tell a story over riot. I can't. You know how hard that's gonna be for me to do that?
It's gonna be a handful of adjectives. I'm not gonna tell anything. I'm gonna go around in an
adjective circle. Okay so three days ago I went to this already over already done. Not gonna happen.
Quit reading chat. The level the levels get I'm just gonna pause whenever I have anything to say.
The levels get progressively more difficult and more elaborate. So okay let's start. Let's do it
again. Uh this is statistically by the way one of the most rage quit games in video game history
if you were questioned. Look it up. Especially level five. There's a portion where those you're
gonna go up down up down left right up down right left up down down down down that's where everybody
rage quits the game. I stayed and I was able to get past it. Oh I just found out by the way
they're making a vr version of this game. If not this one it's gonna be a new one entirely I believe.
That's exciting. Oh nice. Take best of me again. The hardware note is not. This is on steam.
You can play this right now on steam. The dreamcast collection is uh I mean like
Sega bass fishing is cool for five minutes. It's not much there other than like a potential 10
20 minute session unless you really want to try to 100% the game. Just buy the good ones.
If you buy them all alone the good ones. Is it worth just buying the pack? Isn't the pack uh
cheaper? It's like eight bucks by itself. Wear space michael. Uh don't worry space michael is
available. I'm just warming up because I'm not just gonna jump right into the hardest levels in the
game. It's gonna be horrible. That's good. I need to get less than all right I'm gonna get higher than
67 percent. Down. I gotta like fucking get up and shake my body to like get pumped up so I can do
this. I'm still on slow. Down down. Was it up? Oh my god. I gotta get up and fucking shake my body.
I'm slower than I was yesterday. Okay um I'm gonna get up and shake as fucking hard as I can in a
circle. I beat this. I beat this literally with my eyes closed yesterday. I went to sleep. I woke up.
I'm on like a two or three day gamer cooldown apparently. Hold on. I gotta fucking get up and
shake around. I gotta put like a fucking pair of clothes on though. I'm in like pajamas. Hold on.
I guess I just wear pajamas. What's the fucking camera? You know what this is gonna be embarrassing.
I had to just put this on real quick. I put it there specifically in case I needed it.
I haven't shaved either. I said I was gonna do that. All right so all right that's that's enough.
I think that was enough. I just like saw a spider on the ground. That's not warming up. Okay let's
go up in the air here. This way. That way. I'll spin around once. I feel worse. Like way worse.
How about if I do I have any fruits? Do I don't think don't have any fruit?
There are no sweat stains here. This is a I just put this on. Do you understand?
There's nothing here. There are no sweat stains. I'm certain of that. You know why I know that I'm
certain of that? Because this shirt has only been worn like three times. I don't wear this in public.
You know I'll tell you why I don't wear it in public. We may have talked about it before.
Number one reason why I don't wear this in public is the same reason why a doctor
doesn't wear his lab coat out when he goes to get like food. You know it's like I'm hey that's me.
I'm a doctor. I don't hey if you see go to that hospital I'll treat you. Nah the same
reason why a doctor don't wear a doctor's outfit. Tape over the logo. Not the same thing?
It's the exact same thing. It's the exact same thing. All right preparing a streamer to a doctor.
Guys I really don't want to make you feel like potentially that you don't know this.
Um there are a lot of streamers and a lot of youtubers that make more money than some of the
best surgeons in the world and I know that that's but that you that might be horrible to hear about
that but uh comparing doctor to some streamers the doctor is probably just like what what I go
like this and like in people's fucking like brains and shit that guy plays fortnight and he makes
three times my income. I'm ready. Ten times let's be honest. Here we go. What? What happened?
Oh my button my button is fucked up. The party's just begun. Yes we've heard of the entertainment
industry. Yeah but somebody said streamers specifically. Space channel five. I don't think
like Ben Affleck doesn't walk around in the Batman outfit. It'd be kind of weird if he did.
He might. How do you know?
He isn't Batman anymore. He doesn't want to be Batman anymore.
Didn't he come out in an interview being like I don't want to do that anymore.
How many costumes are there? Did I get a costume?
Uh so I I think we're good. I'm gonna really pay attention.
You can go home. Some dude named Jeremy Elberton is the new Batman.
Well I mean I am a streamer so that means I have to be a billionaire you know what I mean?
All right. Report five. I'm not ready for this. I already I know I'm not ready for this.
Oh fuck. All right come on. Just pay attention. We heard it through Pines broadcast.
I'm ready. Yeah Michael Jackson is actually in this game. What's that?
The reading on Persian the president. He's standing right next to us.
All right focus. I did like the shake. I should be ready for this.
All right clean. Clean. It was so clean it smelt like god damn Clorox. Let's go.
As clean as a goddamn bottle of Lysol.
That was as clean as a goddamn bottle of detergent. Why do you have grimace in your party?
What? This one. All right. This one. I couldn't. This was the wall last night for some reason.
Let's do it. Persona. Oh what? I did it. I made it.
That's got to be the midway point. I think this is the checkpoint. The shadows. Another band.
No this is not the one. Here we go. I yeah I I I remember this. This is the battle of the band.
I gotta beat this. I have to make it out of this. Come on baby. That was as clean as a goddamn bottle
of water. There was three. I keep missing the third one every time. I don't know why.
Couldn't press it fast enough. I hit it. I did it. I got it. I did it. I did it. Okay. I never got.
I did it. This is the part where you gotta get. You gotta save the real one.
Shh. I got it. And save him. Don't fuck this up. Come on. That's gotta be it right?
Yes. Can't be much more after that. I gotta have pretty decent. 70 percent. That's the best I've
ever had. Thank you. That's the best rating I've had. Now he joins the team.
Oh man they messed up his face. What's wrong with his face? I didn't get a good look.
Everything is wrong with everything.
We got another report I think after this right?
Mobile is delayed. I'm sorry to hear that. So I'm at the drive-thru right? Three days ago.
And I ordered a large Big Mac meal. And I can't. I'm not gonna talk over this.
Purge report. This is report six right? I got the whole team now.
A lot of these like pointing. The walk point.
Uh oh. This seems pretty end.
Wake up.
Come on with the power of the whole team. You had more...
Not really good at ad-living are you? Stage fright there. Uh oh. Come on Michael.
Get out of my face. I'm as clean as a clean floor after.
I don't know. It's very clean.
It's so stupid. Why would you in the middle of your number there just go
hey you got something better to throw at me? Mr. Sprinkle. What is his name? Oh god.
What? What did he say? What? What did he say? Did he say down?
Neck is broken. He just went ahhhh. I don't know. It's down apparently.
You're supposed to hold down. Oh god. Get out of here. Did I lose?
That was a very quick technical break. Uh oh. Clap?
This is wonderful. Where's Michael? There he is. Come on Yalala.
Give up your... Give up your power. That's it right?
Ninety one percent. Holy shit. I got a hundred percenter level. I can't.
I fucked up that part in the middle. What? It's hard to do that.
All at once. He said Red Dead Redemption 2 music. Well that's how you get better than purpose.
We're in a full-motion cutscene.
Again, not very good at ad-lib. Not 200 percent.
Are we still going? All right. No. I got some things to say. I got a few things to say.
And look at how much fun everybody's having. All right. There it is. That's not the end.
It's not unusual. Is this Tom? What's his name? Tom Hardy.
Tom... What's his name? Tom Love?
Tom Hard... No. Tom Jones. To be loved by anyone.
So this is Sonic Team, right? Yes. So they made two of these games.
And they made like 25 Sonic the Hedgehog games. This was such a delight. This game is an absolute
delight. And yes, they are making another one. It's coming out soon for VR. It's not Sonic Team,
but a lot of the Sonic Team devs. Oh, okay. There was a space channel port for a Game Boy.
This is just so fun and whimsical and wonderful. Why not make this a more
elaborate print? Did nobody buy it? Nobody... It's just sold badly or something. Doesn't suck.
And it was on Dreamcast. Yeah, it kind of sits in a weird spot, doesn't it?
Derma by the rights. It'd be great to see another
ooh-la-la adventure. I really hope the VR game is not just a goofy gimmick that lasts like 30 minutes.
There are some bonus modes and bonus levels, so we're not done with Space Channel 5.
Sega, please give more Space Channel, Jetset, Samba, Nights, Julie Hatcher... Yeah, there's
so many different IPs that are good. Is Sonic the Hedgehog the only thing that they are confident
that they can make that somebody will buy? What else? Didn't Sega just put their money behind
something recently that was not something like... What did they just do? They've done something...
Yakuza, right, yeah. Sonic, Yakuza, and Football Manager. Rhythm Heaven? Yeah, I would love Rhythm
Heaven. All right, let's see what the bonus content is. I was actually looking for...
I think these rhythm games are a ton of fun, but this is kind of equal parts rhythm game and Simon
Says. You know, needing them no prompts. It's a little different than most rhythm games.
Do I have to like turn off the console here that doesn't exist?
We just got like an endless string of robots running. Do I just have to wait till the James
Bond music is over? Play... All right, so get on your radar here. We're gonna play Rhythm Heaven.
I'm gonna find a way to play that. That's DS though, isn't it? I'm gonna have to get like a
modded DS. Is there one for the Wii? The Rhythm Heaven on Wii is good. Okay.
That was really close. After I went down, things started falling all around me and there was
screaming all around. I didn't think I could move. I have a 3DS, so I'll figure out. Oh, and I have...
Um, I don't have a Wii anymore though. I gave that away. Just point the webcam at the DS.
All right, I want to do like the bonus mode. Can we, can we get away from this like,
loading screen? There it is. Doing the walk. Step left. It's, it's... Remember I told you,
it's right foot left hand, left foot right hand. Where do you think I got it from? What? What?
What? What happened? What? What? What was it? Was it up? Oh my god. It was up. Give me a
fucking break. All right, here we go. We got, uh, Ulala's Dance. Nonstop 100 round battle.
What's the best costume? There's 40 costumes. Dirty retro gear. How do I get that? Clear 24
consecutive trials in dance mode. Clear all 100. Clear report one with a rating of 100%.
Be in the game for over three hours. Well, I got it. It's ugly. You gotta clear with 100%.
Clear 34. Okay, we're going to do dance mode. Like a little character selector.
There's Michael Jackson. Space Michael. All right, let's do it. This is just 100 rounds.
Let's see what I can do. It's just Ulala's Dance. 100.
All right, level one complete. Level 10.
All right, we're getting there, getting there, getting there, getting there.
Level what? What? What? I don't understand. What? That's just chew. I'll get it.
I'll get back there quickly. Level 10 group. All right, let's go.
All right, here comes the whoops. That like threw me off.
Okay, my hands are so sweaty. I'm going to fuck it up.
Tapping it. It's so greasy. Meow. Oh, I thought that was it. All right.
I can't speak. I'm sorry. Toyota.
Toyota. Placement. Please get to 100%. Please. It's so long. Here comes Michael.
Another car commercial. Here comes Honda. What's another car company? McDonald's. Last one coming
up. Has to be. Come on. Sweat. No sweat. How did I do that? No!
It was the first one with like, oh, it just threw me off so bad. But like Toyota, Toyota,
Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota down. It's like, oh, fuck, how many was
that? And I was just getting old. Oh, I can't believe it. It was that. Shit. No, it's so long.
Oh, it was so close. Damn it. Hold on. Wait, I think I, I got like three achievements.
There it is. 100 trial. Oh, I'm so sad. I'm so disappointed. I'm so sad. What's we got? Can I,
can I do it in like different mode? I guess not. I thought that was like a hard mode.
You can go home. 100 stage one. Okay.
Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, Toyota, down. And what happened
was in my head, I was like, oh, that's hard. I'm going to count the next ones. And I counted wrong
instead of just doing it by the beat. All right. Let's, I'm going to a hundred percent level one.
100%. Here we go.
Oh, I'm so sad. I had it. Oh, I can't get over. That was perfect. I got to beat it and you won't
be sad. 100%. Can you imagine how impressed we'd be if you beat it? I know that's in my mind too.
I got so close and that was just the first, it's okay. I tried. That's all you can do.
All you can do is try. Let's get this perfect. I fucking God damn it. This is what happens when,
this is what happens. You know, I'm, I know I'm going to get, I'm telling you,
know what I'm going to get. I'm going to, I'm going to buy like gamer fucking baby wipes.
You know what I mean? I'm going to get a packet of baby wipes that I'm just going to have here.
It's going to be, I just put them all over my fucking hands of the controller because this is
wet. I need gamer wipes, baby gamer wipes. No, you know what I mean though? God damn it.
I pressed up and before I could press up, my like frog chameleon hands like slipped over it and like
pressed above it. I need like baby wipes over here. No, but the baby wipes are bigger. I need
like a drying agent, like baking powder or something to like put all over. Okay. I need
the thing in the Olympics. We are, we, I talked about this already like three years ago. Chalk
and you like, we talked about that already. Did I make this reference like more than two or three
years ago? I already did. So just imagine I said it again. I need baby powder all over my fucking
stuff. Oh yeah. I actually even did that. Yeah. I put baby powder all over my hands. Oh yeah.
Cause a cup head beat that game on stream by the way. I'm too obsessed with this game. I have to
100% some of it. All right. Let's do it. Ooh la la. Here it comes. Okay. Let's go.
Yes. I know. I know what directions are. Press B. What do you hear? Hey, save them all.
Save them all. Am I even going to get a hundred percent?
Hey, hey. So I can't get a hundred percent. I'm missing something.
Right, right, left, left, chew, chew, chew. So where are the secret timings
during the transitions? So where are they? There are secrets in the, in the cut scene. So I can't
get a hundred percent. Hold on. This one. So where are they? Okay. Somebody said this like,
on today's edition of Ulala's various man, just ahead. Was there,
I don't see any prompt or anything. I missed it. Already missed it. Character pro,
that's a rule of thumb. Anytime she winks at the camera. Hold on. Why would a secret happen?
It's in the first three notes? Okay. So I, I apparently just got it. What?
How the hell would you ever do that? How would you ever know where those were? I guess.
Okay. So I got one percent. Just use the guide. Okay. I'm fucking. So what is the highest percent
you can get just simply being in the game? There will be three horn beats at the beginning. Well,
in the second horn, when Ulala points to the left of the screen, press a button at the split
second. You hear the horn. Then there will be three horn beats at the very beginning of the stage
on the third horn beat. When Ulala points forward and screen moves away. So there's two. Oh my God.
That is two percent. After the first battle. I didn't hear a horn. After the first battle
with shadow, you will save two rich people in quotes. After the rescue, all three of you will
do a quick dance, then pause striking a pose. Just as they strike a pose and they pause briefly,
hit a button, hit like a button. Okay. So when I, when we get the rich people,
when we save, they're going to do a pose. Which button? I think it's the A button.
Just hit your favorite button. Wait, is this it? No, then you say, okay, after the rescue,
you will all do a dance and then pose right when they strike the pose. Hit A. Don't fuck this up.
Just spam A during the transitions. Don't make me laugh right now.
This is not the time to make me laugh. That is a legit strategy.
Rich people, we strike a pose. What? I did it. I did. I hit A when they did a pose.
They did like, I pressed A. I didn't do the timing. What timing? We're going to go with
the original burger boy technique. Here we go. It doesn't work. It doesn't work. You can't do it.
Damn. Why? All right. Even timing it to try to do it correctly. You can't spam it.
Wasn't there a hard mode? Or do I have to 100% every level to do the hard mode?
All right, here we go. He's torturing himself again. I'm not. He's torturing himself.
We just need to pass it. I don't care about perfect timing.
Oh, all right. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. All right. This is the one. Let's go.
All right. Let's go. Right.
Colors are blending into my brain together, I think. It's not hard. Bring on the cat. Time
for meows and then Toyota and then Honda. Toyota. Just playing. This is digital bop it.
Eventually, you're going to hit the fucking twist when you're supposed to pulp. It's going to
happen. Come on. I can do it. I know I can. Almost there. I pressed. I kind of had to take my...
Oh, God damn it. I'm going like this for like eight straight minutes during that. Just going
and your brain and your body eventually just have to like...
And then I just go, damn it. My hair is white. Continue from the middle. Really should just close
my eyes. How do I start from the middle? All right. Let's try it. Hold on. Let me move this
just so I can prove that my eyes are closed. Do you think this will work?
I'm just going to lean back in my chair. I need the visual. I think I know I need the visual.
I need the visual. It's like I have to see the hands moving. Mute it. I can't mute it. Coward
journalist. I got it now. It's over. It says continue from midway. It doesn't work. I just
tried it. Mute the rhythm game. See, I need that. Seeing his hands go up and down. After you pass
No, we got to 93% last time. I think this is like the first of a few different levels.
Now everything's scrambled in my mind now. Like I'm reading chat. I'm like looking at
fucking the OBS settings. I'm like taking a sip of my coffee. I gotta like put my brain into the
game. All right. I'm gonna do it one more time. Look. See? It doesn't matter. I was so close that
first time. All right. Here we go. I'm going in and I'm going to just be silent and stare at
the screen. I'm turning off the other monitor. No, I can't. What the fuck is in my throat?
Ah.
Let's go. I forgot. All right, go.
What the fuck? Oh my God. I don't understand. Oh, I had. Oh, man. I can't. I almost beat this
first and then second try. And we're slowly going down the mountain where like up, down, left,
right, A, B, Honda, Toyota, cat, meow, dog. They're all the same thing in my brain at the moment.
It's like, oh shit. It's so bad. Cause when you come so, when you get so close,
I just had to do one last little string and it was just too much. Take a break,
play dynamite cop and come back. Yeah. That's what happened last time. Remember last night,
I couldn't get past the level five. Came back and first tried it. Perfect. Yeah. All right.
We'll come back. We'll come back. We'll come back after this one.
What's the premise of this game? The premise of the game is you press button in beat.
It's Simon's. It's digital. Simon says with bop it mixed in.
Stop reading. Oh, I turned the monitor. I turned the chat monitor off.
I do back, fucking me, fucking me up. All right. That was the second time I got there and
fucked that part up because of it's got to be good. This is so precise. I fucking beat it
the first time, but I fucking didn't beat it. And there's, there's like a devil, there's a devil
sitting right here. I don't know if you guys get this with you too. Does this happen to anybody
else? Tell me if I'm crazy enough, but like, let's say you, you get to a very, like a hard part of
the game, right? And it's the first time you got there and you, you kick the thing's ass. You,
you do so well. Everything's going great. Oh, that was really fucking hard. And then you lose
right at a moment where you had confidence that you were going to beat it, right? All of a sudden
here he is, you know, you're not going to beat that. You're not going to fucking beat this.
You already got to this point at 93%. You got so close and then you failed. And it's just like,
get the fuck up, man. I'm trying to do the level. You guys get that? And then the angel,
the angel's this tall. Okay. Devil is a special edition halo master chief in the collector's box.
You know what I mean? He's this big. The angel's like this very, very softly being like,
I'm like, I can't hear you. You can't speak louder. I'm trying to.
You're not going to fucking do shit. And I'm like, oh, I'm not. I'm not going to do shit.
Huh? Let's go play crazy taxi. You're sure? Look at how far you got. You got to 93%.
Oh, well now. Oh, good. Good one. You did a really good string there.
It wasn't as good as the first time though, was it? No, it wasn't as good as the first time.
You're right. Hey, you just looked at chat, didn't you? Yeah, I did just look at chat.
Why are you doing that? You're just not going to be able to do this.
I'm not going to be able to do this. That's right. I know. That's why I keep telling you.
Let's go play crazy taxi. Get S's. No, I'm not going to get S's in crazy taxi. Wait,
German, no more taxis. But that always happens when I do very well the first time I attempt
something and then I don't do well for a couple of attempts. And then it's just like, well,
I've expelled all of my fluid apparently. Hey, hey, come on over. Have some fun with crazy.
No, no, no. Get off my shoulder. Oh my God. Did you hear that? He's talking to me still.
Hey, what's the place? Crazy taxi. You fucking idiot. You're not going to be able to get to shit.
Why does this look like this? It's very loud. That's better. I probably should change this to
crazy taxi cool down. Crazy taxi. So by the way, something I didn't know about crazy taxi,
they have a version of this on iPad and it's like an eye. It's an idling game.
Play the last Jedi. Actually, you know, speaking of cool downs, let me, let me go get,
let me get a glass of water. It's been about two hours. Let me get a water and we're going to do
a crazy taxi cool down period. I'll be right back. All right. Somebody, let me just say, okay,
somebody said, no water. Don't go get water.
Wait, where do you, where do you have me locked right now? No, no, no water. Don't you dare go
get water. What are you trying to do to me? It's been a few hours. I've had like a coffee. I want
to get like a glass of water and like pee my pants on the way down there. I'll be right back. Left,
right, left, right, chew, chew, chew, chew, chew, up, down, down, down, up, chew, chew, chew. Hey,
that's like wolf. What? Let's play a little crazy taxi. One of my favorite games. Oh, Gus,
please mod the music in. I'm going to go to jail. You know, I don't want, you know,
you don't want me to go to prison, dude. Let's see if I can get, can I, can lightning strike twice
with me here? I missed it already, but it's all right. I'm getting a lot. All right. I gotta
remember the controls. He's going to be streaming from prison. Hey guys, I have an idea. Let me play
a game to like just relax for like a half an hour or so and then go back and try to do,
how does this crazy taxi sound? It has it in the title. All right, let's try it again.
It's the devil. Yeah, the devil made me do it. Not only, okay, none of this did the devil make
me do that. While I wasn't looking, he like Galaga watermelon smashed the angel's head
with a mallet and he hired his own pretend angel that he controls that just wears the white
and has like fake angel wings. Don't pick up the, there you go. So what you're going to do is you're
going to tell him, you're going to tell him whisper in his right ear like crazy taxi. He thinks he's
going to be like calming down and like cooling down. We're a idiot. And he's going to like rage
with that game too. Oh, it'll be scrumptious. Oh, that's the one that baits you. The devil made me
do that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not reverse. Oh, come on. Still salvageable. I can
still get more than 6,000. Yeah. Three bucks, three bucks, five bucks. Yeah. Install the old music
mod. You really want me to like, you really want me to turn the game off. Go download a mod,
go install the mod. That's going to like derail the stream for the next like 12 straight minutes.
I might as well just play the YouTube video of the music. What's going on with the car?
All right. Next chance I get. Okay. Where are the angels? Where are my angels?
Roller coaster tycoon. I'm on a roller coaster scream. It's a really nice touch. I don't want to
pick that person up. I really don't want to pick either one of you up. Right here. Got to go back
to the marine plaza. All right. Drive the car up and over and bang. Don't get baited. Here we go.
Not terrible so far. Could be a lot better. Well, I think I'm standing up in the car
because he's fucking crazy and he wants a thrill. I'm not going to get there.
Just go. I can at least get to 33. It's possible. Depends on if I can pick somebody up right here.
I don't know if it's possible. I'm not going the wrong way. Boost it. Sir, 3600. I'll take it.
It'll be B. Good. Always 21st. Always. Okay. I will go. I'm going to go get the song that everybody
wants me to go get and then I'm going to go to prison. So what is it called? Just original
crazy taxi OST. Hey, come on over. Have some fun with crazy taxi.
Is this what you want? Is this what you guys want? This is the one. Okay. Hey, come on.
Lincoln chat. Well, do the mod. Why would I, why would I need to do the mod?
If I have the video right here, that's like use the mod. Why? That doesn't make any sense.
It makes the sounds better. Okay. So let me, let me like, just let me spend the next like 15
minutes installing a mod to crazy taxi. Are we for real about this? Okay. Also stream your
windows 10 updates. I'm not, I'm going to have to, I think I'm going to have to put a veto on this.
Like I just want to play the game, go get the original sound effects. I'll make them with my
fucking mouth. I get this, like a bunch of drop box files. There are like three, there are like
four, five drop box files here. Now let me get them. All right. They're in. I just like click drag.
That one's in. Okay. So this one's like, this one's about that. I got to like get into the
main frame on this one. That one's in. Okay. I think we're good to go. Let's, let's test it
and see if it works. There we go. It works. All right. Let's go. It worked pretty good soundtrack.
It actually makes you play better too. Stop the car. Why is my frame rate dying?
That's kind of annoying. I wasn't this frame ready yesterday. I got baited again. No, no, I didn't.
No, this is different. This is the lighthouse. I think it's the mods. Yeah. These mods are all
fucked up. It's slowing my game down. It's giving frame rate issues. What the heck? Sometimes the
mod had to load the next song. God damn it. I love the frame rate fix mod. I'm sure it's something
like that exists. This is zero, zero, zero. Pretty good soundtrack though. The music usually stops
right now. Maybe this is like a continuous mod. I'm gonna, this is gonna be the one. Forget about
drifts. Let's try and make some time. I didn't get tipped for that. Cross street. Do I have to
turn the car around? I might. There's so many cars on that fucking road. All right. This YouTube video
is actually making my frame rate drop. I swear to God. Sorry. Whatever. I don't care. The video on
my other monitor is making the frame rate of the game suffer. He's been exposed. The devil made me
do it. I don't care. Fucking goddamn YouTube video. It's like Flash Player playing in the
background. Dragging my frame rate down to like fucking 18. You can't live without the devil.
Are you guys the devil in that scenario? I try to get funky with it. It's HTML5.
Whatever it is. It hogs resources. No, we're only doing like a few rounds anyways. You guys realize
that even if I installed the mod, you would only hear probably three songs. The ones that you just
heard. I'm not gonna play crazy taxi for like another three hours. This is just to get my brain
off a space channel. Game over. Have y'all, really? All you guys are gonna be like this right now?
How many devils have moved into my house? First it was just the big collector's edition one.
Angels gone. Now, now you, how many devils are here? You guys are on my couch. You're eating
food out of my fridge. You're using my toothbrush. Laughing and high-fiving each other. You haven't
changed the category on Twitch yet. Yeah, I did. Refresh his crazy taxi cooldown. You're out of
toilet paper. You guys are like shitting in my toilet. You just beat your driving by and beeping
at me. That shit was already there when I started. It's all part of the plan. He's gonna fucking be
so angry. He'll never complete space channel five on this stream.
And I'm going like this with my hands. I'm so evil. New evil emote. That's not an emote.
Just trying to get money. I actually got a lot of money. I thought somehow I took a wrong turn.
Get over there. Come on. Oh my god, please. Am I even doing the boost right?
You come here. Isn't it out of into drive acceleration? Isn't that how it works?
Or is it the same time? I don't, I still don't understand how that works.
Yeah, I'm, I think I thought I was doing it right. The lack of all I want by offspring makes me sad.
Let me see. I want to just do 10 minutes because I want to try to get this boost correct.
It's in reverse. You shift into drive and hit accelerate.
Yeah, so how come, how am I doing it wrong sometimes? Can you just,
you have to be stopped for it to work? You have to be stopped, right? No. It definitely doesn't
work when you're driving the car normally. You have to be like it's stopped. I guess it doesn't
work. So hold on. So why is it not working here? It is. I guess it's working. All right. Let's try
it again. So what is the difference between arcade and original? What's the difference?
It's not, it's just different spawn locations. Okay. That makes sense. Let me try it here. All
right. Why? I swear to God, I did that the exact same way every time. What's going on down there?
Why is the city destroyed? What the fuck? Stop, stop, stop, stop. No, don't stop. Stay on the,
this is a lot different. Oh, so many cars are just in the way here. Some of them just parked
on the side of the road. Really? What the fuck did I run into? I don't understand. I think I'm
going to lose. Have I thought about inviting Son Goku? Um, nah, nah. Are you holding the accelerator
during the switch? Um, I am not. I'm doing, going into reverse, letting go, going into drive, pressing
accelerate. Like a half second later. Not even like a 10th of a second later.
Thousandth of a second. That's rocking. Did I finish Resident Evil 2? I did. I finished Leon's
campaign. It's done. I did not do the whole game, but I'm not entirely sure I will. Claire B.
Watch out for the other cars, sir. No points for that. Come on. Not good. Not good. Not good.
God damn it. Oh God, give me a break. It's all right. 75 cents for a jump, but we almost die
and I'm going to get like $3. Fuck that guy. I'm going too fast. Jesus Christ. I don't know
where I'm going, but apparently I went the right way. I have to. You're right here.
That guy's just rocking out so hard. Bye. Come here. In. I'm not going to be able to do it.
Is this guy filming? Hey, turn off your live stream. It's all right. I'm getting the hang
of the boost. How long does he need to cool down? I should have just played like minesweeper. All
right. This is the last cool down period. Okay. This is it. And then I'm going to beat it. Let's
get this guy. I got S ranking yesterday. I'm going to get it right now. Here we go.
He was like in an explosion. That's just what's going to happen. Fucking God game.
Try it twice. Whatever. Try it ahead. Get in. Straight into a fucking tree. Oh, I'm so mad
about that. That was a good turnaround too. Fuck. Any of you. Popcorn mania. Popcorn mania. There
it is. Get up. Where's a good pickup here? I mean, you're right here. I don't like this though.
Bad spot to be in. Out. Thank God I just did that and turned around. There's an asshole in front of
me though. You stupid fucking imbeciles in the road. Just throw fucking cards at random spots
everywhere. It's my road. Back in the parking lot. I think I just saved a few seconds though
by doing that somehow. Oh my fucking God. They're everywhere. They're in every direction. Cut me off.
I just got fucked cut off. What an asshole. Unbelievable.
No. You need a brake job, man. Seriously. You have the, in this game, your brakes are as effective
as a fucking locomotive. It takes like four hours to stop this car. I might as well be on train tracks.
Stop. Just don't crash. We're playing crazy taxi. You don't not crash. That's like part of the game
is fucking being crazy. See? Like that guy's dead. Everybody in that car is dead. It's crazy.
All those people. See? I can't control that. I can't control when the guy fucking drives into me
from across the pond. You know, the title of this game is not moderately fast service vehicle.
No. Reasonable taxi. Yeah, when is that one coming out? It's a horror. I don't like that turn.
That turn sucks. Oh God. All right. We're okay. What's the helicopter doing here? Huh? This is
aero. Green. No, I think I dove out of the way that I wanted to pick up. What? Got it. Oh fucking
whatever. Just pick somebody up. Almost there. All right. Green pick up right ahead. YouTuber.
Oh, I'm getting stuck. Not good. Very bad actually. Oh, I hate this fucking game's directions.
Give me a break game. What the hell was that? Go this way. Go this way. Go this way. You're
going the right way. Yeah, go this way. Go that way. Would you like to restart your computer? No,
I would not like to restart my computer. I'm ready. This is a pretty good title.
Anger field complaint to Sega. He's got an angry review on like the steam page.
So I got to a point where I need to do a U-turn and the arrow is pointing straight and then it
turns around in a tenth of a second in the other direction and I'm trying to focus on not crashing
into every car on the road and the frame rate by the way drops all the time. Bad port. I don't like
it. Should have got the mod. All right. We cooled down a little bit from Crazy Taxi. Let's uh
continue here. Let's go back. Had a small break there. Let's do uh Space Channel 5. This doesn't
look right. Am I cooled? I'm pretty cooled down right now. I should have just like ate candy on
screen. No, I should have just ate a whole bar of chocolate on screen. All right. I'm ready now. I
took a break. My muscle memory was able to uh get angry at Crazy Taxi and get yelled at for no mods.
This is easy to me. Look at how easy this is. Speed it up. Why are people doing Manka S? Cool.
Let's see if I blow it in the same place every time. Get off my shoulder. What did I just tune
into? The best stream on Twitch. I'm kidding. Probably the uh it's bring on the cat. By the
way can I pause it? Okay so somebody just said that I left for a while and came back and he's
still doing this. Um well what happened was I did a cool down period in Crazy Taxi which elevated
my blood pressure because I people you guys can you guys can explain right but I just I just got
here this first attempt all right so you understand this is what it's the cool down period is over
let's get this done I love this silent streamer it's the way it has to be otherwise we'll never
leave here it was fucked it up get out of my fucking way there's more oh I just needed to
cool down a little crazy taxi um what there's more why don't you come over here and join me
too quickly it's just it's like boomer gamer old fuck hands just pressed it I got oh come on
my like slippery old fucking greasy hands now I'm not gonna calm down oh I want to just keep going
damn it why I was sitting there for too long holding the controller I just permeate liquid
why does this happen to me it's all right I did it I did it it's all right I did it
let's see what the costume is damn it there it is um that's the costume like a vest oh god
cliff 34 consecutive charles and dance mode while wearing the marillion suit
do I have that more than 10 hours play time I have to do with this two player mode
88 man suit boss marillion suit marillion suit oh something will happen if you play
lala's dance mode while wearing this suit what'll happen what's gonna happen I didn't
confirm the suit yeah I did didn't confirm uh I mean did that all right so now I've confirmed
it right what happens so it is a different character stop playing this game you fucking
loser what why did you say that now there is no midway point I did it though don't worry I got
to 100% that's all that I needed to do is there anything else I can do in the game I don't the
100% stuff is sort of I'm not interested I don't want to have to pinpoint exact random secret
timings there's a Michael Jackson suit is it really what's the marillion suit like how you
get the marillion cheat command is printed inside the clothes what the cheat command
his grandma mr nervous to save the neo-japanese astronauts just body paint and color contacts
well we don't have the body paint suit sorry guys noise costume peace costume space michael
no indication of how to get it but they're a cheat code there are cheat codes in that guy's clothes
let's see if they are where are so this is the marillion wait a minute talk to people
main characters special characters okay where's this idiot ordinary folk rhythm roads
uh
where's that dude with their clothes send you a crimson rose you need to get 100 report for
where was that dude that has the cheat codes I've sent you a green onion check the changing room
green onion it's just a green onion suit coconut lala clear 53 oh I did it no it's just a tan
when you want to that manly feeling using the kitchen investigation so what do you just get
hints for the costumes crimson rose laced with jaguar's passion this rose will never die
oh it's just a microphone what was the onion oh well that's it huh you get like a celery stalk
and some new costumes all right well I think that's all we're going to see from the game
so let me know unlock space michael uh I'm not gonna 100% that level if 100% meant to just beat
the level perfect I would do them all but the little hidden time the thing and get a wikipedia
page out to press a at the exact moment I'm gonna fuck that up over and over again uh there's also
the first one that one is just on dreamcast that's not ported anywhere maybe I'll just buy it
because this one was a lot of fun you know why don't just get the first one I have a dreamcast
we don't have to have a dreamcast night in quotes we can just do it whenever
because I thought this is this is a great game a lot of fun rhythm heaven is another one yeah
all right so uh what does that leave us that leaves us with I wanted to complete space channel
five go back to flick oh wait actually I did I was going through my discs and there is one
more dreamcast game that was underneath hidden that we didn't do and I brought my dreamcast
away from the desk so I have to go like set it up to do it and it's not going to be worth doing
I can guarantee you this is absolutely not worth me setting the dreamcast physically back up again
but it's right here and it's gonna be such a waste of time what is the game uh it's not good
it's not gonna be fun do it I have you know what I bought it it's here we're capping off the
dreamcast we are done with the dreamcast except for in the future um space channel five I'm gonna
do just for fun I'm gonna play the whole game one night and then seaman maybe I'll do like a
seaman first and then space channel five because that's all the space channel games
are less than a few hours of game time unless you want to really 100 percent everything
so we'll do that at a later date uh let me go set uh no jetset I did jetset radio
but I had a hard time with it I couldn't really get into it I did this pretty large learning
curve that I couldn't really want I didn't really want to dedicate time to it for some
reason yesterday uh but the game is all right I'm gonna tell you what it is and you tell me
if this is actually worth me going and getting the dreamcast we'll do that how's that sound
the game is I didn't even take it out of the plastic there's a film of plastic on here the
game's called stupid invaders is it worth it uh well never mind you guys never mind do I have
to get scanned like fucking twice in a row seaman didn't come with the microphone and the only disc
in here is disc two is that gonna is that gonna work is that actually is that gonna open is there
like a special edition that's disc one or did I just actually get like the final fantasy seven
like 12 hours into the game disc all right well I go get the dreamcast can you guys do me a favor
and just type in stupid invaders disc one and figure that out I'll be right back
fucking scam all right so what's the verdict is uh is this gonna work is it gonna open the game
yeah I got I got one more game we could play well no I don't it's disc two yeah just send him
the microphone send him the microphone with uh no microphone he doesn't need it
disc one we don't even have that just put disc two in there who cares
I'm just gonna plug it in see what happens put the disc in upside down let's see if we can
let's see if we can post this thing let's see good luck everybody I wonder what's gonna happen here
find out I gotta change my mic okay looking forward to this one what's today's date who
cares what today's date is here it comes let's hope it works is it I can't see anything on
the screen yet is there a voiceover hello is there anything on this disc a nice space wallpaper
I agree okay sega mpeg soft deck I don't think we got we didn't get this save settings not found
on vmu started okay ubisoft made this uh I bought this game I paid for it if it's just a special
features dvd we'll watch it the stupid invaders this was a french kid's tv show
was it really way to go candy so what do we do now steal a bicycle
okay gentlemen please try guys don't get excited it's not serious
hide in this abandoned house while I repair the spaceship if you only take a few minutes
so this actually is the game a few years later
that's as long as I can make it I'm gonna make a change the title here
kids tv show kids tv show dreamcast shirts that's weird it says minions
it's
why did I buy this but I want the spaceship too don't disappoint me polak otherwise it's
you I cut like the 40 or 50 dollars I spent on some of these bad old dreamcast games
I could have got stupid invaders do I actually get to play I have a mouse no no don't load game
foot subtitles on stereo let's give it a go stupid invaders disc one iso it's not illegal I own it
I own it it's like it's on the screen is that illegal I own the game I was cheated out of
owning the game that I paid for it's I have it it's right here whoa what's going off my camera
they were spinning too fast why are you doing this why does it save like the last fucking frame
let's get it out of here I want to show this to you look right here in my hand I own it's right
here I own it I paid for it now I'm out of sync well we don't even need to be in sync there there
that's better I own it I don't it's got a neck beard don't make fun of this until I shave it
this is how I feel right now I'm just gonna sit here like this how do I duplicate this are there
two here where is it that just scared the fuck out of me so obs I don't know why you do this
shit sometimes I can't duplicate this for no reason well here's the thing kids when you buy
used games make sure very very important kids always under every circumstance make sure that
you get exactly what you paid for in that box because if it doesn't come in there you end up
in a scenario like this oh and he doesn't have the other disc it's so fucking annoying because
you just you just expect somebody to just put like you did you just not know that it was the
disc that that was not the correct disc did you not put the c-man microphone in there on purpose
did you open the package and take the microphone out and then decide that I don't understand
send me the thing that I was supposed to have why would what do you mean I didn't read no
that'll make it I'm going all out on this one because it's not even me saying it it's fucking
logo whatever this dumb ass's name is what's going on what's happening
hold on I'm going all up I'm trying I'm getting the voice changer we're going all out for this one
hang tight okay so let's do this again
am I synced up does this work can you see me can you see is it is it audio delay
quiet well I'll turn it up all right anyway
do you think this is what he sounds like no he doesn't sound like this probably
what do you sound like hello hello that's horrible hello no hello hello this sounds pretty good this
is what this guy sounds like so I'll walk up to the street where we talk about very important
topics for instance number one when you buy something on amazon and it says in package
inside of package is going to be microphone and seaman maybe you might want to go on the computer
and ask them to make sure that it's in there because uh this is all the second used game I
purchased that the shit on the description is not in the box anybody gonna like it skills
okay
I will sit here for the next hour no I won't that's a lie
just play click yeah I'm gonna move on we'll play I'll play something else
oh no no disc hold on a minute here man no no disc
oh
one second