["The Star-Spangled Banner"]
No, I'm not sure. This one right here. How are you?
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to TheGerber985
and partnership with Andy Mark Carnival.
Now, I know a lot of you are probably wondering
what's going on here.
I'll give you a brief description.
I'm so excited for this. I literally...
This has been a long time coming.
And I do have to just really
shout out a few people here.
You're going to have a lot of fun.
First of all, I want to thank Andy Mark
for their contracting of the robots.
They did an insane job.
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Listen to me. You have no idea.
We're going to go to this camera too because
I can't see chat. That's my problem.
We're going to this one.
I have power. I have real power.
Now I can see chat.
Yeah, that's my fault. I'm an idiot.
I want to thank Andy Mark
especially. You don't see them
but they're back here.
And they did a hell of a job making these robots.
But what are you talking about?
We're going to be playing games on this stream.
This is a carnival. So what do you do
at a carnival? You play games. And there is not
one game.
There are not two games.
There are not three games on
this stream. Not four, not five, not six!
Hopefully this doesn't
blow away. I really hope it doesn't.
Because we've got strong winds in the forecast.
That thing goes...
Fuck it.
You know, whatever.
There are seven
seven games that are going to be
played. That's right.
And they range from all kinds of different things.
These games are going to be
played by you.
Not me. They're going to be played by you.
By you. Yeah, so I'm seeing
some Jerva Venuses over here.
What are you saying?
Seven hundred thousand... No, no, no.
I know. I know. Listen.
I know I look like a group of soccer
coaches banged a bunch of
red lobster employees. But that's beyond
the point, okay?
We are going to move to different games today.
And some other
special surprises as well.
So stay tuned. I hope you enjoy this.
A lot of time went into this.
So, I mean,
if we can really decide
when we're going to move to the first
game. I have the power here. Remember, this is my
controller. I press this three or four times.
And we move to the next game.
So, I am just going
to be going like this. Somebody gift that.
Put it on the fucking
Reddit. What are you saying?
No stop. No stop.
What do you mean stop? Why am I stopping? Get it
quick. He's a Redditor.
So I use Reddit.
I've been on Reddit like twice.
Is it a problem?
There's a bug on the camera?
Which one?
Which one
on the camera has the bug on it?
Top right. I don't know which one
is my right. This up here?
No, that's a German 985 logo.
To make sure that you know where this
fucking came from. All right.
So first up,
you're going to have a series of controls
on your screen.
Series of controls. They're going to be
W, A, S, D.
Up, down, left, right.
Power. Decrease power. Increase power.
You're going to see them on the screen.
The first game that we're going to do
is ring toss.
That's right. I'll demonstrate
before we go. You know, I'm going to demonstrate
the ring toss for you. Ring toss
is the first one. And we got
ring toss. We got a pitching
machine that we've got.
You guys have no idea. This is like
literally, I...
Can you hear the wind?
This is going to be crazy.
So, are
we ready for the first game?
We're ready for the first game.
You know, I'm getting worried about having a secret service.
Do you see this? You didn't think I was going to have a fucking
secret service thing in my ear. I do.
First game. Let's go. Ring toss.
Cue it up. Hey.
How are ya?
You see on the screen right now, you have a series of
commands and graphics.
And those commands are going to directly
connotate to the movements
of the robot that you will see on the screen here
very shortly. Right now.
I will prove that
this game is winnable, by the way.
If I can get a ring over here.
As we see.
Exhibit A.
I heard a balloon pop.
Get down. Get out of here.
I'm the Carney. I gotta prove
you can do it first. Give me another couple.
Okay.
Three more tries and I'll get it. Fuck.
I practiced this for like an hour.
Yes!
So it's possible. You see, I gotta prove it's possible
first. As you see
here, this is the first
of the three
Andy Mark created
robots.
Get a shot of this robot, please.
I want to get this thing in the camera.
Look at this thing. It's absolutely stunning.
This is a launcher.
You have to go
where you want it to go to launch.
By the way, very important.
This thing is going to have a timer on the screen.
There's a rumor
here. I don't know if you heard that.
There's a rumor here.
They fucking follow me everywhere.
They literally flew across the country.
I can hear that.
Literally.
That's unfucking believable.
There's going to be a series of commands on the screen.
They're right there.
You have to control this.
It will only accept inputs
when there's the green light on the bottom of the screen.
When the timer reaches zero, it
fires.
Make sure you get it in the right spot.
I'm seeing people spam it already.
That's not how it works. You have to wait.
Wait until it's ready.
Green light means go.
Can we get a demonstration of what it looks like?
Interesting stuff. Let's see what it looks like.
Oh!
I was a little overshot, but you get the idea.
I thought I could do it without looking.
So,
when the command is green,
please control the robot
if you will.
Let's see if we can get it loaded for you.
I actually have to make sure I collect these.
I have to make sure I collect them because
they're going to be gone.
When the timer is on the screen and you see the green light,
that means you can control it.
I see green light go!
It's actually working!
It works!
It's phenomenal!
When that timer reaches zero,
it's going to fire that ring.
Don't shoot at the guy.
I just want to make that really clear.
Don't shoot at the guy. You've got to get three of these.
We're not going to move on until you get all three.
Shoot at the streamer.
Shoot at the streamer. You've got to get three.
I've got a drink around here somewhere.
I don't know what the hell it is.
Zero? Nice try.
Disabled commands, by the way.
Do not write commands when it's at red.
Because when it's at red,
your commands are not going to be taken
because we're doing it on a timer.
That's wonderful.
Nice to see you. Aiming directly at my face.
You have to win the game!
You have to play the game.
When it's green, that's when you do it!
Win the game! Forget about shooting it at me.
What have we got?
You think that's a good spot?
You think that's a good place for it?
It might be a little too high, I think.
Alright, that was close.
That was close.
It was a little too far this way.
But you get the idea.
This is a warm-up, guys.
You are getting warmed up
for the inevitable, incredibly complicated
events that are going to take place here soon.
Seeing some pog jams, that's good.
What have we got? Timer on the screen.
Let's see it. Chat commands have been accepted.
Anybody going for the back row?
No, they're going this way.
Where are you going?
You're going right in the middle?
This is insane to see this,
by the way, live happening.
The wind is picking up.
You guys might get lucky from the wind.
Oh, shit. Strong winds.
It's going to knock all the bottles over.
Oh!
No, that's not a point. Not a point.
You're in the middle. Sorry.
I should probably show you the prize that you're playing for,
but that'll be a surprise, too.
That was actually pretty close.
That was as close as you're probably going to come.
This is hard. It's not easy.
Look at that. You can see your movements on screen.
Remember, there's power as well.
You're not just controlling left and right.
You're talking about power level.
Control your power.
You've seen Dragon Ball Z.
I haven't. I mean, I'm never going to watch it,
but you've seen it. At least a hundred of you.
Maybe. Possibly.
I've got to get you a better view.
That looks good.
Nope. That one wasn't even close.
That was not even close.
That's so funny.
So how many did we get? One, two, three, four, five, six.
Oh, like six.
A hundred? Were there a hundred bottles?
I think there's a hundred bottles
for you to choose from.
I'm going to give you a tactic here as the person
that's the carny here.
I'm going to go right in the middle because
then it can bounce around.
You've got to do these tactics. Get the fuck out of here.
What a wasted throw.
Thank you for listening.
Are you going to listen? I don't think you are.
Are you not going to listen to me?
You're just going to fire it at my face.
You're going to just aim it this way? Good. Let's go.
Let's go. Yeah.
Delete it. Delete it.
I just did it with my mind.
I looked at it and just snapped it out of existence.
Just like Big Bird.
I got a purple guy.
Have you never seen Infinity War, by the way?
It's a great movie.
I would recommend it.
I just out of nowhere just wanted to say
that that's a good movie. You should watch it
if you have a chance. No spoilers or anything.
I don't have a spoiler here. It's just a good movie.
Remember, it's when it's at
zero is when it fires.
You guys are never going to win this game.
I'm starting to come to the realization that it's just not going to happen.
It's just not going to happen.
It's unwinnable. Snap that one
out of existence, too.
Like Elmo.
No, no. We got it. We got it. We got it.
You didn't give enough power.
You didn't give enough power
on that one. That was like zero.
You have to put more
power. You have to put more
power. It's got to be at least
like, come on.
You're raising the hammer.
It's a hammer. So you
raise it high enough to launch
the ring over here.
It's simple instructions.
It's very easy. You saw me
do it. I'm surprised that you
can't. And now you're going all the way down.
Now you're going all
the way down. You guys
are breaking this thing. You guys are going too far down.
Pull it up a little bit.
Up higher. That's not going to do
anything. Higher. Higher. Higher. Higher. Higher. Higher. Higher.
I'm just trying to help you here.
Because you've got to pull it up
a little bit like 10, 20 percent higher.
Because seriously, let me show you.
I'll give you a quick little look.
That's just not going to happen.
Shit.
I think the wind like shot that one.
The wind just like shot it down.
I don't want these to fall.
We've got some extreme winds.
These fall.
This took like 67 minutes
to put all these in the right place.
You understand? If the wind
picks up high enough, these are going to fly.
And then we're going to have to move on
to the next game.
I'm scared. Let me show you how it works.
Damn it.
We're waiting for the wind to settle for a second here.
If you can believe it, let's go.
So,
let's do it. Pull it in.
I'm not very good at this.
So the wind is
kind of causing a few problems here.
That's what happens when you have
million people
all at the same time putting commands in
with torrential 60 mph winds.
As you can see,
we're trying
to accommodate for it.
But it's pretty difficult.
There's no way you guys
would even get one anyways.
Not like it was going to work.
Chat inputs are now disabled.
Get a good look. Get a great look.
Because that's what you're looking at.
I'm going to make a prediction for you.
At some point
during the stream,
there's going to be a scenario
where the wind takes something.
Don't worry.
We've got plenty of trained staff on board.
And it looks like you've figured it out.
You've got the machine moving in the right direction.
There you go. There you go.
There you go.
Come on. You can get one. Please get one.
This is so insane.
Two. One.
Fire!
That almost went on.
That's so funny.
Oh.
I've got to clear these out.
I want to make it easy for you.
Are we ready for commands?
Are you ready?
I'm not sure.
Let's see what happens.
I just want to see if you get one.
I want to see if you can get at least two.
Power. Change the power.
Come on.
Don't wait. Don't wait.
Move it this way.
This way. Please.
Make it worth it.
I have nothing to say.
This is just fucking hilarious.
I just like to watch.
Going for the back left row.
Interesting choice.
Let's see if you can do it.
No. Changing your minds. Collectively.
I wonder how many of you are actually trying to...
Nice shot.
I can't even do it from fucking two feet away.
People popping balloons.
The wind is like taking balloons.
This is going to get ugly.
I don't know if you can just hear that.
But there was a very loud crack.
Right there. Right here.
Try to get in the middle. Less power.
I don't want to break it before we're done with it.
Too high.
Less power.
Is more utility.
This game is really hard at the actual carnival.
Let alone one that's controlled by
600 million people right now.
I don't think you're going to do it.
I don't think so.
You know, I probably shouldn't be standing here.
That's giving like 60% of the people a target.
The last one was here.
That next one was here.
You got to pull it in a little.
Just a hair tighter.
You want it like here.
Right there. Right here.
You want it right here.
This game is not complete.
Welcome to the carnival.
Nothing is winnable.
I want to see one.
Get the fuck off me.
Now you overdid it.
You overdid it by like
100%.
Now you under did it by like
Remember your commands are only accepted when it's a green light.
I ain't going to touch anything.
I'm going to hold this thing down.
Look, I'll aim for my fucking face.
We'll make it easy for you.
Just aim right for my teeth.
And then you'll get it.
60% of people that want to hit the streamer in the face with a rock.
Just go ahead. Right here.
Right in my face.
You can do it. You can do it.
I know you can.
Damn it. You had a chance.
You had a chance.
Oh shit.
It's coming this way.
It's going to be like a tornado in the background.
Get away from me.
You're ruining my carnival.
Right here. I like it.
I like the idea.
I can even body if I have to.
Unwinnable.
Good luck.
This is going to fly forward and it's going to take up the whole table.
So I am only here.
I'm just going to T-pose over here to make sure this doesn't happen.
There you go.
No, no, no. A little more. A little more. A little more.
You're going too far.
I think that's good.
Don't listen to me though.
I'm a liar.
I like collecting rings.
By the way, you win this.
You win.
It's kind of rolled all over the ground.
It's a goat. It's a prize. That's what you're looking for.
You just got to get one.
I would laugh so hard if it's not even one.
It would be great.
It would prove just my total superiority.
Let's try it again.
Too much.
You guys go too far or too little.
You got to go like that sweet spot.
And you got to try to hit it right in the middle.
So bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce, land.
And even if it doesn't, it's hard to do.
It's hard to do.
Pay no attention to the guy that's putting his hand in here.
Remember, this is just to teach you how this works.
What did I do?
I think I fucked up.
This is a lesson because there are six more games
coming up here after this.
This is the tutorial.
And you failed the tutorial.
You know how you guys give me shit all the time from messing up tutorials?
You guys failed it.
I was really thinking you were going to get at least one.
Go back and redo the tutorial.
See?
I just did it.
It's really not that hard.
You have to do it like 60 or 70 times in a row
with varying degrees and angles.
I think this will be the one.
I think you're going to go harder than that.
Remember, it's a mallet that is dropping.
You're pulling the mallet back to land on the platform
to launch the ring.
So use the force that is there, Luke.
God damn it.
Unfortunately, you still can't get it.
By this point, you guys have already spent
probably like $400 or $500 on this.
And that goes directly to me.
That goes directly to me.
So I'm going to give you guys
I'm going to give you guys a shotgun here.
Can you shotgun blast this and land on one?
We've got like five rings loaded up.
And then you're going to have to move on.
It's just you guys can't do it.
It's very imminent.
Come on.
We'll see if we can shot.
This is going to hit me.
I should probably back up.
I don't think I should be over here.
I'm going to get it in the eye.
Can you get one?
Why am I squinting?
Honestly, it doesn't matter where you put it.
It's just going to go.
Oh, shit.
Not even fucking close.
Not even close.
You failed the first game.
You can't even do the first game.
Well, all right.
So what's going to happen here
is I'm sorry you don't win this.
I don't even know where that went.
Who cares?
What we're going to do now is I'm going to give you guys
a special little treat here.
I'm going to give you guys a little treat.
We're going to move on.
What kind of carnival exists
without, of course,
some delicious,
nutritious,
potentially illness-causing,
bacteria-infested
cotton candy?
That's right.
I'm going to need somebody, one of you guys,
one of the people in the chat are going to have to come up here.
Does anybody,
does anybody want any cotton candy?
You'd like some?
Son, you over there? Why don't you come on over here, son?
I am going to make you a special treat.
I have trained
in this, son.
Is this your brother?
Daniel? Daniel, good to see you.
So I have trained
in the art of making
cotton candy.
I can't.
I hope it's just fucking
shattered. Oh, shit.
Okay, so,
alright, so everything is good to go.
How big do you want it, son?
How big? You want it big?
I can do that for you.
All you can hear is probably a loud noise.
Does mom want
one too?
Alright, I have actually been trained in this.
Let's get a good, nice, big
surprise for you.
This is not
what I thought was going to happen.
Alright, I'm not very good.
I'll get a big one for you and your brother.
I have no fucking idea how to do this.
I read the instructions.
Very, very quickly.
This thing's going to
fly off.
Okay.
Well, hey.
There you go.
Son, this one's for you.
There you go. Take it. There you go.
So, oh, Jesus Christ.
Alright, go home.
Do you want one too?
Would you like one too?
I'm going to get like burnt.
No, no, no, no.
Don't do that.
Just like
mom used to make.
Alright. Just like mom
used to make. I taste soap.
I don't know why. I don't know why.
It tastes soapy to me.
I can't believe you fucking.
It's delicious.
Oh, let me get some more.
Here we go. Okay.
Well, I'm going to give you
a double there, son.
If you would like to take that.
That's like a bug
zapper.
Alright. Look at that.
Imagine you
got this at the carnival.
I'd be like, I would fucking return it.
Can you return cotton candy?
That's like
so shitty. That's so bad.
Oh, God. This is bad.
This is bad. No, this is not an injury.
Come here. Come here.
Bring your brother too. Come here. This is not an injury.
People think
I got like a cut. No, it's cotton candy.
Relax.
It's going to be fine. Alright.
That looks good.
I'm going to need a shower after this, I think.
That probably looks disgusting.
I don't know if you can hear anything I'm saying right now
because there's a loud machine over here.
So coming up next.
Oh, there's more. There's more. This ain't it.
Sprint $645
million on this fucking project.
I don't know
if I should turn it off.
Coming up next is
what do we got next? That's a good question.
I'm going to have to take this off.
What a great like fucking joke.
I made shitty cotton candy for five minutes.
Wonderful.
Don't put your hand in here by the way. That's dangerous.
Like I'm doing.
I'm a professional. There's like 15
people on staff here.
They've taught me how to do this. Don't worry.
Actually pretty good. Where are we going next?
We are going
to another game.
That game is
I've forgotten the game. Tell me what it is in my ear
because I don't fucking remember. I sweat.
We're going to frog launch.
Launching frogs.
I'll see you over there.
So
in this game, this is another
hard one.
We've updated the graphics because they were
incorrect on the last one. So the
graphics have been updated.
I'm going to need like a cup of water
if it's possible.
Actually it'll probably help you because these things
are probably going to stick. So we have
Hold on. I'm just going to put it over here.
We have these frogs as you know.
Frogs are here.
Your goal is to land
these on the lily pads.
You remember this one from when you were a kid?
I do. So if you
land on a lily pad,
you win. If not,
then you lose.
So this one is probably going to be
like five times harder
than the last one. So I would be surprised
again if anybody
got this at all. I mean
it's the first couple of just like impossible.
And I thought it would be kind of funny
if we made the games like just fucking
uncompletable. But then out of
thank you sir. Thank you. If you could just
dump that on my hands. That would be wonderful.
Alright. There we go. Just a little bit
of you taping that. Okay.
Not sure why you filmed that.
Not sure why you had to get that on camera.
But I had to have that happen.
Anyway, so you got to land the frogs on the
lily pads. The controls have been updated.
They may have been incorrect before.
But it's a live goddamn show. Okay.
This is all happening live right now.
And you haven't seen anything like this before.
I've never seen...
Okay. We're good. We're good. The ground
just moved. So
again, you have the controls on the screen.
You launch on the frogs, land on a lily pad. If you land
on a lily pad, the game ends. By the way.
You win the game. Good luck.
You're going to need it. Because we've actually
tested this like a
dozen times and I don't think anyone has been able to do this once.
Back to back we're giving you hard ones.
This is the new one of the hard mode.
You've got it. Watch the timer
on the screen. Chat. Commands are only accepted
in the green light. You've got to get that
frog on a lily pad.
Hopefully in the
air too. Fucking cotton candy.
That was such a
waste of time. It actually was not that
bad. It did taste a little bit like soap. Of course, hit the streamer.
I won't move.
It'll hit me right in the face. It'll hit me directly in the face.
I don't care. Do it.
Come on. Come on. Do it.
You want to make that joke so bad.
You actually did it.
I actually can't fucking believe
you did that.
I mean, did it hurt? Yeah.
Am I going to cry about it? No.
Maybe not.
That was a direct fucking hit.
Unfucking believable. Anyways, now
could you play the actual game?
That would be fantastic.
Come on.
You've got to land on a lily pad.
Ooh.
Too much.
Too much. I got some for you
if you need them. You got enough back there?
I'll just toss them in the box. I'll toss them in the box
so they get them. Oh, God.
Wind, you're ruining my whole show.
Hey, let me show you how easy this is.
Pretty easy.
We thought it was going to rain. You understand?
So, like, I'm not sure what's worse.
If it rains, then the whole thing
has to be canceled. But if it's wind,
then you have to compensate for the wind like a
golfer. You ever play golf? You go to the
driving range, you have to compensate for the wind?
You have to do that here. I'll give you a good
example, right? I'll throw it in the air so you can see.
See, there you go. Wind's going that way.
Just so you know. Wind's going that way. And it's on the bot now.
You have...
That scared me.
I got actually startled.
I actually just got scared by that, so
it's coming up all over the place.
Oh, we got rings, we got frogs.
It is possible, as you see.
Fuck, I forgot to prove that.
I'm supposed to prove that it's a possible game.
This is, by the way, it's too hot out here.
It's time for me to de-robe. And just be in
my fucked up train
conductor outfit. Okay, that's not
going to be in the... Okay, that's good. I don't want to be shown
the whole fucking blue man shirt. Wait, oh,
I think I just ripped out my mic.
Can production staff still hear me?
Can you still hear me? I think I may have ripped the mic up.
Okay, good. You guys can hear me. Okay, let me
help you. Too high.
You gotta find that spot. If you guys find
a spot that lands on the table,
if you find
a spot on the table, you want to try to keep it there.
You guys are moving it too much.
I should put my head down there. I should put
my face down there so you guys actually do it.
Oh, shit. I forgot.
That's too easy.
Right in the middle. Good, good, good.
Good. Good.
More, more, more power.
More power. Oh!
If I were you,
I would aim for the bigger ones.
Because, I mean, these are
smaller. If you go to the carnival,
they're gonna try to get you to throw it on the smaller ones.
Use your thinking phases. Use your
6000 IQ. Put it on the big one.
These don't count, by the way. These frogs.
They're just there for fun.
And to squeak when I need to.
Like that. See?
You want to get them all? I'll do them all.
One more? This one sucks.
Replace them. It's not good enough
on camera. Alright.
Is it gonna be enough?
Almost at it. That was right
there. Almost there.
You had an opportunity.
I wonder if you guys are gonna be able
to do any of these. I bet you
I bet you you don't do one.
And by the way, the dunk tank
is coming up. So, good luck with that one.
I don't think you're gonna be able to do that one either.
I hope you proved me wrong today.
I can't believe it. Ah!
By the way, if it bounces and lands,
it counts. That does count.
If we go from here to here,
you just have to land on it. It counts.
It is really hard though.
When we were thinking about these games,
when we were designing them, when we were going back and forth
with Andy Mark, we were trying to figure out
like, hey, what can we do? We don't want them just to win.
Immediately.
Hi, I see. Yeah, I know.
I know. You're gonna go for it again? I won't move.
You think I'm scared? No.
Have you realized that you can't win?
Okay. I may have just
cheated.
That was getting close.
But I may have just influenced that a little.
Now that was right here.
It was going right here.
Don't give me that bullshit.
Can I take this hat off yet?
It makes me look like a dickhead.
No, that's worse.
I think it might be worse.
Don't invite me anywhere.
I'm a scary person.
What's worse?
I'm using the production monitor as a mirror.
That's how much of a vain fuck I am.
Oh.
I'm paying attention to the game.
What do I look like right now?
Do I look okay?
Let me see. Okay, nice.
What's that? What's that? Yeah?
Yeah, okay. I got you. Roger that.
I'm not fucking bald.
I see it. I can see the emotes right now.
Cut that out or I'll fucking ban you.
You wanna get banned from the carnival?
There's two ways to get banned from a carnival.
One is to puke on a ride.
And two is by
riding the ride too many times in a row.
Because they get sick of you.
I know this because I did it.
I didn't puke on a ride.
I rode a ride too many times in a row.
Because I bought like 150 tickets
and they just like, you can't do this like
fucking 20 times in a row. So I was like alright fine.
So I left.
I was just getting back and they were sick of seeing me.
They thought I like stole them.
All the tickets. And I'm like I didn't fucking do that.
I paid good money for this.
I don't wanna influence that. I'll take it off.
Something going on
that way. You guys have
You seem to have figured out the controls though.
I like that.
You gotta go for the middle ones.
Have you done?
No. No.
No. That's safe in baseball.
You're out. You can get a photo of it
if you want. Get a photo of it. Cause that's no.
The foot don't count. No you gotta get the whole thing on.
That doesn't count.
It's gotta be on the actual pad itself.
That doesn't count. That doesn't get you anything.
That gets you a
nice try. Not a hole.
It's not rigged. It's not.
It's not rigged.
Where have you ever been to a carnival before?
I know you've been to a carnival.
I know you've never been to a carnival but I have.
Everyone's been to a carnival.
How have you not been to a carnival?
I'm projecting on you. I don't know why.
Everybody that's been to a carnival knows
you have to get it.
There's a very specific area you have to get it on.
That don't count.
You didn't win shit.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
What are you guys pretending?
Are you guys pretending?
Stop. Stop pretending chat.
Right?
Stop pretending.
You doing this hard thing
that's really hard to do
and you can't do it?
Stop fucking pretending chat.
You know what I'm saying? Quit pretending.
Let's go.
Get it done now.
Oops. Double.
Not enough. Didn't count.
I love this so much.
This is amazing.
I love watching you guys try to do something
and you can't do it.
And I just get to sit here. I get to be the backseat gamer
because I know how to do this.
And I just get to watch you guys fail
over and over again.
I get to watch you guys suffer through Dark Souls 3
which I beat on stream.
I did the DLC too if you weren't curious.
I know some of the new viewers that don't know that I beat it on stream.
I play Demon's Souls.
I beat it on stream.
Beat Demon's Souls on stream for me.
Come on. Let's go.
That jumped up
and then fell.
We're going to leave that there.
We'll get a referee to verify that.
By the way, completely independent
of anything going on here that I have hired
to bring on.
Completely independent
third party reviewer that I have brought on.
I have hired.
By the way, it's me.
Do it.
I know you can.
I'm certain you guys can.
Right in the middle. Right in the middle.
You gotta up, down. Pull it back a little bit.
Work together on this shit.
Work together on this.
You were right here. You were literally right here.
Now just pull it back.
Don't even move the fucking thing.
Just pull it back like a little bit of power.
Don't go forward.
You got it.
Work together.
There you go. There you go.
Don't turn it. Don't turn it.
Somebody fucked it up. Who did it?
Who screwed that up?
It was me. It was me.
Too much. Way too much.
You had it right there. You just had to pull it back a little bit.
I think there might be some pranksters in the chat.
There might be some people joking around too much.
No, it was right here.
You had it.
Blame the people in chat that didn't follow along.
That's what I blame.
No, that's just extra cotton candy.
I don't have a cut on my arm. Don't worry.
I just saw it over here and I was like
get that fucking thing off my head.
I look like one of those guys
that goes on surveys.
This is seriously like a traffic cough shirt.
I can't take it off though
because my mic is hooked into it so I can't take it off.
I have to look like this
for at least another 30 minutes.
By the way, look at the glue man shirt. That's available.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It doesn't count.
You guys got the feet. You got two feet.
No.
It does not count.
No, it doesn't count.
It needs to land.
It has to be on the pad.
Not kind of on the pad. You guys get it together.
I'll leave it.
But I'm not going to count it. Why would I do that?
And now the juggling
of Terminator 5.
I have no idea how to do that.
You guys got to go higher than that. It's too low.
Although it's not my game so that's not me playing.
Come on.
I want you guys to win. I do.
That's so bad. I am so desperate
for you to win.
Because if you don't win any, there's no fun.
Just keep going until you just do it.
You have it in the right area.
I know you're completely capable of it.
So do it.
Look.
The wind is going this way. Do it.
I have complete faith.
No, more. Pull it back.
I'm just trying to help you. That's it.
Because I'm seeing this the complete desperate.
Close. That actually was pretty close.
That was close.
All of these are so close but so far.
To a point where
I don't think it's going to happen.
I'm pretty sure you guys can't do the first.
These launching games are the hardest ones probably.
That's why they're first.
It's like a training thing.
I'm the only one holding this.
I'm trying to train you
to win the fucking
carnival game.
And at the same time, I'm training
to hold this before it falls down and crushes me.
Whichever one of those two things happens first,
we'll find out, won't we?
Same spot. Same spot
as the yellow one.
How much is it usually to do this?
Five bucks?
You get three tosses for three or four dollars?
I think it's something like that.
What is it? Five dollars for three tosses?
Three bucks for two tosses?
Usually?
This is a different style here. You guys are going for a different style.
This is the one.
I'm calling it right now.
If I hit zero, what's going on?
I'm certain of it.
Don't let me down. Don't let me down.
Right now. You had a chance.
We are going to do this
only a few more times
before you guys have to get thrown out
of the carnival here.
There's a line behind you.
Only a couple more times.
You guys have a line forming behind you.
You can't just hog it.
It is not completable, rigged
just like a real carnival.
If you hit it, you get something great.
I'm going to put that out there.
They did it!
They got one!
You actually did it!
And of course,
if you win,
you get a prize.
And hey,
how's this for a prize?
How's that for a fucking prize?
You like that one?
What I have here is some kind of animal.
Some kind of teeth animal.
Big grinner.
I think it's a Pokemon character.
You'll get it later.
You did it!
Actually, that's going to get dirty.
Do you want to know something funny about that prize?
By the way, that's for you.
But it's for me.
That thing's like a hundred bucks.
Why? Why the fuck is that thing?
I can't believe you did it.
I was getting kind of concerned though.
After the first one and the wind and everything,
I'm just sitting here going,
I'm not going to do this.
This is going to be impossible.
But you actually did it.
And in fact, I have to inspect this because,
wait a minute, it's not on there all the way.
I don't think that actually counts.
I'm not going to touch it.
No, it does.
I'll count it.
I don't want to kind of stifle your victory here.
So, whale lord is your prize.
It's going in my office.
I'm going to hang it up behind a door or something.
I don't know.
What we should have done is we should have said,
if you got four feet,
then you get a prize.
Good work. You actually, actually did it.
I'm so happy about that.
Can I touch this now?
Can I put my hands on this?
Get your photo!
Give me this thing.
I got those.
I'll leave that.
Should I not touch it? What are you saying?
Oh, you're taking photos.
That's a good idea.
You took a picture.
JPEGs, whatever they are.
But,
I have something here
for you guys that's incredibly special.
We're going to move on
to something else. This is not a game.
Please, please give an incredibly
warm welcome
to the amusings
of Cuddles
and Pauly Polite!
Cuddles! Cuddles!
Cuddles!
Oh, yeah.
Sit down.
Sit down there.
I'm making balloons.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want a dog.
Can I have a dog?
I can do that.
I make front legs and back legs.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa.
I'm going to fix it.
I can fix it. I can fix it.
I'm watching. I'm watching.
Boop.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
Ah!
Oh, boy, yes.
I know what I want.
What? A dog.
We can make a dog, aren't we?
I want a dog.
Oh, my goodness. I'm coming undone.
Can I have a dog?
How about a dog?
A blue dog. A blue dog to go with my pink dog.
Okay. Hang on there.
Wooshy, wooshy, wooshy, wooshy!
Oh, I can do this really fast
because I'm good at this.
Yeah, uh-huh.
What's he doing?
He needs a friend.
Yeah, uh-huh. See?
I want a friend.
I forgot my nose.
I know what I want.
Oh, yeah.
Uh-oh, yeah, I can make a dog.
Yeah, I can.
You're all right.
What you doing?
Sit right on there.
I'll make a dog.
Woosh.
Let's try the other way.
Ooh, a purple one.
Yeah, I like purple.
Purple.
Yeah, I think they're really brittles.
Yeah.
See my nose?
Oh, yeah, you got a little wrong with that.
A purple dog cuddle.
I love the purple dog cuddles.
Yeah, yeah, what now?
I know what I want.
What?
I want a dog.
Please, can I have a dog, please?
Let me think.
That one.
That could be a weenie dog.
He's a cute one.
That's a hound dog.
Maybe a Yorkie hound.
Yorkies are popular.
Stay right there.
Patiently.
You're not waiting patiently enough.
You're a big yellow.
Whoop, whoop, whoop.
That one almost fell away.
I know.
Whoa.
I'll hold it for you.
And dogs like me
can be
We'll see.
That is a leg, right?
Yes.
That's a leg.
I think he's pretty.
You want that one back?
Okay.
Can I have my yellow dog now?
Thank you very much.
My god.
You're not all done.
I'm going to take my dogs out.
Thank you, cuddles.
Bye.
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Polly polite.
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful clowns.
We got them. Oh, you didn't think they were going to be
off course they were. You didn't think I was going to have something without clowns?
Are you out of your mind?
Anyways, this is it.
Right here behind me.
I know I've got my hair in front of my face.
This is a dunk tank.
So what's going to happen here
very important.
You have to shoot
this thing here while I'm
sitting up there.
And maybe you dunk me, maybe you dunk. I don't know. We'll see.
This is the idea that I had
two or three years ago.
And I'm ecstatic.
I'm so excited to get up there.
Because I
this is the main event here.
This is what I did this for.
And we've got a new robot in play here.
This is the pitching machine robot.
It is loaded.
It is dangerous.
Do not, under any circumstance
and I'm going to make this very clear.
Do not fire at me.
That's no, okay. Do not.
Not okay.
Do not fire at anything besides the
red circle over there on the right side.
Okay. You have my understanding?
Good. Great. Can't wait for you to break that rule in about
fifteen seconds. Anyways
I'm going to get up there.
Good luck. Because I don't think you got
what it takes. You bastards.
Was that good? Did I call them
bastards? Was that good? Okay.
So if you've ever been to
the carnival before
I'm not sure which camera I'm looking at here.
You got one chance
the same exact rules are in place.
Wait
for the timer
to get down to zero.
And then it's going to fire wherever it fires.
I'm actually a little bit nervous about this
because I'm excited. And yes I am wearing
jeans. That's to cover
an area that it may have been
that I don't want you to see.
You know what I'm saying? I got shorts on too.
So anybody that's typing OWO in chat right now
it's not going to work. Because
I've got like four pairs of underwear on
and now I'm going to leave it at that.
So
are we ready
to do this?
And mom if you're watching
mom. I know you thought I was
probably going to be a doctor but
not today.
Am I in the right spot?
I gotta make sure I'm sitting in the right place.
You have to do the wind.
You have to go for the wind too.
This is steel
by the way. I am protected completely.
No one
can get through much steel.
250 HP
per
softball that goes in.
25 HP reduction.
Gate. This is cold as shit.
Can I ask you a quick question?
Can I get a quick question into the crew?
Did anybody piss in here?
Nobody pissed in here, right?
You didn't piss in here, right?
Did you piss in here? You're nodding yes.
But I know you didn't.
Did somebody put ice cubes
in this too?
This is disgusting.
This is absolutely revolting.
I'm just
singing in the rain.
Ready to get dunked.
Those of you that don't think this is real,
there's real water in here. You can hear it swirling.
I don't want to pop this because it's going to make a loud noise.
This wind is scaring the shit out of me.
Best of luck.
Why am I nervous up here?
I should be completely
into this, but I'm just like, oh fuck, I have to get dunked.
That sucks.
That's not fun. I don't like that.
I don't want to go through with that.
And yes, I'm stalling.
That's what I'm doing right now. You figured it out.
The 15, 16,
20, whatever thousand people are here.
Yes, you figured it out.
Good for you. You want a balloon?
This is an elaborate
setup we got going on here.
Oh shit, okay.
I can hear it.
I can hear it now.
Where the fuck is it?
Where is it going?
You're aiming for there.
You're aiming at the
circle.
At the circle.
Oh, not even fucking close.
My voice cracked.
Don't delete that, rewind it and fucking remove it and edit it.
Not even close.
That was so awful like that.
What the hell are you aiming at here?
You're aiming out of a cereal box?
Guys,
you got one frog on a lily pad.
You think I'm supposed to be impressed by that?
No, I am dry as a
coat on a
rack, if that makes any sense.
Oh, hi there.
How are you? Yeah.
You gotta try it at least once, right?
They're going
for my head.
Can this go over?
Is this enough?
They're gonna be right in the face.
Same place, come on.
You're better than this.
You can do better than that, I know you can.
I'm actually concerned that
if you aim high enough, you're gonna be right in
fucking eyes.
I'm gonna have to duck.
This should be enough protection here.
Make sure I have the right plate.
Don't you fucking Jesus
Christ.
Oh my God.
You don't know how scary this is, okay?
This is a real machine.
They're trying to kill me.
I'm doing gamer neck.
You guys are so
bad. What are you
doing?
I'm going up there.
What the fuck are you doing?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me help you out here. Can I help you out here?
Let me give you guys a little bit of a hand,
because you guys are having way too much trouble.
Laptop, because I figured you guys were gonna have trouble with this shit.
This is a Dell Inspiron 4100.
This is, you don't know, this is the
computer that is all the way to the left
of Best Buy.
I almost fell in. This is my
brand new computer. Let me go and see if I can help you guys out here.
You guys are fucking
this whole thing up. What are the controls?
What are the controls?
W, A, S, D?
Let's see if I can help you.
I gotta log in though. Just give me a minute, I'm just gonna log in.
I don't know my password.
What the fuck is my password?
I have no idea what my Twitch password
is.
I think it's like Ballsack21.
Oh shit, I shouldn't have said that.
I lied!
Ballsack21 got me.
I gotta help you, because you guys are fucking
this whole thing up. Test here.
Let me do a test here, because this is...
See that?
You guys, you guys, let's go.
Let's do it.
Go down. Pull it down with me here.
Down, down here.
Yeah, looks like that makes sense.
A little further.
Come with me here.
No, go to the left.
Just listen to me, go to the left.
You know what, listen, you guys just don't get it.
That should be it, right?
I think I lied it up.
I should say fuck you streamer, that makes sense.
You guys know I love paying attention, you know, listen.
This thing, by the way, this thing
feels real new!
Can I just tell you? This is a new
laptop. Got it.
Left most spot at Best Buy. Make sure I
reiterate that. That's at least $215.
It's got a
Celeron. Intel Celeron
whatever
fucking denomination they have.
22? 2 GHz?
I don't know. How bad
would it be if for some
fucking reason
I was on the computer
and we were somehow
what an expensive piece of
technology the streamers use.
Let me help you get the dunk.
Oh, how bad would it be?
I don't know what it was.
I have no idea what it was.
I can't even.
Whoa!
You know what I love to do? I love to just like
toss stuff that's expensive.
I love to just go like this. Oh, that's fucking expensive shit.
No, I
didn't get this from, it's not a Vtech!
It's not a
Vtech. How long is that
joke gonna go on for? Let's find out.
What, 20 more seconds? 30 more seconds?
The fire, buddy.
Make it real easy for ya.
It's gone.
I can't even.
Well!
Ooh!
He's got some skills with that thing.
Let me get it on the computer.
Use mics!
Did I mention how expensive this laptop was?
Did I explain that?
Did I explain?
Ow!
Shit!
That got me.
That just got me, Odell.
Oh, it actually did.
Of all, honestly,
of all the fucking things that
injure me on this stream,
that actually
cut my hand.
Of all the things,
this like hurt me.
The tiny umbrella
is the thing that gives me like a welt on my hand.
Bring it back on the computer.
This has been tested, right?
I think so.
Down, bring it down,
bring it down.
Oh, god damn it. Oh, please.
You
killed the broadcast
and the stream.
They aimed at the gate.
That is not alright.
Get back up, I can't believe that little umbrella.
We have machines here
that are firing at me.
And I get my hand pinched
by a fucking baby umbrella.
That hurts me.
That's unbelievable. What a joke.
Get it!
Get it so I can put the laptop down.
Don't you understand the joke?
They're not going to get it. They're not going to get it.
It's too hard. It's too hard.
It's too hard. You're not going to get it.
You guys, you're not going to get it.
That was pretty close.
If this goes in, that's my whole
life liquid.
So anyways, you are not capable.
This is the easiest
game of the day.
I want to be very clear on that.
This is the easiest game of the whole day.
You did the frog launcher.
You can't do something as simple as hit the target.
Hey,
do I have nerd neck
to say yes or no?
Do I? Do I have a bad nerd neck right now?
Should I stand up? Should I stand up straight?
Okay, on a scale of one to ten, how bad
is my nerd neck?
I might as well just drop it.
They're not going to do it.
No, way too high, way too high.
You've got to go lower.
It's not going to fucking happen.
I am as safe as you could possibly be.
It's never going to happen.
You'll never dump me, you
fuckers.
Fuck all of you. It's not going to happen.
Oh no.
I can't believe it. Not my Dell Inspiron
100.
Oh shit.
Not my Dell Inspiron.
I said fuck you.
I said fuck you. That's what happened.
I didn't think they were going to do it.
I really didn't. I really didn't think they were going to do it.
Are we good?
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't believe. It didn't take
that long. It didn't take that long.
Nice job. I'll accept it.
What I really can't believe
is the fact that
I have an injury
from hiding it from you guys.
Stupid fucking umbrella.
I don't know what the fuck I was thinking.
I was getting tiny umbrellas.
I literally pinched my fucking finger
and it hurts. I hurt myself.
All the fucking things.
How disappointing.
You could have taken my skull cap off of the ball.
No, I pinched my hand on a poly
fucking
whatever it is.
How fucked up is my hair?
I probably look so bad. This is like
real Jeremy. You know what I'm saying?
Jeremy Albertson is in front of you right now.
I can't pretend. I can't fucking. What are they saying?
I can see the chat, but I can't sit too far away.
Just yell out a fucking word.
Whatever they're saying.
You said balding.
You guys have hit my eye on you.
I hope you accept that. Any boogers coming out of my nose?
Just nod yes or no. Yeah? Are there?
That's great.
I thought it was going to take longer than that.
They're making it harder.
He's like
Just for the next few minutes, I'm just going to take a nap.
It's been a long fucking couple days.
Somebody grabbed his blanket
that's down there and I can't
reach it. He can't reach it!
I actually can't reach this blanket that's over there.
I'm going to go to bed
and good luck.
People that come to this stream that don't know what's going on
I can imagine if you see a guy
sleeping on stream
in a clown
like parade thing
with a donk tank underneath him, you're probably going to be like
this guy sucks.
No you won't. No you won't!
You're going to be like this guy's awesome!
And this stream has been awesome!
And it's been a fucking awesome day so far!
And we've got way more to do!
Can somebody get that blanket underneath me?
Let's go!
Get out of my face! You're fucking blocking the view!
This thing is so heavy!
What a bad idea!
Alright, I'm ready to go to bed! Let's go!
Don't do it again right off the bat!
Not immediately!
Can I get some resident sleepers in the chat please?
You guys are just so
bad at this!
I can fucking sleep!
Oh!
I can feel it every time!
It sucks!
This joke is funny
but I actually have to close my eyes and I don't like that.
I don't like closing my eyes
for this.
Does my hair look like a fucking rabbit animal?
It probably does.
Hey, remember how funny it was?
Remember how funny it was when you aimed at the cage?
We should do that like 5 or 6 more times.
Hey, remember how funny that was?
Hey, that was really funny!
That was incredibly funny.
Why is it a package in a package?
Get out of here!
Go over there!
My phone in my pocket?
I hope my phone is not
in my pocket.
That would not be very good at all.
Hey, don't worry over there,
sir. You got it once,
I don't think you'll get it again.
That's part of the act!
Hey, why don't I go back to bed?
Why would I smoke in bed?
I have to like swear at you more
because that's the only way you're going to do it.
What's wrong with you? A bug?
Alright, you guys.
You got it once.
I don't know if you'll get it again.
That was a fluke. It was just a fluke,
that's all it was. You broke my fucking computer too.
You know where I got that?
This thing weighs like fucking
100 pounds right now.
Do you like this? Do you want to see it
go under water? Well then play better.
It's not that hard. Play better, and you'll see
this go under water. How long do I have to do
the resident sleeper? I'm sleeping on stream joke.
Do better, play better.
That's the power of doing.
Home, whatever the
company is.
I don't need the cigar.
Get the fucking cigar away from me.
You're not going to do it. It's not going to happen.
You guys can't
do it twice. Did I think you'd be
able to do it two times? Absolutely not.
You only did it once accidentally.
Accidentally the first time.
No fucking way
you'll do it twice.
How many people are
watching right now? How many people are there?
With a count of how many people are watching?
Like 200 of you can't do this?
How many? 200?
I can't see the chat from here.
There's at least 125
people here. You guys can't figure this out?
Did it already? What do you want?
You guys, there's enough people
here to do this. And I'm shocked that you
can't do it. It's kind of
embarrassing at this point.
I had this joke where I was going to ball
in the dunk tank with a fucking pillow and blanket
and you're not even capable of doing that.
Don't show my feet. Don't show feet.
That's not good.
I don't want my feet on camera.
That's a thing.
Trust me when I say that. Don't show my feet on camera.
People will fucking scream about it.
Anyways, I mean seriously,
we're looking for
skill here.
I know you. I know you very well.
How bad's the hair?
Give me like a scale of 1 to 10.
Hey, whoa, I'm going to
bed on stream again.
Come on. Come on.
Do it. I'll catch it in the air.
You got lucky that first time.
I don't think it's going to happen again.
There's a smell emanating from this tank.
And it's
very much like, it's
an ammonia smell.
I didn't piss in it. I promise.
I'm going to keep doing this routine
until it works.
You're not going to get it. It's not going to happen.
I really don't think so.
Close. It's not going to work.
Oh, wow.
You can't hit a target that's sitting in the middle
of the canvas.
It's right there.
It's so easy. It's right
there. It doesn't move.
It doesn't go anywhere. It's right
fucking here. It's a circle.
You can't even hit a circle.
That's unbelievable.
I will
hold this against you
for the next ten fucking
years. You want to...
I almost fell off. I'm slipping.
I'm going to fall off.
You're not going to get it.
You guys...
It wasn't enough power.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait. You got to get it
in the circle. That was me
falling, not you winning, by the way.
Because I'm wet and I'm
sliding off the seat.
I'm just doing
weightlifting.
Don't do it, don't do it, don't do it.
You guys...
You guys suck.
I'll be real honest.
Wait, wait, wait.
This thing is...
It's that way, blind streamer.
It's that way. Are you blind?
Are you guys blind?
Are you blind?
You're looking for that.
Can you see that?
Can they see the circle?
I just want to confirm they can see the circle.
Okay, they can.
Oh, right here. Come on.
Come on.
Oh, this is technically a circle
but not the right one.
Some of you wanted so badly to hit me in the face.
It's not going to happen. Good luck.
I'm real tired.
I just swallowed one of those.
And I'm not going to freak out about it because
it sort of slid down my throat.
This is not on screen.
I swallowed a lock that was this big.
You got two. Congratulations.
Fucking animals.
This is heavy.
Actually, it's pretty great that you can do it at all.
I got jeans on.
Don't fucking panic.
Is the GoPro in the right spot?
Only operate these things
if you're a professional, which I am.
Fucking laptop.
What happened?
What do you mean chat got me?
Chat got you?
How did chat get me? I don't understand.
Alright, so...
Are we doing another one?
Let's go. Line it up.
Come on. Give me everything you got.
No, no, no.
We're not pulling me again.
We're going to shoot the robot.
Chat has to shoot the robot at the circle.
Don't pull him again. I heard that over production.
I heard that over production.
They said pull him again.
I don't want to do that.
We're going to fire the bot.
Over here.
Pull him again.
No, don't pull him again.
There's much more today.
This is not it.
I'm happy that you can at least get me once.
The second time was bullshit.
Let's go.
I want you to give me everything you have.
Everything you have.
First try.
Get it first try.
Get it first try or I'm done.
First try or I'm done.
I'll say it five times.
This is so wet.
It's so uncomfortable.
I'm just going to scream.
You guys don't got what it takes.
And that's fine.
You did get it.
You beat this more than any other game though.
That's good on you.
I'm going to scream the whole time.
Just be ready.
This mic is going to be loud.
I'm spelling.
No, that didn't work.
I thought it happened.
You know when you have like a flash
of something that's going on
and you kind of process it in your brain
you know what I'm talking about.
When you have a flash in your mind and you know what's happening
right this second.
That's like, what the fuck is happening right now?
Is this a dream?
Is this actually
happening?
I guess it is.
This was a dream that I had.
I didn't do a live stream.
So technically it is a dream.
You're coming up here and I'm wondering why.
So you have something to ask?
You? You have something to ask me?
What is it?
You're just coming up here.
You're just getting in my way for some reason.
Well, I can tell you a quick little story
while we try to have a little bit of a production
issue.
I don't have anything for you.
Literally there is like
I'm telling you don't do that.
I told you that like five times.
You should have listened to me the first time.
Get this guy out of here.
You understand like Twitch TV has
this thing where they fucking just
scream the word. It's an F word.
It's not F-U-C
No.
Get the fuck
I'm dead
That was intentional.
This is so disorienting.
I'll get like arrested.
So what do you think so far? You having fun?
We still got four more games to play and more.
By the way, I just want to make
it very clear. How fucking
incredible was
Cuddles
and Polite Bully.
That was unbelievable.
That's like the best show I think I've seen all year.
I saw Far From Home and that was a better
movie than Far From Home. I mean Far From Home
was a great movie though so I don't know.
Has there been any
No, not really.
But I think for time
purposes you guys have already
done it. And plus I think I'm
going to get like a disease if I stand here for like
more than another ten minutes. Like I really think that
there's like, look, just look at the water.
This is disgusting.
I have to like breathe this in. Do you understand
that this is like green at this point?
I have to get the fuck out of this.
I'm going to go take a shower and I'm going to
go dry off. We're going to move on.
And what is next?
We are going to something very important.
So when you go to a carnival there's very
some things you do at a carnival. What do you do at a carnival?
Let's see it in the chat. What do you do?
Just look I can see a stick. That's not what you do at a carnival.
I mean like funny but
you play games
you see clowns
and you ride rides. Enjoy
getting onto one of those rides at a carnival.
Have fun. I'll see you in a few moments.
Go ride the ride.
And don't show my fucking feet on camera.
Music playing
I'm the biggest fuckin' fucker you've ever seen in your life!
What the fuck can we own it for?
Go check it out! Have fun! Have fun in the filler segment!
Take a look outside your screen, I know you've seen Las Vegas, beautiful Las Vegas.
But, there's something else, there's other stuff here.
That was cool too, I don't know what that was.
Was that a, um, the sandcastle? Castle?
I can give you, I'll give you a reality of what happened here.
I can break it down for you real easy.
Uh, you broke it. You broke it. It's okay.
Too many people were typing at the same time, and you ripped the, uh, you ripped the belt off of the pitching machine.
So, good work.
So, uh, don't worry, it's gonna get fixed.
We're working on it right now.
There are many more things that are gonna happen here.
So, but you have, you have put too many inputs in,
and you've crushed the robot that was gonna be the pitching machine.
Well, but thank God we did the tongue-deck first, by the way.
Because that would have been bad if we didn't.
Uh, but yeah, we are almost at the, uh, point of the show where we're gonna do something else very special.
We're gonna, what do you think, we're gonna do something for you?
When you go to a carnival, you tend to, like I said, check out the rides, check out the, shut this fucking thing off.
I can hear it, and it's irritating me.
Uh, when you go to a carnival, you typically ride rides, like I just did.
When you go to the midway games, you lose over and over again.
But you also get this thing taken care of, if you know what I mean.
So, what we're gonna do is we're gonna paint a picture of you.
That's right, you.
You. I'm talking about you in the chat right now.
You're gonna get a painting of yourself.
Do what you want with it, but it's gonna take a while.
Because obviously the artist has to actually draw you.
So, they're gonna do that.
They'll take care of that.
I want you to sit down.
Have a seat over there.
And I know I said that a little weirdly.
I said that, like, as if you're in trouble.
You're not in trouble.
You're not, I promise you are not in trouble.
We are gonna go, again, to the amusings of, again, Cuddles and Polly Polite.
Uh, and they are gonna draw a picture of you.
Hey Pollyanna, you're supposed to wake up.
You've got work to do, you know that?
Oh, yes you do.
Oh my.
Yes you have.
Yeah, well you better not forget anymore.
Because you've got to pick out somebody and you've got to draw a picture of them.
There are one of the people in the home in the audience that are watching the show.
Oh.
Yeah, and you've got to do...
I know what I can do.
Well, you just wait a minute because I'm gonna give you your tickle feather.
Because that's gonna make it easier for you.
Yes, I am.
I'm gonna help you with the tickle feather.
Because then you'll be a real artist.
And yeah, that would be good.
And then you'll do a good job, okay?
Okay, let me see.
Oh, you're looking fine.
Oh, pretty dolly.
Yeah, you're looking good.
I'll see you later and don't go asleep.
Yeah, okay?
Stick off your sleepiness and draw a nice picture, will you?
I will.
They're waiting.
All right.
Thank you so much, cuddles.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
She said I look nice.
Oh, I do look nice.
Oh, I look so nice.
Oh nice! I look like a real artist!
Yes, I do!
The kids must be trying to advise him.
Oh, they're too fuzzy! They're too fuzzy!
Oh! Oh, I can find somebody!
I can look, I can look deep into the homes of my viewers!
Oh, I gotta find someone! Oh!
Oh!
I found someone!
Oh! They'll do nicely!
Very, very cute!
What? No, I must pee!
Eenie meenie minie moe!
What do I want to do? Okay.
Oh, he is!
Four minutes.
I'm so tired. I'm just so tired.
You wait till you see you!
You're doing such a good job and you're working so hard.
I thought I would give you a present.
I brought you something.
For me?
Maybe you're a little tired, yeah, because you haven't had a whole lot to eat today.
So I thought I'd give you a little something for you. Is that okay?
Oh, is that for me?
Oh, cuddles stink so very much!
Check it out! I know you're gonna like it!
I'm so hungry!
Oh, you'll like it!
Oh, boy!
Oh my God! We have a quarter pounder!
Oh, thank you so much!
Yeah, check it out!
Thank you so much! I'm so hungry!
I know!
I'm very, very hungry.
See? There it is!
Open it up! Yeah, that's a quarter pounder.
Okay!
That's a quarter pounder!
I got it, I got it, see?
Oh, well, cuddles, I need that!
Well, so what?
That's nice.
Beautifully beautiful. We'll see what they come up with at the end of the show.
Maybe they're painting you.
Well, they are painting you. Of course they are.
So what we have here is we have a series of images on the backdrop here.
You've played Down the Clown before.
You're about to play it on stream, motherfucker!
That was rude. That was really rude.
But you just dunked me in the tank and I just had to change.
I had to change my clothes, for God's sake!
That was rude. Was that too rude?
Should I have been a little bit nicer? Was that too rude?
Was that fine? Was that too rude? Okay.
I feel like I was a little rude.
So, you need to aim this machine.
It's the same machine that was at the dunk tank, by the way.
You need to aim this machine at the various images on the screen.
And there are quite a few, as you see.
Knock them down. Down the Clown.
You're in control.
The controls will be on the screen.
They're pretty similar to what they were at the dunk tank.
So, obviously, right?
We've got German Dupe 1, German Dupe 2.
Can we see some of the chat, please, by the way?
We are. We can see them.
I have to get out of the way.
Because I've been told that this will hit me from any point inside of the cube.
So, I kind of have to get the hell out of here.
Because you guys will seriously injure me.
And the only injury I've had all day was from the little umbrella.
This is true, by the way. All the production people.
I actually got injured by the little umbrella.
Like, seriously.
And we had to wrap it up.
There was blood everywhere back there.
But, do your worst.
Knock them all down.
Try to get as many as you can.
Good luck.
I will be commenting, and I can see the chat this time.
I don't trip over this.
Good luck.
Make it work.
Your inputs are disabled at the moment, but they will be active very soon.
Any food in this carnival? Yes, there is.
There is plenty of food.
What happened to audio?
I'm still here. I'm fine.
I just have to get away from the machine.
Wow, that was close.
That was close.
Right off the bat, almost right there.
Nice feet, man.
Give me a break.
We've got a guy here that wasn't aware of the feet thing.
Take down the Jupiter first.
There's no feet on camera.
Stop talking about feet.
Jerma Jupiter first.
Take it down.
It's clogged.
Oh, you got it.
Jerma Jup 4 has been knocked down.
Congratulations. Good job.
I did it.
No, you collectively did it.
Together you did.
Can you get them all?
Can you get all four?
No, that was me.
It was me.
It was all of you.
You all did it.
Can't you just give yourself some credit, all of you, together?
Let's go.
Go for Jerma Jupiter 1.
Jerma Jup 1.
Let's go.
By the way, these robots are all provided by AniMark.
That was a fucking terrible display.
Absolutely disgusting.
Were you guys even trying?
What the hell was that?
See, right now I get to be right over here.
I can see the cameras.
I can see the chat.
That was disgusting.
That was so bad.
Let's do better than that.
Like, seriously, I'm watching right now.
This is the first time I've been able to watch.
I suck.
You suck.
What are you talking about?
You guys saying I suck?
I have nothing to do with this.
I'm an observer of what you guys are doing.
I didn't do anything.
You have to control this.
Tilt up.
Tilt down.
Aim left.
Aim right.
W-A-S-D.
Get it.
Oh.
Oh, it went down.
It went down.
That technically counts.
That counts, I guess.
200 IQ chat.
Something like that.
By the way, if you get all four Jerma Jupiters down, I will dab in front of the camera.
I ain't doing it unless you get all four.
I will dab on camera if you get all four Jerma Jupiters.
How's that for incentive?
Come on.
Do it.
You want to dab?
No.
You got it in the same spot.
Right in the same spot as before.
Come on.
More to the left.
Pull it over.
A is left.
D is right.
You have to tilt it.
W is tilt up.
S is tilt down.
Play by the rules, god damn it, before I cancel it.
Where are you going?
Where are you going with this?
There you go.
Come on.
Do it.
You got one second.
Oh.
Too far.
Let me get back there.
Let me coach you guys a little bit here.
I feel like if I was on camera and I was back there, aim at the streamer's face.
You know what I'm saying?
It's like, let's go.
Come on.
Right here.
The streamer is now ready to get hit in the face by a fucking ball.
You actually did it already.
I mean, surprising.
Yes.
Hit the streamer in the face.
You can do it.
I know you can.
I know you have it in you.
Once there's real danger involved, real danger, I could get hurt here.
Do it.
Right here.
Jerva Joop 3.
That's not in the right spot.
Turn it.
Turn.
Get it.
You've got to go left.
Pull it this way.
I think the ball got stuck.
The ball was lodged.
You see, you guys are going, and I feel like somebody is spying on me.
It's you.
You're the spy.
It's always you.
You're coming and you're showing my feet and shit.
You know how long it's going to take to get over, it's going to take like three years for
this community to get over the fact that you show up my feet on camera.
You show up my feet on camera and all of a sudden, literally, I've got to shuck the balls
because we're running out.
It's going to take like two or three years because to get over that.
You know when you do something that you regret, that's one of those things.
I regret showing my feet on camera.
Can I ask you a question seriously?
I can't see the chat from here, but what the fuck is the feet thing?
What are you talking about?
It's just hands.
They're bigger and they're longer and they're on the bottom of your body.
Get over it.
Wait a minute.
Have you got it?
Are you going to get it?
Come on.
Get it.
You got to get the full Jupiter.
It's not even worth it.
The whole Jupiter.
You can do it.
No.
More to the left.
More.
Too much.
Way too much.
Let me get some balls for you.
Guys, I know.
I mean, not here.
Here.
Can I demonstrate?
Can I demonstrate for them?
Guys, you're aiming so far to the other side.
Oh, sorry.
I'm going to knock you.
What are the others?
Any others?
Let me show you.
I'll show it to you.
You guys, you're going so far this way.
Collectively try to get it in the right spot.
Look.
Easy.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Hit the streamer in the face.
Remember what you did with the fucking frog game?
Wasn't that funny?
That's how we shuck balls to get them so we can continue to play the game.
Down.
Further down.
Get German Jupiter or I'll delete the emote.
You guys have like 10 minutes.
I will delete this emote if you do not knock it down.
You don't want that.
Nobody does.
The timer.
Get it.
Where the fuck are you going?
Where are you going?
I've got to have a talk with chat.
I'll be back.
I've got to go see the chat.
This is unbelievable.
I can see what you're saying.
Predicted aim.
I'm going to delete the emote.
It's hard.
We're trying.
I'm rubbing my hands.
Of course it's hard.
It's really hard.
Please, we need a crosshair.
We need a crosshair.
I'm just sitting here rubbing my hands.
This is exactly what I wanted.
Somebody give 10 community subs.
Holy shit.
Evil crucifix.
Thanks for the 10 community subs.
Maybe you'll get it.
Chat needs food.
I ain't making any more food.
I almost hurt myself making cotton candy.
That's not a joke.
I truly almost hurt my hand.
That thing spins at like 400 miles per hour.
I didn't know that and I almost like fucking burnt my hand off.
Get it.
That was really close.
You had a chance.
We hunger.
Hold.
Shift it left.
I know.
That's what I'm saying.
Every time you go left and right, it's one step.
That's not bad.
Bring it down.
Too high.
Come on.
It's not.
What do you mean rigged?
How is it rigged?
You guys are in total control.
I'm not controlling this shit.
I'm all the way back here.
Look at where it is.
It's rigged.
It's only rigged if you think it is.
Let us hit you again.
I didn't let you hit me.
You actually did.
If you delete Jupiter, we'll do only feet clips.
I'm all right with that.
That's not bad.
To the right.
Come on.
One second.
To the right.
Oh, come on.
You guys got one so quickly and then you've got two so quickly.
Come on.
You guys can do it.
Feed chat.
All right.
Somebody gave 50 community subs.
Holy shit.
AB Joe, you just gave 50 community subs.
You've got to be kidding me.
Thank you so much, AB Joe.
I might have missed a lot.
I've been up in tanks and over in the corner, but seriously, that's a lot of subs.
Thank you so much.
Really appreciate it.
You guys have to at least get some of these.
What about Jerma Payne?
Come on.
Work together.
You guys beat Dark Souls, for God's sakes.
No.
Almost there.
Close, but not really close enough.
What do you get for Jerma Payne?
Well, what will happen is if you get Jerma Payne or all four Jupiters, I'll dab on camera.
You're talking about those?
Because it's easy to get the top four.
Jerma Jup 1, Jerma Jup 2, Jerma Jup 3.
I can't even talk.
If you get Jerma Payne, I will dab on camera, I swear to God.
I promise.
I'm going to stand behind the net so I don't die.
Sounds like a good idea.
See, now I fucked it all up because everyone's going to freak out.
People are going to be like, well, now we have to do that.
I thought an incentive would help.
Oh, now you're going down there.
Good, good.
I'm going to get some balls here.
Let me help out here.
I've got to get a few balls.
I have faith that you guys might be...
I don't know.
Depends.
How bad do you want me to dab on camera?
This one is stuck there forever.
If you guys want me to dab on camera, you're going to have to get Jerma Payne or all four Jupiters.
That's the only fucking way.
That's happened in no chance any other way.
Let me try to get this one.
That's wedged.
That ain't coming up.
I hope I don't break this.
Get out of here.
I promise I'll do it right in the middle.
Remember, you can only do it when it's the green light.
If you are doing commands with a red light, it's not going to work.
Jerma Payne, there it is.
That's not even a real emote.
I put that up there for you guys.
That's a community place.
Oh, they're close.
Oh, you got to go up a little higher.
If you go up even 5%, 10%, I will literally dab on camera and do it.
We suck.
No, you dunked me twice.
That's pretty damn good, I will say.
Get Jerma Payne.
Get it.
I know you can.
A little bit more to the left.
Maybe to the right.
Is that it?
No.
More.
You got to go more.
It's the wind.
The wind.
It's getting caught in the wind and flying forward.
There is a lot of wind.
You got to remember that.
More to the left.
That's too much.
Don't overcompensate.
That's not going to help.
I wonder.
That looks all right.
That's not bad.
That could be it.
Did they get it?
Oh, that was so close.
Don't move.
Nobody touch anything.
Do not move.
Just don't move.
Don't move.
Don't touch.
Nobody touch any buttons.
Just put, somebody press W once.
If someone presses W one time, it will stop.
Just W once.
Don't move.
No.
Stop it.
Stop pressing S.
W.
It's going to go up.
Up.
Right, right, right.
Stop, stop, stop.
Don't.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop.
Too much, too much, too much, too much.
That's too high.
That is too high.
Down, down, down, down, down.
Oh, God.
I love this.
This is fantastic.
I was wrong.
All right.
I'm not going to say anything.
You guys just do it.
I won't.
I'm not going to talk.
I'm going to watch.
Okay, don't listen to me.
I'm wrong every time.
I'm coming over here.
I'm coming to you.
I'm coming around.
Is the wind causing problems?
We have to have people hold this.
That's pretty good.
Oh, man.
All right.
Listen.
Listen to me.
This is, bring it down once.
All the people that are fighting going up, up, up, up, down, down, down, down.
Just bring it down once.
You have to, people, there's gonna be overcompensation.
If you're gonna go down, somebody press up
because some people are spamming it.
Go, keep it there, bring it up, down a little bit.
That's all you gotta do.
Down a little bit.
You wanna dab on camera, that's how you're gonna get it.
That's the only way you're gonna get it.
You can see that like, which way do we go?
I think it's up.
I love it.
That's so funny.
Look at this wind.
What the fuck?
The wind just instantly stopped it.
That's so funny.
It's never gonna happen.
A good thing I don't have to ever dab.
That like hit the front.
It's crazy because you got this one in five seconds
and then none for like 20 straight minutes.
There's so much in-fighting, I love it.
I love it.
Get, oh no, you're changing tactics, I think.
Going up.
I don't know, going up it seems, maybe down.
You can do it.
Oh, up.
All right, hold on, let me get a few.
Let me get some, let me get some.
Can I get some balls?
Look, I'm the shucker, so.
You guys have to do this, I mean, come on.
We got all this stuff here, you're gonna get shown up.
Down the clown.
You guys can't do this.
This one is stuck here forever.
Hold on, let me get it out.
Yeah, let me throw a few.
Let me see.
I have to, look, I have to prove it's winnable.
With the wind, I know it's hard to prove, let me get two.
All right, the robot's right here, right?
It's a twister!
All right, I tried, I tried, let me, hold on.
If I can get one of these and just prove it, all right.
My own game doesn't work, it's rigged.
Surprise.
All right, I'll give you one.
Okay, I got you one.
It's rigged, it comes back up.
Here we go, here it comes.
It's actually rigged, well, that's what happens.
Let's go, accept it, let's do it.
10 seconds, come on guys, I know you can do it.
That's too low, you gotta pull it up a hair.
Pull it up a hair.
There, oh, oh, so close.
Reloading the robot.
All right, we're gonna give you guys two more attempts.
Two attempts, I know you can do it.
Do it, I know you can, please.
You've only got a hair, it's very possible.
I know it's completable, I know you've seen me do it.
From the same distance as the robot, come on.
You need to win the prize, which is a dab,
which I'm gonna regret for the rest of my life.
That's not a bad spot, not bad.
And that's pretty bad, and that's pretty bad.
We'll get one more shot, you got one more fire.
One more shot, you got one right off the bat.
You got one, and 25 minutes later, we can't get any others.
That's surprising.
Make this be the one, come on.
Do it, oh, oh my God, unbelievable.
I can't believe they actually did it.
That was your last shot, that was the final shot.
Oh, wait, that means, hold on.
That means I have to dab on camera.
Well, that's not good.
I fucking can't believe it.
It deserves some claps, it does.
Two of us will give you some round of applause for that one.
All right, time to dab, we're gonna move on.
You did it, I actually can't believe it.
Oh, I have to dab on camera.
Which camera am I on?
Can I just pretend to do it?
Do I have to actually do a full dab on camera?
I have to?
Why did I say that?
I should've just said you have to get all four.
My own worst enemy here.
So which way, which way, left or right?
That way, okay.
34 years old, by the way, tomorrow,
in case anyone's curious.
That's not a lie, that's real.
Oh, that hurt.
You can tell how many times I've done that
by me hurting myself on a dab.
Okay, so we're gonna move on, thank you.
I'm like afraid this is gonna shoot me in the chest.
Imagine that, it was just like, ugh.
We actually had a joke that we were gonna do,
but we couldn't, because it was too dangerous.
We were gonna load in a little dummy ball,
a little like foam ball,
and they were gonna shoot me right in the chest
with it right in the beginning.
I was like, oh yeah, I'm introducing the games,
and I get hit right in the chest by a fucking ball.
But there was just the legal shit,
it was just that we couldn't do it.
We could not do that.
Because if there was a chance that a regular softball
got in there and I would get hit in the chest,
it would be like Happy Gilmore.
That's not all right, that's not okay.
And medical staff speaking,
we've got plenty of people that are over there
that are ready to wait in case I get hurt by an umbrella.
But medically speaking, we didn't have the staff.
To be prepared for me to get hit in the face
by a real softball.
So, we didn't do it.
But we are at the point in the show where,
and I know there's gonna be a lot,
you know what, I can already see it.
This is like, there's already 100 images.
I can see them on the subreddit.
And that's at the German N95.
So by the way, it's still September.
What day is it?
Is it 22nd?
When does September stop?
21st.
Okay, so September stops at the end of September.
If you feel like subscribing to the channel,
then don't, don't.
It's not worth it.
This channel sucks.
You're better off fucking buying
like a pack of bubblegum or something,
but just don't either.
Anyways, we have way more to do.
Let's talk about these.
So over the course of the stream,
how did I hurt myself again
with this little shit I don't understand?
I'm hurt.
I actually hurt myself again.
How the fuck is this possible?
The tiny umbrella, the paper.
I just paper cut my hand.
I just wipe it up my ass.
On my ass, not up, you know, you get it.
We have been tracking how many bits have come in
through the course of the stream.
And over the course of the stream,
there has been quite a few bits that have come in.
So what we're going to do
is I'm gonna try to collect as many as I possibly can.
And we're gonna do that with a very, very important task
that I will have to do
and any bits that I do not collect through this machine,
we're going right to charity.
You heard it here first.
So why don't we, you can take this from me.
Why don't we cut to the money machine?
And welcome by the German 95 arcade.
This is the arcade.
We have some cool stuff here.
Got an authentic Pac-Man stand-up cabinet,
which is, you know, that was,
you can get it at Walmart, it's not that much.
Money machine, I have to collect as much of this as I can
otherwise it's going right to charity, you understand?
We also have, I forget about that, that's not real.
I am going to get eye protection first
because if one of them's right there,
you know what I'm saying?
Let's see how much of this I can actually get.
By the way, thank you to anybody that has given any bits
during the stream.
I am ready to collect as much as I can.
And what have we got here?
Somebody gave two, wait, there was, wait, there was a,
there was $200 donation, a bit donation?
Two fifties, a 10?
All right, so we've got a lot of money here.
And there was a lot of money that was given so far.
It's all in here already.
And just total transparency.
There it goes, it's in there.
I cannot see it.
I can't touch it until, of course, this is closed,
which, and then I got 60 seconds to figure it out.
Let's see how much I can get from me,
how much money I can collect.
Are we ready to turn this fucking thing on
so I can embarrass myself in front of my parents some more?
Because I heard they were watching.
Mom, I'll take you out to dinner tomorrow night.
Probably like next week.
I'm ready, begin!
I got a dollar, I got one cent!
I got a dollar, I got one dollar, two dollars!
I got a 10!
Always going to the corner.
I'm just gonna try to scoot.
Where's the 100?
I need that 100.
I got a 100!
No, don't put it in your pants, that's bad.
It's way harder than it looks.
I can't see!
They're all wedged in here!
Is that it?
That's it?
So, that's it, okay.
That counts, that counts, that counts, that counts.
This one counts.
So what'd I get?
A dollar.
Did I lose the 100?
I have one cent.
One, okay, a dollar and one cent.
Can we keep track of these so long?
Okay, all right, that's gone.
A dollar and one cent?
So that's $11 and one cent.
$11 and two cents.
$12 and two cents.
$13 and two cents.
$14 and three cents.
$15 and three cents is a big one.
That's $24 and three cents.
Oh, you didn't think I got a fucking big one?
That's $73 and three cents.
$84 and three cents.
$84 and four cents.
There you go, that's what I get to keep.
You want me to go again?
I get to get more money?
All right, let's do it again.
Did more come in?
Oh, more money came in.
More money came in.
Fucking thing up again.
Let's see if I can get out of here with the fakers.
By the way, this doesn't work.
Let's sit here for show.
I'm sorry, I had to put something here.
How much was that?
Hold on, wait, wait, wait.
Did you just put in like nine cents?
It was like, yeah.
So if we're going again for nine cents.
Here we go.
You want to lock it?
I'm ready.
I'm looking for that hundred.
I'm only going for hundreds.
What if I just pick them up now?
Is that legal?
No?
Okay, can I?
Got it.
$200, $220,000 bits.
20,000 of them.
I got enough tactics.
Oh my God.
Okay, I need help.
You don't help me?
Son, you need to get out of here.
That one counts.
Hey, I need somebody to take these.
I did it.
10, $10 and one cent, $12 and one cent.
I need somebody to count.
What is it?
$12 and two cents.
Oh my God, $12 and three cents.
$12 and four cents.
That can't be it.
$12 and five cents.
That tactic was not good, apparently.
How did I not end up with a hundred?
I was like doing the vacuum.
This is gonna, hold on.
No, there's nothing else in here.
That was it.
Okay.
Well, that's going to charity.
We are gonna move on to the next game.
And why am I, I don't need to still wear these.
We're going on to the next game.
The next game is going to be the cheese game.
Get the fucking ball with the cheese.
See you over there.
Let's go.
This is back in the launcher machine.
We are going to do, get the ball and the cheese,
switch cheese game.
I feel like you guys can do this one pretty well.
Because if you take a good look, you will see we have,
there's a lot of holes, but we do have one, two, three,
four, five, six green holes and some wiffle balls.
You have to get the wiffle balls into the green holes.
That's the only way it counts.
Nothing else counts.
You have the launcher at your disposal, make it work.
You'll be launching wiffle balls.
Let's go ahead and show how it works.
As you see, we got to take a look from here.
I lost.
Into the green holes, the only way to get points.
That's it.
That's the game.
If you can get, all these are worth one point, by the way.
If you get to five points, I'll fucking,
I'll tap on street, I don't know, what do you want?
What do you guys want from me?
Five points, then you get to live with it
for the rest of your life.
And you collectively, I don't even know how many people
are watching, there could be 100, there could be 100,000.
How many people are watching, you get to live with that
for the rest of your life and you won a game
with a bunch of people.
So if you could, work together.
Make it happen and have fun.
Good luck.
We're setting up the bot, making it work.
I actually, I still can't believe
they only got like $11.
What, like 300 bucks to come in?
That kind of sucks.
I gotta say, this room is very expensive.
I'm gonna have to hit them.
I'm gonna have to try, I'm gonna have to take it alone.
All right, let's go.
Whiffle balls, they travel differently than the frogs.
The same machine, different game.
Keep that in mind, the controls are on the screen.
You're looking for the green holes.
Not the yellow ones, the green ones.
Get them in the green ones, only, please.
Otherwise, I'll be very upset with you
and I'll start fucking talking shit.
You don't wanna hear that.
But hey, you probably don't wanna hear me.
Maybe better off if I stopped talking at all.
Oh my goodness, guys.
Holy shit, not even on the board?
That's not good.
Get your whole family here, maybe they'll help you.
Call your siblings, your grandfather, your grandmother.
That was pathetic.
I'm just gonna call it like I see it.
You fell off an edge in Dark Souls,
that's what you did.
That's kinda how I can tell you how that was.
Green holes, I know you can do it.
Sun is shining, you're here.
You got a little bit more control, I think.
That's not bad.
Not bad.
More.
You gotta get it in the game board, at least.
Not just, you gotta get the right spot.
Here it comes, zero, all the way in the corner.
That is not any points.
You're kinda close, but not really.
Kinda close, but not really.
You have quite a few chances here.
Going for green.
Green only.
Here, here, here, here.
There, there, they're random.
So it's not, they're all in one spot.
15 seconds, come on.
Cue it up.
Do it.
Fuck off, come on.
I'm walking around doing a presentation
and everybody wants to fire at the presenter.
Hey, that guy walking around,
why don't we take fire at that guy's face?
Like we did last time.
You got 20 seconds to do this.
Line it up.
Two in the corner, don't aim in the corner.
Oh, they're not close enough.
Now the balls stay, so that helps.
But you do gotta get three points.
Otherwise you lose.
You'll lose if you don't get three points.
Wink.
I'll leave it, I'm not gonna fuck around, I'll leave it.
I would try to go short, not go long,
because then it'll roll.
Oh, almost, not quite.
So close, so close, so far.
You don't win unless you get it in the green.
I'm sorry to say, I hate to crush your dreams here.
And you gotta get three of these.
You want a shotgun blast at one of these?
Maybe, for fun?
Because remember, you gotta go,
once they fill in a little, you have a chance here.
I would go for the left side, but that's me.
I'm not you.
It got stuck.
But you aimed it wrong anyways.
The wind is like pushing it.
I'll give you a wind denominator, ready?
Watch this, ready?
See?
Wind's going this way.
I mean, these balls sure are bouncy.
Hey, I can't believe how bouncy these balls are.
Jeez, I can't believe it.
What the heck is going on here?
This is a bouncy grass.
I'm a trained magician, at least they're pretending.
Right here, they'll get it right now.
Too high.
Pull it down.
Let me help you.
See, normally Akani would not do that for you,
but I just filled in a few more slots.
The hammer is like trying to come down so bad.
And this is the real deal, by the way.
Take a look at that.
Look at that engineering.
This thing is the actual real deal.
Not a bad spot.
You gotta get one point, otherwise what a waste of time.
Zero.
You don't get points for getting almost there.
You only get points for getting there.
One point is worth a pretend sneeze on camera.
Just in case you're curious.
I'll do like a funny, I love how I laugh out loud.
Sneeze on camera.
That's what that's worth.
I love watching it just fight.
I love watching the little like.
Judging, that's not even in a hole.
You got four in the same corner.
Judging by how much is in here,
I would probably pull it out a little.
You gotta come out just like a full foot this way.
You guys are going way too far into this corner.
Pull it back a little.
Hi, okay, sure.
Let's see what you do.
Let's try.
There, I'm just, I'm filling holes for you guys.
These don't hurt like the frogs do, the frog hurt.
Green means go, red means stop.
You know the controls by now.
Right here, this way, this way.
Pull it right there.
You can do it right here.
Yes, yes, more.
That's gonna be the one.
That's it right there.
That's a point, I think.
That's a point.
I thought you guys were gonna do it.
You tried though, almost.
Look at all these, look at this.
One over, one over, two over, one over.
Do it.
There you go.
Bingo.
That's one.
What did I say?
Oh, right, sorry.
Let me switch to this camera over here.
Get to this camera here.
Please, get to this camera.
This one over here, if you can for a second.
I wanted to clear.
Switch this one here.
Yeah, switch this one over here.
You good?
Thank you.
What a stupid fucking shitty prize.
Whatever, keep going.
Imagine you go to a carnival and the guy's like,
hey, it's $5 for two balls.
If you get one point,
I'll sneeze in front of your girlfriend.
Okay, see you later.
It was nice to meet you.
What's your boyfriend's name?
Greg?
Hey Greg, how are you?
My name's Steve.
Thanks.
You got one though, three is worth something else.
No, I thought I was gonna keep rolling.
Good, you got one.
You got one, that's all it takes to get a sneeze.
Top 192 variety streamer on Twitch.
I've been the top 500 variety sneeze streamers
on Twitch TV.
Very proud of that.
What did he say?
Have I dropped down a few spots?
No, look at that.
Look at, you guys are so close to the connect four.
Look, you need one, look at how good that is.
It's just not good enough.
So close.
You think the ball standing would help?
Apparently not.
Good, I like the angle.
I like the angle being used here.
What happens if I get three points, what do I do?
Should I elbow drop the table?
Come on, shit.
Should I just elbow drop right in the middle?
You guys win.
Probably break my elbow.
Let me, I wanna see what you guys are saying.
I wanna go see the chat.
How's it going?
You guys capable of this shit?
I know you are, come on.
Give us the goat.
You don't get the goat unless you get two.
If you get two, you get the goat.
We get your feet if there's three balls.
That's not gonna happen.
I can't, I'm so sad that that turned into a thing.
Say Peter for the next point.
No.
No, too low.
That was such a miss.
I wanna see the goat's feet.
Why?
Why do you wanna see that?
That was too low and too high, yeah.
You guys are crazy.
Come on, turn it.
We're not making it easy for you.
That's not bad.
No, it's over.
Way over.
Not bad.
You're not gonna do it.
You're going too low.
Two is for the goat.
Yeah, if you get two points, you get a goat.
And I'll hold it up so you can see it on screen.
You can screenshot it.
Cause I ain't sending everybody goats.
That whole corner is now taken up.
Here, ready?
Give me your hand here.
There it is.
Two, get two.
You know what, I'll help you out even more.
How much help do you guys need?
How much do you think?
Shit.
Right there.
Do it.
How much coaching do you need?
No score.
You're running out of space to put these,
but I can see where you're going with them, right?
You can see where you're going with these.
Mostly on the right side is where you're going.
Not a whole lot on the left.
Take one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
More than 10 shots on the right.
Less than six on the left.
You might wanna go for the left here.
That would probably help.
Cause remember, it bounces around.
So it would bounce into the corner back over here,
but you're going too far.
Damn.
At least you got a sneeze.
Hey, let me help.
Come on.
Do it for Wailord.
Okay.
All right.
Hold on.
Keep playing, guys.
I mean, like, for real.
What the fuck is going on here?
I mean, like, give me a break.
Guys.
I mean, if you can't do it, you can't do it.
I'm trying to help you.
I really am.
What the hell was that?
Okay.
Go on, go on.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Let's go.
You got like six extra spots.
Come on.
I know you can just do it.
Two points.
You got like a three or four extra spots now.
Come on.
Look at, look at that.
Look, look, look.
Look at how many spots you got there.
You need two points for a go.
Do it.
Come on.
At this point, it's impossible to lose.
Oh, come on, come on.
Wait a minute.
Just shoot it in this fucking corner.
Get it in that corner.
Just get it in the corner and you can win the game.
Oh shit.
Hey, can we get that water jug back over here?
Oh, it's.
All right.
That's not coming off.
It's green forever.
Just get it in the corner and just please win the game.
All you have to do is get it in that quadrant.
That's two points.
Get three, please.
Just get three.
Just get three so we can move on.
Just get three points so we can move on, please.
Thank you.
If you aim over here, you're an idiot.
I just want to make sure we're clear.
If you aim to the right, you might be an imbecile.
I just want to make sure that we got to be very good.
Go on.
Let's go.
Do it.
Come on.
Right in the teeth.
Hey, but break all my front row.
Break the whole front row of teeth.
Right there.
Come on.
Damn.
Do another one.
I can't touch my face.
If I touch my face, it's pain on my face
for the rest of the day.
That way.
I'll pick it up and put it over there.
Go for it.
In there.
There you go.
You're way off.
You are so way off.
It's not even funny.
More to this way.
There's like, there's like a pain over here.
Good.
More power.
No, no, no, no.
More, more, more, more, more, more, more power.
More power.
That's not enough.
More.
Give me the ball.
Hey, wow.
Would you look at that?
I can't believe you got swans.
You actually did it.
Holy crap.
Holy heck.
You got a point.
You got three points there.
Holy heck-a-rito.
I can't believe it.
So, coming up next is a group of clowns.
We've got cuddles.
We've got Miss Polly Polite.
There they go.
Bring them out.
Wait, am I on camera?
Oh, shit.
I'm on camera.
Hey, we got cuddles and Polly Polite.
We've got to go to those two.
Oh.
I'm awesome.
What do you have?
I am not having.
Cuddles, easy.
You came.
You unpack it, put it on the tray,
and bring it over to me.
I'm gonna get ready.
All right.
All right, all right.
I'm coming back.
Just leave it out there.
I'm gonna need a bag.
A bag, a bag, a bag.
A bag, a bag.
Okay, cuddles.
Put it on the tray and bring it over to me.
I've got it all ready for you now.
I got the bandana and everything.
All right, all right, all right.
Just because you want to be there.
Magic in a box.
This is the magic bandana trick.
The Acme Company wants to thank you
for purchasing this month's trick in a box.
Empty the contents onto a tray
and place it in front of you.
Now, we're going to learn some magic.
We're going to make bandana disappear.
First, pick up the bandana.
Now, fold it in half.
That's right.
Fold it in half.
Fold it one more time.
Take the folded bandana
and secretly hide it in your left hand.
Keep your hand in a natural position.
This is known as palming.
Open up the folded bandana.
Greet the audience by waving it up and down.
Hey, to prove it's a real bandana,
why don't you wipe your face with it
or use it to blow your nose?
Pick up the red scarf.
Now, gather the four corners together and make a pouch.
Doing okay?
Fold the bandana on the same line
that you previously folded it.
When you have done that, place the bandana in the pouch.
Squeeze it tightly.
What the audience doesn't know
is that you never really put the bandana in the pouch.
You kept it in your left hand, right?
Remember, palming.
Make a magical gesture over the bag
and fling it open and await your just applause.
Finneum, tell me about that.
I don't remember.
Where's the bandana?
It's all gone.
The bandana's gone?
I ate it.
You ate your bandana?
Yeah.
Well, I'll tell you, I'll tell you why, why, why.
No, why, I'll tell you why.
Why I meant to, why I meant to.
I was like, that was really great.
Yeah, I, I, I, you look over there
because I've got something over here that I want to show you.
Come on, you can turn around and look at me, see?
Because I want to show you something that I've got.
You see, can you see that right there?
Oh, I can see that.
I can see that.
Well, basically, there's just all of these cards here.
Now, I want you to concentrate on one of the cards.
Now, I don't care which card it is, but just concentrate.
Don't tell me, don't tell me.
All right, I'm gonna pick a card.
I'm gonna pick, I'm gonna pick.
Yeah, you don't need to spin around, just pick the card.
Nevermind, don't tell me.
You're pointing at it.
That's not good because, you know,
see what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna make that card disappear
because you're gonna look at me.
Yes, you are.
You're gonna look up right there at me.
Yeah, and you're gonna concentrate
on the card that you picked.
Right, just stop.
Not so close.
I don't trust you.
Just concentrate on the card, yeah.
Poly, poly, yeah, you'll be a very poly, yes, you will.
All right, concentrate, you're concentrating on it.
All right, I'm gonna make it disappear.
Is your card there?
Oh, oh, somebody stole my card cuddles, it's gone.
No, it's because I'm smart, you know, I'm very smart.
My card is gone.
I'm a very, very, very good magician.
You're pretty smart up here.
Yeah, you know that?
You respect your elders.
Pretty smart.
Right.
Okay, well, that's all for right now
because I think I'm gonna have to get rid of some of that.
I'm gonna take that banana.
Yeah, yeah, okay, see ya, bye.
That trick.
Okay.
What is this?
Hehehehehehehehehe.
I think those used the wrong one.
Used the wrong one.
Oh, hi, cuddles.
I'm not a private with my Nana.
You can wipe.
I gotta go get some water.
I want some water.
Go get your own water.
Okay, I can get my own water.
All right, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
You're so nice to me.
Okay, oh food, you know, I gotta tell you,
I don't think she's got it yet.
She did pretty good on that trip though.
The secret is, is I never gave her the pan.
Oh, I didn't.
It's the tray and she didn't even.
I gotta tell you, I took a banana.
I was gonna eat it.
It's been a long day and I'm really tired.
I took the banana and she went like this.
She folded it like that and I can't eat it
because now it's a folded banana.
And I don't know what happened to the yellow banana.
It disappeared.
Thank you very much.
If I can bring you back over here to the carnival section,
the arcade section of the stream.
Thank you again.
Cuddles and Polyphilite.
Doing great work over there as the two best clowns,
probably in the universe.
I still got pain all over me still.
Anyways, what kind of, we're gonna be playing Pac-Man
for a little bit because we're in the arcade now.
Welcome back to the German 95 arcade experience.
As you see, we got Pac-Man and Pac-Man Plus.
We're gonna play, this is a video game stream, right?
Sometimes has to be for a little bit.
Do we have audio on this thing?
Let's find out.
Does it have audio?
Can you hear it?
Oh!
Don't go for it just yet.
Bait him around the corner.
Oh, did you see that fucking play?
That was the best play I've done all day.
Remember I told you this didn't work?
Oh, that was a lie.
I have one of the top 50 times.
This is so fucking loud.
I have one of the top 50.
Okay, I lost, but that's okay because, you know,
I have one of the top, I don't have any high score.
I'm just lying.
Let's go.
We're doing this for a little bit just so.
There we go, that's better.
Just so we have an opportunity to set up the next event,
which the clowns are.
The clowns are fucking hot right there.
I'm gonna give it a break.
Come in a little tighter.
I want them to see this.
You know, they actually sell these.
They sell these machines at Walmart now.
They're really not that expensive.
You can get one of these for 300 bucks,
which is what we did.
Holy shit, that was good.
Doesn't even require quarters.
Come on, level one, level one, level one.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Level one done.
I've actually never gotten to level two in Pac-Man.
I don't know what it looks like.
I guess it looks like this.
Louder.
Out, out, out, out, out, out, out.
I would never do that on screen,
or off screen for that matter.
I lost.
All right, I lost.
I don't know.
Come on, Pac-Man.
Let's see what you got.
Don't ever go for the balls first.
I don't, I don't, this, it came off.
How many things are gonna go wrong?
I don't know.
One, two, three, four.
God damn it, get it.
Yes.
Enki is faster than, Enki's faster.
Enki's faster than everybody.
I don't need that shit.
Up, down, right, left, down, up, go.
No, you guys don't get to play this one.
This is just me.
We didn't have the time to set that up.
So unfortunately, this is just a me thing, not a you thing.
Sorry.
The smallest things are hurting me.
Got it.
Two, three, get it.
What happened?
What's that, what, what, what, what does that mean?
What does that mean?
What's the ding, ding, ding, ding mean?
Did I win something?
What does it mean?
I've never seen level three before in Pac-Man.
I don't know what it looks like.
Don't get angry.
This is a fucking important screen.
All the way to the left, up.
Just go for it, just wait, wait, wait, just go.
Win, win, win, win, win, win, win, win, win, win, win, win.
Get it, get the, get the cutscene, quick.
Get in there quick, get, I want the whole thing.
Why are you not moving?
I did it, I won.
Why is it so loose?
This thing is so, this thing's gonna fall off
at any moment, seriously, even if I screw it in.
What an idiot.
Now it's, there's paint on this now, I've ruined it.
That's game over.
Nah, fuck it, I ain't playing again.
So what's gonna happen now is I am gonna do something
that has never been done before on the platform,
on Twitch, I'm talking total on Twitch.
What we're gonna do this time is we are going to do
Twitch play Pokemon, you've seen Twitch play
complete Dark Souls, Twitch control robots.
But, but, very important, have you ever seen,
have you ever in your life, and I mean in your entire
existence, seen Twitch versus the fucking broadcaster?
You have not.
Twitch fights broadcaster with controlled inputs,
put it on the screen please, come on, bring it in.
Get the commands on screen.
Twitch fights the guy in real life.
I'm going to wait for the commands.
You've got a left punch.
You've got a right punch.
Are we ready?
Tell me when to go.
Do we have action?
Are we doing inputs?
Jesus.
Ah, shit.
Ow, my elbow.
Don't go for the face.
Don't go for my face.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
stop, stop, stop, stop inputs.
Stop inputs.
We didn't even shake hands.
Please raise your hands.
Please raise the right.
Thank you.
Don't trick me here.
There it is.
Ow, ow.
OK, all right.
Let's go.
Inputs are taking.
Eat that, huh?
Get in the hand.
Eat this.
Eat that.
Come on, what do you got?
Right in the face.
I'll give you a free shot.
Oh, he lost his head.
Well, he regenerated.
He has regeneration powers.
Wow, that's unbelievable.
Come on, right in the face.
Do A on your keyboard.
You're going to have 100,000 of you hit A at the same time.
All right, that was pretty close.
Pretty good.
Almost.
All right, you know what?
How about this, chat?
How about this one for you?
Yeah.
That means I win.
You thought you could fight the fucking streamer?
You thought you could beat him?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Give me this.
Ah.
What is this?
Oh, this looks like some kind of mechanism.
I always win.
Don't let anybody fool you.
You got one shot in the face.
That's all that mattered.
You lost your head twice.
And I really, really hurt my hand.
Do I need to use my right hand anymore?
Because it seriously hurts.
God, I got you loot.
Plus one to fucking damage hands.
I'm going to keep this one on, because I really did.
I may have sprained my wrist, because that was a hard punch.
Somebody fucking sell that on eBay.
All right, so now we have another game for you to play.
Oh, god.
Stay there, please.
Don't fall down.
The next game is a classic.
We're going to move on to the milk bottles, the milk bottle
game.
See you over there.
So this one, all you have to do, ladies and gentlemen,
you just have to knock the bottles down right in the middle.
If you can do that, you win.
Take them all down.
The controls are on the screen.
Can you do it?
Let me get back.
There it goes.
Right in the middle, right in the center.
Looks a lot easier than it is.
I can assure you.
It's aiming directly at me.
Right in the center.
You can do it.
You just have to take them down.
Probably shouldn't be standing there.
That's way too far.
Where are you going?
Are you going into the sky?
What the hell are you guys doing?
I got a net here.
I am in complete control.
No, there's a net here.
Funny, though.
Would have been funny.
No, I'm protective.
I just want to see your reaction when you hit it.
Because I want to see it fly back.
Get it in the middle.
Remember, only when it's green.
Come on.
No.
Pull it in tighter.
You've got to go much tighter than that.
Otherwise, it's never going to happen.
But the target's so much bigger.
OK, but the last one like this, the down the clown,
there was a small little section.
You can hit anywhere on these cans.
Just hit a can.
Anywhere.
Anywhere, right in the middle, preferably.
Should do it.
Look, right in my face.
Come on.
Right in the center.
That looks good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, too high.
Down, bring it down.
Oh, darn it.
Darn it.
I almost had it.
That was close.
Very close.
Let me help you out here.
You did manage to get one, though.
That's good.
You did manage to get that one.
Let me help you get it back stacked up here.
Nice try.
Darn it.
That's unfortunate.
Too bad.
Try it again.
That was close.
Closer than I got last time I tried this.
You got the top one, though.
That's still good.
It's not bad.
Still doesn't count.
Still does not count, unfortunately.
Oh, I'm getting stuck.
I'll leave it off.
I'll leave that can off.
I mean, you just hit the top of it.
You got to get the whole thing.
You can't just hit it right at the top.
You've got a look.
Let me show you something here.
It's important.
Look at this.
So if you hit this thing here,
now people think this game is rigged, right?
Which, I mean, obviously you would think that
if you were a, you know,
your mind was a lot slower than mine was.
If you don't hit it directly in the center,
these things weigh like 45 pounds, right?
So this whole thing is like about 50 pounds.
So you got like four, eight, 12, 16, 20, 24, 28, 32,
and then a higher one, like 40.
They're very heavy.
So you can't just hit one at the top,
and then you got to get it right in the center mass,
like right here.
If you don't do that, it's not going to fall over.
Somebody probably says, prove it, prove it,
but I want you to do it.
I don't want to do it.
You've dented them.
They're very heavy.
Look, see?
You see how fucking heavy this is?
You got to go from straight on directly in the middle.
Not going to work unless you do it that way.
I'll leave the top one off.
And you broke it.
Second time today.
You guys are going too hard.
You popped out the, you popped out the sphincter.
Just realizing live the word I just used.
But that's kind of what happened.
I saw it come up.
You popped out the sphincter.
That's what, I think that's actually,
that's the technical term for the whole thing.
Maybe, I'm not sure.
Hey, want to see this?
How about this?
I, can I not do that, really?
Let's kill some time.
How the fuck do people learn how to do this?
I don't know.
Can I do three?
No, no, not a chance in hell.
I'll try to do three.
From my understanding, you have to do,
no, that's not going to happen.
Oh wait, I put you guys to chat.
What are they saying?
What are they saying right now?
I wonder.
I wonder what things they're screaming at me.
Jeremy, what the fuck is happening?
Why can't we play the damn game?
And I'll just very quickly,
there's another balloon popped off camera.
We've had like a balloon pop like every 15 seconds.
I'm not sure if you can fix it on the microphones or not.
Jeremy, I want to throw the ball at the can.
And I know you do.
Trust me, I do too.
Here's me.
Look, those of you that say that I'm bald,
if you want to take a look at the,
sure, take a look.
That's as far back as it goes.
You're getting real Jeremy Yelbertson.
There's no substitute right now.
If it wasn't so windy, oh well.
What are you going to do?
So why are you getting,
I can see you getting that close.
Pull it back.
Get the whole image.
Let me go like this.
We're trying to fix it.
This robot has seen hell.
It's gotten a ton of inputs.
The server crashed like three times,
but it still worked.
And it still works very well.
This thing is a modern marvel of engineering.
It's just taking thousands of inputs at the same exact time.
So one of the things gets busted,
they fix it, and we keep going.
Not a problem.
And I think, ladies and gentlemen,
I think we're going to be,
we are going to be close soon.
Let's go.
Oh shit.
I hear it moving.
I'm getting the fuck out of the way.
When I hear that noise, it's just like,
all right, time to get, I'm trying to move.
Please don't hit me.
Boom.
Knock it down.
You had plenty of downtime there.
You had like at least a two minute, three minute downtime.
Maybe five minutes.
Knock it down.
Get those bottles.
Get those 45 pound cans.
Wind's picking up.
Can you compensate for the wind, I wonder.
Oh.
You can see them.
Oh, those 45, 45 pound cans are really,
really taking a beating.
As you can very reliably tell.
I don't think you guys are capable
of knocking the cans down.
It's very hard.
Three seconds.
Can you do it?
Look at this thing.
Oh, too bad.
You guys don't get the Wailord prize.
Oh shit, I'm stuck.
It's a spider web.
Oh, they're going to kill me.
Just like the real thing.
You can't fucking do it.
I win.
Don't ever play this game at the carnival
because it's impossible.
You cannot win this game.
It's not completable.
It isn't.
They weigh them down.
We don't do that here.
Absolutely not.
Does that technically count as a win?
That doesn't count.
I don't know if that's a count or not.
Should it be?
All right.
No, okay.
That counts.
That's a count.
What the fuck?
Hey, welcome to the carnival.
Well, even when you rig the game,
it don't matter because
they'll find a way.
All right.
So we are moving towards another game.
But before we do,
we are going to complete this whole arc here.
We're going to go back to,
who do you think?
Where are we going?
I want to see it spammed in chat before I go anywhere.
Who's coming back out here?
What do you think?
Dog?
Is it a cat?
No.
Who could possibly be coming out onto the main stage
to perform for you guys?
That's fucking awesome.
So let's move it over once again
to Cuddles and Poli-Polite.
I'm taking him out.
Whoa!
We'll play a game.
I promise.
And we'll play a game, okay?
Any time now.
Okay.
I'm ready to play.
All right.
Stop the game.
I'm ready to play a game.
All right.
Now.
Hold the bag up like this.
You know what?
All the colors of all the ones.
What you're going to have to do
is I'm going to hold the bag up here just like this.
There it is.
Nevermind.
Can I look?
Let it go.
I'm going to hold the bag up just like this.
I'm going to reach right in there just like this
and I'm going to get a ball.
I've got one in my hand.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
So smart.
I'm so smart.
Hey.
That was pretty smart.
Careful.
I saw what that was.
Put it back in there.
Okay.
Pick out a ball.
All right.
You got a ball.
I got a ball.
I got one.
So now what I'm going to do is I'm going to hold the bag up
just like this.
And I'm going to reach right inside there
and I'm going to get a ball.
All right.
Turn around.
So you can't see.
I'm ready.
You ready?
One, two, three.
See, I told you I was smart.
Oh yeah.
You did.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So all right.
Put it down inside of there.
Okay.
One more time.
One more.
Hold my bag.
Hey, come on.
You took a ball.
Now I'm going to take a ball.
I got my ball.
You got your ball?
Yeah.
I got my ball.
You ready to show your ball?
Yeah.
I'm ready to show mine.
Oh boy.
I can't get over that that I'm so smart.
I can't believe that I did that.
Oh boy, that's good.
Now I'll show you something else if you'd be alive.
Okay.
All right.
Show me.
I want to see.
I'm sure.
You need to turn this right here.
See, these are my little doggies.
Yeah.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
If you can count, I'm glad of that.
Now what I want you to do is I'm going to make a prediction.
When I make this prediction,
I know which ducky you're going to choose.
You think you do.
Yes, I do.
So I'm going to take my prediction.
There's my prediction.
And I'm going to put it right down there inside the box.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to pick.
Yes, you can do that.
Come on.
The ducky.
No, you have to come over here and pick up the ducky.
Which ducky you're going to pick up?
Pick it up that way.
So you pick it up.
Now, would you look at the ducky's bottom?
What's on the ducky's bottom, please?
It's a number.
Yeah, there's a number.
And what's that number?
They don't care.
I care.
See, we got one, two, three, four, five, six.
But look at that.
Number three is missing.
You got a number three on your bottom of your ducky?
Because I need a prediction.
I do.
Where's my prediction?
Yeah, I got a prediction.
Hey, it says right here.
It's a three.
Hey, it says a three.
What's it say?
It says, this was the ducky that would be wearing
the pink sweater with the pink and blue hat.
I got it.
Yeah.
And if you hadn't found it, you know what?
I was going to stick a $20 bill in there
just to get you going.
But you see, you were just, no,
you were just jumping up and down and you made me forget.
So yeah, now forget it.
Forget it.
Yeah, very much.
Well, take him on my way.
I can't tell you how smart I am now.
Do you want to play the ball?
I'm the polite one.
I like to play ball.
Let's go.
That was fun, right?
Hey, well, can you believe it?
Thank you again.
Thank you.
We have a very special, special treat for you here.
This is the final game of the evening.
If you were curious.
Watch that.
Watch that final game.
Final game.
The final game is going to be the crane.
We have a crane here.
And the crane is going to be controlled
by you guys in chat.
And I hope you can get prizes.
There are various prizes in here for you to collect.
You are in control of the game.
It is you.
You got the claw.
You've got the button.
You've got the timer.
Try to grab whatever prizes you possibly can
in the time limit.
This is the last game of the evening.
But that's not true.
I'm a liar.
I'm a pretty bad liar.
So enjoy the crane game.
Have fun with it.
Try to get a good prize.
I will see you guys in a moment.
Let's see if we can get something.
Camera back.
Crane back.
Crane toward, crane left, crane right.
Got a bunch of various prizes in here that look good.
Did you just get one?
No, you didn't really just get one right off the bat, did you?
Did you get a panda right?
No, you didn't.
They didn't just really get it right off the bat.
No, they didn't.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
They won.
The first try.
They got it first try.
You did it first try.
Really?
Well, do it again.
Okay.
Wait, is it a pant?
No, it's a cat.
Wait, wait, what?
Hold on.
There was a prize in here.
What are you going for, the goat?
I picked up the wrong prize.
Oh!
No, you did it again.
You did it, you got it again.
Holy shit.
Wow.
There are a bunch, you didn't get this.
Where's the panda?
What the fuck is this?
Oh, there it is.
You guys are good at this shit, apparently.
Nice work.
Going for another goat?
You guys aren't gonna be four for four.
Is this too easy?
No, nothing.
Sorry.
Not that time.
You can see me.
You can see, oh, look at you.
There are some rare prizes in here, as there always are.
You got some orange and blue stuff.
I think that's a Fortnite pinata.
I know a lot of you guys like that game.
I mean, I would be going for the Fortnite pinata
on the right side.
It's dropping, where's it going?
No, it's gonna get caught.
No, it didn't.
Do you guys like Fortnite?
Oh, I was trying to get it, nevermind.
No, you didn't get it, unfortunately.
But you guys have a few prizes here.
You got a wheel, a cat, a panda, a goat.
I'm gonna put these down.
Only do the commands when it's green.
Zero.
Oh, they're going for Fortnite.
Are they gonna get in there?
Oh shit.
Another goat.
Really?
Winner.
I'm keeping all these, by the way.
Goated.
The controls are inverted.
Good, extra hard.
Remember, toward is toward the screen.
Back is back towards the mirror.
Thank you Invader Lurr for the five community subs.
Appreciate that.
You almost got something there.
What are those?
Close.
Those are socks.
Some type of video game that has an RPG.
From the video game Nintendo.
That's a Nintendo sock game.
It's all right, though.
I don't know if you'll get it or not.
I don't know if it's worth it.
Going for Fortnite.
Drop it.
Oh, is it gonna happen?
People are saying the controls are inverted.
Why inverted?
Yeah, guys, remember, S is towards the screen.
W is back towards the back of the machine.
When you press S, it's coming forward, like toward you.
A should be left, D should be right.
And thank you 8BitZig for the five community subs.
Appreciate that.
I love how you guys like the pretend Fortnite thing
rather than the Pikachu socks
that I've been lying about for a year and a half.
It's kind of surprising to me.
I said the word Fortnite.
Really, another goat.
Okay.
They're saying A and D is inverted.
Is A and D inverted?
It shouldn't be.
There's no way to change that.
D is left, A is right, apparently.
A for Pikachu.
It's not inverted, I'm being lied to.
Okay, well, that's fine.
What's that?
Oh, you've got Jake from Adventure Time.
Another balloon just popped.
Nice work.
This is the best, you guys are, seriously.
Oh, there's the panda.
Take a look at this shit.
That's the first thing you won.
I know I'm in the way, but whatever, you got two goats.
Wait, what happened to the thing you just won?
It's not even in here.
Where the fuck is it?
I don't see it in here.
Uh-oh.
No!
Are you gonna get it?
Oh!
They got it!
No, drop it!
Drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop, drop!
Oh!
You did it!
Congratulations.
I'll put them on.
You got the Pikachu socks.
Congratulations, guys.
Excellent work.
Nice job.
I can't.
I have to show them.
Get the Fortnite thing.
Come on!
Get the Fortnite goat, whatever that video game is.
No, nice try.
Get more goats.
Turns out out of the four plus hours we've been doing this,
you guys have been better at the crayon game
than anything else and you got the Pikachu socks.
Congratulations.
Nice work.
But can you get the not licensed bottom of the shelf
at the grocery store cereal non-branded
Captain Crunch character that is Fortnite?
Can you get it?
I wonder.
Can you get the off-brand Fortnite?
This is not Fortnite.
Don't sue me.
Thing.
I don't know.
Can they get it?
The suspense is killing me.
Another goat.
You got to get the orange Fortnite character.
Just wait a second.
Hold on.
Get Fortnite.
I love that game.
I love building and jumping and firing my shotgun.
Is this the one?
No, it's another goat.
No way.
No.
Remember, three goats get you a dab.
Oh, five.
Sorry.
We already have three.
Oh, this is fucking, this is so fun.
Come on.
Get a good prize.
What are you really, you guys are going for the goats.
Are you going to get every goat that's in here?
No, sorry.
Goat spotted is one of the things we're seeing here.
Sorry.
Now, when less are available to grab,
they get harder to get.
What do you mean rigged?
It's not rigged.
You guys, you got like seven prizes.
How is this rigged?
Oh, it's rigged.
You pulled out like eight things.
All right, come on.
Let's see it.
Get the off-brand cereal Fortnite.
No, you went for the goat.
You didn't.
Okay, another one.
Good job.
It's going to drop.
Shit.
All right, we got it.
Here we go.
There you go.
You won it.
Nice job.
And there's Jake from, Finn and Jake,
fucking throw swords at monsters,
whatever that show is called.
Better than anything else today.
Funnily enough,
chat is very good at grabbing stuff out of a box.
Not so good at firing a ball
or flipping a ball into a hole.
But very, very good at putting a crane down.
Did they get it?
Oh, no.
Almost.
We had a chance.
We're not, guys, I'm telling you right now,
I'm not stopping this till you get me a Fortnite.
We're not moving on till I get a Fortnite.
I got to stop saying that before I get in trouble.
A neon orange Jolly Rancher.
But that's a brand too.
I can't say that.
What's a non-branded orange thing?
Orange.
It's just orange, okay.
An orange dog.
I can just say that, apparently.
What do you got?
Pull it up.
Oh, they got another cat.
You guys are pretty good at this.
Cute.
By the way, all these are going to my office.
There you go.
Nice job, nice work.
All these are going up in my office.
Whatever you guys pull out of here, anything.
It's going to be a goat office at this point.
There's like a zebra in the back.
You haven't gone for the zebra?
Come on.
They want it, but I don't know if they're going to get it.
They want it, but they're not going to get it.
Is that a double prize?
That's a PogChamp right there.
That's a Garfield.
That's an orange Garfield and a unicorn.
I think they got a double prize.
Are they going to do it?
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
You got the orange fucking Fortnite Garfield
and you got the unicorn.
Unbelievable.
That's a double.
That deserves a dab.
I give it to you.
You get one.
What's all over me?
Fortnite Garfield.
Don't worry, guys.
That fucking dumb game will add Garfield probably next.
You got to double twice.
That's a quadruple.
Holy shit.
No way.
Wow.
You got two shitty dumb, that game sucks,
Fortnite characters.
That's twice in a row.
Are you kidding me?
That's two dabs.
No, you get one.
You only get one.
I'm not doing another one.
Stop saying Fortnite.
Say whatever I want.
This is my carnival.
Zebra, zebra.
Oh, almost.
Can you get the zebra?
Can you get the zebra before we move on?
Can you?
Come on.
Shroy it.
Shroly it.
Thanks for the 10 community subs.
Appreciate that.
Do it for Shroly it, please.
Get Fortnite.
I stopped saying that.
Get orange Garfield.
Or the zebra, please.
Make it happen.
He wants another goat.
No, we got plenty of goats.
We don't need any more goats.
But that looks like maybe what you're going for here.
This is a lot of prizes, though.
This is fucking awesome.
I love every second of this.
I'm so happy about this.
I hope you guys had fun.
I want another goat.
Get me another goat.
No, no, no.
Oh, the seal.
The seal is important to me.
This is the last one.
One more.
Get either the zebra or the seal.
That's what I require.
That's what I demand.
Get the seal.
Last chance.
I demand the seal.
Get it for me.
What, Jerma, old?
What?
Why?
Get it.
I know.
You guys got Jerma pain last second.
You can do this.
I think they got it.
Just get the tail.
That's all you need.
Get the tail.
I know you got it.
Oh, you gotta be shitting me.
They went double time on this one.
You got, is that three?
There's no way that's three.
Is it three?
Holy shit, you went out with a bang.
No way.
It's three.
One.
Where is it?
Wait, what?
No, wait.
This is all you got?
No.
What?
This is it?
No.
Shit.
All right.
That's it.
Calling it there.
Nice work.
No, we're not going,
this thing's saying go over in my ear.
All right.
We are going to do,
we've had some more bits come in.
Let's maybe go ahead and turn on the money machine
one more time.
See, you guys can't hear this.
Maybe.
Maybe you can.
But every,
every like 30 or 40 seconds,
a balloon pops.
It's just like,
it's just,
everyone just kind of freezes and goes,
what the fuck was that over there?
But we're going to do the money machine one more time
to get the bits from the stream.
And then we're going to move over to something else.
Just stay there.
Don't move.
Hey, there it goes.
There's the money.
How much, how much money was it this time?
I don't know.
40 bucks.
That's it.
Why is it not 4,000?
I need eye protection.
So I don't get my eye like slit.
40 bucks.
No, don't lock me.
Like you make it so scary.
Oh no, that's another balloon.
I'm ready to get the money.
Come on.
What's that?
It's all of the sealant.
Okay.
Later.
We got at least a dollar and one cent.
You know at least for a couple of cameras.
Hold on, just wait a minute.
I've got, no, don't put this on camera.
No, they can see it over there.
They can see it in the mirror.
Just cut to the, it's like 15 bucks.
All right.
So it's like, we got, we got 15.
We got, which one is it?
This one?
We got $15 and two cents.
Congratulations.
No way, I got a 10.
I got a 10 here.
Seal, seal, seal, seal.
Where?
What?
What are you talking about?
What the fuck are you talking about?
It was seal, where, where?
Trapped.
Where's the seal trapped?
Where's the, what are you talking about?
Get the seal, get the seal, foot cam.
No, where's the seal?
Free the seal.
You are on top of that today.
You are literally like making my life trouble.
He's just like aiming down.
It's in the claw machine?
No, you guys lost.
I'm sorry.
You didn't win.
So what we're gonna do now is
we are going to show you
somewhere in the beginning of the stream,
you were getting a caricature done of yourself.
We're gonna reveal that and show you
what the artist has created.
If we're gonna cut back to,
who do you think we're cutting back to?
Cuddles and Polly polite right now.
What's on that screen?
Who is the,
it's a view.
I can't wait to see this.
I did it.
You did it?
You finished.
I finished.
So you've painted, who have you painted here?
I have painted a very special audience member.
Okay, so you got a special audience member.
I did, I found one.
You got one?
I did.
Okay, well why don't we show,
there's a special audience member here
that we're gonna be showing.
Let's see who it is.
Are you ready?
Who did you paint?
Here we go.
Oh, she got you.
That's you.
Wow.
Is that me?
That's you.
No, I think that might be me.
Is that me?
Is that you?
No, that's you.
That's you.
Wow.
Unbelievable.
That looks just like you.
It does.
It looks like you too.
Yeah, it really does.
It looks just like you.
Yeah.
Well, thank you so much to Cuddles and Polly polite
for their wonderful job and a great painting too.
Watch out, she's gonna steal my socks.
No, these are mine.
These are mine.
These are my socks.
Okay.
So what we're gonna do now is we're gonna do something.
That was a pretty good caricature of you.
I think so, of me.
And there's like a dollar bill
like going down my underwear right now.
There is a dollar bill going down my underwear
at the moment.
And it's currently causing me some discomfort.
So I'm gonna go ahead and try to fix that
while we move on.
What we're gonna do now,
we're gonna go back to the fan favorite machine
because I know a lot of you are probably saying,
Jeremy, yeah, Jeremy, Jeremy sucks.
And I know it's fine.
But what we're gonna do is we're gonna do
one more segment with the dunk tank
because I know a lot of you wanted to see that again
and try to dunk me again.
So that is what we're going to do
when we come back from potentially a few minute break.
We're gonna come back
and we're going to do the dunk tank one more time.
So if we will cut to a be right back screen,
we'll be back in just a moment
for one more dunk tank extraordinaire.
This is the main event.
So I figured we'd do it for a little bit longer.
Try to dunk me.
We're gonna do this until we break the machine.
So what I think I would like to do
is if the folks over at Andy Mark,
the supplier of the robots,
they did, first of all, let me just say,
they did a fantastic, a fantastic fucking job
this whole day with the robots and everything.
It's been an absolute delight.
Incredibly talented, fucking awesome people there.
We're gonna try to break this bot.
So if you could, whoever is in control,
drop the slow mode to zero.
Let's try to break this fucking thing.
Let's make it happen.
Drop the slow mode to zero.
Let's try to kill this bot and try to drop me down.
If you could.
Let's see what we can do
with one more dunk tank appearance.
I'm ready.
I don't know if this is a test or not,
but we're gonna find out.
Get rid of slow mode.
It's been on five, 10 seconds the whole night.
Get rid of it.
It's like,
holy shit.
No, that's not gonna do anything.
You're gonna set it to space.
Seven seconds, come on.
There it goes.
See you later, come on.
Where is it?
Where are you going?
I think they broke it.
All it took was one time.
It's still going.
All right, this is freaking me out.
I'm kind of scared of this too much.
Okay, you broke it.
You already broke it.
So we're gonna go back to the five to 10 second slow mode
because you've already broke it.
This thing is seeing so much.
It's been hit.
It's been run through the ringer so many times.
I can't believe it still works.
That just shows how well-made this thing is.
It's taking thousands of commands at the same time.
So you broke it.
So congratulations, you didn't even fire it.
So we're gonna go back to the way it was.
Dunk me.
Let's do it.
I have no monitor so I don't know what's happening.
Why are my nails painted?
Oh, that's paint.
You know what I mean.
It was paint from earlier.
Did you piss on this?
Remember I made that joke like three hours ago?
Yeah, you did.
Dunk me, let's go.
Uh-oh, that's close, close, close.
A little more to the left, pull it in.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, God.
You might as well.
You know, all the toys,
everything you guys collected is right here.
So remember, if you dunk me,
and the Fortnite Garfield,
and the Zebra,
and the, I don't know.
Wait a minute.
I can feel this and I gotta figure it out.
This two cents in my underwear.
Hold on, hold on.
There's like this money in my pants.
I have like, that's a dollar.
That's one dollar.
I feel like incredible.
One dollar.
If you dunk me, you get rid of all the goats too.
I'm scared.
I think I've removed all the money from my underwear.
Have I?
One more.
You know when you go to the beach
and you just feel the sand just all over you.
There's like this like one cent bit donations
all over my like underwear right now.
I think I'm all right.
We lost somebody though.
Did it die?
It killed it.
We're dying.
For every minute that it's not ready,
another Garfield goes in the fucking tank.
No, I want that in my office.
Why is it not coming towards me?
Get the fuck over here.
These are actually pretty nice.
These are nice.
He's in there.
He's just in there.
I can't get him up.
There goes another one.
No, I want to save these.
I don't want them.
I don't want.
I got to save Fortnite Garfield.
That's the most important one.
All right.
We're good.
I got him.
He's saved.
I feel like Steve Urkel.
My pants are riding so far up.
Oh.
Get a hang.
Oh, you like Garfield?
You like Fortnite Garfield?
Oh, do you like him?
Do you like him?
Wait, hold on.
He's fine.
Only done it twice.
Can you do it a third time?
I don't know.
I'm just the fucking idiot in a tank
that has to accept whatever happens.
Oh, I felt that one.
That was pretty close.
Hey, fucking fucking Fortnite.
Fortnite sucks.
I hate this Fortnite.
I can't do it.
I'm trying.
I'm doing what I can.
I'm still dry.
Should I pop a balloon?
What do you think?
It'll scare me.
Wait, hold on a second.
Let me get this out.
Is it going to pop if I put it?
Don't use your teeth.
Oh, I'm okay.
Gross.
I don't want this to pop.
Why is there still the air in it?
All right, get it away from me.
Oh, whoops.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, there it goes.
The machine broke.
I can't believe it took this much anyways.
Look at this hair.
I gotta get a haircut.
Get it.
What camera are we on?
Over here?
Eat shit.
I got goats for days, motherfucker.
Oh, shit.
It's never gonna happen.
Hey, go to the GoPro.
No, don't do that.
I zoomed in gross face.
You can do it.
I know you can.
We got two more shots before the robot
is no longer functional.
Didn't work.
The bot is grinding.
We got one more shot.
Last shot.
Oh, God.
We've grinded it to a halt.
Oh, shit.
That robot actually was done.
The grinding part of it is done.
Oh, my God.
That's funny.
Why did you guys do this shit on the last time?
The last time, every time.
You get the pressure involved,
and then all of a sudden you do it.
Oh, my God.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, that's gonna be it.
Thank you so much, everybody, for joining.
You might have thought that was rigged.
It's not.
That was the last shot.
That robot could possibly be fucking done.
It's broken.
It's fucked up.
It's been through hell, this whole stream.
Why am I like, oh, they splash around in this disgusting water.
By the way, this has been here for probably 48 hours.
And somebody pissed in it.
At least two people did.
I know they did.
I can smell it.
It's been filled with ice.
You know what?
Let's accept it.
That's the end of the stream, everybody.
Thank you so much.
I really can't even express how much
I can fucking thank everybody for participating.
Even trying.
You did very well considering the circumstances,
so thank you so much to everybody that participated.
Special, huge thank you to Andy Mark.
They've made all these bots,
they made this whole thing possible.
Without them, this does not happen.
So Andy Mark absolutely killed it.
Thank you so much for even giving the robots
and putting the technology in place
and making it happen to control the chat.
JK Productions, another company that came in
and just knocked this out of the park
with location and media services
and just fucking unbelievable work.
And then, thank you to you.
I said that already, but thank you so much.
I am going to take a shower.
I hope you enjoyed this.
It's been a wild ride.
I'll see you in a few days when I come back.
And we play, I don't know, fucking like Mario Kart
for like fucking four hours.
See you next time.
Take care.
Good luck.
Good night.
See you when I get back.
This fucking tank.
I'm gonna puke on stream.
I did too.
Who gives a shit?
It's my motto from now on.
I feel like a fucking game show host.
Hey, who gives a shit?
Can I knock?
You know, that took like an hour and a half to set up.
Don't even knock it over.
No, no, it went away.
Hey, my motto from now on.
Who gives a shit?
Sure, my nine eight five.
Don't step on any nails in like four or five days.
Who gives a shit?