Hey, what's happening guys? Today, we're gonna be doing TF2. We're gonna be opening up some boxes.
I've opened up quite a few of these already, and we're just gonna get into it. Hopefully I get something good, because I've been shafted quite a few times.
So, enjoy the unboxing. Let's go ahead and get number one open. It's a lightning rod field tested.
You know what? You know what? Get them all open. You know, get them all open. Open them all right now, at the same time.
Yeah, come on. No, I take it back. No, no, no. Oh, shit. I just blew through that. That was so stupid. What an impulsive, stupid idea.
And now I got a backpack that's in even worse shape than it was before this update, and it was in pretty bad shape before.
But look at this. I got so many of these now, from doing contracts and opening cases. I don't know. I counted. I have 13 of the McDonald's Happy Meal Shotgun.
What am I supposed to do with this stuff? Look at how many of these I have. Like, this one is well-worn with a strange on it. I don't even know what these things are worth.
And look, look at this. I didn't even notice this before. Why do I have 10 strange knives? What purpose do these serve? You know, I'm just gonna take the backpack off.
I just gotta get it off. Just get it off and take a look inside and see what you're actually working with. I don't know what this is. I don't know what that is.
It might be a strange... Here's a scatter gun. I want to keep this. This is my strange scatter gun. This is my Tommy Slav. I know I have to hold onto that because it's worth like 15 cents.
Here's... Oh, Jesus. What? This is a fucking dog bone? There's no dog bone item in TF2. I don't know where that came from. This is part of a sandwich, obviously.
I just... I don't know what to... I don't know what to do with this stuff! I have too much of it!
Hey, if you're going... Hey!
I'll be right back.
No, hit me up some french fries. The good ones from Wendy's. Are you listening to me? Fucking idiot.
Ten knives. You gotta have ten knives, don't you?
Hello. Hey. What's going on, dude? How you doing? You're outside right now? Yeah, yeah. Just give me a second. I'll be right out.
I'm so glad you're here. It's been like a year since I last saw you. You want to do something? What do you want to do? You want to go out?
I don't have any more room. This is your problem now.
What?
Come on, man.
That was my first time!
Jesus.
Ow.
Damn.
Assistant?
Yes?
Get in this room.
What's wrong, sir? What's wrong? What's wrong?
You piece of crap.
What?
I called you fifteen seconds ago, maybe even twenty. And it took you this long?
I'm so sorry, sir.
Get that fucking door open.
I'm so sorry. Thank you, sir.
You know what? The next time you're late like that, the next... Connor is a real bitch. You do something like that again?
You embarrass me like that in front of all these fifty-five million people? You're fired.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, shit!
I'm fucking dead.