Okay, I'm back. It's time to switch to a scary game. It is October. We played Scorn
a few days ago. What should I title this? It's Deadly Night. What do I title this? How about um...
Look Out. Watch Out. Uh, I don't know. You want me to title the name of my stream? Play Scorn.
I'm not gonna do that. Um, I believe I just turned on my Xbox. I may have. I'm not sure yet.
Doesn't look like it, but I could have. All right. Uh, Halloween Approaches. Ghost.
I don't know. How about just like, You Scared. Yeah, You Scared. You're safe. You're safe in the
comments. Yeah. The smiley face. You're safe in the comments. You don't remember that? That's not-
You don't like that one? I'm keeping it. All right. Let's go. Oh, lights off. You're right. Hold on.
Nobody even said it. I just did though. This is not Vampire Survivors. Yeah. Lights off. Creepy.
Sorry I'm like stalling really bad, but it's a scary game and I fucking hate these. You know me.
I know. I hate these. I hate it. I hate these games. I don't know why I just screamed. It's way too
bright. This is kind of scary. All right. I like this. This is scary. What do you think? Also,
let me know. Let me know if it's- if this shit's still happening. Webcam glitching. Because it
really shouldn't be. How's that? Are we good? Does it look- does it look scary? I think that looks
all right. Very spooky. Good? Maybe a little bit more bright? Just a little bit? I think that's
good. Yeah, this is perfect. All right. I'm ready. Lights off. Deadly night. No more stalling. It's
time to fucking go. I'm ready. This game contains nudity. Uh, did I? I don't know. I want to censor
the nudity. I mean, it's asking me if I want to censor it. Is it TOS? Anybody played this yet?
Other people have played with it on? Okay. It's part of the game. Other people have played with
it on. Uh, I mean, is it- how- is it really- means- okay, honest to god, let me just tell you.
If- if I could show scorn, the- if I could show scorn, I- I don't think- I think it's- I don't
know. I think it's gonna be okay. Motel? The house? Susan 9-1-1 call. I don't know. Is it like- is
sent- is it like- like a big black bar? Is it gonna take me out of the game? I don't know what
it- what that means, but whatever. Jesus Christ, dude. What the fuck? Where are you going?
Where am I going?
Are you sure I look good?
Where are we going? Is this gonna be loud?
Is this game- is this game scary? Tell me the truth.
You're welcome. Okay. Okay, whatever. Okay, I've got run inventory. Pause. Crouch flashlight.
Look around. No, we're not doing gamepad. All right, so there we go. I have an inventory.
Is it me? Stop. My- I'm so- I'm so jumpy right now, too. I don't know why. I don't want any
drinks. Motel. Highway. Motel. Single room $20, double room $40. It is mandatory to pay in advance
and leave the room before $12. If you do not have phones in the rooms, the only phone available is
at the reception. Talk to the person in charge for more info. Like, grenades? Why do you have
a bunch of grenades? My cam's not on the edge of the screen. Oops. Okay, so, um, I guess I can't
do anything in here. I can't play this tonight. I actually don't think I can. I'm so fucked up
today. You know what I mean? I'm super, like, hmm.
I see. The bus usually arrives at 8 a.m. I can let you know an hour earlier if you wish.
Um, sure. It would be perfect, thanks. Are you coming with someone? I'm alone, but I want a
double room. Many people come here to have sex. Is it your case? What the fuck do you care?
I care. I'm sure you're great at wiggling that ass, right? Do you like sex from the front,
back, or both? I will not say here. Fuck you. Yeah, I'm sorry. Fuck you. Who the fuck is this guy?
Crash. It stinks. It seemed to be pretty dirty. Door number one, door number two.
Do I have to, wait, do I have to get a room? I, okay. I think I have to just demand a room.
I think we're, we need game progress here. While you're playing this and not stay out of the house,
I will be playing stay out of the house. Just not right this very moment. I will. It's on the list
of games to play in the next week or two. I guess I have to get a room or something. I have to get
a room. I can't just, all right, well. Have you had second? A young girl like you shouldn't be out
there alone at this hour. Okay. Give me the fucking room. Give me a room. What door is this?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, number eight. Are you lost? School. All right. Eight was
right. Okay. Use. Turn the light on quick. I need to lock the door, right? Like where's the door lock?
That's scary. Is this a bathroom? Yeah, turn every light on so all the spirits can't get in here.
Oh my God. I hate this. Yeah. Why is it automatically put on like a horror channel?
Uh, okay. What kind of TV channel is this? Let's, can we break this down for one second?
This is a scary sound effect channel. It's just creepy noises, scary music.
What is this? Why is this on TV? I'm not putting that on. All right. I'm sleeping with all the
lights on. Every single light is being turned on. Uh, oh, the door is stuck.
Water. Water from the sink. Water. Smash the window. Glass is too hot. Uh, break something.
Hit something. Um, TV. Door's stuck. Go, go, go, go, go. What the? What does that say?
My God. That's a nightmare. I'm gonna scream in my face. We're gonna get ready for a scream in my
mouth. That nightmare. Right now I don't need the backpack. I can hear a noise in the room. I should
see what it is. What is this noise? Today's August 17, 1987. What does it say? 911, what is your
emergency? I'm at the highway motel. The owner is a sicko. I've discovered hidden cameras behind the
mirrors in my room. They were recording. Don't worry. I'll send a patrol car. The area is quite
remote and it will take some time to get there. So please be patient. Okay. Um, okay. Okay. All
right. Backspace. Backspace. I don't want. How do I get out of this TV? Does he make porn movies
by filming? I also appear in the recording. I heard the door open. Hey, what are you doing here?
I have discovered your secrets. You sick. I've already called the police and they're on their
way. You're going to end up behind bars. Oh, the police. I don't think so. You're going to stay
locked in here until I decide what to do with you. And maybe I'll fuck that sweet hairy pussy.
What the fuck? Just trashed the TV on his head. It's Matt. I got to fucking hit with the TV.
I have to fucking kill this guy. What the fuck? What is laughing? Oh, it's this.
If only I had a coin. Do I have a coin? This is fucked. Do I have a coin? I don't have a coin.
Okay. Go back to the room and get my backpack. Oh, come on. You know, I didn't have anything
important. I can. Was this car here before? Was this car here before? Was this actually here before?
I don't think it was. I'm staying right in the middle. A car comes. I, it won't hit me. I mean,
right in the center. They're going to pull some bullshit with it. A cop car is going to be flying
down here. No, I'm going over here. Why is that music? How come I touch that music starts? Oh my
God. You're going to reverse. Oh God. Oh, I heard something. I'm going back. I'm going back. I'm
going back. I'm going back. I'm going. I'm going back. I'm going back to the hotel. Get off the
road. Should I go back to the motel? I'm going to go back and get the backpack because he's driving
that way and he has not turned around yet. He hasn't turned around yet. It's invisible. Well,
I can't. Is he still just parked in the middle of the street? Honestly, I'm going here and like
get down in like the weeds and shit. Oh God damn it. Shit. God damn it. If I keep my eye on him,
then he can't get me. What happened? Why did you stop? Why did you stop? Why did you stop the car?
Why did you stop the car? Can you beat it? Can you beat this? Like, can you win? The murderer's
house. Oh, oh, there are four acts. Okay. I hate this. Okay. I got up. Oh God. What is this? Turn
it on. Turn it on. Oh, how do I use it? No, no. Where the fuck is this? I have to get out of here.
Oh my God. Can't turn it. I don't know the combination. All right. I need to know the
combination. Can I hide in this? There's so many places to go. You can hide under tables,
beds, and in some furniture. I got to practice that. How do you do that? Crouch. I can crouch.
This door is locked. How can I get out? There's nothing to hide under.
I'm alive. I'm alive. Spider. Oh my God, dude. Where do I even go? What do I do?
No, no, no, dude. I don't know where to go. How do I? Home? Rust remover. I can't reach it. There's
something in there. Dude, how do you hide? How do I hide? Oh, wait. Where the fuck am I? Am I? Where am
I? Am I hiding? Where am I? I want to play the Batman game again. I want to ride around and
protect Gotham City. He's right out here and I'm gonna, I'm gonna walk right into him when I get
out of here and I have like one slash and I'm dead. Where is he going? Okay, this is, somebody make
this into a poster for a horror movie. Honest to God, somebody needs to turn this into a poster.
Like, with the title, like, you're not getting out or something, right? What is the title of
this movie, do you think? You tell me. My eyes are all red. Why do I look so fucked up? Holy shit,
man. This is fucked. I look like Voldemort. Oh, this is a screen cap from Dumb and Dumber.
I hope people AI expand that one. I hope so too. He's right. He won't leave. Just leave me alone.
Rust remover. Yeah, you can see through that knob doesn't turn. Maybe I can use something to make us
make the psycho pull it down. Bandage. How do I use this? How do I use the bandage? Is there a save?
Hide in the box and shimmy out. That actually could probably work. I hate this game. I hate
this. Right here. Okay, so I have rust remover. Something was rusty. Sink was rusty. Sink was
rusty. You know what? Scared. That's what you want. I'm gonna march out here and just start singing
fucking John Jingleheimer Schmidt. What are you doing? No, you're supposed to be scared.
John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt. His name is my name too. Whenever we go out,
we always shout. Here comes John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt. Get in the bathtub quick.
John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt. His name is my name too. Whenever I go out,
the people always shout. Here comes John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt.
Where is he? Dude, I can't see anything. Break this door. Break this door. Break this door,
dude. This game is fucked. This game is fucked up. That's wicked funny. We got to see this one.
This one's perfect. I don't want to play this. I hate this. This is a good one though. Wait,
come on, come on, come on. Why can I not save this? This one is so good. This is fucking actually
one of the funniest things I've ever seen. I have to get these on stream. I have to. Okay,
well, everyone bear with me for a second. I got to get these all loaded because these are gold.
These are actual gold. Here's the first one. This one's pretty good, I will say. This one's
pretty good. They get better. They get way better. And I mean, way better. This one,
um, apparently, so an AI decided that this is what I was doing. Okay, makes sense, right?
Why would I be this concerned? Here's the next one. I, dinner, I'm making dinner and I'm very,
this is an oven that I'm shocked at. But wait, it's not even the best one because the best one
is right here. And it could be the funniest image I've seen ever on the channel. And I mean that.
This is probably the funniest thing. This is probably the funniest image that's come through.
This is so good. Look at how bad that form is too. It's so bad. This is like the old guy.
This kind of has to like stay. Okay, retry. How far am I in the game? Not even fucking close,
dude. I don't think I'm going to beat this. Close the door. Close the door. Close the door.
I can't close it. Is it open? I don't think I'm going to be able to do this. I don't think I can
play this game. Trying to commit this house to memory and he's wicked fast. I need to get items
and shit. No way. I'm not going to be able to beat this. I'm going to panic every time he shows
up. Was there an item down here? No, it's back up in the house. All right. This is a good one,
too. I'm going to show this one. This is also a really good one. I kind of just want to like
do this for the rest of the stream. This is fun. Apparently like very, very, very excited at the
birthday party. I'm very surprised at my surprise birthday party. What do I have my arm? What am
I holding? Is that like a clipboard or an iPad? One more and I'm going to move on. These are very
good though. They're very good. I feel like chats is going to be chat's favorite. I can't play. I
can't play this game. Okay. I'm going to just be quiet. I'm going to shut up and I'm even if it's
scary, I'm just going to go and I'm going to play it. I don't care. Fucking come get me. I don't
care. I can't. I quit. This is the first time I've ever quitting a game. How do I get out of here?
I can't hide under the table. Oh, Bugleberry radio. I wish we would just go away for even five
minutes. He's just camping me. You know what? I feel like I'm playing and it's a game I never
beat and I just rage quit it. I was just, I scare rage quit it. That grandma game for iPad. I
couldn't do it and I was like, I'm just fucking uninstalling this. Oh, we're in a circle.
That was the chicken. That was a fucking rooster. That was a rooster. That was actually a rooster.
That was a chicken. That was like a, what the? Oh, bandage. Nice. Hide. This game's impossible.
This game's not possible. This game's actually impossible. It seems to be something in the pipe.
I can't reach it. Okay. That's not rusty though. I need like a stick. Nothing in there. God. The
valve was rusty. That's right. That was down in the basement, right? I can't carry any more objects.
What are you talking about? Oh, I just put, I can't carry any more items. Where should I put this?
Oh, right here. I'm going to put it right here. I'm going to hide under. I'm going to hide under
the bed. Okay. Put it down right here and put it down. Oh, was that a key? I got a key of some kind
and a trunk. Can I open this? Okay. Open the trunk with the key, dude. Excuse me. Open the trunk with
that key right now. I can't get in my inventory. Why? My inventory doesn't work. Inventory doesn't
work. Why does my inventory not work? Tab. It's broken. I actually can't use my inventory. Yeah.
Tab. I. Tab and I. Yeah. Doesn't work. Tab. Try hiding again. Maybe it'll reset it. God damn it.
Please, man. Don't even. Why is his own fire? Oh, what? What the fuck happened? This is why I
couldn't. What the hell is happening to me? Okay. I can use my inventory again. Where's the, where's
the door that I just was at? Where's the door? Where's the, where's that door? Rust. Rust. Where's
the, where is it? Where is, where is it? What happened? I just shut down my computer. I think
I shut my computer. I think I shut my computer down. I opened the power menu and it shut. Dude,
what? How do you? I quit. I quit this game. You start at the beginning every time. You start at
the beginning every time. There's no checkpoints. Huh? I don't even want to. I mean, these are just
weird. These are just weird now. I'm just going for a speed run. Fuck it. I'm going for a speed
run right now. Chemicals are upstairs. So many fucking doors in this house. I don't even know
where. I get so lost so easily. I can't play these. I need the alarm clock to throw in there. Alarm
clock. Okay. Here he comes. Where was the alarm clock? I don't remember. I don't know. I don't
know where I am in this fucking house. I don't even know how to get downstairs. I'm serious. I
don't know how to get downstairs. I don't know how to get downstairs. How are you still chasing
me? It's impossible. You didn't even see me. I can't run anymore. I can't get away from him.
He's too fast. Dude, you can't get away from this motherfucker. You can't get away from him. He's
so fast. I can't see. I'm so bad with like permanence and locate. I can't play. I don't
fucking give a shit about this game. I don't care. I leave. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I give up.
Is there an alarm here? Every room looks exactly the fucking same and like he runs so fast and
like there's just items fucking sprinkled in every corner and you're gonna take the fucking alarm
clock out of this room and then go to go up there and then take the fucking rust pour and pour that
and get the chemical and get the chemical and then get the key. I have to hide immediately.
He's like already in the fucking room and he's gonna grab me out of this canister and he's gonna
slash my head. Stop. Why is he still here? He should not be coming back in this room.
Going upstairs. Okay. I think I've got every item that I need. There's nothing else down here,
right? I got the valve is down here. I gotta bring. I gotta go all the way upstairs, get the
rust remover and bring it down here. If I'm gonna try that problem is I don't even know how to get
up. I need like a fable to breadcrumb trail, dude. I like seriously. I can't even know what hallway
we're in and he's just right up your ass the whole time and I don't want to turn the light on
because it'll attract him. See, I don't, I can't commit anything to memory because my brain is in
a constant state of distress. So I can't commit anything to memory straight across from that weird
door is the basement. Okay. I gotta remember that. I need to draw a map. He's just, he's just,
you do. I have to speed run because the dude just never going to leave me alone. Just get out of my
way. Fuck you buddy. That's fine. I quit. I quit this game. I quit this game. Where's the stairs
to go up the stairs? I quit this game. Draw a map. Do you want me to draw a map? I can't. I'm just
trying to lose him. Do you can't lose the guy. I can't lose him. Why is he still right behind me?
Dude, you can't see in your own fucking house. That's horse shit. Which way is it? Right here,
right? Get out of the fucking way. You huge asshole. Dude, what do you even?
Rust remover and paint can room valve in basement alarm clock and fireplace room door with hole
in the room with the two bedrooms. Thank you for the help. All right. I'm just,
I'm going to try this one more time. This dude's up your ass the whole game. He doesn't go like
disappear for like a minute. No, he's just, he's here. It's terrifying. It's horrible. And he's
going to stand here like a dick. I bet she comes back in the room. The alarm clock is random.
This is really, that's so horrible. Okay. How do I get up the stairs? This is a door that leads
to another door, which leads to the stairs up. He's walking by. Okay. Downstairs is there. That
means he is another door over here. I think it's straight ahead. Is he upstairs or downstairs?
Is he, where is he? Is he upstairs? I think he's upstairs. Like, is he upstairs? What the fuck,
dude? Why? Where am I? Yeah. Go look in here. There's a fucking clock in here. Oh my God.
You can lower the, I'm getting Luigi. All right. I'm getting Luigi. This change will be permanent
and you will only be able to play again at the real difficulty. If you start a new game,
if you continue without making changes, this message will be displayed again. If you die
again, do you want to lower the enemy difficulty? I can't believe I got fucking Luigi. I can't
believe it. I'm too. I don't care. I want to see this. I want to see. I don't care. I don't care.
I'm getting Luigi. I don't even care. I'm going to laugh my ass off. Can you imagine if I die
like three more times and it's like, do you want it even easier? Fuck isn't here. Get out of here.
Get the fuck out of here. Get out of this hallway. Like get out of this hallway. You chump. Okay.
All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Where's it? Where's the clock coming down
here? You should try murder house. I played murder house. I beat it. That was pretty,
that was recently. I don't know if he's still here. Where's, I don't have the clock though.
Can't hide under that. Where's the clock? I don't know where he is, but he's, I don't know. I don't
know. You can't be serious. Right when I come out of the fucking hiding, he's now walking around here.
You can't, I'm not even scared anymore. You're just making me angry. You're just pissing me off.
I need to hide right now. I need to hide right now. I would love to just jump out of here and
jump scare him. Grab the sickle out of his hand and just right in his head. Don't even, you open
that and I'm fucking uninstalling again. If you open this cabinet, I'm going to uninstall the game.
Thank you. You still here? What are you still doing? Okay. He went upstairs. I think he's upstairs.
All right. Valve time. You know what I mean? Like they say, they're going to make a game and then
it takes like another extra few years working on valve time. The rust is still dissolving.
I probably should hide. He's going to come down and go like,
whatever he says. Still dissolving. I was sitting here the whole time. I don't care.
There's a raid from where? I didn't see a raid. What does that do? Water is already flowing in
the pipes. I should check the bathrooms. Oh, the sink. There's a sink that has right wherever that
is. I don't remember where that sink is. You look like Kenneth Copeland for a few frames here. What?
Oh my God. My eyes are bugging out of my head. My, holy shit. My eyes almost come out of my head,
out of my socket. How do I save this? This is a crazy image. Watch my eyes. That's insane.
Skeleton for a few frames. All right. Back to this. Check the bathrooms. All right. He's down
here again. Wait till he comes. He's going to walk through here. Or should I just run for it?
Where's the bathroom? Don't sprint. It's instantly going to give away with the other.
I'm getting speech jammed by butyl berry. Sorry. Only sprint when he's chasing you.
Okay. Everybody's under the tables, reached over and just like did this like out in the hall.
Okay. I need a bathroom. I don't know. Is he, did he try? Is he turning around? He's in there.
Okay. He just went up the stairs. This is my opportunity. My opportunity. Opportunity.
Let's go. Don't sprint. Bathroom. Is he above me or is he over here? I think he's above me.
What is this? This is like, I got to get something to break that open with. Bathroom. Here we go.
Oh shit. He's right there. Right next to me. Where's the bathroom with the thing that was
in the sink? It's upstairs. I haven't heard him move. He's like over here. He's up here.
I'm dead. Oh, I hate this. It's on easy mode. It's on easy mode. I'm just going up the stairs.
I don't give a shit if he hears me. I thought he was downstairs. Oh my God. That was the worst
thing ever. That was probably the worst thing ever. I quit. That was the worst thing ever.
I thought he was downstairs. I actually thought he was downstairs. I thought he was downstairs.
Nothing. Well, that hurt my whole body. I don't think I can play this. Okay. You took my advice
for three minutes and then you said fuck it and he immediately died. He wouldn't get away from
upstairs. I was waiting and waiting and waiting. I was hiding under the table and I heard it's him
going up and down the top floor. So I'm just like, all right. I don't care. I'm going up there.
I'm doing it my way. I'm doing it my way. Your way is correct. My way is stupid and it's going
to get me killed. But I'm going for it. Not now. Not now. Not now. Please not now. I'm going to
sneeze. No, we're supposed to be doing this my way. I got the rust. We're going downstairs. Turn
the valve on. Fuck it. Run upstairs. What am I doing here? This is not my way. This is my way.
Where's the valve? This is my way. Okay. Now I need to go get clock. We're doing it my way.
Clock is upstairs. Clock is up. Fireplace. The rust is dissolving. The sink will be available.
This is an Adventure Time bit right now. What happened in Adventure Time? Okay. So there's a
bathroom up here. I got to fish out whatever's in the sink. I then have whatever's in the sink.
I still need the alarm clock. I didn't turn the valve. Oh my God. You're right. All right.
That sucks. I'm in trouble now. Oh, that actually sucks. I think it's over.
Close it. Close it. Is he still here? I think he's gone. Yeah. He went back upstairs. Okay.
Now we got to go all the way upstairs. What's up, buddy? What's up, buddy? What's up, buddy?
I need the clock. He went upstairs. I need the clock. There's no clock. Okay. Guys,
where's the clock? Honestly, where's the clock? It's not in here and I haven't seen it in any
other room. Just tell me where it is. Oh, Raid. Oh, Mr. Sark. What's up, Sark? Thank you, Mr.
Sark, for the raid. Welcome, everybody. I'm currently about to rage quit this game and
never play it again. You're in the middle of it. You're coming in right with that. This is the
fiftieth attempt. I had to put it on easy. They can't do it. It's a pretty fun game,
I would say. I'm about to uninstall it. Pretty good. Where is the clock? It's a wrench. It's
too hot. Are you serious? Just grab it quick. Gotta get upstairs again, right?
There seems to be something in the pipe. I can't. It didn't happen. It didn't push it up from the
water. It seems to be something. I can't. How do I use the sink? I need the wrench. How do I need
to get water to put the fire out, to get the wrench to come up here? How do I put the fire out
from the tub? I need something to hold. Find the alarm clock. The key you get unlocks a save point.
Really? Cork, cork, cork. Is it right here? I have something to cut it with. I need to
get scissors or scissors. But anyway, say thanks to Sark for the raid. Follow Sark. An awesome dude.
Get the key. Key. All right. Just give me a route to take. The key is a route. I need a route.
I gotta go. Alarm clock, bedroom, fire, key. But I don't know where the alarm clock is.
It's in a random spot, apparently. I don't know where the alarm clock is. Alarm clock, key, plywood
door. It's a random spawn on the second floor. You buddy. Not in here. Random spawn on the second
floor. Spawn on the second floor. Where's this dumbass clock? Shitting me. Okay, now we gotta
go upstairs. Get my bearings. It's up. Hide. Get them to run into the door. Get the lock. Get the
key. Come back down here. Open up the thing with the boarded hallway. And then apparently that's a
checkpoint. Okay, I'm going for it. I'm going. No, I'm not. He's still here. Why can't I just press,
like, like B and get, like, the fucking seam through the wall? Every video game has that now.
Every video game has it. Put it in this. I'm doing it my way. I gotta listen closely
because if it sounds from... Is he up here or is he downstairs? I don't know. I'm here. I made it.
Okay, give me a second. I think he was up here, actually. That's terrifying. He was. He was up
here. I just didn't see him. Okay, so, lock. Get in there. Grab the key. Downstairs to that plywood
thing on the wall, right? Open that. Look, people are dancing. Get out of here, man. You're making
me angry. We get this weird cutscene again. Yep. Okay, this is the... Right? Okay, okay. Yep.
Ah! Okay, don't get caught here. Okay, okay. Here we are. It's right here. Isn't it right here?
It's right here, right? This is it? What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong, though?
What's wrong? I didn't even read what it said. What does it say? What does it say?
I couldn't read it. I need to remove rust and then... Okay, this guy's a real piece of shit,
I'll tell you. Is he gone? I wish this thing would shut up so I could hear.
Is it open? Is the door... The door's open. Is it the wrong door? That's the wrong door. Where is it?
It's the hallway in front of that one. I just wish it would go upstairs or something. Just go away.
Go downstairs. Go upstairs. Go anywhere else. He walked that over there. Well, that way on your
screen because it's flipped. He went to the left. Go the fuck away. Go away. Go away. Why is he still
here? Go away. Go away. Go upstairs. Go away. I hate this game so much. I actually... I'm done with it.
I'm just done. If I die again, I'm over. It's over. Damn it. Okay, open. He's coming down here
and he won't leave me alone. He won't leave me be. He won't leave me alone. If you die... Hold on.
If you die before you manage to unlock that padlock, I'm going to unsubscribe.
You're not even subscribed. I think you don't have to change anything. You're not even subbed.
Still down here? You piece of shit. I swear to God. Where's the door? Where's the door?
Oh, fuck. I've never played this game again. This person... That person was subbed for three months.
Oh. Oh, sorry. No, they're not subbed. They're not subbed. They've been following... Okay.
So they aren't subbed. I'm waiting till I hear that sound go off and then I'm going back up.
I'm going to unsub if you don't get that padlock off. All right. The amount of fucking unsub Andy's
in the chat, apparently, if I can't open this door. They said Omega Low. I got gifted a free sub.
Omega Low. Get out of here. On your left. I know. I'm fucking scared, man. He's going to come and get
me. I thought he was right in the hallway next door. I can't even see. I don't know. He could
kill me right now. I don't know. You were right there. The game uses your microphone. It doesn't.
I got it. Don't move. I can't carry any more objects. Crowbar. Should I drop something?
Sub stays. I saved it. I saved it. Do I need this anymore? Okay. There's a panel I can open
with the crowbar. I'm so happy. I'm just going to run out. I'm just going to do it my way now.
Can you read the dialogue? What do you mean? Wait. What do you mean? Limited saves?
What the fuck? We're doing it my way. You have to hide, you fucking idiot. What's even in there?
Love Tweed. Hey, Love Tweed. Thanks for the raid. Welcome. Thanks for the raid. Playing a game. I'm
about to rage quit it. I'm about to rage quit this game. Welcome. Hope you had a good stream.
I'm ready to play. And I'm doing it my way, by the way. But no, welcome. Thanks for the raid.
What is in here? Diary and a... It's missing batteries. Okay. I don't... What should I drop?
I'm going to drop. Which I don't even know what to drop here. Why? How am I inventory so bad?
Do I still need the crowbar? Someone's coming. Use the rope in the hole? Yeah.
But I need to pick up whatever this is. Can I open the fridge with the crowbar?
Okay. Let's get it. Where is it? Okay. I got the diary. Very bad at diary.
I don't like being here. The house is very dirty and smells like garbage. It only feeds me.
Why can I not read this hiding under here? Why can I not read this hiding? It's a book.
You seem pissy tonight. What? I'm playing a scary game. It's a scary environment, man.
Go read it in the save room. Oh, good idea. Where's the save room again? I don't remember.
Let's read this diary. Um, it feeds me raw meat. It tastes really bad, although at least he feeds
me and doesn't look lock me up like mom and dad did. Today, my new father got angry with me because
I grew up in my food, but I couldn't help it. He took my stuff and threw it down the well in
the basement. Although luckily I had my video game console hidden away. Tonight, I was brave
and went down to the basement, but I got scared when I got close to the well because I heard
someone screaming inside. So I, uh, I ran out into my room. I'm getting moved to the food
my new dad gives me. I think I like it. I'm getting used to the, all right. Today we went hunting and
come back with lots of new meat. Father told me that we have to leave them alive until we need
them to eat that way. They stay fresh and the meat tastes better. I don't know why the smell of me
new home bothered me. Now I find it cozy. I don't want to be anywhere else but here. What does that
even tell me? I'm going up. I'm going up. I'm going to run out. We're doing it my way. I'm going to
get into the, we're going upstairs. Drop the diary. Yeah. Good call. Should I pick up the, uh, crowbar
again? What can I nuts? Fuck. Um, I'm going upstairs. Is he up here? He's up here. He's up here.
I need the wrench. You man. You idiot. You idiot. Get out of the fucking way. Use the rope for the
wrench. I ain't going to make it. I ain't going to make it. Thanks for watching this stream everybody.
You guys have been great. I'll definitely see you tomorrow. We're going to be playing, uh,
Breath of the Wild for an hour or two. And then we're going to do one more Omega sponsored Gotham
night stream. We'll play Breath of the Wild first. And that doesn't work. Doesn't work. Doesn't work.
What time? 2 p.m. tomorrow. 2 p.m. Pacific. Breath of the Wild first. Gotham nights. And that's
probably it. Tomorrow's going to be a little shorter. All right. What, what's the, where am I
going? Use the get the rope. Can I put that down downstairs in the basement? Can I go, can I drop
that down in the well in the basement where the padlock was? Use the crowbar on the floor near the
diary. Um, I don't remember. Where's the crowbar? Did I, where did I drop the crowbar? I hate being
in this room. The kitchen. Ah, that's not the kitchen. That's the bathroom. What are you doing?
You fucking dumb. Are you dumb? Why would I come out? I'm, I'm not like Burger King or something.
You know what I mean? I want Burger King right now. I'm going, I'm going to go. I want Burger King.
I'm getting to Burger King. Yeah, I'm going to get Burger King. How many bandages? Okay. Now
use this where the diary was. Lower where the di- I'm going in here. Just be safe.
Should I save it? Should I save the game? No. So you're saying the diary or the trunk you couldn't
open. That's right. I, I tried the trunk. The trunk was up here. It's that. Video game and a note.
Dude, does the note say? Can I open this? Stop, stop. Stop. It's open. I gotta close it. Back to where
you found the diary. Pick up the game console. I can't play this game. Combination of the lock
in the well is the same as my score in the mutant horde game. Although I don't remember it. And for
a debris pair, I have to get more than 6,000 points. Sick. All right. All right. Okay. Grab the
game cartridge. Grab the game console. Get the padlock key. Okay. Do I have room though?
What do I do with the rope? Cause I can't carry anything else. I don't know what to do with the
rope and these batteries too. Should I save it? I think I'm going to save it. I think I gotta stop.
I'm going to save it. It's probably a stupid idea. No, but I'm doing it. Yeah. I gotta stop. My brain
is, is on, is my brain's fucked up. Yeah. I'm stopping. This is ridiculous. I can't believe
I even showed that. I'm, I'm covered in water. I don't even want to show you my back. It's fucked.
This is, it's a horror game. All right. All right. That, uh, it saved in case I ever come back to
this game. This is fucked up. This whole game was a fucking nightmare. It's disgusting. You're
whatever. You're fine. Yeah, that's going to be it. Uh, I'll see you guys tomorrow. Uh,
tomorrow is breath of the wild and, uh, Gotham Knights. I will probably open with this when I
play, uh, stay out of the house. Yeah. You've been good. You guys have been good. You get to have it.
That was fun. Again, uh, thanks for sticking around and you kind of jumbling around a lot
the last day or two, but it's been a lot of fun. This dream has been very fun and having a blast.
Gotham Knights is going to conclude tomorrow. Tomorrow's stream is only going to be probably
four hours long. We'll play breath of the wild for like two hours to three hours and then move to
Gotham Knights for a couple hours. 2 PM Pacific, but just make it 2 30. Be safe. Appreciate it.
Thanks guys. Thanks for hanging out. Thanks for the raids. I'm going to get some food and take a
shower. Have a great night. Take care. Call your mother. See you soon.