Hello everybody, welcome to episode 10 of Germacraft.
Sorry it's been about a week since I last... Oh my god, a wolf!
What do I do? Oh my god! Oh my god, he's mad! He's mad!
No! Get away from me! I didn't want to have to come to this!
Oh, I'm sorry Mr. Wolf. I did not mean to kill you.
But anyways, we're in the Forest of Wondrous Secrets.
Or something like that, I have no idea. But let's just keep going here.
I'm going to... What is this? What the hell is this?
What? Who built the castle? Oh my god.
Grandpa! Need to talk to you! Get down here! What? What the hell?
Did you build... What the hell is this? It's a castle. What is this?
It's a castle! You can't see that with your own eyes, you stupid! Hold on, you built a castle?
Yes. You... It was fucking easy! You have a moat? How the hell did you get this?
It took me like ten minutes. Does the bridge come down? No, it doesn't.
It's just for show. Are you friggin' kidding me? How did you do this so fast?
It's probably like in the top ten easiest things I've ever done.
So you built a castle? Yes. You gotta be shitting me.
So what the hell else have you done? I mean, you built a castle, what else?
Why don't you go check around the back there? Why? What's in there? It's a secret stash over there.
What are you talking about? Go check! Oh, okay. Yep. What do you got in here? Nothing.
Oh my god. Just a bunch of fucking diamonds. This is ridiculous.
It's not ridiculous. Hold on, back up. I am really, really confused right now.
You've played for like three days. How do you have this many diamonds? It's not possible.
No, it's not. It's easy. Like diamond everything, diamond armor, diamond swords.
Listen, listen. You just have to be good. Wait a second.
Why? What are you doing? Why what? You're playing in creative mode!
No, I'm not! I knew I loaded up the wrong game! I'm not playing in fucking creative mode!
You shut up! No, but I mean, creative mode doesn't have, you don't have to gather resources.
I was wondering. I was like, what the hell's going on? How did he build smooth stone so fast?
I'm trying to make you look better. Because you said you were going to build a castle, and you never did it.
So I think it took the liberty to build a castle for you. And you're going to do this to me now?
You're going to throw it right back in my face? No, I just didn't know that that was the...
Well, I was trying to make people think that you were good at Minecraft.
And I just figured maybe you would appreciate it and maybe you'd like it, but...
No, I do. I'm sorry. No, I'm sorry. Come here. Come here. Give me a hug. Come on.
Give me a big one right here. Yeah, that's a good one.
So let's go get some ice cream. My treat. I have $1.25, which you'd buy us one like Kitty Cone and we could share it.
I'll just buy it. Okay, that works too. Okay.
So thank you guys so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
Just wanted to throw this together, a special episode 10, because I did promise you guys a castle.
So here's the castle. It's a piece of crap, but at least I tried, right?
Or at least Grandpa tried.
So where this series is going to go in the future now after episode 10, I'm not really sure.
I think I want to try and do a duel. Let's play with somebody, get on a multiplayer server and do something fun.
Maybe do some mods. We will see where it goes from here.
So yeah, thanks again for watching. I will see you all next time.
And take care everybody, right Grandpa?
Take care everybody.