Hi guys, how are you? Good to see you again. My name is Germo. I'm here to present a stream for
you all today. A little late today, but that's because we had a couple of different small
issues and by small I mean major issues. Issue number one, earlier about like an hour and a half
ago my internet was off. It was shutting off and turning on, shutting off, turning on. I'm like,
what the heck's going on here? So I had to figure that out. Issue number two, we're going to play
when I say we, Star is here. He's muted though. You can't hear him. Star and I were going to play
executive assault 2. And wow, that sounds like a fun idea. Let's go ahead and do that. Let's jump
into multiplayer and executive assault 1. The CEO game with the first person RTS. The game crashed
every time we tried to do it. We would get into a multiplayer game. We would try to figure it out.
Crash, crash, crash. So after it happening a few times, we were just like, uh, let's do something
else. And that's something else is viscera cleanup detail. Star has never played it. So we're going
to have to teach him how to play it. And here they are now. Oh yeah. We're talking about how
we're going to have to teach you how to play viscera cleanup detail. Yeah. He's never played
this before. I've never worked a day in my life that my hands are on callus that I've never even
held a mop before. I need to teach you how to use a mop. He says that's true though. Have you worked
a job? That's not true. I've mopped before for work. Yes. I have. Okay. All right. Okay. I
thought that you were just, I thought you didn't have one of those. I thought, okay, I didn't know
you have one. Okay. You just thought I was lying to you. I guess, I guess you had a job before.
I guess, I guess you've had to do like nightly detail work before. Yeah. So do I, do you still
need to explain this to me? I can't. Okay. When was the last, I'm curious. When was the last time
you held a mop in your hands? Um, it might've been eight years ago. Really? Yeah. I don't know.
A long, maybe like six actually. I don't know if that's true. I'm talking, you don't have to do
any cleaning, but when was the last time you held a mop in both of your hands? Yeah, like probably
six years ago. Okay. For me, for me, it was like two weeks ago. So, okay. I think I have some
authority to teach you how to play. And I think I'm, I think I just went to zero. No, thank God.
I hear your voice. It's going to be a struggle today. It's going to be a struggle today, guys,
but we're going to, I, I'm going for it. It's going to be a struggle. All right. Uh, so more
importantly, let's, let's just get in the game because we're already in the game. We already
spent the time getting into the game. I'm trying to touch your face and I can't. Hold on a second
here. There is that star. This is me. I'm on this side. You're, you're purple. Yeah. I'm lagging
right now. Yeah. I think, uh, my, my graphics up too high. That's what it is. All right. So
let's talk. What do you know about, um, cleaning? Uh, you, you dip the mop in the thing
and then you mop the stuff. Okay. Wrong. First of all, you have to clean up your area.
So these boxes here, you come over. I remember he's never played this game.
So hold left click. Oh, you don't have to hold it. You just click it. If you want to tilt it around
you hold left click and move it around in a circle. Your mouse, right? You can tilt it around this
way. If you press, uh, what button is it that you press to make it so it stands up right?
It is not T. Uh, what is it? How do I make it just stand up right? What's the button? Oh yeah,
this is the guy teaching me. I don't know what the button is. What's the button? F. No, no,
people saying F cause the internet queue. It's not cute. Double click, double art. So what you're
going to do is you're going to double, if you pick something up, you're going to double click
if you want it to stand up right, right click, drop stuff. Everything is physics based by the way.
So be aware of that when you're cleaning. So we need to, these are the boxes that you have to put
the trash in. And when I say trash, follow me up the stairs. Watch out for that. So in here,
as we open this door, you're going to see, well, this looks pretty clean. This is actually a clean
house. I did not think this is going to be clean. Um, over here on the, okay, nevermind. So over here
on the left, you see that there's been a couple of murders. Okay. And we need to pick up the whole,
the whole entire house has to be clean before we clock out. I have an idea. You have to listen,
no, you don't get ideas. This is my job. Okay. The rest of the house looks pretty good. So what
if we just wallpapered over the rest of this and just that room was back there. You want to just
build a wall here. Yeah. But then what happens to the, this part of the house?
This just can't go in this part of the house anymore. Oh, we can like clean the front porch
because once we sell it, we're good. Yeah. But they're going to want to see the kitchen and
shit. How are you going to convince them to do? Yes. You're understanding. So we have to just wait.
I wasn't done explaining. So we have to clean up everything. We have to rearrange everything.
It has to be spotless. There is an incinerator somewhere. I have no idea where. Okay. Is the
meat grinder part of the cleaning or is that the horror? I don't, uh, have I ever seen this before?
Okay. I think, I think that works. Oh, I can't pick you up. That's too bad. Hey, there's no
incinerator on this level. So we have to put, you have to pick up the things and throw them in there.
Okay. What are we putting in that original bucket? Okay. So come over here.
As you can see, this is the slosh romantic. This is a machine. And when you press the button,
it comes out with a fresh bucket of water. Where are you? I'm right behind you.
Grab the bucket of water. Don't spill it. I get made fun of for that. It is very easily spillable.
You're going to take your, I couldn't do it. How did you know? Really? Okay. Well,
just be careful with these. You very easily spillable. Very easy. I don't know why it was
not spillable. Uh, so you need to take this and obviously bring it. Let's start over here.
Get a couple of my own. Yeah. Get your own bucket. Take out your mop. Now your mop can only be used
a certain amount of time. So you take a look down here, see how that's doing that. It's cleaning it
up. Your mind is going to get dirty. Watch your footprints. Don't walk through stuff.
And once it becomes too dirty, if you keep mopping, you're going to make a fucking mess.
Don't do that. Come over to your water and dash it, dash it like that. Clean it up. And then you
get to use it a little bit more. By the way, when you get to a point where you've done this a few
times, the water is going to get dirty and you're going to have to dispose of that bucket because
you can't use it anymore. Let me just grind this person up. Hold on. This is my first day on the
job. Thanks for training me. So you're going to pick that up with your hands and then clean it.
No, no, no, no. Well, now you've ruined that bucket. So you've already screwed it up. See how
the bucket's ruined now? Okay. So now your head's clean. Let's just put this in here.
Okay. So once there's a big mess over here, you start to clean it up.
All right. So do you have a basic understanding of how we're doing this?
Yeah. I'm tracking blood everywhere.
Yeah. So you stop doing that job. And by the way, this is happy Halloween, everybody.
Happy Halloween. I don't know why we started. We thought we would do something festive for a
change. Yeah. Let me just tell you something right now. This map is supposed to take four hours.
Oh, estimated. So it's like, is this like a gamer equivalent of doing like a thousand piece puzzle?
Yeah. Except you don't have to really think where the pieces go. You just, I mean, I guess.
Oh, by the way, get these USB drives. Hold on to them. Why? Because they give you extra points
at the end. You put them in the computer. Okay. Okay. So we have to wait. I need a designated
area. Think of a desert because we don't want to lose these. So designated area for these are going
to be over here. Yeah. Just drop them like right here. If you find a green USB drive.
All right. Well, I need a bucket of water. Where's that bucket of water? There it is.
I'm going to bring this upstairs. So do you want to work together or do you want to change rooms?
Um, I don't know. This is going to fall. I think we could probably do different rooms.
You said you wanted to, uh, said you wanted to embarrass me and show me how much better you
were at cleaning. Yeah. I mean, I could, we could do, if you want to pick a room and we could, um,
we just do it in the neighbor's yard. Yeah. Oh, I'm just realizing. So the next people have to
clean up the next house. Okay. So come over here. Let's, we have to pick equal rooms.
Let's go upstairs. We have, they have to be equal. Is there an upstairs? How do we get upstairs?
Is there an upstairs? It looks like there is. This is a closet. Okay. Is your room clean? I think
it's pretty clean. Oops. Oops. Oops. Hey rookie, come in here for a second.
Open the door. Open the door. You open the door. I'm doing a joke. You have to open the door. No,
you open the door. Hey rookie. Oh, your bucket. You're fucking this up for me. All right. No,
wait, how do you get upstairs? I was going to make like the Hey rookie thing where I hold the glass
and drop it in front of you and it breaks and I walk out of the room. Where's the upstairs?
How do we get upstairs? There's a basement. This basement. Why is there no light down here?
There's a USB. Yeah, grab it. How do we turn the lights on? Is there no upstairs? How's this
thing going to take four hours? This is going to take like 20 minutes. How long have we been
down? Oh, oh, candles. This is how we get light. Come over here. All right. Let's, let's go down.
We're going to work together. We're going to go. What the fuck was that? Yeah. Grab a candle. We're
going to start in the basement. We don't need to do, we can do that later. While we work together,
this is going to take like 40 minutes. Not even. Grab a candle from the vending machine.
Where? Out here. Why do we need candles? Because it's dark. It's not that dark. It's very dark.
Vend out a candle. What is that? What does it say? Do you need light? Let me help you.
Read it out loud. Turning hardwood into soft pulp. Power. Pure diesel. Fueled wood.
Rending power. Tired of hauling branches, logs, and tires, and even bodies for miles just to get
rid of them? Well, that ends now. What you need is the ultimate tool. Chuck Torrance's diesel
deforester. Is this just an advertisement for the thing in the back? All right. We'll
vend another candle. That's, hey, that's dirt. That's dirt. That's trash. Get rid of that.
I can only do one thing at a time. We're going to bring, hold on. Where's the,
it's too dark. Okay. Any trash has to go in here and then this has to be ground up.
That's not, why did you put the candle in there? Because it's not dark. I can see very clearly.
Turn your gamma up, kid. Do I turn my gamma up? How do I turn up my gamma? All right. I turn the
gamma up a little. It looks better. Oh, I can see now. All right. Okay. Now, now we skipped a whole
step. Now it'll be 30 minutes. All right. Well, let's, where's the meat grinder? Are these
pumping in the back? Okay. So take this. We don't need a candle anymore. All right. Take the,
just follow me down to the basement. We're getting paid to do this.
There's the stairs. All right. No, no, no. Upstairs, upstairs, upstairs, pronto.
Making it worse. No, upstairs. Oh, okay. Stairs. There are stairs. All right. So I'm going to,
I'll take, there are a couple of rooms up here. Get out of my way. Get out of my face.
Holy shit. This is going to take a long time. Oh no.
All right. We'll throw him away. We have to go from the edge of the house out.
Oh man. This is bad. This is fucking horrible. I found some belongings. All right. We need,
we need to do this right. I need, where's the thing that pushes out the, um,
why is this room so perfect? No, it's like fucked up. This one's like fucked up.
All right. So come here. Where are you? All right. So we're going to pick rooms. So I,
you take this one. Where are you? I'm right here. So you take this room here.
This one here with the bed. Okay. Oh my God. Yeah. It's pretty bad. Okay. So you take that one.
This one's really bad up here too. I'll take this one. And then let me see. I want to see
where to compare. You can look at this one. Oh, this is, oh, this is so, oh yeah.
This is pretty bad. Let me just walk around real fast. You didn't even go in the closet either.
That's an attic. No, no, you know, you know, you know, I, I don't want you to examine my shit.
Come here. You, you, you pick, pick a door and then whatever you get, you get. Come down here.
I'm, you know, I picked this one. I'm going to do this one. I don't know. I have no idea
what the fuck's behind that. I don't know. So. Okay. I'm going to do this one. You can do that one.
Yeah. No, it has to be an actual room. You want to do this one? I don't know what's behind this one.
So I'm going to just. Oh, okay. Just fine. We've been spending 10 minutes. I'll pick this room.
Just take that room. I'm going to take this one. Uh, maybe let's, you gotta grab buckets and shit.
So come here. Okay. What did you put in here? Oh Jesus. All right. You need to have like at
least two or three buckets as a technique. Now where's the thing that Prince fights?
There it is. Okay. On the left side of the house, there's a device. What the fuck am I breaking?
All right. So there's a, on the left side of the house, when you come out,
where'd you go? Come out of the house and you need to see this. It's important to know.
Yeah, I'm coming. Are you coming? What are you doing? Wait, wait, where are you? Wait, wait,
hold on. I'm being assaulted. Come out with the back of the front. How many minutes has it been?
It's been six. Just go out the front door. You need to see this. I'm coming. All right. So
over here, this green stand up display box thing, you click it and it gives you one of these.
It's so much easier just to clean a room by putting shit in here first and then taking that out
and putting it outside and disposing of it later. Okay. So what I like to do is I like to grab
two or three stack them up on top of each other and bring like two into wherever you're cleaning.
You feel what I'm saying? Okay. Yeah. Oh, by the way, holding down shift is walk. It's your best
friend. Okay. So we're going to go clean those two rooms. Yes. I, I, I, yeah, yeah. What was
that Flintstones thing? Oh no, no, I know what that is. Stack. Where are the stairs?
Where are the stairs? Are you serious? I don't remember right here. All right. I got that. Now
you're going to want some buckets. There's already, there's already been a fucking mess.
The buckets count as trash too though. Stack them and get rid of them. I recommend stacking them
one by one into each other and grabbing the bottom bucket. You can also do that when they
have liquid in them, but you have to be careful. I'd like to do at least four or five. Do you really
like to do this? What are you talking about? I'm talking about like you have some free time.
You just like hanging out and cleaning. Yeah. Yeah. What? Yeah. Stop. You're doing a great job.
Just do it. Oh no, I'm good. Oh, by the way, be careful because sometimes it might,
you might get a troll. Spill. You get your own. You have your own room to do upstairs. So get
your own. No, bring more than one. He's an idiot. He's an idiot. I'm the idiot. He's an idiot. He
doesn't understand. You're on like your fourth spill. Oh, I wonder why that is. Maybe it's
because somebody keeps taking them and throwing them into the trash behind me. I only need one.
He's an idiot. He doesn't even know. Where is he? I don't like how quiet it is. I can
hear him like walking around. Are you starting? I guess. Okay. Just wait. We have to do a three,
two, one countdown. I almost just dropped all this. Okay. Stop. Why is it doing that?
Why is it doing that? Guys, why is it doing that? Is this too big to go in the door?
The hell? Oh, fuck. Okay. Why are you leaving doors open? That's your issue.
There's blood all over every wall. Why are the doors open? You're going to get a draft.
You gave me like a Nickelodeon guts staircase to go up, by the way. Thank you.
Can you move that chair, please? Can you move this stuff for me, please? Oh, my mouth.
Not funny. No, time out. Time out. Time out my mouth. Time out. I'm bleeding. I'm moving. I'm
moving. I'm good. It was funny until you fuck. I got to go to the hospital, dude. Did you move
everything? Yeah. It's just. Oh, my fucking God. Take the one on top, please. Just take the one out
of the top. Thanks. Server reaching net actor saturation. Uh oh. What does that mean? We're
about to be over saturated. Server reaching over saturated levels. All right. Are you ready
to start cleaning? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Let's see whose methods better. Okay. So on the count of
on the count of three. Uh, what? Hold on. Let me. I'm not ready to count yet. This is oversaturated.
Okay. On the count of get out of here. You've done enough. Okay. Are you counting? I'm not
ready to count yet. Hold on. You're cleaning already. I'm not cleaning yet. I promise. Look
at this room. Okay. Ready? No, I'm not giving you another viewer. Okay. One, one, two, start
cleaning. Okay. Got any music? What? No, I have to play that. Yeah. Isn't there a radio in the
game? There is a radio in the game, but it's it doesn't really work that well. Oh, are you
allowed to listen to music? Uh, maybe. Am I? Does your mommy say you could? Did you take my?
Take your what? Nothing. What the fuck was that? Is that you doing that? Or is that the game
doing that? That's the horror mansion doing that. Is that the horror mansion? Yeah.
Fuck. Too many actors. Can you, can you clean up some of these actors, please? I'm doing,
I'm doing it. You okay? I'm going to be okay. Dastardly. I'm sorry. Did you not use that word?
I just said dastardly. I'm sorry. Having a fun time. I wish I had the candle in here and it's
too dark. It really is. Are you serious? I just need can. I'd like the candle. How are you doing?
You doing okay? Yeah. How are you like halfway? Yeah, I'm getting there. I think maybe I should
have got more buckets. I told you I'm trying to get this as clean as possible. Clean, clean, clean.
Now remember, it what it matters is to be valid. Your room has to be completely empty
of no like trash cans. No, but if this stuff like belongs there, like there's books and stuff.
I mean, the books are fine, but no like trash and no buckets and no enough. Yeah, it has to
be out of the room completely clean room. Okay. And we'll have we'll have some like a chat
inspection. I'm not in a game. No. All right. Well, you you try to host this time. Damn it.
Hold on. I put in so much work. I did too. You don't know how much work I put in.
God damn it. Okay, hold on. I'm setting up the host. Maybe I can actually do it this time.
Oh, wait, I'm in like the normal game now. It like kicked me to the normal game. Oh, you got
on the normal game. Oh, my God. Do I have your stream restarted? It was playing on my stream.
It was wait, what? Forget about just don't even talk to me. All right, I'm gonna go like this.
And I'm gonna go like this. And it's gonna be really fun in like another 20 minutes when I go
to zero again. Okay. Well, I'm hosting it. I'm in the game. Wait, frick. Hold on. I'm not hosting it.
I closed the game. This is too hard. Cleaning was easy. Cleaning was easy. This is hard.
I'm going to zero again, I think. No, why? Why? If you can't clean it, just call it off.
No, I can't call it off. Just admit that I win. We can move on. I'm not going to admit.
We can reschedule. We can do something else. All right, let's try one more time.
Okay. All right, you got a game? Okay, hold on. I'm fuming right now. Oh, I just like I'm fuming
right now. Okay, I'm in. I think I invite you. I don't do I don't know. I've never used a computer
before. The mic still on. I know I'm live right now. We'll try it again. We'll see what happens.
Oh, yeah. Well, now we both know how this works. You know, it's fair.
It's hilarious because you want to know something?
I just got murdered. Why? I was going to say something funny. Not funny, actually. The funny
thing is they did a hardware node upgrade. They did like hardware maintenance, like upgraded the
node as worse than ever before. Holy shit. What are what are you saying? Holy shit. Like fucking
the Internet's stupid. Okay. Anyways, you got a game? I'm coming. Yeah. Let's see if this works.
See if I can stay connected for more than a minute. Oh, did you put the password in the
in our in our DM here? It's the same one from the other game. We tried to play another game
before this and my computer like restart it. And then it crashed to desktop the second time.
So so far, you know, playing games with Jerma, a lot of fun. It's going pretty good. It is fun,
isn't it? God. All right. Hey, okay. So what would you look? Okay, so here's how you play.
It's funny. Here's what you do. Go over here. Shut up. And there's you pick it up, you press
you can rotate it. What does this thing do? It tells it's a smell machine. It tells you what
when you turn it on, and you point it around. It'll tell you specifically what direction is
still trash. You can change the you can change the mode. If you right click one of them is blood
and body parts. The other one is trash. And it kind of beeps the closer you get. Okay.
That's great news. Yeah, it is. You are not going to get that same room again, because
we both know it was already. Yeah, I know. Yeah, I know. It was it was fun. So how about
how about you get the room that I had with the bed? And I'll do the basement. You think you can do
that? Yeah. I'll just do you one higher. I'll do the living room. I'll do the whole living room.
This would be completely completely spotless. I think the other room was worse because it's
upstairs and you got to walk all the way up there. Is that not fair? Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You get my
old room. I get basement. You're the one that had like the bed with the blood in the Freddy Krueger
hand. Yeah. All right. You got it. Get situated. Get ready. Okay. And I'm not going to like close
the game when I'm embarrassed about my room or anything. Okay. And I'm only doing the
there's like two rooms down here. I'm only doing the actual basement. Why did that cause more?
Not this like no just do the actual basement. I'll do your old room. I'm loading in more stuff.
Okay. I know what room is yours. I'm going to get some stuff situated and we can go
up. Get this back over here. Making a lot of noise up there. Yeah. Cause I'm moving around.
I'm trying to get situated so I can start this cleaning job. Okay. Where? What the fuck? Good
call. Nice. Nice call. Not a bad idea. I just ran around. I walked around the whole house
to get this. I'm only going to do two. No, I can do three. I know I can do three. I've done like,
I've done like five before. I can't even fit two through the front door.
Let's go. I can't do two. No, I can't apparently. Why are you leaving doors closed in this house?
We're doing a job. What? Why am I leaving doors closed before it was open? And it was
irritating. What am I? What's going on? Am I stuck on something? I was just walking on the table.
That makes no sense. Okay. I'm about ready to get going here. This is the room right here.
I thought we started. No, that's fine. You can go ahead. No, that's fine. You're that confident.
I'm pretty confident. I am. What the fuck was that? I'm confident. I am. All right. Here we go.
Jipple sandwich. Why are you doing that? I don't know. Did you almost get crushed?
I don't know. I was just thinking about Jipple sandwiches. We're kind of in a house of horrors.
Why am I even doing this? This can just stay in here. Remember, no trace of any liquid.
Everything has to be perfect. Not even water? I mean, no, no, no, no, no water. The room has
to be done. Okay. You're something of an expert. How many rooms have you cleaned? Let's get that
straight. Ever? Yeah, because you're about to be beat by like a one-time room cleaner. I mean,
I've cleaned a lot of rooms before. It depends. How many? I mean, we all know you haven't picked
up a mop in like four years, as you said, five years, something like that. Very respectful.
That's not a bad number. All right. I'm getting, I'm doing pretty well. How are you doing over
there? Things looking good? Very good. Very good. Good, good, good, good. I like to hear that.
I like to hear the competition is, you know, not just a one-sided thing, right? Yeah. It's
nice to see that the server is like stable now. Yeah. I wonder why it was having problems before.
I don't know. I'm just going to make my own internet. Yeah. Maybe I was saying before,
maybe you should like move to like Vegas to fix your internet. Everything sucks. Don't you know?
Everything sucks. Oh, we're getting the actor. We're getting the oversaturated actors thing again.
Who's an actor? I don't know what that means. Nice spill. Did you hear it? I heard you say
fuck and I heard a bucket. I haven't spilled once yet. This game is easy.
I need another bucket up here. Do you need any help? No. What? Why? I'm just trying to move
some stuff in that house. It sounds like you're having trouble. Like I could bring you a bucket.
No, that's good. Do you need a bucket? I could bring you something if you need.
No, I'm good. All right. Good. Just trying to help each other out here.
United friendly competition. We just we help each other out.
You know, do you need something? I don't need anything. I'm good. God damn it. Let me get out
here. I just need to dispose of these buckets that I have in my hand and then go this way.
Cool. I need like two more buckets. I think maybe. Why do I always go this wrong way?
Two buckets will do it and then I've got a little bit more time.
Come on. Do two. He's getting ahead of me. Come on. Hurry up.
Do you know the speedrun strategy so you can like be hop and everything?
I have my own strategy. You do yours. Are you trying to lock those out? Illegal move.
Illegal move. Illegal move. How is this illegal? You didn't set any rules. Illegal.
Are you still behind me? I needed that bucket too. That's an illegal move.
If you win, you're disqualified. I don't see any rules written anywhere.
There was a verbal agreement that you were going to be nice today.
Jeremiah, I'll be nice today. How you come? Almost done. Really?
Yeah, it's actually isn't that bad. Fucking illegal move. It was bullshit. It really was.
Oh, if I lose, it's because of that one bucket. Yeah, because I needed that. I would be almost
done by now. Can we get a ref? Anyone? Anyone want to be the ref here?
Anyone see that? I just like rubber banded. Oh, lag. Lag. I was going to win by lag.
That was an actual illegal move. Yeah. You don't need to mean it. I don't need to tell you that.
Oh my god. Okay. Watch that. Watch it. Okay. Give yourself a percentage. What percentage
you think you are? Like 80. 80. Yeah, I'm probably around 70. I got a way to go, I think.
Don't get too confident, though. I hear comebacks are very common in the
high level of competition. Yeah, I would say I'm like 65% probably.
Going backwards. I think I may have gone backwards a little.
Do you know the background for this house? Like, is this?
It's like a Freddy and Jason or something. Something like that.
On the classic Indian burial ground. There's some empty graves down here.
Cool. I like graves or something. I'm focusing. I'm focusing. I'm focusing.
I'm way behind you. So I need to focus. I'm probably at like, I'm getting there.
Fuck. I'm done. Done. I said it first. I said it first. I definitely said it first. I said it
first. I said it first. No, you didn't. You didn't say it. You did not say shit. I said done and then
you said done. How about we based on whose room is cleaner? I bet you have a spot somewhere like
you left something. No, I'll let it slide. Okay. Let me come see your room. All right. Don't track
shit up here. True. Okay. Hold on. Let me walk outside and clean my boots. Hold on. I'm getting
clean. I think I'm clean. Okay. Inspection. Oh, what's that chair? I see a knocked over chair
behind you. I just bumped into it because I was scared that you came in here. It was like this.
Jack took a screenshot. No, you startled me. It's not right. No, I'm sorry. If an inspector
walks in a room and goes, the person's going to go, what the fuck, and turn. That's what you did.
Okay. I'll let it pass. That's good. Everything's fine. I have to deduct a point for the chairs.
What is this chair? Where is it facing? It's not like a desk. It's just in the middle of the room,
a chair. What's wrong with that? You guys just leave chairs around your room? Yeah. Is everyone
okay with there just being random chairs? Where would you put this chair? There's no where to sit.
There's no place for that chair to be. It shouldn't be in here. What if I want somebody
to come in and help me? Maybe if you turned them and you at least pretended that this was a desk.
Automatically assuming that there's no small baby in this house, that the mother would have
to sit here and nurse. What are you talking about? You need the chair for that. Yeah,
you need to sit in a chair for that. I don't know. I wouldn't put a baby on a chair like that.
You need a rocking chair. The mother sits in the chair with the baby in her arms.
What are you talking about? I don't know. Fine. Deduct a point. I'll take that. Okay.
You can't open these? No, you can't open those. What the fuck was that noise? That was scary.
I got spooked. Nothing. It's nice and clean. All right. You got a 99. Nice. Thank you. Okay.
99. One point off. That's cool. Wait. Wait. I just got a tip. What do you mean a tip? Okay.
If you're the inspector, wait, wait, wait. Hold on a minute here. If you're the inspector,
do you have to call other inspectors to do your job for you? That was you just did.
You just inspect photographs and then you get the final review is from chat we said.
So I'm taking their input. I know you don't read yours. I read mine a lot
and I take their input all the time and I'm very nice to them consistently. I would love it if
from yesterday's stream if anybody could pull up some data on how many times my eyes looked over
at the left monitor. Now that's chat and it was probably four or five hundred times.
Is chats on the right? Chat is on the left actually. Nope. Excuse me. I've seen it. Okay.
How would I pick up? How would I pick up the one guy? That person's coming to get you.
That was weird. That freaked me out. Never mind. You're bringing an axe. Yeah. Because the person
who has the least score has to get their head chopped. This is a horror game. Inspectors first.
Okay. Let me clean my feet. Let me rub my feet. Let me. Wow. Entry way is a little bit of a. Nope.
Hey, not judging based on the entry. Wow. Well, first of all, this is not the basement. This is
the. Okay. Whoa. Whoa. I don't know about this.
You idiot. Well, thanks for concentrating. You're next. That's the joke. You're one of them now.
I win. Oh, oh, oh, I got me. Well, here's the funny thing. I have a confession to make.
Yeah. I won. That's a confession. Confession. I won. All right. I threw everything out the window.
Oh, so you cheated. So did you. So you're disqualified and I. You cheated too.
How did I cheat? Look, come over here. My. Wait, did I cheat though? Or did I just move?
Wait, did that? No, that didn't come out of here. We both cheated. We both were wrong,
but I was. I was very deliberate. But your room is not clean. Who's room is cleaner?
I think the precedent first is who cheated. Like if you're caught using, you know, what,
what were they using the cork baths or, you know, way back in the day when they're hitting slammers.
You're old enough. You remember, right? So I threw stuff out my window, but cleaned the room.
You made the room way worse. Who's room is cleaner? You deflated the football. You lose.
Uh, what about, what about the illegal move where you knocked the shit out of my hands?
That wasn't illegal. How is that? No, my room was cleaner and I could have just like kept that lie
up and you would have just been so disappointed. I can't believe you did this though, but thanks
for putting everything in the right spot for us to clean. All right. We're going to work together.
We're still doing this. What do you mean we're still doing this? I would love to see you actually
clean the basement disaster zone now. You're just going to watch. Show me how it's done.
You're just going to watch me do this. Well, okay. Let's, let's do it together. Nice catch.
All right. So that's not the basement. Hey rookie, catch this. Oh, no. Open the door.
Open the door, please. My lip, my lip, my mouth, my mouth. Look at my mouth. Is it bad? It's bone.
Oh, fuck. No, no, no, no, no, no. I got, I got it. I got it.
Is it better? Let me see. No, it's bad. You're beeping. All right. Let's go. Okay. Where do you
start? I don't know. What's the method? You have to just grind the people. You have to grind them.
That's not the method. Um, all right. Where's the back door? There's no back door down here.
Oh God. All right. Well, we got to bring them all up the stairs.
Wait, is there, there's a cut. There's a thing you can cut. Where's the cutter?
A cutter? Yeah. There's a cutter. There's secret tools. Is that another point deduction? You didn't
tell me about the secret tool. No, no, no, no, no. Can I, can we cut? There's this, there are secret
tools, but I don't know if they're in here. I can't believe you did this. This is like so bad.
All right. Just start grabbing people. Just grab people. Okay. People first. People try to get two
people in one of these. What about respecting the dead? Um, says the guy that piled them all up down
here. Now get your own bucket. You said try and get two in here. I got two. We're working together.
Are you picking this up or am I picking this up? You should take that. Okay. I'm gone. Here. How
about I pass the bodies up the stairs? Just throw them up the stairs. Where's the grinder?
Backyard. This guy doesn't even know where the grinder is. Yeah. Nice clean room you had there.
All right. This is not, this is not doing so well. I think they're still alive. Are you sure? Are you
sure you killed them? Are you sure you killed these people? I am sure they're dead. We're missing
somebody. That person's gone. Wait, there's more down here. Oh dude, dude, dude. What? Dude, there's
another house. There's another house? There's another house. Where? Oh, there's a back path.
Four hours, by the way. Oh dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude, dude,
dude. I can't believe it dude. Yeah, there's definitely a back entrance though. I mean,
you go around the back. Yes, they do. Dude, I don't see a back door. I guess there's no back door,
but why? I found the one true ring. The one true ring. To rule them all. The Lord of the Rings.
Okay. What about it? Do you like that movie? You've never seen that movie. It's literally, it's.
What? You've never seen Lord of the Rings. Stand still. Drop the body. Look forward.
Just pick a direction. Just stop. Just pick a direction. I'm stopped. Don't touch my ring.
Oh, it actually is the ring. All right, we're gonna do a bit of golf impression. Uh, wins the
contest. Okay, uh, go. Go, your turn. Go, go, go. Did you just throw out the ring?
Yeah, that's a, that's a fucking whole series then. Oh, okay. I'll hold the box because you can't.
Spoilers. Spoilers. Spoilers. Just bring them. Still. Spoilers. The Lord of the Rings. Spoilers.
What happens if we destroy this? I have the ring in my hand. What happens? Destroy it. What,
is this how you kill Sauron? Don't you have to drop it off Mountain Dune? Like this probably
can't do it. Yes, Mount Dune. Mountain Dune. Dune's a good series. You can't even get it in. Here,
let me show you how it's done. There you go. World still stands. All right, keep, keep it going.
Go get the rest of them. I lined up the bodies. I did my part. Hey, where are you going?
Get this out of the way. Well, you did bring them in a nice concentrated zone. Yeah. Jesus.
That was horrible. It's really like, it went right in there. How far away were you?
Right behind you. It's like a glove. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't throw this one in.
Okay. New competition. New competition. Okay. Let's see how far away you can stand and get the
body in. Oh God. Um, okay. Did you just get it in? No, I'm right here now. Well, I'm waiting. You
first. Okay. Now I get a throw. We trade off throw. Okay. That was the equivalent of a boxing match.
You just like punched me once in the face and I fell flat down and just took a fall.
Okay. See, I didn't get mine. Now you, now you go again. How about not farthest, but
the stairs are the limit. You can't walk in front of the stairs. All right. Stairs are the limit.
That sounds good. Is it, is there a way to, um, what is it like a way to put momentum behind it?
I don't know. No, I can't like golf them in there. All right. I'm going to try. Here we go.
It looks so silly. Try to get like full momentum. Okay. Move, move, move.
We show you how it's done. Holy shit. That was close. That was pretty good.
Wait, wait. Somebody says you can hold left click, hold left click and shake the mouse.
Oh, it's just to rotate them. Uh, I lost mine. What? How did he go backwards?
Are you trying to, you didn't even dunk it. Oh, you don't think I can dunk it. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. I'm just going to place them in. I lost them. Did you just die? Oh shit. I guess I win.
I'm back. I respond. Yes, you can die in visceral cleanup detail. All right. You dunk.
How are you doing that? I'm going to get it. Somewhere in the future. Someone's going to pull
up this video and they're going to be like, what the fuck was wrong with people?
Why are they stimulating, like throwing each other like dead bodies into a grinder?
What were they doing this for? Come on. It looks like,
oh, it looks like you're doing like a magical spell.
Thank you for just standing by and watching too. Cause like you could stop this.
I could, but will I know if I could stand a little closer? No, you have to get it from here.
Whoa. I don't, I, it's hard to see where I'm throwing it. Cause I'm not looking where I'm
throwing. You're standing closer. How are you doing that? You're going like, you're doing like
swing up, down, up, down. Yeah. Look up. Yeah. Look up. Cause you need to get some height on it.
And at the end, when you, when you pull it forward, you got to, you got to right click them.
It's really hard to get height. It is really hard to get the height on it.
Please hurry up and do this. So my fucking great grandkids don't, you got it. You got it.
You did it. You actually did it. I was going to say, because I'm like great grandkids don't
think I'm like a fucking psycho. Did you see me? Did you watch me or were you like looking at the
stars? No, I saw it. It was great. I just spun my mouse around in circles and like, oh, like I
totally gave up. All right. Let's do it. Let's do it. Alley-oop. Ready? Yeah. All right. Let's look
back to the basement. Four hours, by the way. Go one at a time. You're still doing like the
magician trick. All right. I gotta, I gotta like try. I gotta make the job fun somehow.
Well, that was weird. Oh, you, if you do it too fast, you just drop them. All right. And wait,
is that all the bodies? What am I doing? Why did you do this? Oh, that was a clean throw.
This is classic star. You know, what's classic star. Where are you? We're not,
we're not working on the basement. I am in the basement. How is this still clean?
We gotta go inside out. Oh my God. Put this guy on a team inside. I don't miss anymore. Look,
I get that extra step forward. I don't miss. I don't, I don't know what that's a reference to,
but I may or may not have been funny. I don't know. It's not a reference. I'm doing so good.
I'm not missing my shot. That's not like a, like a CS go like pro didn't say that during a
competition or something. I don't, not that I'm aware of. So you did, you just made, you just said
that. Yeah. I got, I'm two in a row. Shouldn't we, shouldn't we be getting all this stuff out first?
Just when you get, when you have to just get the, you don't want to, you don't want to track stuff
everywhere. Or like we're going, like we're going to. No, but you're not. Oh my God. Look what you
did. Look what you fucking did. Look what you did. Stop throwing it. Look what you did. Um,
you don't even talk about my throwing. There's a skeleton in here.
All right, let's go. You really did. It's like too much stuff. Hey, hey, hey, do we get rid of the
boxes or we just reshelf? No, we gotta get, no, that's not the strategy. What? This is where they
were. I'm going to get two more buckets and I'm going to go get like, there's one already here.
Nice. But this one's dirty. So get rid of it. Whether you like it or not, as long as my internet
stays on. I know what it is. You can't reach the top shelf. Is that some kind of joke? Is that,
is that, I don't understand. Is that like a, like what do you mean? What do you mean? Like I,
you would rather take the boxes out of here, like all the way up the stairs for each individual box
and admit that you can't reach the top shelf. But you, you can't reach the top shelf. No, I. What?
Like you can't reach the top shelf, right? That's what you're saying. No, I'm saying you can't,
like I can't, but you can't either. I totally can. So if I came over there right now and we both
tried to grab the top shelf, you, I wouldn't deal with it. No, put a box up on the top shelf.
I don't think you're putting it down when I'm picking up here. I don't. But I'm, I'm very,
I'm a huge, I'm, they actually call me massive man now.
Massive man? Yeah. M.M. for short. That's my new thing. Why are you massive man? I just like,
I just heard like a. Yeah. Well, the outside's going pretty well because I'm doing some work.
I'm working on it. Remember where we're going to put the collective? Why is there only, oh yeah,
because my internet turned off. Remember what? Remember to put the USBs outside the door,
the front door to the right. That's that way we get our bonus. Yes, there is a bonus.
And then there's a nice clean house you can feel, you can feel proud of. Okay. And then you like
take a screenshot. Yes. Put it on Insta. Sure. Wherever you want to put it. Don't matter where.
Look mom clean. Wherever, whatever social media you'd like to put it on. Oh, what the? I broke
it. I can't, I broke the box. Do I have to, do I have to get on the roof? I'm going to check out
the roof. I broke it. I can't wait to be on that. What do you mean you broke it? I can't,
the box is stuck. Well, we can delete it. Hey, hey, what are you talking about? What?
I sincerely hope you're not getting into any shenanigans. I know I'm trying to get on the
roof, but I can't. We're cleaning the basement. Why are you trying to get on the roof? I'm outside
doing the outside. Cause look, no, every time we agreed to both do the basement. Look, the email
that I got clearly stated you two need to work on the project together. And wherever you feel most
comfortable being at this here, when we're at the cleaning job is where you can go. I hear when
we're at the cleaning job. No, you said I see, we were both going to do the basement and we were
going to help each other. I did say that, but I'm still going to do that. But I, I'm going to,
I am going to rub a corpse all along the roof if you don't get down here.
That'll go in the email that I write. So do whatever you think is necessary to do in a
professional manner. I'll come help you. Basement. That's where I'm going. Just get, please move out
of the way, please. I'm fine. Grab that top one. Grab the top one and be gentle. Very gentle there.
I don't know how you did that. What did you do? What did you do? Why did you do that? Why did you
do that? How can you possibly say that? You took it out. You, you took it out. You must have done
something. You had to have done something. Look at this. What are you doing? Well, I'm not. Oh,
oh, it's because we deleted the ring. These are ring wraiths. I don't know what you're talking
about. You just, there's no, you don't even know anything. Just grab a bucket and meet me downstairs.
You know nothing. You fucked this up so bad down here. It's not, I don't think it's even
possible to do this. How is it not possible? Okay, here's your job. You want to send like a
message to HR? Fine. Go just bring buckets down here and go get like, just keep bringing them down.
Okay, I'll bring one down, take something out. Talk about cans of peas, all the random vegetables,
get them into the trash can and then incinerate them. You can reach the top shelf down there.
Hold on. Okay, he's in. Uh, didn't put water in this one. There, there were a couple that I
brought down from before. Fuck this bucket stacking. It's a waste of everyone's time.
Dirty water. Okay, put those. All right, we're gonna have to take the box, the boxes up like
one by one, I think. I'm put, I'm shelving them. You're, you're putting these on the shelves?
Yeah. Oh, you're standing on a bucket to do it. Cute. You didn't even clean up here. You didn't
even clean up here though, dude. Like, come on. What do you, what? You can clean after you put
the boxes there. You can put, you can't, you're gonna knock the boxes off. What do you mean?
You're gonna clean under the boxes after the boxes are up there. I'm sure you can. Oh man,
I don't think I can work like this. I don't think I can.
Holy fuck, I just jumped over everything. I'm good. That would have been very bad.
All right, can we at least take care of the entryway? Can you bring a candle down here too?
Are you, I just heard a spill. That wasn't me.
What? What? You spilled the bucket and it wasn't me. So it's funny to me. What bucket? I heard
like a up here. That was me throwing out old buckets. I thought you were back in the fucking
basement. You made permanent marks on the wall. Permanent. Yeah, these are permanent marks.
Oh, maybe not. Just clean around. Slow. Easy. Bring, bring a candle down here.
Yeah, I know you can. They're right next to you. Okay, I'll do it. Thank you. I just, I want to
be able to, it's atmosphere. We're doing the Halloween map. You don't want to have atmosphere
here. There's a little, there's a little cache. Okay, I got it. I got it. What was that? What was
that? Focus on, focus on what's in front of you. What do you mean what's in front of me? Like do
your task. What's that noise? Worrying about everyone else is doing. I'm getting you the candle.
All right, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Take this. You're like, what's that? There was a chainsaw
sound. I thought you brought a chainsaw down. Take this. No, that was the creating a candle.
Oh, that, right? Like put it on the, yeah, no, no, no, I'm gonna have to clean there.
Take this up with you when you're out. Here, you put it where you want it. Yeah, I will. And then
just take this. This one's dirty. Let's get rid of that one. Throw it in the incinerator.
There we go. Thank you. That's, that's so much better. Why are you up here? I just wanted to
check. Check what? I just had to check on something. Not a big deal.
I'm gonna have something else for you to take. Why would we get grind these up? These are
perfectly good beans. All right, this is starting to do the thing where there's too many physics
objects in the thing at the same time. So you have to take this and get out of here with this.
Let me shake it up. Okay, okay. Drop it, drop, drop it. Hold on. Drop it. Easy.
Easy. Careful. It's going to do the physics thing. I'm, I'm well aware of the physics thing.
See, don't you, don't you think this is a cool game? Hello. It's great. It's great. It's great.
Don't, you don't, don't be sarcastic about it. It's fun. It's great. Just wait till we do another
one after this. Uh, which one's next? I'm already looking forward to it. Well, we bet you better
hurry up. We got work to do here. Oh, nice job. Back on the shelf. Nice job, like hiding the beans.
For yourself. What do you mean hiding the what? Put the box in front of the beans so no one knows
there's beans back there. There's a broken plate over here. Do you want another box? Is that what
you're saying? Stand over here for a second. Just stand over here. Get like in the light right,
right there. Right there. Oops. Sorry, I dropped it. Don't do it. Why did you, what, what, how did I
end up with this in my hand? What? Just, okay. Okay. I didn't do that. That was mean. That was
a mean thing that he did. Are you bringing some new, you're not bringing new buckets down.
These are still clean. The one you just dumped on me was full of blood. And now I have to take out
this box. There's two clean buckets right here. And now I gotta take this box out. Look what
you've done over here. And you're tracking mud all over the place. Thank God that candle's down here.
Did I just break the grinder? What? We need that. I heard like a, but that's fine. That's fine.
USB right here. All right. Look, come on. It's looking pretty good. It's not looking bad. Yep.
And this is almost one room done. Well, this room was like 10 rooms because you made it that way.
Anything in this? No. The only reason why this room is taking so long is because you put all
the trash from all the other rooms into one room. I, all those boxes were in that room already.
What about the 10 bodies? Where'd you get those? I got the bodies from a lot of places.
Are you calling those bodies trash? Respect the bodies. Thank you for the new water. No,
come here. Give me this candle. There we go. Now I can see better. And now here we go. Okay.
I consolidated the trash. Like that word. Consolidated. Yeah. I could, what is this?
Like a credit card payment? No, this is like almost cleaned up your whole mess.
That was a Jerry Seinfeld level joke. Seinfeld was a hilarious show. That's a very funny show.
So that's okay. That's like a nine out of 9.8 out of 10 on Rotten Tomatoes. Why would I be mad
about that? Yeah, it's like one of the best shows of all time. I mean, that's like saying like, oh,
man. Well, what you just did right there. Oh, that was like, that was like something God would do.
He's very comparable. Like, oh, well, yeah, I get it. Okay.
Isn't streaming much better with an audience? What are you talking about? Oh, like when you
hear Ashley laugh. It's like you can imagine you're streaming in front of an auditorium.
Well, there's like one person in this stand. There's one person in this stand.
But at least they showed up. I don't hear any laughs from your side. No, no, that person's not
here in the auditorium. You brought a cell phone in and put it on speakerphone and put it in the
chair. And they're watching the live video of my like stand up routine. Yeah. Critics are saying
as good as Seinfeld. Go get Otto. All right, this is almost full. I feel like I'm doing more than
you. You're not doing more than me. You have a live feed of my work that you can critique
anytime you want. I don't have like the multi stream. Who's watching both? Who's doing more?
Are you streaming? Yeah. I thought you had, I thought your stream was off. Why are we not in
squads? I don't know. I thought you, your stream wasn't on. What? Add me to a squad. Okay. What
the hell is going on here? I don't know you streaming. I know. Do you invite me? Hold on.
I'll invite you. No, I'll invite you. Yeah. Fine. Fine. Invite me. Invite me. Okay. Invite me.
Invited. All right there. I didn't know that was happening. I thought you had your stream turned
off. No, you weren't live when I turned it on. That never happened. I checked your stream.
We both started at the same time. Yeah. But did you turn your stream off after you played
Overwatch? Yeah. As I'm saying, all right. All right. You ready? I've got, I've got most
of the trash. Wow. You did a good job. You did. How satisfied do you feel? I'm not that satisfied
yet because there's still things that need to be done. Can't you just take a moment and like be
happy? We can after we get it all done. I've actually never seen you smile. You look at the
ceiling. We're not done. Do you need another bucket? I don't think I need another bucket.
Thank you for the consideration. How long has it been? Four hours? I think we're at like seven.
Okay. It's up. The basement is pretty much done. There's a little bit left on the floor,
on the wall a little bit. Oops. All right. He'll pick that up. What's up with this broom?
What's with the broom? Yo. What are you talking about? I found like a broom that I used like a
mop, but it's a broom. Oh, I don't know. I figure what that does. All right. I'm going to use the
candle. We're going to check. All right. Everything looks okay except for that. That's why I need the
light down here. Well, don't you have like the speedometer to check where the blood is? Yeah,
but I mean it's easier to just see it. Yeah. Don't you have this speedometer saved? Yeah,
that was a little that was just a little a little boop. We're fine. I don't mind the little the
little boobs. It's the your internet turns off to zero is the one I don't like. Okay.
We can you can use the little oh no no no no no this the the the red rum room.
There's a bathroom in here. There is a bathroom. Oh god. What did you do in here?
I was like that when I found it. It's actually not hard to clean, but unfortunately
I'm sorry to say we need another bucket down here. I'm sure you do. I'm going to bring one up.
I'll go get it. You just you keep doing anything. I'm bringing the bucket. Stay in the fucking
basement. Well, okay. I'm going to stay in the basement, but just don't there's a lot of blood
to track. So don't track it up here. I have two buckets that are full of gross stuff that I need
you to take. Clean your feet. Clean feet. Clean feet. I don't have. Yeah, there's an intestine
over here. Hold on. Okay. Take that. Is that yours? Yeah, it's mine. That's my intestine.
Ah, god damn it.
Did you spill? Do you still have the one of me complaining? I don't. People asked for it all day
and I forgot. You're gonna have to give me a new one and I'll have to remember.
Hey, hold on. I'll just bring it. I'll bring the second ear over here.
Watch those feet. I'm not moving. You're tracking stuff everywhere. I don't want to read that.
Hey, give me one. Give you what? You're gonna give me a line. When did I say I was gonna give
you a line? I thought you just said, okay, never mind. I'm crazy. Never mind. I said what happened
to the one you recorded? Yeah, I said I like didn't save it by accident and then you said,
hold on. I'll give you one and then. Did I do that? Yeah, then. I don't think I did that.
Did I say that? All right, well, turn it on. Okay. No, let's talk about the. Yeah, I've talked about
the ear. Yeah, I wasn't. I didn't say that. All right. You ready? Yeah. Hold on. Oh, yeah,
I was complaining about DPS, right? Okay. Hello. I can hear myself. Why can I hear myself? Hello.
Hello. Hello. God damn it. Why does it have to quit me out too?
Ah, that was a Charlie Brown yell. I know. Hello. Stop it. Stop it. It's not funny. I'm upset.
Stop it. It's not funny. I'm upset. Hello. What the fuck? We're never gonna be able to do a full
one of these. Hold on. Oh, yeah, I was complaining about DPS, right? Okay.
No. Hello. No. Why? Why? We can't get anything going. Hello.
What a sad day. Are you coming back? I mean, like the server's still up. What? It is? Yeah. Oh,
it is. Holy shit. Okay, cool. I'm coming in. How did you? You didn't get that? I thought that we
like I thought everything got disconnected. No, I'm fine. Because I'm hosting this one.
Oh, cool. Hello. I'm so fucking sad right now. Like, I might sound like, oh,
I'm so angry right now. This isn't it. You can't, you know, there's no consoling me.
Hello. Fucking angry right now. I'm so angry. I'm so angry. Hello. All right. So where were we?
Uh, we were cleaning the basement. Okay, we're cleaning the basement. Cool.
All right. So where were we? Hello. Stop. Leave me alone. Leave me alone. I can't.
I have too many emotions right now. I'm being stretched. I'm being stretched in two different
directions. We're almost done with the basement. You're gonna pull me in half. I have like anger
and upset and fucking rage. And then you're making me laugh. Hello. Are you in? I'm in. I'm in. I'm
in. I'm here. I'm here. I'm very angry, but I'm here. I'm very angry. I forget what door is the
basement door. That's how fucked up I am. Okay. The basement is clean. I think basements clean.
Yeah. Did I drop again? Uh, no, I, I know. All right. The bathroom is clean. The toilet is clean.
Oh, I broke the toilet, but it's okay. Oh, typical fucked up. I am. No, I know. It's fine.
I can close it clean, clean, clean, clean. All right. This is clean. That's clean. That's clean
over here. Clean this way. Oh, don't do it again. Don't do it again. It's going to do it again.
No, it's not. You're fine. Your streams up. Everyone's loving it. Everyone's loving this
content that you're providing. Thanks. Thanks. Thanks. You really make me feel better. All right.
Let's go. Basement is clean. I'm so happy that you brought me along as backup streamer.
You're like the, you're like the never turn off the battery thing. Yeah. Whatever it is,
the thing you plug in to make sure your power doesn't turn off.
I'm the backup generator. Yes. What did I, what did I call it?
I'm the battery thing. I think you called it. The never turn off.
Whatever. The never turn off battery thing.
Okay. So I need, what's going on over here? Are you throwing more stuff out the window?
What? No, I'm, I'm finishing up the basement. There's a couple like empty bucks down here.
Okay. So this is, what's in here? This one can be done quickly. Yeah. I remember this was me.
Yeah. I'm going to clean up over here. Hello. Hello. Just get like 10 of them. You ready?
Yeah. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Ashley's ruining them. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Uh, that was just a Charlie Brown's yell. I know. That's a nice car. Can you stop goofing
around with your soundboard? Get this building clean. Oh, I'm doing the, uh, the garage. Hello.
Hello. It's going to be easier to demolish this building. Yeah. It would be way easier just to
do like a controlled demolition. What happened tonight? Did you see the car?
What car? There's a really cool car in here. Yeah. I saw it. I took a body from that room.
You left a body in that room too though. Oh, well see I was having a hard time running around
and grabbing bodies and also making sure you didn't see me grab all them.
But little did I know you never left the room. No, I did not walk out of the room. I didn't really
hear you walking around. I was wondering what was going on. Scheme. I had a scheme going.
How fucked up I am. That was so angry. I am so bad right now. Scheme. I think we're done.
We are not done. Do you know how much is left in here? I think we're done. We are not done. Pull
out your little ecto gun thing and see where it is. It says all clear on it. Oh, hold on. I'm
getting a phone call. Hello. Hello. This is the boss man. They're calling it in. We're done.
What the hell was that? Yeah, all clear here. That was my phone. Our walkie. This is the boss.
All janitors have them. This is not done though. You got your soundboard.
I don't even feel wallpapered that room. Why is there on the camera? We could use that somewhere.
All right, the car looks pretty good. Johnny, we've left money in the pantry for you. Remember
to call us straight away if Jason or Danielle try to reach us in case something goes wrong
at the Crystal Lake summer camp. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Let's get this trash out of
here. Hello. You can use that. You can use that somewhere. I think you can use that somewhere.
Hello. Testing my mic. Well, don't worry. You'll disconnect again and I'll have plenty of use for
the hello. Yeah, you'll have plenty of use when I disconnect a fourth time today.
How about you stream when it's working? Like during the day? That is the theory. It is during
the day. Oh. Hello. Garage is almost clean. There are a couple of knives. I cleaned the front yard.
Front yard is clear. This is not trash. They're just knives. That's not garbage. It's a knife.
Here's the question. If we do such a good job of cleaning,
does that mean the parents never know what happened to their kids?
Well, no, because when they know what how would. Well, I just read that note that was telling them,
good luck at summer camp and blah, blah, blah. So if everything is spick and span and perfect
when they come back, how do they know what happened? So shouldn't we leave one blood
stain with a murder weapon? I mean, they've already been notified. Are we the bad guys?
No, we're just the cleaning crew. How do you know they've been notified?
Did Big Boss Man tell you that? I don't know. I'm just assuming that they've been notified.
Don't you ever think like outside what you're currently doing like your job? Do you ever think
like, you know, what if it's not all true? You read too many fucking books. You read too many
books. You should just be drinking tap water and eating fucking Cheerios like the rest of us.
Fuck, I broke the glass. Hello. I was on the front door. Hello. Hello. Hello. Let me fight
myself. Hey, what's up, dude? Nothing much. Hello. How are you? Hello. Hi. That's all I have.
I don't want to press the wrong button too. I'm forgetting which is which. I'm fucked up. I am.
Oh, I was pretty. So I got some stuff over here if you need it. I got some. I need a bucket over
here. Oh, cool. No, that was pretty cool. But not cool because the internet sucks. So just deal with
it. Cool. I'm not going to deal with it because that's fucking bullshit. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
cool. Stop. Not funny. She laughed. The measurement of what's funny is if my wife laughs. So I think
you're wrong. I was trying to have me yell and talk to me. Oh, cool. You don't even you don't
get comedy. I've heard people compare this stream to
think I get comedy. And he's pretty close to the man upstairs himself from my hair. Yep.
What do you do with the USBs when you're done? You put them in the wrong way first every time.
You never get it right. First try. Oh, my God. And that to truth. Oh, my God. Is this how you
get on the roof? I know I tried to use that thing earlier. It doesn't go up on them. What's the
point? Dear Mr. And Mrs. Adams, I'm sorry to report that your son Jason has been implicated
in another unusual incident. This is the third time. So there was a look. See, they left a thing.
Where? Where? I want to read it. It's just it says like, it's like, could you please
next time respectfully hand it to me? Thank you. It's a game about physics. There is no such thing
as handing it to you. There is. No, this is a previous. This has nothing to do with everyone
being dead. No, this is you don't write like a kindly worded letter because he murdered like
eight people. Will you just come back into the room with the big dinner on it? All right. Is
this done? Give it a look. This room? Yeah. Bloody here. Chairs on the floor. I'm trying to do it.
You asked. Make sure you make sure you're not tracking like I am. I'm not tracking.
Glass. Respectfully putting the glass here. Actually, we need to put the tableware out.
That needs to be glass. Put it all out. So I can come home, have a nice dinner with no family
remaining. I want every goddamn honey. Calm down. It's your favorite breakfast. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Please give me them. Why are you stacking chairs like this? Well, you just smashed the plate
because I had to have to be glass breaking. What?
I'm trying to set the table and you'll be a dick. How am I? You're breaking things. I'm
Can I ask you how the chair got on the table? Can I just ask you smashed it? And I thought we
were smashing. So I joined you thought we were smashing things you made. We were smashing things.
So I joined you. I'm a follower. You know this about me. You and stuff with this chair.
What? Yeah. Oh, yeah. That's right. Somebody gifted you a sub last time.
The table is clean so I can do the table is going to be set. I should just move the chairs out of
the way. This is the oh my this is the grossest thing I found the whole time we've been doing
this. Where are you? This is the grossest thing. Like an old food container. Yeah. It's like green
and red like the pigs that we're cleaning up after. Okay. Table looks like I'm setting it.
I have to be completely honest. Yeah. I don't know why I'm doing this. Like why are we still
doing this? Because this is the game. So all right. It's kind of a bad job setting the table.
Three people eat on plates over here and then only people only get to have drinks over this way.
You're gonna put the push the chairs in like what the I bet you you won't break a plate. Oh,
and the head of the table. The head of the table gets the light in their face. That's no that's
just so they can inspect the food. No, that's so like you know that they're the one hosting the
dinner. Like a spotlight. Me, me, me. Hello.
Dude, I'm getting achievements like crazy. All right. So we have let's take a little bit
of an indent area here. Okay. I thought this was blood. This car was designed in MS paint.
All right. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Right. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool.
Right. Hello. Well, here comes. Yeah. Hello. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool.
Is that because you want it to happen? I just was waiting for it to happen.
Do it. It's not funny. You do it. That's the thing. You've done it every time. Do it.
You're you're making me very uncomfortable. Do it. You do it every time. Do it. I'm just trying to
clean up. I don't think I can keep working under these conditions. Can I go home? One time he
doesn't use his like a fucking electro board to make like I don't feel well. We're almost done.
Are you going to check out that new game? Which new game? I don't know any of them. I've played
quite a few new games. Which one? I don't know. Do you have any new games you're going to check out?
Unreleased new games? No, not right now. Nothing new is coming out. There's a few things coming
out. There's always things coming out like every day. Um, I think super sexy made two is out on
steam for a few days already. What? What? The sequel. You're just trying to get yourself,
you know, ashes of remnant. Are you trying to like get your channel banned? No, that's a banned
video games. That's not streamable on Twitch. That's a banned stream game, isn't it? I don't
know. Don't they have like a banned no stream games? Probably. Nice. You did it. I didn't.
I didn't do that. You did it. I did it. You did it. I'm telling mommy. I'm telling mommy.
Get them all away. Wait a minute. We're doing this so stupidly. Put this in here.
You did it. You did it. Where's dad's flood light? I need it. I'm getting dad's floodlight for you.
I know you are vision impaired. I don't need it. I don't need it. I don't need it. I thought you
need it like a solar eclipse to be able to see anything. I don't need it. Okay. Clean.
Except for me. And there is a stick in here. Am I a vampire? Holy fuck. There's so many of these
here that I did not put here. That just surprised me how many you've put there. I thought it was
broken. How many of what? How many USB sticks? Oh no. I've been doing my job. Oh dude frying pan.
No, no. There was nothing wrong with that. Why'd you do that? I want a new one. Use this one.
Hold on. This one's good. Thank you. Now finish up. We're almost done with the house.
The house is almost completely good. Oh dude. Why did that? Why did that happen? Yeah. I wanted
to pick up the fucking torso that was buried at the bottom of the barrel. I didn't want to pick up
the barrel. I wanted to pick up the torso at the bottom. What is this? Make sure you hold shift
when you're walking too. To walk. I wouldn't want to drop anything. I wouldn't want to drop anything.
All the gold on the table. Gold on the table. You left some gold on the table. That's your joke.
That's not mine. If you want to make that, you mute me. Mute you and do that on your stream. Hello.
Oh cool. There it is. There it is. There it is. I watch any good TV lately. I thought that was a
soundboard thing. It was weird. Watch any good TV lately. It really was. It was like
abrupt and weird. Have I watched any good TV lately? What's the last TV that I watched?
I don't know. What's the last TV show that I actually watched?
I'm asking you. You should have that information. I don't know. I really don't know.
I don't know. Spider-Man? That's a movie. That's a movie. I'm not counting movies here.
I haven't really watched any TV. Outside is good. All right. We'll have to go through a little bit
and check out on it. What about the garage? The garage was good. Is it completely good?
I didn't detect any. It's the MS Paint car that I wish we could trash.
It looks like blood. No, that's Sting's car from WCW. Was his car MS Paint airbrushed and drawn on?
No. The car is awful. What is wrong with that car? What's the problem with that car? It's
really ugly, but it's not that big of a deal. It's ruining my immersion. We've got to get a
trash container here. Okay. I'm on it, boss. Let me get the gross light to see the fluorescent
light bulb so we can look at the ground and be like, oh, gross. The blue light behind you.
Where do you want this? In the living room. This is what happens when your landlord comes in and
is looking for piss. That's what he's looking for. What happened over here?
What? I'm just dealing with... Oh, there it is. Piss. Don't track. I don't track ever.
All right. Let's do this together. Why not? Two hands are better than one.
I've already put in like eight. Four hands are better than two, right? Thank you.
Let me get that for you. Put it down. All right,
to the first person I can chug one of these wins. Cool. I did it. Didn't you?
I love how much you fucking hated what I just did. No. You hated it. I respect the roleplay.
Here's a question. Stale joke.
What's your question? What's the worst character you can think of from TV or movie?
What would be your ideal worst character? Are we talking like things they did in the show
that were bad or... Like their personality, just like how bad of a... You don't care about,
they're just awful. You know, the worst character. I don't know. I can't think of
the character that I just hated. What do you got? I got nothing.
I was talking about it the other night with my significant other.
The worst character from any TV show that I've ever seen.
She hates the lawyer from Jessica Jones. Specific.
It's very specific. She said it was the worst character, so I was trying to come up with worse
ones. I forget what I came up with already. It was just last night and I have no intentions.
People saying Garfield. Garfield was a comic book before he was like a TV show,
and the TV show was good. Garfield and Friends. That was not a bad show.
You're smashing blood. What? You just destroyed that doorway.
From the 100. That's a good one. That's good. I don't know. I don't watch that much TV.
I don't have a base on anything.
The mood is very live. And all you have to say is...
Oh, I'm cool. That went the wrong way.
Come on. Come on, dude. Why can't I play that back to you?
Come on, dude. Come on. Because you don't have the thing.
You'd be more than welcome to do it if you had the thing.
What about the pumpkins out here? We should probably set those up.
Hello? I need one of these.
There's still lots of buckets out here that need to be disposed of.
Delete yourself.
At least it's good to know I have a future in being a janitor.
I'm stuck on this. What character is the worst character in any TV show?
Who the fuck is it? Name me a TV show that I've watched, that you know I've watched.
The only show that I know you've watched is Breaking Bad and Game of Thrones.
Oh. Ross from Friends.
What? I've never seen that.
I don't... Why? I thought people liked him.
Peggy from King of the Hill. That's disrespectful.
She is a loving, caring, family woman. She goes to great lengths to provide when Hank can't.
She makes a miraculous recovery from falling out of a fucking airplane.
And she's not good enough for you.
I mean, I like Peggy Hill.
How about The Vision? I hate The Vision.
Open this door. Open this door! What are you doing out there?
I'm fucking cleaning.
Who's closing doors?
What did you do with the USBs?
What USBs?
The USB drives I've been collecting. This whole time.
You were just out... Do you think I'm capable, like,
number one, physically, or number two, mentally, being able to move all those in less than 30 seconds?
Yes. You really think that?
Typically, you would be the one to be like,
no, you could never do that in that amount of time. You're just so slow.
You're very athletic when you want to be. You did a...
What's it called from the top rope?
What? A whirlwind or something?
A whirlwind?
I don't know. What's it called? Triple Lindy?
A triple... What? No, it's called a...
Hurricana?
Hurricanrana.
Hurricanrana. Yeah, he can do one of those.
Did you guys... You should have seen him at the trampoline park.
Oh, I was... I was good.
Dude, this six-year-old came up to him and was like,
can I help you out a bit? And he freaking hurricanrana'd him right off.
Bam!
You had to go home early.
Yeah, that was you in that scenario. I hurricanrana'd you.
He started talking shit and I just, like, jumped way high over your head and just, like,
boom! Landed right on your shoulders.
Twisted back and you flipped forward.
I remember specifically the whole time you were going,
I'm sorry! I'm wicked sorry! I'm sorry!
What was I sorry about?
The fact that you... What am I gonna do with this?
You, like, made fun of me. You said I was acting like a six-year-old.
No, I said you were... I said you were using wrestling moves on six-year-old.
Oh, all right. Well, let's go ahead and move on from that conversation.
I did rip my pants, actually.
Yeah, you did rip your pants. That's actually rude. That's true.
I'm... Your voice when you remembered.
He did. He did. I can turn this on.
No, he ripped his pants.
It's not about me. He ripped his pants.
He ripped his pants.
It was embarrassing.
Nope.
Okay, wait. For a second. For a second.
I thought I... I thought I threw away X.
And I was about to be like, oh, fuck.
Good thing I didn't throw away X.
Yeah.
They are shaped the same.
All right. So, how's the episode?
So, the vision.
The vision. No. Yeah. Okay. You think I do embarrassing things?
You not only have ripped your pants in front of me.
You've also shit your pants on spring.
So, I think I get like times one million points in the other direction.
I won that quick play match.
So...
It's like, honest to God, the most fucking disgusting, fucked up thing ever.
Ever.
It's, uh...
What am I doing?
Pretty low of you to judge another man's butthole.
What is this? A vacuum?
I'm sure yours has done some things it's not too proud of.
How do I turn on the vacuum?
Oh, yeah. Not talking about this anymore.
Oh, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
Jerry! Jerry, come out here.
Jerry, get out here.
Hello? Get out the front door.
What?
Get out the front door. Out the front door. Quick.
Why?
Because you're about to see something amazing.
Coming. Coming, honey.
I found the vacuum that plays music.
Look, I'm jumping. I'm jumping.
Can you see me?
Look at your map.
Come here.
Okay, now you do the work while I'll be the support.
I'm your healer.
I'm leaving if you don't get rid of that.
I was at a vacuum.
Wait, now we can't get it.
I just realized what I'm doing.
That can never turn off.
I threw some pumpkins out there earlier.
You're gonna get us in trouble.
Don't do that.
You think you can get one over the fence?
I think so.
We both get one throw.
One throw to get it over the fence?
Yeah, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Into like, crabby Carol's yard?
Yeah, fuck Carol.
Holy shit.
I just, that was like, I, there's nobody's gonna,
I just went to the driving range.
No, I'm sorry.
I went to the driving range.
Hey, you want to take this and like throw it out?
Dude, no, it was over the roof.
Oh, Nuddy, no, no, no, no, no, no, Nuddy.
Close, I'm going over Carol's roof.
Check this shit out.
Where'd it go?
You got it over the house.
Did it go so far over the house?
It didn't go straight.
It went off to the right.
You got in my way.
I don't know where mine went.
I'm gonna assume I hit the moon.
Okay, why do I still hear the music?
Why is music coming from the house?
Oh, there's a new one over here.
Oh, get rid of this fucking thing.
Does it spawn?
Now I miss the music.
All right, back upstairs.
God damn it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Take this trash out.
Take the trash outside.
When do I get my obligated?
I'm like, ugh.
Just running and heaving the trash into me.
What am I doing with my trash?
Oh my god, this music is like all in my left ear.
Where are you?
Are you up in the?
I'm in the backyard.
What are we doing?
All right, go upstairs.
We need to get in a bucket.
Is that okay?
That's fine.
Where are you?
I'm coming upstairs right now.
This music is so loud and annoying.
Why did you have to do this?
The fuck?
Turn your music down.
It's really not that hard to turn your music down.
No, it's the principle.
Where is this coming from?
It's like in the wall.
Don't get that trash out of here.
Are you going to get in Krabby Carroll's front yard?
We're never going to complete the level now.
I hope you're happy.
No music.
Quiet.
I want complete silence.
All right, so let's take this party upstairs.
I'm going to bring a couple of buckets.
Oh yeah?
What else are you going to do?
Oh, relax.
Relax.
How many buckets?
Two.
Oh yeah?
Do you have one of those trash compactors up there?
Yeah.
There really is just party music playing.
Why is it in the house?
I turned my music off.
I don't know.
It was like in a wall and I couldn't find it.
All right, I got two buckets of water.
Which room are you in?
I'm in the hallway.
Okay.
Please be careful.
Are you trying to do something dumb?
Because we need these buckets.
And you just came over and whacked me.
Won't happen again boss.
It's getting louder.
Yeah.
All right, so which room are we doing?
Excuse me.
This one?
This room is nearly done.
That wasn't this competition room?
It might have been.
No, you did the other one.
This closet is bad.
Ah, fuck dude.
What's up?
Are you good?
What happened?
I'm good, I'm good.
This one, I can take this one.
It's just blood, a little bit of guts.
I guess.
There's a note too.
Where does this lead?
This window.
We're good.
I'm good.
My room's clean.
I beat you.
Which window is near a thing?
No, that's it.
I think I can get it.
Give me a hand here.
No.
I have my own duties.
Got it.
Come on.
Do it.
Do what?
I'm in trouble.
Coming, coming.
I'm going to come and kill you out.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on.
Did you do that?
Do what?
Weirdly enough, the whole game's procedurally generated.
So we kind of have an issue out here.
I did not do that.
I think it's procedurally generated.
Hold on, I got this.
Did you just kill me?
You just killed me.
How did you kill me?
What?
I don't know.
You just goomba stomped me and broke my neck.
I got her off the roof.
Why did I die?
No time for your jokes.
Why is this about number four?
There is no joke there.
You actually jumped on my head and broke my neck.
That's not funny.
Please don't imply that I would be involved in any tomfoolery.
All right, you knocked her off?
My mom's watching, okay?
Where is she?
What?
Did you knock her off the front or back?
My mom?
I threw her off the front.
Stop tracking it.
You're tracking it.
I don't see her.
Where did you knock her off?
She was in the bushes.
I got her.
There's still a spot of blood up there that I can't get.
Where did this guy come from?
Thanks for nothing, game.
Thanks for nothing.
When do we get guns?
You don't get guns.
Not every game has to have a gun.
Not every game has to have like,
get on the cart and shoot the gun.
I don't know.
I'm a back-in-the-day gamer.
A purist, if you will.
Why not?
All right, we are getting very, very close, my friend.
Take my buckets!
Hello?
I thought that was you, but it was me.
I thought you were doing a, quote,
German impression.
Hello?
No.
Kid thinks he's funny.
Hello?
Fucking kid thinks he's funny.
That's, uh...
Okay.
When you're walking down the street,
and 50% of the people are germos.
Hello?
No, I didn't see it.
Where else would I have come up with this if I didn't, like...
That's a great video.
You think I have an imagination?
Something in the attic.
Is it creepy?
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Oh, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Come here, come here, come here.
I'm gonna...
Ow, my head.
Come here.
Where are you?
This is authentic.
Like, four people died on this.
It's gonna work.
Oh, shit.
All right, bring it to the bathroom.
Oh.
Oh, it's a weed.
I thought we were gonna try and go down the stairs on it.
No.
All right.
So...
Authentic people have died on this.
Vooja.
All right, you ready?
Put your hand on my...
Put your hand on my hand.
Thanks.
Okay.
No, wait, we need to...
I need to...
Ghost!
So...
Ghost, can you hear us?
When the tip is on that.
Hello?
All right, you ready?
Take...
Grab my hand.
Tight.
Tighter.
I'm tight.
Ow!
Fucking God!
Not that hard.
What's wrong with you?
Tighter.
Dear...
Ow.
Dear spirits of the realm of...
Let's turn the light off.
Can we?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, that door closed by itself!
Okay, hand back on.
Okay.
Spirits of the otherworldly creatures,
give us a sign.
Are you here in the room with us right now?
No, I was talking about the...
Yeah, I was talking about the ear.
You fuck...
Stop fucking up the spirit mojo here.
Come on.
Okay.
Are you in the room right now?
You fucking guys are so bad at this game.
Like, I'm missing dinner now.
Are you doing this?
Yeah, what?
No.
Are you moving this?
I'm not doing this.
Are you doing this?
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
I'm moving it.
No, wait.
No, I'm not.
That's not how this works.
Put your hand back on.
Ow.
You just admitted you were moving it.
No, just put it down.
Put it down.
No.
Okay.
Okay, it's down.
It's down.
Hold on.
Wait, we gotta get some more blood on this.
Wait.
Just keep it there right there.
Get in the shower with me.
Wait a minute.
Oh shit.
Okay.
I thought it was done.
It's too dark.
It's too dark in the house.
I can't see.
I don't know.
My camera's turned way fucking down.
All right.
Where's the bathroom?
I need blood.
Give me blood.
Why do you need blood?
Because I need to...
All right.
It's bloodied up.
Good.
Set it down.
All right.
Let's close the fucking door.
Everyone, put your seat belts back on.
All right.
Put your seat belts on.
Put your hand...
Put your hand on my hand.
What?
Ow.
Why was my face?
Put your hand on my fucking hand.
No.
I was doing the clapper for the video.
Okay.
Grasp.
Yo.
What's going on, everybody?
Just being German here.
Hey.
What's going on, everybody?
We're here.
We're doing the Ouija board.
Are you ready?
Spirits, are you in the room with us?
Dude, this is fucking freaky.
Is this you doing that?
I don't think it's me doing it.
This is on yes.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
Don't touch it.
I'm not touching it.
I'm not.
What the fuck is happening then?
Okay.
Spirits, are you moving around the object?
I'm not touching it, dude.
I'm not touching this.
I never touched it.
G.
What's G?
Do you have a family member named G?
Oh my god.
It's for you.
It's Germa.
No, that's a J.
Do you have anybody named G?
Oh my god.
It's Gerald.
Are you doing this?
I'm serious.
Are you moving this?
A.
G.
Gary.
Do you know anybody in the family named Gary?
No.
Spirit, are you Gary?
No, not Gary.
Spirit, spell the rest of your name.
M.
Gam.
Game.
Game, game, game, game, game, game, game.
Put it down.
Are you touching this?
No.
Fuck.
It's on the S.
Fuck, dude.
Gam.
Gam's.
Game sucks.
I'm not moving this.
Gam6.
Gam, I think that's the demon's name.
Oh, terrible demon of ours.
What do you want us to do?
Oh, okay, sorry.
Gam6.
I forget where the letter is, Gam6.
I don't remember where the letter is in the alphabet because we're upside down.
Gam6, please move me in the right direction if you could, please.
Gam6.
Oh.
Whoa.
Oh, fuck.
He just made me move over here.
Q.
Are you moving this?
You?
Can we?
There's an I.
I think that's an I.
Quit.
Are you moving this?
I'm not moving it.
Are you doing this?
Is that you moving this?
Dude, stop me moving this.
Dude, are you moving this, dude?
It's not me.
Are you moving that?
Oh my god, is this the demon lord?
Game sucks.
Dude, are you picking this up?
Did you move this?
Dude, I'm walking down the stairs.
Are you walking down the stairs right now?
I'm not.
Am I?
Good job.
Oh, shit.
I even said that you hit the first funny part.
Dude.
Are you moving this?
I gotta turn my game back up.
What was it at one?
Dude, are you moving this?
I'm not moving this.
Are you sure?
I- something's fucking weird.
I'm not moving this.
All right, get- move.
I'm not moving.
Let's go clean the house.
Why did you have to bring that up here?
So that you can see what you're doing.
Thanks.
That actually is way too bright though, for real.
Like, get rid of this.
This isn't as good as Seinfeld.
Where did that go?
How are you still holding that?
You can't take it out of my hand.
My hands are too strong.
I have pure titanium grip strength.
Okay.
The bathroom's clean.
No one's ever taken anything from my hand.
My hands are massive.
They have like hairy knuckles.
Veins popping out.
Gross.
Yeah, but you think it'd be nice to be held by these hands.
I got veinier hands than you, I guarantee it.
I'm vascular.
I have the veiniest hands in the world.
I swear to God.
Let's compare.
Come here.
Show me your hands.
Honestly, if- if-
You would think that I was an old lady if you saw my hands up close.
That's not vascular.
That's wrinkly.
No, no, no, no, no.
You don't understand.
Like, my veins pop the fuck out of my hands.
Okay, you win.
We should compare hands.
I mean, it's the music that's doing it to me too.
Show hands.
Are you- are you on camera?
Are you like decent right now?
My camera isn't plugged in.
Well, they're not that vein-y right now.
They kind of are.
Should I prove it?
Prove it.
Prove how veinier your hand is.
I'm opening the stream.
I need to see.
Prove it.
Let's get vein in that.
Yeah, I know.
I'm wearing the same shirt as I was yesterday.
Deal with it.
It's 100 degrees.
Wait.
It being 100 degrees is why you're wearing the same shirt.
Look at that.
Look at those.
Are you shitting me, dude?
Can I get a light on that?
Get a light on it.
No, you're not- hold on.
You turn the light.
You turn- you got the wrong side.
No, no, no.
That's towards you.
Towards me.
Not in my fucking eyes.
Okay.
Can you see?
Yeah.
No, my hands are way bigger.
Like hairier.
More defined.
And more vascular.
And thank you.
Put the fucking light down, dick.
Like you still- it's right in my face.
Never letting go of it.
Asshole.
You can't get inside of my hands.
Not with trickery.
Not with force.
Ooh, that was an explosion.
Oh, is that my switch that went all the way down?
No, it's not.
Thank God.
I was supposed to be fucking sad.
Look at those hands.
Wait a second.
Are you moving this?
I'm not moving that.
What about now?
Are you moving this?
No, you are.
Can you get me- can you get me out of the bathroom, please?
I'm not moving that.
I'm not moving it.
Get me out of the bathroom.
I get you to wipe your ass.
We're almost done.
We're at the finish line and we're wiping each other's asses.
All right.
I've reached the level of like we're so close to being done
that it- we can't finish because we're so close.
That's why we can't finish.
What is this?
We still have that whole other house.
Oh, scary.
Yeah, there's a home of the house here, right?
Is that a book?
All right, I cleaned up the book.
All right, this is the house.
Let's do a walkthrough.
Come with me.
Bring the ghost light.
Why do I have to come like-
Because we're having a fun time in the game together
and you need to find-
I'm having so much fun.
You fucking guys are so bad at this game.
Well, hey, I'm missing dinner now.
Calm down.
Okay, walkthrough.
There's a USB here.
Yeah, pick it up.
There's a couple of these-
There's a couple of mobile toilets in the bathroom.
Let me get these mobile toilets out.
Looks good.
I'll put this pumpkin here.
Ah, excuse me.
Not done.
I never saw the attic
because you had to do the Ouija board thing.
What Ouija board thing?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
And you brought trash up here, too.
All right, what would it take me to drink trash juice?
Wait, what?
You're not even going to give me a response to that one.
Come here.
Well, I'm paying attention.
Sorry.
Okay, the attic.
Did you see the attic?
It's pretty crazy.
Why did you bring this upstairs?
Getting it out of such a pain in the ass.
You brought the trash all the way up the stairs.
Jarma.
Yes.
There's been a murder.
What murder?
Where?
I don't think this house is as normal as it seems.
There's been a murder.
No shit.
There's like 30 dead people here.
What are you trying-
What's going on here?
You're just putting splats all over the ceiling and the wall and stuff.
Hello?
Did you hear that?
I think maybe he's still alive.
I think that's coming from the attic.
Hello?
It's coming from the attic.
Okay.
Where's the attic?
It's in here.
This is the attic up here?
No, wrong room.
It's coming from over there.
Hello?
Over here?
I hear it.
Up here.
Is it-
Get a camera.
Get a camera up.
What's in here?
This is fucked up though.
Anybody here?
All right.
All right, Dave.
No more fucking around.
Like you're messing around with me.
Okay, real funny, Dave.
Like, haha, got me.
Hello?
No, you are.
Well, I'm gonna get rid of this.
I can't.
I need a bucket.
Hey, Dave.
Yo, it's time to go, man.
What are you doing?
Look at this mess.
You know, you're just adding more time than we have to be in this map.
We have to.
Not let-
You think that we're gonna leave without cleaning this up?
I think I'm fully capable of it.
No!
I think I could just-
No, no, no.
You can't.
Because that-
I'm in your game.
No, no, no, no.
It was done.
And we could have clocked out.
I mean, neither of us cleaned it.
All right, well, just at least get the USBs.
Where'd you put them?
I'm not playing games with you.
Where are-
Where are the USBs?
I'm not playing games with you.
Turn in the USBs.
I think I saw them over here.
At least turn those in for me.
Come out the house.
Where are they?
Where are you?
I'm not playing games with you.
Huh? Hello?
Okay, man.
I'm gonna just hang out for a bit and maybe I'll talk to you some other time, man.
But I've gotta-
I've gotta go.
The fuck?
No, you are.
Hey, rookie!
Rookie, what?
I thought you were gonna keep doing the demon thing.
Nice fucking RP ruin.
What?
I wasn't doing a demon thing.
Nice ruined RP.
I wasn't doing a demon thing, Jerma.
It's coming from inside the house.
Is it coming from the toilet?
Is he in the bath?
Is he currently taking a bath?
All right.
Can I get in the bathroom, please?
Excuse me.
Game six. Oh, fuck.
What do you want from us?
I want my house clean and you're gonna fuck it up.
I mean, we're just trying to entertain some people and make them laugh.
You were hired for a job and you're goofing around.
I mean-
I'd have an ear to take this up with you.
No, no, no, don't, don't, don't.
I don't want to get-
When was this last time you wanted to be written up?
You've been written up before, huh?
Once, but it was for something unrelated.
But you don't have to do that.
When do you want it done?
I'll get my colleague on it.
We'll make sure they get it cleaned.
Twenty more minutes.
Twenty minutes?
Or I will call your manager.
No, that's uh-
Twenty minutes, that's enough time.
No, that's more than enough time.
Do it.
No, we'll get it on top of that.
We'll do it in twenty minutes.
Be gone, you little piece of-
Shitty-
Okay.
Yes, we will.
We will get it done in twenty minutes.
I'll try.
Hey, Jerma!
Hey, I need you up here.
I need you to get the job done quicker than we thought originally.
Okay.
Okay, well I'm fired up.
I'm ready to go.
I'm so excited to clean.
Yeah, no, for real though.
We have to get this done quickly
because our boss was going to write us up if we didn't.
Oh, what's-
Like, I quit.
What?
I quit.
What do you mean you quit?
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to get written up by that shithead.
No, dude.
That balding middle-aged piece of trash.
I don't think you understand.
Can't even please his wife.
I'm sorry that you don't get this.
Yeah, I saw his computer open the other day.
Like, the weirdest Craigslist wanted ads I've ever read.
Let's just turn on my stream.
Turn on my stream.
Turn on my stream for a second.
Important.
Turn on my stream.
Watch my stream.
We have to get this done in twenty minutes.
You know what I mean?
Like, we have to-
Like, uh-
Us.
Ghosts.
Um, I can't-
Twenty minutes, man.
Are you watching?
Twenty minutes.
Twenty minutes or-
I don't-
Like, I'm watching you.
Twenty minutes, we're gonna eat the farm.
We're gonna eat the farm in twenty minutes, dude.
Fucking just start cleaning now.
You're just the American psycho.
He's gonna wipe your neck.
I didn't do the one finger.
I did, like, the whole palm.
He's gonna wipe your neck.
Oh, no, okay.
Hey, be careful.
He's gonna-
He's gonna go like-
You gotta get, like, some fucking fry oil on your chin.
He's gonna wipe off.
I'm okay with that.
Okay, so, uh, how do you wanna-
How do you wanna do this?
Dude, I don't-
I don't know.
What is left to do?
It's the attic.
The attic and then-
The USBs.
Give me the USBs.
Stop with this USB.
I quit.
I will quit.
Don't quit.
Get out here and come out the door with a pumpkin's fall.
I will destroy you.
Get out here.
Do one more USB joke and I am-
Get out of the-
Spreading my blood everywhere.
Get out of the house right now.
I'm out.
No, I mean, like, the other side.
The side with the pumpkin's fall.
Here, Mo.
Listen to me.
Listen to me real good.
I'm gonna cut myself open and just crawl along the floor.
Real sicko shit.
All right.
How about this?
I have-
I have a job for you, okay?
In this-
In this house somewhere.
Somewhere.
There's a fucking treasure.
And if you can find this tre-
If you can find the treasure in-
20 minutes.
Then-
No, less than that.
Five minutes.
Then I will give you-
I will give you a hundred dollars.
What is the treasure?
The USBs that I hid.
Okay.
Good luck.
And I have five minutes.
You have five minutes to make a hundred bucks.
Okay, chat.
Where do you put them?
You can't do that.
That doesn't work.
Okay, I can't do that.
Close your chat right now.
Okay.
That's bullshit.
You know, that's unbelievable.
He's cheating.
You have five minutes.
I'm counting right now.
I'm looking at the clock.
Found it.
That's one USB that's outside.
Not the, like, 40 that I hid.
Hundred bucks, please!
No, I said find the USBs that I hid.
Not find a USB on the clock.
You hid it right here.
No, this is not like an Easter egg hunt for four-year-olds.
This is-
No, it's going to be harder than that.
They don't-
It wasn't harder than that, though.
It was right here.
You thought, like, I would see it in the grass because it's green.
You only have three more minutes left.
That is not how quickly time goes by.
Yes, it is.
Nothing in there.
Fuck!
You'll never catch that money!
What are you going to spend your hundred dollars on?
You read that.
All right, well, can you pick those up?
Hello?
Can I-
I don't know where they go.
They were in one central location.
Why is there another body in here?
I don't understand how this is-
Was he in the attic?
Hey, Dharma.
Yes?
How about I hide the USBs and then you have to go find them?
Okay, that sounds fun.
And then it'll be even.
Sure.
Okay.
I want to clarify.
To find them, you, like, need to, like, pick them up and hold them
and prove to me that you found them.
Yeah, where's- you can just- I have a stream going right now.
Yeah, you do.
You're gonna have to prove to your stream by holding one of the USBs
that you find the USBs that I hid.
Okay.
Just one.
Or do I have to find them all?
You have to find- like, I'm hiding the stash.
Okay.
So as long as I find the stash that's in quotes.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you can prove that you found it by, like,
picking it up and showing I have found it.
Okay.
Yeah, whatever.
Like, I'm going to hide or something?
Do I want me to go-
You need to- you know what?
Oh, it's clown on the town list.
You turn around and count to 15.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Yep.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
Thirteen.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
And?
Good luck.
You didn't even walk over here.
I hid them.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, no.
Nobody move.
Nobody fucking move.
Give me one!
Is it in there?
It's the stash!
That's the stash!
Come on!
Some one of them had to have fallen off.
No!
At least one didn't make the journey.
Oh, god damn it.
That was so sad.
What just happened?
Okay, so-
Okay.
So that's 200.
There was no monetary bet there.
As reliable as ever.
Good old Jerma.
Hey, Star.
Yeah?
Found something.
That's not a stash.
There are three here.
There are three that fell from some portal and made their way in here.
That's a stash.
I just put them here so that you wouldn't destroy them.
Hey, come over this way.
Hey, come over here.
That is classified as a stash.
Over here.
There's also a stash, but it was the stash.
Jerma.
Why am I doing that?
We need those.
All right.
I swear to god.
Okay, so, um, let's finish up.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You've ruined everything.
You've put-
You won't stare at this cat.
This is like a fucking haunted image.
If you stare at this picture for more than a minute,
you get haunted for the rest of your life.
You won't do it.
Holy shit.
You're just disrespecting the fucking cat.
Do it!
No, no, do it!
If you stare at a black cat for more than a minute,
you get bad luck for like five years.
Will you do it?
Do it.
Candyman.
Don't do that.
I don't want you to do that.
I'm not in the same room, therefore I'm not in the same zone.
Whatever you do, I'm not in that room.
But I'm looking at it too.
I can't believe you actually looked at it.
That was a mistake.
Shouldn't have done that.
Are we still on call?
No, he didn't do the thing.
He just leaves, right?
Did he leave?
He left.
No, he didn't.
He's here.
You can't fool me.
You're here.
You're there.
I know you're there.
He's gone.
He ended his stream too.
God damn it.
I gave him an out and he took the opportunity.
He was looking for an opportunity and he found it.
I should have told him, like, look at it for four hours.
Well, that was fun.
That was Star on Twitch.
He's still streaming.
What is he doing right now?
He's offline.
All right, well, it's supposed to be co-op day.
I'm like Matrix dodging bullets here.
Internet sucks.
Executive assault 2 doesn't work.
Star looked at the cat picture for more than a minute.
That's three strikes.
Time to do tier lists.
All right, let me just take a break.
I've been live for about four hours now.
Maybe more than that.
The stream turned off like three times.
I have no idea how long I've been live for.
It's been probably four or five hours or so.
But we'll come back.
We'll do the tier lists.
And I'll see you in not even three.
No, the stream turned off like three times.
How long has it actually been?
Let me see.
25 minutes.
No, let's see.
How many VODs are there in this stream?
Oh, yeah.
This has been much longer than that.
No, this is 20.
One hour 30.
Oh, yeah.
No, this is four hours.
One hour 30.
Four hours.
Star just hosted me.
Thank you for that, Star.
Oops.
Oops, oops, whoops.
Whoops.
How do I actually turn this up?
Why is this playing?
I don't have one window.
I actually don't have one window.
How do I actually turn this up?
Why is this playing?
I don't have one window.
I actually don't have one window.
How do I actually turn this up?
I'm going to turn, I'm going to turn my light.
I'm going to turn my capture screen on.
Oh, there it is.
Okay, I was on a different, I was on my videos tab
and it was still playing the stream
even though I was on the videos tab somehow.
Okay, I'll be right back.
I'm going to just go to the bathroom
and we'll do some stuff.
See you soon.