You didn't get scammed. I'm here. You didn't get scammed.
Uh oh. Uh oh. No, no, no, no, no. Don't tell me I have to change servers again. Don't even do that.
I just turned it on. Don't even tell me I have to change servers.
Come on, man. We'll see.
You know, every couple weeks I have to change my Twitch server.
Because... I don't know.
It doesn't like where my connection's coming from, apparently.
But hello! How are you? Good to see you.
What's up? I'm doing good.
Talk about baseball? I just wait. We're gonna get to that.
Let me wait to disappoint everybody.
Give me a few minutes to come and sit down.
Eating any olives today?
Uh, yeah, of course. I eat olives every day.
Talk about your Roblox server.
I don't have one of those.
Make me a cake.
That's the point. That's what we're gonna try to do today.
Don't, no, don't leak!
Don't leak.
People are already leaking the bad news for baseball.
Don't leak. Don't leak.
All right. Hey, no, it's not time yet.
I had a wild six or seven days.
Did the beerio cart thing with Ludwig, which was ton of fun.
I didn't think I could drink that many beers. I really didn't.
You guys didn't really get to see that much of the beer drinking, but holy shit.
I've never drank beer faster in my whole life.
We almost won, too.
When we got to Rainbow Road, it's just like, I can't do Rainbow Road.
I couldn't. I can't do Rainbow Road sober.
I can't do Rainbow Road at all.
I would skip that level.
In fact, I I would stop playing Mario Kart at that kind of what is it like the Star Cup, whatever?
No, I don't feel like it. I don't want to play that.
I don't want to play that part of the game, but that was fun.
Then this whole Mr. Beast versus Ninja Tournament.
That was crazy, too.
Got to hang out with a lot of people.
There's a lot of fun.
I wish I wish more people would come to Vegas.
It's so much fun when people come here.
Rainbow Road is easy.
What did you say?
I want to see this person said Rainbow Road is easy.
You just need skills.
No, it's not easy.
You lost 10,000 at 10K.
No, I did not.
I did not lose 10K at the casino.
Which Rainbow Road?
Aren't they all the same exact course from when it first showed up in Super Nintendo?
It's the same one, right?
Did they change it?
Why would they change it?
They don't even need to change it.
It was 20K.
Where are you getting this idea that I lost $20,000 at a casino?
Who told you this?
It was 30K.
Well, the number keeps going up.
So whatever.
We know.
No, it was awesome.
It was really fun.
Anytime a bunch of streamers come into Vegas and I ever have an opportunity, I'm just like, oh, come to Vegas.
All right.
You'll be in Vegas.
Really?
What are you up to?
Hey, what are you doing?
It's always a lot of fun.
Why do you live in Vegas?
Because, you know what I mean?
That's it.
Okay, I'll do it slow this time.
Why do you live in Vegas?
Because.
Come on.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean?
That's why.
Oh, it's close to LA, but you don't have to pay LA prices.
It's only 45 minutes in a plane to LA.
The real estate market out here is way, way cheaper than some of these other places.
There's no state tax in Nevada.
Isn't that interesting?
There's also lots of entertainment.
There's so much stuff to do here.
24.
Do you have to do this whole thing every few months?
Do I have to do this every few months?
Do you have a yak trick?
Taxes?
I didn't move here just because of the tax, the state taxes not being a thing.
I mean, it was, I mean, you know, all right, but that's not why I'm here.
Again, it's close to LA.
I don't have to pay LA prices.
45 minutes, wheels up, wheels down.
The real estate market is that I'm not doing this anymore.
What happened to the mystery game?
Every single stream is a mystery game.
I figured out what I'm going to do 10 minutes before the stream turns on.
Every day is a mystery.
Besides the event streams like baseball, by the way, talk about with baseball.
So I got enough people here.
Let's do it.
So baseball, baseball is supposed to be on the 24th of July.
I told you the last time I streamed, I kind of had it was kind of a sad moment.
I said, we're trying really hard to get stuff to work.
We've had some venue problems.
And I was given the opportunity to either do it in a different place that would kind of suck.
It's not what I want or push it to August and do it where I want to do it and how I want to do it.
So I said, OK, this do you delay another few weeks, another month or so, right?
And do what I actually want to do or keep the same date and do it in a different venue, potentially in a scenario that I didn't want to do it in.
And of course, I'm going to pick the one that I want to do.
So we're going to do it in August.
Thankfully, it does not have to be in October or November or something.
So we're good.
And also, here's another good thing about this.
There is a couple of things that I may have wanted to do that I didn't have enough time to prepare for it if it was in a week that now I can I can add into the show.
So it's going to be a better show now overall because there's a couple of things I get to put in it now that I may have had to cut for time.
So I hope I don't sound like a broken record here.
But August 19th is the new date for the baseball show.
Now, I'm going to tell you right now, I am 90 percent confident in that day.
I don't think it's possible at this point for it to be not that day.
If it's not that day, then I'm doing it in my backyard.
You know what I mean?
Like, I'll do it.
I'll do it in fucking in a backyard, right?
Only 90 percent.
This stream is going to happen before the summer ends.
OK, that's what I can 100 percent guarantee to you.
Delay, delay, delays, delays, delays, delays.
I know.
But here's the thing.
If I don't delay the show, think about it.
If the show were to be next week and it's I mean, look, it's going to be good.
I am so excited to do this.
I've been looking forward to this for like two years.
It's going to be fun, regardless of where it is or how the things that I want go.
Right.
But why not do the thing you wanted to do, the thing that you've been planning to do,
the thing that I've had written down on a piece of paper?
Well, that makes it sound like it's on the back of a fucking napkin.
The thing that I have spent.
Yeah, I wrote down two sentences.
No, the thing that I've had sitting in various documents over the last few years.
Shit that I really want to do and I'm going to do the thing I want to do.
And that's all there is to it.
20, 22, not 20. No, not 20, 23.
We're talking about our grotto beast NFTs.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, stop.
Stop asking.
No, no, they're not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Clip any of those.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Any one of those will do.
Clip any one of those.
They're physical.
Do we get two raids right at the beginning?
Wait one?
Kit Boga just came in with a raid.
What's up, Kit?
Hope you had a good stream.
Kit Boga, thanks.
Welcome guys.
Hope you had a good stream.
I'm starting pretty early today, huh?
Hey, guess what? Starting early tomorrow, too.
Are you ready for this? EU? All the EU people here?
Let me tell you something. Tomorrow. You ready?
Tomorrow's stream is going to be at 11 a.m. Pacific.
Do you understand? 11 o'clock in the morning. Pacific.
I love EU. 11 a.m. Pacific. I love EU.
Usually once, once a year.
No, but thanks, Kit. Also, uh, Sagey.
Sagey with a raid, too.
Welcome everybody from Sagey's channel.
Hope I'm saying that right.
Thanks for the raid.
And yeah, Kitboga.
Fuck yeah.
I feel like it's been a month since I streamed.
It's only been a week.
But why am I streaming at 11 o'clock in the morning tomorrow?
There's a sponsor stream tomorrow.
Oh, okay.
What is it?
Tomorrow, I'm going to be playing
a power washer simulator.
That's right.
Hell yeah.
Let's go.
I love that fucking game.
Sponsored by water.
That's not going to be the only thing we do tomorrow.
We'll play another game or two as well.
But starting at 11 o'clock in the morning.
You should get sponsored by sick.
What people I don't know what it is recently the last month
or two.
I was what's the cigarette thing?
Is that the thing I'm missing somehow?
All right, let's go.
Today, we're going to play Bakery Simulator.
Bakery Simulator.
This feels is this made by the same people that did
cooking simulator?
It's the same people.
You're going to do a raid song that guys.
It's not 2018.
We don't do raid songs anymore.
Is it by the same people?
I think you can drive around from the trailer.
It looks like there's a car in this game.
So it gets an automatic a start today.
And let's go is ready.
Why is it asking me if I want my my Nintendo Switch one?
Okay.
Hi.
How you doing?
I know you cam socks.
You cam is blurry Ralph.
Oh, whatever.
All right.
So should I do the tutorial?
Should I figure out doing how to play this already?
I'm just gonna do it.
You're all orange.
Do you look like an orange?
I don't I don't care.
Everything is in PST.
That's right.
I'm in PST.
I also figured out to I don't know what it is about this
camera, but I looked at the images from the last stream
to this makes my head go like this.
It makes my forehead and head look way taller and bigger.
I don't know why it's doing that.
What lens does that?
Do you see what I mean?
I have this big forehead with this camera.
I don't look like this.
Oh, I was off the loading time.
All right.
Welcome to your bakery.
Your biggest dream came true.
You opened your very own bakery and you're ready to flood
the city with fresh pastries.
However, it's just the beginning a lot of hard work ahead
of you build reputation gain experience and become successful
in the world of baking.
There's a lot of responsibilities, but don't this is a guitar
is kind of I don't know something about it.
There's a lot of responsibilities, but don't worry.
You'll make it after all.
This is all you've dreamed of.
Your first order is waiting for you.
This is just bad Ratatouille.
You have not played it.
You don't know that.
Okay, WASD.
That's got to change for sure.
Is this a piano or is this a guitar?
Is it no way this is this is the guitar setting on the piano.
No, this inputs too high.
That's the lowest I can do.
Please tell me it's all right.
Right.
That's better.
All right.
Go to the ordering board and press left mouse on the folder.
Ordering board left mouse folder.
There it is.
Got it.
Oh, five minute bakery three breakfast bun at the road.
Okay.
I don't know why I thought that was like three breakfast
bun road because I saw this whoops.
Okay, this is how you're going to start your work from now on.
Okay, so it's take it takes five minutes on the left is a
list of shops with current orders.
Now only one order is available.
Okay, but later in the game, you'll be able to pick more
than one request from a much longer list.
All right.
That's a map with marked shops based on it.
You can check the location of orders.
You can decide what part of the city you want to make a
delivery to.
All right.
So yeah, you drive around in this game.
Are you wearing a wig?
You'll make it up if I say no anyways.
All right, pick the available order and press confirm.
So this one here after selecting order will appear the ordering
board pressed on the board.
All right.
So this is the order three breakfast buns, but before you
move further, let me teach you about the recipe book to open
the okay press tab.
Is this by the house flipper people?
This menu looks very similar.
Okay, so where's the recipe book wig select the recipe book
now here are all the recipes that you already know right now.
It's not that much but don't worry with every new level.
You'll learn new ones bookmarks on the side make navigation
easier.
Where's my there is that's looks like a lot of information.
That's a lot of info.
That's a ton of steps.
Okay, this is gonna I don't want to this.
I don't want to do this.
Each recipe page contains information about the steps
required to prepare the order as well as ingredients mixing
time ingredients and baking time.
You can stop tracking it.
I was like a quest log.
All right, you should recreate this on stream.
No, I don't like the smell of eggs.
I like the way I like the way eggs taste.
I don't like the smell of raw eggs after you crack a raw egg
and if it just sits out there for more than more than one
to two minutes.
I hate that smell of raw egg.
That is not like gone away from me.
There's no eggs in this.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about though?
I don't like baking because it is a flower and eggs.
It has this weird off-putting kind of essence to it.
I really don't like it.
It's weird.
You know, some of you guys get it.
You don't smell the eggs.
No, you don't.
I'm not smelling them.
All right, I'm trying to play.
Okay, you can choose the number of products to bake by.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, use the arrows.
The recipe will adjust accordingly.
Oh, okay.
Cool checklist is visible on the right.
So this is how to make the breakfast buns follow the recipe
and complete it perfectly cooking is not a science man.
Come on six ounces of wheat flour.
I could do five 2.4 fluid ounces of water.
You could do two milk.
Just don't even put it in because milk is gross yeast
extra yeast.
I want one ounce of yeast and then what?
By the way, don't do that you like milk and flour is incredibly
important in all these recipes.
So don't be an idiot.
All right, let's do some baking bowl.
This bowl is the average and small but don't worry during
the game.
You'll be able to unlock bigger and more professional bowls.
Okay, that's what I do in the kitchen.
I'm here for like I'm like the comic relief.
All right, so now what oh time to collect the needed ingredients
go to the ingredients rack.
Let's go.
So I need wheat flour something on fire.
Oh, I don't like that.
Is that what it is?
I feel like that's dangerous.
What if you walk by and you like get your your pant leg catches
on fire.
This is not controlled enough for me.
All right, ingredients rack.
Where's that over here in the bottom left corner of the screen?
You can find the scoops for now.
You just need to a one gram scoop.
Click the ingredients by clicking with my scoop bottom left
of the screen.
You guys see any scoops every time you're using the scoop or
pressing and holding left mouse the spoon will refill itself
one by one.
All right.
So how much do I need?
This is this is butter pure creamy butter.
Is this even in the recipe?
What do I need?
Where's my scoops?
Pick up the bowl.
Oh, that looks to be about one cup.
Let it go and a quarter of it is stuck to my sweaty hand.
I just have to like shake like this.
All right.
So now we go water.
No wheat flour.
Where's that?
Where's a flour?
Okay, wheat flour scoop it out.
There's no butter in this recipe.
Do you see butter?
What there's no butter in this recipe.
Okay.
Oopsie.
Look at the checklist.
Seems you've added the wrong ingredient.
What will you do now?
This is what I've just was saying the whole time.
What are you talking about?
What do I do now?
By the way, anytime you make a mistake, you will see the
exclamation point icon.
Okay, don't worry.
This mistake can be fixed easily.
Why is it all over me?
It's literally all over me.
You can remove only the last ingredient by pointing on the
ingredient container.
Oh, that's actually pretty helpful.
Okay, right click.
It's still in there.
It's still in the bowl.
This is...
Did I sneeze into this bowl?
Why is it like this?
Did I put a bunch of ingredients in here just like...
All right.
What...
There's still butter in here.
In the bowl, you can move them by using like a...
Wait, hold on.
I gotta read this slowly.
Cool.
But what to do when more than one ingredient in the bowl is
wrong?
Throw them in the trash.
Okay.
Now move to the trash.
Who puts butter in a bowl like this?
Guys.
Fucking children don't even do it like that.
This was sprayed out of a jokey clown seltzer bottle.
Children don't do this.
Okay.
Where's the trash?
Is there a trash...
Oh, okay.
It's still in there.
Okay, with this message you get rid of the entire content
of the bowl.
You can also use the trash to throw away other things.
I don't fucking look like this.
I swear to God.
I don't look like this.
I don't look like this image.
I truly don't.
Fucking pepperoni forehead.
Guys, I don't look like...
I'm unplugging this camera.
This camera is fucking messed up.
You have a massive...
No, I don't...
There's pictures of me.
There are pictures of me on the internet.
I don't look like this.
My face has been like stretched 50% this way.
What?
No, that's okay.
I was gonna...
No, I was gonna say there's no fucking way.
No, these are all...
Okay, you guys are fucking with all these.
I look like if they ever remade Frankenstein, right?
This would be...
This is like a new age Frankenstein.
This is like Frankenstein in high school or something, right?
This would be like the Christopher Nolan Frankenstein.
Frankenstein's monster.
Frankenstein...
Yeah, whatever.
You don't care.
All right.
Let's go back to what we were doing, please.
Yeah, I don't know.
Some cameras just fucked up.
What were we doing?
Oh, yeah.
All right, right, right.
Okay.
Use the trash bin to throw away...
People playing tic-tac-toe on my forehead.
That's fine.
10 times smarter than everybody in this room.
You know what fits right here?
Hey, what's the part of your brain?
What?
Okay.
What's the part of your...
I don't give a shit.
We're gonna pause for a minute.
This part where your forehead is right here.
What's in there?
Your frontal cortex, right?
That's hearing.
That's math.
That's knowledge.
That's baking, right?
That's everything.
What's in there?
Hearing.
What's in your frontal lobe?
What is it?
Useless shit.
What's right?
What is...
What goes right here?
Hearing is the only thing.
It's personality and shit.
Come on, man.
That's where the funny noises come from.
It's my brain.
My brain probably looks...
It's probably just this big mass in the front and then it's just squished down and flat in the middle and down at the end.
It's your whole personality.
All right, let's go.
All right, you can throw anything away.
Who cares?
Let's get back to baking.
Look at the ingredients rack.
It seems that one of the ingredients you need is missing.
Don't worry.
This is where all the baking supplies tab in the radial menu comes from.
All right, so put this down.
Put the bowl down.
All right, so let's do the radial menu.
It's like baking supplies.
This is...
I thought this was a chess board.
The baking supplies tab is where you can buy missing ingredients.
Okay, choose the missing product.
I need wheat.
Okay.
Purchased products don't immediately arrive to your bakery.
Usually you have to wait for the delivery to get to them.
This can be a little troublesome.
Yeah.
However, you can speed up the delivery.
Be careful.
It may cost you.
Press U on wheat flour.
Oh, okay.
Do I have to use gems for this?
Thank God.
This one simple trick, which will help you avoid paying for a faster delivery or
waiting for ingredients to arrive.
Just buy all the missing products before choosing an order.
Being prepared for the day will save you some money.
Good.
Okay.
Well, now what?
It's time to start and leave for...
What's wrong with me?
What happened?
Am I donating blood right now?
What's going on?
What's going on here?
Okay.
You can collect the ingredients every time you use the scoop.
All right.
The edibles are not kicking in.
I haven't taken one.
I think somebody's just playing music in my ears.
This is why I don't listen.
Do you have your voice playing on a delay?
No.
What blood type am I?
I have no idea.
You know, that's actually kind of hard to figure out if you don't already know it.
You have to specifically request that they do that.
If you get blood taken and you ask, hey, so what's my blood type?
They'll go.
I don't know.
They have to actually go look for that.
You can't...
They won't just tell you.
How big is the wingspan that you have?
I don't know.
15 feet.
Maybe 16 feet.
All right.
You can collect the ingredient by clicking.
Yes.
All right.
So let's go.
What do I need?
Into the bowl.
There's still butter in this bowl.
Can I rinse it?
Whatever.
I don't care.
All right.
We need...
I want ounces.
So wheat flour.
Can I just...
Yeah, use a big spoon.
What the hell?
What am I doing this for?
Just use it.
Just get a shovel.
All right.
Four ounces of flour.
Get it in there.
And then two ounces of flour.
All right.
We have six ounces of flour in this bowl.
We need yeast.
2.24 ounces of yeast.
So this is that.
And then 0.2.
Got it.
0.24.
We need milk.
Full fat milk.
Yuck.
2.4.
All right.
Do that again.
We're going to do 2.4.
Bingo.
We need water.
Okay.
Water.
2.4 water.
Good.
Sugar.
Okay.
0.12 ounces.
Good job.
Now you can mix the ingredients.
Where?
Transfer the dough to the mixer by pressing...
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
Press...
Did I do it?
All right.
Everything's in there.
Press the button on the mixer casing and wait for the dough to be ready.
Watch the widget carefully.
You don't over mix the batter.
Upgrade the machine.
It's almost done.
Check.
No, it's almost done.
It's going to over mix.
I can't wait seven seconds for this.
Okay.
So turbo mode.
I thought you don't want to mix things quickly.
Sometimes that you needed to do.
You don't want to be that...
All right.
Be careful.
How do I do a turbo mode?
Hey, hey.
Turn it off.
Okay.
Take the bowl back.
Put the dough on the forming board.
What's up?
Is this a forming board?
Buns are formed with bare hands.
Put down the bowl in the table and in the middle of the bakery.
Okay.
With my bare hands?
There are various forms of pastries from longbread to...
croissant.
As you gain more and more experience, you will learn how to create different forms.
But for now, let's just do a bun.
Okay.
It's like buns.
Dividing dough is the first minigame.
Wait for the indicator to reach the green area.
Press space.
That was fucking perfect.
Literally right in the middle.
Exactly 50%.
Okay.
Form the dough is the second minigame.
Grab the ring and move the mouse to match the images with their shadows.
What?
Grab the ring and move the images with their shadows.
Form the buns.
What?
Oh.
Now put the freshly formed buns on the tray.
I keep thinking the restaurant is on fire.
It keeps freaking me out.
Okay.
Do this.
Grab and hold the tray.
Put it down.
Oh, grab.
Okay.
Wait, I can do it from the tray.
I get it.
Okay.
Bake your buns.
However, you have just an old oven for now.
Don't worry.
You'll acquire better ovens later.
Open the oven door.
This is so scary.
I don't know how we will come to determine that.
This is just a normal thing to have just in people's houses and shit.
I'm serious.
Okay.
There's no timer on this oven.
I thought you're not supposed to open it.
Boost.
What is this doing?
Holy shit.
Is that okay?
My hands.
Why is there a boost button?
Find the delivery crate next to the door.
The amount of delivery creates is always determined by the number of orders you
picked up in the current day.
All right.
So this is delivery crate.
Is he live?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Is this live?
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
How does that not delivery crates?
Where's the delivery crate?
Oh, I guess the tutorial blocks me out.
Okay.
Each delivery crate has the client's logo on the side to help you identify the
correct crate.
This one is going to be delivered in two.
I thought it's to be delivered in five minutes.
Okay.
Where's the delivery crate?
Is it the crates by the door?
Is this a crate?
Which one of these is closer to the door?
The crates by the door.
Oh, yeah, just go to the crates by the door.
That's not by the door.
That's by the oven.
Okay.
Put the tray back on the counter.
Now last step time to prepare the buns for delivery.
Pick up the crate and place it in the orange highlight in the blue area.
Crate will then be moved to the delivery car.
Ooh.
Remember that later in the game you'll be able to stack crates on top of each
other to deliver multiple orders.
Now the order is ready for delivery.
Move to the door and press to do it.
Let's deliver the food.
Here you can choose which order you want to deliver.
You've got only one order available.
So we're already picked it for you.
Press the move to city button.
This is one man operation.
This is not the end of your task.
Delivering the orders is as important as preparing them.
During this part of your job, you have to be as fast as possible.
Remember to watch the timer in the top of the screen.
This is crazy taxi with buns.
Later in the game, you'll be able to hire a courier to deliver the orders for you.
In the bottom left corner, you can see a mini map that will help you
navigate through the city streets.
To check the whole view of the area.
You can open the city map.
I didn't do anything.
I'm already in trouble.
Open the radial menu.
Call for a delay.
Okay.
Reset position decline.
Oh, I can just cancel the order.
How come your ears are twitching?
Okay.
WASD.
Spacebar.
Why is this original GTA?
Where am I going?
Oh, right here.
Shit, this guy's on.
That was 30 minutes or less.
Deliver.
What happens if you crash?
I don't know.
I don't want to fail the tutorial.
What the fuck did I just do?
All right.
Time to take a little break from baking.
You know, what's always fun?
Makeovers.
It's time for the bakery to get a renovation.
Okay.
Customization tab.
Point at the main table and press the...
Okay.
Tables.
Is this not the main table?
Is this wrong?
It's time for you to do a makeover scene.
Which one of these is the main table?
This, this is a main table.
Should I just bought that?
You just completed your first order.
Don't forget what you've learned.
It will be useful in your further experience as a baker.
Good luck.
Oh shit.
Nice.
All right, let's go.
I got, I got a million dollars.
I forget everything.
All right, over here.
Do you want to check orders and start a new day?
Wait, not yet.
I got to get ready.
Am I ready?
Yeah.
All right.
I just want to make sure I have everything.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
I thought I could just drive around.
All right, let's do it.
New, it's time for a new day.
We need one bronze bed.
Bronze bread.
Here we go.
All right, one bronze.
I got eight minutes to do this.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Get, close the map.
Get the fucking map.
I don't want to leave the restaurant.
Stay.
Okay, get off.
Oh, that's what I'm looking at.
All right, let's go.
Go, go, go, go.
What do I need?
Where's the recipe?
Recipe book.
All right, just track this.
Whatever.
I don't care.
How do I track that?
Track it.
Track this.
I need one.
Track it.
Okay, let's go.
Bowl.
Rye flour.
How much do I need?
1.2 pounds.
That's a lot.
Pounds?
That's a shitload of flour.
Okay, 12 ounces of water.
How much is a pound?
How much is a pound of water?
Oh, wait, hold on.
Hey, 12.
What is a pound of water?
Two fluid ounces of olive oil.
Okay.
Any milk in this?
0.2 of yeast.
What happened?
I can't put any more stuff in here.
Yeast, 0.2 ounces of yeast.
Good.
Okay, salt, 0.2 of salt.
Oh, that's sea salt.
0.08 of sugar.
Okay.
How's that wrong?
How do I put the sugar back?
Okay, we're good.
Now we need to do 30 to 50 seconds in the machine.
Go.
Why does it sound like an old car?
All right, then we have to form it.
Okay, form it.
All right, put this down.
Go.
What is it called?
Bronze, bronze bread.
What is this?
No, no, no, that's not right.
That's not right.
That's wrong.
How do I do this?
Is that correct?
Is it, is it round bread?
Is it brown, bronze bread?
Oh shit.
Oops.
Just one?
What fucking weird person ordered one of these?
All right, go.
Turbo.
What?
300, how many, can I tell the degrees of the oven?
Me?
Come on.
I only have five minutes to do this.
Steam powered Andy.
Holy shit.
Oh my God, that actually looks pretty good.
That looks really good.
Guys, the floor is cleaner than my hands.
Okay.
Sir, trust me.
So now where's this going?
Do I, did I order it myself?
No, wait, what?
Am I cooking the books and making fake business for myself?
What am I doing?
Can I get a better camera angle with the car?
Why are there roadblocks?
Wait, AM.
No, that's good.
All right, deliver.
Right on time.
Did I just make six?
That's it.
I'm saying that's it.
$60 for one piece of bread seems a little absurd.
All right, cool.
I got 1060.
Wait, should I clean up?
No wonder it's like 80 degrees and 90 degrees in here.
Do I have to clean up or is it just, that's it?
Okay, two golden bread.
You got it?
I think I'm actually, I'm pretty good at this.
Recipe book.
Golden bread.
Two.
Oh, wait a minute.
I have to make two of these now.
All right, two track two.
That's very helpful.
Two and a half pounds of flour.
Let's get it.
1.2.
What is it wheat flour?
All right, two and a half pounds, one pint of water.
Is that one, how much is a pint?
Is 1.25 pounds of pint?
No.
How much is a pint?
What's a pint?
Why would I be scooping this up with one of these scoopers?
I need one pint of water.
What is one pint of water?
How many ounces is a pint?
No, don't speak in milliliters.
I'm American.
16 ounces is a pint.
Okay.
Thank you.
Eight ounces of milk.
Eight ounces of salt.
Oh no, eight ounces of 0.56 of salt.
That's 0.04.
0.56.
Okay.
0.4 sugar.
I got 20 minutes to do this.
I'm fine.
Wait one.
Oh, we're good.
All right, 0.48 of yeast.
Okay.
All right, 30 seconds in here.
Do the other bread while you wait.
There's no order for it.
Oh wait, I'm doing this for too long, aren't I?
All right, we're good.
All right.
This is golden bread.
What kind of bread is this?
Is this too much air in this?
What kind of bread is it?
Is this a round bread?
Or is this a, what kind of bread is it?
It's a long bread?
Okay.
Go!
I feel like this is a captcha.
Oh, you're better than 95% of all other players.
Which by the way, I don't know how long it's taking some people to do that shit.
But even if you do it wicked slow and you're deliberately trying to make it so you're doing it as slow as possible,
you still apparently have done that faster than like 65% of the population.
I don't, how?
You can't let this get light on fire, right?
I can't wait to open this and be like...
Let's go.
Ooh, any more orders?
No, that's it.
All right, let's go.
Why are you so red?
I'm filled with blood.
All right.
Can I get a better view of this car?
There's got to be like a better like car view, right?
I don't want this like GTA camera.
Is there a better view?
Inputs.
Okay, character movement, character actions, minigames, cut dough, car movement, change truck camera, V.
Okay, hold on.
That doesn't work.
C.
I just drove by it.
I can't see the little things in front of me.
Okay.
I'm starting to get the hang of it.
I think the game is going to start to get a little more difficult now.
All right.
Two old-fashioned loaves and three golden breads.
This is going across town.
Okay, I got 20 minutes.
Let's go.
All right.
Three...
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, wrong, wrong.
Is it?
Okay, three golden breads.
No, it's...
Okay, I was making sure it was tracking three.
All right.
Wheat flour, three points pounds.
Water, 1.5 pounds.
Okay, milk, 12 ounces of milk.
0.84 ounces of salt. Okay. Sugar. It's all right. Let's do it again. It's all right. We're good.
All right. 0.72 of yeast. Good. I'm gonna try it. I'm gonna get the other stuff going too. All
right. Get that started. Let's do the other one. Can I not make the other one? How do I make the
other one? Can I only do one at a time? Do I not have the capability to do more than one right now?
Cheese. What? Where? Get it. All right. Three golden breads. All right. Let's make this quick.
That's not three. There's only two. Why is it only two?
Fucking move. Move. All right. Get it. 20 minutes. Okay. Can I start another one?
You're smart. You just don't know object permanence. I mean, I know object permanence,
but not really. It just, it doesn't stay there. Okay. Things like, well, if I put something down,
it's hard to remember where I put it, which is object permanence.
Fuck it. I could dodge an axe if you swing it at me. I don't give a shit.
All right. So now what? I have 20 minutes to do this. Oh, those look good. All right. They're
not ready yet. Now we're going to do the other one. Okay. So this one's ready. Oh shit. I have to come
back and do it. Why would I do that? This, this oven can fit 10 pizzas in it. Why would I
not do all these deliveries at the same time? Why am I, why am I doing only three pieces of bread
at once? What a waste of energy. Can I, where's my buy tool? Whatever. Let's go. I just keep,
I don't know why I keep thinking about this. Oh dude. What's the baseball stream? Oh, he's
going to shove a whole baseball up his ass. Like at that person that asked the question.
You know how many times I keep, how many times I've thought about that comment?
Do I even know what this is? I think I just lost the tire. Oh yeah, guys. Sorry. I got a delay.
Oh, there's tons of preparation I got to do. Oh, what are you doing? Oh, why he's shoving
a baseball up his ass. How do I even get over this other road? I don't want to drive like this.
Why can I not be at third person angle? What is this? Where's this bridge? Oh,
can I get a faster car eventually? Holy shit. That was cool. Are the cops after me? I'm still
unsure what's going on with that. Yep. This is a far away delivery. Is this the last possible
place to deliver that's on the edge of the whole entire world here? This is the last
possible place to take this. Donut dude. All right. Donut dude. What do I got? 150 bucks?
All right, let's go. My stomach hurts. Um, step on a little bit of ginger ale. Just a little.
Very small sips. I have to do a new day. That's okay. Come on, man. All right. This one's right
down the street and it pays the same amount of money. Why would I ever do the other one?
Wait, can I, how do I upgrade? I don't know. 600 bucks for what? I just changed the finish of the
wood. Oh, it's everywhere. Okay. I actually prefer the other one. All right, let's get started. Come
on. Uh, it was bronze bread, right? How many? Three bronze breads, 3.75 pounds of rye flour,
2.5 pints. So that's din, din, din, din, din. No, din. Olive oil, six ounces of olive oil.
Is it actually olive oil? I guess that would be, yeah. All right. 0.6 of yeast. What happened?
Okay. That thing would have came alive. Salt, sugar.
What the fuck is this? Who delivered the Willy Wonka candy machine?
When the, what is this thing? All right. Free bronze bread. I can't say it. Excuse me. What's
happening here? What happened? Fucking go. Was this brown bread? Yeah. Toy boat check. Okay.
That's right. Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat, toy boat. Oh, it's close. I got it. Pretty close. That's the wrong way. This game's
pretty chill. Oh, Undertale. Where'd it go? What happened? Oh, it's over there. The music.
It sounded like Undertale. Do I have to come on? Come on. I'm not fighting you on this one.
Okay. It's not even close. Come on. That's like the dog theme, right? I'm kidding. Holy smokes.
Look at this. Don't you feel like that you would take this piece of bread and you would go like,
it would make you, you would be like, you can't bite it. And you just put it down. And then
somebody would come over with a big ass knife and it would be like,
I like the middle. Everyone out here trying to be the next ball fondler. Yeah. Yeah. Sorry, man.
You're just going to get timed out for, you know what I mean? People out here trying to, you know,
follow that trend of what ball fondler said, man, there, by the way, mods, why that comment is
strange because there is no turkey baster. There's no, there's nothing here. This is not a
turkey baster. Where? Show me the turkey baster. Okay. Three silver loaf or four golden bread.
This one, because it's right down the street and it's 200 bucks. What's, what is he talking about?
I'm talking about the crazy things that people say in this chat. All right. So what are, what
are we doing here? How many, what do I need? Four, right? Four. So can I pull it up? All right.
Recipe book. Let's go. All right. Four puppet bread. What the hell is that?
What was it? Bronze bread? I don't remember. What is it? Go for golden bread. Okay. Let's go.
All right. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, five pounds of wheat
flour, whole meal flour. What? What's wrong? What is it empty? How do I buy more? Oh, it's empty. How
do I buy more? 20. Deliver it now. How much did that cost me? Is that too much? I don't care.
How much is in here? Five. Yeah, we're good. All right. Two pints of water.
One pint of milk. This is almost, I can't fit any more in this bowl.
Salt. Sourdough comes out of a can. What? Okay. Salt. That's a lot of salt.
Oh, shit. How much do I need? What? Sorry, I bullfrogged for a second. All right. 0.8.
And then 0.96 of yeast. This is just bullshit, to be honest. 0.96. Just, it's one ounce. It's one
ounce. Does it really have to be exact? Okay. I have not even turned this machine on. I don't
think it has to be exact. Stop using Imperial. I have to use Imperial. I would not be able to
do it the other way. What is this? This is long bread, right? I hope. Do it. When are
we gonna get new emotes? Here's when you're gonna get new emotes. I say every six months that new
emotes are coming and I haven't added a new emote since 2018. So just take that, I guess, with how
how you will. We just put it on BTTV. You know what I mean? It just goes on Better Twitch TV.
Boost. Does that hurt everybody's ears? Upgrade the oven. Oh my god. A good old simple oven can
bake up to two oven trays. Why can I upgrade it? I just own it. Can I replace it? I don't think I
can replace it. You? I pressed you. That's me pressing you to open that sub menu. All right.
First person to get this right gets a pretend gold star. What song is this? Let's do it. Ready?
What song is it? Mods keep track of your programs. I want to know who gets this first.
I'm not doing it again. They're fine. All right. I'm gonna say it. There was a Stone Cold Steve
Austin intro song. Did anybody get it? Anybody get it? Who said it? Who got it? See, in my brain,
how did you not get that? To me, that is such an iconic piece of musical medley that there's
no way you would not have gotten that. Nothing else sounds like that. By the way, do you guys
think that the person that makes all the WWF, WCW, whatever theme songs, that person has more,
they've made so many iconic pieces of music, right? Think about that.
Some of the most recognizable tunes ever created were made by the WWE music composer guy.
Don't you feel like they deserve a lot more credit? You think the guy that made the Undertaker's theme
song sits around going, that's one of the most recognizable, that's the Super Mario of music.
Like seriously, I think he deserves a little more credit. It's not one guy. Well, it's, I don't know,
a group. Who makes it? That's the most boomer shit I've ever heard in my life. Okay, back up.
If I played for you the first 10 seconds of Do You Smell What the Rock is Cookin' and then 10
seconds of whatever music is popular right now, how many people would recognize the Rock's theme
song versus something that is like popular kind of right now? How many humans on earth would
recognize the Rock's theme song? And you tell me this is boomer shit. Relevancy bias in a hundred
years. Is it really relevancy bias? Because I just told you right now that Stone Cold theme song,
Glass Break. You know what that song is immediately. Everybody. Trends come and go,
artists come and go, but Stone Cold Steve Austin's theme song is forever. You will never forget it.
I'm sorry, I feel like that's pretty iconic. A hundred years from now, they'll know that.
I don't know that. I don't. I don't. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We didn't know. Literally,
we couldn't do it. Yeah, but there's a difference between me going like, and you actually...
There's a difference between... Hold on, let's just fucking... You know what I'm saying?
Don't make me do this. Don't make me... Okay, here we go. How many people in chat know what this is?
How many people in chat know what this is? I want to see it. Just shout it out when you get it.
That's right. That's right. No, this is not the Home Depot theme song. This is...
This is not the Home Depot theme song. This is The World's Most Dangerous Man. Ken. Shamra.
It says... All right, I can see how it does sound a little like Home Depot.
It sounds a little like Home Depot. Oh, fuck. It is Home Depot. How dare you
not know what this is and know what Home Depot is? You've been consumed by capitalism.
You've been consumed by capitalism. This is Ken Shamrock's theme. This is not Home Depot theme
song. This is Ken Shamrock, The World's Most Dangerous Man. Okay, how about another one?
Let's do this one. Who is this? You know, it doesn't matter if you choose left or right,
because they're both chewy, crunchy, and delicious. You know, it doesn't matter if you
choose left or... This is a Twix commercial. Twix is gross. Okay. I'm kidding. I love these things.
I'm not going to even play anymore. Who is that? What is that? Don't you dare say the Taco Bell
fucking commercials. I'll be pissed. Don't you dare. I know. Yeah. No, it's not Taco Bell. No,
it's not... Leave the bun behind. It's not you guys have been consumed by capitalism.
I saw it already. Taco Bell, Taco Bell, Taco Bell. This is the goddamn Undertaker.
Why does it have to be Taco Bell? It's not fair. Here it comes. Somebody said this is what they
played at the Taco Bell Chihuahua's funeral. Oh my God. You guys are too much. Okay. How about
this one? Now, excuse me. I don't care. I don't give a shit who you are, how old you are.
Doesn't matter. If you guys, if this chat room does not become electric, electric when I play
this, I'm going to prove my point right now. I'm going to wait until I know. I'm not even going to
play the intro. If this room does not become electric when you hear this, everyone spam it
so I can prove my point. Let's see it. Spam it. Excuse me. What the fuck is happening right now?
I take a stand. It don't help to hide.
Holy shit. This is not... What? That's Hulk Hogan's music. That's Hulkamania. What happened?
Oh shit. I'm yelling at clouds again. Oh no. We only know three wrestlers. Undertaker,
John Cena. Dude, we're like 20 years old. Shit. You're right. Nobody cares. Sorry.
Oh man. Okay. All right. I'll go make the bread again. Okay. I got, okay. I got one more for you.
One more. Come on. Yeah. You guys, you guys should know this one, right? Let's see. Yeah. This is a,
I think pretty popular wrestler. You guys should get this one. Come on. Everybody knows this one.
We don't know. We don't know. We don't know. You don't know? Really? That's Gloom Man's theme song
from Jerma Rumble live action. I can't say I'm disappointed, but I am. Let's go make bread.
I have a shirt of that guy. Yeah. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I'm obviously too old.
Fucking Home Depot theme song. That's seriously one of the funniest things that I've heard in a long
time. I want to take like a five minute break to go laugh about that in the bathroom. You know what
I mean? Just sit there and just laugh in the bathroom. Just like pissing. You know what I mean?
I just want to laugh in the bathroom about that. Nine puppet buns. All right. Sure. It's the Home
Depot Taco Bell Home Depot. You guys are fucking hilarious. All right. Where's my bowl? So wait,
do I even? Can I put nine breads worth in here? I don't think so. Nine. I need 11 pounds of flour.
I need a bigger bowl. Can I? Okay. I can't do that, right? Yeah. I can't fit anything in here.
I need a bigger bowl. How do I get a bigger? Where do I buy a bigger bowl? Baking supplies?
Where's bowl? No, do not order everything. How do I get a bowl? Don't do it all at once.
But I wanted to. I don't want to. I want to do it all at once. God damn it. All right.
Does it really matter? I don't think you can fail missions in this game. I don't care.
No, give that back. Give that back. That was like that was eight pounds of flour. I threw in the
trash. Shit. Whatever. Oh my God. How much is that? Okay. 11.5. What's half 11.5?
It's close enough. I don't care. Okay. Water 2.5. I need more water. Shit. Oh my fucking God.
How big is this bowl? Why would I only have one bowl in this whole bakery? You've got to be
kidding me. I have one bowl in the whole bakery. What was that? Go use the toilet bowl. I can't
even. Give me this goddamn thing. Come here. Okay. Stop tracking. Let's do two. These are
going to take forever. All right. Well, I'll do batches of three batches of four. Can I fit
that? I don't know. This can hold eight and a half pounds. Okay. Two pints of water. One pint of milk.
Salt. Okay. Sugar. Yeast. Sesame. I don't think I. Oh yeah. Okay. There it is. Sesame seeds.
When you put those on at the end, why would these go on now into the gross thick mixture?
Wouldn't you put these in like at the very end when you bake them? I guess not. Oh fuck. What's
wrong? 1.1 ounces of sesame. I don't. I can't hold that much in the bowl. Whatever. Upgrade the bowl.
I don't think I can. Get a bigger bowl. Okay. So this is puppets bread. What kind of bread is
puppets bread? Is it a baguette croissant? What kind of bread is that? Is it long bread? No. You
idiot. Whatever. This batch sucks. I don't care. I just want a nice warm piece of bread right now.
Just super crunchy. Is there a bread that I don't like? I'm trying to think if there's a
bread I actually don't like. No. Don't even put it in yet. I have two trays. All right. Back to it.
I need to make nine, right? Okay. So I need to make five more. Can I fit? Okay. I'm just going
to do a shitty batch. I don't care. We're going to do five. Yeah. We're going to make a shitty
batch. I'm just going to cut this whole thing in half and whatever. It's going to the bread's
going to be a little stringy. I don't care. All right. Wheat flour. What was that? Somebody just
went like, okay, I don't want to go too hard here. That's fine. A little bit less water than usual.
Okay. That's fine. A little bit less milk than usual. Okay. Salt is fine. Okay. Wait, pull that
back. Okay. Sugar. I want to see if I can fit the rest of it. One ounce. Where is it? Oh, up here.
Fuck. I can't fit it. Shit. How do I upgrade the bowl? I can't even put it. I can't just shove a
bowl full of milk into the oven. Although I'm going to try. No, I can't. What if I just hold
it like this? Will it cook? Fuck. I have to do it right. Um, just give me. I'm going to do two or
whatever. I don't care. I'll do three track. I can do three reliably. Yeah. Buy more of this shit.
That's fine. Okay. Water. Okay. Milk. Salt. Who's trying to get my attention behind me?
Okay. Sugar. Yeast. All right. Now I can do the right sesame seeds. All right.
Am I feeding a shit load of birds? What the hell? Why do I have so many seeds in here?
There's a lot. That's a lot of bird seed. Okay. Turn around. I broke it. This bread sucks. Baked
milk. What would baked milk even be? It would, nothing would happen. It would just be good.
It would get hot. All right. If, if you put milk and a little bit of yeast into the milk,
what would happen? Okay. A little bit of, all right. What would happen if you did this?
If you took milk, yeast and sugar and you put them together and baked it, what would happen?
You just put it in an oven safe bowl and put it in the oven. What would happen? It would just be
custard. It would just be flavorless, flourless cheese. This flour and cheese. It would just be
sour. What did? It would be cheese. Isn't cheese a much different process though? Those of you asking
why I'm doing this is to be able to get nine of them. What the fuck are you talking about?
I thought I was going to be able to split them. It wouldn't be cheese. No. Oh, that one's ugly.
Whatever. They don't even care. I still get 80% guys. This is whatever. I'm going to take them
out anyways. I have to wait. I still have 12 minutes. What hair gel do you use? I don't use
hair gel. I don't put any product in my hair ever. All right. Come on. Let's go. Liar. That's not a
lie. I shampoo and condition, but that's it. No, I don't put hair gel in my hair. Do you know why
I don't put any product in my hair? Because all the way from when I was a teenager up until
my late 20s, anytime I put hair gel in my hair, I would get this. It didn't matter if it was,
oh, you got to get a different brand. You got to get this brand. You got to use a pomade. Don't
use that. Use mousse. Didn't matter what I did. Use a lot. Don't use that much. Use a little. It
doesn't matter. I would get this line right here. This line of acne that because it would just get
kind of greasy and sweaty and I hated it. And I'd get this line of pimples and acne. So I just
started saying, you know, I'm going to use a really good conditioner, really good shampoo,
like very, very high quality and go from there. And I don't put anything in my hair. I, I'm missing
two. All right, two. Where's the bowl? All right, two more breads. It can be cold, but they'll get
it. Okay, let's go. I mean, plus my hair is kind of wavy anyway, so I don't really need to put
that, nothing in my hair. My hair will naturally just go swoop, swoop, swoop. Baked milk. Baked
milk might be better for you. It's good for people with intestinal issues. Holy shit. Okay.
All right. Water. What song was that? What song was that one? It was Super Mario. Sorry,
you got it wrong. All right. Where's the, what the fuck is going on? This one would be normal.
This one's gonna be good. It's all right. 2.6, 2.5, 2.52, 2.48, 2.44, 2.4. That's what I did.
All right. Um, I can probably start putting these away. What? Uh, excuse me. Puppets bun.
Puppets bread. What's the difference? Puppets bread. Puppets bun. I mean, these, these ones got
bacteria growing on them anyways. That's annoying. Oh my God. I'm about to quit the game. I'm about
to quit the game. I'm going to quit the game. Um, all right. Well, let me see if I can, how many do
I have in here? So it's not a lot. So it would be a round bread. This is correct, right? This would
be a puppet bun. I only have enough for two. How do I only have enough for two? Bro, I don't know.
Cringe fail baker. This is not even accurate. This is puppets bread still. How do I make a
bun? What? Bagels, croissants, baguettes, long breads. Oh my, it's literally right there.
Oh my God. That's annoying. Just put it back on here and we'll redo it. Just reform it.
Holy shit. I think I have enough to do it. I have enough to do it. This is saved. No, I have enough
to do it. I have six minutes, but I should be okay. How many is that? This is one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. All right. That's nine. Go puppets. These are buns. How are
these still? I don't understand. That's buns. I just chopped them into buns and I formed them into
buns. I don't care. Those are literally buns. Go to the clipboard. What's happening? Who's that?
Oh, I was like, who the fuck is this three puppets alone in the dark? I was like, who is this?
I didn't accept the recipe. So what can I? I'm so confused. Self-made tasks. All right. Whatever.
I'll start over. I only have four minutes. Just quit. Just redo it. Somebody just walked in with
a fucking pan and went like right in the back of my head and I just went to black. Okay.
$700. Let's go. Okay. Three farmers loaf. All right. Farmers loaf. You got it. What do I need?
I can do this one. All right. 2.4. My eye. 2.4. That's a lot of water. I'm gonna run out of money.
Fuck off. Okay. Good. All right. Rye flour. 1.8 pounds of rye flour.
Sour dough starter. You put a pint of this? What? I thought it was just like baking soda.
I didn't think it was something else. What's in this? I need to buy more of this shit. Okay.
I thought it was baking soda. It's ridiculously hard to get right.
Do I have no money? Oh, you guys have any experience making sour dough? All right. 1.4
ounces of salt. I'll get it right first try. All right. Only 15 seconds in the mixer.
You have to put bugs in it. I don't think you do. Okay. Then this is bake for 70 seconds at...
Did I spill any? Oh, I don't just bake it. I have to form it. All right. What is a farmer's loaf?
What's a farmer's loaf? Is it a longbread? I hope that's right. I need three. How the fuck is this
not? Yeah, that's two and one little tiny shitty one. Dude, I could go for a huge pretzel right now.
You know what? Honestly, a big crunchy hot pretzel. This might shock some of you.
Might be the single greatest food item that's ever been invented by humans.
It really actually could be. If I really sit here and I really think about it,
that could be the greatest tasting greatest thing in the world. In the whole world.
Golf sucks. Yeah, it does. I'm not... Why do you think I'm going to disagree with you on that?
Donuts are better. No, they're not. No, a pretzel. A nice hot soft pretzel with a thing of
honey mustard or spicy mustard or even like cheese, nacho cheese or something.
Or just straight up right out of the oven. Just a little bit of salt on it. Oh my god. Pizza's
perfect. Yeah, a really good pizza. I don't think it makes me have a child's palette.
I think, oh man, the best steak I've ever had in my life. The best steak. No,
I would rather take the best pizza I've ever had in my life over the best steak I've ever had in my
life. Also, I'd rather have the best piece of salmon I've ever had in my life over the best
steak I've ever had in my life. Steak is overrated. It just really... I don't know. I think I really
just think it is. I genuinely believe that. I know it's really good. It is. But I just... I
kind of think it's overrated. Pizza and salmon pog. When I have a really nice piece of meat... Oh,
wow, dude. This is like ribeye or this is wagyu. Whatever. I've had it before. It's like, yeah,
that was... Yeah, that was really, really... That was really good. But it's not good enough for me
to care that much to me. I think it's incredibly... It is. It's very good. But I don't know. The best
piece of fish I've ever had is higher than the best piece of steak I've ever had.
But then it's not even a red meat thing for me because... Okay, I love cheeseburgers. I love
steak and cheese subs. Steak bomb, right? I love meatballs. I love red meat. But I don't like the
red meat where the red meat is just, hey, eat it. It's just a piece of red meat on a plate.
No, I don't like that. It needs more. It needs to be... There's gotta be something else there.
Season it. You know what I mean? I don't... I'm just not into the whole... All right. I got a steak
and then there's broccoli and mashed potatoes on the plate too. Even with a good bunch of
good seasoning or a marinade or whatever. Garlic herb butter. Yeah, it's phenomenal.
It's phenomenal. You're right. But I've had a piece of salmon before that I'm not kidding. And
look, you can say this about a steak you had too, but I've never... I've had a piece of salmon before.
I don't remember the restaurant. I genuinely don't remember. I do not know. It was in the
north end in Boston and I seriously thought that... It felt like God came down and talked to me for
like 10 minutes. It was just... It came out. It was no bullshit. It was just this delicious
fresh piece of salmon and the fork... It was sitting on, I think, a piece of asparagus,
whatever the hell it was. And I remember taking my fork and I went to go touch it and the whole
thing disintegrated. It was just like... It's like, what the holy... So then you fork off a little bit
and by the time it hit my lips right here, it was like cotton candy. It was just like...
It was like cotton candy. It didn't taste like cotton candy, but it acted like that.
It was just gone. And I remember just going like this. I dropped the fork. I went like...
And I was with my family and I was just like, I don't know. I don't even know what I can say
about that. Ratatouille? Did you eat cat food? Whatever. It was so good. And I remember when
the waiter came over, I remember just... And do this, by the way. If you really do like something,
I'm serious. Please start doing this. If you eat something at a restaurant and you go,
that was actually really, really well made and really well done. That was fantastic. That was
unbelievable. Tell the waiter. Go, hey, tell who was back there that that was fucking phenomenal.
That was phenomenal. And they should be proud of that. They should be absolutely proud of what
they did. I'm serious. And then they go back there, they say, hey, the salmon at table four,
they were like, that was the best salmon they've ever had. You know what I mean? They need to know
that. They've got to know. That's not ratatouille. Wouldn't ratatouille be if I hated food and hated
the restaurant or something from a chef that makes our day? Yeah. And guess what? If you know that
somebody is eating your food and they think it's like one of the best things they've ever had in
their life, that that's going to be all right. Let's go. Let's go. You like that salmon? You
should try my catfish. Give that a try. I've got I've got a risotto on this menu. It's going to be
good. Did you ask for the chef's number? Okay, so let's go. What am I doing? What about that's a
rich person restaurant? No. Some of the best food that I've had has come from places that were not
expensive. It's the person behind the goddamn curtain. Don't you understand? It's the person
behind the curtain. I've been to really expensive restaurants and the food sucked absolute asshole.
I've been to restaurants where you'd go holy shit this is that's how much the entrees are
and some of the best food I've had in a long time. It's the person behind the curtain.
That's a weird flex. Guys, I've been to McDonald's that are better than some five-star restaurants
I've been to. I'm telling you this is my real take. The way that I feel biting into a double
cheeseburger from McDonald's and how delicious it is and then eating oh this is a pan seared
freaking fish steak with tuna grazed a row on it and it has a piece of parsley all over it and it's
I don't like this. I've eaten stuff like that before and I've had stuff like
that that was very good and I've had stuff like that that's very bad. Would you ever eat a snake?
No. No. Nice child's palate. I know for a fact that there are people in this chat right now
that have eaten at McDonald's and had a five-star restaurant like filet mignon and went that one
sucked that was not that great that actually was kind of not good. I know for a fact you've done
it. I'm positive. I know for a fact that you've been sitting in the back of a car that went to
the drive-thru and you were eating fries out of the bag sneaking them. Just eating fries out of
the bag you weren't a bunch of friends whatever and you enjoyed that more than the like a tuna
tartar that you had at a four-star restaurant before. I know it. Don't pull one over on me
and by the way why are you eating tuna tartar? Why are you eating steak tartar? What's wrong with you?
Somebody on the phone right now that that called the restaurant so I mean I ordered three pieces
of farmer's loaf for you. Is that coming or? This delivery I've already burnt five minutes.
Tuna tartar is sushi. All right yeah no no no that's right. Steak tartar though I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I just I don't understand why people do that. I don't understand why people do that.
I don't get it. What is it? Tell me what it is about it. Steak tartar is but tell me why.
Tell me why. Why are there so many viewers? I don't know. Wait okay somebody called me an idiot.
Hold on. Somebody said you're a fucking idiot. Why? But why? Somebody said why oh why do you
say tartar like that you fucking idiot. I thought you were calling me an idiot because you liked
tartar and you were giving me a reason why. How am I saying it wrong? Steak tartar. Tartar. How do
you say it? That's how you say it. Tartar. Tartar. Tartar. Tartar. What? I might you guys follow?
I'm saying it right? That's correct. Steak tartar. Steak tartar. Okay thank you. Steak tartar.
One more time for everybody that was listening. Steak tartar. How do you pronounce steak tartar
correctly? It's a regional thing? Oh I have an ad. Announce this name as well as how to say more
interesting French cooking terms too that many get wrong so make sure to stay tuned for those.
Okay this is the real deal. This is a meat dash made from raw ground beef. Some say it can also
be made from horse even though even in France that's really not very common. Anyhow how do you
say it? For reference in French in France it is said as steak tartar. Oh come on! Therefore in
English it is generally said as steak tartar. And that by the way this is directly from I went
I went. Steak tartar. Steak tartar. That's what I said. Why are people so mean to me?
Okay that was 11 minutes by the way. The guy on the phone is still there. I don't care about
steak tartar dude. I mean you have like you've got like a five star review so I'm gonna sit
here and wait for the bread. But are you all right? All right let's go. Track it. What am I
even doing? French is not a real language. Okay I don't know. What does that mean? All right.
Bronze bread. Four. Let's go. Why are we what? Five pounds of rye flour. Is this gonna be too much?
I understand. Okay raw. I understand raw food like raw fish right? I understand it. But something
about raw hamburger meat. Raw hamburger meat smells. It has this smell to it. Kind of like
I talked about with raw eggs. I don't want to eat that. And it's not ground beef. What do you mean?
It's a hamburger meat. It's raw meat. Yeah all right I get it. You're not going to the grocery
store and getting a pound of ground beef and eating it raw with a fork. Okay hold on. Hold
that thought. Yeast okay. Salt. Sugar. Whoa too much. It's the natural way of eating it.
I just don't like it. I don't know. And I'm not even saying it. Dude it needs to be
well done. I'm just saying it needs to be cooked. All right but honestly who started cooking food?
Why did we start cooking food then? Right like who started cooking food? Cavemen? So you're telling
me that the cavemen were like raw meat. Yes. And then all of a sudden they put it over a fire
and then went good good good good good good good. And they all started fucking screaming.
They decided that. We didn't. The only reason why we do this now is because the cavemen decided to
burn a warthog that they fucking found in the forest. What was this again? I don't remember.
All right bronze bread and it's just a regular brown bread. We started cooking food. Hold on
somebody's got the answer. Actually I'm very curious about this. I really am. I swear to god.
Cooking food allowed us to get more nutrients out of it so people who cooked food survived
more than those that didn't. We started cooking food because our teeth became less sharp and we
also didn't want to die of diseases. You English major. Different people do different specialties
and that's what I need to know every single thing. I have to be a doctor, an English teacher,
a scientist, and an astronaut. People do different things but to me to me it tastes better.
Like a medium even like medium rare right? Like medium to medium rare medium to me just that
tastes better to me than just eating it raw. And we add you know garlic and butter and flavors and
parsley. Oh I want one now. Bro this is high school knowledge. Yeah that's what the cavemen
thought too. You know how many people it's crazy to think about this honestly.
The flavors that we like over thousands and thousands and thousands of years.
Cavemen were just going and picking up berries and squishing them and putting them on their
steak and eating it and just dying. No no no don't eat us. It's crazy like I'm
under the first person to piss on the fire. No pee piss on fire. No I don't know. I don't
know about that. Yes flavor. And then they ate that guy. Where's my bread? They didn't start
making bread until pee pee on food. Yeah they had to be away. You would eat a person? No I'm
saying that. They maybe I don't know. I wouldn't. I'm just saying in fact I'm fucking million years
ago. Guys they didn't have the McDonald's drive-thru. I don't know. I don't know. You
don't know what it was like a million years ago. Nice granddad joke. You guys are fucking so funny.
Yeah they used to they must they they probably put so much gross shit all over their food.
You imagine how disgusting food probably was for a long time. That's for us to to complain.
Oh um excuse me. This drink is a little too sweet. Redo it. They had steak tartare though and I'm
sure it was good. That's literally you. I actually I actually don't complain about food if it's wrong.
I really don't. Okay it has to be very very wrong. Very wrong. You know how much of a pain in the
ass it is to deal with a shitload of people. You know it's crazy. All right here we go. Okay
everyone hold on. Here comes a take. The amount of people that you see in let's say like a
McDonald's drive-thru. Think of the how crazy it gets at a lot of these places.
There are sometimes 10 plus 20 cars for hours outside of these McDonald's restaurants or
Burger King. It doesn't matter. It's oh no you I wanted a Sprite and you gave me a Coke.
Okay that's all right. Like whatever. It's not that's not a big deal. It's not that big of a deal.
That's not a big deal to me. It really isn't. Now if I ordered you know two double cheeseburgers uh
fry and a Coke and I got three chicken sandwiches uh McFlurry and like this is not my order. This is
not even close. Like I'll be like oh hey this is it's no problem at all but this is uh probably
somebody else's order. All right what's what's the next? What's coming up? What am I even on? Okay wait
didn't I do this? Wow that's a great take. That really wasn't a take really now that I yeah you're
right. That actually wasn't a take. What was the take? I just said that's fucking crazy.
That's not a take. Hey dude that's crazy. All right let's move on. The take is I don't complain.
Oh that's right. Well no no no my take is that. All right here's the take. That a lot of people
that work in the fast food industry have to deal with a lot of horse shit and I don't want to be
one of those people that adds to the stress of like a bunch of people fucking screaming at
them through the intercom and like fucking with them through the like you know like fucking with
them and it's a lot of bullshit um so I don't know I try to and why can't we tip at the fucking window
some places they can't no we can't we can't we can't do that not saying that like you know you
know obviously people you know tipping is a whole nother can of worms right but a lot of places you
can't why do we have to tip yeah I know I know I know it's a confusing and it's like the worker
is relying on your tip because they're just not getting paid to be there at a wage that's a
reasonable fucking wage right so it's like is it 20% is it 15% is it 40% 30% is it 12% what if I do
15% is that bad what's wrong what did you do what's your tip we're doing tips together should we
give 50 should I give $100 I'm gonna give $100 should I give 10 I get it I do but I will also
be honest too though I do like to if somebody's you know really nice they do a good job and it's
like you know you're actually you're working your ass off here fuck it I'll give you why not I get
it but that that's on me right that's on the individual yeah really doing a good job placing
trays over and over again but and sometimes tipping is gets weird because I how expensive
was the meal right where where it gets weird technically we paid for the tip yeah you know
also too like a lot of times tipping if if the restaurant just paid the you know you think about
what your check would be right let's say your check is $20 or 30 $40 the extra money that you'd be
tipping I don't know how somebody there's probably some mathematician or economist in here
but like if you took away the tipping and even if you needed to charge a little more for the food
I'm not paying potentially more to tip and pay for the food and you could pay potentially the
workers better right can an economist tell me that here even if you made the the food more
expensive by enough but it wasn't it didn't reach that point where it was the tip on top of it
right run a restaurant then you get back to me um I know I'm dude I'm talking up my ass I know
am I gonna make bread or what all right stop I get I can't one I've I can literally do one thing
at a time all right four I need uh by the way I'm moving I'm gonna do play a different game after
this this game's fun but I'm gonna do something else this is I like this the game's relaxing
right this is a very nice relaxing gameplay shit make another bread apology I haven't had any bread
uh eight ounces of olive oil 0.8 ounces of yeast looks good eight of salt looks good 32 of sugar
whoa one oh okay man that's so wrong how would you suck it out with a vacuum I'm taking like
a nozzle and just yeah I took out enough sugar we're good okay go just scrape it off scrape it
out go back to Morrowind German can you talk about no all right but the whole thing is not
to start arguments in chat the whole point is I is to just tell you how I feel you started it I
know it's my I know I started it I did you didn't say anything though yeah you know what fuck that
I didn't say anything I agree with that guy that was bad how do I feel about lizards I love lizards
and I never got exposed to them really or experienced them at all because they're
not really on the east coast where I lived there's not very many lizards running around
Massachusetts I mean there are there are some but not like they are out here
they're everywhere out here oh come on all right this is the last delivery and they're gonna play
should play that choose your own adventure thing that Kyle is famous is that any good
I wanted to play it I heard it's good I'll try it I can't even upgrade this stuff when do I get to
upgrade five nights at Freddy's 2 Kyle is famous had two votes in pre-stream chat yeah but I mean
it still seems like a fun game all right let's go five nights at Freddy's 2 you don't actually
want me to do that do you actually want me to play five all right mods do a poll this has to
have 80% yeses or I'm not doing it by the way this needs 80% yeses and it needs at least 5,000
responses at least five 5k responses at least oh come on I can't see where I'm going all right
we're good oh my god where is this I it's not across the bridge okay let's drive into a police
car all right what's it look like um you got five thousand no I'm not moving sorry it needed to be
80% close all right so let's do um what else do I got I have we could do that we could do my time
at Portia Portia Portia that's the game that I had open all last stream we could do Kyle is famous
we could do this I got a few things we have all right I'm gonna go pee I'll be right back
we'll figure it out get some water all right I have some here but I'm gonna pee
I'll probably fix the camera too it looks like shit all right I'll be back talk amongst yourselves
beer b