Wait, hold on. I didn't clear my throat before turning on the microphone. So that's my fault.
Hi guys. Why was everybody striking? I said, hey, we're on strike. We're on strike.
We're on strike. We're on strike. We're on strike. Why? What? What happened? What did I do? We already
forgot why. Look, I already know. I already know about the blank space thing. I was on my phone
checking in 20 minutes ago or so. And I just see a bunch of blank spaces, blank spaces,
blank, blank, blank. And I'm like, what's going on? I thought it was a bug on my iPhone.
It's not. I've already seen it. I thought it was funny. I laughed at it for a minute.
So, all right, you got me. Congratulations. I thought there was no stream today.
How did this stream today? What do you mean? Last night we streamed late and I said we're
going to go tomorrow too. We tricked him. Yes. Are you going to destroy any more marriages today?
I hope not. No, we're going to, we're going to dial it back a little bit.
We're going to play. Well, actually, that's, I say that, you know, I'm not, I'm going to stop
saying that because every time I say that, every single time that this live stream you've heard
German nine, eight, five say, we're going to dial it back tonight. We're going to just chill
and play a game and hang out and relax for a few hours. It ends up being like a 15 hour stream.
And I lose like 300 hair follicles. So what, you know what? This stream is going to be crazy.
It's going to be nuts. I'm going to go nuts on this stream. Okay. That's how, you know,
it's not going to happen. My nose blocked up. No, no, my voice sounds nasally. I don't know. Am I?
Maybe I got a little, maybe a little, maybe just a little bit. Yeah, maybe a little as I can. It's
kind of dusty and allergy out here today, but my voice gets deep. Look, my voice has three or four
different places where it sits. This is what I sound like if I, when I don't speak with a little
slightly nasally blocked up nose for like 10 hours in six hours. If you keep watching the stream,
two or three, four hours from now, my voice is going to sound different. It's going to sound
a little higher like this because I've been speaking for a long time. I'm very boisterous
right now because I haven't had, there's been no words coming out of my mouth. It's basic science.
I literally cannot tell a difference and neither can I. Thanks for coming to class.
We're going to play hidden folks today, which is a hidden person object game. I've been told
it's really, really fun. I've been told it's, I would, I was told you're going to love this game.
I'm like, okay. Am I though? Like, we'll see. Wrong. Well, there's one thing that I do know for
certain. We'll switch over to it now. It's, um, what you're about to hear is, well, not that. I
mean, that's pretty cool. It was a rumor. You're about to hear every single German nine eight five
stream from start to finish. I don't even need to say anything. I should just put this on repeat.
Okay. I've made all of these noises before, all of them multiple times.
It's hurts. It hurts to hear this. Anyways, I've, I don't know how this game works. I know you've
you have to, it's hidden folks. It's like looking in the mirror and I don't want, I don't know,
no more looking in the mirror. It's kind of, it's, uh, it hurts my eyes. Hold on.
That's better. Which one of these things is better?
I don't, I don't like the, all right. Jeremy's,
Jerma shut up for a second. I'm trying to talk. I think this one is good. Dark mode always. Yeah.
Yeah. He just spit on me. I'll do them all.
Oh, this looks worse somehow. Explore Garland is fascinated by the tongue of this reptile.
I mean, this is the reptile. There it is. That was, hold on. We need less. We need less German
noises. It's already, hold on. All right. That's better. All right. I got it. There it is. Now,
what do you want? Isn't that the tongue of the reptile? Now what do you want? Fascinated by the
tongue of this reptile. This big snake is a real bush crawler. This looks worse though.
I really like this game. Hold on.
Oh, that's, hold on. What about the sepia one? Oh, this is, this is all right. This is okay.
What does yellow look like? Not bad actually, but I, I need it to be a little bit darker.
Yeah. This is better. Should have, maybe I should darken it up a little.
This is cool though. Yeah. We're in night mode. Okay. So I got, got you. There's a brightness
setting. Oh, is there? Yeah, we got, that's better. Ah, all right. We can get this right.
Let's do. Yup. That's what I'm thinking. That's what I'm thinking. Nope. Nope. Nope.
I'm going to, it's going to, I don't know who's talking.
This is what I'm going with right here. This is perfect. Okay. Here we go.
The big snake is, I look for a snake. Snake. I got the chameleon.
There's a snake. Anybody see a snake? I don't see a snake. The land of the Jermas. I don't see a
snake. Kiki the monkey loves a good soft shelter. I can, I can cut stuff down.
Oh, Oh, okay. I get it. I get it. I understand too loud. All right. I'll fix it. I get it. Okay.
So now we need to find the snake, the big snake. That's still so loud. Okay. We've got a wink.
Okay. Now we need to find the snake. This big snake is a bush crawler.
So we need to find the snake. Got the snake. Big snake. It's still so loud.
You watched me fucking turn it down. Okay. Now we need Kiki the monkey. It's not you. You in here.
A good soft. Okay. Kiki the monkey. Now what? The only ripe white banana is pretty much up for grabs.
Oh, isn't everything white in here? Like it's, I can't, there's no, it's too loud. What do you
want me to do? The only ripe white banana. Everything is, I can't, there's nothing here.
Ripe banana. Pull one of these things. Oh, oh, oh, got it. This game is fucking not even,
I almost just said not even fun. I meant to say not even hard. You found everything here.
Stay here a little longer. Enter the jungle. Oh boy. Well, now this is a, oh, that was the
tutorial. Now we play the real game. For this man in distress, the uncomfortable seat is the
least of his troubles. Okay. What else we got? Why are they, why do we still have to hear they're
like, if you ask classy Jesse, treetop naps are the best. Treetop. There you go. This game hurts
my eyes, man. Sorry. This woman with a guitar plays music that will warm the hearts of men and
reptiles. Guitar. I don't even need 10 seconds. Zoom. You zoomer. What do you mean? No. Why would
I? Oh my God. No, why would I? Oh, that you can move to. Why would I want to do that? I could see
everything here. Oh no. Wishes he had paid more attention during his Tai Chi classes. That you?
No. See, why would I zoom in? Okay. And there's woohoo. I'm looking for silhouettes. That's what
I'm looking for here. And I, I can, I, I, I can see everything. I can scan this whole environment
in one second. Just look, I'm looking for that exact silhouette. My brain has not found it yet.
Silhouettes. That's all we're looking for here. There it is. Told you.
Fluffy Panda does what Fluffy Pandas do. Eat. Scan the environment. Okay. End in five, four, three,
two, one. Fluffy Panda eats. Fluffy Panda eats. Who told him to play this? I don't like 300 people.
I'm not done with this yet. Relax. Relax. It's been five minutes. Fluffy Panda likes to eat.
It's been 15. We spent five minutes introducing, six minutes picking a color and five minutes in
the game. Fluffy Panda. Oh, I can, I forgot I can interact with the environment. Fluffy Panda eats.
What is it? Say it again. Where are you? I'm just destroying the whole entire forest to look for
this one. Got him. Oh, I did it. Wait, stay here. There's more to do. The others watch jealousy
while King Kiki sits on his throne of bananas. Oh, wait, no, he's got a crown. Where's the monkey
with the crown? Got you. He sits on the throne of lies. What are you talking about? Long elegant
birds lay long elegant eggs. Just give, just give us a few minutes. I like this. All right,
let's go. Let's check the next area. Help that walking folk get across. How do I do that?
These snakes? How do you, oh, move. Please stop. I'm high as fuck. This game's scaring me.
Dude, you're fine. It's not that big of a deal. All right, with the noises, maybe,
maybe I could see what you're talking about. Please. I'm working high. What are you doing?
Cut it down. Make this louder. I'm not going to make it louder. I have to get this bridge over
here. Oh, I can pull things. I have to click and hold. I like this game because just because of
this. Cut it down so you can get through. It's just because of the Adam Sandler noises. That's
why you want to keep playing. That's kind of an interesting game. That's not even an Adam Sandler
noise. I'm sorry. I disagree. This game's fucking disturbing. It's a cute little hidden object game.
Why? Oh, dude, I'm on drugs. What the fuck? You can't do an activity that's in like an
eight-year-old's book when you're like high, apparently, but I probably can't. Yeah. The
guitar is having a real good conversation with the swing. Got it. Jerma's freaking out. Dude,
you're on crack, man. Stop being. Aiden really wants to be found. Yeah, what are you smoking?
What do you do? What drugs are you taking? Oh, man, the swears, the swears. Waldo fucking game. I
can't. Oh, it's coming at me. The walls are closing now. Air bed. I'm too high for this, man.
Jerma, I love this game. Also, I had my bunny. What? What happened? Wait, what did it say?
Jerma, I love this game. I had my bunny since September. I have somebody help me name the
bunny. It's an all black bunny. How about, uh, how about, I don't know, um, uh, how about, uh,
Jetson? Yeah, that's pretty good. All right, what's this one? With filthy hands, the bullies
quickly return to the campfire. Ella will never find her hairbrush. All right, which one of the
bullies has the hair? I did not get it. Filthy hands. It's in, it's inside the fire. Pepper's
pretty good. Pepper is pretty good, you know. Where's his hairbrush? Wait, no, I thought that
was gonna be in there. With filthy hands? Jerma, quick, say something funny. Sure. Ban that guy
for expecting me to be his personal clown. Funny enough for you.
All right, I'm done. I'm not doing this anymore. This is too much. No, I'm not. I'm still here.
We got a wink? You said I shaved? Nobody even commented on that. Why has nobody commented on
the fact that I shaved? Like, I mean, I do something and nobody's seen, nobody notices.
We couldn't see. Yes, you could. All right, where are we going? Beekeeper Barry. I'm still here. I
mean, guys, everybody relax. Relax. This is just, this is the pregame. Relax. This is the pregame
to Mega Man Legends. I wanted to play this for a little, for a little bit. But guys, everybody
just cool. Just cool off. You have an Instagram filter on. I do not have an Instagram filter on.
I don't even know how to use that. Beekeeper, Beekeeper Barry. All right, there's the bees.
Beekeeper Barry, where is he? Beekeeper Barry.
Fuck, I'm getting interested. Harriet, am I making the bee sounds? No. What if I just stay here for
like five hours and just play this all day? Am I? All right, listen. Mai releases every butterfly
she catches. That's why there's still so many of them here. Oh, no. Where are you? Where are you?
You're going to only have one viewer of me. I'm not even watching my own stream. What you meant
to say was zero. That means I would have to have my own stream open, which I don't. Let me just find
Mai, please. I want to check this game out. I got Mega Man Legends sitting in the tray right now.
What tray? In the PS2 tray? I like this game. You guys are too harsh. Where are the butterflies? Wait,
I see a butterfly right here. That's a clue. Let's see you foster this harshness.
Don't blame me. I'm playing the game. I'm playing this game. I like this game. What do you mean?
If I was fostering something, I'd be fostering you enjoying this game because I like it. That's me
fostering. I got to find this person. No Mega Man until I find this person. By liking the game,
you make chat hate it. What am I, your parents? What are you? What? Dude, I found this really
cool game today called Hidden Folks. No way, dude. Is it fun? Yeah, it's so cool, dude. You like find
monsters and pigs and there's fucking people here. Dude, that's awesome. Let's play it. Oh,
I'm so into it. We're both hitting or hovering over our desk. The fucking door opens. What are
you boys doing in there? Oh, we're just playing this game called Hidden Folks, Ma. You wouldn't
even like it. You're an idiot older. Oh, Hidden Folks. What are you looking for? Ma? Oh, she's
right over here. Boys, if you need help with anything else, especially with Lumberjack Fleck,
I know where that is too. I beat this game last night. Fuck out of here, Ma. Fine. I don't even
like this game, Ma. Mike, do you like this game? Yeah, you do. Fucking loser. No, I don't. This
game's a fucking loser. Yeah, I don't like it either. What am I doing right now? All right,
I'm like projecting, I'm fostering some hatred here on you guys. That's all right. All right.
Let's go. I'm going to play Mega Man Legends, but I have to find these people first.
I'm not leaving until I find the bat. I don't care. I don't care if every single person leaves
this frame. I have to, I'm going to beat this level. Are these every butterfly she catches?
That's why there's still so many of them. Found the bat. Monster Mo. All right, what about this
one? We'll go back to this. Hayden tried to escape the internet, but he put his tent next to the
only Wi-Fi point of the campground. Is there a cell tower here? Oh, I found her. Hayden tried to
escape the internet. It's over here. Campground's over here, right? No, the campground's down here.
Oh, there's the Wi-Fi spot. Where is he? Is that a secret? No. There you are. Got it.
Mom, can we please play Mega Man? No, not until you've done your homework, which is
watch this guy play hidden folks as your only assignment. You can't even do that. What the
heck? No ice cream for you after dinner. Who's this dog? The sun is shining too brightly today,
even for classy Jessie. That's not her. For all an unusual punishment.
Key? This is satisfying. It's a really satisfying game. What about this one? Lumberjack? What's that?
Sun is shining too brightly on like a beach camping. In the car? Maybe you're in the car.
I don't know where she is. This is kind of fucked up, by the way.
I'm just some otherworldly force opening up everybody's tents. No, no. Where are you? Right
here? No. No. Oh, chat. Vote on this. You don't vote on an unofficial poll. Guys, the unofficial
poll is the same thing as... All right. If you guys all... Unofficial poll. That's like watching
a TV show and being like, oh man, I really hope they kill off this character next.
Let's all vote for it and send it to the fucking CEO at Disney. CEO at Disney is going to read it
and be like, what's this? Who do they want? Who do they want to die next to the show? Oh, I would
throw it in the trash, but I get fucking a hundred of these a week and the trash is full every day.
So I'm just going to rip it in half. Recycle this, please. Where is this person? At least he's
recycling. Not realistic. Disney CEO wouldn't recycle. She's classy. Yeah, but what does that
mean? I mean, look at the results. Where are the... What is the poll? Let me see it. Let me see it.
It says, do you think Jerma could beat this game? No. Omega lol. Yes. Oh, I see what's going on here.
Okay. This is really interesting part of the stream. This is like a thousand of you. This is
very interesting. So like about, but probably like 700 of you are like, no, I want him to keep
fucking playing this game. Like I like this game. This is like kind of cool experience. This is like
fun to me. So let's say, let's make him think he can't beat it. So then he stays and tries to
prove us wrong. It works, but the Lord of the Rings, Fellowship of the Ring, it has to work
with something like this because he's already interested. It's not going to work. I already
know that. The sun is shining too brightly. Are there more than one campground? It's working.
Chat, keep up the pressure.
Classy Jesse found anybody who likes this game. Also, I'm not reading the rest of that. What the
fuck are you talking about? Lumberjack. All right, we got one more. Lumberjack flex stands in front
of his grand final challenge. Forest or a tree or wood or cutting or like a huge tree or something.
I mean, there's a bunch of trees. Zuma was a big tree. That's pretty big. That's pretty big.
Not that big though. That's there it is. He's blind. He's blind. He's blind. He's blind. He's
blind. He's blind. He's blind. No, I can't move on. Oh shit. This banana was parked into a fruit
basket. What about this one? This truffle is about to be discovered by a hog. Together with her bunny,
friends, Black Bitty hides in a hole chewing on some snatched wheat.
Ivan hitched a ride without permission. It doesn't have an escape plan. What are you guys doing right
now? I don't get it. I don't understand. What does this have to do with anything going on right now?
Is that what you think I'm doing right now? Somebody wrote LUL fuck chat. Do what you want to do.
Oh, I am. See, I said Mega Man Legends was coming, but I don't even own that game. I just made that
up completely. I don't have that. This spider has a particular taste. All right. There was a spider
over here. I don't understand. Fuck me. I don't even own Mega Man Legends. I just own Mega Man
Legends 2. I have to fucking have the sequel and not the first one. What's wrong with my floor?
I just picked up the PlayStation 2 controller instead of the mouse. Hi, nice to see you. It's
time for Mega Man. It's not time for Mega Man. You'll know when it's time for Mega Man.
It's how you know it's time for me to switch a game. I usually don't talk for about 30 straight
seconds. I go, all right. Okay. That's cool. I haven't done that yet. Usually it's a lot of,
all right, where's this thing? Cool. When you hear me fill air time, because there's nothing
interesting going on for me in the game or I have nothing interesting to tell you. That's how you
know like to start the countdown for about five minutes. All right. Rock pile, rock pile.
Dog, cool dog. Yeah. Saying things that I'm currently touching or what just the actual
noun. That's how you know it's like the person's done with the game they're playing. Because I'm
a streamer, right? So it's like, was it just dead air? No, I'm not going to have dead air.
Tractor riding along in the tractor. Oh, beep beep. You know, tractors. That's how you know.
And this is not just me. This is every streamer you've ever watched. You'll see it. You'll,
you can see it now. You'll know. All right. Ivan hitched a ride without permission.
Doesn't have an escape plan. So he's over here. He's like under the one of the cars.
That's not him. It's to ride without permission. No, saying the thing like this, saying any word
or phrase like this. Okay. It's to ride without permission. No. All right. I'm not doing that
anymore. All right. Where is he? Where is he? Over here? Nope. He's lying down somewhere.
Wow.
If he was going to be somewhere, he'd be down here. It's beaker.
Beaker. No, that's not beaker. Let's get him to do a whole symphony though. Cover your ears.
It's probably going to hurt. Can't figure out what's, what's germa and what's this game.
What's germa? What's germa? Well, what's germa? I can help you out there. What's germa? What's
germa? But I, but that's a good question. If I were to think, well, let's answer the second
question first. Second question is, this is a hidden folks game about hidden objects,
but here's the thing. What is germa? Hey you, person that just landed on the channel page.
What's going on? My name is germa985. Or you can just call me germa. That's what most people around
here call me. I'm a gaming channel. You probably could guess that by all the different playlists
and all the videos below, which you should check out and you should go watch some of them right now
and possibly subscribe. That's the whole purpose of this video. I'm trying to get you to subscribe
to my channel. So hey, subscribe to the channel. Subscribe. You see on this channel, I like to call
myself Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Germa, because I have two different sides. I have the very professional
side where I review content and I review packages. What? I don't review packages. No, I don't do that.
I review like games. Oh, here's like, here's a cup. This cup is good. There's a whole lot of stuff
here though. I have my fun. I have my professional side and I mold them together into sort of this
lunacy that is germa985. So hopefully this little trailer will be able to give you an explanation.
Did you review packages at once? You subscribe as well. So please subscribe, subscribe,
and subscribe. And I'll subscribe to you all next time. And of course, subscribe, subscribe.
Oh, I hate it. I hate it. Hey, what is going on everybody? Hey, what is going on everybody?
Hey, what is going on everybody? Germa here. Who is this guy anyway? To gameplay commentary.
Meet me at the statue at 12 o'clock. Okay. I don't know what the statue is. I don't play this game.
No, what? Oh, what was that? You were going to bank what? What were you going to do?
Oh, there we go. So of course, as Mario, you have to do all the dirty work because
you can jump real high. I never understood that by the way that why does Mario have to do everything?
He's like the savior of the world because he can jump higher than Michael Jordan.
Right. Left or right. We're going to go left. Oh man.
Fucking scary game. I knew it. I knew what was going to happen too. And it still doesn't matter.
What I'm talking about here is you'll see it. I go like me, me, me, me, almost like I'm sweeping
the screen, not with my mouse, but with my A and D keys. And it's something I don't know why I do
this. And I think it's because I have a lot of trouble aiming with the mouse more so than I do,
which just kind of getting people in front of my cross here, but I kill every single person almost
by doing the sway in quotes. Oh no, I'm dead. Who did this? It's Otto. Okay. I don't want to alarm
anybody here, but I'm sorry. I may have taken a shit in your house. Being one of the top 10 players
in the world. That's right. This is Germany's grandfather here. Not Germany. He's not as good
as me. He can't give me the tips. He can't give me the strategies that I can. So let me just tell
you that I'm one of the best players in the world and I'll show you right here. Look at this. Get the
fuck out of here, buddy. Let me tell you. Did I really have this in me the whole time? And the
answer is yes. Yes. Everybody does. We all do. Everybody has it in them. You have it in you. You
do do it. You can actually do it. Oh, you just have to tell yourself it's possible and you have
to act on those possibilities. Oh, what a sick trick. Hi guys. Today we're going to create a
fucking washer dryer on Jeremy's channel. This is so long. All right, fine. Right here. So he
already finished it. So thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it and hopefully
you subscribe to his channel. Hopefully I have convinced you to do that and you can be part of
our little community here, The Germs. So join The Germs. I hope to see you all in the comments
section and thank you for watching again. So take care everybody. I'll see you all soon.
So that's somebody. Who's German on A5? That's who he is. Did you subscribe to
the channel yet? I don't know. That video needed to be three and a half minutes shorter than it was,
but this is like 2011 YouTube. Come on. Delete that video on stream. That video actually does
not exist anymore. It's like, I think that's a private. This video is private. I just showed
you a private video or unlisted at least. Make that your sub sub. All right. Anyways, what were
we doing? So the person that just came in, what is, what is German? I don't get it. And what is
this? Hopefully we answered both those questions. You probably left 15 seconds into that video.
But if you were still here, thanks for watching. All right. So we got the spider. I was over here.
I saw the spider web right there. It's right here. What do you mean? It's right here.
Video shouldn't be public. Actually the video should not be public. I don't know. Whatever.
But it has like 30,000 views. Save it quick. I'm not, what do you think? I'm going to just
delete that video. I got to get this one. I haven't hitched a ride without permission.
It's gotta be like this car park here. Is he just inside one of these?
There's no escape. Super Bruce. Thanks for the six community subs. Thank you Bruce.
Thanks for the subs. Hey, thanks for subscribing to the channel. All right. I need, I gotta, I gotta
level with chat here for a second. A lot of you guys might be newer viewers. Listen to me.
There was a time, I'll get on cam for this. There was a time between 2010 and like 2013
but I didn't even swear on this channel. I didn't know what I wanted the channel to be.
I didn't know if I wanted the channel to be a channel where I did, I was a professional
reviewer or something. This is like, nobody knew what the fuck they were doing back in like 2012.
No one. Not one person did. And now there's fist formulas for all this shit now. It is where
everybody's at that everyone's got the perfect way to do everything now. 10 years ago it was like
there are people watching my YouTube channel. Why? What do I do? Wait, what? There's how many
people, how many people clicked on that video? Why did they click on that video? Did I do more
of that? What should I do? Should I do like, should I do like another TF2 video? Should I do,
I'm gonna do this grandpa video. I think. Yeah. I think that's what I'm gonna do. I hope. And then
you make videos like that trying to like, it was different. It was, it was the wild west. It was
the wild. I never did clickbait videos. No, I didn't. No fucking way. Not in a million years.
No, I did not. I refuse to believe that. When, when did I do a clickbait video? I never ever,
ever did that. Ha ha. Oh God. Ha ha. Oh God is me not knowing what I want to title a video,
not clickbait. That's, I have no title for this. So it's going to be a TF2 uncensored
German. Ha ha. Oh God. I don't have any other words to describe the video. So I was going to
write ha ha. Oh God. Give me a clickbait TF2, bring on the thunder. That's not clickbait. That
happened. I got clickbaited in that video. Don't you understand the purpose of this video was I
was clickbaited. I was baited in this video and I was very upset by it. Watch it on stream. No,
no, I'm trying to hold on. Let me get through level one of find the hidden people. Somebody said,
what about the video where you said this is the scariest game ever? I really thought it was.
I really thought it was. It was the scariest game ever. And the reason why I thought it was
the scariest game ever. Okay. If you were to go back to like the 1700s and you brought a DVD
of Adam Sandler's Jack and Jill, and you gave it and you brought a TV and you plugged it in
somehow. You got it to work and you, and you watch, you showed like the pilgrims fucking
Jack and Jill. That would be the, they would be like, holy fuck. This is the most insane,
ridiculous thing I've ever seen in my life. This is the best, but it's just called a movie.
That's the best movie I've ever seen in my life because they have no, they didn't have any other
experiences watching any other movies. So I didn't play that many scary games. So that was
the scariest game I had played, but there was a million of the scary games that I hadn't played
yet. They had Shakespeare. It doesn't matter. I have a magical box that plays Adam Sandler on a
TV. This one is actually clickbait. No, it's not. I'll give you, I can explain all of them.
What is it? I didn't, I didn't make this video. I didn't make this video. Games that you see in
this chat. I'm just going to get it off with because, wait, hold on. Wait, everybody, everybody
settle down for a second. I got to get this. Okay. Hold on. I can rebuttal this. I really can.
You give me any of these, I'll rebuttal them. This is painful. I bet I can't load anything.
You used to switch to Boost Mobile. You get four free phones when you switch. Switch to Boost Mobile
and get four lines for $25 per line per month with unlimited data and four free Samsung Galaxy A20
phones on our super reliable, super fast network. No, I didn't even get paid for that. One of the
most requested games that you see in this chat. I'm just going to get it off with because
it's all everybody talks about before every stream. It's based on a bunch of fucking animated
characters, like your fucking anime bullshit that everybody seems to like these days. Animated
character. Can't wait. We're just going to get it over with real quick. Of course I'm talking
about Garfield car. How's that clickbait? That's just me. Let's do it. I'll get you and I'll look
like a bloody accident. How about this? If I don't win this race, then, okay, if I don't win
this race, come in first place, then I will, I will beat Doki Doki Literature Club on stream
10 times in a row. Holy fuck. When did that? Why did I do that? All right. Focus now. Okay.
If I do not find the rabbit within the next 10 minutes, I will beat Doki Doki Literature Club
on stream 10 times in a row.
That's wheat, right?
Why didn't I say the mushroom? Why didn't I say the mushroom?
Get the fuck out of here. Don't have to do it. Three winks. Did it.
Fortress Raphael dries in the sun.
You have a Snapchat filter on. You don't want to show. Okay.
Jerma, Jerma, you got a Snapchat filter on. That's why you look so good today. Fine. We'll turn,
we'll turn, we'll get it on all the defaults. You ready? Fine. You want to see? I'll turn off
all the filters. All right. That's the, that's the smoother I turned off because I had kind of a
glossy look today. Turn off this one. I had a, I had a lip reducer that was on too.
Had a shine removal and there was a gloss there over there. Okay.
The what? Do I look any different? Oh, actually kind of a little bit. It's not even that much.
It's not that much. Turn them all back on.
That's better. That link, what? Stop doing that with your head.
So I stopped doing, stop doing the like, I need to be, I need to, I want to tilt my head in every
photo. That's what people, that's what people do. Hold on, hold on. We can't even get through
one level of this game guys. What is this? Why do I have this? Why is this saved? Why is this saved
in OBS? Why is this in OBS? What is this image called? This is just in OBS. That's actually a
scary image. I don't know, you know how you did that that fast. Guys, that's, that was like 42
seconds. How the fuck did you do that? Do you guys just have Photoshop ready and you just,
I don't even, how do you even do it that fast? All right, where's, I gotta find this person.
Oh, by the way, hey, listen up. All right, this is important. Listen. No, you gotta do,
you gotta do the side one, the side one. Hey, listen to me. I'm trying, hey, listen.
It's Kim and I's anniversary tonight. What do you think about that?
Four years. Long time. What am I doing here? I said tonight, tonight, we got plans. We got plans,
me and her. I'm streaming. No, no, I'm streaming right now, but we got plans tonight and tomorrow.
I gotta find Ivan. That's why you shaved. This dude leaves his girlfriend for big bits.
Oh, why did I say that out loud? No, just forget it. Where's Ivan?
Yeah. Okay. I'm kind of, I kind of can't stand these noises anymore. How do you guys watch this
stream? It's taking me an hour and two minutes to be like, nah, I don't want to hear these noises
ever again. We don't. All right. There's no, he's not down here. He's right here. Probably.
Bathroom doors.
All right. I have no idea what this guy is. There's only, the cars, they're only here.
He's a stowaway. He gets to ride without permission. That's not him. And he can't escape.
Oh, shit. Wait.
Wait. Where the hell is he? Well, that's a tortoise, right?
All right. Let's go. Why it takes his job as a wheat supervisor very seriously.
I bet you German never even kissed anyone before.
Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork versus hay.
Where's the fucking hay? Wouldn't it be right here? Hitchfork. Hitchfork versus hay.
Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork. Hitchfork.
This picture makes me laugh every time.
That's like the ultimate narcissist photo.
Yeah, it is. Imagine if you were that, like, follow yourself that only you...
This can't be even real. Make this the thumbnail. I'm not going to make this the thumbnail of the
stream. So you want me to sit here like this for like two straight minutes to make sure this is
the thumbnail on the stream. No! Did it already happen? No, it didn't already happen. Stop blinking
me that weird picture of my face. That's top tier clickbait. I can play. I'm sexually attracted to
me. If you water your crops well and give them a little bit of extra attention, you may see this
flower. Got it. All right, ForresterAman is as much an artist as he is a lumberjack.
All right, he's an artist. Artist, artist, artist, artist, artist. What are you doing?
It's another one of those streams, huh? It's another one of those... Here comes
an image every three minutes. It's one of those. Yeah, that's not even turned the right way.
Oh! Oh! Oh! What is this? What the fuck is this? Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh, that's the New Year's kiss.
Here's the thing, though. Okay, everybody looks like that when they kiss somebody.
You ever... Here's a little tip to make yourself... Take your iPhone and put it
right up to your fucking face and close your eyes and go like that and tell me what it looks like.
Go like this. Go like this. Take your phone. Go like this. You're going to look like that.
I'll do it right now. Okay, here we go. Ready? You see? Okay, so exhibit A. I rest my case.
Who cares about the fucking pizza guys? He's avoiding playing this. No, I'm not.
I can't even. Guys, there's too many pictures you have here. You have too many photos.
Oh god. It looks like I'm made out of clay. Oh, all right. All right. All right. Okay. All right.
It's time. It's time. It's time. It's time to go. It's time to go. It's time to play. I'm playing.
It's time to play the game. That's the thumbnail now. Okay, that's fine. It's all right. It's time
to go. Show us. Hold on. I don't even know what image it is. Not this one. It's not that one.
Where is it? And just like the crowd in the background making all these fucked up noises.
You guys ever fucking think that like Intel is going to approach me for anything?
No, not this one. Not this guy. What? The title is perfect. Oh, all right. All right.
All right. Artist and a lumberjack. It's time to tell your girlfriend you love her.
I just found a chicken. Yeah, I've now. Oh, there's a cow. Wait. Oh, that's not you.
I want coffee right now. What can I get coffee quick right now? All right. I'm going to go. I'm
going to get coffee quick right now. All right. Anybody find this? Anybody find this person?
You lost viewers. What the fuck? No, are you fucking kidding me?
How many? How many? How many? No, what the fuck? 100, 200, 300, 500 got stupid. Oh,
I've never taken another break ever again. All right. Where's uh, where's this person?
We're going to find the art artist artist. It's right there, dude. Hold on. He's a lumberjack.
He's an artist. We got a wink. I'm, I'm getting really tired of doing that.
I didn't think I didn't think it was going to take. Um, I don't think I thought it was going
to be way longer. People have to get to 75,000. I'm done. I'm tired with the links, but they can't,
I can't move them. I can't leave. I have to stay. It's like in two months. Oh, right. That's
you're right. It's been a while. Okay. Who is this guy? It's time to get some fruity physics
into Newton's head. All right. Here it is. I didn't even take me one second.
Okay. Anymore apple to drop on somebody's head.
Apple, apple. There it is.
This is interesting. Did the Joker laugh? Why did the Joker laugh right now? How appropriate
would a Joker laugh be right now? We already, we just talked about this.
We just talked about this.
Scarecrow. Oh, here we go. Where is this? Fake Bull Barney is not moved by this pen. Maybe
because he's fake and has no feelings. Fake Bull Barney.
Yes. Fake Bull Barney. Five minutes on the clock.
Needle might not be in a haystack, but she sure knows how to roll.
Clues. Cool clues. What? No.
There you go. Oh, I did it. Oh, let's stay here for now. Okay. We have another image
that's circulating. Okay. What's wrong with you guys? What is wrong with you guys?
Why did you do this? Why would you make this? Okay. No.
It's like, it's the fact that it's come out of the coat. He's like five, five. He's like five, six.
Why is it like a person? What are you doing?
Okay. No. Community crack night. No, it is kind of. I hope to God that's not the thumbnail because
that would be really fucked up. No, I've been doing too much fucked up shit on the screen.
All right. Too many. All right. We got to dial back the fucked up stuff.
Okay. Oh, look. It's me as the Joker. It's full moon. It's just constant images.
I did. I said it was going to be crazy and I should, I do. I shouldn't have said that.
I should have said it was going to be chill. Constant conflict. No, I saw that one. It's not
the thumbnail. All right. Where's this fish? This rotting fish is repelling potential customers.
Well, here's the market down here.
Come on. Where is it? Here's the fish. That's be close, right?
Drawing away potential colors like a trash can somewhere. It's rotting fish.
Okay. Good. All right. I got to turn. I got to mute. Where's this fish?
Which staff and scrolling by that thumbnail be like, I got to click on this one.
Where's this fish? The hell is this? It's right here somewhere. It has to be.
Where is it? Shit. Is there another market scaring off potential customers? Oh, wait.
What's going on down here? There's only two. There's a scarecrow in this fish and then needle.
Oh, got you. No, shit. Really? There you are.
Staff is here. Everybody, quick. Duck. I keep passing the fish.
Well, I found that. That's good. No, don't scatter. No, no, no, no, no. Just everybody.
I'm having a family reunion party. We're all family here. Your brothers, sisters,
your cousins, your relatives. This is like thousands of us. We do it every year.
Shit. Stop. Stop. Shut up. All right. Fuck it. I'm going to the next one.
Fabian wants to get back to the festival, but the signs aren't helping him.
Oh, God. Oh, this is not going to be good.
Oh, shit. This is look at how huge this is. Oh, this is so big. New here. Is this the Twitch?
Okay. Well, the signs aren't helping. Found him. Got you. Fabian. I got you.
What are you guys doing? Dude, you know, the thing, you know,
if you ever heard like the phrase, like, don't ever post anything on the internet.
You ever heard that before? So I had like a cute moment with my girlfriend.
And it's been it's been ruined forever. I don't have a post anything on the internet,
but let this be a real lesson for you. What you see on the screen right now should be a warning.
Don't tell anybody fucking who you are. Don't give him any photos. Don't send anybody a picture.
Don't ever take a picture. Never take a picture ever again, unless it's on a disposable camera
and you have the originals. You have the negatives.
Oh, why? There's so many of these. I wanted to see him kiss the dog again from staff.
Okay. It's real, by the way. Oh, that's fucking funny. Is it bait? Yeah. No, this is a test.
Now this is a test. I don't want to fail the test. Like, oh, I want to see him kiss the dog again.
He's got his finger hovering over the 72 hour suspension.
The chief was standing up a minute ago. Standing up a minute ago. So what does that mean? Standing
up a minute ago? Is it flying down? The axe in that one. Oh, you guys really. Why are we airing?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Why are we airing all? Why are we airing all the grievances of this stream?
Why are you guys trying to get me to get like in trouble? You guys are just.
Why are you gaslighting Twitch staff into making me like investigate me? Why? What are you doing?
Hey, dude, I took two weeks ago. Check the timestamp here. Check that out.
That serves you right. You're playing hidden folks on board. Hey, you're going to get what?
You're going to find anything. Hey, don't don't let this chat gaslight you staff.
What is it? It's fucking lit. Lit Fortnite arms and arms up and down, leaning forward and back.
What? OK, so you're pulling a log of what everything I told you guys. What did I fucking tell you?
What did I tell you? I specifically made this use this as an example. Don't ever everything
you've ever written on this website is logged. All of it. Every single thing you've ever said
is tied to you. Somebody just pulled that back. That was like four months ago. It's all here.
Let me be the example for you. Everyone wasn't enough to for scavenger fury max. Wait,
the sombrero cactus resides somewhere on the outskirts of the desert.
Who's this? Oh, wait, something going on out here. Help.
Meet me. Do we help them? What the fuck? It's fucking two hours until this joker's
dreams. P.S. team all this piss and shit time. Grow up. No, guys, that was that was me quoting
someone. I didn't say that. That was me saying, hey, look at what this crazy person wrote.
I didn't say that. I'm not crazy. Not me. Not me. I'm normal. I'm very normal.
I mean, I'm exceptionally normal. I'll prove it to you right now.
Hello. How are you? I'm doing very well. You see the Red Sox last night?
Yeah, they did a very good job. I can't believe they're trading for Ronson Arroyo. Also, I my
anniversary tonight with my girlfriend should be really fun. I'm gonna go out and maybe
to dinner. I will, you know, I do very normal things with me and my girlfriend. We just go do
things. I'll be wearing a suit with a bathing suit underneath just in case. You never know
when you're going to get invited to go to a pool or go into water. You got to be ready.
Did Twitch staff just give a hundred community subs? Did Link, the Twitch staffer, oops,
misclick? Holy shit. Wow. That's a lot of fucking subs. Link, what are you doing? That's insane.
Link gaming. Dude, Link gaming? No, thank you. Thank you for the hundred community subs,
which I will take as a free pass to have dog kiss images on my stream. All right, good.
Free pass granted. No, thank you. Seriously. That's a ton of money. All our hopes are for
this one plant to grow here in the desert. Don't drown it. I failed the test. Oh, dog kiss pass.
This lone vulture ate literally everything around him. Everything. Is this a vulture or
is this every Justin Roiland character? What's going on down here? Wow, funny stuff, dude.
So where is it? I will tell you that Justin Roiland is so good at doing a loud, high-pitched
scream. No one will ever be able to do that. No one will ever be able to do that. Like I can't,
no one can do it. Only he can. No one else can ever do that ever to ever live.
I can't even try it because it'll be embarrassing because I wouldn't, it wouldn't even be close.
SOS. The trail ends here. Aladdin surfs the mild winds across the desert like nothing weird is
happening. Let me send help. Oh, shit. I found you. This is Eric. That would have been so hard to
find that. Hurry, Max. Glasses. It was the, I'm right here. I can help you. It was only the
woman's glasses the three vultures didn't eat. All right, I got to find, hold on. I need my help.
I'm trapped in my bathroom. Start at the beginning of your bathroom and do a false sprint and then
put shoulder into door. Don't do that. What do you want me to say? Do you have access to a phone?
No? Can you not like slip like a, like something in the lock on your side to open it? Is the door
completely lodged? You have no access to anything. Do you have a window in that room? You don't have
access to the window. There's no window. All right, well, that's weird, okay? So how are you
going to get out of it? You're going to do that? What do you want me to tell you? Lie on your back.
If you're in a scenario where you're stuck, it's trapped and you can't get out and there's literally
no one to help you. Lie on your back and put your knees at a 90 degree angle at the door and just
like infant toddler tantrum, one, two, three, five, five, sit with both heels into the door until it
opens. What do you want me to tell you? Why are you asking me for this advice? What do you want me to
tell you? Is your door made out of wood? Probably. Mega Man Legends 2 looks great. Yeah, that's,
that boat sailed like an hour ago. I do, I will prove that I own it though. Here it is. I will
prove, I will prove that I own it. That's the Lord of the Rings. I'll prove that I own it. That's
like the serial number. Wait, what's this? Oh, there's like a Capcom hint telephone number.
He's got Lego hair. No, I do not. Not today. Bullshit. Bullshit. Do I? No, I don't actually.
This is normal human hair. Normal human hair today. This is hair. This is just human hair.
Now I've, I've made it Lego hair. This is what a normal person looks like. I, this is what a
normal person looks like. If you saw me on the train. All right. If you saw me on the train,
if we were on the fucking train together and you saw me like this, what would, you wouldn't do
anything. Yeah. That's a normal person. He's doing an alien monologue. This must be the
right Oasis treasure hunter. Open sesame, open sesame, open. Nope. This rocky door needs a
different kind of magic. I'm going to start wearing like a mustache. I can't grow a mustache.
So I'm going to start wearing like a fake mustache. All right. We're going to find this.
We're going to find the vultures. Vultures, vultures, vultures. If I saw you on a train,
I'd say is that Jerma from JermaCraft? You would not do that.
It's chats full of vultures. I didn't say that. You did. Would you cringe if someone actually did
that to you? No, I wouldn't. I would laugh. I'd be like, Oh, that's funny. And then I would get
off at the next stop. Even if I didn't have to get off at that stop, even if it meant I'd gotten a
taxi cab for 30 minutes to go to where I was going. What is this? This has been a fun stream.
This has been like the chat takes over the stream and I kind of, I'm all right with it. I think
it's fun. It's Lego hair again. That's all right. What? Dead people. This has been a downward
spiral. I don't think so. I think this has been an upward spiral. Wait, open sesame.
Martin waits for the music to kick in, but he will dance primarily on the inside.
No. What about these animals? This bottle of water could save your life in the dunes of the desert.
Bottle of water. I got to focus on one thing at a time here.
The chainsaw. This is my first stream of yours. Could you kindly explain what's going on?
Well, first of all, welcome to the stream. Thanks for joining us.
This is a game. It's a hidden object game where you have to find, it's like a where's Waldo hidden
object game. The whole purpose is to find these things. Like for instance, the vulture. That's
fine. It's just a fun little game. We're just hanging out and just talking about stuff and
I need to find a bottle of water. All right. Where's this bottle of water? Looking for water.
Looking for a group of vultures too. What's with the rocks? This is weird rock formation.
You look like someone hit random in a creative character. Oh, that's a crock of absolute
bullshit. That's not even remotely accurate. All right. There are many things that I am,
but one thing I am not is you look like someone hit random on a character creator.
I am no for a fact that I am not those things. I might not be able to do basic children's math.
I know that and I've told you that. Mr. Bone, come on. What about down here?
Too many places to be. Mail preset number three. Oh, please. Fuck. I'm never going to find this
shit. Who am I looking for? Looking for who you? I'm missing the music. Aladdin searched the mild
winds across the desert. Hey, no, no, he's right there. Where? What? What? Oh,
look, I can't see where you're pointing, guys. How many times do I have to tell you the title?
Says he likes to go be inside.
Martin. No, he's not here. He's not even over here. That person is.
All right, let's go. We need to find where people are dancing.
Ladies and gentlemen, that's not what I need. Ladies and gentlemen, ladies and gentlemen,
let me tell you, ladies and gentlemen, how do you guys like to be referred to?
Ladies and gentlemen. Hey, you guys. Hey, chat. What would you prefer? Folks. Hey, folks.
The germs, the germaniacs. No, that's not what this that's not what you guys are called.
We have gone over this many times. You guys are the germamites.
Anybody see water? No, not the rats. You are the germamite, the germamites. Yeah,
to say it like that. Otherwise, it's not accurate. It's the the accent there.
No links resident sleeper. Are you sure? That's I see a lot of them. Oh, here we go. What's down
here? Martin waits for the music. Martin waits for the music. Martin looking for the music.
Martin music. Wait, yeah. Oh, Rick. Oh, Rick. What? What? We made that reference before. I wasn't.
That's the original image. Why are you linking the original image?
Instant minus two for saying Rick. I wouldn't even I wouldn't even do an impression.
Instant instant just reaction when they Rick and Morty down vote. I didn't do anything. OK,
I'm doing it again. I've said it again. I got to stop saying the word that show. What? What? Why
are we so fucking crazy about that show? It's like it's ear poison. If you hear that word.
Why? It's all right. It's I mean, whatever you do. You guys don't care that much, do you? Yes,
we do. What's your favorite TV show? What's your favorite TV show? Current TV show that's currently
on the air. Fear factor. That's not even on the air. The NBA. I mean, that's called the NBA school.
Roe Jack Horseman. OK. Better Call Saul. It's a good one. Power Rangers.
America's Funniest Home Videos. Always Sunny Philadelphia. That's a great one. Here we go.
We made it to the festival. How come I'm not? I am disgusted. I am absolutely revolted that I'm not
seeing any Curb Your Enthusiasm fans here. I'm disgusted by this. I'm fucking actually disgusted.
I think one person said it. Curb is for boomers. Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no. I'm revolted right
now. I got to go brush my teeth after hearing that. OK, we need to find the person that
music only likes to dance inside dancing inside. Where are you? Oh, oh, I turned the music on.
All right. Everybody dance. There's there's the only dances on the inside.
How many more do I need to move? One more. And it's one of these hard ones.
This reptile is a narcissist. What's this image? Narcissist, narcissist, narcissist, narcissist,
narcissist. This one's good. I like this one. I'll show this one. This one's actually really
this one's this one's pretty good. It is. Can you imagine like walking into the bathroom and seeing
this public restroom album cover? He's an egomaniac. This reptile is in this cactus
forest is so well camouflaged often loses itself. It's extremely rare. Whiteback scorpion is
surrounded by its children. A king of the desert never goes underground. All right. King of the
desert never goes underground. Well, I found the snake. How is that not the snake looking for a
bunch of scorpions? There are no more people left. Scorpions, tons of them. We want face cam. Oh,
OK. Thanks for the feedback. Appreciate the feedback. Scammed out of a wink. Let me just make
sure. Oh, fuck. Yeah, I did scam you. Hold on. All right. I need either a snake or I need the
scorpions or a bottle of water or a reptile in a cactus place. Bottle of water, cactus forest,
cactus forest, cactus forest, cactus forest. No, what a handsome young man I am. Hey, thanks.
I don't even know what this is. What is this image? This is like a bunch of dots, like three
mapping of me. I don't know what that is. I don't want to. Why does every one of your winks look
like you're trying to get something out of your eye? Because I am trying to get something out of
my eye. I'm trying to get a wink over with so I can go back to doing a live stream. Remember,
those are codes. He hates us. No, I already told you how I feel about the winks now because I
thought it was funny for one day and it's been two months and I have to stay. I can't walk it back.
I'm not going to walk it back. I never said I was going to walk it back. Increase the wink
price. No, no, no, I can't. It's too late. Come on, where are these scorpions? I need to find one
more damn thing. Would you be mad if I made winks 200,000? But I kept 75,000 and 75,000 was
my channel points. I say shpee. No, I don't want to do that. That's worse than winking.
Imagine how often I would be doing that. You guys watch a lot and there's people that have a lot of
points. I didn't even think about it. Oh, wait, I got it. Mom's waiting for the bus to the big
city to buy some diapers. Yes, mom. Okay, the TV technician is fine tuning a signal.
TV, TV tech, TV tech. There you are. Move it out of the way, please.
Hello. Where's my wink? Well, you know what I'm going to do? I know it's 7,000 IQ play here.
Soon, winks are going to be 75% off for one day only. And then it's going away.
Is he on B? I'll cover fire for you. I got a few hits on him. He's dead. One more to the right.
To the right. Yep. Got him. You're clear to go up. Go up. I got you. There's an old person's
bone in some wall. Freaky stuff. Let's go. Winks are going to crash. You need to sell them now.
Please don't. No, your wink. Don't you understand? Your winks are worth a lot now and you're selling
them because you know that winks are going to be really, really inexpensive in like a month.
That's insider wink trading. Oh man. Why did I just fucking say that? That was, why did I say this?
Oh man. All right, what we got? For move or buck, this job was one box too many.
Looking for a moving company. Moving company right here. Follow them. What happened up here?
Whoa. Whoa. Why? What? What's going on up here? What happened? Why is it up red? I didn't fucking
zip development going on up there. I hate that. Don't you hate it when you know you just got zip
development. There's a whole block on the street forehead and you just know and it's here it comes
and there's this four or five zits moving in. It's the worst. All right, where's this moving company?
What's the other ones? Swimmer Sven got the address right, but the pool wrong. Peter Griffin.
Oh, Lois. No, I don't think that's another one. That instantly is just like that. He said family
guy word. Now I have to do, I hate him. Painter? What are the other ones? Maybe a bunch of sugar cubes
and 20 lollipops wasn't the right recipe for lemonade, limo. Charlie's yard sale is a big
success, but where is the salesman himself? There's the lemonade, limo. My favorite voice so far.
That's every Casio keyboard that has the weird human voice. Every time you went into the stores
that just had the keyboards and you just put it on the voice one and just start pressing buttons
and then you look at this is $700 okay bye who's this in the all right where's this one
mover buck all right this is the moving truck right here i'm gonna follow it is the yard sale
remember this tv no it didn't even go anywhere what the fuck what else is there who's this
Vito is halfway to hearing his fortune driver Dave is being tailgated by some crazy truck driver
Elvin wants to dance so he's waiting for the music to kick in his link time is over
all right uh this this is just what happens this is the fate this is in all the movies that have
this in it this is uh all right this is what happens after seven days uh in all the ring movies
to the people and they spin they spin the chair around and that's what it looks like oh no he
watched the tape seven days ago hey who are you all right i need movers movers you guys i gotta
pay attention one box too many and this kayaker got home from a long kayaking trip he just wants
to watch tv now but ah no signal movers one box too many there he is got you got you
swimmer Sven got the address right but the pool wrong he's gonna be in a fountain looking for
this guy in a fountain it's definitely he there's a pool party but he's spend
uh redeemed a wink redeemed a wink i can see that your text is like
bobby you owe five links no i don't shit i owe like three why do i look like that
your cheeks are red did someone punch you no i'm just i'm in a little flush uh the way i'm not
allowed to be flush in my own house all right where's the swimmer change the channel points
to make it so you have to say a dumb peepee poo poo joke no that's that would not i'm sorry
that's not gonna happen all right pool pool okay there it is is that him pick up skull please pick
up the skull and put skull down in diablo please oh yes this is pool ah ah can you make that sound
nope some people can i can't you go if you want to know how to do that you go like this
why are your cheeks ready you all right what happened to you why do you look like that have
you to tell me what's going on what happened ma i was trying to do the fucking water drop sound
okay i always know where your saw is hanging out when you're renovating that one's boring
probably yard sale is a big success but where's charlie yard sale is over here somewhere where
where are you charlie lots of money in here charlie charlie
okay gotta rock but where's charlie
charlie i'm pissing somebody off so fucking much by saying this
i'm like just hitting somebody's like a trigger point in their brain with just like
fuck up oh i hate it where's where's this guy though seriously
glasses wait don't need glasses what something going on in this house i need to do definitely
the signal's bad right he wants to watch tv got the saw yeah it says like oh he wants to watch tv
but the signal is bad that's being tailgated so you very wanted to but what the no signal for
the tv i'd like to play a game oh somebody said pre-pre-game by the way it's been two and it's
like two and a half hours oh shit whoops i like the sounds who else can we look for what do i need
five more all right veto is halfway to hearing his fortune whatever that means this plant wants
to use radio waves to communicate okay squirrel use its cuteness to persuade passerby to give
it fresh food passersby it's got to be somewhere over here squirrel where's the squirrel that was
in the food got you there i told you you guys were like what are you talking about
you need a squirrel if i was a squirrel where would i be in a tree near a bird
in a bird's nest no all right what's going on in here got you oh i got that's jolly i don't know
i'm just asking out loud all right three more when i suddenly the squirrel who are you mama
loves the sound of electricity so much all right we got a 5g brain here elif can't stand that
ugly statue her husband put in their garden didn't i see that over here it's a big ass
statue over here somewhere where is it you know i'm talking about right was like over here there
is got it two more squirrel is this a male too some say that opening ghost mail will curse
you for a thousand years that also land you a thousand days in prison because it's a federal
fence it's a squirrel nothing
you know why i'm laughing but i i can't say it apparently i'm i cannot tell you why i just
left that's one of the forbidden things phrases driver dave all right driver dave is being
tailgated by somebody where right there right dave that you this guy's pretty close
tail right there
all right we just need to find the ghost mail or mysterious pyramid shaped object still needs
to be delivered fortune teller terry is still a few blocks away or someone wants to dance
he's waiting for the music to kick in didn't i turn on music over here somewhere i did oh ghost
mail i went stay here for a second though because this i turned on a stereo didn't i yeah it's right
here got it what's next why are you still playing this i don't know but did i seriously just shut
just shut off the citadel reactor with my toe i'm gonna be so what the fuck is this all right
last level last level and then we'll do something else last level and then we'll do something else
i can't be megaman legends i can't i'm sorry it's too late i took too long by the first one i don't
uh yeah i don't have the first one that's true yeah fuck fuck you're right i can't play i can't
play megaman legends because god damn it i only have the second one fucking idiot i'm so stupid
why would i do that that's all we can do it next time we'll do it now we'll do it later
that's a good point fuck i'm so stupid sometimes i'm an idiot all right a real businessman stays
up to date folks the bad day for this beggar people have stopped using her metro entrance okay
there it is right here i mean the people clearly look like they're using this entrance maybe
there's another one metro there it is okay i'm gonna sneeze i just want to give you a large
at least probably 60 second warning it's gonna happen any second it's gonna happen is that
businessman businessman businessman businessman businessman staying up to date businessman
we're handing out uh papers businessman right here somewhere this i mean this person is just
standing up there all right well businessman staying up to date businessman shit no what are
you doing up there who are you no you can't get away i with the glasses what was that how the
fuck is this guy got it okay i don't even what do i need two more and then we'll move on to
something else but what are we gonna do though what are we gonna do it's tricky i don't know
this is just a few options georgio is leaving no he isn't yes he is no he isn't yes he is no he
isn't there was a guy getting out of the train off the train out of a bus off the bus like that
who talked to transformer we'll see i don't know not doki fucking doki doki literature club
that's never gonna happen guys the only way that happens is if i lose a stupid bet like this
if i don't find the toolbox in the next 30 minutes i will play doki doki literature club
for at least 30 minutes okay good go toolbox is so happy builders couldn't carry it up
so
someone left their sexy sacks in the cargo hold
it's trash why would i want to get trash all right gani forgot his stuff at the bus stop but
no worries he's got a round trip ticket and he's on his way back all right here he comes off the
bus stop i think that's probably his stuff wait for him how about drew crew no no i'm not feeling
drew crew right now replace wink with open doki doki literature club and close it no that's just
a waste of bandwidth that means i have to go spend the data and the bandwidth and the internet tubes
to download that game open it and then close it and then uninstall it that's just a waste of
internet is this guy gonna come back and get his shit or what this is very clearly just stuff you
left at the bus stop where do you get this game it's on steam it's called hidden folks where is
this person got that found georgio stay here he's gonna get off the bus and and is this stuff
over here let's get a big view play a game please what is what is the what am i doing right now
is this this is not a game dude come on like when are you gonna play a game cause it's not a game
playing tag with your friends is a game doing a like a sudoku in the newspaper is a game
play tag on stream no where is this guy to get his stuff all right fucking give me this is a
children's book this is a video game that i purchased on steam the platform that sells video
games dump king dlc or chat makes fun of you i'm old for that i know i don't i don't have it in me
to do that right now visual novels yeah all right wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait i'm
about to i'm about to throw this right back at you here this is this is not a game but a visual
novel is it can we explain that to me for a second yes so reading pictures on a screen
with text is a video game but this is not i think you guys seriously to re-evaluate what a
what a video game is to you guys look up the definition of a game it's a game i can make up
a game right now first person that says one out loud wins the game one i won my game that i just
made up that was a fun game i actually didn't you guys did this i already said it before me
all right what are we doing what are we what are we what are we i'm done with this game it was fun
i'm done with this game i'm done with this game that was a good game oh my god on my floor of
video game lost his own game resident evil 2 remake claire b i don't even have that installed
i did i got the toolbox look i'll prove it there it is i never lied about mega man legends yeah
because mega man here's the thing about mega man legends i got my anniversaries tonight
and i can't be late so uh starting mega man legends right now would be not very good because
i would probably stay here and uh kim and i have a reservations and if i'm like yeah let me just
keep playing mega man legends because i'm gonna do that in one stream the game's only like six
hours seven hours long so uh get the fuck out of here no no not yet i'm we're good this is tonight
this is a little bit a little bit later this is a circus restaurant all right let me see what we
got here what's that hmm taking her to chuck e cheese now that's too fancy for me that's too
fancy all right what have i got what have we got on steam either that or i'm gonna put in i you know
what yeah you know what uh you know what it's all right uh all right if i start mega man legends
right now i'm not gonna be able to finish it i'm saying this is supposed to be its own thing and
then we'll have to put this in somewhere no yeah no that's i'm only gonna be able to play this for
like two or three hours pops it's a shitty game what all right we'll do let's do talk to transformer
let's just hang out let's hang out maybe we'll do a couple of tier lists too might as well
all right let me get out of here this was fun i liked this i enjoyed that all right let's get uh