Why, hello there. How are you? How you doing? Moving the ice cube around in my drink. Hold on.
This is a big ice cube. I like big ice cubes though. Who cares? Hi, welcome to another stream.
Me, Jerma. How you doing? Who cares? How big are the ice cubes? All right, the best part about a
huge ice cube is it takes so long to melt. That doesn't dilute your drink. How do I feel? Okay,
so I feel... Let me go over my sort of COVID story, I guess. So, I think I'm over it. I have
to test again to see if I'm still kind of shedding the virus, but I lost my sense of taste and smell
for a little while, which that's scary, because who knows with that, right? I'm still a little
sloppy. I would say I'm not sick anymore. I have a residual cough, like kind of deep in my throat,
in my kind of chest area, but I wouldn't say that I am sick. I was sick. I'm definitely,
I'm definitely over it, but maybe not completely. Yeah, I just kind of feel sloppy. But yeah,
I'm doing better. And here we are. We are going to do a couple things today. Well, couple by one,
I have a very important thing to talk about with Origin. I told you and everyone thought I was
crazy, but it was true. So, today we're going to play The Sims 4. No mods, no additional modded
content. And I think there's a couple of reasons why. Every single time I've played The Sims on
stream, an hour goes by and people start killing each other. That's my, that's every single one of
my streams for The Sims. So, I've never really experienced any of these expansions. And I got
a lot of them. I have almost everything. So, if I have the mods installed, I'm going to be tempted
to use them. And that includes like the funny faces mods. I want to do a vanilla Sims 4 with
every expansion play. I won't, I can't ever do it. It's like playing GTA and you get through the
second or third story mission and then you just start doing the cheats and you don't even play
the rest of the game. You just run around and just fly around with like the mods and stuff.
I don't even play the game. This man doesn't know that non-murder mods exist. I know, but
I cannot install the like the drug mod yet. Which by the way, if you, and I will say this,
the hardest I've ever laughed in the ever that I've ever streamed. If you want to know the one time,
I think I've said it before, the hardest I've ever laughed on stream to a point where it physically
caused me discomfort and hurt me. I don't know if there's any clips of it. It was a long time ago.
It was a guy was on drugs with the drug mod and he walked his dog in his house
and the dog like pissed on the ground. It started like rolling around in it.
I know that that whole concept was just unbelievable that you would put like, oh,
put like the leash on the dog and walk your dog in your house. I think that's the, I think that
gave me a hernia. I think that's the day that I got it and it developed. I actually believe that.
I remember having to wheel away from the computer because it hurts so much to even be in this room.
And that was a lot, not this room. That was a long time ago. You can't get a hernia like that.
I don't know, man. This, this hiatal hernia that I have, I feel like I gave it to myself somehow.
Can you start playing? We're just hanging out for a second. Hold on.
You're going to play The Sims 2. We played The Sims 2 earlier this year.
I don't know. Do I, this is where I'm going to leave this up to you to help me.
I don't think I'm, I'm just going to make some random guy, right? I was going to make a random
person. I don't think I wanted to be like, oh, making like Jerma and it's going to be like the
Jerma house. No, no, no. We're just going to, we're going to pick a guy and we're going to play as
random guy. I've done the, hey, it's Jerma playing in The Sims, Jerma985. I've done that like 10 times.
We played all of them except for two. What? Didn't I play The Sims 2 earlier this year?
That was, that was The Sims. No, it was The Sims 2. But I don't know what I want to do because I,
it's overwhelming and I got to say something to Origin and EA. Guys, why is there, why is there
not an option? Should I even do this? I feel like everyone's waiting for me to do this.
Is everybody waiting for this? Everyone's like leaning back. Here he goes. He's going to,
he's going to talk about there's no cart on Origin for 20 minutes. I feel like everyone
just leaned back and was waiting. Do I need to, I don't think I even need to do this right now.
No, I don't think so. I'm going to, okay, I'll do it in one sentence instead of like 25 sentences.
So we're going to do that in one sentence instead of doing a 25 sentence explanation of what I mean
by this. So here comes the one sentence to explain this and it goes as follows. There is no add to
cart option when you're trying to buy shit on Origin for The Sims. There's like a hundred things
to buy individually. There's no Omega bundles. There's bundles with like three things in it out
of a hundred. How is there no cart? How is it? I just don't get it. And people said, dude, just
buy it on Steam. Listen, I already bought like five or six expansions on Origin. So I was like,
I guess I'll just do it on Origin. And I had to, I had to tell my bank, I got texted by my bank.
Hey, we've declined purchases. There's like all these like fraudulent purchases going through the
EA store. Like, no, that's me. That's me and it's dumb. I was individually buying every one of these
things. I was, dude, I was sitting there. I thought I was crazy. I'm like, there has to be a different
way to do this on Origin. I was like looking up like adding things to cart Origin. I don't, why?
You have to go through the checkout process on each individual. Oh, one sentence. Shit.
I'm sorry. Oh my God. I didn't, I didn't realize I was doing that. All right. All right. All right.
All right. All right. We're done. We're done. We're done. We're done. We're done. We're done.
Fuck. Oh, I'm like embarrassed. That was at least 20 sentences. That was more than 25. Okay. All
right. All right. All right. Enough, enough, enough. We're going to play The Sims 4.
Oh shit. You know, it's like, you just know that you just get called out with something
and it's completely true and it just makes you angry. No. Hey, we got to take, we're going to
take the dollhouse out of the, out of the title. People are going to see German dollhouse and
they're going to go, what? This is another dollhouse. Oh, we got to get that out of the title.
Okay. Hold on. Origin doesn't have a shopping cart like that. Items are all purchased one
time for the origin store. The only exception would be the build your own bundle option.
What? Build your own bundle. Build your own bundle. Where is that? Where is build your own bundle?
Is this a pizza place? What do you mean build your own bundle? The bundle is three items at once
though. Build your own bundle. I don't, if it's available, it's not advertised at all.
I was looking for it everywhere. All right. Okay. I can one of the mods change that title
to something that I spent two hours individually buying all these DLCs. You better enjoy. That's
better. Build your own bundle. I'm so annoyed and I'm going to get over it. All right. So let's go.
And I know I'm going to get the comments of like, Oh dude, but like, Oh yeah. You just want to be
able to click one button and spend a thousand dollars. It's like, I, I don't want to do that.
I just want to add stuff to cards. I don't need like the, the kitten costume pack. I don't want
that. I just want the stuff that I want, but I don't want to individually buy every single one
of them. But I think, you know what? I think I did buy like the pet costume pack. I don't know why,
but I did. He said we get started and people are going to be, I got to, I'm going to preemptively
tell you this. Um, just so you understand. Yes. Yes, there is. It is a, it is a different. Did I
tweet? Did I tweet this yet? I did. All right. What's on the screen? Jesus. All right. Here comes a
new game and let me turn the camera on. Everyone's going to freak out. All right. Okay. Everyone's
going to lose their mind. Yes. It is a new angle. It's a new, there is a new camera angle today and
people are going to think there's like a, there's a monster's not coming out of this door. I just
want to make sure everyone understands. I'm not in a new, this is not a new house. This is not a new
place. And a monster's not coming out of this door. Okay. Why are you so red? Because I'm a,
I don't know. I've, I've, I don't know. Where's the red shelf? It's, I'm going to put something
here instead. I just, I wanted to change some shit around. I wanted to move the room around.
You know, when you just kind of feel like, you know, the room is getting stale, the room's a
little stale. I want to make this better, right? You just kind of have to change it up. That's how
it happened. Anyways, is the camera delayed? Somebody's saying the camera's behind. It really
shouldn't be. Let's find out why. Is it behind? And audio slightly. Really? That's weird. Is it
behind? Maybe not. I just don't think I move my lips that much sometimes when I talk. The audio's
behind. Is it? That's weird. I don't know. I don't know why I can do this, but I can. I can't escape.
All right, let's go. Can you hear it? You guys can hear it, right? All right. We're going to,
we're going to make a sim and we're going to play. I don't know. There's like werewolves and shit.
I got the werewolf expansion. I don't know what to do. Okay. So hello. We'll do the name last.
And should there be more than one person in this house? Skip 10 hours. We're not going to spend,
I'm telling you, I promise we're going to spend 20 minutes in the character creator, maybe 15
total. Maybe. I already kind of like it. You need to have a dog too. I don't want to do a bunch of
animals because every time there's ever been animals, it's like they make like seven and
there's like five to seven animals in the house. And it sucks because it's like, it's like,
there's too many animals in the house. Just one pet. All right. Maybe we'll do one. All right.
First of all, I gotta remember how to play this game. I think, I don't think I want to do anything
else. I think this is perfect. I don't know why I like this. That's not me. I don't look like this.
Yeah. There's no, there's no slider mods. We're just doing straight up regular The Sims. I want
to keep the hair. I think the hair is perfect. What do you mean? I lied already. It's got to be
okay. I want him to, I want him to, why am I so red? That's weird. I just looked over here and saw
that. I want it to be a little weird, but I don't want it to be crazy. I don't want it to be insane
looking. Holy shit. Okay. I like it so far. Hold on. What do you think? I think that's good.
What about the shoulders? I don't know. I'm kind of torn between the wide. All right. This is,
you gave him reptilian eyes. All right. What about, those are small feet. How tall is this?
Let me look at the hair. I don't know. This looks pretty good. I think I'm all right with this one.
All right. He's going to have huge forearms and small biceps. I think that's fine. Big hands.
I need to make his hands as big as they can possibly be. How do I pick his hands?
What are the aspirations going to be? This is going to be interesting. How do I give him big
hands? You can't. Oh, okay. All right. I need, we got to do clothes. Okay. That looks good. All
right. Clothes. I really, I don't care about the clothes that much. It kind of looks like he would
be on Pee Wee's Playhouse. All right. How about just outfits? How about, oh, styled looks. Oh,
what? I made, I got the, the Star Wars shit. I could make him like a Jedi. Is that like a path
you can take? Can I get, I can, I can give this guy a lightsaber and that's not modern. I swear.
What is this? After party. No, no, no, no. This is every day, right? Oh, wait. I don't, is this a
fanged and wild? Oh, it's a werewolf. Am I going werewolf right off the bat? I don't know if I'm
doing werewolf. These are all werewolves. Okay. Something about this is what I actually kind of
like. You made Adam Sandler. What? No, I'm going to hate this after like 15 minutes. Something else.
I got to finish the face. Get the, we got to get the hat off or maybe not. No, he can't just
be like a weirdo. Why is this locked? First order rank three trooper. You're going to be a storm
trooper? Is that a career path? That's all right. I'm sticking with this. So what is this? This is
party. Okay. This is for a party. Okay. All right. Summertime. You're going to keep the
glasses. All right. This is fun. I think this is all right. Every day. I don't like them.
Please change the outfit. We can change the outfit later. All right. We need to make personality now.
All right. Aspiration, family, food, location, knowledge, nature, wellness, werewolf. Okay.
These Sims get an initial relationship boost when introducing themselves to werewolves.
Do I have to talk to other werewolves? They get Star Wars. Wait, what? Sims who are prepared
voyagers fill up their needs slightly when, God, this is perfect. Hope versus order or galactic
privateer. This Sim isn't about choosing sides. They're happy just mingling among the smugglers
and bounty hunters on the fringe planet of Batuu. Burning a few extra credits along the way is just
a bonus no matter how they get them. Okay. On the world of Batuu, there is a growing conflict.
This Sim, there's no Star Wars shit in this, in real life. What? Is this just, I'm like a fan of
Star Wars or am I actually going to be like a lightsaber wielding attacker? You know, with the,
why can I not say the, why can I not say the fucking word? Bounty hunter. I'm just a bounty
hunter. This is, okay. This is Jedi. Which one of these gets me a lightsaber? The left one. Okay.
Understand whether they should stand with the resistance of the first order. All right. You
got it. That's, okay. That's what we're doing. That's what we're doing. All right. So what else?
Likes and dislikes. Activities. And you know what? You love bowling. You know why? Because I bought
the expansion. How do I add it? Okay. Does that mean you like it or you don't like it? Okay.
Okay. You like bowling? What else? How about rock climbing? You can choose up to 20.
Is there a lightsabers or something? I like lightsabers. What else is there? Favorite color
is Sith. I'm a Sith Lord. Okay. Favorite music genre. Excuse me. Where's video game music?
Lullabies? Where's video game music? How about romance music? Dude, retro music. Yep. Doesn't
like pop. How about activities? Definitely comedy. Do kids radio? Wait, you can do kids radio?
Okay. All right. So, so far we're okay. So what about activities? You like bowling? You like
acting? No, no, no. You like mischief? You like playing the piano? And you don't like singing?
And you don't like video games? You like writing? And you like snowboarding? And you think rocket
science is cool, but you don't like the pipe organ? And you like programming on the side?
Rock climbing is kind of fun, but you don't like it that much. You actually hate it.
Okay. What else? All right. Traits. Hot headed. Loomy. Genius. All right. What did we, what's,
okay. It's going to have to be something like self-assured, right? Confident. If you're going
to be a Jedi, then you have to be pretty confident. I would imagine you'd be pretty confident. Bookworm?
Geek. Oh, I just voice cracked a little. All right. So you're self-assured. You're kind of a geek.
I mean, if you're choosing as your career to be a Star Wars Jedi master, you have to be a nerd,
right? That's not, that's not an insult. That's just, I mean, you kind of have to be a geek,
right? How about a perfectionist? How about lazy? Make a lazy Jedi? A squee, oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no. We need like squeamish. How is he going to handle the Sith Lord? So he's going to see
somebody get like slashed with a lightsaber and just start puking. All right. Proper cat lover.
I think this is good. I think this is good. Think of a vegetarian. I don't, I don't, I don't know
a name. What's a good name? Hello, my name is, I don't know. What's like a, what's a good name?
John? No, John, that's.
You just said what a Sim says in conversation. You did. That's just, that means like, hello,
Blork Snorkels. I'm going to say this out loud because I think this is a very terrible name
for a Sim, but I do enjoy the comedic effort for Jerkel Hoffman. I do appreciate the effort.
Effort is there. How about, no, I'm not going to name him Stinky Dinky. I always have such
trouble with names. I just can't do them. Bobby Tom Tatooine? No, that sucks. No, I'm not going
to name the guy Bobby Jerkoff. He's not going to be named Jerkoff anything. Not Bobby Jerkoff,
not Jerkoff Stevenson. I'm sorry. That's not this person's name. So we're going to like move on.
We're moving on. What's a Bobby, Bob, Bill, Bill Solo. That's even worse. How about, what was it,
Blorg, Blorg's, Blorg Solo? I like Blorg Solo. How about Blorg McDonald's? This is the hardest
part. I can't do it. I hate this. Blorg Hendrix, Blorg McNulty. Do we like Blorg McNulty? That seems
actually pretty good. OK, we got Blorg McNulty. Who's next? We have to do a pet, right? We have
to make a dog. One dog, one dog, no cats, one dog. I'm not making 10 animals. It's hard to take care
of them all. It's going to be a poodle. It has to be a Star Wars looking dog. You know what I mean?
How do I make like a Star Wars character? Can I make like the legs bigger and stuff?
I need to make like a Star Wars monster. There's no body slider enhancements or anything. So
I can't do those right now. All right. I like it so far. What about ears? Hold on.
I think it has to stay this way. It has to stay that way. Yeah. The dog's name is going to be
Chewie. It looks like Otto. OK, I think Chewie's fine. Is that too much? Is it too weird? OK,
how do I change the coat? I think that's fine. Think of a green dog. Chewie's not green.
This looks strange. No, this doesn't make any sense. It's Yoda. That's actually. All right.
Yeah. No, it's going to be like yodel, right? I'm not getting sued. This is yodel. You don't
need. You just yodel. Yodel. That's it. Yodel. All right. What do you like? Smart. What is this?
Oh, OK. Smart troublemaker. Aggressive. I don't want it. Hunter. Jedi. Active. Smart. And no,
not vocal. Special effects dog. Yeah, you guys can key this dog out whenever you want.
Whenever you feel like it. I think yodel. Yodel. Yodel is fine. I don't look. I want to play the
video game right far too many times that I've opened this game. We make a bunch of weirdos
and then they all attack each other and stab each other and shoot each other. Well, I we need to
play the Sims. You know what I mean? We need to keep these people around. And it happens within
like an hour. And then I sit around. Do you remember last time I played this when an hour
went by, they started killing each other and then I dropped two meteors on their house.
And then I was like, I don't know what to do now. Like, I can't play the game anymore. I can't play
it. There's no you don't go make macaroni and cheese after that. It's over. You don't go back
and like, yeah, I guess I'm going to queue up, go to the fridge, take a shower and take a bath.
No, no, you can't. We can't go that way. Why do you look like this? I don't know. Do the deal.
Yeah, we're going to do DLC. All right. This is the house. We've got the dog. We've got the guy
and I'm done. I'm not micromanaging 10 people. It's impossible. What the fuck did somebody
just post? Your webcam audio is late. What is happening? Are you guys for real? All right,
I'm ready. Let's take this household. We have everything we need. It's the McNulty family.
Wait, I want a different pose. How do I do a different pose? I like that one. It's off by
a split second. I don't know why that would be the case. Hold on. Oh, I do know why it's off.
It is off your. Yeah, it is because of the delay coming through. No, it's not. No, it's not. It's
not. It's not fun. Is it? Am I? Is it one guy? OK. Oh, is it early? I thought I had a delay,
but I didn't. All right. So this is important. It's very important. I have like every expansion
I have no idea where to go or what to do. What season should this be? Spring is a great time
to plant your garden to take advantage. I don't know. We're not doing that. Temperatures are
climbing, so beat the heat with water balloons and sprinklers. Watch out for the thunderstorms.
All right. That's kind of cool. Gather your garden. No, no garden. When you're not bundled
up indoors, have some fun in the snow and ice. All right. Summer or fall, summer or winter.
I mean, can we get a poll in the chat? Let's get a poll. Summer or winter.
Pick one. Whoever gets more wins. You got to pick one that shouldn't have been on.
So did my mic sound fucked up because that literally should not have been turned on?
Are we good now? It actually probably sounds better now. Winter is winning by a landslide.
Oh, my God, it is. OK, yeah. Let me just double check there's not some weird setting that I turned
on. I don't think there is. No, I don't have any like filters on. I don't have any delays on.
Everything's set to be not delayed or anything. That's so weird. I wonder why.
All right. Winter. I bought a bunch of winter packs too. I have no idea. This is so overwhelming.
I'm not going here. That's what I know. Newcrest, Magnolia, Promenade, Windenburg,
Sand, Forgotten Hollow, Del Sol Valley, Glimmer Brook, a mountain, Moonwood Mill.
Go to Forgotten Hollow. OK, this looks like a werewolf one. Go to Glimmer Brook.
The quiet town of Glimmer Brook may have more to it than meets the eye.
But do I want to do a bunch of weird shit right off the bat? This is like a map.
This place sucks. There's one place to live. What? There's one house and a bar.
Only one person gets to live here? Well, there's a magical portal. That's kind of cool.
How do I go back? What's the other one? All right. This is like a scary place.
It's like Halloween town. This place. This place. It looks weird. It's weird. Two story.
This place is it's eighteen thousand dollars. Yeah, but people can visit you from around the
world, right? Now we're starting. We're starting normal. I can move to one of these places.
Keep that in mind. What about what's this? Oh, look at this. This place is a bustling town.
How much does this place cost? Oh, look at this one. So where is this? Starlight Boulevard. Have I?
Sims cannot live on this residence. Didn't I do a thing where I was trying to be like a famous
person? Was that Sims 3? No, this place sucks. Boo boo boo. Go to the mountain. Let me check it out.
Oh, look at this place. It's got a ski resort. This is only two grand. This is perfect. I think
I want to do the mountain town either. OK, it's a toss up here. All right. I'm going to give you some
choices here. The mountain town. What's this? Wow. Wow. This is unbelievably beautiful here.
There's a big fountain. It's like a port. I think I think I'm making my decision. I'm going to buy
this place right on the beach. I'm doing a beach house. You can batches me all you want. That's
fine. Hold on. All right. This is kind of a city. We can visit this place, right? We can visit.
I'm doing a beach. The beach. Yeah, beach. I'm going for it. Let's go. It's time. Unfurnished.
I'm going to build the house. Bat chest. I got we got eighteen thousand dollars. It's winter.
Yeah, but I'll be I'll prepare for the where's my where do I build?
Oh, this is I don't want to wait. This is where I have to build right on the water.
Wait, where's my house going to be? That's kind of I don't know. I don't know about that.
This is it. Look at this. Look at this neighborhood. All right. We'll go for it.
We'll go for it. If I don't like it, I'll just fucking do the cheat and bulldoze it and go
somewhere else. All right. Build time. Let's go. Challenge yourself. No, thank you. This is new
music. All right. First things first. We got to do the right angle here and I want to be able to
literally just look out my window and there's the water. You know what I mean? Right here.
OK, this is a mailbox. Yep. All right. Let's do it. OK, here we go. This lot is not that big.
There's not very much space. OK, let's start with just right here.
I don't want to blow all my money. Hold on. Wait, don't do that. How about like this?
How do I flip? How do you flip something? Is it middle mouse? How do you flip something?
How do you flip? L? What are you doing? How would you do that? How do you flip something?
R? No. Period. There it is. Thank you. This is going to be much bigger.
How much money do I have? I don't blow everything. All right. So this is going to be
the kitchen kind of bathroom area. Oh, shit. I'm putting it. All right. Well,
that's actually makes sense, right? How do I do the angle pitch? What's upstairs?
All right. This is fine right now. Make it a little bit bigger this way and then a little
bit bigger this way. I only have 15 grand. Period. Now, how do I like, you know, like
go like this? All right. Now I need steps to get up here. How do I just do steps this way?
Actually, I don't hate that, though. Hold on. Comma. No, I want to pitch the camera.
OK, now I need a door here. I need to put the walls up. A set button.
Use the Sims 3 camera is in the settings. Is it actually game camera? Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Thank you so much. What a million times better thing to do.
That's what I was looking for. Yeah, there it is. All right. We're good.
OK, now I need to put the I need to put the walls up.
Helper Andy's. How do I put the walls up, please? It's not period. Page up and page down.
Thank you. All right. I need a door. I don't know. I don't hate that.
This is like how to get to the kitchen in a restaurant. I'm going to put that for the
kitchen door. I do have like every expansion, so there's just a ton of random doors.
Wait, wait, I need a Star Wars door. First Resistance blast door.
Now, this is lame. This is too. This is lame to start with that VIP door elevator.
It has to be something interesting, but not weird, right? How about how?
OK, that look at that. That looks all right. I need it outside.
I did. OK, I need wallpaper. All right. This is for the outside of the house.
OK, no, no, no, no. Just something solid like paint siding. Here it is. No, no.
It's a beach house. There we go. That's pretty beachy.
Yeah, I'm going to have such a cool you understand my back deck and back patio
and everything is going to be so awesome. It's going to be a huge thing.
It's going to go down. All right. So now I need to do this.
I don't know. I don't like how this looks, though. I don't care. Page down.
All right. I need to start to think about this.
You're going to walk right into the kitchen. So here we go. Let's get this blocked off.
All right. So I'm thinking kitchen is going to be boink.
Bathroom is going to be boink. Living room is going to be boink.
And bedroom is going to be boink. I think that makes sense to me.
All right. What did you say? I think that would make sense to me.
It's a Minecraft house. Yes. All right. All right. First things first.
I need to do this in order because I always do this wrong.
I need a kitchen area. Stone is a Minecraft house. It needs to be beachy.
I'm thinking, you know, yellows, oranges, blue, light blue, light blue, yellow, right?
Let's just go with the wallpaper. Just a solid color.
How do I just do a solid color? Oh, here it is. My paint.
All right. Wait, this is kind of beachy. Sandy. Yep. Look at that.
Right to about here. That looks good.
And then let's get a little bit of blue in here like this.
Okay. Remember, it's a beach house. Why is it invisible?
It's not. There's no light in here.
Okay. Dude, I'm telling you right now. Guess what's going on the wall.
Can you tell me what I'm going to put in here? I'm going to put a ship wheel on the wall.
I'm going to have a ship steering wheel on the wall. All right.
G hides the grid. Thank you. That's actually really helpful.
Floors. Floors. Floors. Floors. Floors. It's pretty beachy.
That's pretty beachy. It kind of looks like you pulled a carpet up
and that's just the wood with the glue all over it. Don't matter.
You need windows. I'm getting there. Hold on.
I have to make. Wait, I want a huge bay window looking at the water.
Can you imagine? How big can I make this?
Now that's kind of cool. That's pretty cool.
Poster house. I don't even know what that means.
You can make big objects bigger or smaller.
What the? Holy shit.
Okay. Wait a minute. I didn't know you could do that.
Oh my goodness. All right. Well, it's not going to fit.
That's insane. All right. I think that looks fine.
Now I need. We got to do the floor in here. Remember, one of the. Wait.
Where's the bathroom? Bathroom is definitely not going to be here.
A full window. No, no, no, no, no, no. Bathroom will be here.
Section that off right now. There we go.
All right. So this is, you know, the little area to kind of hang out.
Living room, bathroom, bedroom right here.
Let's do bathroom. Let's get bathroom out of the way.
I want tile tiles. I don't like tile. I like tile.
Get over it. Hmm. Beachy though.
This look. I like that. No, I don't.
It's like a public bathroom. Oh, no, that's cool.
Yeah. Now we need wallpaper for the bathroom.
What are you guys thinking? How come this Halloween music?
I don't know why this. Yeah.
It's just whatever the Sims music is cycling through right now.
Hmm. Should we tile on the wall? How about masonry?
Ooh. Yeah. It is like scary music.
It's because of the werewolf expansion turned on.
I think it's because the werewolf expansion is currently active.
I don't mind this. Look at that. That looks kind of cool.
Kind of. No. It's a solid color for now.
How about like something light? Light.
Yeah. Who cares? It doesn't matter.
All right. So that's the bathroom. This is the what should I do for this?
Fucking cop it. Oh, I want to tell you something.
So Holly and I were laughing on the couch the other day because she told me
that I have a catchphrase that I do.
I she's like, you say this all the time.
I was like, what are you talking about?
She's telling me that, hey, you know, you say that a lot.
I'm like, say what? Apparently I don't.
I have a catchphrase between me and my girlfriend that I don't even realize I have it.
And apparently I say like, oh, fucking like, garlic, garlic, kid.
Oh, yeah. Give me some fucking garlic, dude.
For no reason, apparently. And I'm like, no, there has to be a reason
of why I'm saying like, oh, fucking garlic.
I just do like a Boston accent joke and I say garlic.
But I don't I don't know why I'm saying it.
And I'm like, well, no, it's something that garlic is on screen.
You know, somebody mentions garlic. She's like, no, no, you just be sitting around.
You just look over to me and go like, oh, fucking garlic, kid.
I'm like, there's no way I do that. It's impossible.
But apparently I have a catchphrase that I did not know I had until literally two days ago.
Fucking garlic, dude. I don't know why.
And I'm like, why would I say that? She's like, I don't know.
You just do. And now that I think about it, I kind of like I kind of do that.
Oh, fucking garlic, dude. I don't know why.
No, no, not floor tiles. I actually I don't like wooden floors.
They're so noisy and it's so I hate them.
I know that's the modern thing to do right now is, oh, man, wood floors wouldn't mean authentic wood.
When you step on a wood floor, it goes like this.
Every single time you put your feet down and sometimes randomly,
randomly, you'll be lying in bed and you will hear this at four o'clock in the morning.
And go, what was that?
That just makes they just loud. It makes sounds that they could expand. I don't I hate them.
It's called slippers. It's noisy.
It's noisy and it sound bounces off of it.
I like fucking carpets, dude, just like I like garlic.
How do I turn the camera off? I forgot I redid this whole setup so I can't escape.
I have to sit here and live with what I just did.
Yeah, carpets are gross if you don't take care of them.
All you guys saying carpets smell like puke and stuff.
Are you wearing your shoes in those rooms?
Take your shoes off before you get on the carpet and vacuum it every so often.
For God sakes, if you spill an entire two liter of coke on the ground,
you're going to need to clean it.
You're going to need to get in there and clean up the carpet.
You don't just move something of rug over it.
Nah, dude, nah, you're fucked up. Every carpet smells like puke.
Did you puke on it and didn't clean it?
It's called vacuuming. It's called cleaning.
And it's called don't not wearing your shoes in the room where the carpets are.
OK, let's do carpet.
What's with all these patterns here?
Wait, why? What's with these patterns?
Oh, there it is. OK.
And I'm just going to go. We're just going to go standard.
Yeah. OK, let's get some objects.
13 grand through the kitchen.
Why is it getting weirder?
Music seems all right. I don't want to do anything too crazy.
You want to spend money on the cookware, though.
Right. So you don't burn the house down.
Oh, I need windows.
Short classic casement.
That's fine. Right.
It's classic windows.
I don't think I need a window in this room.
This whole room is a window.
Maybe one or two here.
OK, you should use Linux.
All right. This whole room is a window.
No, I'm not putting any more windows in here.
There you go. There's your window.
And we'll do a bathroom window.
Like, no, no bathroom.
All right. Here we go. Kitchen stuff.
We got the fridge. We need a stove.
I need counters, too.
Remember, the theme is beach.
I think that's a that's a decent color, too.
Do two counters.
Stove is when you sink.
So let's do stove.
I don't want to lose all my money, but this is how you burn a house down.
So I'm thinking of going with London's choice.
Ooh, this is a London's choice.
Food quality seven, power consumption, reliability.
It's been plus cooking skill.
You need lights in here. I will.
It's the best place to get light.
How do I get lights?
It's lighting its own thing.
Objects by function lighting.
OK. Oh, this. Look at that.
All right. So let's do wall lights.
I'm a big fan of just basic lighting.
I don't like chandeliers.
I feel like they're going to drop on me and crush me like a cartoon.
I don't like them. They freak me out.
I don't like anything hanging.
I don't like ceiling fans.
Ceiling fans, they they scare me.
I feel like they're going to fall and just chop me up.
Anytime I've ever had a place where it's like, oh, there's a ceiling fan
literally right above the fucking bed.
It's just like, I don't want to turn that on.
Oh, let's turn it on high.
This is a helicopter blade that's about to drop.
I don't like them.
They think they kind of freak me out, even if they're installed properly.
I don't know. It's weird to me.
I'll just try to get a fan in the corner.
It just kind of right.
You like ceiling fans. It's up to you, but I don't like shit.
I don't like any hanging objects.
There we go. This is perfect.
Should we do ceiling lights or should we do on the wall?
These are probably the best, right?
Just do like two, three cans.
Wall lights are probably. You want to see wall lights?
No, I'm not doing fluorescent lights.
Oh, look at that. That's cute.
We'll do two of these.
Where are lights usually in houses?
You would like to stop and think.
Don't look in your room and don't look in your house.
What is it? Like, where does he?
What are your little lights on your walls besides the ceiling?
Right. Forget about the ceiling.
If you have like a like a wall, a wall light.
Like, where is it? Where does it go up on the ceiling?
Yeah, but you know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying about that?
Like above the door, right?
With a shelf in corners.
Yeah, I'm going to go like this.
We're going to do a cute shelf here, too.
Is this painted?
Look at how charming that is.
There's 30,000 people here.
What the? There are 30. What are you doing here?
Why are there so many people here?
What's going on? Why are there so many people here?
What the fuck? These are Minecraft torches.
That's fine.
Anyways, hi. How are you doing?
It's the Among Us waiting room.
Holy shit.
Oh, welcome everybody. Hi.
All right. So that's good.
I need to sink every time I buy.
No, don't do this, right?
Everyone just goes to the top left section
as buys the top left sink.
Don't in the Sims. They break every five minutes.
It just water just shoots out of them.
Bring up some extra cash here and buy a good one.
Yeah, like this one. This one.
What? This one here is like a hundred and twenty five.
No, no, no. You got to get plenty up here.
Yeah, like this one.
See, this one's nice and modern.
Could you please say the McGriddle in the scorn voice?
I understand that you're in your editing program.
You're in like Premiere
and you're hovering over this section of the video you're editing
where you're like, fuck, I really have to get them to say this.
It's like the last thing you have to implant in the timeline.
But I mean, I'm sorry.
We just you're going to have to you're going to have to wing it.
You're going to have to wing it.
All right, that's good.
Now I need a toaster oven.
Should I do one more counter?
Yeah, just in case.
What about a dishwasher?
No, they don't. They don't use it.
Put trash over here.
But you people need to be able to come in the fucking house.
Oh, my God. I'm so dumb.
It can't be anything here.
How about like this way?
I think that's good.
Yeah, that looks fine.
And then put like, you know, a coffee maker, a toaster oven,
all the appliances.
Let's see what we got.
Should I just install a subway into that?
I feel like this would be awesome.
Can you imagine if you just woke up in the morning
and went into your kitchen
and it was just like a subway station?
Somebody has to maintain this, though.
Can I actually make food with this?
If I remove everything here except the sink?
Is this can I make food here?
It's a beach house.
It's like a vacation house.
That's all right.
I think that looks that's all right.
Put a trash can right here.
Got it. All right.
Now we need a microwave and a coffee maker.
This one seems fine, but it's coming together.
Now I need a trash can.
Just a little bin right here.
Is it too big?
What about a little one?
This one?
Come on.
Really?
I don't like this weird space here.
I hate this so much and I can't I can't fix it.
That's okay.
I don't just I don't despise that.
And then we put a little table here.
Move the door one over.
That person is smart.
Well, I didn't want to do that.
Actually, that's kind of better.
I want to pick this up and move it.
Hold alt.
Oh my God.
Wait, I could just hold the mouse button down.
All right.
So that I can put this here then.
That's definitely better right in the corner.
Door will be moved.
I can get it to move.
All right.
I got to go into build mode, right?
I am in build mode.
How do I get this to move out of here?
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
And now I want to extend this out this way.
Can I not extend this out?
Oh, that's better.
All right.
Now this moves here and the door goes right there.
Perfect.
Okay.
Good.
And then just have a bathroom door.
Oh, God damn it.
I got to delete this thing.
Do I have a big barn door?
Hey, no, we're going all night.
So don't worry.
This stream is not going to be over in like an hour.
Don't worry.
I'm down to play this.
I'm here.
I got a nice clean room.
BB move objects on.
For the love of God.
Wait, what happened?
BB dot move objects on.
It's being spammed.
What does that mean?
What does BB dot move objects on?
Control shift C.
BB.
What am I doing?
BB dot move object.
What does this do?
Move objects cheat is on.
What does it do?
Did you just fuck up my achievements?
You can place objects anywhere.
I can't get Xbox achievements now.
Thanks.
Okay.
Let's get back to this.
Kitchen looks good.
Now we're almost ready to get started.
Remember, you're making the shittiest house I've ever seen in Sims 4.
That is a complete fucking lie.
Considering you've watched other streams of me play this game.
And they were way worse.
There were no windows.
It was one floor.
You've seen it before.
You saw it like a year ago.
You've already seen me play this.
This is a major marketed improvement from what I was doing before.
It's still one floor.
Oh, yeah?
Wait till you see what I've learned so far.
All right.
Let's go.
What about other little things here?
Fire prevention system utility?
Gotta have like a plant.
I don't know, a bowl of fruit or whatever that is.
Who cares?
All right.
Ooh, what's this?
A basketball.
Where's the thing that I want?
The ship wheel.
What is this?
No, wheel.
What?
I have to be level four actor to buy a ship pirate wheel?
I'm putting this right over the bed.
Cheat?
No, I'm not cheating.
I'm playing this legit.
Now I need bathroom stuff.
I need a light in the bathroom too.
I forgot.
Oh, there it is.
What the fuck is that?
All right.
No, no, we're not doing that.
We'll do these.
These are kind of fine.
That's better.
Then put a mirror right there.
And then, I don't know, have something else.
I need to be an actor level four.
That shouldn't take too long, right?
All right.
There's enough light in here.
I don't care.
Now I need toilet, bathroom, toilet.
All right.
There.
So public bathroom.
I want a public bathroom.
Can I do that?
How much is this?
This is $2,700.
You have a public bathroom.
If you need to go to the bathroom, you go outside
into the public bathroom.
That's fine.
I don't care.
I don't care about wasted money.
Dude, why would I even make a bathroom?
Just put a shower in the corner or something.
Who's going to clean this?
I don't- me?
Should I even have a toilet?
I don't think I'd buy a toilet if there's a-
just like a full public bathroom over here.
I'm going to hold off for now, but I'll get a shower.
Wait, hold on.
No, I can't have- what?
Why- what is this?
This is no shower?
You just spray yourself with water in the corner?
I'm very curious.
How does this work?
I need- I need it for now.
And then we have like a bathtub running out of money.
I only have $2,800.
All right.
I got to get more essentials.
Shower?
I need a sink.
Need a mirror.
This one's fine.
Just like a little medicine cabinet.
That's fine.
I need the walls up.
Oh, not that much.
I want to put this on the other wall.
Oh, fuck it.
Who cares?
How do I make this?
How do I make this lower?
Oh, there we go.
Does this have to be this tall?
Okay.
Well, whatever.
All right. Bathroom's good.
Oh, I need a door.
I'll figure- I'll figure that out in a minute.
All right.
This is the living room slash bedroom slash hangout zone.
First of all, let's get something out of the way here.
Let's get a nice rug.
I like the frog one.
That's pretty cool.
All right.
Don't run out of money.
Why is only half of this house-
What is going on here?
Why did it not paint the whole thing?
This-
All right.
Wait a minute.
Something's wrong here.
Oh, it's panels.
Where is it?
No, it's siding.
It's siding.
Can I not do that?
Oh, it just looks so weird.
Okay.
That was weird.
Doesn't it look like the same thing?
Is it the sunlight?
All right.
I need a roof.
Everyone will yell at me if I don't make one.
What kind of roof?
Does this cost money?
Make it so it only-
You bet your ass.
I put a fucking shitload of solar panels on this thing.
Just make sure-
Aim it directly to the sun.
Are there solar panels?
What if I'm going to flip it?
Actually, it wouldn't look so weird if it was flipped.
And then shrink it.
They were building two different houses when they got here.
All right.
No, no, no.
This is wrong.
Let's get rid of this.
I want it to look cool,
but I don't want it to be stupid looking.
Oh my.
Whatever.
That's not bad.
It just needs to be smaller.
Is it going into the house?
Wait.
The roof is going into the house.
This is wrong.
My god.
Whatever.
Just do a fucking regular ass roof.
Who cares?
Dude, no one even sees this.
No one even sees this.
It's never shown.
It just has to exist.
So who cares?
It's never shown.
It just needs to exist.
That doesn't matter.
It exists.
That's the only thing that matters.
If it exists.
I just heard my girlfriend laugh at me.
I heard her laugh.
I heard her.
I could hear it.
I heard it.
The movement sheets are fucking everything up.
I told you I didn't want my Xbox achievements to be messed up.
It's fine.
All right.
I just need to paint the outside.
Siding.
Look it.
It's fine.
It was an addition.
Place things better.
A lot of architect.
Okay.
So let's get in here.
Page down.
No.
Excuse me.
There we go.
All right.
So now I got bathroom set.
I just need to do just a little bit of entertainment and a bed and I'm done.
We can add to it later.
I just want a huge bed.
Can I make this like a quad?
Okay.
I kind of want the gigantic fucking bed.
How does somebody sleep in this thing?
Do they actually get in here and sleep in it?
I don't.
How?
That's a man-sized bed.
What happened to the stairs?
Excuse me.
Why did that happen?
There's no explanation for why that happened.
That's a man-sized bed.
All right.
I'm almost ready to start.
Any of the necessities that I need.
Maybe a TV, right?
Television.
Just a TV to have.
Just to have it.
All right.
I have 300 bucks.
It's time to go.
Let's play.
Bingo.
Start the game.
Here we are.
How are we going?
Hold on.
I got to turn it up a little.
It's a little low.
Oh my god.
I have to save this.
All right.
So what's this guy's name?
Lord McNulty.
Where am I going?
Chat with Jace.
What do I need?
Where are my needs?
Where am I going?
He's going to shoot me with a cannon.
So my house is right next to like a playground?
I've been to the Flaxfire Outpost on Batu.
I missed the text.
When you're ready to head to Batu,
click on your phone and select take a vacation.
And select Batu.
All right.
What do you want to do?
Play video games and listen to kids music.
Oh, well, this is...
Leave there, please.
Listen to kids music.
Wait, can I play on this stuff?
No, you can't.
Wait, I can.
I'm not doing that.
Fuck out of here.
I'm going up.
Why does he want to listen to kids music?
I should have waited.
Listen to kids music be one of his aspirations.
There's no bathroom door.
I got it.
He's got a bathroom.
He's got an old public bathroom down there.
All right.
You're good.
Let's go.
All right.
So first things first.
Where's the dog?
All right.
What are you up to?
You doing all right?
Give a $10 treat.
Can you not?
Oh, that's right.
I don't have the mod that means you can play as the pet.
Okay.
So let's go talk.
Let's go get to know the dog.
I think that's a good idea.
All right.
So I do want to go do the Star Wars thing because that's an aspiration.
Actually, I need to get a job first.
Do you actually use the public bathroom?
How do I make it go fast without having to click down here?
Is there a certain button combination?
Of all the expansions laughing my ass off, you're going to play Batuu.
Is that something wrong with that?
Friend.
Friendly.
Okay.
Who are you?
This is Hillary Lawrence.
Neighbor.
Should we talk about Star Wars?
I need to play video games.
Do you have any video games?
I hear a DS on you.
Is it really that bad?
Move the cam.
Oh, it's covering the needs.
You're it.
Yeah.
Should I put it up here?
I'm going to flip it horizontally.
People are going to freak out.
People are going to lose their minds right now.
No, no, no.
Top right.
Top right has info on it, though.
There's no information on the top left.
This is fine.
I'm just going to be flipped.
Oh, what'd you bring?
Gourmet fruitcake.
Why is everybody showing up right now?
You don't have to knock on the door.
We're standing.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
How do I eat that?
All right.
Invite everybody in.
Come on in.
Have you seen my dog, Yodel?
Everybody come on in.
This is a hazard.
Somebody could literally fall and break their ankle.
Please get in.
This is a hazard.
There's no handrails.
Someone's going to fall down and get hurt.
All right.
Say hello.
Come on in.
Where'd that fruitcake go?
Where's the fruitcake?
I don't have a fruitcake in my inventory.
Give it to me.
Where is it?
Pet obsessions.
Like almost all pets,
Yodel can get inexplicably obsessed
about things around the house.
Keep an eye on your furry companion.
What are you obsessed with?
A fridge?
Oh, there it is.
I'm going to put this up.
Yeah, I'm going to eat this later.
Why is he obsessed with the fridge?
Okay.
So I can eat that later.
Anybody know how to welcome wagon?
Oh, that's what it is.
Should I hire staff?
I'm going to serve brunch.
Eggs and toast.
How does this work?
Is it actually like a subway station?
This is actually dangerous.
Chorg.
Wixana.
Sarpah.
Yabba too.
Wanjini.
What am I making?
Holy shit, dude.
Relax.
Where's the herbs and cheese bread, man?
Come on.
Where's the Italians herbs and cheese?
Yodel is an active dog.
They will frequently run around.
Where'd you go?
Stay out of there.
Wait.
No, no, no, no, no.
I thought I was controlling the dog.
Wait.
Oh, I have a cooking skill.
You don't like dogs.
This shit is a fucking bad hole.
Wait, did I save it?
No.
Somebody help.
What are you standing there for?
You psychos.
Somebody help me.
I'm the new neighbor.
What do I do?
Put yourself out.
Quick.
Am I alive?
Okay.
What happened?
Holy fucking moly.
I just got money.
Who is this guy?
Did I fuck up my entire house already?
Would he just take out green sludge out of this?
Why did you just empty a whole can of peas?
Who are you?
Why are you in my house?
I'm venting about this.
Why would you eat?
What is the peas for?
You brought peas?
You're a lunatic.
If you bring a bowl of peas to somebody's house.
Just unprompted.
Oh, yeah.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
I dumped a can of peas in here.
Can I clean up?
Who's screaming?
Do you hear that?
Oh, you turned the TV on.
Okay.
Well, this is obviously destroyed.
That's great.
All right.
Fear of fire.
I wonder why he has a fear of fire.
No shit.
Okay.
We need to get this sorted.
First of all, I'm annoyed that you brought him here,
but I'm going to eat the peas.
Exy.
This is so weird.
I am burnt.
And nobody's checking on it.
Nobody's caring.
Send them home.
Well, I need to make friends in the neighborhood.
Yeah, I'm the guy that invited everybody over.
A new neighbor.
And burnt his house down with a fucking grilled cheese.
Whatever that was.
I don't even know what that was.
Eggs or toast?
I have to delete this stuff, though.
Because should I replace the floor?
Dude, that's what happens when you just jam.
God damn it.
How do I fix this?
Do I have to clean that?
You need a dog bowl?
Oh, fuck.
You're right.
Okay.
Do I have to replace the floor?
Just put a big rug there.
No, I have to replace the floor.
Probably like head hurts.
That was so fucking funny.
Okay.
What even is the floor here?
Which one of these?
I don't remember.
DIY job.
Sorry.
No, I don't have a stove.
Let me clean up first.
I'm going to take a thoughtful shower after that.
Extinguish fire.
Weird.
Is this going to come out?
People can see you.
What?
Because of this window.
Can you?
No, you can't.
All right.
I'll fix that a little bit later.
So I need to...
What's wrong?
You want to play?
All right.
I need a dog bowl.
You're just going to be permanently scared.
I probably am.
That was ridiculous.
I've never seen that happen before.
The first literally one minute of playing the game.
If you don't have a subway station for a stove
and get a guy that's never cooked before
to go pretend to be a chef on it.
Okay.
I need a dog bowl.
Where would that be?
Bedroom?
Oh, wait.
Okay.
Here we go.
So here we go.
Is this a cat bowl?
No, this is a dog bowl.
This would be right here.
It's good.
All right.
Are you scared for life?
I don't know.
How long does it last?
57 minutes.
That's not bad.
Oh, somebody filled that?
When do you guys fill the bowl?
I'm inspired.
Ooh, maybe next time.
What does it say?
Oh, there we go.
I'm good.
What's my problem?
What's going on?
Maybe next time.
All right.
Fill and call yodel.
Oh, I need a trash.
Where is my actual outdoor trash?
Do I have one?
Okay.
I need a trash can and I needed a stove.
Can I even afford a stove?
I can.
All right.
This time don't be an idiot.
Okay.
What else was over here besides the stove?
I think anything else damaged?
This shit's so fucked up.
This stuff's damaged.
This is damaged.
Okay.
Now I just want new counters.
What?
Look at these.
Look at the difference.
Why is this one so screwed up?
These ones are burnt.
What?
Oh, okay.
Well, whatever.
That's fine.
Let's get this stuff back on the right counters.
What do I just do?
Okay.
Coffee maker.
I need that microwave back.
That's fine.
And then I get just a little place to serve.
And now I need a trash can.
That's better.
All right.
Nice trash right here is good.
And it's this way.
How do I make it so it doesn't do this?
I thought I had that cheat code on.
Alt.
Okay.
Thank you.
Back to normal.
What do I have to go to the...
I have to go to Batu.
All right.
We got notebook.
There are no entries in Blorg's notebook.
Blorg.
Allender.
All right.
What's coming up?
Well, this is today.
Add event, right?
Yeah.
Well, I was going to write like...
I got it like burnt.
Winterfest.
Ooh.
All right.
Where's Winterfest?
From 6 a.m. to 2 a.m.
Wait.
It's right now.
Father Winter.
Santa Claus is coming in three days.
I have to do festive stuff.
I'm going to throw a party.
I'm going to be ready to throw a party.
Can I go in the water?
Am I going to take my clothes off?
And excuse me.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Uh-uh.
Go.
This is...
I get in the...
Go in the water.
Hurry the fuck up.
Get in the fucking water, please.
Oh, my God.
I didn't think he was going to walk out the front door naked.
Did he pee?
What are you doing?
Go jogging.
No, he's not going to go jogging like this.
Bro, you've got to be kidding me.
You've actually got to be fucking kidding me.
Go home.
What is wrong with you?
Who is this?
Hello?
I'm going to introduce...
Wait, is this a famous person?
Ask for a selfie.
What are you doing?
What are you calling?
Who is she calling?
You need entertainment, dude.
Where did I go?
Get over there.
Sol Sol!
What's up, buddy?
That's not how I would not introduce myself to a celebrity like that.
I'd just be like, hey, what's up?
Bro.
Okay.
Global superstar.
Did I have an autograph?
Who asked for a P.A., Floymo?
Me.
No?
Oh, okay.
What about...
Can I take a picture?
Can we have a picture?
Oh, Pernosa.
Can I have a marathon?
Oh, Espanol.
Damn.
Oh, I need Espanol.
Um, what else?
All right, well, bye.
I can't just...
Thank God the fire is out.
Oh.
You too.
All right, what's wrong with me?
Oh, you're obsessed with the fridge.
I forgot.
Yipsy.
There's been a couple of partly unhinged things going on the first 20 minutes of this game.
We're going to try to dial it back a little.
So, I need bladder.
Hunger.
Don't...
This time, I'm eating a snack.
I'm eating a microwaved meal.
We're not touching the stove for a little while.
We're gonna have microwaved chicken nuggets.
Like, the worst way to make chicken nuggets.
That's the worst possible way to do that.
He needs a new...
Okay.
So, let's do energy.
Maybe.
Oh, right, this huge bed.
Can I actually get in it?
You can't...
This is not gonna have a problem, right?
It's just microwave chicken nuggets.
You know where to sit and eat?
It's okay.
I only have 300 bucks.
I need to get a job.
I need to make money somehow.
For a second, I thought that was the fire alarm.
No, you can't have any.
Oh, they suck.
He hates it.
Okay.
Now, why would you do that?
That's just weird.
That was weird.
That was very weird.
Who smells their chicken nuggets like that?
All right.
Let's fill the dog bowl.
This is why I didn't want like 10 cats, guys.
Because you have to do this.
Where are you going?
Just running around?
What else do you need to do?
Listen to kids music.
Is there like a...
All right.
My energy is kind of low.
What should I do for...
Let me look for a job.
Where is it?
Business, right?
Okay.
Buy a restaurant.
Buy a vet clinic.
Register with the Ministry of Labor.
All right.
What about...
What about a job?
What can I do?
What should I do?
Detective, doctor, scientist, or actor is to get the...
I don't want to be an actor, though.
Critic?
Everyone has an opinion, but not everyone is paid to have it.
Sims who feel they have superior judgment can either enter the critic career,
food, or the arts.
Should I be a food critic?
Culinary, freelancer, gardener, painter, politician, salary person, secret agent,
a style influencer, a babysitter, fast food employee, retail employee, secret agent.
I don't think this guy is going to be a secret agent.
No, I need to be a Jedi.
Can I still do...
Can I be a secret agent and a Jedi?
Can I be a doctor and a Jedi?
Does that work?
Right?
I could be a doctor and a Jedi.
Should I be a doctor?
I feel like doctors are boring to do in The Sims, though.
That's like, since The Sims 1, that's been a thing you can do.
Maybe I will do secret agent.
From infiltrating enemy headquarters to the art of interrogation,
the more you learn, the less you'll be known.
Diamond agent and villain.
Should I do this?
Just be a villain?
Yeah, whatever, let's do it.
Browse intelligence.
Starts in three days.
Oh, no, no, it starts tomorrow.
All right, I got to be ready for work.
Browse intelligence.
What is it?
Can I do that on my phone?
Do I need a computer?
I need a computer.
Oh, shit.
Why would you be able to browse intelligence on your phone?
Please get a dog bed.
Do I have enough money for a dog bed?
Oh, yeah, I do.
Let's get like a big one.
Yeah, this one's good.
You sleep right here.
Right next to the frog thing.
There we go.
Browse high-level government secrets with a...
Would you say a library computer?
Hold on a second.
Why am I red?
I don't get it.
I think it's the light coming off the monitor.
Save, yeah.
All right, let's do our secret agent career.
So I got to get up for work tomorrow.
So look at me.
Ready?
Let's get some sleep.
Okay, go on.
The bed's too big.
Can you even sit on the bed?
The bed is way too big.
Okay, we're going to fix that.
Did I make it too small?
Why does it look tiny?
What's wrong?
This looks so small.
You should go to bed.
There we go.
Okay.
All right, I got to get up in seven hours.
There we go.
Raining?
Tense.
Oh, he's still thinking about the fire.
Watch romance.
This is such a small TV.
Browse the web.
It's 5 a.m., man.
What are you doing?
All right, I need to eat breakfast in two hours.
We're going to eat something and I've got to go to the bathroom.
All right, I'm going to have a quick meal
and I'm going to just drink blue milk.
What?
Blue milk?
Is this supposed to be?
Is this a Star Wars?
This is the Star Wars thing?
Oh, I liked it.
Really flirty.
Okay, work from work starts in about one hour.
Okay.
How are you doing?
Bladder, use the bathroom and then wash your hands.
Brush your teeth too.
Brush your teeth.
Oh, yep, car's going to be here any second.
And eat.
Eat the fruitcake that's in your pocket.
Quick, eat it before you go to work.
Oh, whatever, fine.
Where are you?
Where's he going?
Oh, you're off to work.
Okay.
Hack it.
While performing a routine background check,
Lord runs into an unexpected firewall.
Hmm.
He didn't think the information he needed was going to be protected.
You need to hack through the firewall to dig deeper.
I'm calling a senior.
I don't hack it.
I don't have any experience with a computer.
I don't even own a computer.
I'm going to hack it.
After some ingenious crypto work,
Lord beats the firewall and discovers that nothing is what it seems.
He rushes findings to his boss and turns out he's uncovered a nefarious plot.
$50.
Are you coming back?
What's wrong?
So gross from using the public bathroom.
Setting foot in that public bathroom may have been a mistake.
My public bathroom?
Or which public bathroom does he not like?
The one at work?
He's got minty fresh teeth.
What's this?
Meet a celebrity.
Oh, okay.
The humor and hijinks festival is today until four.
Oh, leave work.
Just leave.
When do I get back from work?
Can I just leave work?
I'm not missing this.
Wait, $75.
All right.
I'm not going to miss the hijinks festival.
Where is it?
All right.
I'm going to go to the event.
Let's make sure the dog is okay.
Stop watching TV.
All right.
Now let's say, you know, I've got a skill in comedy.
Oh, all right.
I take a photo of the dog.
Okay.
Yodel has gained 17 Simstagram followers.
All right.
Let's go.
You got food, right?
There's food in the bowl.
You're good.
You're just chilling.
Have the TV on.
All right.
I'm going to...
I'll eat at the festival.
I want to go to the...
I want to do the festival.
Let's go.
Should I bring Yodel?
I guess we're going.
I can't tell if your cam is delayed or not.
People have been saying that the whole stream.
I don't know why it would be happening.
I don't know.
All right.
I'm here.
Who's this?
This is a bee-lister.
Okay.
Chat with Minerva.
So I have to meet a celebrity and...
Why is the...
Okay.
Where's the dog even going?
That's a huge TV.
Should I start telling jokes?
I'm not going to be like that guy.
I'm telling you right now.
I don't know what happened.
Fainted.
Because you...
Is that going to be all right?
What are you doing?
This is a weird place to do a photo shoot
in the public bar bathroom.
Get on the mic.
I got to start.
I got to impress somebody.
I'm going to practice singing.
Let's ruin the whole party.
He gave up immediately.
This person's shit-faced,
and they've had one drink, by the way.
You just gave me two dollars?
People are giving me money.
Two bucks?
Congrats on landing that sweet job.
I think this is going to be great for you.
Oh, thanks.
I thought the bar lit on fire.
I was like, oh my God.
What is happening to people?
You're face down in trash.
Somebody needs to help this person.
Is this weird to do in front of the celebrity?
No one's paying.
Wait, squeamish.
Oh, he doesn't like this trash.
I forgot.
But he wanted to play in it.
I have to meet the celebrity.
Call over.
You made him do it.
All right.
Didn't I meet this person already
in front of the house?
What am I holding?
People need to relax.
What am I eating?
Is this the old fruitcake?
This guy's fucked.
This guy's a fucking weirdo.
Photographer.
Wait, I can sell this?
I can sell the picture of the dog.
I need to meet a celebrity.
Come over here.
We need to talk.
All right.
So let's talk.
How you doing?
Nice to meet you.
Did you see my dog?
Can I not say anything?
I have to meet a celebrity.
Is this a celebrity?
What the hell?
Who smells?
Somebody stinks over here.
Who is it?
Is it the dog?
Hey, I'm going to come to this
really cool insider party
and I'm going to bring my wicked smelly dog.
I need to meet us.
Anybody want one of these old fruitcakes?
I'm going to put it in front of one of their faces.
Who's wicked smelly dog is this?
All right.
I got to get it together.
Call everybody over.
Hey, everybody.
Old fruitcake.
Are people going to eat it?
Wait, does this smell?
Yo, we're good.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Let's talk.
You like the fruitcake?
I'm going to lie and tell you that I made it.
Don't do it.
You're going to hit your head.
Watch your head.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe Judith Ward was eating dinner.
I forget the guy's name.
Did I get it?
Debate.
It was a fun filled day with a celebrity.
Are we getting kicked out?
Is this a celebrity?
Why is this person glowing?
Wait, what does it say?
What did that say?
All lifestyles have a limited amount of progress
that can be gained daily.
You reach the daily limit or a lifestyle.
Humor and high drinks festival is in town.
What?
That's not where I've been.
All right, put it down and go to the fun festival.
Let's go.
So this is the high drinks festival.
It was across the street.
All right.
I'm in a good mood, though.
So now what do I have to do?
I have to meet a celebrity.
Oh, Chorg Chorg is the dog that smells.
Come here.
Don't do that.
What the fuck?
Yodo.
OK, you know, you just want me to go home.
With soup, I mean, how do I get to see the the usually
there's something in the top left.
It gives progress, right?
What's this?
We look up squids.
Join the pranksters.
What's this?
Oh, by swag.
Let's haggle.
Where are you going?
Wait, did I smoke?
Sit and try.
Let's try that.
What are you doing?
It doesn't like what?
I guess I don't like it.
Change the flavor.
How about golden rush?
Let's go light fireworks.
All right, let's go.
I'm here.
I'm already here.
Bring some friends.
Light fireworks.
OK, I have to go to work.
What's this?
Energize.
He's keyed up.
All right, where do I get fireworks?
Right here, right?
Does not own this item.
Aren't these fireworks?
I have to buy them for the stall.
Where's the dog?
I invited somebody.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Here they are.
We're going to chat and I got some golden.
What was it called?
Jokester.
What flavor do you want?
What?
Uncomfortable suddenly.
Uncomfortable state of life, but not on the floor.
Wait, am I like too high or something?
I don't get what's wrong with me.
I'm going to test singing ever again.
No, let's be.
Let's just, I don't know.
Wait, somebody's on a mic.
So they have an aura.
They have a celebrity.
Where do you get the fireworks?
Because I can't buy them.
Painting.
You need to go to the bathroom.
Is there a bathroom here?
Where do I buy fireworks?
Oh, no, no, no.
I want to do it.
This person just got hurt.
Oh, I did it.
I did it.
Celebrity aura.
Why is your face so red?
I don't know.
Hey, talk to me.
Getting in line.
I don't want anyone to know that I shit my pants.
You're good.
We're good.
The red face is the celebrity aura.
All right.
So I love the fireworks.
Is there anything else I have to do?
I'm going to buy some food.
Let's get a, I don't know.
That's 20 bucks.
Let's get that.
The game's kind of loud, isn't it?
Please do the fountain already.
Did I eat?
Okay, I have it.
I need to eat first.
Did I leave the plate on?
I didn't take the plate.
I forgot to take the food with me.
All right.
Eat.
Who are these people?
Do you know some of them?
I don't know.
There's fire just coming out of my mouth.
Lord isn't used to eating spicy food.
The time he would be able to eat the spiciest food around.
Wait, what?
Oh my God.
The dog.
I need to feed the dog.
How do I feed the dog?
I don't know what the dog is even doing here.
Jokesters win.
All jokesters got 500 bucks and a comedy mic.
Where did I do it?
I didn't join a team.
Hurry up.
Join a team.
Quick.
I'm going to join the jokesters.
Drink the jokester drink.
Join the jokesters.
Okay.
Perform pranks or something?
Impossible sausage mine.
What is that?
Remember the dog.
You're a little late.
Eating food from the city unlocks the ability to cook it.
Really?
That's kind of cool.
All right.
Finish up activities.
That was fun.
All right.
We got to go.
Me and the dog.
And I have to go to work tomorrow.
Do I have any food like dog food?
What was that?
No.
Stop.
Turn these off.
Enough.
The festival's over.
Everyone go home.
Turn that off.
What is what is what?
Do I like someone?
I saw the hearts.
Raid.
Connery.
Oh, Connery's pants with the raid.
Welcome everybody.
Thanks Conner.
Appreciate it.
I have to.
I got to take.
I got to take the dog.
We got to go now.
We got to go home now.
Bye.
We got to go.
I just cleared everybody up.
Everybody's got cleared out.
I need to pick this up.
So we let's go take a bath.
Bath time.
Come on.
Let's go into the bath.
Yep.
And then we're going to get you fed.
And why are you so red?
I don't know.
I had no.
It's like a thermal camera pointed at my face today.
I don't know why.
Do I have to go?
What time is work tomorrow?
All right.
I got to be ready for work.
I actually am not in bad shape.
Okay.
That's better.
Can I see the dog's needs bars?
Okay.
Get some food.
Wash the green off.
This dog.
It's yodel.
Okay.
Here we go.
Have some food.
I should probably eat something too.
Right?
I need to learn some skills.
I need to.
Okay.
How much is the cheapest computer?
I need a desk and a computer.
Like a bundle.
What's the cheapest bundle?
They sell it in bundles.
Oh my God.
This is a thousand dollars.
Eight hundred dollars.
A thousand dollars.
Go to the library.
Am I actually going to browse sensitive intelligence files at the library?
Okay.
That's whatever.
Yes.
What time do I have to get up?
I think my energy is fine.
All right.
I'm going to take a nap.
I'm going to go to the library.
Okay.
Let's go to bed.
What are you doing?
Work starts in an hour.
All right.
I don't have time to go to the library.
It doesn't matter.
Have a coffee.
And then microwave a chicken nuggets.
That sounds like a plan to me.
You're good.
I'll fill your bowl.
You're all right.
I need to.
Okay.
I need a ball or something.
I need a ball.
I need a toy or something.
Right?
Like dog toy.
Where are they?
These are cat toys.
Do these count as dog toys?
Just give them one of these out here.
All right.
Go check it out.
Oh, you're going to go for it?
Use your new...
Oh, he went to work.
Where's the dog?
Oh, bottom left for dog needs.
Where?
Use the new poles.
Okay.
Well, dog's fine.
We're good.
Winterfest starts tomorrow.
Oh, fuck.
How do I make sure Santa comes?
File presents?
What's with the scary music?
Will Santa come if I have presents like this?
Just on the...
Just hanging out?
Add a present.
Oh, do I have any object?
I'm going to make macaroni and cheese
or grilled cheese and put it in there.
I need a fireplace.
I have a hundred bucks.
That's not going to happen.
I need a fireplace.
I'm going to have to sell the bed.
I could sell the public bathroom.
You don't need a fireplace.
Oh, okay.
Starts tomorrow.
Work until three.
All right.
Why do I have a public bathroom?
I don't know.
I just saw it and I thought it was funny.
Put it in here.
All right.
Let's prepare the house.
Let's have a Christmas party.
I'm going to throw a holiday party.
So let's do that.
So tomorrow I want...
Is there a way I can plan a party?
Add event.
Okay.
Should I just invite people over tomorrow?
Plan a social event.
Okay.
All right.
The social event is going to be a house party
and it's going to be a McNulty residence.
I'm going to be the host
and I'm going to invite everybody.
I'm going to order a pizza.
Entertainer.
I don't need to...
No, I don't need this.
I don't need to cater.
I'm just going to order a pizza.
No, this is right now.
I want to do it for tomorrow.
Oh, I have to order a pizza quick.
How much is a pizza?
How do I order a pizza?
Oh, shit.
I have to get gifts.
Two apples.
A camera.
That's $670.
Ball for the dog.
A little robe.
I...
A little...
No, these are so expensive.
Charlotte's pig.
And a little wood toy.
Okay.
Got it.
You guys came way too quickly.
What am I putting in here?
No.
Put these in the...
What?
What am I putting here?
My dog is my closest friend.
That's true.
Okay.
I need to...
We need to eat...
How do I order food?
How do you order food?
I hate video games.
Put it down.
What are you doing?
All right.
How do I order food?
Hire a service.
Where do I do it?
Shift-Tab.
Home Services Pizza.
There's no pizza here.
Order delivery.
Where do you see that?
Hire a delivery.
Order a delivery.
Travel.
What is it under?
Business.
Vacation.
Chat.
Under Home Services.
Home.
Order a delivery.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Pizza coming.
We want...
Who wants cheese?
Cheese pizza on the way, everybody.
Everybody having fun at the...
The Christmas party?
Okay, socialize with guests.
Let's say hello.
Thank you for coming, everybody.
Who wants a present?
Okay, we need to clean up this trash.
Pizza coming.
Uncomfortable.
Too many Sims.
Well, I invited everybody here for a Christmas party.
Pizza.
Let me get it.
Please.
I need to get the pizza.
Do not...
Go get the pizza.
Oh, my God.
Get the pizza.
What are you talking about?
He's locked in?
How is he stuck?
What are you talking about?
Get the pizza.
Are you locked out of the outside of the house?
What is happening?
No, get the pizza.
Why is he going to bed?
You fucking weirdo.
Why is he locked out of his...
Why is he locked inside of his...
Can somebody get the door?
It's the worst fucking holiday party ever.
What is going...
Make another door quick.
This guy would have left.
You know what?
Just get rid of the door.
Just open it.
No, he put the pizza down.
I ordered that pizza and I'm going to get it.
I ordered that pizza.
Just get in.
Come in.
Just come...
Just walk into the house.
Walk into the house.
I'm right here.
Why can you all leave and I can't?
No, he's eating the old fruitcake in his pocket.
There's a pizza out here.
I paid for it.
What the...
Everybody, there's going to be sand in this pizza.
Imagine putting a pizza on the ground at the beach.
You wouldn't pay me to eat this.
You didn't show up to claim your pizza,
so I charged you $25 and left it outside the ants to enjoy.
Everybody was going to leave.
Have Sims kiss?
What?
All right, we got our pizza.
Everything's good to go.
All right, let's bring...
Bring the party back inside.
What do you say?
Come on, everybody.
You talking shit to my dog?
What are you saying?
Excuse...
And people just coming in and yelling at my dog.
I think I'm stuck between three people.
All right, that was fun.
Enough of that.
Clean up the pizza.
I need to fill the dog bowl.
You okay?
What's going on?
Who talks shit to my dog?
Why am I dressed like this?
Come here.
Bro, make him leave.
Cake.
Oh, wait, it's time for somebody to have a present.
All right, everybody, it's time.
Merry Christmas.
It's time for all of us to open the presents.
No, open the presents.
Presents.
Open the presents.
Here we go.
All right, everybody.
There's stuff under there for pretty much everyone.
Merry Christmas.
Thanks for coming to the party.
I hope everyone had a good time.
Let's go ahead and get those presents open.
Let's see what I got.
I got...
I can't believe it.
It's...
Who would give one...
What?
What'd you get?
What did you get?
There's nothing in each one of these boxes.
Open the presents.
Hey, this one's for you, son.
New frog.
How come no one's opening presents?
Complaining about video games.
Oh, my God, I smell.
What is going on here?
What was that?
Oh, shit.
Lord McGulty has identified the goldfish,
a new type of fish recorded in certain fishing spots.
How did I learn that?
All right, everybody get out.
All right.
Oh, shit, the coffee maker.
Everybody out now.
Everybody get out of here.
All right, actually, I want to be your friend
because you're actually really nice.
This person's really nice and actually helping.
What's the person's name?
Is her name Hillary?
Lawrence.
All right, I want to talk to Hillary.
Look at the people that are actually helping.
You know how much we're panning the asses
to put a huge house party on?
Yeah.
You don't understand, it takes like three days
to come back from a house party like this.
Like you brought like a bunch of people over.
It takes days to clean this up.
I appreciate it.
That's not me in the bed.
Wait, what?
Who is this lady?
What?
Why is it?
What does that mean?
Assigned to left side.
Did you just claim the bed?
I'm very confused.
Everybody fucking leave.
How do I kick everybody out of here?
Wait, he's putting a person in.
I'm going to look and see what it is.
And?
What is it?
Is it nothing?
Don't sleep in my bed.
All right, that was a fun party.
Now, everybody get out.
I am pissed.
I want everybody to leave so bad.
How do I kick everybody out of here?
It is midnight and they're still here.
This kid's going to my fridge.
Excuse me.
What's this?
Pay for that?
Money got deducted from my account when he opened the door.
I mean, I appreciate it.
Thanks.
Why was there?
Did they?
It's taking out fucking booze out of the fridge.
Put that down.
What is it?
Oh, it's orange juice.
All right.
I think they took all the dirty dishes
and they put them into the fridge
because there's nowhere else to put them.
These people are very comfortable here, apparently.
Apparently, you're incredibly comfortable to take a bath in my house.
And I literally, we met 12 hours ago
and you make it a mess.
It's 1 15 in the morning.
These people, excuse me.
Why are they still here?
This guy insulted your dog.
Wait, he's got a Christmas sweater on.
He's the only festive one here.
He's the only one that cares about being festive.
We're going on two o'clock in the morning.
She wanted to get in the bed and got mad
because I was on her side of the bed
and now she's talking into the mirror.
What are you doing?
You're making like a souffle.
Why are these people just claiming my house?
I thought everybody has to go so bad.
I've never seen this happen in The Sims before.
They usually leave at like 11 o'clock at night.
They're all here at three o'clock.
Even the kid, there's a little kid here at three a.m.
Send them home.
I already did.
It said my party wasn't successful.
Everyone's going to leave now or something.
They're going to be here until I get up in the morning.
Are they actually going to stay here all day, all night?
They have to be, they have to go back to sleep.
They're making coffee.
Bro, enjoy yourself.
Have another, have a latte.
It's almost time for me to wake up in the morning.
It's just a bath house.
I'm actually, I don't understand what's happening right now.
These people are fighting.
It's Christmas now.
Okay, get up, get up, get up.
Use the bathroom.
Guys, I can't make them leave.
There's no send home option.
They all live here now.
Go home.
Stop drinking coffee in my bed.
Hey, all right, get it, you're out.
Get out of here.
Did I go to work?
Winterfest is starting now.
Okay, well glad everybody here was here for the quiche.
Winterfest?
Everybody ready to sing?
I guess.
Nobody slept in 20.
He looked like he was about to go fist in the present.
I seriously thought he was gonna pee.
I thought he was gonna go down and take his shit in the present.
All right, party's over.
Okay, happy, happy birthday.
Is Santa gonna show up or do I actually need a fireplace?
All right, I'll take some coffee.
Thank you.
Okay, goodbye.
Let's share Winterfest spirit.
Catch Father Winter and ask him for a present to satisfy.
Hey, Winter, hey, here's an 8 p.m. near fireplaces.
I'm selling something.
I'm selling the fucking outhouse.
We need a fireplace.
Everyone's gonna be trapped here for some weird reason.
I need a fireplace.
We need open presents.
Okay, presents, open presents and stuff.
Every, even cavemen.
Click on yourself is an option to make people leave.
No, there isn't.
They just won't.
They're just stuck here forever.
You, where's the option to get rid of everybody?
Get actions, form a group.
Click on the door.
There is no door.
I deleted it because the pizza guy couldn't get in.
This is drinking coffee and using the microwave and taking a bath in my house.
I need to, okay, I need a, uh.
I, we're selling.
I'm getting rid of this.
I'm buying one single fucking toilet.
This thing was like five grand.
I need, we need a fireplace for the Santa Claus.
Let's put a regular toilet in here.
And now I have 2,000 more dollars.
I don't know.
This is like the chic one, whatever.
Okay, good to go.
Now I need a fireplace.
What's the cheapest one?
600 bucks.
This thing's cheap.
It doesn't matter.
We just waited.
We just need presents from, there you go.
Okay, I need a door.
There's, I don't need a door.
Okay, here we go.
How do I light the fireplace?
Can somebody else do it?
Oh, you know what?
The worst part about this is people won't leave.
I can't make them leave.
There's no option to make them leave.
But yet every time they open the fridge, it deducts $20 from my bank account.
I am housing 15 people right now and they all have their own houses
and they're spending all my money.
I need a door.
I had a door before and it locked us all in.
They'll leave after Christmas.
Buy a real door.
Change the door.
I will.
Vloggers learn the trade.
Mean.
Somebody left.
Holy shit.
Somebody got out.
Somebody actually got out.
Where are you going is the real question.
The most festive person didn't wait for Santa Claus.
Without a door, your house is a public place.
What?
It's a public place?
Even if it is a public place, why are they here for two straight days?
They would have left.
You wouldn't stay in a public place for two days.
I have a door now.
Now click it.
What's wrong with this roof?
We need to clean up.
I'm waiting for...
I'll order another pizza.
Spiegel, stop opening the fridge.
I'm going to order a pizza.
Dog needs a bath.
Didn't I pick this up off the floor?
Why am I eating this?
How did I get 800?
Oh, because I sold the...
I sold the public bathroom.
Coffee maker is broken.
Just get another one.
I don't care.
Invite a werewolf.
I need to wait for Santa to come.
Can somebody else light this though?
Click door and say no trespasses.
Well, I don't want to dis...
I don't want to disallow everybody.
This is not how you do it.
I don't want to disallow neighbors.
I want them to be able to come over, but...
Ask to leave under friendly.
Something that's really...
This whole routine of making a coffee and taking a bath.
My water bill is going to be crazy this week.
This month.
I don't understand how none of them have gone to sleep.
None of them have slept in two days.
Lord is a lazy sim.
They like watching TV.
All right, let me do the dog a bath.
Stop watching TV and getting...
You got to do some stuff.
Clean up.
Take a bath.
Exercising.
I guess you're going to open the fridge and take something out.
You're going to charge me $20.
Look, I'm giving the dog a bath right now.
You can't...
Is Santa actually going to appear?
Yeah, if you have a fireplace, which I do.
And it's 8 p.m.
That's the only reason why I haven't kicked everybody out yet.
Or try...
I mean, they're just here.
I need to go to sleep.
Sleep.
Move out of the way.
Everyone get out of the way.
You can talk in the other room.
Stop.
Get away from my bed.
What a rush.
The boost of adrenaline is making Lord feel amazing.
Should he finally embrace it with his astonishingly sculpted arms that he likes fitness?
No.
What does that mean?
Okay, this person's cooking.
Should we sing together again?
Oh, kookaloy y'all meat.
Oh.
Plus one future cube?
What?
I got a future cube?
Quick yourself.
Guys, there is no make people leave.
The game is broken.
And I was waiting for Santa to show up before I reload the game and kick everybody out.
Somebody else left.
We were so close to Santa.
All right, so the cube...
Where's the cube?
Tag, tag.
It's on the counter.
Everybody ready?
Santa will be showing up very soon.
I was going to say happy birthday.
Happy birthday to Santa.
Worst party ever.
Will he be brave enough to throw another party after how badly this one went?
Tag, tag.
But Santa hasn't even showed up yet.
They're all actually leaving right before the big moment where Santa comes.
You've been here for three days.
Three days.
At least you're still here.
I'm sorry for that party.
It was so bad.
It was an awful party.
What do you need?
What's wrong now?
Okay.
How about let's sing another song.
And sing pop songs duet with other Sims.
Hold on.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This is not we're not doing that.
Give a Winterfest gift.
Oh, all I have is dog shit.
All right.
A ball of wooden children's toy.
An apple.
A toddler's book.
Or the fruitcake that's been old that I made that I got for a welcome present like a month ago.
Which one?
The apple.
Imagine getting an apple for a present.
Just one apple.
A single apple.
Maybe the wooden toy.
Merry Christmas.
What's in it?
My specialty.
You know how much this fucking place is worth?
Where's a lot of money?
Out on the beach.
Ask what happened.
Can you turn the stove on or whatever?
Hey, Blark, you're so notorious that one of my unscrupulous friends has been asking to meet you.
Can I give them your number?
What do you mean notorious?
What does that mean?
No.
Oh, coffee.
Yep.
Okay.
We only have a couple hours till Santa shows up.
He's pissed.
Let's do, um, let's talk about who's laugh together.
Belly laugh.
Santa's going to show up very soon.
This dog looks like a sock puppet.
Okay, how about, um, how about, um, something just friendly.
New show.
There's a new show on TV.
Let's talk about the new show.
That makes sense, right?
All right.
All we drink is coffee.
I have to extinguish your fire.
Okay.
How about, um, complain about Winterfest.
I wouldn't want to know.
Why would I do that?
Having been a personal emergency and have to leave.
What?
What is it?
Emergency?
What?
Hey, I've heard a lot about you.
Mostly bad things, but that's okay.
People usually don't like me either.
We should hang out sometime.
Want to come over for Christmas?
Who was that?
Santa's going to show up in two hours.
Come on over.
Grace will be right over.
All right.
Quick.
I got to use the bathroom.
No, don't go to bed after inviting some drink coffee and go to the bathroom.
That was quick.
You didn't, I didn't invite you in.
We just walked in the house.
Oh my goodness.
How are you doing?
All right.
What about like mischief?
Incoming phone call.
Hey, blogger.
I've been thinking about getting to know Nina Caliente better as a friend.
Do you think the two of us should?
Why are you calling me?
Don't, don't ever call this number again.
All right.
Let's make a coffee and then we'll be ready for Santa.
Said anything.
This is weird.
Get out.
Get out of here.
Oh dear.
Wait, Santa's gonna be here in an hour.
Where's Santa?
8 p.m.
Right?
Quick.
I gotta, I gotta go to sleep just for a minute.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't leave.
Just pick the shit up.
She picked the shit up with her hand.
All right.
Santa's coming.
8 p.m.
Here it comes.
Okay.
Santa!
What's he putting down Santa?
Okay.
We got a present from Santa.
Put your, Santa is in the room.
Put your phone down.
He's putting tons of shit here.
Oh my goodness.
And all those motherfuckers left.
Eat them.
Okay.
Hold on.
There's cheese pizza here.
Okay.
Let's sing about Winterfest.
Wait, he got a gun.
Oh my God.
I thought he shot me in the face with a gun.
Oh my.
That was fucking crazy.
I, I thought I.
Okay.
We're good.
Pizza.
All right, Santa.
Stick around.
Let's get that pizza.
Why does this keep happening?
The door is locked?
People have been walking in and out of this door.
Hector Laurent is not here.
Is he?
Where is he?
He's hiding somewhere?
Santa, can you get the pizza?
This is fucked.
This is fucked up.
This is like creepy.
This is creepy.
It's actually kind of scary.
We can't get the pizza again.
He's going to leave it on the ground
and Santa's going to take it and then leave.
And then I can, I'm going to go back to work tomorrow.
This nightmare can finally end.
But there are presents in here.
Come open presents.
What did I get?
Santa put these in here.
Plus one wonder game.
Ooh, cool.
That's it.
Oh, that was rude.
That was rude.
What I meant to say was
thank you so much, Santa, for the gift.
I can't get the pizza.
I'm locked inside of my house, apparently.
I can't.
He's complaining about the trash.
He just put it there.
Well, let me go ahead and get the pizza now.
You know what?
I'm insulting you.
Come back here so I can insult you.
You going to get a slice?
I'm going to bed.
I give you a Winterfest gift.
A fresh coffee.
There's an alien.
Why did I play the alien song?
All right, put this away.
Put it in the fridge.
Because can we?
Okay, can I finally?
All right, we're good.
Everybody can relax.
That was strange.
But it's time to get back to the real life here.
Winterfest was really fun.
I got some cool stuff.
Um, we're going to let's clean up.
Feed the dog.
Take a bath.
Clean this place up.
Everything looks okay.
All right.
Well, I don't know where you're going, but whatever.
Host another party.
No, not another party.
I need to rest.
And then I got to get up because I have work.
I got work tomorrow.
Work starts in this morning and relax.
I think your door porch is not big enough for two people.
Is that what the problem is?
The dude put the trash on the ground and then complained that I had like a dirty house.
Dude, you that's what's going on.
Need to make it bigger.
Should I just get rid of it and put hold on?
What if I make like a little like, yeah, okay.
This is what I'm going to do.
I'm going to build out the wall here.
I have a thousand bucks.
I think I have enough to do it.
Just like a little thing, right?
How do I make just like a little thingy?
Make a pool?
Build a deck?
I don't have enough money.
Platform.
Okay, so I'm going to do rounded platform.
This doesn't look right.
This is not right.
This is wrong.
Bottom right.
How do I remove this?
Okay, so square deck.
But this is a big cube.
I don't understand.
Oh, that's wrong.
Why is this so fucked up?
Did I skip to the fridge?
Wait, why is a fridge in here?
How do I undo?
Controls it.
I can't.
It's like going into the house.
Is the movement that cheat that I turned on screwing this up?
Oh my God.
Don't do that.
Wait.
Yeah, do that.
Oh my God.
Okay, I actually have a house now.
Oh my goodness.
Thank God.
I don't know why I was up so high.
All right, so now I got to make an opening here.
A little gate.
How do I put a gate so they can walk in?
It's kind of big.
Okay, I want brick.
There we are.
Hey, look at that.
Okay, nice.
Oh my God.
Okay, hold on here.
Looks good.
All right, now I actually am not up in the air.
I have a little area out here.
I can put like some plants and shit.
All right, now it's time to get back to reality.
Hey.
Things looking good.
I'm blocking the Winterfest stuff.
Yeah, but it's over.
I did everything.
Some sleep.
Go to the bathroom, get some sleep, and then take a shower.
What the hell is that?
All right, sleep, get up, have a quick breakfast, and then get to work.
I need a computer eventually.
After I get back from work, I'm going to get a computer
because I have some secret agent.
I got to get this.
This is way too goopy.
It was weird.
This is super goopy.
It's spreading too much.
This is goopy.
Oh my God.
Why is it?
That one's goopy.
I don't like that one.
Winterfest was, what did it say?
Winterfest was pretty good.
Laura got to do a lot of things he wanted to do, but not everything.
Next year, he hopes to do even more.
That's fine.
Okay, get some sleep.
You need to eat, and then I'm going to get to bed,
and I got to get up in five hours to go to work.
What's wrong with me?
Something was gross.
How do you upgrade the bed?
All right, let's go.
Geez.
We're good.
Starts in about an hour.
Should be fine.
Late for work?
What do you mean?
What?
Did I just miss work?
Who's calling me?
Laura, thank you for suggesting I hang out with Nina Caliente.
We had a spectacular time.
I literally hung up on you.
I hung up on that guy.
Okay, we're good.
That person made that up.
Uncomfortable.
Too many Sims.
Is there coffee brewing?
All right, 123 bucks.
Clean up the coffee maker.
Take a shower, and then I need to get a computer,
and I need to do this, whatever the skill is.
Browse intelligence.
And I'm ready for promotion.
Look at this.
Oh, hello.
Bathroom shower.
Now, I need a little desk and a computer.
Can I afford it?
Oh, why do I have a slice of pizza?
And what inventory?
Made by Titus Peterson.
Who is that?
Okay, let's go with the
needed desk right here.
Just a shitty one.
Just little ones so I can use the computer.
It's the cheapest one they have.
Oh, my God.
It's like a half-life item.
All right, that's fine.
And here we are.
Desktop computer.
I only have 100 bucks and I need a seat.
I don't think I can afford a nice chair to dry though.
Okay, that's fine.
All right, now I'm gonna take a quick shower,
and I'm gonna do the whatever this is.
I need to practice intelligence.
Take a shower.
You seem pretty happy.
All right, hunger.
I'll eat something quick.
Wait, I have pizza in the fridge, right?
Leftovers.
Something smells.
This fridge is steaming with smelly stuff.
What is it?
Can I look in the fridge?
I'm not eating the problem, right?
Clean out spoiled food.
Oh, God, it's fine.
Okay, better.
Now it's time.
Computer security settings.
Career.
Practice, where is it?
Play game.
Vampire secrets.
Where is it?
Web?
Okay, browse the intelligence database.
There it is.
I'm getting a call from Santa Claus.
Hey, blogger, I think I have a crush on Lilith Vator.
Do you think it's worth a try?
I don't know.
Sure.
Why are you calling me?
All right, I gotta do this.
All right.
Just started.
What is he saying?
Does he want...
What do you want?
What does he want?
You love another dog?
What was that?
What does that mean?
I'll give you a bath in a second.
25% done.
Hold on.
Ooh, possible lead.
The discovery of some uncovered intelligence
may help make the next day of work a bit easier.
All right.
I'm in a good mood right now.
That's cool.
100% done, right?
And get to bed early so you get promotion.
I'm gonna give the dog a bath.
Don't go to bed yet.
Not yet.
All right, we're gonna play fetch
and then I'm gonna give you a bath.
He's so dirty.
Pet training skill.
Jujube?
Do they even train dogs?
Dodo is a smart dog.
They're easy to train and learn quickly.
Really?
What do you want?
Play fetch?
Let's play fetch.
There it is.
Are they flies?
Go get it.
You gotta pick it up.
Take a look.
Champy?
Oh, you got it.
Nice.
Excellent dog.
I'm gonna give you a big treat for that one.
Jujube?
I'll spot.
Get it.
Here's a big treat.
Who's this?
Loretta?
Warrant?
Is this a public beach?
Am I on a public beach?
Because people are just kind of...
This is not my private land.
I don't get like this section of the beach.
How does that work?
How does it work if this is my house?
Do I own this part of the water?
I don't know how this works.
I don't know how beach front property works.
Gate this beach off.
Just put a whole gate here.
So you just went swimming.
I need to put a gate here.
Watch the dog.
I keep trying to.
Okay, go to learn how to fetch.
Nice job.
Give the dog bath.
All right, come on, let's go.
It's not your beach.
All right, there we go.
Dog's being very calm.
Such a good dog.
I need energy.
All right, smelly pet.
Let's take care of that.
Get an auto feeder.
Actually, that's a good idea.
But I need to save some money.
All right, time for bed.
Get up.
I have my job completed.
Get some sleep.
All right, let's go.
Good day.
Why is my neck so white?
Because the way that my...
I don't know, the way that my camera's lighting.
I don't have...
I'm not...
I don't...
I want to have a night on the town.
Local businesses want to show some customer appreciation
by offering free food and drinks.
Time to get out of the house and visit a venue.
All right, so after work, I'll go do it.
I'm in a bad mood.
Oh, here's another hack thing.
Yeah, hack it.
You just can't beat this one.
Finally, Blorg has to admit defeat to his boss.
And turns out he just had the wrong password.
His boss is not amused.
Really?
What did I...
I ate something at work.
New Year's Eve is tomorrow.
No, I'm going out for New Year's Eve.
I'm going out.
I'm not staying in.
I'm not putting a...
No, I'm going out.
I'm not throwing a New Year's Eve party.
I keep getting calls from Santa again.
Remember when we talked about Lilith Vitora?
We went on a very nice date.
Congratulations, Santa.
I hope it went well.
Promotion.
Promoted to intelligence researcher.
He doesn't like this career.
How long has it been?
Blorg can't help but wonder if this is the career right for him.
One thing is for sure.
There needs to be some kind of change.
I just got promoted.
Oh my God, I forgot to go to Star Wars Land.
I completely forgot.
I'm going to Star Wars Land for New Year's Eve.
That's what I'm doing for my New Year's Eve party.
Where am I?
Right there I am.
That's a great idea.
That's genuinely a good idea.
It sucks, by the way.
It's the worst DLC.
Well, we're only going to go for like a few minutes.
Not for long.
Where'd the dog go?
We're going to clean that up.
I'm going to throw it away.
Don't pick it up.
I don't...
Do I have...
Do I have a trash barrel?
You have to throw...
I haven't gotten the mail the whole time of the plan.
Don't you need a trash barrel for outside?
Oh my goodness.
$220 for that?
You gotta be...
Where's my mailbox?
Auto-sell.
Lot.
Total.
I have 400 bucks that I owe.
How much money do I owe?
What?
Whatever.
I'm just not going to pay it.
Ask for autograph?
Ooh.
All right.
What's my goal?
I need level two logic skill.
What am I doing?
Does programming do logic?
No, it's programming.
I probably need programming, though.
I definitely need programming.
I mean, I'm a secret agent.
So is this Night on the Town?
Is this what I want to do now?
Okay, so Night on the Town is what I can do today.
But I'm just going to wait for New Year's Eve.
Because that is a night on the town, technically.
Yeah, I'll do that.
I'll wait for that.
New Year's Eve.
Oh, there's a talent showcase going down at the lounge.
Let's go embarrass ourselves.
Um, who is this?
I don't even know who this is.
They all got here at the same time.
This is loud.
I could turn it down.
It's really loud.
Okay, so it's a talent show.
Do I have any talents?
Well, this is a huge pool.
Skinny Dip?
Together?
With who?
Do I pick who goes skinny dipping?
Why does it say together?
Wait, wait, you're doing it too?
Okay, I didn't know.
I thought I was going to have to select people.
All right, that...
I didn't know what I thought I was going to select.
Okay, where's the mic?
Oh, it's right here.
Let's sing a duet.
Let's sing a country duet.
Me and Hillary.
No, I don't want to talk to that person.
I'm going to do a country duet.
We're going to drown each other out here.
Who gets all the screen time?
Let's see.
Come into the party, dog.
Get away from the entrance.
Oh, my.
We are...
We're like...
How high are we?
Holy mon...
Oh, okay.
That's high up.
I've played this before.
Yeah, I have.
I remember I had a wedding here.
And then people just started to attack each other.
From what I remember.
All right, we're going to go to Batuu.
That was fun.
Good night.
Am I going to selfie in the middle of your performance?
Yeah.
That just ruined her set.
Did people pay to see this?
Okay, it's time to go to Batuu.
I'm tired.
I need to go to work, but I'm not going to work tomorrow.
I'm going to Batuu tomorrow, and I'm going to become a Jedi.
My thing says I'm asleep.
What?
This guy is a weirdo.
Am I going to get a full night's sleep here?
All right, I got a night's sleep.
That was fun.
It's time to go to Batuu.
Wait, didn't I come with somebody?
I came here with someone.
Where's Hillary?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Oh, it's like a futuristic toilet or something.
Doesn't like it.
All right.
All right, it's time to go to Batuu.
Rest up.
Why did I even come here?
I told- I said that I wanted to rest up and get my energy levels higher.
And then I get a call from Hillary.
No.
He has worms.
I'm going to travel to Batuu and become a Jedi.
First, I'm going to pee.
And then I'm going to eat leftover pizza.
And then I'm going to wash my hands.
And then I'm going to brush my teeth.
Go.
Am I eating it out of the sink?
Okay.
Everything looks good.
Be the dog.
There you go.
All right, let's do it.
What time is it?
Oh, it's 1 a.m.
Never mind.
I'll just go to sleep.
But I'm not going to work tomorrow.
Go to bed.
Wake up.
None of the time was awful.
Maybe next year?
What do you mean?
Was it- is it New Year's Eve?
Did I leave the New Year's Eve party early?
I slept through the New Year's Eve party.
That's what that was?
Oh, it was.
Wait, was it?
I fell asleep on the couch at 10 o'clock.
Whatever.
I'm going to be a Jedi, so who cares?
No, today is New Year's Eve.
Okay.
Countdown.
Stay up past bedtime and shout at the TV in celebration.
Don't put off until tomorrow what you do today.
Click on your sims like, make resolution.
Okay.
Drink, dance, and play music.
Decorate.
All right, we'll get up.
I need to- I'm going to make a resolution.
Complete an aspiring milestone.
Get promoted, raise a skill, write a book.
Get a significant other.
What should I do?
Significant other?
Okay.
Let's go to Batuu.
I'll celebrate New Year's Eve when I get back.
Travel.
Should I take Santa to the Star Wars world?
I'm taking Santa.
Okay.
Where's Batuu?
Is it even up here?
Where's the Star Wars land?
It's vacation.
Take a vacation.
Okay.
All right, vacation.
Where's the Star Wars land?
Oh, it's right there.
It's time.
Okay, here we go.
Black Spire Outpost.
It's the central hub of Batuu.
Here you can find the dwelling.
Ogus Cantina.
Doc Ondar's Den of Antiques
and a number of food and drink options.
Here we go.
Everybody, get your bat chests ready.
Welcome to Batuu.
You use a different currency called Galactic Credits.
They have special inventory.
Don't worry, your simoleons and inventory are safe at home.
Check the career pin of your first mission.
Santa's dressed like a Jedi.
Okay.
Welcome to Batuu.
Plan your Batuu outfit at the dwelling.
Freshen up at the dwelling
and order food from Docking Bay 7.
Okay.
I'm going to order a drink.
I'm going to get a water.
I don't want to lose Santa.
It was just like Star Wars.
It's just like Star Wars world.
Special Star Wars water.
Yeah.
There's gold.
They put two drops of fucking green food coloring in it.
And it's $14.
I got to order a drink.
Oh, I already ordered a water.
Order food from Docking Bay 7.
Is this Docking Bay 7?
Ask about the resistance.
Yeah.
You know, if I had the mods with people getting hit by cars,
can you imagine just how would this even happen?
Okay.
Order food.
Outpost popcorn.
Rising Moon's Overnight Oats.
That's what I'm going to have.
Add that mod immediately.
Look, we're going to do normal for a little while,
and then I promise I will put on all the clown mods.
They'll all go on in the next day.
Just let me play the Sims normally.
It's been very abnormal so far, but you know,
we're doing clown mods.
I promise.
Okay.
I got my food.
I'll move.
It's time to start the music.
It's time to light the light.
It's time to make the music at the Muppet Show tonight.
It's time to...
Is it that way?
This isn't...
Wait, this is different.
This is not the Muppet song.
This is the Antenna song.
How come I didn't get the credit for that?
Stormtrooper?
How do I join the First Order?
I want to be a Sith.
What does it say?
If you are looking to join our ranks,
speak with Lieutenant Agnon in the First Order District.
You got it.
I'm going to freshen up.
All right, freshen up at the dwelling.
Where's my dwelling?
Over here?
How long am I on vacation for?
And where is Santa?
Okay, freshen up.
Okay, I gotta plan my outfit.
Plan Batuu outfit.
All right.
Where are our fucking pants?
I won't...
God.
That's fine.
I can stay like that.
I got bigger by coming to this Batuu world?
I want to be in a Stormtrooper outfit.
Whatever.
This is fine.
I don't care.
All right.
Now I need to order food from Docking Bay 7.
Which that's...
Order food from Docking Bay 7.
All right.
There it is.
I can't go in here?
Okay, I want a Braised Shack Roast.
Please.
I want a single serving of that.
Ask about the First Order.
Ask about the Resistance.
What if I have no money left?
This feels like one of those information games
about the movie that comes in the DVD.
You know, there's two DVDs.
And you go, oh, ask about the First Order.
I'm just going to give you little tidbits
about the story of the DVD that you just got.
This is a DVD game.
I wonder what happens if I ask about the First Order.
Come here.
I just want a lightsaber to put in my house.
Okay.
Is it every neighborhood on...
What the hell?
Don't leave.
You learned how to...
What do you mean I learned how to make Braised Shack Roast?
Isn't that a made-up animal?
That animal doesn't make...
That's not a real animal.
How would I have learned the recipe?
Is this a...
Hold on.
Is this a vacation spot in The Sims
like it's pretending to be Disney?
Or is this...
You're actually on Batuu.
Is it just a Disneyland?
This is not supposed to be...
Oh, where's Kylo Ren?
Where's Santa?
That's kind of what I was singing.
Come back here.
I need to talk to you more about
the rest of this DVD package ad part of DLC.
Come here.
Can you tell me some more about the world of Star Wars?
Ask about the First Order.
Okay.
I need to talk to Lieutenant Agnon in the First Order District.
Ask about the Resistance.
Three times.
I'm so annoying to this person.
Does this person work here?
Is that what it's...
What it's...
What it's implied?
Okay, scoundrels.
Vile scum are definitely on Batuu.
If you see anything suspicious, report to the First Order.
Can I tell you about my dreams?
I had a dream about a green alien.
It bit me.
It bit me in the face.
And I woke up.
I'm sweating.
No, scoundrels.
Okay, fun.
The festival of snow has started.
I don't care.
I'm on vacation.
Okay, I have to go to find this lieutenant.
Okay, cool.
I'm having fun on vacation.
Congratulations for completing your...
What did I say?
First mission.
Now that you have your bearings,
explore the other neighborhoods of Batuu by clicking travel in your phone.
Chinosa.
Build your reputation with three factions.
All right, let's go.
Let's go do the First Order.
Why are you so red?
I don't know.
I've been trying to figure that out for the last four hours.
All right, First Order District.
I see why people say this is the worst expansion.
How much is a lightsaber?
I just want to buy a lightsaber.
Okay, here we go.
Ask to see missions.
How much was this one?
I don't know.
I think it was like more than 15, 20 dollars.
Spread the word about our vision of the future for Black Spire Outpost.
Citizens must understand that everything we do is for their own good.
Okay, how do I do it?
Spread First Order propaganda.
To who?
This park is empty.
There's nobody here.
It's just me and the actors.
This is a really unpopular park.
Why is nobody here?
There's no other Sims here.
How do I spread propaganda?
Wait, do I have to do I take this back to the regular Sims world?
Should I give Santa propaganda?
How do I do that?
Discuss the force.
Why does he think they're actors?
Wait, are they not actors?
Is this an alien?
This is a real alien.
I don't understand where this sits.
Is this an actor?
But it's a vacation.
I'm I don't get it.
Where am I?
Stop chatting over here and get out of it.
Go over here.
You have to spread some First Order propaganda.
I want a red lightsaber.
I don't care how long it takes.
I will literally I will not go back to work until I get a red lightsaber.
Will you stop talking?
Okay, here we go.
Almost controlling his life will finally fulfill his dreams.
Oh, it's great that the First Order is here to help.
All right, I have to do this a few more times.
All right.
I am First Order.
I'm almost there.
Hey, you, come here.
This is great fucking game play.
I what I paid $20, whatever it was for this, and I'm going to do it.
And I'm going to get a lightsaber.
That's just what's happening tonight.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting I'm going to speed run a lightsaber.
I need to spread First Order propaganda.
It won't take very long.
Don't worry.
I'm going to be on vacation for like three days.
And I'm going to finally I'm going to get a lightsaber.
Scan the First Order supplies and get a blaster.
Where do I get that?
Where's your dog at dogs at the house?
But no, he's been taken care of.
I don't know where Santa is, though.
All right, I need to do four more propaganda.
Come on, let's go.
OK, that person hates me, but that's whatever in the gunk.
Take gunk droid propaganda propaganda.
OK, propaganda.
One more do.
Uh, can I make friends with what's your name?
Not to sit as a kind of friends and they invite you over to the house.
Oh, oh, it's seven.
It's seven thirty Pacific.
We all know what that means.
The Internet doesn't work for like 40 minutes.
Oh, we all know what that means.
All right.
Any propaganda?
Yeah, we just got up.
We got to ride out the storm here for about 40 minutes.
We're going to be dropping some frames.
This is how it is for some reason.
Randomly on random.
What is today?
What's today's date?
Tuesday?
All right, there it is.
Hey, it's all right.
Hey, you were going to skip this part of the stream anyways.
Well, I get my lightsaber.
It's all good.
Is that person all right?
Check your Sim's inventory.
Oh, I get a blaster.
Fake ID card.
I don't have a fake ID.
All right, I got it now.
Oh, my God, this is going to take way longer.
I thought that was going to be a full cube.
It's all right.
Well, the Internet sucks.
Don't worry.
We'll take it.
I can cheat.
I can.
Oh, that's right.
I can cheat.
Oh, Marian alien.
Let me become friends with an alien
because I'm very curious if these people,
they exist in the kind of real world,
like Earth or I don't know where we are.
Can I make friends with this person?
OK, so I'm getting a relationship status.
Easy, Yama Sprada.
Wait, I, I, I know them now.
OK, so can I invite them to parties and stuff?
Are you recording this from McDonald's?
No, it's just randomly at some.
I, dude, I wish I could tell you how this is even possible.
So this is the most ridiculous, bizarre thing.
So do you age here?
I don't know.
So from seven thirty to like seven,
like fifty or seven thirty to like eight.
My Internet goes to fucking like one percent speeds.
And then it goes back to a thousand, a thousand
for the rest of the day, all day.
It doesn't make any sense.
It makes no sense.
It goes from a thousand, a thousand at like seven twenty nine
to one megabit per second at seven thirty.
Exactly.
And then at like eight twenty PM
goes right back to a thousand thousand.
It doesn't make any sense.
All right, I need to go to the bathroom.
But this is why.
So another reason why I wanted to start my streams.
What was that alarm?
All right, I need to use the bathroom.
Where's the bathroom?
Where is the bathroom?
Oh, it's right here.
All right.
So how do I how do I cheat to get myself like plus five first order points?
Does anybody have the code?
I'll show I'll show that tomorrow.
I'll show that tomorrow.
New new viewers.
I have probably never seen that picture and I'll show it tomorrow.
All right.
So what's the cheat?
Yeah, I'll be left tomorrow.
And tomorrow I'll put mods on tomorrow.
But I'm going to make them.
We're going to do them slowly.
It's not just going to be.
Everyone gets hit by a car and everybody gets hurt.
It's going to be slow.
It's going to be going to just very slowly get into it.
Okay, what is it?
Okay, it's control shift C enter testing cheats true.
And then shift click your Sim and do give all items testing cheats true.
And then shift click and give all items.
I mean, I got to read this again.
Shift C testing cheats true.
Shift click your Sim.
Batu cheats.
Okay, this expansion sucks.
But that's not fair.
It's it's cool.
If you're a big Star Wars fan, I'm a big star.
I would probably like this.
At least I don't know.
Like what I you just walk around and like talk to people and just grind out.
I mean, it's kind of it's all right.
It's all right.
All right.
So now what do I do?
It's spring.
Pack cheats, expansion packs, name packs, batu cheats, batu reputation.
First order, add set level to rank five.
Okay, and batu cheats.
Give batu items.
Dude, I didn't want literally the end.
I didn't want every single item.
How do I take this out?
How do I use my lightsaber lightsaber?
You're lightsaber hilt collection.
Don't use a lightsaber.
What do you mean you don't use a lightsaber?
I need a crystal.
You have to make it.
Where do I go to do that?
You have to drag it out.
You need to build the lightsaber.
Control shift, click your Sim.
Woohoo.
Jabba the Hut.
It's furniture.
It's it's just a piece of furniture.
Okay.
All right, Santa, let's get out of here.
It's time to go home, Santa.
It's time to go.
Let's leave.
It's time to leave.
I thought it was going to be like a
I thought it was going to be like swinging around.
I can't leave.
Check Santa's ID.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, wait, wait, what are you doing?
Why?
What's happening?
I wanted to show my I want to put my crystal in.
What did he do?
Why did he do that?
Am I okay?
What happened?
I got knocked.
Santa knocked me out.
No, keep that out.
Don't put that on.
Keep it out.
Train with lightsaber.
Who fbs Andy?
Fuck.
I know.
Shit.
God damn it.
I got to the my favorite part of the entire day.
All right.
Shit.
You know what?
I think I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to throw an audible out here.
Yeah, I think I'm all right.
Here's what I think is going to happen.
All right.
Here's what's happening.
We're going to call it right now.
I'm going to be back tomorrow early, like in the morning.
I'm going to go all day.
I think that's the plan.
The plan is I got to start early.
I'm not starting at three o'clock tomorrow.
I'm starting at like noon tomorrow.
And I'm going to we're going to play this all day.
I'm going to put mods on it and we'll take it from there.
I got to start early.
I got to start earlier.
We got to avoid the we got to avoid the seven thirty p.m.
Internet meltdown.
So if I start at noon tomorrow between twelve and one,
then we can stream for six or seven hours and completely avoid it.
I think that's the play.
And hold me to this.
Hold me to this.
I want you to seriously hold me to this because
I can't start at three o'clock in the afternoon Pacific.
I can't I can't.
The streams have to be earlier.
There's no way you're starting at noon.
I have to, though, because like this,
we hit the seven thirty p.m. hard turnoff.
And I also called my ISP.
Where am I?
All right.
Let me save this.
I got to save this.
We're saving it.
We're going to start fresh and early tomorrow.
Come to the flea market with me.
I don't I don't have time to do this right now.
We're going to start fresh tomorrow early.
Starting at noon.
And we're going until we're going until the Internet turns us off.
I'm glad we got to go at least for four and a half hours.
That's fun.
I'll be back tomorrow.
And for those of you that have been watching for a long time,
I mean, you know, it's kind of frame ratey.
Yeah, well, I'll be live tomorrow.
Don't worry.
We'll go for about six or seven hours.
There are a lot of people here today, too.
I just if you were if you stuck around from the Among Us thing,
that's where a lot of people came from, then cool.
I hope you enjoy the stream.
I had a really fun time.
The first four hours of the stream were really funny.
Had a lot of fun.
We'll see you tomorrow.
But what's this?
Those of you.
Hey, how many old viewers from like 2016, 2017?
Are you ready?
You ready for this?
It's back.
And the music's back, too.
Give you a little bit of channel nostalgia, right?
Before we go.
You know, it's really funny about this.
This is what's supposed to be every single end of the stream.
And I just didn't put the file in OBS.
I just had to drag it over here.
And it was just in a folder.
I just didn't do it.
But thanks for watching, everybody.
I would have liked to have gone for like another hour or so,
at least five hours or so.
But, you know, I got I got to beat the Internet.
So all streams, if I want to have five to six hour streams,
all streams until further notice have to start at between 12 and 1 Pacific.
So that's the plan.
Such a weird problem.
Because sometimes we'll be live at 7, 8 p.m.
without a single problem.
It's so weird because in like an hour or so,
I'll do a speed test and it'll just be a thousand, a thousand.
It's just so random.
You're moving the goalposts already.
No, no, no, no.
Between 12 and 1230 Pacific tomorrow is what I'm going to turn the stream on.
I actually felt pretty good today.
So I felt I'm glad that I was because I'll be honest,
during the among us stream, I might never really want to do that.
That was super important because that was a really fun kind of idea
just to do that one day.
But after that stream, that was middle of covid.
I was like, I, I got to go lie down.
See you at three.
No, I can't.
I can't start at three because that means that I'm giving myself a limit of
a large percent chance that it's going to be a four hour stream.
I got to pull it back to at least one because then it's guaranteed to be
at least a five to six hour stream before we hit that kind of period
at about seven o'clock, seven thirty.
But thanks for watching.
See you tomorrow.
Have a great night.
Thanks for sticking around.
See you soon.
More Sims 4 tomorrow.
I'll probably add a few mods, but I don't want to go crazy with it.
And I hold me to that.
No more cheating.
I wanted the lightsaber.
I know, but no more cheating.
Only slightly funny mods.
And I'm going to go on a snow trip tomorrow.
I want to go on a ski trip.
I'll see you later.
Have a good night, guys.