Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Basecamp Fortress 2. Playing as the Pyro on Gorge on offense. Can I get this heavy?
Yoey! There's a one. And that what? I'm getting quick fixed. Oh, he moved. I'll get him right here. I'll get him right here. I'll get him right here.
Hey, what's up, dude? The quick fix. Come here, scout. I will get you. So I got this medic on me. Quick fix medic, baby.
That guy just disappeared. Sentry. Oh, there's no way. I need help. I need help. I need help. I need help. Come here, you.
Come on. You are not getting away. There's no way this guy's getting away. He got away.
Of course. I say there's no way he's getting away and he gets freaking away. I'm such an idiot.
Don't worry. Don't worry. I got this. Don't worry. Oh, don't worry. Don't worry about a thing.
No, medic. What? What did the bug up? Where did he come from? Whatever. Get right back into this here.
By the way, that's not Dr. Pepper. Blasphemy, I know. It's actually what? What is this? Sparkling grapefruit juice.
What kind of weird bastard am I that I'm drinking sparkling grapefruit juice? What planet am I even from?
Hit that sniper. Dude, that sniper is like going like this. What the hell is the medic doing back here?
Walk into it. Oh, you lucky butt head.
So if you're watching this right now, I am currently in North Carolina visiting my sister.
Some of you old subscribers will know that I do that every now and then. I think I went there last time during Thanksgiving.
Come here. Got him. Got him. Yeah, I went there last Thanksgiving. It was a really good time.
It's a really beautiful house, really beautiful place down there in North Carolina.
Dove before he gets that stupid thing off. I'm supposed to hit him. I don't even tell you the load that I'm using either.
I'm using the flare gun, the regular just standard flamethrower and the power jack.
We need to push this point. We need to get rid of that sentry. Can we take it out? Can I get it right now?
Come on. Keep messing with that engineer. Yes. How did I not hit him with that?
No. Get on zipped point. Hello. There you go. What's going on, medic? Thank you for the heals.
Much appreciate. Damn it. Shouldn't have done that. Mr. Winslow with the face plant. He's AFK.
That's not a good thing. You can't be AFK, man. No, none of you guys are spies. Spy check.
Spy check. Why? What was that lag? Oh, I was just choked. Wow.
I can't believe I actually killed that son of a bitch. Get rid of that sentry. Come on. Yeah.
Tan him again. Do it again. Keep messing with that engineer. Keep messing with him. Yes.
Need some help here. Need some help here. Get me out of there. Damn it. That same heavies.
We got to get on that point. Big time. How many sentries are over there? I'm going to go around the left side this time.
No, no, no. Where are you going? You're not going to... This guy's probably going to kill me.
No, I'm going to miss, but that's all right because he's... Where is he? Where the hell is this guy going?
I'll find you. And when I find you, you're going to get your face ripped off. I'll take it. I'll take it.
How can I not hit the guy that's standing still? Why are they both doing that? Why are they both doing this?
How many is it going to take to kill this son of a... All right. Fine. I'll just smash you.
You want to get smashed? God. Oh my God. That was terrifying. Didn't even need to hit him.
We're going to lose. Come on. Give me those heals. Turn around. Turn around, man.
I got to try and kill that engineer. That's what I wanted. Get him. Hit him.
I'm trying to wait for him just to come across the middle. Oh, this is not good. We're so dead. We're so dead.
Wait. Demoman, go. Quickly. Quickly. Quickly. Quickly. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yeah. Can I get there in 15 seconds? I don't think I'm going to be able to get there in 15 seconds.
What? What? What on earth? I landed on top of that guy's head. Oh my God.
Okay. That's the first time that's ever happened to me.
Imagine if I had the Mantreads on. That guy would have been tombastomped.
Itch. Defense. Damn. Let's play a little bit of the defense.
Nice sentry. Very good start. Sniper. Trying to shoot me in my face. And a heavy.
This guy's not going to... Maybe he is. I got to get behind him. Come here.
Somebody just come here. Two scouts. I'll wrap around you. Yeah.
Give me a heal, man. I need a heal. I need a heal.
Damn. You are a jumpy little freak. Close him in here. Close him in big time.
No. No. No. Everybody get blown out. This guy's got crits. I'm trying to blow people out.
No. Run. Get him. Please. Please die. He's still alive.
Oh. No. He died that far. That long after I shot him. He needed to get a health kit.
Click, click, click, click, click. They're going to capture this.
No. We can't lose two in a row. We got to hold them for four minutes. Come on, dudes.
I might have to switch off pyro. That's something that might have to happen here.
Any spies? Don't think so. Medic. That medic is just standing back there.
Oh my god. That's a second sick shot of the day. Wrap it up and give it to me for Christmas.
Stay away from the sentry. Get this stuff away from the sentry. I got you. Don't worry, buddy. I got you.
I got you. Protecting your sentry. Nothing's going to take this down unless a spy comes behind us.
We good? That dome man still hanging out here? No, but there's a sniper right there.
Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here. I'm trying, man. There's nothing I can do, really.
I'm trying to kill him. They came from behind.
Oh, now we got to hold this for 11 minutes. We're going to get smoked right here.
We are going to get absolutely smoked. Oh, man. Oh, man. Oh, man.
But as you're watching this right now, I'll be on the plane to North Carolina, like I said.
Should be a great time. I love my sister, as I'm sure a lot of you guys have siblings.
Never get to see her that often anymore, which is unfortunate, but I'm going to die.
Give me a crit. Do we have anything on the blast point? I don't think so.
I think we're just dead. No, no, no. We're going to go demo.
You could always go demo and try to make something crazy happen.
Three on the point. Oh, well, that's going to wrap up Face Game Fortress, guys.
I'll see you all next time. And I got something going up tomorrow.
I got Scare Saturdays. Scare Saturdays is returning tomorrow with the game Gray,
the Half-Life 2 mod Gray. So look forward to that.
I'll see you guys when I get back on Sunday. And of course, take care, everybody.