Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here and MLC Stealth.
Hello. Hello. We are going to be reviving an old series we used to do called Timed Chaos Build.
If you don't know what this is, it's where we give ourselves a certain amount of time
to build an object or animal, and we have to stop when we get to the end of that time.
So, what are we building today, MLC Stealth? Jerma, today we are going to be building a parrot.
A parrot? One of those old pirate-style parrots. So, if you are ready. Oh, dude, I forgot about that.
It doesn't even match. Well, match it. I did. All right, well, we're going to try and build a parrot in
six minutes, and whatever we end up with, with is what we end up with. So, are you ready?
Yeah, I think so. In three, two, one. Wait, hold on. My timer messed up. Three, two, one, go.
Okay, parrot. How does it start? It needs feet, right? Why does he have like coal for feet?
Why do you have that color? Because that's the, like, it's toes. Oh, I don't have that color.
Oh, I got it. He's going to be huge. All right, fine. All right.
It has to be. And then we have to do it to the side, too. Whoops. Wait, what are you doing?
I'm trying to, like, continue it. Let me undo everything. All right. All right, you do the feet.
I'll do, I'll do the... All right, so let's do this here. Listen now. Oh, crap. I didn't do that.
Right. That's his leg. All right. Almost a minute has gone by. We didn't hurry this up. Oh, yeah.
We haven't, like, even started yet, huh? There we go. Hey, his butt's got to come out kind of far
because don't, like, parrots have, like, big butts with tails? I don't know. Yeah, they do.
So, there's going to be a green... I thought we were doing, like, a yellow parrot.
We are. Now, change this to red. Wait, he's green, though. Yeah, but he's green just until
this part. So, complete this. Wait, he's a different color? Yeah, parrots are, like, a ton
of different colors. Aren't they, like, tropical colored, kind of? I don't know. Yeah, they are.
I probably should have Googled parrot before this part. All right. No, no, no, no. Now, we have to
go, um, to red. This is already looking like our horse that we did first. No, it's not going to be.
It'll be better. Oh, no. Get it. How many... They only have two legs. Like, you need to make this
even. Like, it's all right. This way, too. Because here's his tail. Tail? Yeah. All right. We're
making Qbert right now. So, let's... All right, yellow. He's got to have a yellow, like, belly.
Oh, it's getting, like, dark in this area. Don't worry. I could change the time if we need it.
Two minutes are gone by. Oh, good. All right. Already, he's looking like a
pancake. Why? Gold plated. He's like... This parrot's, like, doing very well, apparently.
Oh, these gold plates don't mesh together very well. It doesn't make one, like, solid chunk,
does it? No, it doesn't. But you know what? It's too late. I think it's coming along okay.
This just looks like corn. Like, corn on top. He really is made out of corn.
No, this is going to look like an owl. Just keep building. Just keep building. We'll deal with it.
All right. I'll come up this way. Three minutes have almost gone by. We're halfway there.
We need to make his body a little bit more fat. All right. I'll deal with that. You deal with the
body. He's way too big. He's... What is he? He's not even anything. He's a block on top of a block.
We're just putting shapes together and calling it a parrot.
He looks... He looks like the road runner. If the road runner had, like,
ran... It looks like the road runner ran into a wall and, like, squished his face.
All right. Now that's enough of that. Now we need to stop making the head.
Yeah, they have heads. What is that, like, corn on the cob body?
We need a beak. We need to be... We need his head first.
It looks like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle.
It looks like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle coming out of a corn on the cob,
sitting on top of a table. This is the worst thing ever. Oh, whoa. What's going on? Saving?
No, we need a beak. We need a beak first. The beak has to be red.
Beak comes out like this, and this comes out too.
It's like platypus. This looks like a duck.
No, because we're going to give him, like, a big feathered head back here.
Oh, good. Glad we're doing that.
Four minutes and 28 seconds. Look, this is looking good. Look at that.
He only looks like somebody, like, threw up on their screen.
This is not a parrot. This is some, like, cartoon network.
This is a character from, like, Foster's Home for Imaginary Kids.
He really is a character from, like, Cartoon Network.
And apparently he's super saiyan right now.
All right, one minute left.
Oh, got to finish the body.
All right, what happened on this side of his head?
I got to fix up his mouth. His mouth is awful.
Everything about this is awful. He's not a parrot.
No, yes, he is. Yes, he is. He doesn't have wings. He doesn't have wings.
He doesn't have wings. We got to give him, like, wings. Oh, God.
I thought his wings are, like, a part of his body. Like, they combine.
He, like, retracts them so they're invisible.
No, not anymore. He has wings now. 30 seconds.
Oh, look at that, like, beautiful parakeet.
15 seconds. Clean it up.
This guy looks like he's in pain.
This guy is in severe physical pain.
Five, four, three, two, one, and there it is.
You touched his wings to his, like...
Doesn't he look like he's screaming?
He's just got, like, run over by a bus and he's waiting to die.
He seriously looks like he is screaming, like...
Like this hurts.
Look at his staircase for a back.
Oh, yeah, good. Awesome. Let's, like, walk up the staircase
that's supposed to be the parrot's back onto the creamed corn body.
Oh, that's so funny. Look at these eyes.
Okay, he's just like a normal green parrot,
but he's wearing, like, a yellow towel and the, like,
yellow woman's shower gown that they wrap around their hair.
Like, he just got out of the shower and he wrapped two towels,
one around his body, one around his hair.
Yeah, he just got out of the shower.
Oh, that's so funny. All right, so you guys are gonna give this guy a name
and a rating. One to ten.
I think the rating's gonna be pretty low for this one.
Lost his home for imaginary friends.
Oh, that's so funny.
All right, guys, well, thanks so much for watching
and we'll see you all next time.
And, of course, take care, everybody.