Oh, this is a disaster. I don't even have my lip balm. This is a disaster. Give me one second.
This is a disaster. One sec. This is like the weirdest tweet I think I've ever made.
Fucking weird tweet. You laugh, you lose in baby sensory videos today. I've come a long way from
I'm playing Spy on Upward today. What's going on here? Okay, my mic's in a weird place. I got
some new monitors and I'm in the process of making them, getting them set up in a good spot.
And I messed up where my microphone is. I can't even stream yet. I can't even stream today. I'm
gone. This is too much. This is too much for me. I'm gonna go. Okay, I gave you some updates on
some things because I think you deserve them. It's been four or five days since I've said hello to
you. An update on the New Year's Eve stuff. I, the, this dominations obviously have been closed for
about a week. Going through the process of eliminating a bunch of these
nominees has been ridiculous considering, if I'm accurate, I believe there were,
and this is going after going through a first pass through, right? So everybody nominates shit.
We do a first pass through of, okay, duplicates and stuff that just really doesn't belong there
in that category. It doesn't belong here. No, no, no, not this one. After the first pass through,
there's like, I think like 50 best noise nominees that are still there. So I, it's gonna, I have to,
I have to do a lot of reducing. If I can get it down to like 20, have I really, I don't,
have I made that many? I remember somebody said, what's your official comment on the egg stream?
I streamed myself eating like hard boiled eggs or something as an incentive of like dying in
Team Fortress. I don't know, it was like, it was like eight, it was like nine years ago.
Make a best noise, do it again. No, please hurry. Let me get some updates. Updates, updates, updates,
updates, updates. You peaked on the egg stream. Well, that's weird considering I think there were
like 40 people on that stream. Interesting that I thought I had a little bit, a little bit higher
view numbers than that now. Okay. So here's what we're going to do. What? I didn't even update you.
Okay. So I'm going to say something that might sound a little,
there might be some shocked faces here, but the nature of how many nominees have come in,
I'm not saying this yet. I have not said this yet. So don't quote me on this, but just like put it
in brackets and then quote it. I might not do it on New Year's Eve. We might be one of those like
January, like there for, there's a dead pixel on this monitor. I just got it.
What is it? I got a dead pixel right in front of me. It's just a green dot. Come on. Oh, that sucks.
That actually sucks. Maybe. I mean, okay. Come on. Really? I didn't see it. I didn't see it here
before. You mad about one pixel. Yeah. I mean, when you, when you spend the money on one of these
monitors, reset it. Sometimes dead pixels kind of just out of there. And then they,
they just kind of flicker out, right? That's annoying. All right. The monitor is a, I got a
predator. I don't know the company. I actually don't even remember the company's name. I don't
know. Is it a Zeus? Asus? I don't know. I don't know what, what, who made this Acer is an Acer
predator. And it's, I turned it on. It was pretty good, but whatever. We'll, we'll, I won't complain
about that right now. Asus. Yeah. No, they don't. I don't know. So, all right. So I don't know. I'm
not sure if I want to move it like a few days just to make sure we have everything good. I have not
said that yet. I might just do double time here in the next few days to make sure that that actually
happens. Cause there's also rumble too. So we'll see if I get it on New Year's Eve, but don't be
surprised if it's like two or three days into the new year. We'll see. I have not committed to that
yet. I'm going to try. I'm not canceling it. No, no way. So what we're doing today is something
I've been talking about for a long time. It is a, let me turn my light on. So this stream is going
to be a, you laugh, you lose. I've never done it before. There's been a list of meme videos and
there's a, there's a playlist that I'm about to watch. It's got like 200 videos on it or something.
And it's just memes and funny shit. And we'll see if it gets me. If I laugh, we have a few incentives
next summer. I do. I, I think I just read that completely wrong. My microphone's in the wrong
place. And there's a dead pixel on my monitor. This is too much for me. I think I'm done.
Okay. So eat an egg sandwich. No, no, no. Then I'm not doing like incentives where if I laugh three
times, I have to do a headstand and drink a glass of milk. No. I am, I am like the uncle on Christmas
that doesn't buy presents for anybody. He just shows up with cash. Here you go. Here you go.
And here you go. That's $50 for each of you. So here's what we're going to do. Uh,
I'm going to make a pool of money every time I laugh and it has to be an audible laugh. It can't
be, I know look smiling. You're the best uncle ever. Yeah. No smiling, no smirks, no like,
you know what I'm talking about? None of that. It has to be like,
that's what we're talking about. We could do, we could change these rules a little bit out when
we get closer. Cause I have, I get, I'm going to pause it. I get to pause it at least a few times.
I don't think, no belly laugh only. I don't think so. It doesn't have to be a belly laugh.
It just has to be very clearly. I have like, I'm like, I've laughed. I will accept, um,
like if my mouth opens and a bunch of air comes out and it's like, that counts.
Face cam. Well, of course I'm going to do a face cam. So, but after that, we're going to watch a
few baby sensory videos. Um, I have found some, I've got about like half dozen, I think or so.
They're all, they're all pretty long and I don't know how this can play out. They look
fucking really weird. I am also considering, uh, activating what I would call hard mode.
Um, for myself, I'm going to just kind of hang out for a little bit and hard mode might activate
and, uh, it'll be hard to do this. It's, I might activate hard mode.
Well, I will see. I don't know if I'm going to activate hard mode.
Difficulty difficulty. What the fuck? So I, let's switch it over here because
let's see what's going on now. I have it ready. I know the title and that this is a playlist.
So this is just going to go, by the way, for every time that I laugh or like the first,
we'll go with the first, maybe 30 minutes. I don't have like a brand necessarily a plan,
but we're going to have a pool of money. And every time I laugh,
a hundred dollars is going to get added to that pool. Once the pool has been filled
at the end of the stream, I'm going to decide what is going to happen with that money.
A hundred dollars every time I laugh. I've never, yes, I'm, I'm like copy,
copy cat Andy. All right. I've never done this before. It seemed like fun.
Yeah, there's this charity. There's yeah, I probably will. A majority of it will go to charity.
I have a few things that I've in mind, a few places in mind, so we'll figure it out.
But a hundred bucks gets added to that pool. So are you, are you ready? Am I? Well,
hold on. The better question is, am I ready? I, I don't know. We'll find out. And I know I might
look like, I might look like a little weird today because I have this like thing here.
I've got this light. Do I look like I'm looking like a low, but I've tried. You need to be able
to see my face today. I don't care how shitty it looks. It's like a candle lit stream. Yeah.
It's very warm. And you see me well, right? You need to be able to see my face because if I go
like, then you need to be able to pick it up. Is the cam too small? I don't want the cam to be
because we're about to put the playlist on. I think there's 200 videos in this playlist.
Well, I said charity pool, but we're just going to call it pool just for now. Pool. Okay. A hundred
bucks. If I, all right, can I get it out of my system right now? Like when, when does it start?
I do look fucking evil. He's high. I've not activated hard mode. Hard mode is not going
to activate as soon as I click play. Okay. What if I lose immediately? What happens? Oh, I had money.
Okay. What can you make an incentive where if you laugh, you kiss the camera?
That is so weird. That's so fucked up. All right. That's the first incentive. If I laugh,
I'll kiss the camera. You ready? Make sure you guys can, can you guys hear this? Don't spoil this.
It doesn't count yet. I haven't really started. Some of these might be loud. Just be aware of
that. I don't know. Okay. Here we go. Your wicked parasocial. What? I always tell people don't do
that because I'm just a fucking weirdo that you don't know on the internet. You don't know me.
You don't even like me in real life. I guarantee it. All right. Here we go. One, two, three.
Yeah. Holy shit. Wow.
Um, there's some Scottish people that kind of say
the
I wasn't expecting Vince McMahon to show up. I put a hundred dollars in here. Oh no, it's kiss the
camera. How do I do this without being weird? This is, I don't want to do this. I don't want
to do this. Oh no. No, I don't think so. I was weird, isn't it? Okay. How about this?
All right. I got it. I did it. I'm not doing that. Something like that again.
Oh, son of a bitch. Me, Austin. It was me all along, Austin.
That was cute.
I thought this was a baby sensory video. I was about to laugh.
Armand Christophe. Don't worry. We'll get him. Can I help you? We'll get him. What's he doing
over there? That was closer than it was besides the Austin one. Oh, I am not drunk. I am not
fucking drunk. Can you tell the time? Yes. I am not fucking drunk.
This one's very interesting.
I almost, I almost laughed at this because it was weird. Cover all 9,000 taste buds,
aerate it, warm it up, driving up that top note, that cream, pure vanilla,
sweeteners. That's a 10. I've seen this video a million times. I love it. Not this one in particular,
but
I ain't never seen no muzzles on there, but it might be good though. My dad didn't know
about it. I'm out of here to him all around and then I'm going to rub it smooth everywhere.
Mustard. Come on, man. I don't put no mustard. You need to put a little seed on that thing.
What? Man, come on. Get that pep off there. Come on. Somebody come get this, man. Come on,
come on. Get that pep off. That's just too much dog on pep. I don't really want to see this no more.
That's really all you look for brisket. Oh my God.
We're good. We're good. We're good.
Twitter stinks. I'm leaving.
That just scared the shit out of me. That was weird. We saw people in the streets ready to put
2018 in the rear view mirror and say hello to 2019. We also saw this dog with a banana.
A festive atmosphere in the heart of downtown Orlando is what it's all about.
From the skyline, would you like to try our new chicken tendie and french fry combo?
Hell no. Can I get a chicken tendie combo, please? That was so stupid.
What the fuck was that? That was just bizarre. Can I get a chicken tendie combo, please?
That was you working the drive-through. That was just weird. It was just like,
why would somebody ever do something like that? Are you sitting in front of a fireplace? All right,
let me add it. What do they even say? You have the angel filter on. Okay, that's $100.
I want to see this one again. Some of these I've seen. Some of these I've never seen before.
Hell no. Can I get a chicken tendie combo, please?
Okay, all right, all right, all right. Again? Does that count? That shouldn't count twice.
No, no, it doesn't count twice. We were paused. What the fuck? It counts? Should it actually count,
though? Oh, move the camera. Where should I move it? Either 200 or fine. Now it counts. All right.
Yeah, I can't. I'm usually, here's the thing, like, I'm usually pretty immune to most kind of like
memes, but sometimes they get me. I, sometimes they work. We're getting a lot of community subs.
Okay, here we go. Back to it. Holy fuck. I'm so sorry.
That's me. I was laughing at that. That was fucking disgusting. That doesn't count if I laugh at my
own stupid bullshit. No, I didn't laugh at this. That doesn't count, right? Did you guys hear that?
That was an audible disgusting burp and I did like the old man thing. All right,
stop. Stop making me fucking laugh. I'm not looking at chat anymore. You didn't hear it?
Okay, thank God. It was, thank God my noise gate didn't pick it up. All right.
It doesn't count. You're going to cheapen the real ones. Yeah. All right. So stays at 300.
I thought this was going to be really easy. Like the first 10 or 15 videos were just like,
ah, these are humors. You suck at this. This is why I don't do these. I'm such a fucking like,
I'm one of the weasels from Who Framed Roger Rabbit. Guys, I laugh when like my car gets
bumped in GTA. Do you think I'm going to laugh? It's going to be like fucking 50 grand. All right,
I'll add it. No more. I guarantee it for at least the next 10 videos. Guaranteed. One, two, three.
That was just, they just put a bunch of weird shit in the video.
Necromancy may be legal in Cyrodiil, but few will openly admit to practicing it now that
the Major's Guild has banned it. Farewell. Classic. Rest in peace. Forgot about that part.
Richie. What? I might be stuck in the bathroom. I don't care.
That was small. Yeah. Can I get a sausage and mushroom pizza? Hey, how you doing? Can I get a
sausage and mushroom pizza? How you doing? Can I get a sausage and mushroom pizza? How you doing?
Oh, my head.
I love this. Ship my pants. Right here. Ship my pants. You're kidding. You can ship your pants
right here. You hear that? I can ship my pants for free. Wow. I just may ship my pants. Yeah,
ship your pants. Billy, you can ship your pants too. I can't wait to ship my pants, dad. I just
ship my pants. It's legal. It's very convenient. Very convenient. I just ship my drawers. I just
ship my nighties. She's saying shit. I just shipped my pants. They're actually saying shit. If you can't
find what you're looking for in store, we'll find it at kmart.com right now and ship it to you for
free. What is it, citizen? If you've got to travel, by the nine divines, stay on the roads. It's the
digra, you see. By the nine divines. Assault. Assault. You elves are all the same. All flash
and no fear. Let me tell you, I gotta pause it. I tell you right now, all the Skyrim and Oblivion
memes don't do anything to me. Zero. Because I've only played those games with like Kermit the Frog
fucking mods and like Thomas the Tank Engine engine and shit and like huge monsters and stuff. It does
nothing to me. Because that by comparison is like nothing to like Kermit the Frog chasing you with
a fucking battle axe. I've never played those games normally. Ever. Oh. I found some wild blizzies.
Hi, my name is Carla Shaw. You can stop at five or six stores or just one. I don't need friends.
They disappoint me. Hi, I'm Todd Le Roux. You could stop at five or six stores or just one.
I feel like a deer in the headlights of love. I feel like I probably have a video like this.
Like I've like auditioned for things before. You could stop at five or six stores or just
one. You could stop at five or six stores or just one. I would kill it, by the way. Can I ask you
kind of a weird question? You could stop at five or six stores or just one. I am the queen of the
universe. The waves part. Cry it? And they engulf me and the water is warm. You think I'd do a better job?
Or just one. I can see the Statue of Liberty from here.
You could stop at five or six stores. This fucking guy. I swear to God. The only reason why I laughed at that
is because like I just like seeing like weirdly into the future. I'm seeing like a thousand years
into the future or whatever. That's way too long. That's like gonna be me. Like the movements and shit.
Reenact one. You're gonna undie. All right. You want me to try it? I have, okay. I can't stand up.
I'll do it right here. I have to stand up. All right. Well, I got like shorts on. Just fucking
relax. Hold on. I might, I gotta tie this. I have to like tie my little, I don't count.
I have like pajama shorts on. Okay. So it's, you could stop at five or six stores or just one
and then say like a weird Bible quote or something, right? Okay. Here we go. Turn off the room.
You could stop at, how do you do that? You could stop at five or, you could stop at five or six
different stores. Just one. That's what gets you to fucking roll. They know you got emotion.
I actually jumped. I'm so far away. I'm all the way back here. I went like, yeah. How loud was
that? Was that loud? It got me. It did. What did I do? You were coming for us. Was that really that
bad? That actually made me jump. You charged at us. I don't know. It was that bad. I think it was okay.
It was loud. It was loud. All right. All right. I'm not doing that ever again. Let's go.
You scared the shit out of me. I jumped. Oh, sorry. I scared you. Your, your jump was disjointed.
Let me see it. How was it really that loud? Hold on. Let me, let me, hold on. Let me watch it.
I can't hear it. You could stop it. Oh, here we go. Okay. You see it? Right. Wait, that's freaking me
out. You could stop at five or six different stores. Just one. Just one. Wild eyes. That's how
you scare the coyotes away. Yeah. That's like, there, there are like bears in your backyard.
There are animals in your backyard and you're like, hey, hey. All right. Let's go.
Just for just one. I can't stand it when she touches me. People say that time heals all wounds.
I love this song. I'm going to say something to you right now that I've never said to an
all loving soul in my life. No. Stand. Stand. And then there's Chunky. He's dead. That's my
favorite video on YouTube. Chunky's dead. He's dead. I sneezed. Oh, I'm not allowed to sneeze.
I love all these videos. Why are there so many captions?
Why are captions turned on? It counts. I laughed at both of them in a row.
The only reason why I laughed at the second one was because the captions were on the screen.
What happened here? It was just so alarming. Is that Daffy?
He's fucking dead. Like he's dead. That kills somebody. Look at his face. He's so fucked up.
He has a gun. I don't know. Something about that is just, I don't understand the second one, but it
was. Did you know we've come? You want to fight? Why? This is not going to make me laugh. I did it.
Yes. All right, sir. Good one, sir. Good one. He's got the package.
Bomb, sir. The bomb. Defusing. Defuse. Bomb site secure. Bomb site secure.
Ready for you to defuse the bomb. Bomb site secured. Bomb site under control.
Where's the bomb? Where's the bomb? Where's this, sir? The time is running out.
The title. What's this title, man? The title is Zoomer Humor. I can't help it. It's like I'm,
okay. Jeez. It's just, it's too much going on. Zoomer humor. I don't know. You know what it is?
It's the fact that there are just so many sound effects. And so it's so fast. Like that, like,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's just like your brain doesn't know what else
to do besides laugh because there's no other emotion that makes any sense at all. Nothing else
makes sense. It's just like all the different images. Okay, I feel like when you close your
eyes, right, when you're going to sleep, let me know if anybody else has this happen to them.
When you close your eyes and you're sleeping and you're just about to hit that place where you're,
all right, I've gone unconscious and I'm falling asleep. There's this moment where your mind just
kind of goes wherever it just races. You'll go to random places. You'll be sitting at a restaurant
opposite side like Obama, just sitting there and having a conversation. All of a sudden you'll
feel or hear like the wind will blow. The door will open and there is snow outside and I'm going
to go outside. There's snow out there. There's a hamster in the snow. Our minds do this weird
thing right before falling asleep. That's what this is. And having, and having it be in a conscious
state and seeing it rather than kind of feeling it while you're sleeping is just, I can't do it.
It's too much. Okay, so that was by far the biggest one for sure. I can't imagine if this is on hard
mode. All right, let me update this. The fact that like somebody made this like specifically
and they titled it this weird title. All right, you have to go back and do it again.
Where are we? Okay, here. I'm going to lose, I think it's going to, I'm going to fuck it up again.
Yeah, it's just surreal. It's just so, everything is so odd. Okay, I'm fine.
Okay, I got through it. That was cute. That was really cute. That wasn't even funny. It was cute.
See, you motherfuckers are going to think this is funny.
You may got the honey, but I got the sugar.
Croissant.
Beans.
Let's see. Cream and mushrooms. Bro, she might have made beans, but you forgot about the
macaroni and cheese. What do you want? Creamy Italian cheddar cheese.
Well, you may have the cheddar cheese, but I've got
Oh, so it's just scary. What are you eating? I miss my wife tails. I miss her a lot. I'll be back.
I was doing this. Oh, it's on 720p. This is adorable. This is so cute. I just like this
little hamster. Hey, does anybody want coffee? Who wants coffee? I've seen this guy. Anybody
want coffee? Who wants coffee? Do you want coffee? I just made coffee. Do
anybody want coffee? Who want coffee? I just make coffee. Who wants coffee?
Anybody want coffee?
Who wants coffee?
Does anybody want coffee?
Do you want coffee?
Who wants coffee?
Does anybody want coffee?
Is it that bad?
Oh, that was close.
Howdy, y'all. This here's Mike.
Down at Mike's Golf.
Ugh.
It was just the transition between these two.
It was the howdy.
It just goes from XQC
blowing out his microphone
to howdy. I don't know.
It was like the transition here.
Whatever.
Howdy, y'all. This here's Mike. Down at Mike's Golf.
Are the capsules supposed to be on?
Where we buy golf. That's right.
We buy golf clubs.
Mike's Golf Shop.
Come on over here. We buy
golf clubs.
Over at Mike's Golf Shop.
Come on down here. We buy golf
clubs. That's right.
We buy golf clubs.
We buy golf
clubs. We buy
golf clubs.
We buy golf clubs.
That muffin is looking awfully
like a hamster. Someone
baked a hamster into my
muffin. What is that?
He's not going to turn and eat the frog, right?
Oh! Oh!
I'm safe on this one, I think.
I like these movements, though.
It's loud. It's very loud.
That was just scary.
That was scary.
Freezing my nuts off.
Perfect. Thank you.
Brahma. Freezing my nuts off.
That's just cute.
No, not this one.
Not this one.
I forgot about this video.
Why would they do that?
Aren't bits of sweaty? What are you talking about?
You're laughing.
It's fucking crazy.
It's just so stupid.
It's the fact that
Oh, look, I'm sitting there, funny picture of me
with a cap on or whatever, and it's
just like this car.
Alright, whatever.
I haven't seen this video in a long time.
That's how I knew I was fucking screwed.
It's always...
Okay, I have to start it over.
We got a thousand bucks in the pool right now.
It's just this
photo...
Whatever. You know, I don't have to say it again.
I fail. Let's go.
I'm gonna get
fucking locked here.
I have to get over it.
It's the... You've done a lot together.
It's just... I can't...
It's... Fuck.
This is bad.
Once I get stuck, I get stuck for a while.
Okay. You're insane.
You're gonna get stun locked here.
I'm gonna try... Okay.
Why are you laughing? It's fucking crazy.
I'm gonna try...
It's so stupid.
No!
If any of the videos...
I have to... I need to take a minute.
I can't... You can't skip it.
That's not how this works.
We're at $1,200 now.
I'm gonna get through this one. I'm gonna get through it.
I just have to hide. Everybody relax.
It's the music, too.
The music is so... And this photo in the very beginning.
No!
I can't. I'm sorry.
Okay. Skip it for $500?
No. I can get it.
I swear to God, I can get it.
It's a... Oh, remember this?
Like, we just remembered it.
You don't make us remember this again. It's horrible.
I don't want to remember this. I don't even want to think of this again.
Alright. Last try.
And then I'm skipping it for $100.
Okay.
Try. And then I'm skipping it for $100.
I'm gonna get through it this time. I have to have seen it enough time.
God damn it.
I remember this video, too.
And I have just spent so long.
Okay. This is it. This is the one.
Thank you for watching!
Get it off! Turn it off! Turn it off! I've done it too many times.
Oh my god, my head hurts.
I'm good. Uh, let's do Ocarina of Time.
Ocarina of Time.
Hello. Two tickets, please.
For what? Moving.
Hey, Tony, what's going on?
Tony, what the fuck is this?
What the fuck? Tony!
Tony, what the fuck is this, Tony?
Tony, I did what I thought was best for the family, motherfucker!
You gotta believe me, Tony!
Please don't shoot the fucking gun, Tony!
Oh my god!
This is cute.
Not even real.
This one's a piece of cake.
You motherfuckers.
Turn camera!
102, take one.
With overlap. Action, please.
I'm gonna get locked on this one too.
Action, awesome, please.
It doesn't do anything?
No, sorry, cut.
102, take two.
Ah, the French Champagne has always been celebrated for its excellence.
There is a California Champagne by Paul Masson.
So drunk.
Inspired by that same French excellence.
It's fermented in the bottle and like the best French Champagne.
It's vintage dated.
Cut.
So Paul Masson.
102, take three.
I think I'm gonna be alright.
Action, please.
Champagne has always been celebrated for its excellence.
There is a California Champagne by Paul Masson.
Inspired by that same French excellence.
It's fermented in the bottle and like the best French Champagne.
It's vintage dated.
So Paul Masson.
Alright, we're good.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
Orson Welles right there is as drunk as you are.
As you are.
When you get to that point where you have to put your phone up like this.
And hold one eye open to like see if the lift driver is there.
Not fun.
I love this video.
I'm not even gonna laugh at this.
This video is just a good video.
Let me move some of this stuff out of the way.
This is a great video.
I don't think I'm gonna laugh.
La la la la la.
La la.
La la la.
La la la la.
La la.
It's so weird.
Alright, I'm gonna freak people out.
La la la la la.
La la.
Trump dog?
La la la la la.
I played this on stream already.
La la.
If that was you on the phone and you on the bus.
Then who was flickering the lights?
It's me Austin!
Oh son of a bitch!
You already got me with that one.
Oh god!
Why did you come by train today?
Very excited about my new fridge.
Look.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where's the water?
That just sucks. What happened?
Fuck.
I'm staying up extra late tonight
to see a test train pull into Brighton station.
One of my favorite locomotives
might be on it so we'll just have to wait and see.
There's 73962!
Oh it's it!
It's it!
Oh quick, I've got to get around.
I've got to get around to see it.
This is beautiful 73962.
Dick my butt.
What?
What a beautiful locomotive she is.
Check out all the gear in there.
That's not real!
Marvelous loco.
I'm glad I stayed up late for this.
This is a treat.
That's a real train?
In the beaning.
In the in
the beaming.
Yeah.
Listen properly.
In the beaming.
Yeah.
The beaming.
I n.
In- in the be- in the beeninging. In the beeninging.
Three, two, one.
Fast, sharp right. Fast, sharp right. Sharp right.
Sammy, fall, Sammy, please. Medium left, watching out the-
Sammy, you have to stay on the road, Sammy. Otherwise-
Sammy, you're gonna break the car.
Can you just imagine, like, somebody sitting behind Donkey Kong just yelling all this shit to him?
Ugh. You need to stay- when they go up and they do the gliding-
Holy shit, I'm sweating my ass off!
Ugh. It's always cars, I know!
Something about vehicles, just cars, I don't know why, they're just so-
Something about it just does it to me. I don't get it.
1400. It's alright. I don't- it's just like the way he's turning and it-
The car's bump- you don't even go- that doesn't even happen to you in Mario Kart.
Okay. You're admitting it. I'm just finding out what I think is-
Is it just big, bulky machines that we just drive around?
It's so weird that we do this in the first place.
Don't you guys think it's just bizarre that we drive around in cars anyways?
Like, it's such a weird object.
We have this machine that we all just sit in and it just goes fast.
It's just like a- what a fucking weird device.
Okay. Let's update it.
And- alright, I'm gonna try this one again.
He's got the notepad to- ugh.
I'm gonna try this one more time. I think I can get through it.
It was just this part here when he's yelling at him to stay on the road because they're flying.
Here we go! Do hard mode? Maybe. Let's go.
You didn't laugh at the train.
That was more unusual to me than funny.
Go.
Shut up, too.
I'm good. I'm good. That was rough.
What do you mean? They're for everybody but only for you?
Granny, they're dog treats.
No! No!
Oh, that was close. Just her- they only-
Squish that cat. All you need to know is to squish that cat.
And you just gently squish them.
That's not comfortable for the cat or that's safe to be honest with you.
You can just throw a towel on the cat again, squish her with a towel.
What you can do is scoop her up, a little football carry, just like that.
Butt in your hand and just squish her tight to your body.
Just squish him really tight to your body.
You don't have to worry about hurting a cat.
Just squish him against your body.
And there we go. We just made friends with this wonderful little cat.
Look at that face.
Squishing is your best friend when you're dealing with a cat.
You basically just lean forward, squish him nice and tight.
And again, I'm just squishing them into myself.
We always squish that cat.
I'm just confused by that one. Squish?
Why do I feel like this is an edited video from like four different scenes of this movie but it's not?
The end. The scream at the end.
I've seen so many of those breathing videos but it doesn't matter.
I think I just missed one.
How much longer? I don't know. I don't want to look.
Macho Man Randy Savage had some classic breathing videos too.
Alright, let me add it.
I feel like I don't have to watch that one again because I got to the very end and I laughed after the video ended.
30k viewers, what's up?
Welcome to the stream. This is a You Laugh You Lose slash Baby Sensory stream.
Uh, this is fun.
What's going on? What's up everybody?
Okay. I didn't laugh at this one. Let's start this one over.
What is Baby Sensory? I might go hard mode for that one. We'll find out.
Please cut the ringing. It sounds kind of like a...
I know what I have to do but I don't know if I have the strength to do it.
Jesus!
Even the babies are one of the most dangerous animals in the world so I built this cage to keep them secure so there's no possible...
Oh my god.
You know what I'm saying? If I miss this joke, I'm low key. If I miss this joke, I'm gay as hell. I'm gay as hell if I miss this joke.
Yo, Baba, how's the food tasting?
Oh, this stuff is buzzing. Respectfully. No kidding.
Oh, what about you Abuji?
I knew he was going to say it too. That's the worst part. He just screamed it.
Whatever. I have Zoom or humor. I don't care.
I don't give a shit. Whatever.
Make a well-crafted joke.
No, I don't think it's funny. I don't care. You give a whole story of something funny that happened.
Get an old guy to say sheesh on camera and I'm gone.
It's just the first part. The first part of the Zoom or humor is funny.
I think they're quick. That's something I think Zoomers don't get a lot of credit for. Zoomers are quick.
Now, a lot of Zoom or humor I think falls. It just goes right off my head.
But man, they're quick. They're quick.
They're quick.
The best part about Zoom or humor is because it's so quick, even if it sucks, it's over in three seconds.
If I don't like a boomer or like older person's joke or something, I might have to sit there for four minutes while they tell me.
Shit's over in two seconds if you're a Zoomer.
Alright, I just want to see it again because I like it.
We're getting so many subs too. This is ridiculous. Thanks everybody.
25 from you.
Well, OK, I think it's time to do a hard one.
Unionize your workplace. Thanks for 25 community subs.
And then we had 10 from David Shower. Thank you.
OK, I just want to see it again.
Oh, Baba, how's the food tasting?
Oh, this stuff is buzzing.
You can tell he's waiting his turn to do the joke.
No.
It gets me too.
What about you, Abuji?
Shit!
Do you know why he's called Colonel Sanders?
No, why?
Because he is...
Hello, America.
What?
Hi.
The easy way to say
is to say
Hold the yogurt?
Fuck.
This guy's fucking crazy.
Who is this guy? This guy's fucked up.
Heart of Darkness is about a young boy named Andy.
Skipping. I'm skipping it.
I don't...
We don't watch those videos.
If we got to add 100, oh shit, I'll get it.
An embarrassing video.
Cheater?
Well, I don't think I'm going to...
All right, here we go. Listen to me.
I don't think I'm going to laugh at my own streams, if I'm honest.
Because, like, I was there.
No rules, Andy.
400 subs? What?
Oh, you just made that up, Art.
Well, it's because they're not funny.
No, you can have that opinion.
If you don't think I'm funny, then that's fine.
I'm not going to tell you you're wrong.
Be sad for a minute.
And then curse you out when I'm in the shower.
I like a height. I like a climb.
But, like, she stepped on a church.
I mean, a knee building, really.
Because, legally, they're not supposed to be able to ask you about that
on, like, your homeowners' association application.
But they'll ask. They'll look it up.
If she doesn't exist in the same physical timeline as I am...
What's the poster in the back?
I'm not doing that again.
Is it Nightmare Before Christmas?
Hi, this is Tommy Weasel, creator of The Room.
Let me introduce you to the new Joker.
Hi.
Can we laugh, please?
Dude, the only thing that's making me laugh is the fact that we dress...
He's dressed in baby clothes, like, human baby clothes.
It's just so... What are we doing?
Don't talk about this.
This edible ain't shit.
Can you tell me where I'm on this?
I'll add it. I'll add it. I almost laughed at the GTA one,
not because it was a car, but because of something very specific.
Hit F2 to save clip in the corner.
You know that motherfucker was like...
That's what they hit F2.
I have to go back?
I said I wouldn't laugh at myself.
But that was just so fucking weird.
It was so outrageously strong.
All right. I'll get through it. I'll get through it.
I'll get through it. I'll get through it.
This edible ain't shit.
I just look like a different person. Okay.
Can you tell me where Armand Kristoff is hiding?
He's not going to do shit.
I'm in hiding from the Imperial watch.
It's funny, but it's not Thomas the Tank Engine.
I just punched him, sorry.
No, dude. What are you doing?
This is fucking gross!
I'm not even going to laugh.
What the... All right. I'm getting it off.
Get it off. Get it off. Get it off. I don't want to listen to it anymore.
I don't want to listen to it anymore.
I don't want to listen to it anymore. Get it off.
Hey, hold on a second. I don't want to be late.
Let me finish this.
Fuck.
Holy shit.
That was insane.
You're sick right there.
Oh, my God.
That was just cool.
I love refrigerator.
I've seen this one.
It's classic.
It's classic, but it's not going to get me.
This is actually real. It can't be.
It's real.
It's uncanny, Lisa.
It's classic.
It's a real sketch.
I'm trying to...
Okay, I'm good. I'm safe.
Oh, shit.
We're going to go viral with this one.
I've seen this video about two or three hundred times in the last six months.
It's not going to get me, but it's my favorite.
One of my favorite videos ever.
I'm not going to reenact this. I'll die.
That sock dog shooter.
Slimer, it is.
Do we already see this one?
Oh, he just walked by.
This is bromine.
No, wait, sorry.
That was soy sauce.
This is bromine.
Duke, do you want the ball?
What is happening in this photo?
I don't understand.
What?
He turned...
Is it upside down?
It's not a filter.
I think he's upside down in this photo.
Jesus.
God damn it.
That was stupid.
RTX on.
I think he's hanging upside down.
He's upside down.
Fucked up upside down photo.
Is that 18? Did I do it twice?
It's because he's flexing.
That's 18. We'll go back.
This one was crazy, too.
I'm doing it one more time.
Okay, I'm over.
I've seen this a million times.
Where's my lip balm?
Oh, Jesus.
What the hell is going on?
Why is it two?
It's two people.
Oh, it's the dog.
Okay, they swapped out the dog.
That's so weird.
He's not going to piss, is he?
I think I'm okay.
I think I'm all right.
I think I'm going to be okay.
Cute.
Holy shit.
That was...
Could any human do that?
If somebody practiced that enough,
would it even be possible to do even the first part of that?
It's a lucky thing I had my pieces.
Your pieces?
My guns.
Anyway, I started blasting.
I don't see so good, so I missed.
Then they ran away.
I ran after them.
I tried to shoot them in the back,
but I don't know if it's so good either.
I don't play video games,
so I don't know what that's a reference to.
I've seen it, but it's good.
Siri, take a note.
What's the note?
Inside the cave.
Sharing two sticks with a guy,
some homeless guy, threw up in his mouth.
Mickey Mouse comes in
and drains all my battery from my iPod.
I kiss him.
I knew it was coming.
Drains all my battery from my iPod.
I kiss him.
What the fuck?
I'm so weird. I swear to God I'm not high right now.
I thought I was blocking the face cam.
I actually thought I was blocking this face cam.
I was like, oh shit, I gotta get out of the way.
There's another face cam.
I swear to God I'm not on hard mode.
What the fuck?
That was really good.
Let me take some inventory here.
Let me see where we're at.
And I gotta pee.
Let's see.
1,900 bucks is in the pool?
Let me see. I don't wanna spoil anything.
We are getting close.
We're getting close.
I'm gonna go pee. I'll be right back.
We've got about 50 or 60 more videos
until we get to the baby sensory shit.
Which I have no idea how that's gonna go.
I have no idea.
And by the way,
well I'm not gonna say this yet because I'm not done.
I could watch another compilation.
I'm into that. This is fun.
This actually is fun to do.
I'm having a great time.
I'll be right back. I'm just gonna go pee.
And we'll keep going. See you guys in a minute.
Hello. I've returned.
I found my lip balm. Thank God.
Alright. Let's keep going.
We've got about 60 videos left in this playlist
and then we're gonna move to the baby sensory.
It is Burt's Bees.
Why'd I say hello like that?
I don't know.
This is a lot of fun though.
I've been doing this and didn't do it for a long time.
Because I was like, I don't even know how to do that
or where to start or how would I even
do I even really care. It's fun.
I'm not gonna do this every single stream.
Did I find my vape?
Normie?
I'm not a normie.
Alright, let's go.
There we go.
Let us continue.
This needs to be like over here or something.
Let me brighten this up.
It looks like I'm sitting in front of a campfire.
Oh, that looks worse.
Look at how much more handsome I look when it's up here.
Lighting is just
matters so much. Look at this.
This is with a light directly in my face.
Look at that.
Look at the difference. It's just so much better.
Down here, that's why.
It's because I have a big brow bone. Can I make it stay up here?
It actually might stay up here.
Dude, look at that.
I have like a real light in my face now.
Okay. I just can't move that much.
Actually, that's dangerous for it to be up there.
Alright, let's go.
Back to it. Did I scam?
Is it 2000?
He zonked.
Not yet!
Is it 19? Okay. I'm making sure I didn't scam.
Here we go. I am ready.
Can you see it?
Volume back up.
Let's go.
No!
Okay, so my GoPro setup isn't perfect yet.
And I'm glad you guys are getting a kick out of it.
But, I really want it to be better.
This video
exemplifies why
I need to work on this so much.
It's really hard to keep that
long, stiff street pole
all the way out there that you need
for the 360 cam to work right.
He's got a lawnmower
and he's like a little kid right there.
Just scary.
I love this game.
At the end I almost got me.
That was really cool. I wouldn't say that was funny. That was cool.
What?
Why? Do you see anything else?
Kids nowadays.
My baby must be sending letters.
I'll be back in a hurry, great grandma.
Always in a hurry.
Isn't that what Santa does?
It was from my heart.
She doesn't get it.
What's going on?
How? I feel so bad.
We can always work things.
Great grandma, you always know
just what to say.
That was cute. I like how cute that one is.
How to save people in the elevator in Black Mesa.
What?
Can you actually get them out?
Oh shit.
Goodbye.
This is your content, Jerma.
Bright.
This is why I can't play Oblivion.
Ever.
985.
Just auto fill on your iPhone.
What's happening? That was weird.
No.
What?
Is jellyfish a herb?
That was close.
Is it 3am?
Oh don't.
So is it any wonder people are afraid
of technology?
Have you ever had a dream
that
you had
you could
you want
you could do so
you could
you want him to do
you so much you could do anything?
That's a great video.
It's just a good video.
Pay no attention, it's fine.
You want me to go up there?
Trick or treating at my house?
I think I've seen this.
Hey look.
Thanks Jerma.
So weird.
I'm so pale.
I look like a fucking
look at how weird I look.
I've never seen this.
I just did not expect that at all.
You know why
this is so surprising to me?
I've never seen Rocky 2.
I just know that Rocky's a guy
and he wears like pajamas and works out
and then fights people.
I've only seen like an hour of Rocky total.
Hey Brad.
I bet you can't laugh without
smiling.
What are you talking about?
Oh, seriously.
It's not even that hard. Watch.
This is freaking me out.
That was freaking me out. Loud.
23 in the chamber.
They ain't found me yet, but when they do
they're gonna be surprised.
It's the zoomed in
close up. He hit that
hard. You can see his whole
body like jiggles.
Hold on. I've never seen some of these videos before.
Jeez.
Just look at this.
Let us have a moment of silence for this man's
fallen brothers as you see.
It's, okay.
It's the fact that it's just, it's not necessarily the commentary.
It's just the, oh my god.
How? That would be so awful.
Okay.
What do we add? Is it 22 or 23?
Alright.
I actually gotta relax.
Because this still is in place in Baby Sensory
and I don't think I'm gonna be able to handle, I can't handle Baby Sensory.
I don't think I'll be able to handle it.
Let's go.
All
the
All the
Shouldn't
have
Packed
you kill the child.
Amazing mission complete.
That right there is why you are the best.
Everyone knows her
father is a lunatic. He was in here
tonight. Raven.
Mm-hmm.
Um, is it what a mint julep? Okay. What the fuck just holy shit. Okay, that was scary
Wait, wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, I got
Six I gave points for the tattoo reveal. I thought that was completely unique
I also gave points because she had delicious barbecue
I took points away because I was stung by a bee for the first time
And I think that is attributed to the 50 000 bees that are kept on the premises
Oh, look at them they're having so much fun
It's all right. You know, here's what's happening here. They both want the other one to chase them
So when they're realizing that they're getting stuck in like a math loop of like their ai won't do it
They keep resetting
Like why have you not chased me yet? I'm supposed to you sit. Well, why are you not chasing me? That was fun. That was cute
Hey, guess what i'm having today. Fuck man
Fucking steak, baby. Yeah
the ribeye mashed potatoes
beans
Yeah, baby. Fuck
Fucking steak. Yeah
Monday brunch, baby. Fuck
This is what to make on your monday. Fuck
Any day it's what what makes it your day make it a happy one. Fuck man. Fuck fucking steak, baby. Yeah
fucking monday
Yeah, fucking monday, baby. Fucking monday
Steak, baby fucking monday fuck
All right
Make monday a good day, baby. Yeah
What the fuck
Can you imagine that happening to you?
That was really close
What was what what was this one titled protocols not banished in origin it's
Sturdier than I expected. I don't play halo. I don't get it cortana
No problem
I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right
I knew it was coming. I love this video
Look at how pissed this cat gets. This cat is so angry that the dog farted god
The end of that that ad went on a very long time
What how why do you laugh at this laughed at nothing?
Because I because I know i'm gonna laugh at this video and the thanos one was holy shit
It was a miracle. I was able to hold through that one and then oh my god
Here comes like one of my favorite funny cat hits the dog for farting videos
Nope. Okay. I got it 24. It's fake. I just it's still funny
No, no more thanos shit
That's so annoying. What a bunch of fucking assholes. What a bunch of dicks
This is the last video in this playlist
Just okay, it wouldn't be funny to me if it was anywhere else, but he's at like the airport
He has to show his id and the fact that they're like very far away
That's the only reason why it was funny if they were anywhere else. We are at
$2,500 this playlist is over. That does not mean that this is over
Coming up next is hard mode
And baby sensory videos and after that
We might actually do a few more just compilations. Maybe some of the mods can um, I don't want to say this because I don't want a fucking
Five trillion people to hit up the mods, but maybe another compilation or so get a couple maybe one or two more
What's the pool for?
So at the end of this stream i'm going to divvy this up and we're going to give it to charity
So I have a charity in mind that I might just give the whole thing to find out. Well, not not a charity necessarily
But an organization, so this is fun 2,500 so far. All right, let me let's watch this last one and see if it's going to work
Work
Okay, we're good
Tell what the pool is for in your title
Uh, okay. Yeah, i'll update the title because now we're nice lighting that wasn't in the playlist. This was just autoplay
What are you serious? Okay. All right. Give me one second. Let me uh,
Let me just instead of putting in the title. It's probably easier to do this
I'll make it a little smaller too. So it's not
Okay, uh getting a lot of community subs too. Uh, thank you. Kiki lime pie for the 10
Uh, thank you oi pmc for the 10 vessel for the five and then sarah ryan
Saran ocean for the 25 community subs. I don't I don't know if I can handle this. This is gonna be really weird. Um
I was gonna have a notepad open where I write my feelings down
But I think that you laugh you lose shit still is fine. So let me get that on
Let's get the first one on here. So this one is oh god
This is still you laugh you lose by the way. I just found these on youtube. I don't know how they are
I don't know anything really about them. I have no idea
Absolutely, no clue here comes a baby early learning sensory video three two one
Hello, baby
Circle
Okay, it's like breathing i'm just thinking about the fact that i'm doing this right now i'm actually watching these and it's it's making
This is scary. It's kind of scary for adults
So what this supposed to be high contrast is a clockwork orange. I'm about to veto this
all gone
I think I have to veto this whole thing
Fucking cloud music in the background is it is it circle? What is it? It's a circle. It's a circle
Okay, um
I'm gonna i'm gonna just go ahead and uh say this
um
Feed your babies a well-balanced diet, please
and
Like you have like objects in your house like keys and stuff. You can play like peekaboo
I don't know if I want I don't know if i'd want a baby to sit down
This is 22 minutes. I don't think I want a baby sit down and like get we'll see this
I want to like draw this in a notebook and be like that's a look that's a circle
I feel like if you have this on autoplay do it on times two speed
All right, maybe there's a bunch of science about it that like this is like developed like it's okay
You know like um when adults play a brain age for the ds
Maybe that maybe this is literally just brain age for an infant. I have no idea. Okay
Shit is for babies
It's it is i'm getting scared
I have to put it like a warning here because it's gonna be um, this is times two
But what in the meantime, uh, if we if there's any more you laugh you lose compilations
I'd love to watch them. Maybe just we can get them vetted quickly or something
But um, I ain't watching i'm done after this. This is fucking what a shit idea
This is one of the worst ideas i've ever had
Well ever one of the worst ideas i've ever had
Uh, so i'm gonna put a warning here first
Okay, there we go. I'm not doing all 22 minutes. We're going to another you laugh you lose
Okay, here we go
crazy
I forgot it was in times two speed
I forgot it was in times two speed man. I thought like what the fuck is what is this alien video?
We're watching I was like, why is it like this? I forgot it was times two
But yeah, if a mod has another good compilation
Uh, is it just even when you find?
Okay, here we go. I'm doing this up to up to five to ten minutes and that's it. I gotta turn that off
It's too much. This is horrifying. Okay, i'm done
No, i'm not gonna keep it up and keep it times two. Okay, there are 30 000 people here
What a weird like it would I feel like if I clicked on this stream
They're watching a times two speed baby sensory video. Why are they doing this? What's wrong with them?
This is cultish at this point if I was just sitting here like two times baby sensory videos
I this is getting I don't know. It's freaking me out. I don't think I can do
All right, i'll do times two for for 10 more seconds ready
Okay
It is wario where holy shit that person get that what's happening
I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. This is over. I'm done. We're doing a laugh you lose
Get the fuck out of here. Get this fucking thing off the screen right now
No way. Yeah, but like like 3 000 people have left the stream. This is off
Like immediately let's put on a you laugh you lose
I've got a lot of ideas on this stream
Some of them need to go through the first phase of like the carbon filter for your sink. Holy shit
Okay, best one guy moment. All right. Let me give me one second
Let me just look at to see if we have any more compilations to do
Do we do we have any more wario where?
I don't think we even have any more
All right. Here we go. I got one. I got one. Got one. Got one. Got one. Got one. Got one
That last bit right there. I don't know. I can't do that anymore. All right
This one's called
This is unusual memes compilation version 169. Okay, let's give it a go. All right. All right. Oh, you can't see it
Now you can and here we go. Three two one
I really wish I had a shopping cart right now. There's none around
Good god that was
Fake I know it doesn't matter. I know like that part of your head and that part of the garage
All right. Here we go. I really wish I had a shopping cart right now. There's none around
There we go. Is that meat?
This is not yours though. What's that?
Oh, I thought that
Taylor what time is it?
Oh, i'm, all right. Oh
His ass he just scraped. Oh, I thought it was I thought he scraped his ass
It's not in two-time speed
Look feel it feel it
That is a basketball I know a basketball
What does it say how to operate
I don't know. What is he trying to do? Oh, okay
People's breaking shit in their houses
This is smashing stuff in your house compilation. These are zoomer sensory videos
I can laugh at that because that was funny
Hold on I i'll give it to you i'll give it to you
Go back did I miss one? Sure, please, uh, get a better playlist. This is 2013
Well, we're off the original playlist. I've been here for two and a half hours doing this. Holy shit
Damn. All right. I'm not going back to baby sensory
No, all right. I'm gonna finish this one out and we'll get another one. Okay. Here we go
Cheeseburger hand pies are a fun twist on a classic meal in a large
Fun hold on
Let's get oh man that hurts
Holy shit
Oh that sounds like his teeth
I don't get it
Yeah, these are too quick for me to react to my brain like moves on the baby video was better
When's auto's birthday auto's birthday is
Uh, we don't know probably somewhere around march
Because auto's a rescue. So I don't know exactly when
But they think march somewhere between march and may
What happened to the what happened to the tv resolution burning guy? It was a joke. We got had
Uh, he sent another video that was that was him doing a rick roll. So
That was the ultimate one guy for sure. We're on animal videos. All right, let's let's let's let's get this one out
And then i'm gonna take one more break and we'll see if we get another one coming up. What's up house?
All right, it's so hot
I could feel that all the way over here
What on america's money's home videos do we just watch an old episode of america's money's home videos
That actually sounds awesome
I'm just realizing what this poor guy just did that you what what just happened the whole tree fell apart
Hold on I need to see what you're talking about somebody said they thought that this was a
Teller was like this guy was a dog
It is a dog
What are you talking about? I thought that guy was a dog
Yeah, because it was a dog
Oh
I was waiting for like the chandelier to fall
Like I thought it was gonna be like the chandelier was gonna go like in the background or something
I was like, what the hell is this video?
Watch how it's made. Are we going just full react andy today? Is that what it is? All right. Let me go pee
We'll get we'll let me get like two or three more ready to go. I'll be right back
Do how it's made on times 10 speed
Dude, my favorite part is the zoomer sensory videos
Ah, that's so fun. I'll be right back. You just peed
I've been drinking water. Somebody said do a baby sensory stream where you treat us like babies. I don't think so
All right. Here's what we're gonna do. I only really planned on this stream being about three hours
So we will watch maybe one or two little things here and then I was gonna be live tomorrow
with monster rancher
End of the stream voice not yet
I mean, there's only somebody like hours in a row of of just meme content that your brain can accept that like
Facebook video
Where I got locked and had and that added a thousand dollars to the pool
Yeah, I I mean after three hours of this you kind of funny it out
But I want to finish monster rancher
And what else what else?
I don't think we'll be in monster ranch for that much longer. I don't think so
You but I can't the baby sensory thing was a fun idea and then in practice
Was just way too much that's way too much for me and way too much for you
Especially at times two speed. Oh, no way
It was horrible
Yeah, I don't think I can put on america's funnystone videos like the one that's the current season. It was perfect
I mean, I think it was funny once I realized I had to leave
So let me let me go over this real quick too though
We want more we want more watch the dancing fruits one
All right, i'll put on the dancing fruit one and then after that i'm probably just gonna go
And we'll be live tomorrow with video games
It's too much
You know those like three plus hour long
the meme compilations
after hour number two of that
I kind of I kind of want to go like eat a sandwich
All right. What was it going over here? Okay, let's put on the baby sensory dancing fruit one
Uh, let me break down where this money's gonna go by the way. There is a dancing fruit one. You're right
Please peep the horror
Um, I think I did that for like five straight minutes on the sensory stream. I don't think you need me to do that again
All right, let's break this down
Coming back. I don't think that's even accurate anymore the flashing lights thing
Hey, who knows but i'm this maybe this stuff isn't like very engaging to a child's brain. I don't know just in case
Okay, uh, okay fruit fruit salad dance party. Hey, you just peeped the horror for 20 minutes. Yeah
I can say I kind of like this video
This this ain't bad this one's not bad
How do you guys feel right now?
Like this very second if I asked you and I had a piece of paper and I wrote it down
How do you feel good chill groovy?
Stimulated. Yep mind controlled
Hungry
How long does this go for?
Oh my it's just it's this for 20 minutes
Does the song change?
Don't spoil the video
Somebody just came in
and said
Dude, what do we do here? Is this guy just opening up and watching baby videos?
This is exactly what I told you was going to happen
Oh shit
No
What the fuck? Oh, well, is it all right?
Is it turning on?
Okay. No, no, it's all right. It's all right
so anyways
Uh, that's exactly what I told you. I told you exactly that's what was gonna happen and it exactly did
Okay, so uh, no, this is not what we do here. This is one of many things that happen on this channel
You were vibing. All right, let's vibe for another 30 seconds. What's wrong with your lighting? I've been here for two hours
This is like a lamp. I have that's just right here. It's like a little
digital lamp thing
All right, if the next fruit is a banana
I will add a hundred dollars
Somebody said oh wow, man. It's a bunch of little dancing fruits just for me. Oh, no. Yeah, it didn't change you, right?
Uh banana, right?
I'm not even kidding. This is your worst stream of the year two bad nominations are closed. Oh, yeah
Uh strawberry. Oh, well, this is your worst stream for next year
Oh, I see what you're doing. I didn't pre-watch. What are you talking about?
Holy shit. Wait, this just keep
Oh, there's banana. Okay. What'd you say? This is one
Remember, this is this is the first time i've seen you live. Is this what it's always like?
No, that's you you said what the last person said
Spoilers. All right. Let me take baby sensory out of the title
Because I when I all right, there's no more there's no more baby sensory. I'll give you 60 more seconds
Somebody said put on animal sensory like dogs cats birds. I don't I think the same shit's gonna happen
Just stand still and stare at the video. No, I mean we I about 7 000 people have already left
When baby sensory turned on so I don't want to get the rest of you gone
Okay, let me do this
the weakest 7 000
Do master chef
No, you've seen it a million times you've seen that a million times
So let me let me get this out of the way first if you came for the you laugh you lose
I've never done that before it was really fun
Uh, i'm gonna update this because there was at least a few more
so
That takes us to
3,500 dollars
This is not a beginner germa stream. Well, this is a react andy for three hours stream. I'm gonna i'll be left tomorrow though
This is not just a one stream here this week. I'll be left tomorrow
All right, so 3,500 dollars is going to go
Uh to the I think I want to send it to the that science center nevada
So I will be able to have uh, if you remember from the bugleberry hot tub stream
There was about I think 7 500 bucks came in so to science center nevada
That actually makes it perfect
Because that would be well, i'll just round it out. That'd be five. I was gonna do 5 000 to science center
So then plus 3,500
So here's what i'll here's what i'm gonna do i'm gonna send
$10,000 to the nevada science center to kind of make sure that was combined with the other one, too
So that is going to go to the their center
I'm really really can't wait to send that so it'll be 11k. Well, I was gonna round out from the bugleberry stuff
Somebody said i'm an oaf. I know it's your hardship, but
I want to can you fund my interest in yo-yos? Why did I read that comment?
Well, I had a good time I I knew this wasn't going to last very long and especially when baby sensory is like
That takes a turn off the road and I'm no not gonna have him. He's a philanthropist. Well, I here's the thing I promised
Back in like july or august or something
That um that money was actually going to get used and sent to these places
So want to get that in there? What if you did a yo-yo trick stop with the yo what's with the yo-yos?
All right, that's it. I'll see you guys tomorrow. I could pivot to monster rancher, but
I'd rather just do a whole day of it tomorrow because I think we're pretty much near the end
Let me let me let me type this so people know the final. So it'd be 35
No, no, you say yeah, you're right. So it'd be it'd be 11.5. It's dirt. Yeah, because I was gonna do five
And then oh, no, I'll split it. I'll send some to another place, too
I was gonna do one of the um
Humane societies out here. All right. There you go
Uh 10 000 bucks to the science center in nevada nevada science center
If you don't know who that is and you're wondering why uh, you might be if you're a new viewer or not
They helped out to do the geology archaeology stream and they were really really really nice people
So hopefully they can use it for something cool. Oh, I need an end and that'll wrap up today
I'll see you guys tomorrow
I'll do a full probably six plus hours of monster rancher tomorrow
And then what happened when we were adding no more monster rancher, what am I gonna do?
That's been my game for like two or three weeks. I have to find something else to do. I'm gonna go watch baby sensory
What you guys bet you guys bet earlier over or under 5 000. Oh man. Okay
Now have a great night. I'll see you guys tomorrow. There were a lot of gifted subs, too
I appreciate it. Thank you guys a lot. That was more fun than I will I
That was more fun than I thought
I think the next time I would want to do it
I would want to if if I was going to spend more than two three hours for doing that
Most of these compilations people kind of do it for like an hour, right?
All right. Yeah, hope you had a good time. I did have a wonderful rest of the night. Thanks everybody. See you tomorrow
Monster rancher two have a great night. Sorry. I screamed at you earlier, too. Just trying to scare you
I'll see you tomorrow put sensory on the credits
No
It wasn't actually scary. Yeah, I know I was messing around. I was just having fun. All right, go say hello to nianers
What is what is what you doing? Let's take a look. Okay, let me get it going first of all
Okay. All right. What you doing?
Just chatting
Avoid baby sensory videos. I don't know what you're doing. Uh nianers 3d
Wait new 3d winter model. Yeah
Okay, everybody go take a look. I've apparently a new 3d winter model
Uh, say hello to nianers. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Thanks for watching. Good night. Goodbye
See you soon