Hey, how's it going? Turn up the volume. I have this at a reasonable decibel level, I believe.
How you guys doing? Just making a tweet. Sorry, I didn't start where I wanted to about 30-40
minutes ago. One of my webcams was blue-screening the computer. I have no idea why. I have two
webcams. Remember when I had the Labo stream from this past weekend? I mean, they were
all the things I read about saying that when you open up OBS and you have two webcams
enabled, it blue-screens, but I wasn't having that problem before. I don't know if there was
like a stealth update to the Logitech software. I have no idea, but apparently one of these was
just causing the driver to crash and blue-screening the whole computer. But hey,
I think I fixed it. We're good. Hasn't happened yet, so that's good. So let's see.
Seeing the sites in Hitman 2. Yeah, because that means I haven't seen it before.
It could be anything, you know, it could be whatever. Seeing the sites in Hitman 2.
That sounds pretty good to me. All right, so yeah, we got to the halfway point last night,
and I would assume, judging by we did three areas last night, I'm going to assume that we've
got three more here that will take us to the end. Now, that does not mean this is the end of
Hitman streams. This is talking about end of the campaign, technically, because there's a whole
lot of shit to do. And by the end of this stream, we will gauge whether or not I do it again.
And I will go back, we'll play some other contracts, we'll do some other campaign missions.
But for the purpose of the story, we're going to be done, I think, today.
So put some clothes on. I have clothes. Listen. No, I got to turn this off so you can hear
it. Ready? See? And then I got clothes on. Whoa, that was wicked loud! Why was it so loud?
And the canon vocal cords, just what was that? It was like, so here we are. Where
were we last time? I don't know why that was so loud. So we got Hitman 2. I don't know what
this is. So mission night call, we did it. Blank check. Cinematic. Let's go through our
Microsoft Windows tiles. Chasing a ghost and a ghost. And here we go. Mission Another Life.
This is where we left off. It's like, this is like spoilers. Why is it showing this to me?
Another life. But we're not gonna do it yet. And I know that the I know the audio is not on.
I'm well aware of it. Stop looking. But let's let people trickle in while I talk about
one other important thing. The green screen stream is slated and scheduled for tomorrow.
The thing is, though, I don't have a time yet. Because it's I'm kind of I'm working with a
studio. So I need to get like a time from them. I think it might just be kind of whenever
whenever I can start. So I don't necessarily have a direct exact time. But I will make
sure to tweet either later tonight or tomorrow afternoon the time that it's going to happen.
An estimate I would probably say around the normal start time what it's been for the last
couple of weeks. That's at least when I would like to do it. So it might be a little earlier
than that, considering I might I want to get in there early and get everything set up. So
the rough estimate is probably going to be between like four, like three and six
eastern time p.m. Maybe pull back a little bit earlier than that between like two and five maybe
eastern. I don't I just don't know. I don't have that time from the studio yet. So
I know that I am there for what's a call day. You can either do half days or full days in a
studio. And I believe I'm on a half day. So I think that means probably from like nine in
the morning to ten in the morning to like four in the afternoon Pacific. So I don't know.
I don't know. But let's go. I just want to give an update on that because
and if something if something crazy happens or if it changes I'll make sure to let you guys
know on Twitter. You know what? Just follow me on Twitter. Twitter.tv slash. I thought the
computer broke. The first constant is none other than Janus, the legendary Cold War spy
master, a KGB senior officer and head of the Sixth Column Special Branch at Lubyanka. Janus
is a certified genius and expert of counterintelligence. He retired from the KGB in 1988
when he fell out of favor with the Kremlin and affected to the U.S. Shortly after,
the Soviet Union collapsed. Now it is unclear when Janus stepped down as the constant. But
what's going on? Why is my computer like fucking up?
Right. So here's the catch. As an elite KGB agent, Janus was trained to withstand
interrogation and torture. No amount of pressure will force him to disclose information
he doesn't want to. Instead, we will need to search his home for clues. But if Providence
learns of our presence, the game is up. So we frame Janus, make Providence think
he was the real Shadow Client. Nice computer. Those is not Comcast. This is ComputerCast.
Claiming to have traced a number of calls from Janus's house to the Institute in Romania.
The case will seem clear. Mr. Gray was only a figurehead. Janus was pulling the strings
all along. And by eliminating him, we will have neutralized the militia once and for all.
However, for this subterfuge to work, you'll also need to deal with Janus's security detail.
Providence herald and former Secret Service agent by the name of Nolan Cassidy. Intel
describes him as diligent and inquisitive, and we cannot risk that he contradicts our story
Seems workable. I certainly hope so. Everything depends on this next move, 47. You made this
our fight. Now let's even the pain field. So they did a similar mission like this in
Hitman 2. What is going on with my frame rate? I am, I don't know. It's only like in that cut
scene. Is it Hitman 2 or is it Blood Money? Where you kind of have to go into the guy's
house. So I gotta get rid of these two. Let's take a look at our planning stage here. We
got Whittleton Creek. Oh, I got the silver baller this time. Master card. Mastercrafted.
Well, I mean, I just unlocked it, so I have to use it, right? Suburban suit. I mean, I, I guess
you're just wearing a suit. Should I need, why can I, I should be like a jogger. What is ice?
Oh, that's icy. Okay. Uh, I could do remotes, fragments, sub sedative, fills, coins.
No, give me the lockpick. I'll take the fish, but I'm taking the lockpick. I'm not doing
like the duck again. It didn't serve any purpose besides just throwing it into fucking random
objectives. All right, looks good. So got to get rid of Janice and get rid of Mr. Cassidy.
And now you got to find clues. I'm ready. Oh, so somebody, somebody, somebody who chatted,
but wait, Jeremy, what are you drinking tonight? What's that? Oh, I've both chatted
about random chatter. I'll tell you. So that it's a, um, I ran out of bananas
and I ran out of, of the things that I would put in here. Besides it's a, it's a, it's just
peanut butter and almond milk blended up hard. I'm just drinking peanut butter right now. It's
enough to like, it's a sustainable creek. Just like sustains me on the surface. A picture
perfect suburban dream, wide roads, golden maple trees and verdant lawns. Most residents
here are white collar professionals ranging from university staff to government employees.
So it runs fine now, but not all Janice's unpresuming home is protected by a host of
bodyguards and Intel shows that the fragile former constant rarely leaves the property.
Nolan Cassidy on the other hand, roams the neighborhood streets and he buys weed off the
local, the dutiful Providence paper route kids making threat assessments and settling in with
a security team. Now remember, this is about more than just revenge. Janice is the key to bring
down Providence. So get in there and find us a lead. Okay. Good luck. 47. So this just,
this is not just one house. This is just the whole neighborhood.
Okay. Let's see. You know, speaking of sustainability. Oh, this is not good. 47.
I've marked your map with several points of interest. We're running this mission with very
little upfront Intel. Alright, so I gotta be careful here. These locations could provide
clues to help you obtain the information we need. Good luck. Thanks. Alright, so let's see
what we got here. No entry. Don't tell me what to do. Oh, this is a yard sale. That's one
of those novelty signs you put in your college dorm room in front of the door. That's
cool. Uh, no, it's here. Wouldn't these things blow over? Yeah, they are blowing the leaves.
There he is. That is Nolan Cassidy, former Secret Service agent and current Providence
herald. Cassidy is assigned to protect Janice. Yeah. Well, he's not doing a very good job.
He's going to the college guy yard sale. Blend in as a garbage man. Where are they going?
Deal recording things from up there and then store in the tape somewhere else. I totally agree,
sir. Though separating the tapes from the playback device is necessary in case someone
gains access to the building. As you mentioned yourself, we can't let anyone know this is like
a bait. They're talking. I know what I said. Of course, I'm sorry. I'm just annoyed with
this setup. Understood, sir. Alright, interesting. So they're recording and the
tapes, the recording devices and the tapes are at different locations. Let me just keep looking
around. It's like a birthday party back here. Burlington Morgans. Are you allowed to go in
people's houses? Where's the mission? Am I allowed to be in here? I just opened up
somebody's house. I haven't seen you before. Who are you? Nobody. Is he like your boyfriend
or something? Oh, that's a party.
That's a party. Is this like your boyfriend or something?
He's not going to drink that, is he? Wait, you're not going to drink that, are you?
Oh, shit.
What? Back in the day, Janus was known for his obsessive need to archive
and keep memorabilia. If he has any microfilm in his house, it might contain something
interesting. Oh shit. Oh no, I can't. I can't do it. I can't. I'm not going to do it.
I can't. I can't do that. Oh, god damn it. All right.
All right, I'm ready. I was going to eat dinner. I'm sorry. I didn't want to do that.
We're running this mission with very little up front intel.
I just ran a simulation. I have to see every possibility. You know what I mean?
What's that movie where the guy could see every possibility? Dr. Strange. I need to see every
possibility to find out which one is the right one. You know what I mean? My head's going
all over the place. Look at my face. I'm making different facial expressions and shit.
I needed to see what was possible.
...to help you obtain the information we need. Good luck.
Let's go over there. Yeah, that was not the correct timeline. But I saw the timeline. In
fact, we're going to go to the party because I feel like that's interesting to look at.
I did the Dr. Strange instead. No, see, right now I'm currently sitting on the rock.
I'm sitting there as Dr. Strange. This is how long it took him, guys.
Like he had to see it all. He had to see every possibility and he just lived it.
That's what I'm doing right now until I find the right one.
That's not a spoiler. Dr. Strange like sits on a rock is not a spoiler.
Where does he sit?
Microfilm viewer.
That's an interesting...
Is this her party?
Well, it's sort of a hobby that never really took off. Besides,
I don't have any microfilm to play on the viewer.
Oh, I will. Very soon.
Janus next door collects all kinds of ancient memorabilia.
He might tape or where it is that sort of thing uses.
I'm sure he'd be delighted to lend you some.
The rock is in the New Avengers movie. Sure.
Janus was known for his obsessive need to archive and keep memorabilia.
If he has any microfilm in his house, it might contain something interesting.
Okay, so locate the microfilm is the next part.
Let's see. If Janus has any microfilm in his house,
it's bound to contain something interesting.
I'm assuming that's probably one of these.
An apple a day, breadcrumb trail, charbroiled, a house for sale,
no-spoking, pest control, and whack-a-mole.
It's not yet. Not yet.
Let's save it right here in case I drown somebody.
Sabotage. No, I need a screwdriver.
Just pretend to be the waiter.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, would you like some cracked pepper?
Let me do that for you.
Smells like a gerbil crawled up your ass and died.
Kill that guy. That was just... come on, man.
No offense.
Hold on, wait a second. Can I push him into the grill?
I can't. I can't push him into the grill.
That's so unfortunate.
Oh, it's the propane tank not even on.
I need a propane tank.
Now let's keep looking around back here.
This is like a little party.
Fire extinguisher.
All right, let me install that for you.
Oh, this thing uses gas.
I can't pick this log.
I'm just gonna go around.
Somebody's right there.
All right, does this open?
Far less eyeballs over here.
I think I could get it.
Let's try it.
Okay, this is the Griswold property.
What?
No reason for him to kick the habit when he's already so close to kicking the...
So, Janeless Smudge, despite being dependent on an oxygen tank
and his bodyguard's insistence on hiding his cigarettes.
I wonder what might happen if he combined the two.
Obtain a pack of cigarettes.
Have you seen that oxygen tank near his bedroom window?
Near his bedroom window.
Okay.
So, uh...
I'm currently trespassing though, so I gotta get out of here.
Make him smoke waaaaah.
Kitty pull.
Can they see me?
Oh, they can.
All right, I'm gone.
I'm leaving.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm out, I'm out, I'm out.
This is a restricted area.
And you guys have guns?
I'm being shot at.
I just wanted to get my son's ball.
He threw it over the fence accidentally.
They're shooting at you with nail guns.
All right, I need to go.
Let's, let's, let's track the cigarette one.
Might as well.
We'll give it a try.
So, pack of cigarettes.
I gotta get over here.
I should be able to pop this lock without anyone shooting me.
I think, right?
They didn't see it last time, so why would they see it this time?
Okay, pack of story.
Pack of cigarettes.
There they are.
All right.
Infiltrate the Janus property now.
Which is right there.
He's using the waypoint.
So, I mean, I, whatever.
I just, I, why should I not be doing that?
I mean, I, I just like found it.
I didn't activate it at first.
I'm cheating.
Cheater.
Is this considered cheating?
I gotta get in through there.
But this place is heavily protected.
You get, you get a game refine.
Oh, how do I get through there?
Go get that man some gas.
What?
Place food.
What food?
What?
No, I, I just made it smaller.
I just made sushi in front of these people.
Gas, gas, gas.
Well, I need.
I just lost my fish.
I just turned it into sushi.
Why not just go inside?
It's open to everyone.
I know, I know the main story.
I know it.
Mission story revealed.
No, I don't.
I know.
It sounds like Nolan Cassidy has some interest in the party as well.
But for some reason, he's unwilling to go inside.
Maybe you can help fix whatever's wrong in there, 47.
Well, maybe he's a vegan.
I don't trust a man who can't eat a rare steak.
Yeah.
Call it.
I want E.
Coli.
What the fuck did you say?
Don't let it slide.
Let it slide.
All right.
The propane tank was just like over here.
I already opened this.
Where's the propane tank?
Probably by the grill, right?
Cheater.
Hey, it's in the game.
I'm going to utilize the waypoints if they show themselves.
Otherwise, look, I'm going to level with you guys here.
Like level with me.
You've seen the way that I've played the game so far.
If there was not a blip on the map somewhere,
eventually, I'm eventually telling me where I need to be,
I would just drown people in toilets.
You know what I mean?
I would just throw gas canisters over here.
I would just fucking punch people.
That would happen, and it just would.
I would get lost somewhere,
and I would just start karate chopping people.
And I do that anyways.
Understandable.
Have a nice day.
Propane tank.
All right.
So let's save us here.
Let me help you with that.
Another boyfriend?
What?
Is he your boyfriend?
What is that?
The go-to.
Who else is going to explode?
I love that so much.
Who is this guy?
Is he your boyfriend?
The canned dialogue.
I turned off the stove.
Shoot him.
If you could take a couple of steps back,
make me a little more comfortable.
Investigate distraction?
Why would that be a distraction from that far away?
Somebody turned on the gas over here.
I know I'm going to make a joke that's been made a thousand fucking times before,
but honest to God, that's like the
don't touch the thermostat family guy joke.
And I'm not going to make it,
but I'm just saying like he heard the thermostat from like that far away.
I didn't make it.
I didn't make the joke.
I didn't say anything.
Wait, he's leaving.
Go get rat poison.
Well, that would make sense now, wouldn't it?
Pick up meaty bone.
Can I eat?
I can't eat the meaty bone.
Oh shit.
I got to hide this guy.
Where can I put him?
That wouldn't be a good idea.
Can I stuff him in the cupboard?
There's got to be a closet right here.
Put him on the stove.
All right.
So I got to get rat poison now.
Is this cooked or is this raw?
I just turned it off.
What are they searching for?
Does she not know how to turn it on?
She doesn't know how to work the TV.
How does it keep turning off?
Idiot.
Didn't I have poison?
I poisoned this cup.
Thank you.
Rat poison.
It's probably some like let's suspiciously go out the window.
I put the bone over here.
Poison TV power button.
Why am I trying to jump out the windows?
I'm now the server.
Poison the whole barbecue.
I'm not going to do that.
Is that what I'm going to do?
That's not what I'm about to do, right?
Start serving people.
Serve food.
Now we don't want to add this.
Some seasoning.
That was just a little bit of garlic salt.
Celery salt.
There.
Go ahead sir.
Care for a taste.
Special seasoning.
Yes.
Glad to be of service.
How does it taste?
Maybe why don't you come over here and add some seasoning.
Hold on.
Are they going to fill up the bathrooms?
They're all going to go into the bathrooms?
Oh no way.
Where is he going?
Oh thanks.
You're welcome.
He's going in that bathroom.
Are they all going to try to go into the same bathroom?
I kind of need to find out, right?
They're all going to go to the same bathroom.
Here's this guy.
Where's the other guy?
Didn't this guy just eat it?
How is he fine?
I need to, you need to keep poisoning it.
Oh, I don't.
Only the one guy got poisoned.
You should try this.
Well, oh well.
Obtain rat poison.
Can I go get more?
Hold on a minute.
So you want me to, like I'm going to reload.
I'm going to poison it every time.
So I have one rat poison.
I need to find another rat poison.
Use laxatives.
I don't have, now I'm going to have to go on like a search for those.
Well, whatever.
I'll just wait for him to come in.
Alright folks, the food is ready.
Poison the one that you should.
Yeah, I know, but I told you.
There's something weird to do.
I want to try it.
Excuse me.
Care for a snack.
I didn't poison it, right?
Sure thing.
Hello.
I tempt you with a little snack.
Flip the table.
Why are they playing this music in this current time period?
This does feel like a 50s party, doesn't it?
You want to try something?
Alright, here he comes.
Let's hope he likes his food, 47.
Thanks so much.
Sure.
Well, here he comes.
What?
So, was I supposed to poison that guy?
Or this dude?
Oh, here we go.
This dude right here.
Can I call you Rich?
Need something?
Hey.
This is what I like to eat.
Care to try something special?
Thanks so much.
Yeah, make sure to pick the one with extra seasoning.
What's going on?
Why don't you give this a try?
No way.
Excuse me.
You should try this.
It really is to die for.
Who wants a taste?
You?
Go ahead.
No way.
You sure?
Excuse me.
Hey.
You okay?
Keep it in and you can do it.
Now shoot him.
No.
How long do I plan on serving food?
Uh, maybe another 20 minutes or so.
I'm gonna be in this bathroom, right?
Okay.
Look, I'm not only in my server, but I'm also a bathroom attendant.
What did he just drop?
He just dropped a bunch of-
Okay.
Should have drowned him.
He threw up all the newspapers.
Well, I have him now.
All right.
I'm ready.
Now I am the mailman.
So now I can deliver the mail.
Hi there.
Get out of the way.
Go get some fries.
You know, I did hear that the fries are really good.
Maybe I should try one.
What if I serve as the mailman?
No, I can't.
I can't serve food as the mailman.
That is Nolan Cassidy.
Former Secret Service agent in current Providence House.
Cassidy is assigned to protect James.
Well, now we're doing the mailman arc.
I'll just wait my turn.
He's here now.
It only took you like 10 minutes to get here.
I could have just poisoned him and drowned him.
I gotta get him out of his loop.
What?
What is that?
What is she doing that for?
I don't understand.
What's this for?
Why does she have a question mark?
I need poison.
Poison, quick.
If I was poisoned, I know where I'd be.
In somebody's house.
Somebody's garage.
He's still con-
He doesn't-
He's gone.
Is that even blood in her head?
That's a flower.
Yeah, he's leaving.
Okay.
Time to be the mailman.
What?
I am the mailman.
What do you mean the opportunity passed?
The guy-
I- I am the mailman.
Oh, Mr. Wilson!
Nolan Cassidy is down.
Good work for his-
Whoa, what?
That guy just was being dragged up by his feet.
All right.
So I'm gonna-
I have to wait.
I just have to wait.
I just have to serve people and wait for him to get here.
All right, folks.
The food is ready.
He's gonna take so long.
Oh, god damn it.
I gotta think of something-
I just relax.
I'll be fine.
Do you have me relax?
That was a Dennis the Menace joke in 2018.
That's true.
You really do have to serve for 20 minutes.
That person thought that I was making a-
A joke?
No?
I actually have to wait till he gets over here.
Whatever he's doing.
Yes, thanks.
No, thank you.
Mail guy.
See, the problem there was-
I was supposed to-
I was supposed to take out the mailman before he came to get food.
I did it in reverse.
All right.
Serve a guest to make room for Cassidy.
But Cassidy's not here.
Should I just wait till he gets here?
Wrap your lips around this.
Is he your boyfriend or something?
Let's hope he likes his food, 47.
Okay, mission story completed.
But I-
No, I didn't.
It's made just for you.
He's still not here.
I just have to sit here.
See, this is why-
Here comes the mailman again.
The mailman is the real target.
See, he comes over and talks.
He's like, hey, Rich.
Mail-
I'm not gonna poison the mailman again.
He's gonna make his way over here
after whatever he's doing over there.
And then I'm gonna-
I'm gonna take him out.
Why does the chef have snowboard glasses on?
That's a great question.
Excuse me.
Care for a snack?
He rubbed his belly to indicate he was hungry.
My pleasure.
Oh, wait, I forgot.
I can't have fried food.
You should try this.
Hello.
Can I tempt you with a little snack?
Here it comes.
All right, get out of the way then.
He's like smiffing.
What is this like?
Oh, gosh.
Get out of the way then.
Here it comes.
Wanna try something different?
All right, get the fuck out of here.
Oh my god.
Get out of the way.
Okay, it's poisoned.
Mister-
I don't do small talk.
Mister Mailman.
There you go.
It's an open spot.
He never had french fries before?
He's very confused by french fries.
What?
Hey, hey, just in case you want to know, man, you're sick.
You probably should go see somebody or something at some point or something.
Is this a doctor?
Wait a minute.
Is that his personal doctor?
He's not going in there with him, is he?
Why are you both going in here?
What?
What is-
There we go.
We got to see it.
It was an accident.
That was an accident.
I can't dress up as him?
Oh shit.
What do I put him?
Oh, in here.
Hold my hair, isn't it?
That's the challenge.
He accidentally drowned.
All right, so now what if-
So I'm going to come out here and he's not going to come out.
So what does this guy have to say about that?
You know what I mean?
You're obviously waiting for him to come out of the bathroom.
What?
Why would you hear this?
He's like, he came to investigate?
You know.
Why would-
I don't understand.
Why-
You were standing next to the door.
Why would you come all the way across here?
All right, so I got-
He's dead.
I'm going to try to make my way over to the residence.
I got the key now so I can just go in.
But first.
Okay.
No!
That's the same person that I drowned before.
God damn it.
That's the same person I drowned.
All right, we're good.
We're done.
What did that person deserve?
Absolutely nothing.
They didn't deserve that at all.
They just happened to be standing in this spot in front of me.
All right, so let's take a look.
Mr. Cassidy is dead.
The real question is.
I need to get-
I'm going to go to the front.
I'm going to go this way.
Actually, there's a clue over here.
Let's see what this is.
Public park.
Poison water bottle.
I don't have any poison.
Pick up the hammer.
Yep.
Charles Blake III for a better world.
Okay.
Oh, there's the mailman again.
The mailman was-
What do you even-
Oh, I get it.
Do you deliver mail?
When I was your age, I didn't like having my route interrupted either.
I'll let you focus.
Just give it some thought.
I'll put a good word in for you if you need it.
Okay.
Thanks, I guess.
Is this missed?
Excuse me, sir.
Are you a registered voter?
I'd love to tell you about a new candidate who might just change your life.
Yes, sir.
A total game changer.
Okay.
I'm listening.
Wonderful.
Well, I'm sure you're aware that voting season is upon us again.
Yeah.
And if you're anything like me, a recent immigrant to this fine country,
the candidates this time around just aren't very, um, savory.
But we have a man here today who's about to change all that.
I don't care much for politics.
That is exactly why Blake is out ringing doorbells today.
Mr. Cassidy.
He has no stakes in Washington.
No connections to the establishment, no allies hidden away in lawless groups
that pull the strings around the world.
He's just a common man who decided that he wouldn't take it anymore.
He's looking for him.
He's here to clean up.
He doesn't know where he is.
Give him exactly what you want, and to make sure the government
doesn't stick his nose into everything.
Fascinating.
How is he going to achieve all that?
By imposing restrictions and pushing crippling laws
that will bind legislators to their desks for decades.
His approach-
He's going to keep doing that forever.
I couldn't even pay attention to this.
Washington-based desk jockeys.
So much work they simply won't have time to enforce the existing laws.
Cassidy!
While they're busy looking-
Cassidy, can you hear me?
The law books use his executive powers to undo the existing laws.
It's a radical approach, short, but quite effective.
And this Blake character, he's out here now ringing doorbells?
Sure is.
Why'd you ask?
No reason.
Good on you.
Be sure to vote come election day.
I've got to become Mr. Blake.
Feel free to spread the word about Charles Blake III.
Have a flyer.
Charles Blake III appreciates your support.
Well, I definitely want to-
Okay, he's out here ringing doorbells.
That's what he looks like.
Okay.
Hey, how are you?
How you doing?
Is that him right there?
That's him right there.
There he is.
Cassidy!
You're going to give a flyer to yourself?
I checked the phone.
Three people since morning, Aidan.
Oh, no.
We talked about the importance of the election.
Good afternoon, sir.
Or have you completely-
We lost three followers.
Sir, I absolutely did not.
It's terrible, I see.
You hear me?
That's not fair.
I've given out like a hundred of them already.
I don't keep you around for your excuses.
Well, okay.
Have a flyer.
Read more about Charles Blake III in it.
So when does he have diarrhea?
He's going to go in that outhouse right there.
And I don't have-
The only intel I have on him is the flyer.
Where's the flyer?
I'm going to see the flyer.
Apple a day.
Whack-a-mole.
So this is not even on here.
This is a secret one.
All right.
So objectives.
Where's my-
That's not intel, the flyer.
Free burgers.
In the inventory?
Or you mean like this inventory?
Charles Blake III appreciates your support.
Wait, I don't want to lose him.
Where does he go?
He's going-
He goes door to door.
Okay.
He's going to sit here?
Don't throw a bone at him.
Don't do anything like that.
All right.
Let's go.
Political flyer.
This flyer outlines a political platform
of local politician wannabe Charles Blake III.
Reading through various parts,
it seems Blake is intent on using a higher office
as a way of transforming rules set forth
by the local homeowners association.
That's it.
I'm the only person here.
I've been here for so long too.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just-
I'm not sure who I want to vote for.
You seem like a nice guy.
What's your stance on more than five dogs in a house?
Would you be okay with that?
I know you're only allowed by the state to have three.
But I like-
I like having a lot of dogs.
Will you move somewhere?
Mr. Blake has many important initiatives to share.
Mr. Blake.
Did I miss everything about Mr. Blake?
I'm not going to just shoot him.
No, I need to-
I need to-
He needs to go somewhere.
Dammit.
Is he even linked to an opportunity?
No, I just wanted to see if I could like become that guy
and that would mean door to door
I could go knock on the door, right?
I got an achievement for that.
Okay.
I know there's a-
I know there's a real estate thing going on.
This guy's looking around still for the-
Sir!
Mr. Cassidy!
Are you okay?
Nolan Cassidy!
Hey!
How are you, Mr. Cassidy?
All right, I do-
I kind of need this gig, though.
What?
If you're unharmed, it'd be much appreciated.
He's in a random open house basement?
Mr. Cassidy!
I love hide and seek just as much as the next guy,
but come on.
Frame rate, stop!
Hey!
Where are you, Mr. Cassidy?
I kind of need this gig,
so if you could just show yourself unharmed,
it'd be much appreciated.
That's going to hurt me.
Hey!
Oh, shit!
That's a stone-cold knockout to the head!
Here's the best part about this.
He's going to wake up,
and guess what he's going to do.
Mr. Cassidy!
I don't-
I just woke up somewhere.
I don't know where I am right now,
I'm not sure, but-
Uh, where are you?
Mr. Cassidy!
A very big lump on my head.
Oh, I-
Actually, this is better disguised.
The guy's bodyguard?
Mr. Cassidy, I-
I woke up naked somewhere?
I mean, I'm not sure what this is, but-
I woke up next to a plumber?
I thought it was you?
Maybe?
It was a person?
Are you Cassidy?
Oh, shit!
Uh, is there any-
Whatever.
In the basement?
No.
You're fine.
Close it.
All right.
I can now go-
I'm just going to walk right into the Cassidy residence.
Mr. Cassidy, am I Cassidy?
Have I been Cassidy the whole time?
If you could tell me, that'd be nice, man.
All right.
Let's just-
What do I got?
Let's go meat bone this guy in the head as hard as we can.
Treehouse!
Please stand back.
I'll check it out.
Take care.
Anyone copy?
Looks like we got trouble on our hands.
Don't know what yet.
We need to secure the area.
I need you to get a car away as possible.
I need you to keep your head down.
You want to stay alive.
That lady saw me, I think.
I'm just trying to get him to come over to the-
Up in the treehouse.
What's that command?
Okay.
Yogi Bear is on the loose.
And he may have stole a picnic basket.
I'll be on lookout too.
Don't be kidding.
Again?
Oh yeah, I was gonna shoot up there too.
Come on up.
Come on up here.
Will you get up here?
That's some strong-
I'm out.
I'm out of bullets.
I don't even know where this guy is.
Oh, the thing that's geared by the tree.
Mr. Cassidy!
Is that you?
Should I be shooting at you?
I can't like vault over that.
That's unfortunate.
All right, let's go.
Ow.
I'm a bodyguard here, so I-
This should be fine.
How would I be trespassing here?
I'm like a secret agent.
Secret agents-
I just flash my driver's license to this guy.
Oh!
The bird guy.
Bird guy.
Wait, like-
Like Flavor Bird?
I don't even need that though, man.
Look at me.
What was that for?
Why do they have a statue of like Michael Myers?
With like an axe.
Imagine if it was.
Imagine if your town just had like a statue of Michael Myers.
Like a big bronze statue.
No, I need that.
So I'm allowed to go in the house.
I'm just one of the bodyguards, right?
That would make sense.
Yeah, see?
You need a-
What about a frisk?
I'm the one that frisks you.
You understand?
Who the fuck are you?
You can't be here.
Who the fuck is this guy with the name tag?
Yeah, and stay out.
Are you serious?
To get rid of an aggressively invasive mole in this poor old man's backyard.
Calm down, demolition man.
Unless it's a flesh-eating mutant mole, you don't need explosives.
We're gonna keep them safe in our trunk until you produce that license, okay?
Come on, man.
One of Janus's gardeners has decided to clear a series of mole tunnels using explosives.
Explosions.
I applaud his enthusiasm, but sadly, local police have confiscated his equipment.
You stuff the holes, and then you blow up the tunnel system so it collapses.
Look it up on YouTube.
Sir, if the American pull you there, the bodyguard.
What's this guy's problem?
Is he your mate?
Don't touch that.
Get your hands off.
Mr. Nose, are you?
So keep your hands in the air.
I don't want to do that, though.
I think I'd rather just go in somehow.
I mean, explosives are fun, but I feel like I would just do that anyways, wouldn't I?
Back to the safety of the house.
Well, not for long.
Hey, why is this guy acting like a dog?
Shoot him.
All right, let's do this one.
We'll do the mole.
Seems like an interesting way to get in the house.
All right, I have a license for it.
This is it.
Story revealing.
Let's save.
Save it.
Right back to the safety of the treehouse.
No, not for long.
I need it to get rid of an aggressively invasive mole in this poor old man's backyard.
Calm down, demolition man.
Unless it's one of Janus's gods.
You don't need explosives.
We're going to keep them safe in our trunk until you produce that license, okay?
Yeah.
Police trunk.
Get a procedure.
You stuff the holes, and then you blow up the tunnel system so it collapses.
Look it up on YouTube.
Sir, if the American police force looked to YouTube as guiding principle for standard
procedure, I'm pretty sure civilization would have collapsed a long time ago.
God damn it.
YouTube.
All right, so I gotta follow the gardener around.
Yeah, that's what I like to see.
What?
So what's his routine?
We're gonna find out what his routine is.
He goes to the truck.
I've been holding onto that one for a long time.
I think I've already said that.
Do I have said that one yet?
I think I've already said it.
I've been singing that like in the shower for like the last fucking three weeks.
I've done that already.
I have.
So I forgot that I've already said it.
Where can I put them?
Put them in the mailbox.
Can I put them in the trash?
Come on, that's funny though.
Like that's a funny line.
I can't put them in the trash.
All right, what else do I need?
I'm not the bodyguard anymore.
I've got his stuff.
That's a stand-up comic from 2002.
That doesn't mean that it wasn't funny.
It wasn't meant to be funny.
It was meant to be.
That's what I've been singing in the shower.
While the steam fills my eyes and it fucks with my cognitive ability.
So obviously I thought it would be funnier.
Sir, this is a restricted area.
Can I pick up?
Oh, well, this is lagging the game.
Can I get in here?
This person had been home for a while.
This whole area is out of bounds.
Whoa, psycho.
I saw that.
What are you, crazy?
Don't come in here.
Don't move.
Surrender yourself.
Sir, I will have to ask you.
Look at that guy.
Starting street fight.
Suspect is hit.
Take him down.
I understand.
Oh my.
I thought I was gonna be able to get away with it.
What?
Why did this auto save?
Lining up the shot.
Hey, I was leading my target.
He was eventually gonna come over there, guys.
You're not allowed in here.
Okay, sure.
Clown to my left.
Clown to my right.
You know, where the fuck could I possibly be?
This is not suspicious at all.
I'm just checking on the fence.
Hey.
Okay.
He doesn't.
Everything's good.
Okay.
He can hear this.
He can hear like the animal in the bush.
Oh god.
Does he even turn around?
Geez.
Don't come over here.
Just, no.
I gotta sit.
Hey, you all right?
You must have seen the son of a bitch.
Sorry, I didn't see nothing.
I have no idea.
I got hit with meat out of a bush.
And I'm gonna go home.
I'm gonna go get my mom now.
I pooped my pants.
Haha, poo.
Well, all right.
So I make like a reference to an old song
and change the lyrics incredibly brilliantly.
And I...
That was not funny.
I say the word poo out loud.
I'm gonna go poo my pants.
Oh, he's coming back.
No, I had an opportunity to do this.
Oh, come on.
Oh.
Sir, what happened?
I don't know.
I just keep falling down.
Oh, get up.
Don't waste my time.
Do we have any idea of the suspect?
What?
Don't go in.
I'm gonna take you down.
Do you have any idea?
Oh, I gotta stop this.
What is...
Did this just happen?
Oh, I got an extra chance.
It saved it right when he came over.
Hey, you there.
You should get up now.
Any description?
What does he look like?
I don't see nothing.
Prat.
Hey, what seems to be the trouble?
Rise and shine.
Where I pee my pant.
Right?
These guys are just waiting.
They're like, you know what?
Let's just watch that guy.
See what happens to him when...
Oh, fuck.
They heard that.
What's that doing here?
Hey.
What?
That?
Why would you put it there?
He just like said it.
Yeah, I think you're fine.
Just try and get up.
Do we have a description of the suspect?
It's all a blurry mess.
It could be...
I wish I had more items.
That's the sad part.
I wish I had every kitchen item.
I would keep doing it to this guy.
Forever.
I'm gonna say that you guys might think this is not real,
but it is real.
If I was not streaming right now
and I was just playing this game silently in my bedroom,
I would do that probably for two hours.
I probably would.
I would probably keep doing this.
For like an hour and a half.
It would just be fun.
Do it now.
I can't do it now.
Like, you understand?
There are 3,000 people here watching.
If I sat there for two hours
throwing the wrench at the fucking worker,
how many people do you think would be gone in 10 minutes?
I'm gonna say half.
All right.
Infiltrate the garden.
I would definitely not gain viewers.
If I...
Oh my god.
If I did, I don't even...
That would be the...
Oops-a-daisy.
I have to take this guy out.
I have to, right?
I have to.
Shit.
The fucking security camera.
Did you do this?
I don't know what happened here.
Fucking look at me when I'm talking.
Stop!
Put your hands up.
Sure, projects!
Where was it?
16...
1651?
Yeah.
Whoa, hold on a second.
That's not the right one?
Yeah, that's correct.
All right, I got my stuff.
Wait, I need the hammer.
Okay, let me get over there.
I need to save the game.
Well, there it is.
So you can just walk around
until you find everything.
That's cool.
All right, get to the garden.
I'm not going to go that way.
Although, why would I have to...
I'm the gardener.
That guy can see through my disguise.
And gardening is so cool.
Say hi to your mother for me.
I'm sorry.
Um, I don't...
Okay, drop!
I've been recorded by a security camera.
I threw it into its face.
All right, what do we need to do?
I'm here.
I understand you have a mole.
You're a godsend.
Let's get straight to it.
The sooner this is fixed,
the sooner I won't have to listen
to Mr. Janus's complaints.
Follow me.
Oh, let's see if I can fix it with a bone.
As you can see, we have a mole issue.
Yeah, I do see that.
I know a permanent solution might take some time,
but you could just fill the holes
by the end of the day.
Yeah, I'll do it.
Come find me when you're done.
Okay.
I guess that's one way to go about it.
Yeah.
Well, he's a professional.
Guns are the best to block holes with.
Danny, how does it...
There's some over here.
Hold on.
You know all of his memorabilia.
You know how it works.
Interesting.
Maybe you should try to spark
some of those old stories from 2007.
What?
Who knows what secrets Janus might reveal.
Well, let me do this the right way.
I need...
I don't have the fucking explosive device.
No, I'm talking about like re...
I blew that dude up at the door
that yelled at me.
Something bad has to happen to this guy though.
Why are all these doors locked?
No, I have the key.
I'm like popping the door.
I have the key in my pocket.
Damn it.
I was trying to see if it could...
I was trying to see if it could go up
into the camera lens.
Say hi to your mother for me.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go.
Block the holes.
I understand you have a mole problem.
You're a godsend.
Let's get straight to it.
The sooner this is fixed,
the sooner I won't have to listen to Mr. James.
Into the camera lens.
Yeah, like I was trying to throw it in there.
So I'm gonna have to put an explosive
in one of these.
He's gonna come out in his garden.
He's gonna lean down.
Ah, I remember picking up these radishes.
I know a permanent solution might take some time,
but if you could just fill the holes
by the end of the day, great.
Come find me when you're done.
Obtain an item to block the mole hole.
Conceal an explosive in a mole hole.
Well, I mean, block five more holes.
I gotta block...
I actually have to block all the holes.
Shit.
I don't want to get rid of the meat, though.
Is there any random shit around here?
Baseball.
Just running around the yard,
picking up random trash.
I need to find more objects.
What?
I'm just gonna put the guns in them, right?
I need one more blocked.
The less guns I have, the better.
That's right.
All right.
I just need...
There it is.
Shovel.
All right.
Where's that last hole?
There's one gun in there.
That one's blocked.
This one's blocked.
One more over here, right?
Hello, sir.
Yeah, there we go.
I can't...
I want that meat.
Hold on.
There's a muffin here.
All right.
Done.
And I still...
I get to keep my meat.
That's good.
I'm done.
Great.
Let me have a quick...
Hold on.
It doesn't look in it, right?
A bit unorthodox, maybe.
But you got the job done.
That one has a gun that...
Don't open it.
I'm gonna get Mr. Janus so he can inspect it for himself.
Inspect this one?
Is he gonna inspect that one?
Mr. Janus, the molehills have been fixed.
Oh, fuck.
He's gonna pick up the guns.
All right.
Janus should be here to inspect the work soon.
Oh, no.
I'm sure this whole inspection is gonna remind Janus about something exciting from his past.
I'm sure that he's gonna tell us all about it.
Old people syndrome.
Anonymousgifter.
Better yet, keep your distance.
Thank you.
Anonymousgifter for your 10 community subs.
Thanks so much, dude.
Anonymousgifter for your 10 random subs.
Is he gonna actually inspect them?
Because if so, then I'm in trouble.
I'm afraid I'm gonna save here just in case something bad happens.
I'm gonna save, like, over here.
Janus, Cold War spymaster and the first Providence constant.
I wonder how much he remembers.
How little he cares.
Gardner took a bit of an unorthodox approach, but they do look filled to me.
I think I'll be the judge of that myself.
Thank you very much.
He is gonna check them.
Bulls, moles, moles.
Reminds me of a funny story.
Story?
The embassy in Nicaragua in 1986.
Carmen.
She had a charming mole right next to her perfectly luscious plump lips.
I discovered the mole was fake after we kissed and it got stuck on my cheek.
I kept it in a tin box to remind me of her after they sent her to the camps.
What?
He's telling the old stories?
I just keep hearing the...
Why is it the one?
Beautiful work.
The pests will soon be gone.
And then I can get back to planting my plants.
Blast reactions are the first constant to catch up with you.
Death feels like an easy way out for a man like Janus.
Still, someone's killed a lot of people.
We are close now, gentlemen.
Both targets are dead.
Calling in, calling in!
Multiple homicides on our hands.
Someone's not happy.
Anybody there? Come in!
We got some violent jackass knocking people down.
Fox struck to November Zulu, over.
We've got a certified nuisance that needs to be addressed.
Is he dead? I killed him?
I didn't kill that guy.
Wait, he's talking... I thought he was...
Silence! Stop! He's here!
I thought he was going to shoot the other guy.
That guy just backed up.
Blast reactions are the first constant to catch up with you.
Bye!
Death feels like an easy way out for a man like Janus.
Still...
We are close now, gentlemen.
Both targets are dead.
Think I'm going to let that guy get away with it?
Why? You don't remember that guy?
You guys just forget what that guy did?
I need the microfilm.
I should have got this first.
I should have got the microfilm first.
Is what I should have done.
Microfilm? Not in his bedroom?
There it is. Hidden microfilm.
One of Janus' old microfilms.
It might contain important information.
All you need now is to find a device to read it on.
We have to go into that other lady's house.
I need to be somebody else here.
I'm going to not save it right...
You!
Stop writing business here!
We are all weapons hot now.
You already did.
I already killed them both.
We're good?
Review the microfilm.
I think I can just go next door.
Wasn't the lady having a party?
Was it this house or the house next door?
Where's the barbecue?
It's one of these.
You shaved your head in a few seconds?
I got tired of it.
Vital info revealing.
I have to put the microfilm into the projector.
Wait, is this another...
I think it was the other house.
A robe for Janus?
A robe? No.
It was the other house.
I remember the lady at the party was like
Yeah, I've got this old projector upstairs.
I just don't know what to do with the darn thing.
Alright, let's go.
What?
Other side. Bye.
There's the party.
He's lost. Nah, I gotta go up there.
Because it was in this house upstairs, right?
From what I remember from the conversation
that it's the lady right there.
Thanks for keeping everything safe.
Alright, where's your projector?
That's a pretty...
Who is this guy? Don't know, me?
Bob Ross.
You can't badmouth him, Al.
Shame on you.
Bob Ross painted this?
But seriously, what's the deal with all this stuff?
You don't think?
Maybe that's how they're making all their money.
Nobody ever got rich by cashing in
on their fine arts degree, Al.
You know that.
Unless they create forgeries.
I saw a documentary about
Chinese forgery factories.
They were literally spitting out fakes
left and right at millions.
And this, this sort of looks like
Pollock's number five, doesn't it?
No, Al. No, it doesn't.
Let's move on.
Move on, Jay.
Alright, looking for the projector.
Alright, no.
Who the fuck is in here?
Who's this person?
Did I do that?
I didn't do that, did I?
Was I here?
Did I hurt people up here?
Wilson's house key.
Okay.
Baseball. Baseball bat.
It's oversized, too.
TV.
Not a projector.
Reveal the microphone.
Is it upstairs?
Or is it downstairs?
I'm like right over it.
It's like right here.
Don't, don't save it first
if you're gonna, Jesus.
And just like that, we're gonna subvert your expectations.
Agent 47 doing the crab walk.
I gotta get, I gotta get away from here.
Get away.
No. Upstairs.
Where is the attic? Attic button.
Nope. That's not an attic pulley thing.
How do I get up to the attic?
Do I have to go like on the roof or something?
Cause I don't see any more stairs.
Over here? Attic button.
Just in case I need it up there, you know?
My game. Every time I open like a new door.
Let's take a look.
How do I get out of here?
They're both dead.
Locate his robe.
Why do I need to locate his robe?
I need to look at it more?
I think I got all the dialogue out of there.
I'm killing so many cars right now.
Why would you go?
I just wanna throw baseball at somebody out the window.
That's all I wanna do.
There's a heart and a terminal out there.
They need to apprehend him.
Alright.
Security, I need some help.
Jesus!
Food up. Copy.
Stop running, come on.
Oh no! No, wait!
Wait! No! Oh god.
I have to. I got it.
They went through.
So, how come I can't leave?
Do I actually need to like go to this guy's house and put on his robe?
I need to find the robe.
So this is not just as simple as kill the two guys.
Alright.
Locate the robe.
I was supposed to find...
His house is like empty.
No! I got on the roof!
Mom, I'm not gonna be able to get it back.
Well, you throw it up there.
It's staying up there.
I really have to go and like do all this right now.
I thought I was done.
Damn it, man.
Who the fuck is shooting at me?
The guy's just shooting through the wall.
Alright. Where's the microfilm?
Not the microfilm!
Where's the...
Where's the robe?
I'm getting like a time loop.
Locate the robe.
That's over here.
Hold on a second.
Why did they tell me to do that?
When they're like down here.
Am I still on this mission?
Yeah, because apparently I did it and I already did them.
They're already dead.
I'm trespassing over here now.
God damn it.
I'm found trespassing right now.
Where do I need to go?
I need to go to like the other place next door.
Or objective clue reveal.
I'm just going to load the save.
It's going to go from...
Let's go from here.
Is he still trying to throw a brick?
Wait a minute.
Let me read the intel to see why I can't leave.
So I need to...
I need to do this.
So that's the meeting point, right?
Didn't I already do this?
Like didn't I already reveal the meeting point?
And that's just where I need to go.
So constant meeting confirmed.
That's what I needed, right?
Confirm an existing connection between the constant
and reveal a date they would meet.
So it's like in his robe somewhere.
Alright.
This is the first mission that they've done where I've had to actually
complete like the clue parts.
It was just do the mission, kill the guy, and leave.
So I'm going to go
over here.
I'm going to go back to the Cassidy property.
Hopefully nobody freaks out about this.
Can I like jump down from here?
Come on. I can't just jump down from here.
Alright. Well, whatever.
Walk out the front door.
Perfectly normal, but throwing
baseballs is illegal.
Alright.
So it's just this house right here.
I'm not allowed to be in here, but
I'm going to find the meeting point.
Don't load it. Save it.
That's a clue reveal I'm going to.
Don't I have to do it all?
Or do I just have to go get the robe?
Is that the only thing I have to do?
Just get the robe.
You have to do them both.
Well, I'm right here. I'm going to do it.
I'm currently trespassing again.
I'm going to save it right here.
Just find it.
I thought
whatever.
Golf.
Okay.
He's upstairs. Apparently whoever
it is is up there.
Okay. Let's go stare at him.
Hello. Hi.
Alright. Found the meeting point.
Tactical bathroom.
No.
I don't know where he went.
He was somewhere. Tactical.
So I don't have the clue now.
Now I have to go.
Alright. So
was that guy supposed to have a conversation?
Because now I have to go over here.
Okay. Let's go get the robe.
I can't save it yet.
So the robe is now.
Okay. Straight ahead.
The robe.
Hi.
Well, I would have done this first.
I didn't know I had
to do all this.
I guess here.
When it says eliminate, eliminate. Oh.
So you have to do this too.
I just pressed the button.
Let's go. I would have done this all
in reverse.
So I need to. I don't want to like pop that
in front of everybody. But I think I have to.
Hey. What if I happen to. I get to do what I want
in Hitman. What happened to that?
I have to go find these clues?
No. Just stuff them in the guy's pocket.
He should have a map to
Oh. The guy should have a map up his ass.
I'll have his fucking shotgun.
The robe is upstairs.
Why do I keep having the door?
Okay. Give me the bathrobe.
A ceremonial robe of some sort
with a note from Janus attached.
The note is interesting.
Janus has asked Helen
to do a few repairs on the robe before he leaves
for his annual trip.
He even put a date there.
This is valuable information, 47.
So I just had to pick up the robe.
That's all I had to do.
The shotgun? I'll be fine.
That's Gandalf cosplay.
What's really facing?
Who saw me here?
I don't know what he's reading.
But it looks like it's the most
interesting thing he's ever come across.
The new Cassandra Snow novel.
What do you have to do with this?
You're just on a jog.
You're on a jog.
Why would you be like one of the sentries
that can see through my disguise?
Oh. It's the fucking shotgun.
I'll be fine, guys.
Alright. Let's go.
Shotgun, whether it sounds like it's something I want to play
in Dungeons & Dragons.
Out of my face.
Alright.
Who the fuck is this?
Is this guy reading Janus's diary?
Is that his diary?
He's got all kinds of math problems in there.
Alright, give me that diary.
It's in a weird spot.
Can I just leave?
We now know Janus is meeting
with the Constant at an event related
to the Ark Society.
And we have an approximate date as well.
I think that's all we're going to get.
We're close to the finish line.
It's time to end this.
Yeah.
Mission objectives are completed.
47, once you've left Wittleton Creek
I will notify Providence of our
discovery.
In the meantime, we'll go over the clues
you've found.
Once we've located the Constant,
we'll make our final move.
Let's go!
See you later, sucker!
Past, the present, breaking news.
Wear the robe.
I feel like that's what Chad has been saying
for the last 30 straight minutes.
Zero stars, here it comes.
Well, you can't get stars if you
throw fire extinguishers
at people at some point for the mission.
Like, I just, I can't, that's how I like to play.
In one hour, the last mission
took an hour. The mission before that took
an hour. To get five stars
I would have to just sneak around,
do everything by the book.
You wouldn't get to see a baseball
get thrown, because I wouldn't be able to do that.
I got an auto-MK2.
I did, I got like halfway
into trying this one.
The Ark Society.
One of Providence's more
obscure outfits.
I've heard whispers.
A survivalist club for the global
elite. Billionaires preparing
for a global collapse.
And now we know the constant will attend their next
gathering. So where is it?
That's the catch.
The report is redacted.
No names, no location.
So it's a dead end.
I can't track them, not without ICA
backup.
Now, I'm no big shot
analyst, but
there are two missions left.
So we've got a split personality here.
He's like inside of my head.
Wow.
Same person.
I don't have a problem with this.
I mean, they're short anyways.
It's not like they're big, elaborate cutscenes.
They just are there in between.
The Ark Society.
That animal is twice as dangerous.
Let's be perfectly clear.
We were not
exposed. The threat
is neutralized.
We are back on track.
Even so, from this
point on, we expect you to take...
No. There is no way I'm
doing that. Question my
loyalty. In case treachery
is contagious.
Do you really want to
do this to me?
Is there a problem, secretary?
No
problem whatsoever,
madam.
What? Was this a VR game?
Apparently that's all that was.
Here's
to loyalty.
It's that the constant has arrived.
We had outed somehow.
Classic Syringo.
In case the crew get ideas.
Why are you doing
this, Mr. Gray? You had a chance
to walk away. Why didn't you?
A year ago
I'm working security
for this banker, Cobb.
Only to find out he's
a Providence operative.
I've been running for decades
only to wind up where I started.
We've all got
barcodes on the back of our heads.
Most people just never notice.
47 told me about
your parents. How did
they die? Car bomb.
Sorry, 1989.
Company named Blue Seed
didn't care to pay for the mistakes.
But I like to think
no one's
untouchable.
I'm sorry for your loss.
You feel it.
Unlike him, you feel it all.
Everything you've done.
It's a dangerous thing.
Having a conscience.
I was gonna make a Star Wars joke,
but I'm gonna let you guys do it.
If I make the Star Wars joke, everyone's gonna
fucking scream at me.
If I leaned in the mic right there and I was like, you failed too.
I would've seen minus two's
the whole time.
So, here's the Ark Society.
Attention, gentlemen.
Our source on the island
just made a critical discovery.
The Constant has a poison chip
embedded in his neck.
A failsafe, in case he's compromised.
He can't die.
Keep him alive.
Just feed him Red Bulls.
I figure out a way to get the Constant off the island.
It'll be tight.
But once we're back at the ship, we should be able to surgically remove
the chip before the partners have time to react.
But I'm sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
I have my headphones in.
Zoe and Sophia's father
is president of a powerful conservative
think tank. One of Providence's
prime assets.
The apples don't fall far
from the tree.
No saints either. According to ICA files,
the twins are pampered socialites
who get their kicks from treasure hunting.
Commanding a band of trigger-happy
mercenaries, Zoe and Sophia
prowl the world in search for ancient
relics. With little regard for
local culture, or even human life,
they stop at nothing to claim
their primes. Well,
collateral damage they may be,
but safe to say, they have coming.
So, kill them both.
Alright. Hold on a minute.
Let me make sure, okay.
Zoe, Washington.
Any disguise, any method.
Do not
eliminate the constant.
Do not kill this person.
That's it. There's no
clues, or fine clues.
Just don't kill him, kill them.
Okay.
Planning. Take the silver ballers.
Yep. I'll wear my...
That's not a really good
costume. Why wouldn't I put on
a wig? Me putting a wig
on is more effective than me covering
my eyes and nose.
What's he got?
Proximity.
Breed case. I'm gonna
travel breed case. I keep the lockpick
and the fish. Wear the
robe. I don't have
the robe. I don't have
the robe. Alright, ready?
Let's go.
47 was the channel for Nickelodeon in my
grandma's house when I was a kid.
What?
Alright.
Same, same.
Was it?
I don't know what it was for mine.
I feel like it was somewhere in the Twins.
Okay.
This is an interesting castle.
This is just the first part of
Bioshock Infinite.
Don't kill the constant.
Alright.
Hold on, one second. I need to look at this.
Uh...
What is this?
Oh, nope. Nevermind, I'm good.
Alright. So...
Eliminate the
Zoe Washington, Sophia Washington, the both over there.
Don't kill that guy who's trapped
in what seems to be a
bubble.
Yes.
Alright.
We're gonna get a tour?
Alright. But, what's that
though?
No, let's do the tour. That's what I want to do.
He just said epic, he did it.
This place is epic.
Some people are saying you need to take
his robe. All in due
time, guys. It's all in due time.
My god. I don't know why
every time I load another area, I just
mmmmgggg.
Why didn't he do anything?
He's getting
closer to me.
Good to see you, friend.
Good to see you too.
By the way, do you need to
pee or anything?
Just curious.
It's hard to do 47's voice.
There's nobody... Ah, there are people over here.
Yes, hello.
Hello, hello.
Hey, look, a guy on a piano!
Now, so by the way, I just
reduced my score by two stars, I think.
Okay, so it's a party.
Should I get a drink?
We got sushi.
Popcorn.
This drink isn't even... There he is.
I just took a sip out of somebody
else's wine and put it back down.
Where's he going?
Is he going up to the...
This is definitely off limits, right?
I mean, there's a blood-borne cage
over there. Where's he going?
Is he going to make an announcement
or something?
Let's explore.
Now, he is going to make an
announcement.
I think I'm just going to be with
the party.
Okay, everyone's going to go
to the upper courtyard.
Does nobody else care about this? Why are only like three people
going? Off limits?
Is this off limits? Off limits.
Are we off limits?
No, I got to keep up with the group.
That thing's going to slide.
Initiation door.
A locked door leads to the castle basement with it.
Initiation interview with Zoe
Washington will take place, but to gain
admittance, initiates need to collect a number of tokens.
So,
to get through to
Munchkinland, I need tokens.
This is cool.
What the hell is this?
Then the Olympics can now
begin.
I'm going to get the gold medal.
Come on, I got to win the gold medal.
For swinging at people.
Is this money?
You throw
like a thousand dollars in there?
What's this actual ceremony?
It's the Star Citizen
Kickstarter.
What?
Oh, God.
Alright, it's my turn.
I don't have any money.
Was this like Ebenezer
Scrooge?
He's about to see the growth of Christmas present.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, no.
Okay.
Well, the Phoenix
effigy. Burning effigy
sounds like an accident waiting to happen.
Let's save it here.
Somebody mentioned I do have coins.
No, I have a fish.
I don't have very much money.
But will I come from
this is worth
gold?
Thank you.
I want it back.
Alright, let's go.
Escape.
Locate the escape door hydraulics.
I'm definitely not allowed back here.
Tokens.
How many do I need? Can I give this guy a token?
I want to be like the rich asshole
that's all the way in the back.
That doesn't give a shit.
Everyone's throwing cash up there. They want all the claps.
I'm the guy at the auction.
That just raises
up like 50 million dollars. He doesn't
want any fanfare.
Who cares? There's 20 million.
I need that coin.
I think your fish is done.
This is a secret elevator.
How do I get out of this?
How do I go down?
Hey, close that.
Jesse Pinkman.
Alright, I still have that coin, right?
No. I still have the fish.
Alright, we went back to when I had the fish still.
Alright, we're good.
So I gotta get back there.
Alright, locate the escape door.
Here's the token detailed
with a relief of the Ark Society
insignia. Looks significant. Yes, I need it for the door.
This dude over here.
Is anyone going to
stop me from doing this?
Stop me from doing this?
Okay, this guy. I'm going to electrocute this guy.
That's very, very, very certain.
Like, look.
I need a screwdriver to do this.
Alright, well, is there anywhere I can go from here?
Yes, I'm currently trespassing,
but I can climb through this window.
Let me get some tools.
A wrench. Alright, we're getting to like
the weird creepy section now.
Turn on this case.
It's over here.
I'm in the crypt?
Actually, this is good.
This guy comes over here and I'm going to out fish him.
Ooh, coins.
I'm going to go up the stairs.
I need an outfit though before I do anything else.
Don't kill him.
I have an alt here.
Is it just the one guy? It is.
Okay, why don't we make too much noise?
I should be able to get him both.
Well, there's always a period of adjustment
when you get a new job, I suppose.
This is like eavesdropping.
The point is to keep your eyes on the money.
This job pays ten times more
than what the Russian mob pays
and it's a lot more cleaner.
I wonder how this guy moves.
That was an interesting pose.
I can't dump him?
Okay, we're good.
Man.
I'm going to try and get him.
Okay, we're good.
Man, this place is killing my computer.
Can I put him in a sarcophagus?
He can go in here.
Turn on V-Sync.
V-Sync makes my computer have input lag.
Look at the music.
Alright, so now I can try and go back
to where I was in that other area.
Alright, I might have to because
this is going to be impossible.
I don't think it's going to help but I'll give it a try.
Usually I get bad input lag
when I have V-Sync turned on.
Alright, so here we go.
Locate the escape door hydraulics.
Safety protocol.
Sabotage the hydraulics.
I need a wrench.
Which I have but
this is going to make a lot of noise.
The cage beneath the giant effigy
in the courtyard features a hidden escape door
but according to the safety report, the hydraulic locking mechanism
is disturbingly sensitive.
Even a slight drop in pressure could
jam the lock and effectively trap the
occupant inside the cage.
Okay.
Sabotaged.
Locate the master of ceremonies.
He's up.
Oh, I can go up here.
Definitely I can go up this ladder.
Nice. Sick.
Sick. Nice kid.
Sick kid. Nice kid.
Oh dear.
Don't do that.
Watch out.
So, oh, okay.
Can't really go that way.
Everyone falls for the ladder.
Literally everyone. Really?
I mean, it just seems
so easy, doesn't it?
It just looks like it's so convenient
that it's too good to be true.
I feel like I still could do it though.
I just have to wait until this guy's not turning around.
Yeah, that's the problem. Okay.
Okay, so now I gotta go from here, back here.
I mean, this...
I could drop that, but that's too risky.
He's in here.
Two guys. I don't have any keys.
There he is. Found him.
Okay, well, he's the only one that can see through.
What do we got? Okay, we got...
Master of Ceremonies schedule.
Okay.
A moment to moment schedule for the FG ceremony.
The Master of Ceremonies appears on stage.
He descends to the money pit.
He makes a short statement and lights the money on fire.
The Master summons Zoe Washington on stage.
Zoe makes a speech
whereupon she enters the cage beneath the effigy.
The Master takes the stage
and lights the effigy on fire.
Zoe slips out the back door before the structure
is engulfed in flames.
I don't think I have poison.
What else do I got here?
Coin.
Where's it gonna go?
I got guard here.
I got music box.
And...
Nobody cares about this?
You're the only one that's gonna look at this distraction?
No, that's not how this is gonna go down.
And he got the coin too.
Ha! Did that not hit anybody?
That's just about enough of this.
Did he open the door?
Oh!
Boomerang!
I got the boomerang, but it didn't matter.
Fuck me. Did I really not save it?
What happened?
I dropped the chandelier
and it didn't hit anybody.
It went right between them both.
In a perfect spot.
And then I lost my mind
and started throwing shit at people.
And then somebody was found and I unloaded a clip.
Alright, here we go.
Let's try this again.
Save it here.
One, two, three.
Alright.
Go examine somebody.
So this is not gonna kill him.
I have to wait until he turns it off and then leaves.
Close it!
Same exact scenario.
Just did it.
The same scenario.
Give me his stuff.
I can't even...
Get over here.
I can't believe it.
I can't hide you here.
The only difference is he went the other direction.
Oh my god.
Why is my computer hate this level so much?
Don't let me forget that coin.
Oh, that's full.
Drop the gun.
The master of ceremonies with the fucking machine gun.
Give me the coin.
Was there one on the ground here too or just that one?
Okay. Gun.
Drop it.
All I have is the coins.
As a fish illegal.
They're not gonna care. They're gonna think I'm a weird person.
That's it.
I already know this.
I can stuff this one in my pants.
So we got it. I got fish.
Two coins.
Make sure the fish is what's currently equipped.
Save it. It's time to do it. Let's do it.
All right. Now the ceremony's down here.
They all can see through this disguise.
And here goes Doctor Strange.
Okay, Dad.
You accidentally ordered the giant fish.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You accidentally ordered the children's size costume on Amazon.
You didn't want to send it back.
I get it.
Master of ceremonies.
Begin.
Do I have anything to say?
No speech or anything?
Okay.
I did this earlier and everybody was mad at me.
Just having a dumb shitty costume on.
It's cool.
I don't have time for this.
This is what Jerma does to his bits and
cheers.
All right. There she is.
She's going around.
We're going to save it here.
Because I can't be trusted.
I already know this.
Cook fish.
That guy was going to investigate.
What was that sound?
Ceremony.
Summon Zoe Washington.
Zoe Washington.
The Arc Society
recognizes you as
our founder's rightful
successor.
Our inspiration.
Our guiding light.
The custodian of our future.
When you were at my side?
Excellent work, 47.
Enjoy the spotlight.
Patrons of the Arc Society.
You are part of a select
chosen few.
Our founder, Janus, showed us
how to survive. But survival is
not enough. We must live
and we must soar.
The Arc Society must not only commit
itself to survival, but to progress.
Be it our next home in the stars
or the next step in human evolution.
There's a giant shot down here.
This is the eternal purpose of the elite.
Not just to lead,
but to lead from the front.
She sounds so happy.
When mankind
retreats once more into caves
of superstition, we will keep
the fire alight.
We will be the torch bearers, the trail
blazers and pioneers.
Do not feel guilty for your
privilege.
Be fearless.
For the future
is ours to shake.
Alright, get in.
Hello, sir.
Look at you, Fenneker. All dressed
to kill. Now let's do this thing.
Light her up.
As the world burns,
we rise
from its ashes.
Not just to survive,
but to live.
One target down. Nice work,
Felicity. Next up,
Sophia Washington.
I tried to save her!
Oh, fuck. This is why I can't be trusted.
Zoe Washington.
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
I thought I had to save you earlier.
We have to listen to this speech again.
But I'll be up there and ready.
The guiding light.
The custodian of our
future.
Excellent work, 47. Enjoy the spotlight.
Patrons of the
Arc de Triomphe.
James showed us how to survive.
But survival is not enough.
We must live, and we must
soar. The Arc Society
is not only committed itself to survival,
but to progress. Be it our
next home in the stars, or the next
step in human evolution.
Is the eternal purpose
of the elite.
I'm just her son.
Time comes, and all
comes tumbling down.
Don't mind little John.
Little Johnny.
We will keep the fire alight.
He has attention deficit hyperactivity disorder.
Do not feel guilty
for your privilege. Be proud.
Be fearless.
For the future is ours
to shape.
Look at you, Fenager.
Now let's do this thing.
Light her up.
Hello.
As the world burns,
it's from its ashes.
Not just to survive,
but to live.
No, no, no, no.
One target down.
Nice work, 47.
Next
step, Sophia Washington.
Hey, let's imagine
an invisible barrier between
me and you that extends out to
us.
What do you think it was?
Do you think it's worth investigating?
Hey, wait a minute.
Please get out of my face.
Oh, come on.
Can you just go see what it was?
For sure. This concludes
the performance, ladies and gentlemen.
No, they're not that
stupid.
All right, eliminate Sophia Washington.
Let's go up there.
Let's see if we can find some intel.
Isn't that how it's done?
That was crazy.
I almost shat myself.
I think you are coming on a little too strong.
Okay.
It's time.
Let's head back down.
I think we should go up here.
Okay.
Let's head back down.
I think we should go up here.
Weird.
I believe I'm allowed to go up here.
I'm the master of ceremony.
Yeah, okay.
I got three of these.
What can I do up here?
Thank you.
What is this? The MOC.
The master of comedy.
That's right.
So,
I don't want to kill
That's it.
The constant.
Providence's top controller.
Everything depends on capturing him alive.
But this?
We're really doing this, aren't we?
That we are. Donations.
Purchases. Excavations.
Here comes a poo poo joke.
No, I'm not doing that.
Why is this guy talking like Mr.
Rogers?
Do you want to know my name?
No, I'm not going to poo on the stream, guys.
I'm not going to shit on the stream.
That's an interesting way to hold that gun.
Do you think the gun
is going to shit in your hand?
Good to see you.
Okay, we've got to get in here.
The gallery.
So.
It was lost for over 500 years.
Until Blake Nathaniel unsealed
the serpent's tomb. Hello, sir.
Extraordinary. It's a flippy necklace.
Anyway, the Washington
twins found it first.
No.
That was the only lead on the parties.
Abort mission.
Through the glass.
It was lost for over 500 years.
Until Blake Nathaniel unsealed
the serpent's tomb.
Extraordinary. It's a flippy necklace.
Anyway, the Washington
twins found it first.
The way I hear it, Sophia literally
has the necklace in her hand.
When Nathaniel repels from the ceiling,
triggers this ancient death trap.
Murder may have ensued, but
I thought those two
were lovers.
On and off.
Currently way off, which explains the added security.
I don't follow.
Think about it. Why the need
for an alarm system where all
filthy rich accept?
Ah, I see.
Blake thinks Sophia
might try and steal back the necklace before it's
sealed in the Ark of the Legacy.
So, according to its charter,
the Ark Society collects priceless
art and historical artifacts in case
of a global disaster.
And this year, world famous treasure
hunter Blake Nathaniel
has donated an Aztec necklace called
the Cloud Serpent to the Ark Society's
growing collection. However,
Blake fears that Sophia Washington,
his former lover and
rival, who has hunted the Cloud Serpent
for years, will attempt to steal
it for herself before it goes into storage.
Hmm.
Could be just the bait we need.
What's this one?
I don't know. I didn't discover it.
Good grief. No honor among thieves, huh?
I'll say. Interesting.
You think?
Okay. So I need to steal the necklace.
How on earth am I going to steal this necklace?
Hmm.
Alarm sensors.
You'll need to disable the system to get
at the necklace, 47.
I could just pull the fire alarm, right?
Why don't I just pull the fire alarm?
There's the fuse box.
Can I steal? Are these allowed?
What?
You have to eat all the eggs.
Okay. Well, this is...
It goes up there.
Do I need to climb this?
They're going to obviously... I need to turn the
lights off because they're going to see me do this.
Hmm. Alarm sensors.
You'll need to disable the system to get
at the necklace, 47.
I didn't... I'm trying to turn off the
lights. I guess it worked.
Well...
Hey! This area is off-limits!
I'm getting help!
I don't like... Hey!
Better get your head out of your ass double quick!
Hey, you! This is a restricted area!
Hey, wait a minute!
I'm taking you out of here.
Follow me.
I already told you to follow me.
What's the problem, bozo?
Hey, you!
That's going to hurt me!
Man!
I got to hack the system!
Well, alright.
So there's a shitload of people up there.
Okay.
Alright. And they can all see... I've got to get a different disguise.
It was lost for over
500 years.
Actually, I might...
I might be able to get it.
Anyway, the Washington
twins found it first.
The way I hear it, Sophia literally
has the necklace in her
hand. When Nathaniel repels from the ceiling,
it triggers this ancient death
trap and, you know, murder
and mayhem.
Oh, there's no door up there
though.
I think I might be
able to take him out.
It's very
possible. Right now?
Right now.
I have to go a different way, then.
It could have been possible.
If I had choked him out and ran
around.
Yeah, I know.
Alright, let's go...
I'm going to go this way.
Steal the necklace.
Don't show me the fire axe.
I'm not picking it up.
Fuck it, man.
Oh, I got you.
I got you, motherfucker. Come here.
Cool.
Why are you looking in the...
Why are you looking in here?
Are you going to investigate that or what?
Mistake.
Oh, god damn it.
I just have a fish. I have one fish.
I don't give a fuck.
Hold on, wait, that's not silenced?
That's not silenced.
Well, the guy I need to disguise
as is currently about to...
No, why'd you shoot him?
Why'd you shoot him?
I was trying to shoot him.
Oh, it's me.
This is an elite guard.
Alright.
Elite guard.
I have to dump them all.
Alright, nice. I'm ready.
Let's give it a save.
Right here.
What the hell?
Evening, sir.
Alright.
I thought that was just supposed to be him.
It's not him.
Okay, I need to disguise as
this person down here.
They're going up the stairs.
I'm going to cut you off this way.
I need that mask.
It's not going to happen.
It's just not going to happen.
In fact, I'm not going to be able to open this door either.
Unless do I have the key to the door?
I don't.
I have to sneak through this guy.
And then upstairs.
That guy can see, but it doesn't matter.
Just opens.
And then I should be able to get this...
There they go. Upstairs.
Anything in here I can do?
No, I don't need to do that.
I'm going to get a pause moment here
because I think my dog needs to go outside
before we get there.
When does he end up?
I'm going to do it too.
No, what the fuck are you doing?
I can't move.
I can't go down.
I can't drop down here?
I can't do anything.
You think that I can move to that ledge and clap?
What are they dragging him to?
Yeah, but somebody can see me out here.
I can't be out here for more than two seconds.
Oh my god.
Just slide down.
Why is it so complicated?
Where is he taking off?
I don't even know where the fuck that guy even went.
Where is he now?
Is he just gone?
Did the guy get taken out?
I got to take the dog out.
He was sprinting around
in a circle here.
He just didn't want to be in the room.
Alright.
So the question is,
did they drag them away?
I'm not sure I can do this right now.
I think I have to restart it.
Where did I save it from here?
Right here.
I'm in the same disguise, so this should be fine.
This time I'm going to push him out
and I'm just going to go right after him.
I might be able to take him here.
I don't know what it is about this level, man.
It's driving me crazy.
My CPU is not even doing anything.
I'm at like 24% CPU usage.
Why is it doing this?
I'm sorry.
I take the dog.
Can I not do this?
Is this over now?
Is this over anyways?
I can do it.
Sorry you didn't get to see that.
My god.
Does anybody know of a solution here?
Because my game just does not want to run in here.
We've turned down the graphics and everything,
but my CPU is running fine.
I have a 1080.
Why is this happening?
Don't know why.
I have a shotgun on my back.
Is it the drivers?
That actually might be...
What was this?
I need his stuff.
Well you missed it. It was really funny.
Well it wasn't that funny.
I dropped it right on his head and nobody noticed.
Angry text from Sophia.
To me.
Where is she though?
Up there.
Thank you.
Cap it at 15 frames a second.
This is so weird.
I don't know what it is, but if you're like a billionaire
or like a trillionaire.
Why are they all...
Is it all billionaires at one weird shit?
Like what is this?
Like why would you have this?
What is this for?
Like what are the screens that just have one image?
Hello?
Hi.
Sophia.
I almost didn't recognize you without
a knife in my back.
I see that now.
This should be good.
Follow me.
Excellent 47.
Let's give Sophia her heart's desire, shall we?
You've got one minute.
I did wrong by you Sophia.
I see that now.
And I want to make amends.
Here, this is rightfully yours.
Well, well.
Look who comes crawling back.
Leave us.
You know,
we lost three men because of you.
Wicus was crushed by a rolling
boulder.
We only escape
the arrows by using one of the local
guides as a human shield.
Now this is a nice
gesture.
I know.
May I?
Money counter.
You know, I thought about sending the boys after you.
Grab the necklace and cut your throat
ear to ear. You probably wonder
why I didn't. The truth is
you beat us, Blake. I don't deny
it. And I can't very well get
Both targets down.
Impressive work, 47.
And now to confront the constant.
Kill switch.
Mr. Gray, what's your status?
I'm at the helicopter, but the place
is crawling with security.
47, you better bring the constant to one
of the boats in the harbor where it's quiet.
Can I put her in the chair? You can use the kill
switch to coerce.
Can I put her in the chair like she's sitting in the chair?
In the window?
No, I'm not putting her in the window.
Does he put the cup in the room?
Help Lucas Gray extract the optional.
Talk to the constant.
He's right here.
The Washingtons are dead. I have the kill switch.
What did you say?
How could you know about that?
You will head towards the harbor.
No sudden moves.
No signs or warnings.
I will trigger the device if I need to.
I know you.
The boy in the picture.
You have his eyes.
You're Bynwood's assassin.
Move.
Everybody thinks I'm gonna do it.
But I'm not gonna do it.
Partners, no more. I take it.
I had a notion
Something didn't sit right with my
I'm not gonna do it.
You murdered him
I take it to be
Not just that. He had it coming.
No, I can't do it.
I need to get two stars.
Such sentiment.
If I don't get two stars then what the hell?
The doctor built his serum specifically
to target the seeds of your emotions.
Has Ms. Bynwood's
sense of justice rubbed off on you?
I wonder.
You must keep walking.
That's the original five?
For what it's worth.
Janus always found
Ortmeier's project distasteful
not to mention inefficient.
S.
Sometimes you have to play the hand
you're dealt.
What if it doesn't work?
This is just an elaborate ruse and this doesn't even do anything?
Look at all these ruse patterns.
Just test it to see if it works.
Better test it to make sure.
Make sure it works.
Okay.
I guess we'll make sure it works.
No. 47.
That was our only lead on the partners.
Abort mission.
Alright, it works.
He's faking it. He could hear the button click.
He heard like...
Let me get that door for you.
I take it this is not an ICA
sanctioned operation.
What exactly does Ms. Bynwood
plan to achieve by targeting her clients?
Violating her own code?
She's doing it.
For us.
Us? Or C?
The penny drops.
I should have known.
How does a man leave no trace?
Did I break my eyebrow?
Did I?
Me.
Or was it Subject 6?
He died when the Institute...
Oh shit.
Is it because I ran in front of him and
opened the door?
Okay.
We're almost there.
I take it this is not an ICA
sanctioned operation.
What exactly does Ms. Bynwood
plan to achieve by targeting her clients?
Violating her own code?
She's doing it.
For us.
Us? Or C?
The penny drops.
I should have known.
How does a man leave no trace?
By not existing in the first
place.
Lucas Gray.
Or was it Subject 6?
This guy is my hair.
Nope.
I don't have a bald spot on the top of my head. Sorry to disappoint you.
Unlike you, his rage
never faded.
So, now you want the nurse.
The men behind the curtain
caused you all this pain.
Before you go knocking down
Yes. Hello.
You see there are more people
above me.
It's the water that does it. The first mission did
the same thing. It's all these
waves that are doing it for some reason.
Disable water.
You can't. I can't turn the water off.
Yikes.
Jesus.
Got him.
I mean that was
pretty clean.
Right?
Like if I get zero stars
then I mean
it has to be all the time that I just keep
reloading and doing stupid things.
It was like clean enough to not have
I mean it's gotta be because I'm
fucking restarting and throwing people off
balconies. Plus
zero. It's cause I'm like killing people
and shit. It was pretty clean.
Alright we're going to the chapel. The gatehouse.
We have this mace now.
A mace.
Lethal syringe. Finally unlock the syringe.
And here are the other options for this
particular part of the game.
We're on to the final area of
Hitman 2. This is the last
area I believe.
Final area. Not final mission obviously.
Cause there are six places.
Wasn't that the final
area was it? That was the last
one. Mr. Edwards
I still think this is maintenance.
Oh I thought there was another. I thought there was one more.
Oh Miss Burnwood.
What have you done?
Changing horses
midstream?
Truly unprofessional.
You know what we want.
Where is the carrot?
No carrot.
You're useless to the partners.
Compromised. Even if we let
you live you can never return.
Why die protecting
them? When I can drag them
down with me?
It's a bad hand.
But it's all you've got.
Three families.
That's all it took.
The Ingrams.
The Carlyles. The Stuyvesants.
Three
dynasties. Secretly
pooling their resources
over generations.
Creating a singularity
so dense that nothing
escapes its gravity.
Never heard of them. Well they've heard
of you. In fact
you just became the top of their
agenda. Go.
We can't give them time to retaliate.
Don't take your eyes off him.
He's gonna get out. Be careful.
Well here we are again.
I must admit
I am disappointed Miss Burnwood.
I had such
big plans for you.
Save it. He's gonna get out. I know the truth
now. You're outplayed.
You have nothing left to bargain with.
You're so certain.
So sure
of the people closest to you.
Was he a bad guy?
He never
misses his mark.
You found a window
into his past.
And yet
something else remains
hidden. So it was
me the whole time. A simple truth you learned
long ago.
No one, Miss
Burnwood. I did it.
Is untouchable.
I was
the carrot all along. Oh I did it.
I don't understand the big reveal
there. Did we do that in a previous game?
Was that like Hitman 1?
Look at all these people that made this great game.
Alright. Um. Um. Um.
Next up.
Re-plan mission. Re-play
mission. Exit to menu.
There's a lot of other things to do.
Okay. Alright.
Hold on. Exit to menu. Wait a minute. Hold on a second here.
Wait a minute. Hold on.
Hold on here. Hold on a minute here.
What is this? That's the
DLC. Ah. From Hitman 1.
What else? Okay. This is sniper
assassin mode. And then there's also ghost
mode. I didn't
even do this. Single player.
What is this? Oh this is like
the demo isn't it?
Welcome to Austria.
Agent 47. Your targets are Dorian
Lang, Guillaume Maison
and Doris Lee. Three remaining
members of the international gang of thieves
known as the Yardbirds. The multiplayer is in beta?
The Yardbirds were famous for the daring
heists. In particular, one that
took place against Chamal Casino in Las
Vegas. I- That's where I live!
To be the property of organized criminals
who in turn launched a campaign of violence
and retaliation in an effort to
identify the thieves and find
the money. Feeling the earth burn beneath
them, the Yardbirds entered into
a secret agreement. The treasure would
remain hidden and once the dust settled
the last remaining member was to
inherit everything.
The group retired and all members vanished
from sight until Calvin Ritter
the Sparrow was found dead
on his yacht. But the remaining
members remained elusive.
The group never gathers
in one place but today
is a special occasion.
The owl's birthday!
Alright, eliminate
everybody. I didn't do this.
Kill them all.
Agent and Mastery. Agent 47.
Sure.
C...
Extended mag level 2. Alright,
level up?
Let's do it.
Oh.
So, is the multiplayer
like available right now?
I'll try, I would try it.
It's Battle Royale.
No, it is not, is it?
It's a Battle Royale.
I don't believe that.
Alright, let's do it.
So we got guy in the window,
people showing up by car.
Just wait till they all get to the ceremony.
He's in the car, he's in the window.
This is the mobile game.
It's a flash game.
This was the teaser though,
wasn't it?
Wasn't this the precursor to Hitman 2
releasing? I think I can handle it.
Once he gets close enough I'll try to take out
1, 2, 3. Just play
the stickman sniper game.
Oh my god, that's a long time ago.
Alright, where is he?
The Kingfisher.
Former Interpol agent and the owner of
the mansion and its grounds.
So who is this then?
That is Doris Lee, aka
the Goldfinch.
Former Hollywood stunt woman of Cheyenne descent.
That is Dorian Lang, the Red Robin.
Former military engineer
and father of the bride.
47, the situation is about
to become critical. Lang is down.
Nice work 47.
Lee has been eliminated.
Good work 47.
47, an alarm went off.
They're evacuating.
Oh shit, I got a bridesmaid.
Oh fuck.
No.
There they go.
Nice work 47.
Nice long jump.
They're just shooting up here.
Nobody can hit me. Oh my god,
this sensitivity. Wait, DPI.
One, two, three. DPI up.
Someone's getting away. Someone's getting away.
Yes.
Nice work 47.
That was fun, I guess.
There's so many ways to do that.
Now do ghost mode. Yeah, okay.
Oh my DPI.
Alright, let's try the multiplayer.
Let's see what it's like. Ghost mode.
Okay. Briefing.
Eliminate targets to gain points
and beat your opponent. Find opponent.
Quick match. Game rules.
I kind of need to know what the hell happens here.
Are we in the same game?
The first player with five eliminations
is the winner. Targets are
randomly selected every time
so no duel will be the same.
Since you start off with no equipment
you'll need to improvise.
Find ghost crates and grab
disguises as you go. Can we see
each other? If your opponent scores a kill
you'll have limited time to react.
Will you risk blowing
your cover? Be careful.
A spotted kill does not count.
Does not count?
You exist in separate realities.
So a messy, chaotic
approach on your end
does not affect your opponent.
Quite the contrary. While you're
busy cleaning up or running for your life
your opponent is free to advance
like a ghost. Be cunning,
be creative, be ruthless.
Good luck.
That's kind of unfortunate.
I guess you kind of have to do something like
that though. Because
how would you ever do this?
Somebody would just throw grenades
and it would just ruin everything.
Alright, I'm going up against
Coca-Cola.
It would just be a cesspool game mode.
Yeah, it wouldn't work.
It'd be fun to do something like
that Assassin's Creed
game mode where
it was a game that I played where you hit around
and you had to get... Can we actually see each other though?
I guess we can see each other.
Don't orcs. Anything can still happen.
Your opponent is now
disguised.
Silent takedown.
You're following me.
Why are we the same target?
I got it before he did.
What's going on?
Next target in 10 seconds.
Hold on. So it's just a race
to get to the guy?
Okay, this is way cooler.
This is not...
New target. Find
and eliminate. Good news.
Your opponent died.
Your opponent is back
in the fight.
Good news.
Wait, is he upstairs?
Damn it.
Good news. Wait, is he down?
What the fuck?
Go!
Go over it!
Your opponent killed the target.
Warning. Target
will be lost in 15 seconds.
Target lost.
Oh, okay. I get it.
I get it. I get it.
I get it. I understand.
Wait a minute.
I understand.
So it doesn't matter.
I get it.
So wait, why did
Why does he only have one
point?
Where's his point?
I don't get it.
How come he doesn't have a point right now?
Because I killed it in time?
He got noticed too? Okay.
When does this end?
Your opponent changed disguise.
Where is this dude?
Is he down?
He is down.
He is down. He's in the garage.
Okay.
I gotta get down to the garage.
I gotta go down the stairs.
Neither one of us can get him
apparently.
No!
Damn it!
I'm not even changing disguise.
It has to be a stealth kill.
That's right.
Alright. I got the jump on this one.
He's up there.
We'll see.
What's this?
Target eliminated.
He's in a bird costume.
Clean kill.
Score two to one.
Wait. Give me that costume.
Score two to two.
Two to two?
Your opponent just picked up additional
equipment.
Where did he get the extra point from?
Three, two, one.
New target.
Find and eliminate.
Pool ball?
Alright. I got a pool ball.
What was the extra point?
I can't go this way.
Yeah. We both killed the same guy though.
Let me just disguise. Come on.
Prime noticed by somebody.
Who the fuck saw it?
Oh. Fuck you.
Oh well.
I'm still...
What is happening here?
Get out of the way.
What the fuck are you...
Your opponent just picked up a weapon.
I can't vault over that.
Oh my goodness.
I can't vault over that either.
I can't unlock that. Shit.
I gotta go down.
I gotta go down. I gotta go down. I gotta go down.
I have no items.
Snap his neck. Frame rate.
Why?
Is there anything in here?
Score three to two.
What the fuck is happening?
What are you talking about?
All even.
Move carefully. Five.
Four. Your opponent
just picked up additional equipment.
New target.
Find and eliminate.
I'm in the game too?
He's up. He's this way. Up or...
I'm secure though.
I should be fine.
Your opponent changed disguise.
Your opponent just
picked up additional equipment.
This is where I take the lead.
Right here. This is where I take the lead.
Did I not get it?
Your kill was
witnessed. Fucking god damn it.
Let me just repeat some ground rules
for those of you new...
What?
I lost a point for that. I lost...
Two to three.
How did he see me do that?
Five. Four.
Three. Good news.
Your opponent died.
New target. Find
and eliminate. So that's what happened.
That's what happened to him.
Your opponent is back in the fight.
Oh my fucking god.
One to three.
Your opponent changed disguise.
Just get me out of
the game already.
He's gonna win.
If you kill somebody that's not
the target you lose a full point.
That's a rage quit right there.
Like what the fuck?
Guy gets behind and the security camera sees
me. That's why I got compromised.
That's bullshit.
Why would you even give this to me?
How the hell are you supposed to use this without being seen?
Don't retaliate.
You'll lose points.
Back in the fight.
Careful. Your enemy
will still recognize you.
You are losing. Assert yourself.
I had a chance and then I threw it away.
Score. One to four.
Your opponent has almost won.
Good. I hope he wins.
I would have won the game too.
Seven. Six.
Five. Four.
Three. Two.
One.
New target. Find and
eliminate.
Just kill me.
Just go win.
Your opponent changed disguise.
Let me open the door for you.
I'll go scout it out up here.
Your opponent just picked up additional
equipment.
I hope he uses it well.
Use some assistance here.
Your opponent just picked up
additional equipment.
I don't see how this works. I have no items.
I'm not allowed to be in here.
If it's a camera, I swear to God.
Knock him off.
Why would they give you guns like this?
I want to see what happens if I do this.
Target eliminated. Your kill was witnessed.
Target. Score.
Zero to four.
Nine. Six.
Five. Four.
Three. Two.
One.
Target. Score. Zero
to four.
You just kill him. He's in there.
Is there a forfeit button?
Just exit.
Congratulations, you won.
It just quit me out of the whole game.
It's updating now.
I have an update to download.
Why is this the second time this has done this?
No, I was doing fine.
That's the first time I've even seen
that game mode, first of all. Second of all,
killing somebody that's not a target,
you lose a full point.
Is that their way to make it so you
never don't ever do anything bad?
Is that like the anti-grief
to make it so you just go to zero and you just lose
if you shoot somebody that's not a guy that you need
to go after?
Because if you play into five points, losing one point
is a total disaster.
It's a complete disaster.
Only play into five,
then the only way you can get a point
you'll never make it to Hitman 2 Nationals.
I want to try that again,
now knowing that that's going to happen.
Guns exist to stop someone else from getting
a point if you don't have time to get unnoticed
and kill.
But wouldn't you lose a point?
So you shoot the guy
from far away,
not if they're the target.
But that makes it so they can't
get the point. But wouldn't that person be
alive in their mode?
I thought it was like
separate realities.
You can't get to him in 20 seconds.
Alright, let's do it again. Let's try it again.
But how did he
get two points?
Because he had two points at one time after one person.
He got a
costume bonus?
No, that's not even real.
There's no costume bonus.
There's a syncing issue? Oh.
Okay, let's try this again.
Who the hell are we?
Alright, what do we got here?
Um,
crowbar break.
I'll take it.
Wait, where'd you get that disguised?
He's waiting for me.
He's
waiting for me. That was so
nice of you.
He's like, okay, you ready? Alright.
I'm actually in the co-op mode.
Do you think
or I mean
what?
Target eliminated.
Your kill was witnessed.
Next target in 10 seconds.
Your opponent
killed the target.
And nobody noticed it?
Nobody noticed his kill?
No, he's like running around
punching people.
He didn't use a brick.
Well, he got noticed.
What's going on here? Who's firing?
Coming up here? Nope.
This is not a bathroom. I thought this was a bathroom.
What do we got? Ghost coin.
Uh, are we both not killing him?
I don't think this is... Where are you coming from?
Get out of here!
Five. Four.
Three. Two.
One.
There's like too much going on here.
Find and eliminate.
Opponent changed disguise.
Alright, well it's zero to zero.
Back in the fight.
Careful. Your enemy will still recognize you.
Alright, so when you...
I'm automatically just still...
I don't get to start over.
I'm out in combat still.
Yeah, I know she just said that
but that's still like where the fuck am I supposed to go?
Careful. Your enemy will still recognize you.
I'm still hunted.
So I'll just pull the guy in the fucking tank top
aside and take his tank top?
I can't even take his disguise.
I need a disguise.
He'd want to do better this time.
Your opponent just picked up a weapon.
I can't take that guy's clothes.
There is still some time to go.
Your opponent just picked up additional equipment.
Wow.
Jumped by this other man.
The upper down, he's down.
I need a disguise.
Your opponent killed the target.
God, I'm gonna lose.
You are losing. Assert yourself.
Okay.
Score zero to one.
I'll assert myself.
Target will be lost in ten seconds.
Anybody here? What? Hold on.
Your opponent just picked up additional equipment.
Five, four, three.
Target lost.
Target eliminated.
New target.
Find and eliminate.
I don't even want to play this anymore.
I don't think this is very fun.
I really don't.
All even.
Your opponent changed disguise.
Back in the fight.
Careful. Your enemy will still recognize you.
Yeah, I know.
So I...
Oh my fucking god.
This is the same outfit.
It's the same guy.
You are losing.
Assert yourself.
That just hit me. I just killed me.
Score zero to one.
I don't know where to put him.
Someone's gonna come in here.
Gotta go up.
Can I get up through here?
I don't have any items.
I need to find something to kill him with silently.
Christ.
Oh god.
Give me a break.
You can't be here, sir.
Your opponent changed disguise.
Yeah, I have a mini...
I know I have a minimap, but I have to find something.
Back in the fight.
Careful.
I hate it. I don't want to play it anymore.
I hate that.
I can't do this?
No. Do the patch notes.
I want to do this.
I'm gonna go back to here.
I understood how it all worked.
It just seems like...
I don't know. I just don't...
I didn't like it at all.
There's more multiplayer? What?
This is the only one that's here.
I already did the sniper mode.
I know I'm not a great hitman player,
but I just want to scream right now
about how much I hate that fucking game mode.
I just want to yell it as loud as I can.
All right.
Create a contract.
Contract search. Trending.
Easy. With a heart.
Let's do easy.
Easy. By salt.
This one's trending.
Eliminate Christopher May.
All right.
Are you serious?
That's it. Okay.
That's it. Just shoot him and hit the button.
Is this what you wanted?
How do I get a two-star?
Hold on. I'm gonna replay this mission.
Let's get a five-star on easy.
So what do I have for items?
Just fiberwire? Okay.
So I'm gonna coin this guy
and fiberwire him.
I'm so...
I'm so tilted right now.
From that fucking multiplayer mode.
I just need like a stress ball
to bite him with my teeth.
I think I have to stop playing.
I have to stop playing. I'm so...
Oh my god.
All right. I gotta get ready for tomorrow.
Oh, I'm so upset.
So tomorrow is the
green screen stream.
That should be a lot of fun. Tomorrow afternoon.
Why not some more ghost mode?
No, I'm never opening that ever again.
I really don't know what time.
I think it's kind of whenever
I want to start it, I think.
But actually, let's do this now.
Yeah, I'm out of here.
Because there are some things I need to do.
And I'm going to freak out
if I don't get out of here.
Like this game.
Why would they put that in the options menu?
Anyways.
Let me get this back to you guys.
Tomorrow, probably around
let's see, 1, 2, 3, 4.
I'm going to try
I'm assuming it's going to happen around 12 or 1 Pacific.
So.
Probably around 3 to 4 Eastern is when it's going to start.
I had a poll. Might as well show it
one more time.
One of the mods
have that poll for the memes.
Because I
have it somewhere here. It just would take me a minute to find it.
There it is.
So, there were a lot of responses.
Take a look there.
And it looks like
I'll leave this open for like 5 minutes.
It looks like
the top 3 are JoJoPose's
CSI Sunglass
One-liners and Infinity War stuff.
So, I'm going to have to look up
some of those. I know there's already
some highly requested ones.
But, let me see
here. Yeah, so that's what it's going to be.
It will be
these listed here.
With that, if you want to take off
I'll see you tomorrow.
Probably around 4
to 5 PM Eastern.
I'd say between
like 4 and 7 Eastern is
I'm going to try to start at the typical time.
I'm trying to think of anything else to
talk about here before I go.
I'm just sitting here trying to think.
Uh, Deltarune.
I will play Deltarune probably
at a later date.
Not right now.
Because I have to go to
Best Buy.
Or Walmart.
Or Target or something.
Because there are still like
at least a couple dozen things that I still
need. And I need to go while
they're still open.
So, I'm not entirely sure
which one of these stores I'm going to be going to.
It is a good question.
Because there's still props that I need.
I bought some stuff
but I need... Whoa!
I'm coming in.
Thank you to
Amphiric for the 5 community subs.
Have some subs before you go.
Oh, thank you dude.
Means a lot. Thanks a lot.
Because the thing that I need to buy
I was looking at online
and you
have to kind of get it at like a Target
or a Best Buy or something like that.
I need to see. I know there's like a shitload
of like Best Buys,
Walmarts, Targets. They're everywhere around here.
This is Las Vegas.
They are fucking everywhere.
Alright, let's do the bits.
He's an inflatable microphone.
Take care everybody.
See you soon.
It's time for me to read.
So, with that, thank you for $3
to Hasnain. Thanks with 3 bucks.
Terrible late streamer. Thank you.
I was a little late today.
That's right. Thank you Superspy
Burger Flipper for the $1.
Hey Jerm, I had a dream last night with you in it.
You were a guest speaker at some event
and asked if everyone, if they
knew you. I jokingly said that I knew you because
you murdered someone very specific, but then you
stared to be dead in the face.
And so if you say that again I'm gonna
blow your head off.
Jesus! You still
had the mic on.
What the fuck?
Why are you having that kind of dream about me?
Thank you so much dude. But
Jesus. Zero Sue,
thanks for the $1.50. Thanks for starting the stream
the second I got home and turned on the tub.
Too bad I had to kill a lot of rats
today at work. Sorry to hear that.
I'm sorry about the rats too.
But thank you Zero Sue. Thank you Hasnain again
for a dollar. I have a report for Unium in for tomorrow.
I've been called to do
it with
mates as soon as the stream starts.
Have fun though. Thank you Hasnain.
Hey Mad.
Thank you Mad47 for the $1. Can we expect
a one on one cage max between Jermis Conscious
and the chat telling him
to drown a woman in a toilet
in the next rumble?
What? Thank you.
Thank you GarfieldTheMondayKiller for the $1.
Jerm, I'm running away from smileydons.
They're a kind of ancient
tune tribe. Whoa, that was
close. Remember how
you made me your feline ambassador?
I mean, you
are. You're the only cat I think that
watches. Well, the
Goodwill tour turned sour real
quick. Just showed them Otto's
Big Adventure and they flipped out at me.
You've got no idea how much
it's been finding a place in this temple with
Wi-Fi. What the fuck?
I'm so lost. Thank you Garfield
for the $1.
What the fuck? Thank you
WinceRind for the $3.
I just finished fall quarter and
totally nailed my art history exam.
Yes, I'm paying money to boast about this.
Congratulations.
Hopefully you did well. Fall quarter.
So is the first semester
college and university
done?
Semesters are weird because
some of them start in September.
Some start in January, right?
Midterms, okay. I see.
Not yet. Okay.
But congratulations, dude. Thanks a lot for the $3.
Matty numbers.
Thanks for the $10 Matty numbers. When are
you going to finish your Hitman Absolution
Let's Play? I will
finish it after doing ghost mode.
Three more times.
And the answer to that
that means it's never happening.
But thank you for the $10, dude. Appreciate it.
Flub a gut thanks for the $1.
Hey Jeremy, you hear about
Nolan Cassidy. Poor sucker drowned himself
in his own vomit and put himself in the bathroom
wardrobe.
That's fucked up.
I can't believe that happened.
Thank you Teetles for the $2.40
No messages, just thank you, dude.
Anonymousgifter gave the $10
community subs
earlier. Thank you so much, dude.
That's a lot of community subs.
Hopefully people
Is there a way
to tell? I can see who got them, but
I wonder
I wonder what the actual algorithm here is.
Is it possible just to
get one if you've already been subscribed?
I wonder if there's a wait on it.
Somewhere in the back end.
So they just show up as regular subs. Okay, that's cool.
Well, congratulations to everybody and thank you
for even doing that, man.
Thanks for the $10. Going through a really hard time right now.
Thanks for the laughs. Hoping to sub soon.
Well, you've already paid
for that sub. Twice here.
So thank you for even
considering. Thanks a lot, man.
Smellyboy, thanks for the $1. Do you think you'd be able
to fight off a man your size
but with more ambition if he challenged you to
a fight? Yeah.
I would kick the shit out of myself.
Definitely.
Stopit gave $1.45
Thanks a lot, Stopit. You can tell when
it goes into sociopath mode when it becomes really quiet.
Coable, thanks
for the $5.
The smoke from the wildfire here in California
is so bad I can't leave the house.
So thank you for keeping me entertained while
I'm stuck inside.
Stay safe. Be careful.
I'm glad to be hanging out here.
Hopefully you don't see
anything too bad from that.
Take care. If you're in California, take care of yourselves,
guys. Much love to you.
It's Rusgara,
thanks for the $1.
Hey, Jerm's just dropping in and noticed that you pronounced my name.
It's Rusgara, but it's actually
Itrus...
Itrusgara.
Citrusgara.
Like citrus and gara. Anyway, I gotta go.
Oh, okay. Cool.
I get you. Thanks.
Thank you.
For the $1 and correcting my pronunciation.
Lazy Luke, thanks for the $1.
I am from the future and wanted to tell you that it was a good stream tomorrow.
Just don't eat that spider.
Gross. I gotta get out of here.
I gotta go.
E-Cookie, thanks for the $1. If you were an instrument,
what type of instrument would you be?
Probably like a cello.
Thanks, though, dude. Thank you, DivUSP for the $3.
Thanks a lot.
$3 from Div.
Talix gave $2. Thank you, Talix.
Kraiken recently started his
Ghost Commander series
where he sends four actors into a haunted house in order to
hunt a ghost.
At the same time, Chad is able to either help the actors by
voting on what they do or
help the ghost by voting on how it scares
the actors. It sounds a lot similar to the things you
wanted to do, a style
Twitch TV show with chat interaction.
Can we possibly expect a collab
in the future?
If it happens, it happens.
Yeah, there are plenty of things that I
want to do.
And if our paths cross, our paths
cross. Yeah, that's pretty
cool. We shall see.
But thanks for the $2, Talix.
That sounds really cool.
Hey, uh, Julis.
Julis. Julis.
Julis.
Thanks for the $1.
Hey, Jeremy, I've been watching you for a few months and I have to say you're one of a kind.
I usually don't subscribe to anyone but you.
Do you subscribe to anyone on Twitch? Do you have a favorite Twitch
streamer? By the way, so far you are my
favorite. Thank you for quality content. Thank you.
For the $1.
Do I have a favorite Twitch streamer?
Um...
Not necessarily.
I think that...
Talix, Vinny.
I think that the
friends and the people that I like that I know
on here, I would probably recommend their channels
because that's kind of how I found them in the
first place.
But I think I don't necessarily
have somebody that I watch
that I'm like, oh, that's my favorite streamer.
But yeah, I mean
I would say any of my friends that I know on the platform
or people that I would highly recommend.
He likes himself the most.
Oh yeah, yay.
Thank you, creepy ghost sales
for the $1. Hey, Jeremy, here's the last of my free
bits. My college campus is closed for the
rest of the week due to the horrendous air quality
in California. But hey,
that means I get some time to see the green
screen stream tomorrow. See you
then. Yeah, I mean
that's not...
I'm glad you're able to
participate and have fun on the streams
but also I'm sorry to hear
about you having to deal with that
shit. It sucks.
But just be careful.
We're all here. Glad to hang out.
Thank you for the $1, creepy ghost.
Afmeric gave
the five community subs right there right
now. Ten minutes ago, thanks a
lot. Thank you, extra cheesy for
the $1. How many vitamins does one regular assassination
give you?
Vitamins? I don't know. What does that mean?
Hey, double thanks for the $1. Hey
gamers, I fell asleep while watching the stream but don't
take it too personally. I haven't gotten
very much sleep today or the past week. Just kidding.
It's because Jerma doesn't know how to work save slots.
What?
Thank you, Dr. Clay
for the $1. I probably will not be able to watch
the green screen stream live sadly due to schedule
conflict. But I hope it goes well.
Also, the stream was a real hit, man. Take care. Thanks.
Ah, I got it. Nice.
Fudgean, awesome. Thanks for the $1. Hey
Jerma, I love the streams. I just wanted to ask you what your favorite
gorilla song is because they're my favorite band too.
Styla
That's probably my favorite song from
the band. I just like it.
There's a lot going on
in Styla. But yeah, there you go.
Thank you, Fudgean, awesome.
Thank you, Mad47 for the $1.
Nicest streamer, 2k18
Hey, is that me?
It's still surprising to have all your streams in my house
time zone. My home time zone.
Thank you for making your chat such a kind and welcome place
to everyone. Seriously.
You're a great influence. Thanks, man. Thank you.
I think this community is pretty good.
Except for when I have a meltdown
about multiplayer modes.
Fucking mode.
I just, I don't
nobody bring that up to me.
Then I command it. I demand it.
If I'm playing a game
like in a few days and all of a sudden I look over here
and it was like nice job in the Hitman multiplayer ghost
mode. I'm gonna
delete the chat. I'm just
kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding.
I'll put it into ghost mode.
Mario tennis all alone. No, that's not
even close to the level. Maybe it was.
How bad was Mario tennis in
regards to how mad I was at ghost mode?
Combine the two. Okay, if
Mario tennis was about
the same. Mario tennis was three
or two times as bad.
Mario tennis was way worse.
I love how that's the
that's like the barometer there.
Alright, is it
Mario tennis levels of fucking
meltdown? Mario tennis
you were upset for like two hours.
But like
let me just speak
my piece, right?
If I'm doing really bad
and I'm angry at losing
or something going wrong that I don't like
and I look over and chat and everyone's like oh my god
you're so stupid.
You're so bad. You're so dumb.
I'm just like I can't. I can't get it.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying? It's like a
perfect trifecta.
It's like all three of those things
have to be happening at the same time.
Fucking Mario tennis.
The curve bullshit.
I never thought I was going to think
about it and now I'm twice as mad.
I'm going to have a nightmare tonight
that I'm playing Mario tennis
and ghost mode at the same time.
We've sent him into a
rage spiral. Call animal control.
Hey, don't ever bring it up
to me. Don't ever bring it up.
Animal control.
These are three things never to bring up
on one of these streams. Never bring up animal control.
Mario tennis or ghost mode.
Or skate 3.
Or Karazhan.
What's wrong with the first? Nothing.
Alright, that's it.
I will see you guys all tomorrow.
Devakitty gave $1 here right there right now.
German Jax, German Jax 2, German Comet, German Polito.
Thank you.
Double D with $1 right here. Anyway, what's the
update on the spider crab situation?
How many frogs have you put into each room?
There's a frog in every room.
We're good.
They have plenty of water. But
thanks everybody for watching. Here come the credits
for all the new subs. And old ones.
So I will see you all tomorrow
for the green screen stream.
It should be interesting.
I can promise you that.
Somewhere around
between 4 and 7 PM
Eastern time is when the stream will probably start.
If not, I will absolutely
let you know. It will be happening
tomorrow though, that's for sure.
Good night everybody.
Thanks again for watching. Oh, my
Hitman. Okay, so my rating
for Hitman is
all the new areas were fun.
I think the first area and the
last area were the best ones in
regards to how interesting I thought they
were for me. You can't really
racetrack like a
cult mansion.
Those are pretty amazing.
Seems like there's a lot of
content. I would say
give the multiplayer a try
if you really are into
pain
and stuff
that's not fun at all.
I brought it up again. Alright, alright.
The multiplayer mode is
good. I just didn't understand
it at first and when I finally understood it
I lost my mind because I was getting
fucking beat and then
it spiraled out of control after I shot that security
guard. Everything was just fine.
It was fun and
things were going well and then I started to
hate it. You still don't understand
it.
Am I supposed to understand how every
single thing that works in the first game
mode, first time I ever play it?
Watching a YouTube briefing
video about how to play it?
You rage quit both times.
That doesn't mean I will...
I mean I'm never going to play it again, but if I did
I would take it
slower and
hit the deck.
What is this?
Fuck you.
You guys suck.
That's for Dark Souls.
What the fuck was that?
Somebody links me that clip like every
couple of months here or every like...
Is that what I was doing during... Okay.
What was I doing?
Was I doing that during the
ghost mode? I don't remember
doing any. I just remember being angry.
Anybody have a clip during ghost mode? Was that
my worst? Because I will definitely
watch an embarrassing
meltdown right here.
You were going, oh my god.
You walk up into a food stand.
The woman running it looks at you...
I can even see the thumbnail for that one.
Like...
I don't know what that is at this point.
I can see the thumbnail.
Everything in this whole area.
Oh my god.
Oh my god. Look at how far away
I am.
Fuck this weapon.
This is Dark Souls again.
You swing over every...
Only use that weapon.
Only for a fucking boss. What a worthless fucking item.
Jesus Christ.
Oh my god.
I mean, that was probably what I did.
That's probably the same...
Is that the same clip? That could have been...
If you placed that on top of the ghost footage,
would it be the same thing?
I'm just like clicking...
Oh, this is the worst ever.
Oh my god.
Who ever said that in chat?
That started that.
You are fucking hilarious.
The Mario Tennis Link is legit.
You mean it's probably a gnome?
Let me check it.
This really is the Mario Tennis Link.
How did you get this so quickly?
Look at that shit.
What the fuck is this?
This guy's throwing a wiffle ball across the court.
Oh my lord.
That's not even the worst part.
Here it is.
I think I have to stop playing.
I have to stop playing.
Alright, I'm getting out of here.
I gotta go.
I gotta get out of here.
Anyways, thanks everybody for watching.
See you tomorrow. Have a great one.
I gotta get out of here. I'm not gonna be kidding.
Take care everybody. See you soon.