Oh my goodness. My god. Okay, so let's see. Yeah, there's less than 200 to go.
You guys are fucking hilarious. Here we go. I was just doing a breathing exercise downstairs.
I went downstairs. I got some water. I was just going one, like two. Here we go. Welcome back.
That was by Tom McGowan, by the way. Coming up next, we've got Jax.
Jax. Yes, Jax. That's all it's called. It's John Wick. Me? I don't... Wick's here.
That's it. That's it. It was just getting started. It was just getting started. All right,
that's not even true. We got like 11,000. How many of these dances did I do? All right. That was...
No, we're back. Do it again. Oh, there it is. Looking good. Uh, Teeny Germa.
Nice, nice. Very nice balloon entrance. Absolutely perfection.
Me, me, me, me. GermaCraft. No. The series where I play Minecraft. This is going to be a single
player. Let's play. And when I said let's play, I used that term. Longing. Son, can you give me a
little pep in one place? Hey, what's going on? Please cut, John. What? Thanks. I love you, son.
I don't... When have I ever said this? I'm not sure how to react to this one. What's happening?
All right. So I woke up on the side of the road. That's it. All right. That was B versus Omega
Germa. It is another Undertale reference. Bring on the Undertale. Wait, is it going to go...
Here it comes. By the way, if you haven't played the anime Undertale,
it's uh... Just be careful because this is a spoiler for that show.
Holy shit. This is fucking terrifying. Holy fuck. My prized possession.
Germa eating ass certificate. I told you guys this before.
Red ass clap. Absolute perfection. Donald review manager of ass eating. No ifs,
ands, or buts. This right here is my ass eating certificate. Absolute perfection.
How did you... This is today. This is today. This is actually today. Oh, nice job. This is Jurassic
Park. Full movie.
Wait. Go back. I need to address this on stream again because listen. This picture. This is...
By the way, this is Mr. Slyne. Great fucking guy. Swell guy. Me and Slyne are the same size.
We're both 5'7 and a half. 5'8. I was leaning down in this picture. Me and Mr. Slyne are the
same size. I was pushing my fucking knees down and leaning forward. This picture is the reason
for the internet calling me a small guy. And I'm small. I am a small guy. But not that small. Me
and Mr. Slyne are the same size. Ask him. He's a great guy. He's a fucking swell guy, by the way.
Total Maniac tries to break down your door and the situation escalates extremely fast.
When do I try to break in? You think he would have attempted by now?
This is Jerma Invades Vinesauce, by the way. Vinny and I actually played... We didn't actually play it.
We tried to play Red Dead 2 online last night. Didn't work out. Vinny's a great guy. Vinesauce.
Check him out sometime. So you guys see what's happening with Jerma?
What's happening with Jerma? Because I don't know what the fuck is happening.
There's an Elvis impersonator. He's wearing a cloak. He's in the middle of the desert.
Can someone... Oh, yeah. Here's the picture. Can anyone figure out what's happening here?
I don't think he... You know. He doesn't look happy.
There it is. Hunt down the Compact Man. I don't know the... Whatever that was.
Here's the bee problem. This is just... There are no bees here.
There are no bees. Why does everybody use this? It doesn't have to be in every...
Alright. Speed Racer. Jerma. Jerma screenscreen stream.
All he talks about. All he seems capable of thinking about is automobile racing.
Racing's everything. From my family, it isn't just a sport. It's way more important than that.
It's like a religion. Are you ready to become a real race car driver? That's sign that contract.
He's just trying to scare you, son. What you do behind the wheel of a race car
has nothing to do with business. You walk away from me. You walk away from this deal.
No matter how well you drive, you won't win. You won't place. I guarantee you right now you
won't even finish the race. You think you can drive a car and change the world? It doesn't work
like that. Maybe not. Why is it so deep? The only thing I know how to do when I gotta do something.
It wasn't my idea. Oh no. It was his. Oh, it's me. It was mine.
He's going to be very good. Now he's going to be the best if they don't destroy him first.
That's pretty good. Pretty good. The Jervatrix has you.
You have to let it all go, Neo. Fear, doubt, and disbelief. Free your mind.
Hey, can you get your hand down here? That's like a 400 foot jump.
I guess I'll give it a try. No, no, don't worry about me.
So what if he makes it? Who's ever made the first jump? What if he does?
Oh, you got me. What does Jerva look like? You're tiny, tiny. It ain't the size of the
fucking ocean. It's how much motion is in that ocean. Like when I take a shower and I'm out of
the shower and I'm looking at myself in the full body mirror that I have and I just like
start fucking flexing and like squeezing my butt cheeks together. I go, damn, that guy's compact.
Describe what Jerva 95 looked like. Fucking tiny. Say tiny again. Say tiny again. I dare you.
I double dare you motherfucker. Say tiny one more goddamn time. Go on. He's balding. Does he look
like an old? Yeah. Stupidest thing ever. Oh, this is called shut it all off.
Turn it off. Are you in charge of this? Turn it off. Get to shut this off. Shut them all off.
Turn your lights and your house off too. Another shpeak. That's it.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of Journal Martial Arts.
This is the best part right here. I can't take it anymore.
This is my failure part. This is the best part.
Stop talking. This is the best part.
Nice.
This is terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
Nothing about this is good. Not one thing.
I don't know if you guys are actually really ready for this.
God, I hate this. I hate this.
Remember, if you hold shift, you don't fall off.
That's something I didn't know when I used to live stream this game.
What a god of a gamer, seriously.
Ready to go see our new home?
Alrighty then.
I was a little...
What?
I was a little s-word, guys.
I was a little jerk when I was younger.
This is the thing I'm talking about right here.
I've told you guys this before.
Absolute perfection.
Not very nice.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
This right here...
Absolute perfection.
I have to do it.
My brother got in a fight with this kid and I heard about it.
And so I had to bust off one day.
Alright, this is German green screen entry.
This is called this one.
Idiots.
Nobody use...what?
I don't understand what we just watched.
But here is a Jerem intro.
Jerem intro.
The Elder Scrolls V.
I'm driving the chariot here.
Finally awake.
You were trying to cross the border, right?
Walked right into that Imperial ambush.
Same as us.
And that thief over there.
Damn you Stormcloaks.
Skyrim was fine until you came along.
I like the use of two different Germans here.
About three.
Why?
To watch the soldiers.
Inside the house.
Why are we stopping?
Why do you think?
Why am I getting up?
I need a fucking advil.
This stream is killing me.
It better not be the raptor.
Please no.
Centuries. What do you see?
This is a completely normal video where nothing happens.
I hope they're right.
You mother fucker.
I'm going to be the sweatiest fucking tryhard in this server.
I'm going to kill you.
You're dead to me.
I'll tell you right now. I'm going to put my foot down.
It's over.
You got me.
What?
Oh.
German adventure.
I need to see.
There's less than 150 remaining.
Did you want to play for 10 with this weirdo?
Stick around.
I'm going to find a way out of here.
Why this pain?
I hate.
How are you guys doing?
Jojo.
Fucking bizarre adventure.
Shit.
Tardy piece of shit.
Star Platinum the world.
Oh shit.
By the way, if you watch animated sequences.
That I have more than one.
Like 22 minutes per sequence.
And this may be 10 to 12 per long sequence.
And they're animated.
This one you might have.
It might spoil your dinner.
Why are all the Jojo ones so well made?
They're so well done.
I can't skip them.
They're so well made.
This is show business.
I don't even know what.
German watches made in abyss.
Okay.
Spoilers.
This actually says the word spoiler.
Another animated sequence.
Spoiler for this.
I don't know what this means.
But this is a spoiler.
This is by far.
This is the best part right here.
This is my favorite part.
This is the best part.
What is this a spoiler for?
I don't know what this is a spoiler for.
It's just a spoiler for a show.
If you watch television.
Just be careful.
This is just a spoiler for a TV show.
It's just me watching a TV show spoiler.
Only 140 more.
This is so funny.
Oh wow.
I'm so happy.
I love the TV show.
up with me here here's the subscribe button and if you like a content you want to subscribe
and potentially lose i'm gonna have to take a week off after this because we don't do that anymore
you can click a bell bell's over here by the way click that bell right there and then click
another couple of buttons and then maybe you'll be able to see the content you subscribe to
this is your space let's get this this is it right here world
oh
not another t-pose it's too small small please ed it's compact
you got me with that one good work lord compact wedding it's a compact wedding
oh my goodness okay can we just skip ahead to the i-do
if you ever take track how about that this is the end
wait wait hey wait a minute listen to me look you love this woman don't you yes
you want to hold her yes please yes then you got to got to try a little tenderness
the chicks love that romantic crap oh hey cut it out when does this guy say the line
we gotta check it out and this is just we're just watching the end of trek
this is just copyright infringement i'm gonna lose everything i need to talk to you oh now you
want to talk well it's a little late for that so if you'll excuse me but you can't marry him
i don't want to watch the end of shrek on my stream okay dude i don't even know are you all
right dude i don't even know that's star i don't know this is this is called germanetta
oh culture attack smoke brad heaven the interview
please repeat this one forever
every day my life that was great thanks for that one here comes on something of a scientist myself
i hear you by the scientist what i can't even hear it what all right it's called germa sans
another undertale or delta rune reference coming up shortly
oh
sorry old lady this is why i never make promises
you it's time for you to pay
i'm five eight not five six get it right
right
you better be ready here it comes
uh
all right count it how many world explosions has that been from rat movie that's at least eight
good use of the explosion if you haven't seen rat movie two or rat movie one uh mystery divine
treasure if you've been to animated movies that are less than eight minutes long i recommend you
don't watch it but if you do just there's a spoiler here the aliens did it so wow hey it's
me germa and you're watching the disney channel germa kills the younglings oh great this could only
go well this one can only go well i just did this all right that's it we're moving away from star
one germa there are too many of them what are we going to do i'll be drinking toilet water
you'll be rage quitting in a heartbeat coding this will be easy
my training will see me through oh no what is soccer juice i run a delivery service for pain
don't forget about me the newest turtle socrates i may be small but i sure got lots of power
out
i need a second fucking t-pose okay there's the brand new teenage made ninja turtle fighter pack
three what a gamer what a god of a gamer seriously where is this what where am i supposed to be
germa a star wars story
yo steady like a big playground when suddenly batman burst from the shade
and hit godzilla with a bat grenade godzilla got pissed and began to attack
but didn't expect to be blocked by shack he proceeded to open up a can of shack
when eric carter came out of the blue and he started beating up shakilo kneel then they both
got flattened by the bat mobile don't make it back to the bat cave abraham lincoln popped out
of his grave and took a naked 47 out from under his hat blew batman away with a rat at that chat but
he ran out of this crime can you save the day this is the ultimate showdown a whole new destiny
guys and explosions oh there's the raptor
are you serious
stole it and he shot and he missed and jackie chan deflected it with his fist and he jumped in
lethal league drama mod version 2 plus download what is it actual mod actual actual mod here
actual download get ready no fucking way play ball are you kidding me holy shit oh my fucking god
this is this is fucking incredible is this real there's your t-pose
i actually like 10 out of 10 what's the special that's the coolest thing ever this is the coolest
thing ever i'm a reskin of what characters because that's pretty damn cool
of the raptors
well that was uh thanks everybody that was one of the coolest fucking things ever
germa and what hollywood wait hold on germa and what hollywood has mostly become in the
animation industry and whatever that means it's very compressed video turn it up turn it up
fucking loud i saved the world right here i just saved the world that was too loud for me
what's next spot the dinosaur here we're playing spot the dinosaur you need to really look and
find them they're hidden all over the place check it out over there to the right you might be able
to find one garfield cart coming up next i'm not even facing the right way it's the wrong direction
that's it no not my fucking old intro not the old intro don't pull one of those on me here
what the hell is this it's from a movie or a tv show
i i think that was halloween
that was fucking great quality that was high quality man of spiel that's the first thing i say
another man oh first of all hold on a minute this is a second man of steel trailer
this is two second here we go man of cement of steel if i look at the ceiling i go yo
merry christmas and then i diary every single morning good shoe tie good use always has to be
a t-pose is really important is that it is there more that's it beanbag sonic tribute
you get fucking garfield out of here you're trying to get me sued on the left why is
what is this what's going why is Thanos twerking where did you get this did you make this
why is this here german watches tv yeah you're trying to get me in trouble here
two garfields in a row really this is my favorite part this is the best part
just stop talking this is the best part that would even fucking this is terrible absolutely
terrible nothing about this is good not one thing god i hate this i hate this this is terrible
no this is your 45th jojo reference what's next what a gamer that's not even me playing god of
a gamer seriously i got this that's not even me playing do you think i can reach germa fucks up
an alternate time there was donkey and diddy kong hold on wait oh i got this is a mouthful
an alternate timeline is created where germa replaces banjo and kazooie for some reason
then diddy and dixie dixie and kitty mario and yoshi okay okay you'll get the point
so what's the big deal well listen up because there's a new dynamic duo from the creators of
donkey kong country and goldeneye that's ready to kick some serious excitement into nintendo 64
the coolest head banging beat busting sky flying rock hop and egg shooting tag team and duo
in a new game with so many thrills chills spills and splats you won't be able to put it down
peter no not another peter oh peter i'm sorry i'm a scientist myself not another peter peter
you're a scientist i'm something of a scientist myself i read all your research on nanotechnology
really brilliant i find myself be something of a scientist myself what i live with my aunt and
uncle yeah peter i hear you fight the scientist well i'm something of a scientist myself
get that in a fucking petri dish mother fucker
oh we already saw one of these this one has music
that's it hey it's me jerma from downtown of center sports you're watching the disney channel
wait have you ever seen harry potter in the deathly hellos harry there's a potential
death here that you don't want to be spoiled of just be aware of that
do you see my shoe stupid girl from this day forth put your faith in me
i i i i i i don't know where it is i have no idea what my other shoe is
stupid
my trusty current player i slash those buddies like nobody's business
check me out you'll see a little bit of footage right here
too many things in that one you didn't even key out the green cloak it didn't work oh man
my god okay jerma does a filthy act at a fair and reasonable price it's probably a spoiler for
jojo's funny land whatever it is quick haggard get under dirty d's done dirt cheap
doja hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa craft the series where i play
minecraft this is going to be a single man you got me partner knock knock who's there
aren't you glad i didn't say banana put this guy in a body bag he's dead intense and tough
so unbelievable let me just say from the bottom of my thank you for all of your support
and for all of your wonderful contributions i must say it's been quite a year quite a year in fact
that i've got two more games to announce that's right two more games with the most ingenuity
and the highest caliber of skill that any of our developers have ever done
it is my pleasure to announce our latest title what the hell was that what was that
what video game was that all right here's talking streamers in a lifetime
all right add that to the list of uh streamers that get permanently banned from the platform
okay and here we go turbo drifts into the void
oddly peaceful this one is there i go that's it i think that's the end of the video this is don't
give in i'm not giving into the dab it's not gonna no no no no turn it up turn it up i'm not
turn it up
thank god he saved me dab.exe has stopped working compact germa getting chased by wasps
i see him down there roger that taking target out god what the fuck really really dude really
oh jesus oh no no please oh my god
no i have to see it again i have to see it again
suck
hi i'm germa985 and his new channel is germa battle of the millennia what is with his face
here we go
with my hair this battle is about to explode fight nice perfect the racers get better you can
stick frags like these sticks that was fucking awesome surrounds us penetrates us it binds the
galaxy together i thought that was me making noises for a second no that's just r2d2
now let's see if we can't figure out what you are my little friend where you come from
what was that
is
germa the creeper can you see i'm spying on myself playing micro
oh
that's fucked up look
put whatever character of green screen please god
okay what have you done
i can't fuck him no he's too good there he goes
no that's it that's gonna be it that's it the winner of the 2008 wait if you haven't seen a
television before if you've ever had a tv before there's a television spoiler here at the end of
this video team rumble is the green screen he's like number one like 11 or 12 anchored by his
victory germa made a new rumble but a green screen can't win let me know what happened all right come
on here comes the green screen green screen stuck on the rope fuck you this is very key
what no like microsoft now you microsoft right now
yes of course you gotta get an ass zoom in as long as editors talking about she was watching
god oh what a reversal i come no no reversal all he needed was it was that going to be enough
one two three super jacks nice job super jacks
hey can you give me a hand down here that's a 400 foot jump i guess i'll give it a try
no no don't worry about me two three three all right great uh yo germbo this i'm doing a dark
souls thing this is out of context that's it man terrified of apples attempts to conquer his fear
i can't do it i can't do it i can't do it this is very creative
what that's it by the way that's a tomato on the right that's not even an apple that's a tomato
of course i explode germa goes to the movies
that's my car this is the best part right here this is my favorite part
shush this is the best part
absolutely terrible
be quiet nothing about this is good not one thing
now this is show business
wow what an annoying fucking break what what the fuck is that
close
oh wait wait what a fucking like megalomaniac
and turn this off and turn the lights in your house off too
okay we are at we are at less than 100 i believe videos remaining i just need a minute here
less than 100 we're almost there that that last one was fucking hysterical they've all been
fucking great but my goodness okay let's go back to it this is called germa this isn't real
oh no we didn't know what is this suggest but by that point we didn't want to know
jeremy elbertson earlier this year was tried for the infamous father christmas killings
after the overwhelming evidence supported by the polygraph test as well as the incident that
transpired he was sent to court to finalize the guilty verdict however during the hearing
his confession brought to light information that changed everything he said if you're good
at something never do it for free after that it was clear this man was an insane person
and so he was sent to an asylum for psychiatric evaluation we discovered that he was in his own
little world talking to an imaginary audience we tried to make contact but he just kept spouting
nonsense he kept saying presto majesto over and over he spoke in pure binary
list goes on no progress was made there was only one instance where he stopped talking to himself
actually responded to us during one of our interviews he told us this shuck prepared is
he is we're still trying to decide it's the best chef best celebrity chef ever
it's 80 and that's where we wake up the germa raptor exhibit wow wow this is what it looks
like up close what the fuck is that what is that supposed to be what is that supposed to be
absolute perfection no ifs ands or buts what is that this right here is absolute perfection
that's a 3d render what this halloween testing one two three we're on we're here to investigate
a patient that killed three innocent teenagers on a halloween and now that was good he was
shot by his own psychiatrist and taken into custody that night and spent the last 40 years
in captivity do you know that i pray every night that he would escape
what the hell did you do that for so i can kill him
uh
the bus crashed mom what bus crashed michael escaped i got good dental yeah i get i get
who's waiting for this night who's waiting for me i waited for him
closet door surprise
the creativity involved is just mind-boggling this is called bad japple this is an apple
commercial this is those dancing apple commercials right the ipod it's gonna say ipod at the very
end ipod this is a jojo reference oh okay not a jojo reference okay i thought it was a jojo
a lot of work went into this one this one is very well made
obligatory this looks really stupid what i mean first person just behind you
and it looks like it looks like one of those old 80s movies where the guy you're in front of
like a green screen and you're like apparently driving right now oh wow look out there this
looks really great on my fucking green screen oh i get it i get it that's that's a that's a
meta joke i was okay i was wondering what the hell was going on there makes sense good job
good work germa does nvm socrates with my trusty curved blade i slash those putties like nobody's
business putties that's power rangers right did i get that wrong all right that's it here comes
the weather you know typically i i bring you the weather on a daily basis at six a.m six a.m in the
morning with diane carolyn rick uh but today i want to show you something different besides the
fact that first be aware we are going to have some snow over here in the colorado rockies come
through here down into the southern part of colorado but forget that i want to show you something
that i care about something that i want to show that i haven't been having i had no opportunity
to do until now that's me on my fishing trip that's me and my son i just wanted to show
and back to the weather uh we do have let me set some cold around who cares about this
america go out and live your lives don't worry about the weather you just go outside and sniff
you'll be just fine it's gonna be cold some days it's gonna be hot some days
it's just just go out there go out there what the fuck
what is the fred movie that's my car
this is the best part right here i don't i skip it
i this is terrible absolutely terrible but like an angel who isn't nothing not one thing
until she dies god i hate this this is germa dark soul that's it that's it that's the end
i can't skip it this is the thing this is the context here hold on just wait shut up everybody
shut up everybody shut up for a second this context behind this this is i somebody i had the back in
on youtube back on youtube there was a joke where i was gonna get in a bathtub and make like a duck
face and this is not i don't do this i'll think saturday i don't think this is cool there's a lot
of new people here this was a bet i was a bet that i would get in the bathtub and do this and it was
a star that took the photo and then uploaded it and i didn't want them to but just but those
are that televisions spoiler for the uh four years ago germa 95 channel just in case you were
curious i want to make sure there's no those are reverse spoilers here okay told you guys absolute
perfection no ifs ands or buts this right here is absolute perfection i can't skip it i'm not
allowed to i think we're getting to the home stretch here germa tours what is this
to do that a little shortcut this is disney ride this is a disneyland ride
here's another raptor coming up germtastic park hey germa freeze
so
it's a compact streamer
time
i can't even respond what what is this is this is a just turn off your screen just
delete your computer throw it out the window i'm not gonna i
can a lonely sunday drive careful
fucking car i don't matches with the wheel somehow that's a bad streamer
okay according to germa the hamburger helper is perfection hamburger helper i've told you guys
this before absolute perfection i don't know what that's a hamburger helper's face
this right here is absolute perfection that's not the hamburger helper's face is it no it's not
this germa isolation i guess you need to explore in this game there was a crash oh no
i need to investigate the mystery of the crash which is what i plan on doing let's go ahead and
go oh fuck that's him can i get away without him seeing that's the main thing that's got to be
here that no no he's right behind me he's right behind me oh my god oh my god oh my god
if i can make it up these stairs please it's an alien it's a fucking alien hey where is he
where'd he go how did i make the original uh a lot of time this is an awful video apparently
so
why are they always purple
you should have gone ahead i'm gonna do with two hands and everyone dies
wait wait wait wait wait that means me too no wait wait wait wait no that means me
three count it again there it is again this is the earth exploding
counting that's like 12 all right here comes why did i make this the second this is uh
parappa the rapper
that's referential right there
that was good
i don't understand
i don't know what this is from a tv show i think
look what i'm doing zoom in closer do you understand you understand like what look look at
my knees i'm bending forward complete look at these bent knees look at my arm my arm doesn't
come down to my shins guys are you kidding me do you understand what's happening here
did you really think that my left arm is a foot off the ground do you really think that look at
the ground you think that my hand comes down like a fucking gorilla good use of that say goodbye
to the fucking vaughn the vaughn is gone vaughn was deleted probably an hour ago grandma vaughn
versus socrates
actually made socrates it's so loud was it that loud when we taped it it was that loud
shitty boss from like an animal
gameplay damn you damn you
i have um these spaghettios micros um i'm gonna microwave these and i'm going to eat them
oh my god wish me luck okay it's nuclear hot it's got a soupy consistency like this is not
what pasta is supposed to be like it's supposed to be like 75 percent pasta and like 25 percent sauce
maybe more than that maybe more sauce but this is like soup and it's it's not it's not appetizing
it does not look appetizing don't eat me so um i'm afraid and it's it's really hot
and i don't i don't like the implications of this no no no no please here goes
i made vinny don't fuck yourself no germa falls out his window
that's right it's bold mom i see it
wow why is it taking so long
what is that
shit it worked well if two in the hand is worth one in the bush looks like this guy went shush
shush finally it took it only took it only took hold on it only took 284 videos before somebody
decided to do the Horatio and here comes another sans video i hope you're ready for this one
before i died i love it is number one i've never said that before should be burning in hell
all right this one's pretty good
oh that's it uh bloodborne boss fight uh it's my favorite character in the game by the way
good choice of clip called the gas coin is my favorite character in blood one you caught on
it doesn't have a gun why do i have a gun
no don't turn into the raptor he's got
whatever the raptor that was fucking good let's say onion guy onion man what a god seriously uh
what i don't understand did you kill him
okay this is so creepy
really good fucking dance all right derma stuck in a vent
look there's a bird dude it knows what's good i'm telling you i just heard it inside
nice all right that's it we're moving away from star war i'm done with star war that was good
that was really good
2.0.0 here we go whoa i love how the keys
radically change it's amazing fascinating two hours later well
i do got a pretty sweet house way better than your minecraft house dude another jim carrey walk oh
god do i eat ass what are you talking about that's your question that's it you rubbed the
fucking lamp you rubbed the lamp and that's what you want to ask the genie oh great all-powerful
genie please come out with the come out oh no what is your wish do you eat ass of course i do
sucked back in
took this long to get neon genesis evangelion evangelion evangelion how do you pronounce it
evangelion
that was pretty good that was pretty damn good yeah thank you for making
germa the worm this is a this is a this is a penis thing
there was so much going on in this i don't even know what to say there was so much going on
germa ascend
that's like a 400 foot jump i guess i'll give it a try no no don't worry about me two three
nice where do i ascend to what a gamer okay this ends with the earth blowing up star wars
the earth better not explode in this one that'd make it like 13 or 14 right what the hell what
happened
coming back to earth apparently
you don't need to know what i had for breakfast this morning all right just let's talk about the
deal it's a different rat movie ending wasn't there a guy that was just right here
like 10 birds coming down what's this guy doing here super jacks
dragon ball z why is it the dog if you don't if you've never had an ice cream before
just be aware that like this is good this is good this is a freeze there's a freeze in here and
you're gonna get brain freeze if you've eaten ice cream don't fucking watch this video i'm gonna
wake up tomorrow my mailbox is gonna be full with dmca claims i'm gonna get brought to court
by like 48 different companies i don't i don't get this
super saiyan here we go we're just watching dragon ball z
that and that's the whole you made the whole video the whole video was made to do that that's
what the entire video was made to do too many germs there's too many there's too many there's
too many that was fucking great here comes another quest i thought a planet what's that planet
let's see the sneakers why do you have the disney channel opening here
oh what what a gamer i agree oh look at that i found a bicycle can you believe it
what a god of a gamer seriously what happened i got the answer absolute perfection
no ifs ands or buts i'll see you
oh this right here is absolute perfection
are you in charge of this turn it up here's what i have to say about this
see this bullshit get out of here we're all jeremy derma strep parade
hahaha this back man oh garfield why is garfield in there what's that oh look at fireman
it's time for you to pay
you're going down um ers in here you know what i mean s and then some other letters and then ers
whatever
why am i here why am i in this
oh it's the ender dragon
i don't know what happened does the ender dragon pick you up
uh peter man let's take a look hold on important guys just want to let you know we have about
we have about 50 videos left until it's done 50 this is called norman osborne introduce my
father norman osborne great honor to meet you sir you're a scientist i'm something to the
scientist myself frozen back there i read all your research on nanotechnology really brilliant
yes i i wrote a paper on it they both did the same they both have the same idea
all right uh let's take one final break before we get the last 40 or 50 here final break of the
evening see you real soon howdy so uh i will see you guys well i'm not leaving yet but
when this stream ends i'll see you guys on wednesday nothing tomorrow or tuesday gotta get
some shit done around the house end of the stream voice not even close we have 50 more submissions
man are you kidding me we're not leaving yet just wanna make sure you know here we go uh world of
germa germa movie night this is a take on the world of light trailer from smash brothers why what
and don't forget about me newest turtle socrates
that's my character so he gets to live are we gonna get the lyrics here
falling star going through the sky through
oh two one power chicken
different is the b part two apparently this is part two whoever wins this one v one duel
eats the most pizza and i think it's me not anymore
it's joe joe's fucking bizarre adventures
money
life is pain i hate
it's over did i kill him
ah did i just i think i just killed this guy
well you know what they say they do say that you're right this is fucking awful
that was the joke this is fucking terrible this is the worst one no no this is terrible
am i sim here comes the reveal trailer for me coffee cheetos and of course the chicken
up in smoke
gonna be one of the most professional athletes you've ever seen in this game
nice
oh
super smash brothers oh no from bethesda game studios no no no no no no todd todd get off no
i don't want to hit fucking todd howard's feet by the way how we doing what is this
i'm getting the fuck off get my guy right there it's like a break
this video is going to give me a nosebleed
oh
there's more
holy shit this is too many clips thank god this is terrible
absolutely terrible rendering this it would take you probably three days to render that
god i hate this i hate this this is terrible can somebody edit this edit what so i think the
thing about um i think eating going on a diet it's not a bad idea it's oh shit hold on wait
oh shit there's a button to be in here
okay he landed smoke you see that look at these pog champs oh that's some dumb shit yeah
that was some pretty dumb shit germa is hitman
this is well made hey gamers
oh fuck you oh i'm taking his disguise that's very clever oh
of course fortress hornets there's a hornet's nest in my wall in my kitchen in the light outside
there's a nest you're my guy right there's so many of these
i don't want to be the number one streamer on twitch it's it was a dream come true
i do got a pretty sweet house way better than your minecraft house dude
what a gamer what a god of a gamer it's an ant sim
oh open smoke it was an ant simulator
hold on a second here wait there's more i streamed that game for like 25 minutes
that game was fucking awful so he just left that here it's still good that just made me hungry
i want those so bad right now i would pay a hundred bucks for a box of cheeses right now
attack of the germs
that's good
this must be attack on titan look it's sweaty i know i'm so fucking sweaty let me just say
from the bottom of my heart thank you for all of your support and for it's been quite a year
quite a year in fact that i've got two more games to announce
the man from
just checking to see how much is left boston okay we are uh usually next to roosterteeth
go to because we're good friends with them so we like to set it up that we're always next
to roosterteeth so a kid comes up and he has a poster for roosterteeth's new project ruby
but i signed the poster the kid comes up he's like oh and this kid he's about this tall
that's that's generous he's about hey here's the ground the kid is about this big he's about this
wide he's wearing a uh a sweater whatever and and he's like hey he talks with a thick boston accent
let me ask you guys something if you're bernie let me hear you do the voice i walk up to this
kid who may or may not murder me and get away with it because he's a child uh i walk up to him and i
go all right oh you want bernie's voice yeah let me hold on
if you're bernie and i got a message for you to take back to austin with you this is where roosterteeth
is from austin texas you tell gavin that british fuck he doesn't deserve the achievement from the
minecraft video hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of i have no idea what that was
germacraft that's it derma dances till he's dead is this one big dance energy somebody said
that's enough for tonight there's only like 35 more that's enough for tonight
all right man like that was that's fucking good for now right
i have to pause it because somebody said i reached my limit a half an hour ago now this is show business
this is really good
what a gamer what a god of a gamer seriously germa land saga with an animated television show
oh
i've watched more anime intros than i think i ever have in my whole life tonight and yeah there's
another purple jeremy what's the name of this anime um i don't know super mario 64 bowser hallway
that's not the name of the anime that's all i could think of
oh no viewers should have all that nobody should have all this power
germa i have work in the morning it's almost done this feels like the end well sorry to say
but you've got about 27 more videos to watch oh here's another star wars one there are two
bantas down there but i don't see any wait a second they're sand people all right i can see
one of them now
in a perfect world men like me would not exist
this is not a bad world i mean it's so dark here honey honey no dude no no
driver what the fuck wait hold on a second hold on was that that was just that was just maila
what the fuck was that all right this is called germa's house story plus mining in this one this
germa crap video truck truck made that video that's fucking hilarious well here we go
i got it right there you're my guy right there where's my guy there he is right there
there's my guy what one too many cooks too many this is called germ germa mom that was the baby
okay i see egg give me all your eggs what are you talking about don't have any eggs
you've been no choice prepare to die germasaurus versus floorball germa well this is fucking
incredibly well made throw the ball that's it baseball bat germa church of his journal
thanos journal one is thanos that's it it's over you all right men let's go let's get
him let's go let's get him let's go let's get him let's get oh yeah man let's fuck him up shut up
get that door open yeah man i'm gonna kick that all god damn it i gotta do everything myself
all right wait somebody just made a 3d this is 3d movie maker come on man just let us go home
half the bar is dead and it's been five hours we have no safe we have no money we burned it
all last week please man just let us go home holy shit you actually put this together hostages
open fire oh fuck oh shit oh god is it gonna end with the world exploding i wonder
i jimma the police are all dead you can walk away free now oh neo genesis evangelion what
is that it so last night oh god one of these in las vegas we were walking in together and i i
noticed him at the corner of the eye and i turned and said oh cool it's great to meet you i love
your streams so sorry i won't interrupt you anymore i just wanted to say i appreciate you
he turns around to me frown on his face and he says oh you don't want to interrupt me
like you're doing now fucking god this is coffee pasta in look him in the eyes in what real life
huh huh he says before just sneering at me his hand was opening and shutting in my face it was
it's kind of scary to turn around to finish my shopping i don't want to interrupt him anymore
he's clearly angry i hear him laughing behind me it's really just the nail in the coffin for me
so i finished my shopping and i didn't expect to see him again but there he is he's walking
past the registers and he's just attempting to leave with all his items in his hands
he hadn't paid for any of the lady at the register said sir you need to pay for those that's 40
dr peppers you're gonna have to pay for that he tried to ignore he tried to act like she wasn't
there but he clearly heard her and eventually he came back to the register she started scanning
and she decided to pick one up and scan it just over and over instead of taking them all out of
his arms he said no wait wait i'm gonna need to make you scan each one individually to negate
the electrical interference these were his words exactly i didn't know what he meant he he turned
i can't fucking believe it somebody made this but what what's electrical interference and what's it
have to do with dr pepper that's just what i gotta know anyways he got it all scanned up and loaded
it into one bag i don't know he fit it all but i expected him to take off in a car he didn't god
rode away on a razor scooter guess times aren't so good for him the fellow mafia watched tv last
night confusing science i will say small people can jump double in air
it's from a hat in time i saw this makes mafia uncomfortable with body must go work out
i thought that was the end of the video i was like what the fuck
uh i guess i'll give it a try no no don't worry about me
i haven't even played this game yeah here comes oh by the way in case you didn't know there's
another animated cartoon spoiler coming up here just in case you were curious animated spoiler
and away we go fold metal alchemist you haven't seen it don't just fucking
run away from your screen run just run feet oh my fucking god oh my god it's time for you to pay
it
well that's the end of that one this is called germa ween
it's michael meyers again a lot of michael meyers a lot of halloween parodies here
what the fuck
wow halloween spoiler oh
as a matter of fact it was jesus christ i've died in so many of these videos i yeah i really have
what is this not a big deal
somebody why did you take this one there's this
what let's put cigarettes out on my dead i don't know what i'm saying here i have no idea
it's another harry potter one stupid boy stupid boy please get out of here well i must say i'd hope
for better and who might you be a man quick get on him see all right this time i'm actually
disappearing well never i'm sure we can find a place for you in our rank have i to say something
well never i'm sure we'd all be fascinated to hear what you have to say yeah that's it okay
here comes the wasp beatdown here comes another jojo reference jojo's bizarre adventure
oh come on man what the fuck was that 2018 the germa we all know and love was lost
or on that fateful night what is this fucking voice acting erupting with such force that it
shattered space and time into tiny fragments a germa in each one of them one germa retrieved
the cork and continues dreaming another this is his story what i got you i scared you a little
spring this is fucking insane wait a minute look at me in this
so this is the virtual world
my pc
we recorded streams all right fine fine i'm gonna rewind
flanker turns around and waves to you please join me
okay council main hall okay here we go here we go inside oh he's going it goes his head out
i gotta go i gotta go i see you are a coward unlike when we last met so be it i owe nothing
to any coward you owe me everything fuck you all right that was fucking awesome if it's
201 oh that was actually fucking crazy on september 30 this the voice acting is just was
that was i believe that was its time for slime slime time here we go bring it back so this is
uh germa 19 germa 980 9 1980 or 980 germa i gotta go to work in five hours there's only like 10 more
and by 10 more i mean like 25 and by 25 i mean like 21 it's almost 1 a.m eastern this they're
too fun i have to keep playing them that's pretty good too
what is this intro from what a great time to be alive hotline miami there's the jojo's was
our adventure snap dance the gta5 clip it i don't suppose they uh told you anything in denver about
the tragedy we had up here during the winter of 1970 a heart of man named charles grady is
the winter caretakers from what i've been told i mean he seemed like a completely normal individual
fucking jesus but at some point during the winter he must have suffered some kind of a complete
mental breakdown he ran amok killed his family i'm something of a scientist myself
that's right
proof presents
sure i do it'll be lots of fun the only thing that can get a bit trying up here during the winter is
a tremendous sense of isolation is there something bad here i fear you will have to deal with this
matter in the harshest possible way i'm gonna kill you
this is i've got a currency thing you know who knows what was that clip it
oh my fucking jesus look who's here we are so glad you're here blue and i were just about to
hello it's a bug why am i fighting blue and steve
i don't want to fight you man what are you why would i do why would you make me punch the dog
yeah those shapes go together to make the clue the moon starts with a big curve that's like part
of a circle then a smaller curve that goes back to the start there a moon hey that was our second
clue okay so we have a peanut shell bed and the moon what could paprika's favorite treasure be
that has a bed and the moon what the fuck are we watching is this an actual game
did you see that blue just skidooed right into that poster come on let's go
if you know why am i here the one that is her greatest pleasure i will give you the first key
my minecraft house is better it is a very special key hey here comes f germa gx we are actually
getting down to like the final 15 or 10 or so if you're curious what's with the audio on this one
only only like 10 to 20 more minutes oh whoa that car song this one has been used so often
and again when i sing a car song i've been um i've been driving for like probably
a couple years now i've been driving for lift this is the lift thing
what am i driving into oh shit sorry yeah it's a great place uh derma's killer instinct here
come the skeletons hey got no hell don't scream at me it's scary oh baby who wants some of this
there we go i love the fighting game ones the amount of you don't understand the amount
of effort that takes to do this it takes so much time to put this together it really does
did i kill him did i just i think i just killed this guy back nice perfect
taunt cancelled what's next oh that's fucking loud
oh god you figured somebody was gonna do this one
oh
here's germa bullet hell this is another mod this is actually a real game yeah this shit is
actually downloadable and actually playable three different characters uh do you want to how i know
that would you like to know how i know that well that's because uh i have the game right here
here's the bullet hell i couldn't fucking believe this was real so we're gonna be uh let's just do
his regular germa let's play a couple of rounds here this is gonna fucking hurt so it's a bullet
hell dodge game i'm actually playing right now absolutely terrible i lost seven seconds
nothing about this is good not one thing this shit is real somebody made this game somebody put the
time into making this oh more than 10 seconds come on come on more than five seconds 25 seconds
come on made it watch oh okay i'm fine i'm good i'm good i'm good 20 seconds that's pretty good
yes that's it i did it germa please finish i have an exam i had to play this for at least
fucking 30 seconds uh i gotta i want to get a link to that because that's uh the mod as well
that's fucking insane that somebody did that hey i just want to i need a link to this here's the
game oh that's not the game hold on copy uh i need to copy this like this shit is fucking ridiculous
seriously well done well fucking done i have to play this for an hour no no we got we got like
how many more videos we got oh let's see we are down to the last 60 i'm just kidding let's go
germa fortress that's it for this one this is called mugen another harry and listen listen there's
another mod somebody put me into mugen apparently look at this shit
i can't even comprehend how much work you guys put into some of these seriously
you're gonna be insulting bet
i don't even know how yeah there's a ninja turtle in the answer
oh
this is so good and i got a fireman special move you kidding me
i wonder where i'll be in the meta so fucking awesome p tier what is p tier
what does p tier mean almost all of his crouch moves really the entire fighter is
is a joke character no i'm gonna be at least like in the top 100 so shout out to that dude
that said put fireman as projectile that's all i got well that was fucking awesome he's broken
as fuck and i'm terrible at fighting games but i intend to work more on it well that's
fucking amazing thank you teleportation technique unleashed germa's a hudson
great honor to meet you sir i hear you by the scientist
well i read all your research on nanotechnology really brilliant
yes i wrote a paper on it holy shit get that in a fucking petri dish motherfucker
yeah what just broke it doesn't seem so bad another jedi
oh shit i'm gonna die
are you fucking serious
this is brainwashing is what somebody said this is brainwashing what that's a gun
why is that a gun oh my god that was awesome oh no
today we have a very special guest with us what's your favorite fortnight dance
should i just did i just did a fortnight dance streamer sucks god germa's freaking out
these are all chatters apparently i really am that good aren't i oh my life oh this is actually
my life first try by the way did a first try no i can do it i can do it i can do it i can
get the fuck out of here beat him you can't take that from me
this is a germa sighting i don't get it
what is why is this infinity war i can't handle it anymore let's go
another incredibly well-made presentation is another real game
the pretend civilian i love it holy fuck watch out purple germa is a purple
you were shooting the barrels you gotta shoot the barrels man you should have gone ahead oh god
hello ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa craft the series where i play
germa watches ladies and gentlemen welcome to episode one of germa craft
didn't we just see this i thought we just watched this one please we saw this one
god fucking god terrible put a crossover it's called kung fu chroma key hurry up he lost a lot
of blood t posing in the background well made well made there's not very many more left fireman
versus germa this is really well made
is this this is joe there's another joe joe joe joe no it's not another joe joe thing right
well it's really good germa meets and kills mega leg
all right hold on oh i need to see i need to see oh ladies and gentlemen let me tell you
we are down to the final 11 there's only i think 11 to 12 left we're almost done completely
we've watched almost 400 fucking videos there's still a few more strapping another germa rector
germa fights his clone jeremy elbison was just your normal everyday scientist
until he used his 200 iq genius brain and created a perfect clone
yeah and they were the best of friends and nothing lasts forever his clone became corrupted
fuck is that i don't know to defeat this clone he left the train and become
jacks yeet i've never said yeet before in my whole life germa fights his clone or some shit the movie
that's it it's is canceled though the show is canceled super germa odyssey
hey can you get your hand down here that's like a 400 foot jump
uh i guess i'll give it a try no no don't worry about me two three three
all right who is this uh big germa visits zoltar the movie big with tom hanks
that's terrifying it's an old movie now what's it say zoltar says make your wish i want to be big
what a god of a gamer seriously all right your wish is granted all right so now i have a little
bit longer legs just a little bit though turn it off get the shutters off shut them all off
turn your lights and your cuffs off too plug oh here comes the muffin show featuring very special
guest me seven remain it's time to play the music it's time to light the light it's time to get me
started why don't you get me started that's more than that to get things started on the most
sensational inspirational celebrational
gravitational this is what we call that nobody used that nobody used that
splitting the world of evil here comes bear on patrol pausy bear here we go all right you come
on come on go go go sir i just booked this person on a five eight five oh he could get
20 years for that yes sir what's up what making funny noises in public
well that's me like that 25 years did you read him as rights no not yet okay listen
you have the right to remain silent that could have just been beaker that could have just been
a clip from beaker you have the right to remain stupid
yes sir all right you you'll move into that jail cell you that's it get in there this is my favorite
part this is the best part all right better best part tonight we're keeping score stop talking
this is the best part yes i'm on a scale of one to ten here's your score so far
oh the sound i can't handle that i can't handle what i just looked at
hey it's me you're watching the disney channel call from president germa
oh be a wise guy are you a fucking idiot uh yes mr president you can seek a recipe for
coca-cola of course mr president yes i will get right on it mr president everybody don't
got one thing to say i'm gonna shit my pants houston we have liftoff it's too late for this one
it's me that's right diane we got the wacky brother before coming up here this is all one thing
hey gamer let's go you fuck it's your turkey
oh my fucking god
all right honest opinions what did you guys think that was
i'm gonna throw up oh that was fucking funny
is this the last one this might be the last one this is i want to get off this ride i can't get
off the ride yet there's only a few more left no this look at that i wonder what's gonna happen
at the end of this one all right what do we got is that it did we get no we didn't is an anime
opening just when you thought it was over there's more well that was that was beautiful
hold on a second let's find out oh this is we're down here we go here we go you guys ready
this is called germis it's less than 200 all right guys this is gonna make me throw up
the bitrate can't handle this one i can't stream this one there's so much going on why does this
have to be one of the last ones i this that one's actually gonna make me throw up on stream
and here we go the final one
hey thanks everybody for watching you're all fucking talented
this is the hardest i've laughed in a long time do you eat ass of course i do
thank you for participating that was so much fucking fun
i hate i hate six and a half hours of this i am fucking gonna cry
i'm gonna be playing team fortress 2 as
chicken
seems like a really great one to go out on
and that's it thanks for coming oh no there's another one
what's the matter you freaking stupid this is the final one
none of this makes any sense that that can't be how it happened unbelievable
do you ever dies less than a minute into this somebody used it somebody did it it took 364
fucking videos no you didn't do it you didn't use it you didn't no you didn't use but i actually
did it i did the like give it give it give it there you go holy shit holy shit here's the playlist
i'm going to link this playlist right now there's the playlist thank you so much everybody that was
fucking wild uh my stomach hurts my head hurts my goodness i gotta i gotta go take a bath or
something but surprised me how fucking funny and creative some of you guys really are a lot of you
guys there was there were hundreds of submissions and again it was not a contest if your submission
wasn't used then don't like feel bad about it it was just we would just throw something together
here don't ever do this again oh that was fucking funny uh we had huge money come into from fourth
consecutive line thanks for 75 hope this giving you an idea the love the rest of the community
has for you no i mean this this was something i want to do for a long time and the more that
i can involve everybody collectively it's fun you know but playlists in chat uh i'm i'm exhausted
that was like a hyper stimulation i i'm absolutely honored to pass the 10k mark almost 12 000 people
were here thanks for coming thanks for watching because this was this was you this was you you
know i didn't make any of these fucking things i didn't do any of that i mean i did the green
screen footage but you guys did all that it was absolutely fantastic thank you and um i think for
the purposes of the stream because we went so late and we uh kind of need to get going here
because it is 10 11 12 it's almost one it's almost 2 1 32 a.m eastern and i didn't have the
notifications on all stream so i'm going to take off thank you everybody you're all fucking
incredible have a great rest of your night go take a bath go take a shower thank you for
participating i'll see you guys on wednesday not streaming tomorrow or tuesday there was a huge
amount of money tonight huge amount of fucking support hundreds and hundreds of subscribers
tonight i can't even fucking count you all you know what i mean it's it's immeasurable the amount
of support seriously it's fucking i can't even believe it thank you and then a hundred dollars
just came in as i talk about it you know uh a seville a seville renegade a civil renegade
thanks for the hundred dollars germa five hours ago i was prepared to have a good movie night i
however was not prepared for you to take us on a spiritual journey that was too much germas for me
you deserve a rest thank you for the hundred dollars dude and i want to please give a huge
shout out to the mods there was a lot of work put into that to getting those ready there were so
many submissions so much quality content coming through that playlist is public have a great
rest of your night as we show it here it is i can't even get it off the screen there we go
i'll see you guys on wednesday get some sleep yeah that vod is getting absolutely muted
if it's not even if you know if it's not yet it is see you wednesday take care you fucking gamers
see you soon