Trees. Found trees. Found them. Right there.
We can all calm down now. I found the trees.
And I am gonna starve to death. Oh my god.
Do I have any- I have, like, food, right?
What if I eat the raw beef? Does it give me, like, E. coli?
Oh, it doesn't- the rotting flesh is, like, better.
No, it's not. Not at all.
Alright, tree. There we are.
No, I don't have a- nooo!
Is this the only tree here?
You're killing me!
I need at least, like, a stack of wood to create my floor.
My wooden paneling floor.
Cause I wanna- I wanna look like a rich person.
Is that really the only damn tree here?
The nec- look, okay, look. The next tree is over there.
Oh my god.
I would sprint, but I don't wanna lose all my hunger.
Cause that would be bad.
I'm just gonna eat all this rotten raw beef.
Let's see if I get salmonella.
Alright, so far so good.
Oh yeah.
I wanna get up to that stupid tree up there.
Alright, you've had your fun. Time for you to die.
I'm only level two.
Is that because I've died so many times?
Alright, I have to make the trek up this mountain.
To get this stupid tree.
I haven't been leaving the breadcrumb trail.
I'm gonna get lost.
And I'm never gonna find the house again.
I think I'll be alright.
I can see there's a torch over there.
I have to get up to this one other tree up here.
This is ridiculous.
One damn tree at the top of a mountain.
What?
Where the hell did you even come from?
I'm knocking you off the cliff like I did your brother.
Where is he?
Get out of here.
Oh, whatever.
You can just, I'm just gonna go away.
Go away, I'll take it, I'll take it.
Nice, level three.
Oh, already this is gonna be cruel.
This cow.
Oh, I can watch the sunset.
I'm gonna knock this cow off.
Sorry cow, but you had it coming.
Plus I want your meat.
I want your meat.
Look at this.
Now see.
Now see, this is what it's all about, guys.
Watching the sunrise on the top of a mountain.
Looking down at all the beautiful stuff.
Oh, sorry cow.
Oh man.
Come on, I can't believe I need to find some more trees.
This is bad.
How many wooden planks am I gonna get out of this?
If I'm gonna get at least a stack of 64 wooden planks,
I should be able to cover my whole ground level.
And not even close.
Kinda close, though.
Actually, no, I got some of these, so okay.
If I can get one more tree.
Where's one more tree?
Oh, yeah, right down there.
All right, I need to go.
Oh no.
Wait, hold on.
Okay, it's this way.
That's the way I gotta go.
There's a tree right there, too.
I'll take that tree and just go home,
because I'm gonna get lost.
Oh!
That was close.
I was actually very terrified about that one.
Let's go!
Let's get this last tree and then go home
so I can build the rest of my floor.
God.
Ka-chunk, ka-chunk, ka-chunk.
Okay, let's see if I can't get some floor out of that.
So there's one of my torches.
I see it.
They see my breadcrumb trail I left.
So far, so good.
Give me more of these so I can make some pita bread.
All right, as I go, I'm gonna take the torches back,
because that's a waste.
Whoop!
Excellent.
Excellente.
Blink.
Boink.
Okay, so I'm on my way back,
and I went all the way this way,
all the way down there,
way past that thing up on a mountain,
and there was a whole forest right there.
So...
Yeah.
Whoops!
I'll come back to that later.
We've collected the trees.
We've collected the wood.
Time to go back home and build up the house like we should.
There's no reason to fear, and there's no reason to fret.
There's a creeper in my house!
Oh, I can't!
Oh, God!
Get away from me!
Don't ruin my house!
You...
Come here! That's right!
Come over here!
You ruined my song, you piece of shit!
How...
My boat!
Oh...
Okay, is there anybody else in the damn house?
Okay.
I think we're good.