Hey, what is going on everybody Jerma here with scare Saturdays
Drinking coffee right now. Actually, that's half-calf coffee because I'm really really freaking tired
Overtired you could say so why don't we play some scary games gonna be playing Olaf's demise tonight, which is another and another
amnesia custom story and
Let's get started. Here we go
Okay, so
Apparently this house may or may not be haunted. I
Highly doubt that it's not haunted. So we're gonna do some investigating pot throw it on the ground
We got some like bottles throw that on the ground too. I don't need the hell is that Oh candle
I'm just you know, I'm just gonna go right out the front door. Hey
Hello
Staircase hopefully not. It's not like SCP a never-ending staircase of hell this door opens
Doesn't open you do not open. Come on son of a bitch run down the stairs
Sprint that was there. Oh, so any key for that door? I don't I'm so edgy right now
No, none of these things. I don't have the lamp yet. It's one thing. I gotta find the lamp turn
So was there actually no paper there? There was no paper there, huh? You piece of
No, there's the key
Is that guy still chasing me right now? No, he's not all my this this this this this mod this much sucks
This is horrible already right off the bat in like less than two minutes. There's already two horrible things
Let's go open. Wait, I can't open this door this key. Oh, I still can't get out
I still can't get out this door. I gotta go back into this room down here. Yes, actually telling me
Ah, here's the chest with the lantern and the tinder box
Okay, bugs on the ground squash them. All right. So now is it gonna let me leave? Let's hope so
Get me out of here. Got the lamp. I still can't get out of this friggin room
Apparently not key. Where are you? Maybe you just wouldn't let me like leave cuz damn what the hell do I have to do?
Just there's like sacks of potatoes in here. I already saw these. Oh, there's a door over here
How did I miss this door? I'm an idiot
Mmm-hmm. I think there's a cat in my room and it's freaking me out cuz I think I don't know what the noises are
This mod is already proven. It's gonna scream at me
What's that? Oh gross. Oh, it's that done sanity potion. Hooray. What else I can do in here
There's another door on the other side. Get out of that way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way
No, that's a pig. That's a little piggy. Maybe it's behind here. Maybe it is. Oh, I found a hidden door
Get out of here. God, how many boxes can one house own? There's like a thousand boxes in here. Get out of the way, man
All right, give me that key. Boink. Let's go. Coffee before I spit it out. What?
I hate to say this be prepared when you enter really. What do you what does that mean?
My key. What do I have to do? Be prepared? Maybe there's another key down here
Why would it tell me to be prepared right now when there's nothing here? Don't
Tinder. I should not have done that. That was probably a really dumb idea. Don't like the
Can I open this door? What the hell is that? Oh, it's just a bunch of knights. Yeah, we're good
I wonder what's gonna happen in this room. Give me that. Hi fellas
Yeah, it's good to good to see you good to see you that you're not gonna like jump in my face in one second
What was that? Oh, it's one of these things in here. Poor guy got his like old body. What what what what what what what?
What what what what why did my why did I just spin around? Why did I just spin around?
Why did it just spin me around?
Hi, hi sir. Hello, sir. Hello. Good to get me out of here. Don't do wait
There's like a hidden thing back here get out of my way. All right, take a second here. Take a second here
This room is red
interesting is
I'm running out of oil. No, I'm not boink oil box lost key. Okay, I got the key. What the hell is in here
What is that? Is this like a piece of like meat? What is like meat war doing in here? Where are the aqua teens?
Where's like master shake and
Frylock move move. I want to like drink that sanity potion right now. You still got the keys
Get me the frig out of here. Which one of these keys gonna work this one. Yes, it will
Open the door. What are you serious? Wow, so I can't even mmm
I thought something was gonna be right here. Definitely it will maybe I don't know weird
Well, I got that key was there another door back up top, I don't think so
I think these are just the only two rooms unless oh, no, no, no right here right here one of these
Yeah, it's this one right here. Let's go move, please
You're supposed to hide from the monsters cuz that's what people said in the comments
You're supposed to hide from the monsters and not use your lamp is even in here anymore
My lamp is turned off. The lamp is off. I don't know if there's anybody even in here anymore
Please have there nobody be in here, please. Thank you. Oh
So now where do I go? All right, I figured it out
I had to use the lost key on this door and now I'm completely out of lamp oil
So this is great. What the hell am I what is going on? What the hell is going on?
Oh, this is no, this is the room. I was in before with the boxes. Why are they back up?
Hold on. Why are these boxes back? I came in this way move that jump
Kind of wish I could see oh, I really wish I could see what the hell was going on right now. Oh
I made it like that way. Oh
I feel like this is some kind of like weird bug that I've encountered because why the hell are these here?
Did I make it out? I did. All right. Happy days. I made it out. No lamp oil though. So this is fantastic
I need to light something. Oh, I'm like insane sanity potion sanity potion. No wrong button
Sanity potion. Thank you
That was delicious
Well, I can't do anything else besides go the way that I came up here. So I die. Well, I don't have any oil
I don't know how the hell that ran out that quickly, but we can go up here now, can't we right? No, we can't
Oh
Look at that and she opens and I have no I wish I could see anything
Maybe there's a friggin I'm looking for one of those things on the wall. One of those tinder boxes on the wall
I don't like this hallway, by the way, and I'm going insane. I got to keep moving. I'm going insane. Oh
My god, should I use the key again? I'm going insane right now guys. Thank the Lord
Geez, and I need a sanity potion, you know, I'm drinking the sanity potion first then
Okay, here we go. I'm like completely
Completely shooken up by that right there
You just put me in a coke can and you shook the can until I just exploded out. This is this
I'm not touching the letter last time I touched the letter a person jumped out. Get me out of this friggin house
Get me out of this house. I don't like this place touch the letter Olaf. If you read this
I think something's in our house. I mean look at the dining plates. I'm so scared. I
Pretty much a grammar mistake right there. I left something in this room that might help. Did you?
I love how I said that I had plenty of oil because now it's gone just like that. Damn it
I'm just gonna start smashing into things and see what happens. Can I just break the door down? Going insane?
Is it behind the eagle golden eagle? I left it in this room. Yeah, nice nice vague directions
You fucking asshole. Why don't you just like tell me what it was? Oh, hey, by the way like Bill
By I left you like the secrets are getting out of the house. It's like somewhere in this room
I'm not gonna tell you where the fuck it is though. Oh, of course, it's behind the painting
Damn it. I don't have any oil either
And I have to open this door with no oil sure I'll pry it open person standing right there. No, it's a night
At ease soldier. I don't want to even look item. I can't look I don't even know where the hell I am
I don't know where the hell I am. It's completely dark. It's not this way. I'm going completely insane. My character's freaking out mushrooms
Mmm. Oh god, that's horrible. I don't know if I can play this anymore. I don't know if I can do this anymore
I don't think I can play this anymore. I don't think I can play this mod anymore. I think it's over
I'm really I'm gonna I'm rage quitting the game. Just run just sprint through. I don't know what that is
I don't know what that is. I don't know what that is. Oh, I don't know what that is
But it's a is it behind me or is it in front of me? Is it behind me or is it in front of me?
I can't see anything. I just know that he's there. Where do I go? Should I hide in this corner?
I I'm probably gonna die right now and this is where I rage quit the game GG
Can't see anything if he's still here. I'm in a lot of trouble go in the door
Okay, I can see some form of light. Can I come on? There's gotta be something over here
I can like get into I wish I could see anything right now. My character's probably correct. What's that? Oh, it's a P
Oh, I can't see
Well good, I found like another door doors locked and I need a goddamn key
Is there any was there a good door over here or something? I could get into
We go that same dude in here
Fuck this mod. I'm alive