Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on explain this to me. How can how can I be late
if I don't have a schedule right now? How can I be late if there's no time that I'm supposed to show
up? That doesn't make very much logical sense. Sorry I just had to flush a toilet, look weird.
Need to change my offline image. Yeah I'm I think I'm just going to delete it.
I haven't saved. I'm going to update it. Just haven't been like that's one of those things.
that's like leaving a bottle of water on your desk or in your kitchen you know
I'm talking about you just leave and a half drank bottle of water is just
sitting in the same spot in the kitchen for like a week and you see it every day
and you're looking at it and you're like ah I don't know and you walk away from
it I do that but with like five bottles yeah that it's just like a water bottle
like I see it every day and I'm like should I need to I need like I need to
move now whatever I'll see you tomorrow right down the cereal box stream no that
was real mr. was mr. mr. Dunwich right I'm gonna give credit where credit is due
came up with an amazing idea and I think we're gonna do it so here's the here's
the before we get started I gotta just tell you about this brilliant idea so
you know the cereal box puzzles that are on the back of every cereal box well not
really anymore that was a thing back in like they still do it but not really
like they used to every inch of your cereal box back when it been like the
mid-90s was a puzzle little like ladders and things to play with and crosswords
and now that's like nutritional information you know me like not
nowadays on the back of the box it's like well all whole grains and no trans
vats get that shit out of here I want the puzzles back I want to I want to
fucking like find the five cuckoo birds nobody everyone knows cereal is just
dogshit with fucking vitamins injected into it you know what I mean like what
you don't eat a bowl of fucking Captain Crunch and go like oh I'm so glad I'm
getting my daily C no that's not how it works anyways hi how's everybody doing
we're gonna play some more Red Dead today cuz I am officially addicted to
the game and I think it's very fun and I have the strict policy on this live
stream very strict policy of if I'm having fun doing something I'm gonna do
it and we're about to break the four streams in a row well actually no that's
not true because lethal but I played lethal league for about four hours so
then I never might so this this is like the second Red Dead stream in a row
right I don't usually stream the same game more than four or five times in a
row so it is still technically legal what's the brilliant idea well anyway so
what I want to do which was very nicely suggested to me is I'm going to go on
eBay and Amazon and maybe find some old retailers and I'm gonna get like 30
boxes of cereal and we're gonna do the puzzles on the stream and we're gonna go
over our favorite ones which one had the most challenging puzzle this is I'm
gonna fill my room with cereal and we're gonna go one by one we might even do a
thing we're okay like Cocoa Puffs here's like a Cocoa Puffs box from like 1990
this is gonna hold on a minute this is gonna cost like 10 grand how like okay
Cocoa Puffs like old box or something right can I like buy this okay here's
one empty General Mills cereal box 2009 Cocoa Puffs 2011 yeah oh yeah these are
ten bucks though it's gonna cost ten dollars to buy an empty fucking cereal
box from 2007 something about that is just seems not worth it that's buying
someone's trash that is buying a person's trash out of their trash can for
an exorbitant price ten dollars really that's like come on man that's a little
much just make your own puzzles it's $20 for one from 1990 it's this no shame and
just finding pictures of it all online oh fuck you're right that's true you
don't have to buy the boxes but I don't but then I have to eat the cereal right
and that how it works don't I also then need to eat it and test which puzzles
which year was the best can you eat cereal from like 1990 what happens if
you eat cereal from like 1992 it's pretty bad well yeah at least I'll get
my daily C that's correct oh man that's a funny idea though anyways um yes I'm
we're just I just want to play Red Dead and I'm here last thing we did if you're
curious if you have no idea we just got the bear we just got the bear by the
way spoiler alert in case anyone has not played this far in the game just got
the bear the legendary bear okay just I mean that I know you saw it on the
screen already but now we have this the funny definitely guaranteed every
streamer you watch every single one that comes across this hat will wear it
guaranteed if this is like the streamer hat isn't it isn't it it's a cool hat
oh you dropped some frames oh it was too good to be true we had three days in a
row perfect internet it was too good to be true
clean your piece for oh I think it really might have been too good to be
true I may it may have been too good to be true is it possible was it too good
to be true it looks pretty rough right now we'll see we'll see we'll see if it
strains itself out quick throw salt over your shoulder I know really okay okay
those are the consequences of streaming last night for ten hours I know really
well we're gonna see how what happens so welcome and goodbye potentially hasn't
happened yet we're just gonna go so I apologize in advance if this is just
over before it even begins then let's go yeah my neck is real stiff I don't want
to stomp on it that's no you do you need to get you daily see you haven't got it
yet this ain't good first of the night no I like I'm like looking over at my OBS
time to change the title of stream that one didn't count no I haven't started
playing yet I wasn't playing the game I was looking over to see if OBS was
stable okay so instead of obsessing over the OBS if it's gonna happen it's gonna
happen so here we go turn on your face cam why I want to do like a story
mission so let's we gotta go all the way back here so I'm gonna take the stage
coach so I unlocked fast travel is that mean I can I only do fast travel from
here I think it's still in jail he's probably gonna be there for a very long
time you can pass out from you can't okay well then I'm gonna I'll take the
stagecoach no well Mike is not in jail anymore he's out he's just not happy how
we doing we I think I think we're okay somebody the same honey somebody be
pissed on the line for a second but it looks okay from last couple minutes
knock on wood also I mean I'm gonna I'm gonna go out on a limb here but that may
have been just the initial little hiccup from me starting my stream because
italics is currently streaming too so maybe it was just like oh shit I go yeah
I'm fine I'm good I can handle it maybe go to the fence what's the fence got for
me now this fence you mean do I have I have to go far right am I gonna play
this online yes what does it come on once online come up in this game oh he
crafts the trinkets take a quick sip get in my daily see didn't fall off the
fucking horse didn't fall off a horse you saw how long did I plan that joke
for that I'm done that is not a joke look I'm looking out for my personal
health so Bob Crawford was livid about his coach getting wrong I was very
sympathetic oh shit that's not a gold bar that's not a gold bar that's a gold
ingot only 300 bucks that's still a lot of money I'll take it pocket watch gold
pocket watch it's a ring I'm afraid to sell these things how rich is this guy
oh you got something probably pretty rich looking to get something put
together huh here we go whoa okay legendary cougar
coyote elk Fox I didn't get the elk antler how did I not get the elk antler
whoa it's the brand what's this thing do picking creeping time oregano and
wild mint yields two times more herbs okay and what about the bear where's my
all sorts of unusual ways to acquire goods in this world I'm not one to judge
what happened my bear clock oh shit I need quartz chunk how do I get a quartz
chunk I mean this one kind of sucks do I need the ram horn for anything else
or is it should I just get it what else can I use it for I guess I'm gonna get it
I can just okay I got it should work and now have I can now pick up stuff better
well yikes yeah is it gonna behave is the internet gonna behave today well I
can't get the bear one so true this ranch is losing money hand over damn
well I will tell you that is definitely an indicator for things to come I do
have my trinket skull to the internet oh wow we may not turn off you may see
that a few times I got a lot of money though what I'm gonna do with my money
oh I feel it like hearts every time I was gonna go down here I'm gonna take
the stagecoach from here right I can hear you boiler it's the ps4 ps the
regular base ps4 just chugs while playing this game yeah well you're about
to hear my blood boil pretty soon here well the game doesn't run bad on the
base ps4 but the hardware the hardware sure does let's take will be taking the
train to to here this is Rhodes is there a roads station 30 bounties good why I
butter I just automatically assume that I have a shitload of bounties roads has
a station good that's that's good fruit blood train tickets were expensive back
then yes they were you always wonder what kind of music I'm into
funk electronic I'm really into like electronic reggae funk I mean that's
just asked you don't do anything bad don't use any weapons and don't yell on
me don't yell at anybody keep your voice down in roads don't talking no no badgering
anybody random freak I ain't gonna I'm gonna fuck this one up again here
them Grays moved here a bunch of no good white trash and they somehow got rich
about 50 years ago they moved here cause a whole heap of trouble
yeah he was looking it was Yankee spies during the war and everything I saw
yeah sure
fell off his ladder yesterday I think he would have died I'll be why doesn't
want to why doesn't want to rob this guy I'm sure you got things to do don't
let me folks show some pride in how you look dang it mr. oh I forgot I have a
bear hat on no I'm not I'm no no I came here for a specific reason I was go
talk to Dutch I'm not gonna I'm not getting involved I'm not no Dutch we're
gonna do the mission I'm gonna go talk to Dutch no one's gonna get hurt nothing
bad's gonna happen I will not do something bad and I'm not going to fall
off the horse
I'm so sorry sheriff how are you doing sir tough business you boys had no need
to pretend with me sir life can be tough so it can and no man knows another
anything no sir it's still I feel you were hard done by losing your employment
like that but still here in Rhodes we have work
enough for honest men that's some strong stuff still don't seem to be doing you
the funny hat excuse me a moment I told you we was moving up in this world
deputies amongst these drunkards and slavers good honest thieves like us
we're bound to be moralizers in a place like this stinks
oh you are bad now listen sir there is shine in them woods though and it is
cost in this county it's good name and the state a whole lot of income funny
why are you saying that I gotta set me down not a problem sir not a problem at
all you are safe hands now and people waste time with the temperance movement
liquor never dulled a good man's senses Arthur you ride with the deputies
okay I'm ready let's go on an adventure together me and you how are you pretty
good and your friend is behaving himself oh yes I think he's learned they're
behind us congratulations on becoming a temporarily deputized citizen of
scarlet Meadows County most towns just get bounty hunters to do their dirty
my horse these days but sheriff now I'm sure I don't need to remind you yell
back there hey there is dang straight there is this is a dangerous business
but follow my lead and you'll be just fine sure hey remind us he's in charge
here of course sorry guys so the microphone is inside of them Anderson
boys and I put in a very good word with the sheriff on your behalf we rounded up
the other soon after I'm pushing for the rope myself what are they gonna come up
with a device that just nitrogen pools and it's quiet not just any even come
up with anything since the 1800s you about the great weight a thing that
spins really fast no one's come up with like a fucking liquid chemical they can
put in their chin at one point until well a few changes in the labor laws now
they're dealing in moonshine a refrigerator there stills yes I'll put
like a small fridge unit we destroy one another one pops up but that makes that
makes noise to fall from grace I don't want to hear that not to mention the
fact that Catherine's great weight has a rather air conditioner inside of here
red horses add an extra forty dollars to the big the majestic retail price you
know I mean well that's the rumor but the grays and the brave weights think the
other stole the fortune from but it happened so long ago I don't know for
sure it's true 40 bucks so I imagine that bad writer suits you mr. W just add
soundproof your refrigerator if there's sound coming out of the machine just
block the area where the sound is coming out of and you won't hear it so I'm just
gonna take like rubber cement and put it all over the back of the vent here
and I won't hear it anymore right like thinking face you know I'm saying what
happened here can I can I not loot over here is this well I'd be deemed a bad
guy I can't loot I'm we're pretending to be sheriffs right now I can't do it
anyways this must have happened recently
come have a look at this look loot his body suit and tie that's all I heard one
bullet cleaned through the forehead well my money says this is the handiwork of
a gang called the Lemoyne Raiders let's see if we've got any identification yeah
I'm on my best good boy behavior I'm not gonna do anything that okay we should
get going I'll send someone over here later to clean this up so is this is
a main story mission or was Micah the story mission that I just haven't done
because somebody was like you gonna do a story mission I'm like yeah this is one
of them right get in there do an impression all right I want to have a
look at these papers I want to have a look at these pay I'll direct you I'll
direct you that was not bad I give myself an A no you can never give
yourself an A that's not how it works
I'm not like a comedy computer I'm not like a Mad Libs book
original used to say he had a few stories funny town preacher how do you
even respond to that under the table okay well here's a funny noise don't go
fast this tells you what kind of people the break weights are selling moonshine
to murder give me a break of that no how about way less of that spam of like
LULs and shit content just wait till we get up my long rifle
once did I tell you boys what did I say I said this place was crawling with
vermin and we just found ourselves the rats nest our excellence as they say in
Paris I mean he's talking liberal or metaphorical I don't know this well the
way I actually let my friend here decide he doesn't have your fine way
with words but he is definitely the man for the job me bear let's split up riff
throat up each each throat oh I'd say let's go right I think that's probably a
better idea yeah what was that I was gonna say something but I didn't I was
concentrating on the radar and why am I standing just said yeah I'm so focused
on the Metal Gear Solid aspect of this mission all right I don't think I've
ever like knocked somebody up from behind before I've only stabbed with
knife you know what I mean how do I not kill in this game how do you not kill
that killed him that person's gonna die he's dead take cover oh fuck hot what
hot it's alright I got Luigi how would I be able to take cover my head I have two
heads you know what I'm saying like my head my head is big even when I crouch
my character is too big he saw a bear and ran away that's I mean I was trying
to use the tree funny oh my god I was funny
destroyed all this and your boys can handle it no it's hard to do it dynamite
throw they was the finest family thousand acres or more 300 slaves can I
get from back here decadent scripting blowing that up right okay throw it I
need to go actually up and press the button plant dynamite in the distillery
but do I have to plant it or can I just throw it press R2 to place dynamite
without igniting it and then ignite and then run away and more than one I guess
you want to put it all over the place stand clear I have to ignite it first
I thought it was fucking dead like it my head it's back my head into the wall
fall backwards that's a huge beat that's the biggest be I think I've ever seen
fine bill what's going on with Bill we're gonna do a wheel what's he doing
over here what's wrong with you look I feel like I'm somebody's little brother
playing with toys my hat my hat you don't give me my hat nothing else
matters oh this bill goodbye bill oh my god he was doing the same thing I was
doing can't get on this bullshit come here come here I got to end this with the
tomahawk otherwise all my friends in my party chat won't like me oh god center
mass there's another one no I wanted to go into his head that guy was really
scared of a bear with a tomahawk I mean you got to give that guy a little credit
man what would you how would you react you can do dead I homing tomahawks I
keep forgetting the dead I works with other stuff that's not a gun dead I is
just dead I just means hey slow down time and get to do it hit exactly where
you want where are my other tomahawks I threw him over here I need to collect
the tomahawks because they're expensive there's one right here and there's one
over here where is it up there oh well it's got one of them all right let's go
I don't need the money I got I got two of them back that's fine okay back to
dutch and gang and friends back to dutch and gang and friends whatever want to be
a modern cowboy in real life modern cowboy what would that even be
well forgive me but in getting in front of my man alternate side turn to our
lives save that one for next time failed to destroy the last of the moonshine
sure would you like us to I normally take it for personal consumption it's
sort of part of the job where's the desk trombone I still have it but it's on my
back I better get back home why don't I just take a jug or I really am a little
brother those are nerfs to show that there's no hard feelings that's the
exact color scheme those are nerf bullets my cousin Webster he used to say
some of us is not as American as others if you know what I mean only I didn't
quite come on you degenerate no good white trash hill Billy pieces scum I
know you Billy lime we have a lot of land so stupid a backwater so backwards
the beard is important now I can't what if I shave it off okay I need to be
constantly eating I have to become I can't what's the fattiest thing in the
game meat right premium cigarettes cigar baked beans eat the bear meat I'm
trying to eat too fast these two family eat the animal fat I don't think I even
can just a great bunch of food I really think we can play this from all sides
it's got Jose written all over it this is starting to sound like the young
Dutch again what do you mean young Dutch I'm as strong as I have ever been
hey you know what why don't I race you back what hey hold on let's do it okay
that's like my horse is way better on my word there's a race well you just got
destroyed that was embarrassing okay toad you're gonna get fucking
lapped yeah I do this is this is like a level of embarrassing you what did I
miss I missed the turn oh fuck you man yeah see you later see you later I used
drugs doping during the race never seen it before have you I almost got turtle
in the hair right there and we pulled it back I almost did it again don't be
the dope you don't want to be the hair in this scenario I can't it's over just
trying to cause a distraction like the bad guy in a fucking race cartoon yeah
I'm going to put out spikes on the ground I throw some jumping jacks down
and I will screw up his entire race when you get to be my age they're better
than anything watch out for this butter it's dastardly I was gonna say you're
like a son to me and I have to have a dog more than that I always have to have
a small dog that's laughs at my jokes enjoy this one racer boy release the
butter Springfield and he goes like drops the fucking butter on the ground
got dice over here eat some food and sleep I need to just always constantly be
eating just drink like I haven't been eating any of my shit I just destroyed
one of my cores all right so that was a mission that was fun to do some more
loan you know it's just more lonely money lending and others and you well it
turns out the pursuit of freedom is not a cheap business not for us and not for
some of the locals sharking already I prefer to corded banking you ain't the
one handing out the beatings no but I am the one feeding the women and children
in the camp what choice do we have mr. Morgan I don't know come on then tell me
who here's the list refinery worker turned hunter by the name of Vinton
Holmes you'll find him up in the hills north of strawberry ah an apprentice
undertaker this one working in roads his name was when Hughes and how many of
them do you think will be able to pay with enough encouragement both of them
sounds like a plant so we got some new debts to collect that is right here also
got go to that one right now this one up here let's do the one that's right here
is right down the street shave and change hat I just got this hat can you
pee in this game I don't think so I don't think you can pee and you pee candy
wait I get candy delivered to my door now okay that's pretty cool all right
let's let's go to shave let's take a look at what we can do I don't like that
no it's not only at length four of ten I'm not doing anything I haven't changed
my outfit though don't you guys want to see what it looks like when it gets to
ten out of ten don't you want to see how much of an unruly bastard I look like
clothes I'm gonna Rapunzel this shit you understand right and then we're gonna
do a big makeover we're gonna go we're gonna go on like Monty and like have
like a before-and-after makeover
no no no no no no custom outfits sir
no coat all right I'm gonna start to look like fucking Freddy Fazbear here in
a minute no vest we're gonna go French dress shirt I can't get rid of my pants
though those pants are too important to me no I can't ranch pants chaps off I
can't I these are this is I want to be decked out in right now those of you
that play RPGs or played Warcraft or Diablo doesn't matter right now I have
two legendaries on and I have a shitty common shirt on blue boots no I want to
be decked out in all orange like legendary clothes can modify them though
closed rolled sleeves that looks good and I modify again I get more I can
no I can't could you just get the chaps to match the head I don't think I can
because you know keep pressing down and then you called me a dummy what that
wasn't very nice oh I mean there's plenty of room there to add more you
know what I mean like what there's so much more room bare feet I like these
spurs and snakes I mean I'll take the Slytherin ones fine masks can I have
this on with the bear hood this would make sense this would be great if can I
do this because oh god damn it I thought I could just have the bear head be my
actual head that covers up my whole face I don't think I probably can't wear
these either gloves no no gloves bare hands primary whole eye this is where
you can change your pollsters I need to put my hat back on though bare hands and
bare feet okay bare hands bare hat and bare feet I'm gonna give it up with
like yeah all right well there it is the bear outfit so far I need to put
shoes on I need to put on shoes or my character's gonna die I'm gonna like
stepping some kind of like animal shit with a cut on my foot and get the plague
okay okay so he wants something you want something to everybody wants
something all right so let's go what was that was gonna go collect the debt
right there's a mission right here there's somebody in camp hope you step
on the Lego well that's chicken let's do it this is it's right here we can hey
Molly what do you mean put on all subtitles I will after this touch I
mean how does he seem to you I'm about the same as usual I guess I really love
him you know what if he like he always says loyalty is everything step on the
world's first Lego what you want bring a gift the great gift information so you
got some tip-off so now I can risk my neck and make you some money while you
lounge around you know Arthur it works on the inside as well as on your sour
face if you say so come on over here will you be my other fool you too Charles
what are you talking Arthur's above a little stick up I heard about you just
as long as you ride with us I got a serious medical condition yes you are a
compulsive liar no need to be like that Charles have I ever lied to you I hardly
know you exactly you boys should do this it's easy and I'll only take a small
commission for my information it's now or never I could not take this guy
seriously we're reaching dead rising levels of you don't belong here as it
passes through a crossroads near here where there's an old ruined church it
connects with the rest of the wagon train very easy pick as long as we get
paid or you get shot I'm happy you are a sick man Arthur Morgan a very sick man
not crazy yet not crazy enough yet well I'm not sure what else we could do I
guess I could get like the legendary turkey and get like the turkey feathers
on my back right I mean that we just have to be the fucking legendary animal
we gotta fight I have to kill the legendary turkey right that needs to
happen I can't rest until the legendary turkey is dead and they're gonna put
wings on and try to fly legendary rat I'll get like rat shoes
with the lockbox passes through every week they switch out riders just north
of here but the front wagons by itself for a stretch before the last run down
turkey wingsuit okay hold up here we should cover our faces they'll be
passing through the crossroads up ahead now I do just look like I'm a bear
face should we do any time now let's keep this quiet and clean nobody needs
to die here
it's just like Dungeons and Dragons campaign not even a Wild West anymore
hands up we're gonna rock you that's right you know boys I don't I don't want
to get shot but this is a mistake I work for Cornwall kerosene and tar
mr. Leviticus Cornwall so you know that is respond I hear he's rich enough to
share the wealth around and not miss it oh he'll miss it okay I'm not going to
get around the back not lethal we just don't for the kidney
I gotta help what was that clean your guns I will just give me a moment we got
hundred fifty dollars
being chased by our reason our real name why can't we use our horses names hold
our food look behind you pursuers don't make me look behind me
bitches oh god damn it not one of these
come on up no causing a cascade we supposed to turn I don't want to run
to anything I can't throw the dynamite it doesn't work the homing dynamite
didn't I couldn't do it is this lit this one's like this one's like this one's
lit my friends this is so I'm just gonna come on this whole are three
things I gotta know did I break a snake it takes forever for dynamite to blow up
it's funny when you freak out about it so whatever it doesn't take it takes a
long time stay until dark then we'll sneak out of here Charles you keep
watch for now sure well we get some rest sleep in here we all just woke up two
hours ago let's try and get out of here absolutely shut up shut up there's a
light over by the house damn guys copying my outfit he's got bare feet
too we're in deep trouble I'm gonna search I'm gonna come in here slow
motion like go check out the bar and all of us are like oh fuck place looks
deserted enough sure you head inside I'll go around the back we're all just
sitting in here do it I got his sake just role-playing he's like guys I can't
shoot my character only has tomahawk okay I'd let like the DM just know that I
really didn't want to pull the gun out but like some people aren't playing well
here with us I don't want this person invited back not just playing like this
what I have for like one in proficiency with with a sidearm but I'm being
pressured to take the gun out where'd you find this guy dead shit I was too
busy I'm just standing there I told you I'm not proficient with that Craigslist
Dungeons and Dragons players
oh I can I move all right let's do this for put this away
that's not gonna really am being an asshole I'm taking this guy's thunder
don't do it a big dive no hat I'll get it back over I'm really into that word
tonight huh proficient one on you I mean I do appreciate the left-for-dead
amount of enemies that are coming over here when's the tank gonna show up
burning we get out of here how do I get out of here what do I do I got I'm like
panicking I can't see that guy get out of here how do I get out how do I get
out you can't get out he won't jump escape through the hole which hole oh my
hat wait I gotta go back in my head my hat my hat I get it back shit
I think I lost my hat try to confuse him now you'd be like a good tonic here
with me give me the show I got a shotgun
we need to do this quiet take the left and I'll take the right okay you're
right on my you take the way he just confused me I don't know what does it
mean
what did you not get him there's one there's another guy over here who the
fuck is this guy what
there why don't you make it an old man suffer what did that guy come from what
is going on
yes we should not pay attention damn it that's it right
cinematic I didn't do that he did don't you guys understand that you see the
black bars I'm gonna search the satchel right the hats and flames man we have to
generate a new one how am I course do it this game is too violent what I mean
investigate I don't know what happened where's my horse come here come here
come here come here come on come on
horse wait I'm so like drink it drink it drink it have you not figured out how
drink it drink it horse holy shit his head came off oh my god his neck just
went back with my law this game is too violent come here we gotta go enough of
this bullshit different angles 120 bucks this has to stop now this is a stop now
this is it ends it ends here we're fine we're out of the way okay in the clear
not quite this guy's still coming this way the biggest bounty I've had was
1,500 bucks of God why did that even happen I don't remember I just saw red
was my hat no that's the wrong one there sorry I had to unsub just found
my pills broke don't ever apologize for not being able to give me one but thank
you thank you for subbing for as long as you did thank you so much I need to win
horse needs to eat I need to eat don't tell me what to do okay we got I need
some lightning bolt and a dead eye there it is some more health sweet corn all
right yeah look where am I going now oh right to the debt there's a stranger
here then we got a bounty dude speaking of bounties to collect there's one to
collect on me so I probably should take care of that post office I need to
apologize yeah I need to go in and say sorry with money you don't think that
the sheriff's would have some kind of angling of suspicion when one of their
deputies comes in what are you doing in here deputy Arthur no you know just
paying off some of my bounties oh you already did well what did you do
well I saw the man in his head and looking at me funny and he said the same
dialogue sequence a bunch of times but you won't you okay
I saw the man in his head no you look awful look at me useless I wasn't born
to this I didn't deserve this I used to be gentle jerry mom's instead good for
you that's anything to boast about everything for me who did hey what did
they take my whole life a whole way of living a career I stole a lot of things
but that's quite a lot to steal look at me here living in the shit in the mud
I'm sorry whoops my old house house my grandfather built that was some
exorcist level of insta puke by the wash droid repossessed by the bank
I could get my old things back personal mementos watch my ledger where's this
house again comes instead north of scarlet meadows thanks as I can't go
near my ancestor I'm living rough over by Eris field if I'm ever out that way
I'll see what I can do time time is hail okay well I just got it so let's go get
it it's over there and over there is over here I hate time it's hell time is
hail I hate here have some peppermints I can't even take I can't even cycle
through my weapons huh oh what else we got we're gonna drink the opens gin
they have it how we're doing on healing we're okay you want to peppermint so
we're going to collect this guy's stuff that sounds true adventure one that I
would love to take part in time for gamers what's going on over here oh wait
wait this is a hunting party or is this bandits me I'm sorry you were saying
something I didn't hear what you're saying it's hard to hear it over the
screams Jesus Christ what did I come back to what's wrong with me why did I
just get like a sepia tone Jeremy you're taking this role playing thing too
seriously you will address me by my name which is Arthur Arthur Morgan please me
your queen is holding in the courts of the state of LeMoyne we do hereby grant
repossession of this property and all items here into the bank of roads him
holdin judge holdin Henrietta Blackley clerk him hold the 1895 you think a
notice is gonna stop me now that is both this is that's a spell incantation of
the door guys I can't touch it I can't go near it that's a shielding spell I
can't ledger watch pistol why would I need to look at this hmm which angle
should I look at I'm gonna step on an exposed nail oh cupboard search the
cupboard cupboard where was it excuse me no I don't want to examine the bottle I
want to search the cupboard empty hmm family I don't know that even just said
June 7th 1855 dear sir please accept this likeness of your family as a small
token of appreciation for your assistance in the recovery of my
property like your old paw you're a cunning old dog and a credit to this
community here's Colonel Joshua Nixon the Ascension plantation was it family
didgeridoo thanks indeed for your talk to our Sunday school class thought you
might like this drawing young Josh did of you he wants to grow up to be just
like you Sam is to inform you that your monthly cable bill was not a dear mr.
I'm afraid there's no more work for you down here at the plantation I'm grateful
for the help you've given us and to help your papi and your papi's papi gave us
before you these are trying times for all of us you are in our thoughts and
prayers here's truly Colonel jade Nixon the Ascension plantation oh here's a
pocket watch does it work Wow after all these years and it's even the correct
time what time is it show me the time that's your watch now the pistol that's
the correct time you the pistol in the ledger pistol in the ledger pretty well
cigarettes premium cigarettes what Pokemon card did I get gems of beauty
card for all right time to go upstairs probably old crap well let's go through
your entryway desk and see what you got in there don't be so quick to judge
Arthur I know how many manuals for vacuum cleaners instructional booklets
from monitors and warranty cards you have in there dude give me a break right
I can open this camera but like this looks like they're gonna be opened shoot
duh duh I had to see it first what you doing here I didn't even get the items
we found this place first just looking around for some things Oh revolver yours
finders keepers
never bring a guy out never bring a knife to a gunfight that guy didn't have
anything first person in the whole game that didn't have even a descent on them
Wow never bring up wouldn't rubber bands gunfight the ledger is probably it's
probably like in here oh oh triple triple a game triple a game bugs look at the
bug your diary this is like going through somebody's mail man you're not
supposed to do this well that's that I was somewhere near Rhodes when they
caught me till the day I die I ain't gonna forget the sound of that dog
barking in my heels but I don't suppose that day gonna be far off yet it was 50
lashes yesterday and 50 more to come I don't think I can take anymore man said
he was doing his job funny kind of employment if you ask me but I suppose
you ain't lights fading so that's it for now I do hope I live to see the end of
this war and justice went out June 64 holy shit anything else fucked up no
this your ledger a list of slaves rewards January 15th Betsy 17 dollars
January 18th Louise 12 dollars May 18th Wilfred 18 dollars May 24th many and
child 20 dollars Jesus anything else fuck you oh no I'm okay the hat where is
it that's not it did it fall down oh it's the big it just disappeared it was
right here well did I miss anything else okay I can't go upstairs I can I can I
actually break out this front door no it's boarded all right so let's see how
this plays out from the little 80 mage I mean I can't use weapons in roads
though I could throw dynamite at him but I can't do that it's not allowed and I
asked him to follow me and then like run a moving with a car
yeah shit on there but it's all gone to hell oh man oh man you show some respect
I was respected once I had a profession you asked me to get you something there's
no bringing back what I want what my job pride the respect accorded to a
gentleman what about this old crap huh don't you understand those bastards they
changed everything I was a good worker I took pride in my work they took it away
pissed on my leg oh man some jobs ain't for saving and some legacies they are
history are you trying to shoot me he tried to shoot me
you pointed at me I still exist I can't kick him in the fire I can't what oh no
I just barefooted him I wanted glass no last oh come with me what get over there
oh whatever oh now he's on fire I gotta get him over there it's what I where's
the train almost there no I'm not shotgunning his head I could have just
picked him up okay here we are let's go let's wait no I'm not waiting it's just
I'll be totally turning the fucking dog food real soon here wait wait for the
train it's gonna take forever oh right my hat my hat my hat thank you I'll be
here for an hour wait off the tracks oh right he's already been murdered he's
dead it's over he's dead we want blood we want what dynamiting somebody and then
burning their body you want more what more snakebite I'll take care of it this
guy gonna give me a new gun maybe I'll get a free gun
hopefully I could pay you someday maybe one day I gotta get out of here I can't
wait till he shows up and gives me like a break have a good day thanks for the
free gun in like two hours sucking up venom doesn't work yeah I know I said I
said that last dream and everybody yelled at me when you suck venom if you
suck venom out of somebody's wound you're putting it into your mouth the
poison then seeps into your bloodstream and then now it's your problem and it's
already in their bloodstream everybody made fun of me when I brought that up
last time it was screaming yelling should we just go to Mike and how it's
I gotta turn sick dark in here I always forget to turn the lights on let me just
take this opportunity to go take a pee might as well I'll be right back in like
two minutes he's been gone for so long where the fuck is he? is he still here? I don't have any idea
check his Twitter check it look at his fucking Twitter say where is he? all right we
got Finn so we did I don't remember the last thing we did
okay Grays let me look at that Dutch asked you to sniff around Kaliga Hall to see what you can
find about the Grays okay and then Micah asked you to me meet him at his camp near
strawberry let's do I think someone's been on here for so long is it I think
is it time to do Micah learning how to read I think it's time it's time so I'm
gonna take down or up is there the stagecoach here looks like probably
downs probably quicker and there yeah okay we're gonna go down here I'm gonna
go down here we're gonna do this and then we're gonna go to GR okay forget
everything I just said he's been down there for a long time you know sometimes
you gotta wait I mean like when Sakurai delayed Smash Brothers brawl three
months back in like 2008 it was worth waiting I think it's time to change on
horses to whispers getting a little tired brawl did they delay brawl yeah
like three times they delayed brawl at least two or three times
turn this way I wouldn't say the brawl was the best smash game I would say the
brawl was the most anticipated smash game that of all of them that have been
made so far I would say that that's just shooting with my horse girl come here
you don't get an accident with somebody and start shooting them I did not
deserve that I was I was reading okay well I'll be fair I was reading I was
reading chat but that guy was on the wrong side of the road
all right workshop or office I wonder where this person is I'm gonna say hold
on let's replenish everything and then let's do some cores here this one and
let's have a drink for alcohol gin that's so rude okay let's go in all right
that door didn't open what about this one
why are you dressed up like that I've seen some sick perversions in my time
what is he dressed up as?
this one might take the prize
am I looking in the mirror?
you gotta help me
it's that crazy gunsmith
he made me dress up like this
he's got me chained to
god damn fruit
what?
I don't understand
you gotta do something please
he's never gonna let me go
what the fuck
you gotta get me out of here
hang tight I'll think of something
just stay there
how do I use this lock breaking kit?
I'm telling you the truth
he's got me chained up
I can't use a gun here though
how am I supposed to do this?
your first time in my shop?
whoa now
that's a fool
I wanna see what's in that basement of yours
show me
nothing and no worse down there I swear
why don't I be the judge of that
damn
I want those hands where I can see them
what the fuck
you're under arrest
for keeping somebody
down here
free will
you're
where are the
what was wrong?
I just couldn't face that he was gone
I was teaching Sammy
how to hold the rifle proper
out by the river
the recoil
shot him backwards
he slipped into the river
the water pulled him downstream
so quick
it all happened so fast
I didn't know what to do
I searched up and down that river bank
for days
but I couldn't find my boy
I just miss him so much
and you
you remind me
of him
you look just like him
I'm so sorry
please forgive me
it's too late for apologies
you just count yourself lucky that I don't
kill you for what you did
don't know what else
you want from me
take what you want
tell him to the judge
I mean
the ultimate judge
Satan
did he say he could take his stuff?
what is this?
Lancaster repeater?
what is this thing?
thanks to the free gun
anything else down here?
how much money you got in here?
two dollars in dollars
your ultimate judgment
is getting worse by the second
I'm taking everything in here man
because that's bullshit
you stay right there
I'm taking everything in the whole house
I can't use
I'm only allowed to use the gun down here
no wait
what happens if I walk up this
no I can't
I'm going to take all the money from the cash register
I mean this is easy, free money
I'm taking everything in the store
I'm taking everything
did you have any money in there?
every single thing in the store
it's going to be like
remember in the end of the Scrooge McDuck movie
when the guy had the pants filled with the coins
look at all this shit
it's all mine
I'm taking everything
Black Friday
this guy's not going to have any inventory left
it's not going to matter where he's going
everything must go
any weapon on the walls
I don't care what it is, it's mine
I'm never going to have to purchase bullets ever again
they're worth a dollar each?
yeah but when you take 50 of them
that's 50 bucks
what do I got over here?
I get to take my whole sweet time with this too
this is great
what else is over here?
I'll take these too
is there any guns?
I'm fine
I'm barely bad
what about over here?
this is my only opportunity to rob an entire store
answer the door
what? there's nobody here
what do you mean answer the door?
do I have to pretend to be the shopkeeper?
answer the door
yeah come on in
what would you like to buy?
I would like to have some ammo
we ain't got none of that left
what about some canned goods?
nope
do you have any weapons?
no we're all gone
sorry we don't have anything left
have a good day
okay well now
the whole place is cleaned out
what about inside the cupboards here?
let me make sure I didn't miss anything
can I go upstairs?
no this is just the downstairs
okay so we got everything we wanted
he's down here
okay
the gun? I have the gun
why can I not take a
gold gun on table?
what the hell are you guys talking about?
oh okay
so here's my opportunity I have to
I gotta do this quick
I have 400 bullets to this let me just check
to check out it's aim and everything
no what do you mean no?
don't kill him why?
you don't want me to kill this guy?
now stay there
don't move
so what do you got for me?
gun oil
sun's drawing
oh Jesus
dog? who's dog?
all right let's go
you're under arrest
for being the ultimate creep
you coming with me?
the door is blocking us
I can walk out this way right?
okay where's the jail?
is this jail?
where's the sheriff's department?
here is the general store, newspaper
saloon, blackjack
blackjack I don't care about
anything else
let's check let's get this guy into the cell
okay
he was taken
I didn't have to do anything
the devil fucking grabbed that guy out of the portal
his eternal suffering
putting him in the jail cell I could never
even compete with the eternal suffering he's gonna have right now
all right blackjack
right here
let's play it
I have to double down and win like five hands
or something
two silver earrings
nice okay
that's it
there's a nightstand
okay blackjack time
I'm here
I'd love
to play some blackjack
I got
money to spend
I got 1200 bucks with blackjack's
name on it
what?
what's going on here?
don't pretend otherwise
we ain't looking for
hit the trail come on
no I gotta play I wanna play blackjack I don't wanna start a brawl
okay you're gonna leave here
you got me
that's him
no
police
police I can't throw a punch
in here that's not allowed
I tell you this place is cursed
where did this lady come from?
I wanted to blast
some people in the face
this is not fair
all right now you fucking pissed me off
now you
pissed me off what is this the fucking
three stooges like get out of here
do I have to fight more people?
this guy's a knife
wait why is this guy
I was trying to be a good person
oh my stomach
62 dollars
these guys come up and start
trouble with me and I don't want to fight them
eventually start throwing punches get
curly larry in mode
for two straight minutes and then a guy
just guts me like a fish
a guy that had nothing to do with it
why?
why didn't you outstab the other guys?
I should have fought back from the beginning
I was trying to be the good guy
all right now let's play blackjack
you said something mean
no I
look if somebody's gonna call me an asshole I'm gonna be like
fuck you
hey you're a little piece of shit
you're dickhead
you're an idiot
that's not my reply but you're idiot
idiot
well what do we have here?
some kind of piece of shit?
garbage can motherfucker?
stupid idiot
okay blackjack upstairs
no distractions
where's the table?
it's time for blackjack
let's go
I don't need to
know details I know how to play blackjack
where are my cards?
all right let's see your bets
yes that's it then
no more bets
what do we got?
a fucking four
six
oh god
insurance I'm not putting insurance
is it blackjack?
oh this is bad
six
oh you dickhead
nine
all right come on
nine ten
nineteen let's do it
seventeen there
nineteen
I pushed
I didn't lose I pushed
I actually like this view better
please put in your bets
yeah sure
where's the high roller table so I can bet a thousand
dollars a hand
nine
nineteen that's a stain
nineteen
fourteen
sixteen
I don't have enough chips to double down
what is this bullshit
another nineteen
actually I have to do two dollar bets because the achievement
is to double down
I have to be ready for that
bets are open now
double down is the only way I can make
an achievement here
double on four I think max bet is four
all right give me an ace
give me an ace
that's a twenty
all right double down
looking for an ace
no I don't want to split
split against a three
maybe if you had like a five or six
maybe
busted
oh
oh that's right give me enough chips
no you don't
you know you can't you double down on a twenty
you get another card
you'll just you're guaranteed to lose
you can't split against a three
twenty
well I'm just looking for the achievement at this point
that's a give me an ace
ace
seventeen
that's bad
remember you always got to assume
that the dealer has a ten under there so
I mean I could stand here or I could fucking
hit it and I think I'm gonna hit it
thirteen
yeah
that's a bust
that's what you gotta do man he's gonna turn over a ten and you just lose anyway
thirteen
sixteen
twenty
you gotta always assume
that there's a ten under there
the dealer is forced to play
until seventeen that's correct
fucking three
oh that's a five
that's a fucking eight
bullshit
those are my cards
how dare you
thanks a lot
sixteen
you doubled
against an eight
what are you stupid
what are you an idiot
the guy on my right
doesn't exist that's why you never played a full table
idiot
thank god
that guy was definitely
the bad luck on the table
the guy with the bad luck on the
table
watch this
see
although he'll make
him like twenty one with a fucking
god damn it man
am I allowed to win a hand
of blackjack or what
I'm gonna push every time and then lose
I need to double
I need to get this achievement
there's a challenge to double down and win
you need to be in the right position
what a great start
here it is
no
I can't
did he say never lucky
I mean
I'm just trying to get the achievement
this is the worst thing I could possibly do but I'm doing it
twenty like just let me win
it's the stupidest thing ever
I'm gonna push again
let me guess is he gonna get a twenty
that's nineteen so what is he gonna have
deal of showing
a six is like
the biggest chance for you to win
and here comes the bust
what the fuck
why
a deal of showing six is like
the easiest
most in your favor thing to win
can I fucking win
anything I haven't even lost anything
I've lost like two hands
should I throw the table over
and fucking karate chop this guy or what
seventeen
whatever
this is a hand to win
he's gonna pull over a ten
he's gonna bust
nine
sixteen bust card here it is
you motherfucker
hope to see you for the next one
how many shoes are we playing here
how many decks
there's one deck
fucking god
he better not have it
let me guess
fourteen
fifteen
oh wow
the dealer busted on
unbelievable
first time
it's daytime
I gotta double down some more
I have to win five double downs
I'm only here for the achievement
I'm not here because I love this game
I'm here
here to get the achievement
I mean you can't hit this
I don't have enough money to double down
this is like
it's your turn
card please
fucking told you guys
I told you guys
against a four five or six
and why you
I should have played the fundamentals
cause he's gonna bust
I told you
I gotta play fucking blackjack fundamentals
you're supposed to stand there
listen to the chat room
fucking god
thanks
that's fine with me
push me again sir
he's the only guy ready to be playing with one cent
come on man
you're like the grandmother that sits at the slot machine
and plays one line one credit
and they sit there all day and smoke
four packs of cigarettes
what's his card fifteen
busted
oh my fucking god how many cards
how many low cards are you gonna pull out of there
hmm
I'm about to pull the gun off
that's it
just double down every time
I'm gonna lose all my money
just give me something more
it's twenty but I don't
I want like an eleven
you know what I mean
something I can actually double down on
like give me a ten or nine
nine ten eleven
eleven
oh what the hell
at least I fucking won
I can't double down on every hand
because if it's a hand like
you'll just bust the hand
bets are open now
I told you guys I'm not addicted to this
I'm just doing this for the achievement because
there's a challenge
you want me to unlock the outfit
there's a gambler outfit I need to do the challenges
give me two
sixteen
this is like the worst thing
this is the worst position
to be in
fifteen versus seventeen
like what the fuck am I supposed to do here
I'm probably gonna have to stand it
I mean
you're supposed to hit but
got it
that guy just double down
can I just move up with one seat
don't you do it
nineteen
you're gonna double down and win five times
double down yeah
I mean I guess I could just play
okay I'm gonna play four cent bets
and double down every single
time until I win five times
I did four cents and here comes blackjack
double down
I mean I need to stand on it
why would I hit out of nineteen
fifteen
if you did that at like a
blackjack table the whole table would turn
and be like what the fuck did you just do
I just need to win
we just gotta get it out of our system and do it here
nine, two, give me a two
you had to give me a three
and yet it's a king
that's fantastic
a twelve versus a twenty
wonderful might as well double
fucking down
okay
it's time for the shotgun
joke
just flip over like a five
my fucking god
you just have to always assume
I've been here for four days
I'm not going to shotgun
joke anyone here
double down with the double barrel
shotgun, no
refuse to double down on two cent bets
yeah, fifteen
might as well, versus an eight
might as well double down and lose
oh that's a bust Kermit
I do believe
I'm gonna win
you make twenty one out of this I'm fucking
we'll do the shotgun joke
alright just need to do that four more times
I appreciate a diversion
what did that guy just do
forty cents
alright give me a
there's blackjack on a forty cent bet
or
I could just double down
oh they don't let you do it
you can do that
you don't have to take the blackjack
what the hell
this guy's got a gun
okay
I thought that guy was coming in to fucking
just like light us up
I just saw like the door open and like thing in guy's hand
seventeen
or double down
eight double down
twelve
fourteen
nineteen
no
you actually can't double down
on a blackjack
this is where you are
there are plenty of casinos around here that you don't have to take the blackjack
you can just play it
double down here it comes
give me ten
that's fucking horrible
ten
this other guy's been here longer than I have
yeah that's true
and this guy came back
look at how much money that guy has
give me an ace
ten fifteen oh boy
I haven't been in this position
eighty percent of the time
sixteen
alright whatever he's gonna turn over a ten anyways
bust
yes that's two
I just need to do that three more times
where's my progress update
did that not count
why did the counter not show up
it shows the first progress you did get it okay
I'm playing blackjack so awfully right now
but it's just to double down
every hand
I would have won if I didn't fucking do that
see you in sixty minutes when we get
three other double downs
how much money do I have
I'm just running out of money I have to be careful
there's an ace
no blackjack alright
do I just double down
just double down
fifteen
I think I'm gonna double
that was a good play
sixteen
that's almost impossible to do that
consecutively
I'm just looking for a bust here
fourteen bust
oh my fucking kimia break
there goes the chance of me beating the game
alright then
what do I got here
twelve
I'm gonna get a bust card
and lose
he just got an ace
I just
double down
twenty one there comes number three
don't get it
don't do it
thank god alright this three
only two more and we can get up
alright let's see your bets
have I seen Jeremy do this before on a rerun
alright come on
there we go
yeah
seventeen
that's twelve
I'll take one
you got too many there
thirteen
I will double
eighteen
flip over a ten and let's win it
no
yeah
only one more
I'm gonna do that one more time
that's it then
no more bets
ace
I can't double down this
I don't care about winning this right now
why was I thinking about pressing double down
thirteen
double down and try to get an ace
I would have had it
I would have got it
if I double down right there I would have got that ace
fifteen
you gotta be kidding me
oh my god that's so sad
gone
alright bets are now closed
eighteen
I can't double down on this
nineteen
always double down
twenty you can't double down on twenty
I can't believe
I can't believe that I just lost right there
now I'm the one that's here the longest
alright let's see your bets
yeah but anybody wants to give me
criticism I'll just be
I'm just gonna yell at them like I'm trying to get the achieve
bets are now closed
here we go
and fourteen
I'm gonna double down
the dealer's been here the longest
the dealer is making money
I hear people that are just question marking
anyone that just comes in right now
will just think I'm an idiot
that I just don't understand this game
I just double down every hand
it's double the money
what does that mean
did you know how to play blackjack
I look stupid right now
fourteen
fifteen
and fourteen
bust
you look stupid either way
that guy needs a
that guy needs to be banned forever
for like
I'm running out of sense to double
down on here
fourteen flip over
uh
fourteen
sixteen
don't flip over a ten
yeah
blackjack requires zero skill
I have a little bit
of news for you here
none of them do
the only one that requires any actual
real skill is poker
thank you very much
none of these do
I'll do two cents
newsflash
no I can't double down on this
lightning can't strike twice guys
eighteen
some of the card games require thought
but skill
skill
oh I don't have enough money to double down
here I'm getting up
thank you
they require thought but at the end
of the day it's random cards
being thrown down
I need to get it
one more time
I have to get it double down one more time
so then we can be done with this
he sits down at the slot machine and is like
wow I'm really good at this
you mean to tell me that there's
a computer algorithm
that makes me lose
eighty five percent of the time
but no this is the special
machine I sit at this one
I take up the whole row
of this one
buffalo machine
and I put in five cents on each one
and I go click click click click click click
across the whole row
how much did I just bet?
no
you dummy
I just do one cent
bets
okay we got eights
we're splitting it
no blackjack right? we're splitting these eights
split them
oh baby
ten
do it again
again
ten
card please
twenty
eighteen
by the way splitting eights
versus a face card on the table
do not ever do this
for any reason
don't ever do that
I did it for the effect of the comedy
there you go that's why you don't do that
that's the reason why you never do that
always split eights
as in eights I disagree
because if the guy's showing a face card
you're going to lose twice as much money
like right there he flipped it over
I would say in the German on eight five
gambler's handbook
I know the always split eights
no matter what
I don't fucking buy it
alright double down let's win
fifteen
nineteen
sixteen
twenty
seven
fourteen
violating TUS teaching people how to gamble
I'm talking about in Red Dead Redemption 2's
blackjack fake blackjack table
flip over a seven
thirteen
eight eight eight eight
okay I did it
win three games of five finger
fillet
that's it I'm going out on a job
just now
can I put like predator bait over here
hold on can I get a bear to come in
what
I see something what's that you see that
oh it's just a reflection
alright five finger fillet
let's get these gambler things out of the way
why did we come here I forget
now there is no five finger fillet
in this town
I'm sorry oh we're going to go to GR
there is a bath though
is there a bath can I bathe at the
saloon
just came back I didn't lose any of our earning
no I wasn't trying to I was just trying to get the gambler achievement
man
who? who are you looking for?
listen
have you seen I'm looking for my friend
Gavin
Gavin?
English bloke
lovely fella
he went missing and now I'm all
alone
that's it
that's too bad
did I kill his friend?
that's really
Gavin
I hope you find Kevin
when was the last time you saw
Kevin
if we see a guy
named Kevin anymore make sure
make sure you say something
I think that's all I can do with this guy
press zero to help him
press circle to help him
Jeremy he's saying Gavin
ride the donkey
it's giving me an option to do something here
what is it
what are you doing
Gavin
free the donkey
how am I supposed to do that
I can't free him I can't pull a gun out
I can't do anything here
we're going to go to Gavin
why am I not eating anything
more food please
okay I'm going to mount my horse
this is much further than I thought it was
I couldn't see
him no witnesses nobody can see
easy don't run over anybody
else
I'm a student
of the history of the region
I ain't the one to speak to
think he's down there by
the wood store
okay
let's get back on the horse
I just kind of ruined their stuff that's fine
are you the
boy that I'm looking for
BG definitely
because I'm slowing down
I'll see you at the sheriff's office
excuse me
friend
not yet but he is hoping
I guess
you don't get a lot of traveling men here
and suddenly there's a whole phalanx
of mysterious but strangely
helpful yankees
what are you doing here
I'm just looking for work
looking for something
don't worry your secret's safe with me
I got a secret of my own
are you secretly normal
never mind
like an improv routine
I don't know why
I love her you know
Penelope
but it's impossible
love tends to be complicated
she's a Braithwaite
I'm Beau Grey son of Tavish Grey
nephew of Lee Grey
the sheriff grandson of old Murdo Grey
we Grays have been loyal
to the state and murderers to the Braithwaite
for so long now no one can even
quite explain why
but just because he's got the fucking hair
all of a sudden he becomes me
all to some nonsense while she
she's amazing
she's like a woman
from the future she's like
tomorrow if tomorrow turns out
fine well I'm sorry
for your predicament would you help
I don't want to get involved
gang fusion seems
unseemly I'll pay
I've got money we Grays
we've always got money no brains mind but
money I know
she loves to sit out in the gazebo
on the edge of the Braithwaite property
take her this letter
and this bracelet
please
and you'll never hear from me ever again
sneak into the grounds
around Braithwaite
manor where's my
little friend
come on then
what the fuck happened what the
fuck what
wow that scared the shit out
of me what
what hey
I'm getting shot out of a cannon
we won't run over anybody
shut up
two guards who do you think you are
that was a little delayed reaction
on my part
that's pretty good music
I still have no shoes on
sorry
so sneak into this manor
workers watch out for workers
they're like landmines
you guys don't want to step on them
what sneak past the guards
so there are
there's a guy that way
I can't see the manor
it's so foggy
there's the manor
I think there's one guard out front
but there might be another one
is that it? I think it's just this one guy
he's right there
ahh he's turning
how close do they have to be
I guess maybe not that
I guess I'm fine
I'm just going to keep it expanded the whole time
why don't you do the double foot
stomp there
how much further away are you
where is Penelope
you just sit at the lake
apparently
I don't think there's anybody else
wet socks
I don't have any socks on
I made it so does she know I'm coming
I made it
a gift
what a gift well we don't even know each other
well it's not from me it's from
from Bo
oh he's
so strange
yes he's a little strange
but also so
human the rest of our families
are stuck in the dark ages
well I don't know
cave people perhaps
Bo's different
but if they find out
they'll kill him and send me to live
someplace awesome handsome
smart funny
have you ever been to Ohio sir
no well neither have I
but my uncle has a factory there
he was sort of the black sheep
on account of having left
but now they tolerate him
because he's a vicious snob
families
are are
there's something else
you got a family sir
well they tolerate him
because of the money but me
with my ideas above my station
they can't stand
that sounds pretty complicated
I don't know
quite what to say nothing to say
except I hope they all rot
I don't
well maybe a bit
why'd I have to sneak up on this lady because the
guards there would not let me in
will you give this to him
sure leave the area
without being seen
well
there's a big body of water right here
that looks pretty good to me
wait hold on
I'm not going to swim across
the Atlantic
hold on a minute not the Atlantic
the Pacific what of an ocean
I'm going to swim this way
okay give me a second
I need to heal my lightning bolt
I mean like actually
heal it do I have one that's just
lightning bolt I don't think I do
yeah I do
there we go
I'm going right over here what's with the music
it really is just one two three
three two one this sounds like
when you used to have CDs on in the car
and they would just skip
where is everybody am I far away enough now
oh way far away
okay
that is the first silver medal
alright let's go back
return I can take this away from the regular
come on come on
I think I did a pretty good job
bye
so now I got to bring this back to
uh was
any over here in the morning
maybe maybe it's time to sleep
time to go to the outhouse
um
that's not an outhouse what do you mean the outhouse
these people
don't do these people know me
what are they all waiting for they're looking for
looking at something this one
can't go in there
well I like I gotta get out of here
I'm not still okay there's people there
people there I gotta get no like I'm not looking around for an outhouse
these people are looking for me
let's go out
bye
didn't I pay my bounties
who's in front of me why does this
person have a thing on them
what who the hell are you you're not
a bounty hunter just a guy
that was just a guy
boy no
they're coming
apparently they're still going this way
I gotta
camp it's a camp up over here
this is not the wilderness
oh it's cause they got me in
combat and he'll figure it out
okay we're good time to
sleep time to go to sleep
until morning
tear down the
camp hey stupid streamer do
something funny
no
I'm in the mood
alright so we gotta go back here
Beau Gray
Mr.
Gray are you doing great
thanks I feel pretty great
whoa
who do you think the first re was
back like in the 1400's
watch out for people
some frog
let's hand the
letter back and then I think it's time
to hunt a legendary animal
I'm feeling a legendary
beast I'm back
and I have something for you the legendary
rat I'll go for the rat
you got my money
sure did you give anything
for me how much
might I have it
sure but it'll cost you
I can't be
bothered here take
thank you Arthur
your thank you
my god
what a woman she's
a woman is a killed for sure
what I could explain but suffrage
around here they don't even like
men voting bring back the monarchy
given half the chance progress
is a dirty word in these parts
unlike incest
excuse me I don't want to marry my cousin
Matilda I want to marry Penelope
but they're gonna
they'll kill a woman
is there holding they've done it before
mister you gotta help
I'm afraid I don't want no part of it I'll pay
my family we've still got some money
just thank you
come on we better get going
so this is part two
how much money was it I didn't see
it was not even enough money for me to
bat an eye at
is that what it says
take the road
sure whatever you say
well he's so rich
easy boy
and be calm if we don't get there
in time my true love may be
shot my favorite part about these streams
is definitely the fact
that what who's
I can't let it become a model
to it um
everybody that comes in
asks about
the braided tail
what's with the braid man
what are you doing here
this guy's got a braided
horse's tail where the fuck did that come from
what
oh right
it'll allow us to shout
all the louder
Miss Calhoun
Arthur really is a great guy
sure
okay
all right ladies
true
we know our song is a good one
and we know our calls is a pure one
yes ma'am
oh there's too many people here
don't give me
the frames
there's too many people
I don't think you understand
oh
what was
your name
Arthur Morgan
and people walking on the sides
you don't want to be there
I'm so scared to do
this
shotgun he said it
he just said it
peaceably Mr. Morgan
you can keep your shotgun to yourself
what did you say you keep saying it
you're making me say it
up here Mr. Morgan
I can feel it
lady on the left
you're gonna get squished between the fence
lady
the thing in the
road there's a thing in the road
oh damn
oh
what the hell
Arthur really just said it
fuck
go
We're we just leaving who the hell is this
Let's try joking get out of here you bastard. Oh special roundhouse kick
It was like a figure skater
We gotta go before they think twice. Oh Lord. Oops
Get out of my way. All right, let's go
I'm stained. I'm stained. I'm stained. Okay. Why would I I'm not gonna do that
I missed the old German a guy that would what?
What do you think old German would have just ran into those people?
You want to prove it? Oh
Dad
My cousins are vindictive bastards. My brothers are vindictive bastards. My cousins are worse. They started it
I know but you should leave I
Will as soon as I have enough money when my family we have money, but I don't your family very rich
Yes, well, I believe so, but they keep me out of the discussions. I have more of a
Artistic temperament so
Yes, oh
Some reason I really love her. I do well stick around tell me what this does
Well, I thought you were trying to make me feel better
Look, I gotta go me too. Oh damn I'm gonna be late. My uncle is as bad as you would imagine
Here your payment. Thank you
Excuse me
How much was it?
$30
Micah is blinking. It's just like please go do the Micah mission. It's just like look at it. It's just like come on, man
I'm sitting right here waiting for you
Did not do this and I wanted to
Go get the money
Hump the turkey. Oh, there's so much to do
What's close to here? Okay. We've got legendary
No, that's not legendary
Let's take a look at the legendary map
Legendary turkey. Let's see where he is. Where is the legendary turkey?
There is no legendary turkey
As much as we all wish there was who farted away. What do you mean who farted?
Show me a clip. What was it? Let me see it
Okay, go get the rat. Let me see it. I wouldn't hear it. I'm ready to hear it
No, that's not it. I
Really want to hear it. There's somebody get it too. I'm too lazy to clip
Okay, let's see
There is no legendary turkey, I don't know it's in the game somewhere
I don't know what the hell that was. It was part of the horse. All right, let's go to get the legendary
Beaver well, where are we? Where are we currently standing right now?
So what's down here?
This area of the map is with this is the northern section
What's like right next to the lake in the water the river whatever in the middle?
You've got foxes pigs. Let's go for the pig
Beaver we'll go take a look down here. Although this is it's over here, isn't it? Just go look over here
What's the turkey? There's no legendary turkey
That don't exist. There is a legendary turkey
Well, I didn't see it on the map
My hat hey i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead
Where's my other weapons? Why let his default go back to the horse?
Am I shooting with my tv off? No
He's up top
She dug my tv
I think he can fucking do that to me. Okay behind me. Hey, hey
What are they defending here
Fire bottle what I can inspect something
Oh abandoned church. Let's write it down
Saw an old church found it interesting. Not sure why
Well, there's definitely something in there one has to assume there's something in this church
Uh, there's a lockbox
money how much
Not bad. That's more than I got for just doing the mission
Is it anything else in the corner or something over here?
Is that another one?
There is another box
pocket watch jewelry
platinum earrings
Nice. Okay
another lockbox
that's three
Shoot bell shoot. Oh, hold on. I'm just trying to
Pick up stuff man. I need to have some money
Go buy something nice
Something else let's go up top
I didn't look over here yet
Rest by the fire
nothing else
You can't buy a shot bell i'm gonna shoot the bell
Everybody just hold on a minute. I'm just trying to traverse
Well, that was for no reason
Okay
I don't know about nothing this weird hole
What was at the top?
oops
Something up here. It has to be a reason why there's something up here. Oh, I see something
There's a bird's nest up there. I gotta get back up there. I gotta get to the
There's a bird's nest
I gotta be able to get like some rare eggs
cigarette card
Oh, it's one of the railroads. I just need three more of these and it's gonna be 250 if you land on it
I'm gonna smoke some more cigarettes
It's only 200. Ah, whatever
These look rare
It's a magic car. Is that it?
There's one more thing in there
There's like a pack of gum in there
Whoa, can I get up there?
shoot down
I can get up there. Maybe not
Well, I did it before
I did it that one time. Was that just a fluke?
Did I actually do something cool?
What if I was the legendary turkey?
I don't think so
All right. I'm in this area
I don't know what really what else to do besides. Well, look at this
Lancaster shoulder
I need to get a chance to look at this thing
enemy gangs
We discovered a gang hideout
Well, i'll take everything in your whole entire house inside the building
Fucking scarecrow
Sitting right there
All right, is he trying to go inside
Too bad. I can't go in here. There's no way to get in this building
Oh, I thought that was a belt
You've got a lot of dynamite. Can I pick any of this up?
There's nothing I can do with the dynamite. Can I drive a dynamite truck?
Oh, man. Yeah, you can't I can't take any of this
Damn it. What about one of the little ones?
That's unfortunate
Shoot it. I don't shoot it. Well, this thing is in bad condition
very bad
I have to use two gun oils on this
I don't think I even have any more
Here. Yeah, I need to go my revolvers are really not good at all
But I cleared up this place. I might as well look around for something interesting
You know what i'm saying lock box candy bar gold bar
Could be anything
Great amazing inventions
There are settings to change to make the shooting better lock box
aged pirate rum and money
Not bad, but what about this house?
That's a lot of fucking pez
strawberry pez
I need to heal how many of these do I have?
I just need a drink
No, I don't I need like a health cure
Only kids will remember that
Because it doesn't matter how old you are pez still exists
Okay, let's go
interesting little swamp land
those water physics
Beautiful stuff
What's that?
What's in the witch's hut?
Let's do it
Let's invade on here
What are you doing? That's not a fish
It's a snake
I need to study that though
steady
Just put the gun away so I can study this
Just come here
Why can I not study?
I don't know what it is
That is a midland water snake
Yields of skin and stringy meat used in crafting cooking to be sold. Okay
Oh jesus
american alligator
Yields of skin teeth and big game meat
Use a bow with improved arrows a long scope rifle for a clean kill
Come here horse
In the head what's the correct place to shoot an alligator?
I turned him into a rug
Okay, I was gonna go fishing here
I got him
He's just a little one
He was really small
And he looked a lot bigger in the scalp
This is bad
That's poor alligator skin
All right, let's go fishing
There's a fish right here
Okay bait
Uh track small fish which is a red bait
Lake lure tracks all medium and large sized lake fish
Corn I mean that's all I have appreciate it if you didn't keep throwing it away, okay
Okay
Give me something good throw dynamite in the water. No, it's gonna be high quality
That's it. I think yes
Easy
I got an alligator just fish with your hands
I don't think it works like that
Good to meet you
and it is
four pounds
One ounce large mouth bass
Try a different spot over here right in that spot. I see little bubbles
Come on. Come on. I can't cast and water that deep
Really?
Right into the trees tree snag incoming it's gonna pull me up there
After I get one more fish. I'm gonna grab a snack
See what I got downstairs
Maybe i'll have some soup
No tree joke
Sorry
Where are all the fish in this dirty water?
I'm gonna put cheese on it
Cheese on there
Have I get to change your underwear? It didn't work. What?
Wait, where did this alligator come? Huh?
The dynamite killed an alligator at the bottom and turned it into bundled up skin
All right. Okay. Let's go. I'm like standing in muck
I do i'm gonna check out the witch's house
This place looks pretty menacing
Anyone here abandoned?
Abandoned?
I guess unless they're not here
cigarette card
President alfred mccallister
What is this?
vegetables
What does he got? How about a lock box?
cash money
gun oil
Hair tonic
All right, sit over there
From the cabinet I can
crackers
Opened chewing tobacco. I don't think I want that
Thing little hut fishing rod new fishing rod. Are there different fishing rods?
Okay, now there's no cutscene going on can the force get in the boat
You know what I mean? No cutscene
No bullshit
I'm gonna jump from the dock
Probably not
Try it one more time
Just to moves too much
Yep last ditch attempt, right? What is that?
damn it
Oh, well
Hey, it was an attack
Ah, it's not homing dynamite
Back to what we were doing
Maybe I do want to i'm gonna take a boat there. I'm just gonna go over this way
See what we can find
Are these big boats? Whoa
We have here
I think I sent the score over here
Just me out here right now
Horse is following you
What are you doing?
Get out of here go home
Why are you coming out here?
Hey leave
Not safe. Good boy. I'm gonna take out some cores
lightning cores
That's the horse. That's the horse
Relax stay there. I'm not calling the horse out here. I thought that was my core for a second
All right, he's fine
What is going on here?
What's happening?
Why did I just run?
Why did I just drown? I did I
Did I seriously just get like battlefield ford?
I went out too far
Out of the map
Whatever. Oh, what a nightmare and right back in
Right back into the water
I think i'm dead again
No, I can't get it
I can climb I could climb and I can kick
We're fine. Let's take a break
Okay, so how do I get from here?
To there there's a ladder
Set up camp in somebody's boat
Oh
Oh, well
Broke my chair
Actually, let me cook some shit. Yeah, you guys are right
You guys are right
Plain freaky fish looks good
Throwing the used alcohol bottle into the fire
Just asking to get like
a problem
I'll store this next one
Some shoes on don't tell me
What kind of clothes to wear?
How dare you make fun of my?
wilderness man
plain big game
plain mutton
Although I like this is good because i'll have this for later
You know, if it ever gets dire I could cook the hat
right
No, why not?
I mean i'll give worms but i'll still be able to eat it
eat this
All right. That's good
I'll cook the rest later
Now we uh, you know, why don't we i'm gonna sleep
who cares
sleep until morning
There's lots of nutrients and leather
But you get the bit the snout
You just burn the snout and just
You'll crunch right through it. It'll be like chewing on cigarette ashes, but it'll be enough
Imagine the mosquitoes. Well, I don't even want to imagine what what wait, wait, wait, where am I?
I'm all the way down here
This is a huge place
Okay
well
barber taylor
There's a lot here
All right. Let me uh, this is
a lot going on
Uh, i'm gonna take one more break
P i'm gonna grab uh some soup
Because I want to sip on some soup because i'm a little hungry and I will see you guys
Yeah, I just saw him eat so I know I have to see you guys in like two minutes
Okay, I got some soup in a cup here
I'm ready to rock and roll
Just turn this back on
Okay, so this is a new town
What's the soup?
I don't know. Nobody asked that but I've done
Snake
Did I just run into it? Oh, I did I just bumped into them. Why do they sound like a t-rex?
Whoa
I think gaming might not be your thing
I mean to be fair. I did try to stomp on an alligator's head with bare feet
I need to see what it was gonna happen. I need to see what was gonna happen
Now so here's the deal
Go to this big town or no go the thing that i'm supposed to do the thing that i've been trying to do
There's another town over there. We'll find it later
Picks me up like a dog toy show soup or no balls
What it's like a bean and kale?
Minestrone or something. Oh
Oh Jesus
That's how you make an entrance
Yeah
Where'd that guy go? Ran up here somewhere
Where'd it go? Wait, those are the good guys?
I thought that those are the bad guys
Someone just wrote
The soup
That was more important
This
This is more important
There
There you go
There's the soup
There it's in there. I know it looks like coffee grounds and fucking cigarette ashes, but I promise
Uh
Put them in the coffee
Time's up that casket for you, but you want another what I can get for you. Mm-hmm. Well, go get it
Well, uh come with me to the churchyard
Are we about to dig somebody up?
Hmm do I not want a bowl
I mean, I mean, yeah
Are you able to be like a bowl of soup with a spoon while i'm trying to play a game?
I guess I guess I guess you're correct, but this is I can
What we're doing
I'm like screaming
I came out of a fucking bag. We actually are about to do this though the insane part about that
Why it ain't in there it's under here i'm digging up mrs. Claypole wow
Jesus well, she got a bunch of jewels in there that she don't need
Damn it
These have all been so different bunch of people here. Look you clear them off and i'll wait right around here clear them off
But don't hurt nobody don't hurt man. Watch it. Okay clear all the town spoke
Don't be shy ain't no one around just my auntie your auntie's long
Past prudishness. It's disrespectful. You'd rather disrespect the living breathing woman
You got here in front of you get out of here kids move. Come on
I knew we shouldn't have been here. You missed your chance boy
Get out of here kids
Wind up full don't be shy ain't no one around
Come on I knew we shouldn't have been here you missed your chance. Oh my god
Clearing out of here for some maintenance work
Gladly
It's about time this place got cleaned up
This is not good for my health man
Playing a rock star game
Now go watch the gate. It's honestly it's the equivalent of smoking a pack of cigarettes every time you play
No, I gotta stop people from coming in here
Laughter is good for you. I know but like I I like feel drained after every one of these scenes
Mr. This lady's trying to come in here. Oh, that's the lady that was just here. Excuse me
I'm sorry, ma'am. The church grounds are closed for maintenance work. It's about time too
The place was in need of some care and attention
They come from more than one angle or just right the front right at the front door
Seeing the way you can really get in
Lick them
All right charm, we're gonna charm antagonize antagonize
You boys gonna need yourselves a preacher you hear this fella I heard him all right, we're gonna lick you
Get out of here
Get out of here. I thought I'm not supposed to hurt anybody
No, let him go. Let him go. Let him go. Let him go. Let him go
How you doing?
What'd you find she had a broach here it looks like diamonds diamond
diamond
Well, this will do
Now get out of here before someone sees
Holy shit, I believe it's come to this
All right. Well, uh, how do we like put this back out of here?
Can we put this back?
That's more than than clear what I what I owe you
guys
guys, I
I can't throw dynamite in the hole
You understand
It's not even possible. So let's just leave leave it be
Get recovered. I wonder what a diamond brooch is worth
I can't do it
See
You can't use weapons
Bypass it
How I can't do a hail mary toss. I'm still in town
Yeah, I want to I kind of want to I need to go back to my camp here
You know what I mean?
Oh, I can't look at there's a random stranger here
the fence
Well, he's right here. Do I have anything to sell?
I need to bring that diamond thing back to the camp so I can't really sell it
reliably
Hello
I didn't even touch him. I didn't even touch him. I walked right
Having fun, mister
Good job bro. This guy
Well, I got it. There he is. Welcome. You just discovered my little shop here
What we got a large bag of jewelry
Three bucks each. That's it wedding ring. Give yourself cash
earrings
Give him back. Give him back. How do I give him back? Give him back
Give him back
Fuck I can use these somewhere. God damn it
Is there a buyback?
Shit. No, that's not
I can use those. I just
Didn't mean to do that
Hello, sir. Glad to have a new patron come through
You only need one anyways. Okay, that's fine
too far
Maybe not. Hold on
What are you doing?
I'm trying to double heel stomp the guy lying on the ground
I guess I could do this stranger, but no, I need to do this back to camp
Back to camp. I'm gonna give the provisions back
And never mind spoke too soon
Easy
I can't jump on the train
All right, I can take this
I can sell this to events
But wait about the train don't get stuck in the box again. I know seriously
I'll do everything possible to not have that happen
So that's still there
What am I doing?
I can drive the train
You can drive the train
Let my horse stay get out of here
This guy's waiting for the train
Can I pick up passengers?
It's steaming this guy
Okay
Okay. Bye. That was fun
What's the purpose of this?
My first person to train I can
Like it matters
my poor horse
So we're but it all takes us back to the city
I guess
It's fine
Okay, what if I get robbed?
What if somebody tries to stop this train?
How would they stop this they wouldn't
Hey
Just keep going around in a circle
Just don't stop
I can't go faster as fast as I can go
What about other trains
Can I back up?
Into another train
What's happening over there?
Oh, it's an alligator
There's a legendary fish over here
Um
I think somebody might get in the way
This train don't stop for nobody
You understand?
How annoying am I being right now?
What
I mean, I have to hit somebody with the train
You know, I like I can't go this far into this populated city and not just run a person over
We need to do like maximum overdrive and just wait for somebody to get in the way and then fucking hit the gas
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Everybody fucking hold on. Hold on
Wait
Wait, wait, wait, you think you're gonna get the train?
That's not gonna happen
I'm gonna tie up like 50 people and put them on tracks and then driving
I need to save the game here man, because this is a this is
This potential here. Oh, I can't save
They're never gonna stop me ever
I can go right back. What are they gonna do get on the train?
I hope they find me
Wanted Arthur Morgan
investigating
Oh, damn it
They don't know where I am. I'm hiding in plain sight
the guy on the train
When somebody cross
Cross over with that wagon that found me
Yeah, but i've been i'm in a giant armored vehicle what you're gonna do
Wanted searching
No, he's on me
Damn it
Watch out. Here he comes again
He's a psycho
Did I get him? I got him. Where are you going?
Oh, I so badly want to be able to turn this around
I feel like I can't give up this opportunity
See, i'm just a train right now. Okay. I don't know. I'm I am a train
I need someone to cross this
I need a carriage
That's so important
I feel like we keep rewinding the same video
Come on. Come on. Come on
Damn it
Just so badly trying to shoot in here
It's not gonna happen
Easy easy with that horse
People are never gonna trust this train ever again
What's that what is that?
Never read it's never gonna end
Get him
Watch out for that horse
That guy just shot a random person that person had nothing to do with it
I have to get out of here. This has to stop at some point, right?
It's just gonna go on the sun has set like twice
The sun has gone down now
For like two days, I can't figure out how to stop him
My fucking back hurts
Oh, they hit me. They're actually hitting me
Where's my horse?
Horses over there
Can you see him?
You see he's fine. He's over there. He's fine. He made it see him down there
I think I ran a guy over
Yeah, yeah
Lucky bastard i'm bleeding
I just hit a seagull
I hit a seagull
All right. This is the last ride
I'm just gonna scrape through
I need to do this right though
I gotta do this, right?
I'm gonna wait till i'm not a wanted man anymore. I have to run over a carriage. I have to
I can't have this fucking god powers without ramming into a carriage
So we're about to lose our wanted level here. Okay, nice new carriage come back
Put my fucking Satan powers that I have right here
Why would you do that get out of the way?
I don't want to hit you. I want to run over a carriage
Carriage coming
Here it is boys and girls
This is what you all waited for
Here comes across
Here we come
Come across
Incoming
Incoming cross over there
Right across there
cross
Cross somewhere i'll follow you to you cross
They're about to run out of road real quick here
They're gonna go left
Where does it cross?
Does anybody cross here with a carriage?
I'll put my you know what fuck it
You think I give a shit?
I'm getting out of my turtle shell here for a second
I already touched this
I need a carriage
I'm gonna I need two carriages
That's not big enough
That one like a huge one. I'm gonna line up three of them
You got some problems there friends. It's his fault. I can't move you. I can't like make you go the other way
Look out that one's not big enough. I need there. Here we go
Okay, i'm gonna need that wagon that ain't right what you're doing
This thing is fast
I need that get out of that
Oh fucking hit it in the head
What did it what where did this go?
The horse ran away, of course
Get in the train come on get back in the turtle shell the horses are fucking running away with them drive it quick before they get on
I wish I could reach up
No, i'm getting out of here
A lot of people just died. I'm dragging this guy that guy's stuck in the train
I think he's stuck on it still
Is he still on it?
I won't miss this train. Is that what this lady's saying?
I gotta I gotta get to a
car crossing
Oh, he's gonna get to a place where the carriages come
I'm going to run over every single
How could they possibly lose you because they don't understand that
I'm in the train, so i'm technically under cover
I'm just gonna get to a crossing
Wherever that may be
I think it really is
So now he's just gonna come across
Across what?
I've definitely seen at least one or two
Which way does it go? Can I direct which way it goes?
I don't think I can
But is that track for another train?
Um, somebody's tell me if i'm wrong here, but is this can I crash into the other train?
Is that just not gonna happen?
Oh, we're going way up in wilderness here. I'm not sure if we're gonna make it
Oh, we're going all the way up all the way. Where this is we're going deep
Be on here for a while
Rainfall you up not down
Oh
I'm stopping a train
That was a little too late
Wait, I just want to loot them. Well, yeah, I didn't want to scare them. I just I was
Getting off of a train and it was too late
What'd you have?
What were you going to give me for doing this?
a tonic
What about you? I think I didn't have anything
Yeah, somebody somebody is is guessing the thing that i'm doing
This is the fucking death train at now guys
We're filling this train with passengers
No amount of blood and death will be able to suffice this train
I'm gonna fill i'm gonna fill it until there's no more room
Like it's a storage house like a where like one of those storage units
How I wonder if I dedicate myself to this if I can fill this with people it's worth a shot
Uh, and we have derailed at this point we have i'm gonna crash the ps4
so be it
This is punt a bunch of animals put a bunch of animals and people
This is just like the angel of death like satan's express
I'm gonna fill this with fucking elks and bears and people
Noah's ark we're just gonna drive the train around and pick up the unsuspecting
bastards
No, don't die don't become one of them
Hey, see you guys in like four hours when there's 200 people on the train
I'm gonna come to like a stop and they're all gonna go flying out
It's going to be a disaster
Because they can't they can't stop me. You know what i'm saying?
I cannot be stopped
The only way that I can be stopped here is if these people despawn
We'll find out now. They're still in there
They're still in there
That's a go baby
Welcome to the welcome to the street
I want to see if I put a hundred people here
Yeah, i'm gonna i'm gonna make one slot specific for this
because this is the
Let me just get this straight
This is the one that was just the the actual video game, right?
Because whatever this one is, what is it gonna be called?
Because I want to make sure I can go back to the actual game after this nonsense. Here's the problem
Let's make sure it didn't fuck up
They still here. Oh, yeah, they're still here
You you see animals
People of course somewhere they'll be fine anybody up there any humans up there
Remember and anyone is welcome
Oh, yeah. Hey, we got another passenger
You know what? I mean when you see a new passenger
Oh, we've got quite a few passengers here, don't we?
How many?
Hmm
I'm gonna go too far
Because they might despawn if I go too far now that I think about that
Let's find out
Train's still there. Mm-hmm
Can't tell if it's still in there though
Don't worry. I'll take care of it after
They're still on the train
I'm gonna lead them back here
I wish I had better guns
We got here
Okay, quick quick quickly quickly
Let's go
Here's the thing though. I can't die
I gotta be very very aware of my health
If I die the whole thing is over
The train it hungers
Just i'm gonna see i'm gonna save after every major, uh
Soul gathering
One body pre well, we can deal with logistics later
You understand?
He dead we can set them up
later
Just gotta get enough people in it
one person per seat
One person and one animal per seat
What time is it like 11 o'clock eastern?
All right. I'm gonna give this until
But okay siri remind me in 20 minutes what my progress is on the soul train like the ghost train
All right
I'll sit here and feed it all day
It auto-aimed the horse's head. I didn't do that
Oh that hurts
What was that?
Fuck if only I had my other weapons
Bitch if only I didn't run my fucking horse over
Actually, this is pretty good. I'm not i'm okay with this
Take their weapons
Why did I not even think about that?
I have a lot of bodies to loot. That's for sure
Well, we're gonna test the power of the playstation 4. Can they fall out the windows? I don't think so
Now I need to get I need to get some big bulky animals in there. I'm talking big elk deer alligators
It's just noah's ark. Yeah, i'm not gonna cause any more trouble here. I'm gonna save and i'm gonna take off
Like from this place
Can you pick up the big animals not bears and everything
Yeah, i'm sorry for the for the next at least 30 minutes of this stream
I kind of have to do this though. This is the only opportunity i'm ever gonna have
I just dumped somebody's head
I heard somebody over here
Like turkeys these people are investigating. I was gonna go in there. Did you hear that?
Holy shit
You're lucky
You're lucky. We gotta move on from this stop
I do I do want to go. I do have to pick up a gun though. That's all right
Somebody's getting up
We're attracting
Like once you get on you're not allowed to get off
You know what he signed up for
I'm gonna attract so many
Bears are gonna come in here
Animals are gonna come over here. This is gonna be fucking so ridiculous if they stay here
I don't even need to go hunting. There's gonna be animals in here every single every five minutes
There's gonna be a bear will come in here
It's gonna be so many predators
I'm gonna get like eaten by a bear in the train
Mark my words
All right, we gotta get out of here one more guy down there and that's it. We're gonna move
Well, yeah, what happened in the old journal? You know the guy that used to run into people and laugh and scream
You sure you wanted that?
Be careful what you wish for
You know, you just might get it
More food for the fucking train
I'm about to see that guy knows it's that guy knows what's up. That guy doesn't have to become food
Well, maybe he does
Maybe he does
Wait, whose dog is this?
Why is there a dog in here?
Hey, what are you in here?
Get out of here
Technically, he's not in the train
He's not in the train yet
Get out of here
You need to get out of here
You need to don't step in this train
Out don't go in there
Don't go in there. I'm gonna tell you you're not gonna want to be in there
What the fuck? How did you get in? I don't perfect
I'm gonna pick him up
Get out of here. It's a oh, it's a fox
Well, what would happen?
That's everybody right?
Yep
Okay
Time to leave the station. Is the fox still there?
Hey get
Get excuse me. This is not gonna end well for you, man
Is he just gonna ride with me?
Okay
and so
The death train moves on to its next destination
He's not gonna fall off. I guess
He's just hanging out
I'm so concerned about him though
Well, is he gone?
Wait, wait, where is he? Where is he? Is he gone?
No, he's still there
Come to the next town
There's a witness investigating
Really? No
Where would that where would that be?
Save the game. Uh-huh
I can't
Here's the problem with this
I'll give you one issue
With a game save it doesn't matter
It's gonna put me leaning up against a tree somewhere
You all know it
Have I get followed by vultures?
You did you've survived that
Really?
Fucking bullshit
I gotta go
Mr. Fox
Full speed ahead. Oh the passenger is still in there
Why is this guy trying to keep up with me?
You cannot stop death
I can't feel the train here, man. It's too dangerous
I just gotta get out of here
Under the train right now. Why do I hear glass breaking?
There's so many police
They're just running into the train
They're sprinting into the train
They've lost all control
Holy shit
Oh my god
It calls to them
Almost all over the sky
And then we get up and just pick the blood
We've got a train to beat
Now they're freaking out. I'm now I just became a train
Nothing else
I don't have to move
I'm a train
Officer good evening
Whoa, hey
There's another train there's another train there's a train
Oh, no
I can't go
I'm gonna die
I can't move
Oh, it's over. It's over
I didn't work this fucking hard to have this happen
Two trains
I can't move this train won't move down
Here we go get the bodies. I I can't stick around there man. I gotta get out. I get a good way
There's a whole nother train of people over there. I'm just gonna transfer them to this one
You still there? Hey buddy. All right, how my core is doing?
I'm like running out of food
Can you hear the flies?
So yeah, we're just gonna transfer this is the transfer station
Are there people in here?
Come on
Okay, the conductor and put him in i'm gonna put him in the engine room
The fox just defended his territory
Reproducing
I'm gonna put him in the conductor seat with me. Can I even get him up there? I can't
Oh
He's defending I love the fact that this is his house now
A raccoon came over and he's like get out of here. This is my train
uh
I can study him again
Are there a bunch of passengers on here though for real?
That has to be right
Somebody would be taking the train
Is there nobody on here?
I don't think I can
What the hell is this guy doing here? He's guarding the train
well
Uh, sorry, I mean, I don't think you guard a train from the boiler room
Go get the engineer's hat
There there's another fox
He's died
He can't move his head is stuck. I gotta help him. How do I help him? How do I get him out of there?
Oh shit
Is he okay?
I think
Free him. I don't I don't know where he is. Which one is he under?
Oh, they're going through the train. They're going through the train now
Shit, I think that they're actually falling through the train when I pick him up like that
The corpses are just rotting out
I gotta be quick
Bodies decomposing
I I don't maybe not
I think it's because I picked him up and put him back down
All right. Hey, I need you to get out of the way
I gotta get to the front of the train
He's covered in blood. He's been eating them
Excuse me
Look at his face. Hold on. I got a perfect opportunity
For a fucking family photo
I can't okay. Here we go. I actually can't like get in a good spot because I can't crouch
I can't do handheld and crouched
That's bullshit. Why?
I can't really get the image that I want
That's so annoying I have to be like sloppily facing the right direction
He's inside inside the train
Is he though?
Oh, no, I don't make the rules. I can make an exception
Are we gonna move on to the next town? I guess I they're gonna start to despawn here
unless
No, there are no passengers on that
Let's go
We need fresh blood for a second. I thought I had the wrong train
A little bit settlement. It's not a major town
We're a bunch of animals. It's kind of fun
All right, you can cross
Found our place
Witness investigate
Are these are these lawyers? Are these if these are lawyers?
I got some more food for you
Hello
Watch out
Dinner's here
Don't you dare bite your dad?
Feed me Seymour. I don't like him being right here though. I feel like i'm gonna step on him. Okay, let's keep on
It might be time for a little bit of wildlife
Good spot for that though
Name the fox
Francis
Francis the fox
Why do you take another 10 to 15 people?
I i'm not gonna get out
Why there are like eight
Let's do it. I don't give a shit about the meat quality
Well, I hear something. I hear somebody running around
Oh, there's a house
What is this? I don't have time to like explore
One squirrel one squirrel and I don't I can't even drop them. I just put them in my pocket
Feed Francis i'm trying I just need
Well, here comes somebody
I think it's time to get some lawmen on me here. No tell on me
Bring it back to the train
That guy got up on me quick
Now don't drag him. Don't drag him
He's on a horse. Yeah, but
I don't think it's gonna be that fast
I'm not trying. Okay. Here we go. Here they come
Bring them on
All right, load them up. It's gonna take them forever to clean this train
Yes, it is. He's right there. Francis. He's fine
He just was saying hello
He was like, hey, how are you? How are you?
Are they still investigating?
Apparently not
Oh, they're coming from this direction now
Might have to put them down
I'd rather you come in here
Right next to the train. Perfect. I'm gonna start moving here
I need some poor refilling
Usually tame the fox. That's pretty cool. Actually this guy's falling out
re
Recalibrate this dude
You know some people speed run video games
Do it as fast as possible
some people
Spend a lot of time getting really good and get competitive
Some people are you know personalities and they don't look at all the things that they say and all the funny things that they do
I feel trained with bodies until my playstation crashes
Kind of coming to these terms here
More oh and they're fresh too a lot of people
Be careful. Oh shit
Still here. All right. Let me do some just general maintenance here
How's it doing clean it up? Come on. Hurry up
Well here the real kicker here is to try to see if this works
is
it's
Then you might not be able to have more than like 50 to 30 to 50 or something bodies on the screen at the same time
And it'll be a thing where they just actually despawn
But i'm willing to give it a try
Right here the game is starting to hate this
But what point will they turn us off? You know what I mean? At what point does it not do I not get to do it anymore?
When is the game actually sick of my shit completely?
That's the real question. I think that's it. No, there's one more down here
Save the game save saving the game is not going to do anything
Because when you save a game
It just when you load that save it puts you
Oh, like you just woke up at a camp
Nearby it doesn't it's not like a state that you're saving. It's the time that you're saving
Oh, it's starting to hang
Starting to hang
That's how you know, we're getting there
Hey little boy all aboard. Let's go
What was the point of this again, uh to try to crash the game?
Or to see how many people I can fit in the train
Be either one we're about to make it to micah
people
Anybody in there?
I don't think so. I don't see anybody in there
I'm not even an animal, but you have to hunt the animals like the people come to you
This is actually pretty cool
This looks great
Ass on the mini back. Yeah, i'm being followed right now by even the monster
I just think i'm gonna gas
Gas well, you know what I mean. I mean like can this thing burn out all the coal
It's up throwing bodies in there
Where are we at now?
This looks like animal territory
I think it's time to put in some animals
How far north are we right now? We're okay. We're about to reach back around here to forward
I guess
We'll see where it takes us
Try putting bait in the body room. Well, aren't they already just it's a bunch of bait there already
We're taking the scenic route
I don't see any exes gone. I don't think they they're decomposing
What I can tell you is I can't tell you
This is the same as it did before
I wonder if there's a finite actually a lot of time
30 minutes 20 minutes an hour
Why not they might just be an entity that's like an asset that's there forever
I would assume when you move 100 yards 200 yards that way
And that would be
What's the joke I don't have a plan here
The plan is just fill it
Until it doesn't fill me
I don't have another that's that's it
I mean
I'm imagining a scenario
Where they never do some
And it is just
Stuffed with bodies on top of each other
Have to come to another town
Here's the stop let's see if anybody's here
It's a little late. I think
I don't think anybody is here
On we go
Don't fall off this
Box is still there hanging up
Here comes the fort i'm gonna get a lot of bodies here
harvesting
Yeah, pretty much
All right camp
I could probably get
Is there anybody at that camp?
Because I could just dump them over the edge and pick them up later
I mean there's a horse there
No, i'm not worth it
Not enough
This was Thanos's original plan
Uh, this is absolutely gorgeous though
I've been driving through so many beautiful things that I feel like i'm about to take me in
Still not really
I mean
Wallace station is up here
We'll probably get 10 to 20 more bodies at Wallace station
By the way, I I am so committed to this at the moment that
I i'm not going to stop this stream
Until it's satisfying
You understand
If you put if it's been this long already
You have to see it through
Could I right now be like oh it's kind of interesting. Oh, well
Yeah, it doesn't move on
No
What?
It's been like an hour and 30 minutes of doing this at least
What's the end game for Francis? I don't know
He's currently my
My co-conductor right now. I don't want him in that
Coming up on the town
Let's see if we can't pull a few more people
Actually, i'm gonna go all the way around with my horse
cp 985
The never-ending train
Can you actually befriend the fox? I don't think you can
Does anybody know how many people are actually on the train right now?
And I would say
15 25
No, just one just one
counting the fox
No, i'm not counting the fuck
It's probably like I bet you there's like 16 people
All right, let's roll in
rolling in
to
Wallace station
Please watch the doors on the left
entering
Wallace station
Check for your belongings
So I think it has been confirmed. I think part of that long
Journey there in between bodies going in
Uh, I think I believe that they're not going to these ones because they probably would have already
Oh, I can't pick him up. He's too big for me to pick up
Is he too big?
Shit, he's too big. Oh, well the train will eat it one way or another. That's true
I really don't
Whoa. Hey, hey
Looks like he's coming anyways
the train
Will take him
He's in
And welcome
To our next stop
Howdy
You're waiting for the train
Unfortunately, you picked the wrong train to get ready for
Have a nice day
Oh, yeah, come on man down here
Excuse me, francis
Excuse me
Fucking hell
There they come. All right. What do I got for cores? Am I good?
Can you use a little bit more did I i'm gonna have to craft some meat or something man
It's like all I got
Now we wait. No, I already I have meat. You're right. Come on in. Uh, oh, that's not a good sign
Where the law man? Let's go
I'm waiting for you. I'm here from the west
All right. Here they come. Let us will you use the cover?
three of them
more now
Nine feet. Let's go
Ah got coming in too hot
Just bulky ass elk in the way
I don't think I can go up this way anymore
No, I can't he's he's blocking that entrance
Take the lady's hat
You got it. I don't want to step on you. You need to be in a better splay. Yeah, get out of the way
I don't want to step on him
francis
All right. It's getting to a point where I can't walk through here
I can't i'm getting stuck. It's getting to the point where I can't stay in here
I gotta go through the back
I gotta go from the other side of the train
I won't be able to go in there anymore. Can I even get up from the other side? Are there stairs back here?
I think so
One two three make a count here. I got four more to put in
We actually have to keep track at this point because they might start despawning
There's definitely more than three
francis
I
Last guy there's so many people here
There's too many
Are there less x's? Oh no
They're despawning
No
So I here's what happened. Do you guys want to know the sad thing that happened here?
So the game because these are still actual npcs, right? What happened was
And I knew it was worth testing. We're trying to find out
it
There's only a certain amount of npcs that are like allowed
right
So once it gets to the point where there's too many npcs on the screen
It starts to remove them
Because it needs to make room for the other npcs that i'm calling in
But that doesn't mean we're not gonna have fun with the people that are here
So just let me get them in the right spot. I'm gonna put them all in the same spot
I'm gonna put dynamite down there
We're hitting the entity limit here
Oh, that's the joke
Well, the joke was I wonder how many people I can fit on the train
And I don't even know if it was necessarily a joke
Just wanted to see what would happen felt like doing it
so
Let's get them all
In one spot here
That's fine
Try putting them in a seat. I don't I really wonder what's gonna happen here though
There are quite a few people on here
I think it'll crash here
What the fuck somebody just sprinted by the right side of the screen. Was that my shadow? I don't even know
Oh god, they're starting to move. It's starting to become too much. They're starting to be mailed into one person
Oh boy
Okay, hurry up. Come on. Somebody's still alive down there. What the fuck
Jesus
This is this is demonic this is somebody said this is
That guy came from the ceiling
No, wrong way. It's almost like i'm pulling them from underneath
Oh, that guy is stretchy
You can always tell when they start to get all stretchy. This is now here comes the problem
I'm right here somewhere right here. It's quite the bear bait
Not yet, i'm gonna make sure they're right in the right pile because a couple of them are not in the boy
This is demonic
Okay. All right
There's only like one more person over here. I think
francis
Stay back
Where's this last one? I think this one on top of the train
Jesus
That guy's stuffed under upside down
All right, this is no this guy right here
Here we go
I don't even have I don't even have dynamite. They're despawning. Oh, shh. No, don't burn
No
Hey whisper
You didn't even have anything on you. Did you?
Don't worry. It was only a nightmare
Oh, all right
So what um, what the hell were we doing? All right, I was gonna reload the game
Damn, I wish I had died just didn't realize I didn't have dynamite. That was unfortunate
Was that worth it?
Let me kind of to see if it was possible
All right. So this is 2250. That's the autosave
21 41
I think this is it right?
You knew the rule
You were on the train
Yeah, so this is uh, this is the one
That was some pretty good stalling. You can hear the depression in his voice. You can I like really
I at least wanted to do dynamite there
I guess
That's my own fault for not looking through my inventory first
I demand a one. No, that was like almost and that was two hours. No, that wasn't that long
Let's redo it on pc when the body count gets to be higher
Do I have any soup left? No, that's gone. I was gone a while ago
That's before the first body went on the train
That was a third of your stream. I just joined at four hours when you started
225 bounty
What wrong save that's okay. So which one is it then this one?
The course of true love 36, but why would I get why did the tenth of a percent come from
It's one of these two. Uh, this is okay. I manually saved so it's 21 29
So it was one of these two. I guess it could just be this one
Yeah, I blame the oak
Well, thanks for um
Thanks for taking that journey with me everybody
Sorry, it didn't uh end the way that we all wanted but
It was worth it. It was worth taking the trip
I think
It was a fitting rp ending
ritual suicide
God
So where the hell am I now?
so
this was
What how much money do I got 14 13?
45 bounty sounds about right
You ain't scaring nobody. Oh, this is where the try. I this is where I I thought so long ago
I forgot I forgot about the train going back and forth a bit
This is where it all began. You're right
all right, um
Let me I need to go back to town the thing that I was supposed to do a long time ago
Look out god. It's I i've played the game in like two hours
I'm like trying to think about putting these people on on the train. That's like all I know
Where the hell is he is he in the stable?
You ever let this horse feed
I got space for you. Oh, let's bring out sonic
Yeah, let's give it a a good a good package. Absolutely
good decision
The autoslave side already contains the course of do you want to override? Yes, I do
Let's do this mission and then we'll see where we're at. It's been about six and a half hours so far
Let's see where we're at at the end of this mission here
Rename the horse to francis. No, I have to go get a new francis
You know what i'm saying? I'm not just I I can't just rename this guy. I have to tame a new horse name of francis
How many horses are you allowed to have at the moment? I can have four
Four total
That might increase later. I don't know random encounter. Well, I guess a snake bite
You good
Just tried that plan over there
He was like a gunshot
oh
From the one with the paint flowers
tiny little bastard
steer clear
Thanks, mister
I owe you my life some things you learn the hard way. Yeah
You can
You can say that again
Only the sage is a poisonous herb use it in the crafting to apply poison to weapons like throwing knives and arrows
Menus
Vomit ability unlocked well, I can craft poison
Ah too bad
I was thinking I was gonna puke off the horse
I'm not gonna feed it to the horse. What are you talking about?
gonna be evil
Why the poison?
I don't need poison for anything right now
Feed it to somebody else's horse. I don't think i'm going to do that
Well, I don't know why you guys want me to poison somebody's horse
Killed 50 people and put them on a train and you're worried about being evil
That I didn't do that the fucking monsters in my head did
The demon possessing me made me do that. I didn't do that
Although there is let's see what this is
The demon possessing me made me do it
What what are you talking? What i'm in like a cut scene with this guy why?
uh
They won't leave him alone. I can't stop this
I'm not holding down l2
It's trying to go into a cut scene with him
That train sound is like
Kind of freaking me out
It's back
What if I get it? Can I get it on the horse?
I can't escape this guy
Yeah, i'm permanently locked onto this guy
from any angle
I have to kill him. No. No, I need to see how this plays out
I can't kill him
I want him to get on a horse
I can't get on the horse
Like and here's the train
The train calls to me. It's calling me
I gotta find a cliff to jump off. I gotta somehow find a cliff to jump off of
Get me to i'm gonna go on the top of a mountain
Oh, wait, no, i'm still am i'm i'm locked
No, the jump canceled it. No, I think I got just too far away
He he probably despawned
He probably de-spawned unfortunately for us
Come on, here we go
The train commands it. No, I can't never mind. All right onto this we'll do this last mission
And then we'll call it night because it is getting late
I just want a backhanded hammer fist to punch somebody in the face
Just like burn
You think all this lemon air is free
Oh, that's a you're done that was a that was a guy that was
Horse, hey
Did I tell you guys that I can't whistle when I was younger?
uh my parents we had a dog and
You know my parents house
Hold on francis
Yep
francis
No
I think it was somebody else's dog
uh, but
so I don't know how to whistle like
I could do it for like a tenth of a second like so I used when you called your dog, you know, like oh like
Come here
I would go who who?
Who owl I found an owl perfect timing apparently
well
but I I
I
I seriously used to say who who to call my dog. I just don't know how to whistle
What why what are we angry at up here? Oh bounty hunters
Come on. Yeah bounty hunters
bounty hunters
I don't care. Shoot me. It'll not stop me
He hasn't been the same since the train i'm telling you I know
That's why you I just can't go off the rails in these games because then it's all I know
I can't I i'm trying to go back to let's go to dutch and
Let's get a mission. No, I just
Where was it? I didn't see it. Oh, it's you
It's arthur. I thought it was a welcome back arthur. That was a random encounter
Now that was a funny voice
Well, yeah, you know funny voices is what I do on this channel
Oh
Funny voices i'm gonna put that in my twitter bio
Funny voices look at all the stuff we have
online media
Thank you. Thank you
So let me donate this stuff and take my cut
Do a funny homer bart simpson voice
I don't have I don't I don't know how to do that. All right, what's my cut? I got diamonds here, man
Where's the diamonds?
Did I sell them already?
There's nothing I didn't buy
Let's eat some food. What do you say?
cooked flaky fish
Do a spee voice the spee i'm not doing the spee voice guys
i'm sorry
This is the final mission of the night
and then
You may you got a lot on you may see me tomorrow as well
But there's a couple things I need to do
I might just I might take a break from red dead
We'll try something else tonight
Oh, we might lead into this or we'll see I don't know colored foe
They said there's a gang of fools holed up in the swamps east. I might just play this again. I don't know never ended
I might not stream tomorrow. I don't know raising in these fools minds 30 years later
That ain't my point
These ignorant fools are weapon dealers
And in their dealings sometimes sit on a decent pile of cash. Oh, no, no
I've been selling weapons to cuba and south america for years
I'm I'm absolutely not the old boy. I was talking to reckon there might be a bunch of cash just sitting around
and failing that
Maybe a nice stash of weapons with just a bunch of crazies gardening. Exactly. Well
Worth taking a look at least isn't it? That was my thinking said it was at some place called shady bear
Why does everybody want me to do this? Okay
I just go
Shmeek like that's it. That's that was like the comedy routine like four years ago. I was hoping you'd be in
If that's how they told it
He did it he did it this way all right, let's take off remember that one
Remember I did that four years ago
Well, that's not how I'm I think some of them harangued me and saty when we were coming back with supplies
Mrs. Apple star wars team
It seems like it is these boys got a manner about
But I haven't necessarily noticed all respect mr. Morgan you wouldn't notice
Might call you a nigger lover. They see us riding like this
But most of it is uh, my dog is a glance or a word
And after that you can't whistle but you can do that. No, I can't
Out west is out. I cannot is out west
And you're all who you are
decent folks
Some places down here they judge different
Yes, it can't be so easy for you Lenny
Sorry, you're caught up in this
Well, we demand more. I guess their gold still shines. Oh, there's no more and their guns still shooting
I just played a sound clip by I queued it up and I played it and every one of these bastards for all they got
Okay
Plus it beats being lynched back in black water with all of you by my side
I guess it does
More voices needed
Feels like we're close. It's a rundown old plantation house down in the bayou somewhere
Let's take it slow because
If like you say makes up for no whistle sitting on weapons
It's called sitting here just playing a video game of course and just doing that
They say it fine back before streaming and youtube and everything guys I used to sit here and do the same shit I do now
I can see the recto
See that church up ahead they're supposed to use it as an outpost
Just I was considering like making noises
Okay
I was always watching
Imagine getting caught up in a fight like yeah
I was already here
Well old content. I've already seen this. I already took the stuff from here
Hitman 2 comes out in three days. Look around there's so much out coming out
It doesn't look like anyone's here. We don't know that for sure
Let's have us a nosy
Hear that
Someone's on the track. I was already here. I came here too early
Look there a wagon. Let's see where
He's gone
You're on me now right behind
No, don't do it. It's the last mission
Hey ellen war
He could turn off at any time should we move up on him? Yeah
Did I lose?
I think I lost
Between the tree
I know this place
Okay, springfield rifle without the scope on it
You're real tough. Hey, it's getting late big plantation house must be shady bear
It is getting late up there off the trail
Once it gets to be above midnight 12 12 30 eastern time. It's time to call it a night. Come on
We can get a view on them from that wall up there. Make sure you bring the sharp shooter
I got it
I can't see
Oh now I can't
Maybe I should have the other rifle then
No, this thing's fine. Do you see anything? Yes
Yes
Is my internal clock adjusted almost a militia
Uh, it is at this point. Yeah
It's been pretty good. You got men covering the house
Gatling gun up there too. Well, they got that house locked down real tight
You got men everywhere off near the porch
Hey, you might want to look over to the right. I haven't seen anything worth shooting the stealer
I know. I know. I just wanted to see if I could see him. All right some tans
Or you could go down there acting friendly with these folks just draw them into one spot
I'll start shooting might be the dumbest idea i've ever heard but hey i'm always up for a performance
Well the tuba desk are done
Who's shooting?
What the fuck is going on?
Okay, lenny, uh
The dynamite's more fun
Lenny don't blow up got him. Hold on. Don't do anything yet. He's gonna get charged again
It's so hard to aim this stick
Holy shit
All right, get me out of the scope
Take the scope off
Give me my keyboard and give me my mouse back
Oh fuck that didn't hit him. What else we got?
Front door open up
That was crazy
They might be on the way now. Let's grab something to get out grab something search the area for weapons
There might be guns in these wag. Oh, what about the gatling gun?
This could be promised
What do you got here come on
We can sail those right we sure can we'll check the rest later now come on let's go
This uh, can we remove the dynamite off this thing? I don't think I want the dynamite
Is this a scenario where any little bump will cause a problem?
I'm doing it. I'm trying to go as fast as I can
Shoot the dynamite the turbo boost
Something tells me that's not gonna work
What's a black feller doing coming out of shady bell
In one hour wagon, you see
We already dropped a bunch of your people to get this wagon
You're gonna make us drop the three of you as well
The heart the brain
And ahead
I can't see anyone chasing us. How do you get I are three
We did it let's move
The heart the brain
We'll see what we do I might take a little break tomorrow
Depends who know I could just wake up and want to do it again
But ever since we've gotten internet back
Well, let's rephrase that ever since the internet has been gone
It's really the only thing we've been focusing on every day since two weeks ago. Okay
There's still a lot of other random shit that needs to get done
So I might take tomorrow to do some of that and when I get done with it might be i'll turn the stream on
I'm, just glad i've been able to stream for three straight days four straight days in a row without any major problems. So that's
That's good. Good news. I think
When's the green screen plan the green screen is planned?
For at some point over this weekend
And if not this weekend, then either
I would assume monday or tuesday of next week
the terms, uh
Just based on studio time
I'll have a clear answer for you in the next probably day or two
I still have my la noir save
I don't think I do
You can
Hey you too
Are they cloud safe bolt action rifle is now available to modify it because you now own it
All right. Cool
So let me just
I think it's pretty good time to stop
And that is where we're going to stop
Right here. But yeah, I don't I get to check on the la noir thing. See if I can pick up where I left off
oh
boy
So, uh la not la no more red dead red and if I stream tomorrow
It probably won't be red dead. I might change my mind, but we'll probably pivot to something else
Tomorrow is wednesday, right?
technically, well, yeah
well for it's 9 30 right now pacific, but
So tomorrow's technically wednesday. So
I might give myself a day to get to get the green screen situated for the weekend
And then come back on thursday
Or wednesday night
We'll see like I said, I don't really have a schedule right now
So i'm trying to figure that out as we speak
But thanks everybody for sticking around
I will see you all very very soon
Thanks again for watching red dead is a wonderful game
Uh highly recommend so let's go ahead and do the bits while they're here, you know
Let's go back a while here back to here
had
200 bits two bucks from ivory
Thank you ivory for the two dollars
Hey germa has
It's been a hot while since I caught your live stream due to job searching and european trips
That said I always enjoy the videos that get posted on your second channel and i'm so happy to see wall dad finally posted
Special thanks to holy mac then can't wait to see more of the funny man
Also side question. Have you voted yet or can you not do that now that you are in nevada?
well
Uh for the purposes of uh political stuff
We don't talk about politics on this stream. That's a very very important rule
And unless we're uh, unless we're
We make a joke
He can't do it because he's a convict
Yeah, you know, I mean I did got you like arrested nine times so
I'm actually coming to you from a federal prison right now
so
To answer the first part here
I am very glad to see wall dad as well because that was that's one of my favorite games of the year
Little boys can't vote. Oh my god. It's francis in jail, too
Uh
No, but thank you, dude
Thank you bro. Luck for the five dollars. I'm very poor and I don't have much money
German doesn't know politics enough that yes, I voted. Well, okay. No, I did not vote. There you go
And i'll tell you one reason why because the move
I didn't have like an opportunity
To go register in nevada
so
Sorry
There's been a lot going on. I just didn't have an opportunity to
I am registered to vote in
Massachusetts still so literally satan
I actually was going to do it. I think you could do it. There's like a way you could have done it or something. I just
There's been so much bullshit going on here
The whole internet thing moving in here. I just it was something that I just couldn't even think
but hopefully
All of you have a voice to your opinions
Because it is important at least if you know
talking about the american election stuff
and the candidates for nevada, too, that's another thing like I
Just need I haven't I don't like know the area. I don't know the people
I bet he voted for dean dingus
I wrote in germa
Oh god
but I I am planning on
being uh
Registered
But there's other reasons why?
For do not get political, uh, because I don't like to talk about it on the stream. Like I said
um
I don't know. I can't really talk about it as to why like i'm
I haven't like voted
It's understandable the tough thing with politics is
No, no, no, no, no, wait, whatever
It would be impossible to explain some of these things without
Somehow making somebody angry and that's kind of sad. I think in the current political spectrum
He wants to talk about it so bad
No
He didn't vote because he's not actually american
No, we'll just move on
That is actually something that i'm gonna try to get done here though is to like register in nevada
But we'll move on
Anywho
Thank you to
um
Div usp. Thanks for the three bucks. No message. Thank you
Just the last couple of nights div usp has just given money. Thank you
A burger. Thank you burger b for the five dollars here burger b. Thank you turbo heart to you
Dungeness. Thank you dungeness for the one dollar. Hey germa a couple of people in discord and I worked on this for a few days straight
And I was hoping you could play it on stream
A few sleepless nights were had to try to get this out before you started streaming again
Your move is very close to home
for me because
I'm going to be moving to from oregon to new zealand
For a university in a couple months and i'll be there for the next eight years at least damn
That's a long time
uh
Yeah, well, we'll watch it
We'll watch let's watch it at the end but good luck with the move. That's a that's a long ways, man
It's very far away
Hopefully that is very smoothly go smoothly for you. Okay, except just going from
massachusetts to nevada was
Fucking painful so I can imagine going from oregon to new zealand will be tough. So good luck to you
And we'll play it at the end of the stream
Uh wild fox. Thanks for the one dollar. Thank you for what you said on my ten dollar bits the other night
I'm doing my best in your infectious laugh does wonders
How is life treating you in vegas now that you settled in a little bit?
um
Settling in nicely. I think the last three or four days
Especially the last probably four or five days
Has really let me breathe a little
Because it's been three weeks straight of
Just kind of bullshit on top of bullshit
That I haven't really had much time
To myself
And not time my time to myself. I mean
It's there's been something going on every day that needed 100 of my attention
and now
I can kind of just chill now as as of probably today or yesterday
so thankfully it's
Time to take a breather
Step back and actually enjoy and understand like where I am
So the the moving process went through all the internet you I wish I could even describe
Just how painful that internet process was
We would have to sit here
And wait for a technician to show up
Nine technicians have come over here
three supervisors
It's been every day
We've been doing it every single day. It's the only thing we've been thinking about and doing
And they they told us they finally figured it out. So
Uh, but then just trying to figure out when like the trash comes and
Where things are it's it's a throwing yourself into a brand new thing that you've never seen or done before
It's very i've never done it before it's actually never happened
This is the first time in my whole life that i've just kind of thrown myself into a completely different place
and something you don't realize when you do that is
Everything starts from scratch
Everything so I mean my whole life
literally everything everything i've ever done everything i've ever said everything i've ever been was massachusetts
And you start to realize all the little things that just don't follow you here
It's a brand new fresh start
and it's equally parts refreshing and
um
Kind of nerve-wracking too
I love it out here though. I think it's great
His debt can't get him now
It's okay germ I lived here in texas my entire life and I still don't know where the trash comes
uh
But it's been wild and i'm i'm finally happy just to be able to get kind of off the ride for a little while
And get back to what I was doing
which was this
and
Being able to at least even enjoy
Anything else besides?
Okay, so i'm gonna get a new insurance. I don't have health insurance right now. I've been having like weird medical problems
I need health insurance, but how long does that take?
I gotta get like a letter of termination from my other insurance. Okay. No, I don't have health insurance though
Okay, but what about like other? Okay. I gotta pay the rent. Okay. Hold on but uh
What's what day is it? I don't have a couch. We need to go get a soap. We don't have any furniture
I can only fit so much in my moving thing
It's been like that every fucking day
But we're good now
All everything's gravy
Thank you gaga pudding for the two bucks
I'm just popping in here to give you a couple bits. I'm glad you move went well
And I hope you didn't hit too many squirrels
Well, I was in an airplane. So that would have been really weird
Bullwinkle would have been really upset if if we had hit a squirrel in the ear. Let's just say that
Uh, thank you lazy luke for the three dollars. I already asked before you move
But can I make your ideas of something fun with the end of the stream subs?
I would try my best
Yeah, I think i'd like to get some input
From a lot of different people to see like what would be fun to do and what would be even possible to do
Whatever the possibilities are
I would love to see them
So, I mean i'll be around the discord
I'll probably be talking about i'll probably bring it up at some point in the discord
And maybe talk to some of the mods about
Maybe try to figure out something fun to do
suggestion wise
But thank you lazy luke
And yeah, I I will probably
I'll put up more a cleaner forum than just like general chat
Uh gaga pudding. Thank you again for two dollars. Hey, it's me again
I hope you didn't hit any flying squirrels either. They're a fierce bunch. Well, there you go
There's the flying squirrel
Flying squirrel bit
Thank you gaga
Uh macle grunt. Thanks for the one dollar kill him do it. I don't know who you're referring to. Hopefully I didn't
hopefully
waved at him
Gaga pudding again. Thanks for five dollars gaga pudding
Hey, jeremy never mind the squirrels this time. I remember when I first saw your shme videos and I thought they were hilarious
So I sold them showed them some of my friends in school and only got blank stares
That's when I realized that I had found something special
Thanks, dude
Uh, i've already told you the story about how I showed that girl the auto video and then she like
Literally did not want to talk to me anymore
Sounds about right
Kxc, thank you for the five dollars kxc
Just put the old guy out of his misery. Oh dear
Garfield the monday killer. Thanks for the one dollar. I made this for you a while ago jerma. It's you and your trusty balloon buddy
Liam
Like helium, but his name is liam and i clever
Please don't ban me
Um, there's only one person that I knew in the balloons and I don't know what happened to him
That's a very that's a beautiful balloon
That's a beauty
Thank you garfield
I did not
Thank you dan boss for the one dollar. No message. Thank you
Cool cool g1. Thanks with three bucks. Hey jerma. Can you take your shoes off, please?
I don't have any shoes on right now, but thank you though
Thank you ifs for the one dollar. Hope you're doing. All right jerma
Just want you to know that these comeback streams really have been keeping me sane through this rut i've been in
Uh, you truly are a saint
I also just want to apologize for my drunkenness the other night
Also when you start watching jojo, I want a synopsis on each stream of what episode you watched
Okay
But apologies from the other what happened the last night?
What happened the other night?
You didn't come I didn't notice anything strange
But thank you also for your two dollars here ifs
Uh, I see you did a little recreation of d4c love train. I'm glad that you support
our
We don't talk we don't talk politics on here. Thank you
Is that a jojo thing?
Thank you pilot guy for the five dollars pilot guy
There are some bits for the soul train
Thank you
much appreciated
Uh wild her buddy. Thanks for the one dollar. Can't think of anything funny to say you were a fucking psycho on this stream
I'm gonna go to bed tomorrow. It's tomorrow now. Thank you
Thank you. Thank you reaper for the one dollar. Hey jerma want the best free horse in the game? Yeah
Um
I'm not I don't want to read any spoilers
appreciate the
Appreciate the tip, but I don't I don't want to know
Thank you. Thank you alpha x prime. Thank you alpha prime for the one dollar
Varian thanks for the one dollar much of love from general three
From the discord. Thank you
Varian
Appreciate it
Uh deus morta. Thanks for the one dollar. Hey jerma been watching since swat four
swat four
Now we haven't done that yet. Love you stream. My state of michigan just legalized weed. Can't wait for the green screen stream
Well, there you go
Uh, we haven't done swat four yet though
swat four
Star and I were gonna play swat four, but it's the all you can't play it online
You have to do like weird shit. We were trying to figure it up
But the state of michigan is legalized weed
Hell, yeah
Hey garfield of undead killer. Thanks for the one dollar
uh, you never guess who
Who I heard from francis the fox contacted me after you burnt yourself to death
He got you a postcard from the ghost ghost soul train. He told me to tell you i'm keeping the train full of souls for you
If you ever feel like coming back
Miss you, don't forget to write
You got any nice words for francis?
Getting political. No, is that that's I we don't talk about politics
Marijuana is legal in las vegas. It is completely
I don't smoke marijuana. I don't
But I know the medical
And recreational purposes for it
I mean i'm not gonna get political
That's like okay. But all right. First of all saying that you're in favor of marijuana use
Is as if that's barely even a political statement anymore
That's not that's like not even political anymore
It's just an opinion at this point
No politics. I know I
Sometimes I wish we could just talk politics like very very like just
Plainly insanely, but it's not it's not possible
Everybody's so different. Everybody has so many different views that it's just it's impossible
I don't know. I mean like not that I do but i'm just saying like something like
it's hard
because
I mean there are people that are here, right? Let's just say that there is you know, two three thousand people there and I say something
And I say something that I that I believe right?
It just it's it's always going to just cause a problem
Even if the thing that I think would be I believe in you know, I just it's just hard you can't
It's not impossible. People just need to be more willing to listen to others
Yeah
Yes
Yeah, yes
Political parties. Yeah, I mean like yes, that's all I can say. Yes
We're willing to listen to your opinions as long as you don't support bubzy 3d
Yes
The only thing is people are very dynamic
and
Yes
That's it
How could you say something like that?
Yes, that's it
I agree with that
Who should I vote for? Yes
I honestly don't want to know germans political views. I've already had artists and entertainers
I admire tarnished in my eyes by knowing their views and I'd rather that not happen with me
Yeah, I don't I just don't want I don't want that either
I don't think any of the things that I believe are
That out of the ordinary or that
crazy or anything
I like to try to think as myself is
just
try to look at issues rationally and
I don't think there's anything I could ever really say that would be like, whoa
What the fuck did he just say?
I don't think so
That's what everyone thinks about their own beliefs. That's why they believe it. That's true. That's you know, that that's completely 100 true
Stop before you regret no, I would never i'm not i'm not gonna say
Very much at all. So don't worry
The only reason why it's even brought up in the first place is because like today was the day
So that's the only reason why it's even brought up in the first place
I can't believe how level-headed this guy is. I haven't even like made any opinions. I've said yes
and
That's all i've said
This guy said yes
but anywho
Um, it's just because today was the day
And some people have questions and opinions and and I get it like people want to know
Hey, I I did this. I I voted you voted and what what did you vote for and it's like
You know just
It is today was the day of all these um
changes in seats and stuff so
Makes sense as to why people
wanted to know
Thanks for the one dollar
Excited for you to get back to la noir, although I don't know if you're what your plan probably will be for the save
I don't know if you can download a save for the ps4 or download for the pc and download a save there
Because with a 100 save you can access all the cases or just play it on your own your choice
I'll have to see how that I didn't get that far in la noir. So I don't think it'll be that much of a problem
But thank you, dude
Thank you chubby funster for the one dollar. Thanks for streaming these three days in a row
It's been great that train bit was amazing really needed this after a scary morning
I was going into my room to make some business calls worth millions when I suddenly see and I shit you not the biggest spider
I've ever seen
I slowly left my from saying that spider is fucked the spider now owns my room when I sleep in the bath. Thanks, dude
I was waiting for one. I was waiting for one to show up
Thanks with millions
Shoot man. Thank you shoot man for the one dollar keep up the good work my dude
I'm currently finishing my undergrad at university and i'm thinking of doing a masters
Your streams always give good vibes and it makes studying fun. I had a dream comcast never turned off your internet
And you kept streaming for a month straight
You stayed in the house when new tenants moved in and living in the walls never stopping the stream
The tenants were trying to investigate random snorting noises like it was a ghost
I'm glad that's not real
Thank you shoot man
Uh, thank you hippo rider for the one dollar. Hey germa want to know your thoughts on fallout 76 and doom eternal
Also, love your content helped me through so many very tough times
I don't really I don't have any opinions on either of them
The only opinions the only things I know about fallout 76 are that like the game just like didn't work
I don't have any opinions on it. I just saw my twitter feed was exploding of like fallout 76 is broken and sucks
I can't play it
There's always problems. I don't I don't have any opinions because I didn't do it. So
Political fallout feels
But thank you
Uh, I don't sorry. I don't have an opinion for you
Thank you deus mortay for the one dollar. I meant to say police quest swat not swat four
Oh, right, right, right the fmv game. That's right
Thank you though deus
Thank you dark soul for the one dollar
abnormality for the five dollars
Right now
Oh me. Oh my oh
Floyd come and welcome our boy. The balloon is down the internet up put some dunkin in your cup
Welcome back. Welcome home. Remember to leave politics alone
Say an opinion any opinion
Reese's is the best fucking candy
And I eat full Hershey bars
I'm the weirdo
I'm the serial killer that eats just the regular default Hershey bar
I'm the one guy that you've heard of
Burn him. All right. What do you say? We get the credits going while I set the video up
Thank you to all of the new subs and old subs. You guys are amazing
Take care everybody all of you
Let me get this video set up
while we watch the
list of people
Twizzlers or red vines of both of them are disgusting
I think licorice is the biggest scam in the history of the world. I'd rather eat toothpaste flavored candy
Licorice is awful
I don't even think they make it anymore
actually moron
Toothpaste tastes good
triangle or rectangle sandwich slices rectangle
Left or right twix
They're both the same
You've been led to believe that they're different
from
lobbyists
Being on payday bars
Go back to 1992
Mayo or mustard mix them together add a little sugar and you got yourself a sauce
Put the peanut butter or the jelly on top
Disgusting jelly out peanut butter and fluff fluff goes in. Excuse me
And you're on garlic you should eat garlic all the time. It's great for you
Okay, so democrat or republican, uh, well
Ah, he almost he almost had me with that little in between
Man, I used to love your content, but then you said licorice was bad. You've changed man
Never give your opinions again
Just know I like want everybody
To be I want everyone to be happy, but it's impossible. I want I want
both twixes to be happy
I want
Twizzlers to go out of fucking business
And for their factory to go under
You know, I want everyone to be happy
my dad's business
My dad's business
Oh, I love it. By the way, thank you everybody for subbing
I am just like fucking around now, but
Let's watch
Uh the video here
Say a couple minutes
Twizzlers aren't bad. They're fine. I gotta get the right
image here
Where is it? There it is and then make sure I can actually hear it
Jeremy you're my first twitch sub ever and you've responded to my messages. Thank you
if I can catch him by
You know look
I tell I keep saying this every stream eventually you're gonna be the guy that I respond to you're gonna be the guy the one guy
Whatever you say, I i'm gonna read it eventually
Let's watch this
Is this you made this song?
That sonics gone
Louder
You better not know me here
Fucking lady
Wasting the voice you play
The stream discord reminds me of those streams long ago
The chat I get yesterday
Yesterday
This is actually sad
I stole my chat
Oh there he is
I showed it on stream. I showed it on stream
It's so nice it was so
It was so awesome until
I couldn't I couldn't get rid of it. I didn't know what it was
That was a whole song
Is he crying? Is he crying? Let's prove it not crying. Look look
See i'm not crying. I'm fine red eyes
And I know I know a lot of sync. I know I am don't worry. I'm aware of it
So that's it
Thank you for that video, by the way
it was very touching and
Get out get off get out of here
Not you me
Uh right at the end here. We had abnormality gave five dollars
Oh me. Oh my that's oh, we already did that one. I don't know why it's showing up here as it was right now
Uh, but there was z niner gave fifteen dollars
Fifteen bucks from z niner. Thank you so much
Hey german, I see you finally back at it with streaming. Glad you're moving smoothly despite internet problems. I actually have a question
What happened to exoskeleton bug millennium boy? Uh, did he finally?
Go away, or does he still?
Also, how I had a dream a few weeks back where you played the gta 5 spider-man mod and selected a
Skin of an alternate spider-man. You didn't know who it was. So you called him spider-man jex
Then you laughed and I woke up
Well exoskeleton bug millennium boy is um, he's he's doing just fine. I have a question cheese nips or republican
All right, good night everybody I might see you tomorrow if not, then i'll see you very soon
I'll let you know
Take care
Have a great evening much love to y'all signer. What time you say? Oh, sorry
What time are you setting the susto to I would just set it to maybe tomorrow
Like oh you maybe today, you know, something like that. Maybe
I have some things I need to get done around the house. So
If I get them done quickly and early then for sure i'll be back
Take care