Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some super meat boy. That's right. I'm gonna start this on the channel.
I'm probably gonna play through the entire thing. Not in one sitting, not in this video, but I'm probably gonna try and do each chapter will be a different episode.
So some episodes might be 20 minutes, 25 minutes. Some episodes might be like 40 minutes. I'm not sure. I don't know how I'm gonna break it up yet.
But I think I want to break it up per chapter. Now the reason why I decided to do this, mainly because...
Hold on, we'll watch the cutscene first. Oh, I see super meat boy and his girlfriend just hanging out at the park.
Watch out here! He punched her in the face. If you've never played this game, then oh my goodness, this is a classic. You have to get your hands on this game.
Let's start right from the very beginning. I deleted all my save file stuff, so I'll make sure I'll be right at the very beginning.
But I digress. The reason why I started to do this is because I'm a huge fan of Binding of Isaac, as you've seen on the channel, and the same guy made this game.
Edmund McMillan. Not Edward McMillan. I always say Edward for some reason. I don't know why. There's no W to be found in his entire name.
But he made this game, and he made Binding of Isaac, so I figured I'd pay homage to him, homage to him, and play this one.
What is going on here? Oh my god. Why am I running a mill? What's going on? Okay, my controller is all screwed up. Hold on a second.
What is happening here? Okay, we're back. That was really weird. It was something to do with DXTory and recording, but let me just start playing.
I was just like, just going 100 miles per hour. But I'm pretty good at this game. I used to play this game a lot with Burger Boy.
And I completed a lot of stuff with this game. I got A-pluses on a lot of levels. Let's see if I can't do that again.
Because I gotta go quick. Gotta go super fast. That's the most important thing. And get that, Band-Aid.
No, give me the Band-Aid. Here we are. Oh, right when I say I'm good at this game, let me jump over the bride-to-be.
Let's go, let's go. The faster, the better. Warp Zone? Let's do the Warp Zone. Why not?
Warp Zone is where it takes you out of the game and brings you to a very strange place. Like this.
All right, let's do it, baby. Little 8-bit meat boy. He's so cute. Speed, run, speed, run, speed, run.
Actually, speed doesn't really matter here because you're just trying to complete everything. I could go for that Band-Aid.
But you know what? Just going for completion right now. If I want to go back later and do that, I absolutely will.
This is where it gets a little fishy. All right.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. That was a dumb move. I forgot the dumb idiot.
All right. Nice and easy here. I only got two more lives. Oh, there we go. Super Meat Boy. Oh, sorry, Super Meat Boy.
There we go. What'd I get for it? Nothing. Just keep going with this level. Level 5.
So I probably should explain what this game is if you don't know.
It is a platform jumper where the whole point is to grab onto these walls and launch yourself up as fast as you can to get the A pluses.
Well, you don't have to get an A plus, but that's what I like to do.
And you only get one life. And it's just it's not really a puzzle. It's just a test of reflexes.
And when and if you pull your hair out during this game is the real question at hand.
Because the game gets at least it's a joke how hard this game gets.
Oh, now I'm screwed. I'm going to get that bandaid. I can't I can't skip them all. I got to at least get a couple.
Here we go. No. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Go. No. Now I screwed it all up.
Oh, I can't even get it. All right. Last try here. This is it. Oh, no. I really messed things up. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If I can just do this nice and slow, be good. Let the rage begin. Let the rage turn on here.
I missed it. I missed it again. No, no, no. There we go. If I just I missed it again. You know what?
Screw it. Let's just end the damn level. Just keep going. I'll sneak up. Sneaky snake. Let's go, baby.
Nope. I'll be going this time, though. We are right in there. Oh, snuck in there.
So chapter one chapter. Oh, look at that program.
That's what I'm talking about. And I got the bandage. I see that's what you have to do.
You got to you just got to let your brain turn off and just play the game the way it was meant to be played.
Freaking out warp zone. Let's go for it. And I think this is where do you get command a video?
I think he's here, right? Maybe. Oh, and help me. Don't worry. I'll save you.
Here's command a video. My favorite character in the game. Yeah. Let's do it.
Command a video. Command a video is one of the unlockables.
You can pull down the jump button and you can hold down the jump button and glide.
It's very, very useful. He is probably the best character in the game, at least in my opinion.
Actually, one could be the Minecraft guy is probably the best character in the game. Whoa.
Hey, I could probably make it across that whole thing. What do you think? Definitely.
I now have commander video from Bit Trip runner. Good to go. I'm going to use them. Why not?
Let's use commander video. Yunk. His downside is he's very slow.
Meat Boy is lightning fast and he's kind of like a slug, but you know what? He gets the job done.
Plus, I don't freak out as much with commander video like I do with Meat Boy because I'm not going a thousand miles per hour.
Now let's make this work and drop right down. Hello, girl. I'll take an A plus with a side of cheese and onion.
Make it up. Make it up. You slug bastard. Now this is where we jump and we jump and we jump.
Next level. Oh, this might be hard with commander video because he's slow because he's slow.
Down. No A plus. Come on. No, that's not cool. Jump. Jump.
No, I wasn't going to make it. I would never have made that. I know my limit says commander video.
Are you okay?
Oh, look at him. I'm like off screen right now. I already watched this. Hooray.
Oh, I made it. I'm actually going to die. Nice. Okay. Level 19 intermission. Sounds like a plan.
Rocking. I can tell you a story of when I played this game over Burger Boys and went to a very hard.
It was dark world. Essentially, when you when you get an A plus in a level, it unlocks a harder version of the same level.
And it's in the dark world, they call it. So one of the last levels I got to in the dark world, I was at Burger Boy's house.
And oh my God, I must have died a thousand times, probably more.
And Burger Boy made me stop playing. He's like, dude, Jeremy, you need to stop, man. You you are really freaking out right now.
You need to like let's like go do something. And I just had this like red eyes like, no, I refuse to stop.
And now that's what this game can really do to you is you get sucked in and every death is like taking another hit of crack.
See, this is the part where I get a little antsy because I want to go. I want to go, go, go, go, go video.
You are slow. All right. We're getting close here. Yeah. This is the first boss of chapter one.
Let's see. Let's let's smash a little slugger. Look, let's take a look at the cinematic, of course, going to dump gasoline all over the place.
He's going to turn around. He's going to be like, screw you, Burger Boys. Oh, I just said Burger Boy.
He's going to like the forest on fire. Why? Why would you do such a thing?
And these characters are in Binding of Isaac. If you see them. Oh, God, that's what happens when you don't pay attention. Go, go, go.
And you have to play as Meat Boy for all the boss encounters, which really stinks at some points because I would love to play some of the unlockables.
But you know what? You just got to go. Forget about everything else and just run, baby. Run.
And this is going to be. Oh, my God. Come on. Come on. Oh, get up there, you. Oh, what? What? Oh, what happened?
Oh, God. Come on. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it. Get it.
I was going so well, too. I beat it. I beat it in first try, except I fell off and landed on the guy's skull cap.
This time, I'm not going to mess this up. I'm not going to screw it up this time. What am I?
I got a little time here. I can chill out. Not here, though. Good. All righty.
You are dead, big chainsaw machine, dude. Not a moment too soon. You lose. Oh, I feel bad.
Hi. What the hell? I wish they would make noises like this in games.
I wish there would be somebody screaming like that. This part I don't. I get it. I understand.
But it just is like, wait, what? The poor squirrels. I think it's like the squirrels family or something.
That's a pretty big family. He'll get his revenge one day. The squirrel. I wish he appears later.
Spoiler. He doesn't or spoiler. He does. You never know. Oh, my God.
I don't think I've ever watched that cut scene long enough to know that that happens.
I usually just skip it. He gets his head cut off with a saw. My God. Morbid.
All right. So moving on to chapter two in episode two. Thank you guys all so much for watching.
Really do appreciate it. And let's keep the super meat boy train rolling. Probably going to do this once a week, probably.
You probably see this once a week until I finish it, of course. So the rage will begin coming soon to a theater near you.
Take care, everybody, and see you later.