So I just walk around the beach? Oh nice, this is a pretty good beach party. What's that guy doing?
Somebody's over there using like a hand glider. There's like jet skis. Is this open world? What
do I want to do first? There's so many options in M&M's Beach Party. Nice. Good job. Good return.
Excellent return. There we go. Set it up for you. What the fuck are you doing? Why do we both suck
so bad? Can we get at least a volley going on? My god. Somebody please make a return. Hit it up.
Spike it down. Thank you very much. I'll take that point. Apparently we didn't get the point,
but it's okay. I'll just miss over and fucking over again. Okay, hold on. Please seriously hit
the fucking ball. There we go. Oh my god, how do you control how hard you hit it?
Is there any way to control it? I don't think so judging by the fact that nobody can seem to
make a good serve. I don't think it's possible. Do it. Flick the fucking potato frog thing,
whatever the hell this thing is. All right, I got two points. Yeah, good. This is good fun.
I can't wait to like to give this broken ass. What? Wait, no, it's the computer's turn?
The computer's like worse than I am. Wait, how come he's getting all these points? Look at his
points. I scored two. He got eight. He didn't get eight. He got like two. Why does he have
nine points right now? See, I have to spray these guys orange because I picked orange
and the other guys have to spray their guys, their colors. It's a blast. I mean, we're talking,
this is it. There's only like three different animations and you know what? Time to go try
hard mode because I'm winning one of these. Spray that guy. This guy coming down. I know he always
walks the same route. He ain't going to beat me this time. What do I need? 15. I lost again.
I actually came in last place. I want to ride like the jet ski. Where's the canoe?
Where's the canoe? Looking at the back of the box right now. Where's the canoe?
I bought this game because the canoe was on the back and you're telling me I can't even
access the canoe right now? You got to be kidding me. Do I have to unlock this next game? I must
have to. There's got to be some reason why that's like all boarded up and if you think for one second
I'm going to like five star all the games and get like the points and shit required to open
this gate up, no way. And you know what? I got a better idea. How about we actually play a good
party game? One of the best party games ever made. You probably all know which one I'm talking
about. It's on Nintendo. It's on the Wii featuring one of the most famous video game characters ever.
I'm of course talking about Pac-Man Party. Oh yeah. Pac-Man Party. Look at the party mode.
Got mini games, rewards. You can play classic games? You kidding me? I can play Pac-Man, Galaga,
Dig Dug. This is included. This is all included. I don't have to pay extra. Come on. Are you
kidding me? I'm like pumped up right now to like eat a bunch of spaghetti. All you're going to do
is you move the hand around, roll the spaghetti. All right, let's go. Let's go you fucking punks.
It's time to eat the spaghetti. Oh am I going to win? That guy, that's no fair. That guy's got two
arms. How come that guy has two forks going in? That doesn't seem real fair. Look at that. Look
at how much I kicked everybody's ass. I'm the master of the spaghetti roll-up. How is that guy
still standing by the way? Look at the guy on the left. He has like a legitimate seven. He's got a
backwards seven and apparently it's still standing. Doesn't matter. I'm going to win.
That guy is so fucked up and he's going to beat me. No. No. Give me one more. Get out of my way.
Got to get past the line. Got to get past the line. My ice cream needs a bit. I lost.
Pizza party. Oh yeah. Pizza party. I'm going to be the master of the pieces. Master of the spaghetti.
Hey, who remembers from like the original Pac-Man games? There's a giant spider that tries to eat
and kill you. It's pretty, this is like pretty canon. Can I throw this? Can I throw this giant
like dog bone? How long does this last? I just want to, I want to go back to eating like spaghetti.
I don't want to like fight. I want to eat ice cream, candy and spaghetti. See, this is what
I'm talking about. It's all about just eating candy and eating brownies and chocolate pudding.
No spiders. No scary monsters. It's just good old fun. That guy's picking the brownie. We don't want
to let the bomb drop on the ground and that guy you already lost. Nice job. Why would you pick that
piece? Nobody even got a turn to go. How does he win when nobody else had a turn to go? So pretty
much the moral of this story and the purpose of this video is to simply say, uh, Pac-Man is
unstoppable. He's unbeatable and he's the best video game character ever. And if you want to argue
that with me, then all I got, I got four words for you. Pac-Man is the best character ever.
You will never defeat him. He is a god among men and he is undeniably the greatest character ever
in the history of video. That was like 70 words, but you get the idea.