What is going on everybody? Jerma here again. This time I am gonna be doing a
duel commentary. It's somebody very special in my life. Gonna be doing a
duel com with my grandfather. Yes he is. So grandpa, if you'd like to introduce
yourself right now is a pretty good time. Okay. Go ahead. Hi, I'm Jerma's
grandfather. This is Milford Dougal. He is my grandpa of 87 years. That's right. He's
been here a long time and he loves to game which is ridiculous. I love it. It's
my favorite thing. It's my... video games are the best thing in the world, especially
Super Mario 3. Naturally, yeah. Yes, that's the best game I've ever played, probably
in my life. And today I'm gonna play some... Steve, Team Fortress... what are we
playing today? We are playing Team Fortress 2, grandpa. This is the game I was
telling you about. The one I'm doing online and stuff like that, you know, I
was telling you about it earlier. Yep, I remember. So anyways, you're gonna be
playing what? What? As what class? I mean, sorry. I'm playing as the
soldier with the rocket launcher. It's a fucking huge... I told you you couldn't swear. Oh shit.
Okay. It's okay. You can't swear. I'm sorry. Sorry, I didn't mean to talk like
that. I'm not a sailor. It's alright. I'm not a sailor by any means. Let me get into the game here.
What is this? You gotta click on join. Yeah, okay. He's got it. Give him a second.
He's got it. It might take me a second or two, but once I figure it out... I almost
swore right there again for like the fourth time. Almost. But it takes me a
second. But once I get in the zone, I really start to kill people. And if you
saw my last video, I used to do videos for Insane Aquarium on my old
channel. The channel was youtube.com slash grandpa dickhead, but I can't use
that name anymore because I'm not allowed to use that name. I told you easy. But now
I'm on Jerma's channel for good now. I'm gonna do commentaries with him every
single day. So hopefully... I don't know about that. Maybe soon. Well, when we can, when we can
do commentaries together, I'll make sure to bring my A game. Well good. Hopefully
you brought your A game today because you're gonna need it. Because this game's
not that easy when you first start out. You've seen me play before. You
know what I'm talking about. You're talking to somebody that beat Donkey Kong
in five minutes, okay? Don't even try and tell me that I'm some kind of noob at this game.
You're noob. I bet you I can beat you in a duel, one on one. I know what duels are. I
looked up. I did my research. You did. You were on the computer for like three hours.
Come out of the spawn here. And this guy... What is this guy doing? That's a heavy.
I want to be that guy. I'm gonna be that guy, right? I changed my mind. I want to be
this guy. Okay, well go in the spawn and there you go. Okay, this guy looks like
he's the biggest guy on the game, the game. So I'm gonna play with him. He's
slow though. He's pretty slow. So tell me what should I play? How do I play this
guy? Should I be like a superhero and just jump at people and attack them? Yeah,
that's the heavy. I'm gonna go this way. No, don't. Listen. This is a tactical way. I'm telling you. This is the way you go if you want to be tactical.
Listen, grandpa. If you go that, that's the wrong way. You have to turn around. If you
stand still any longer, you're gonna get back to that by spy. I'm just telling you.
What the fuck is a spy? There's a spy. Okay, I have to explain to you the game
before you do anything stupid. Well, do it. You're playing under my name right now. I
don't want you to... I don't want people to think that this is some idiot like
who took over Jerma's account or something. Listen. If you listen to me,
you'll be fine. Oh, listen. Tell me what you want me to tell me, you know. I'm
sitting here. Okay, all right. So this is Dust Bowl. Okay. This is probably like the
easiest map to learn because there's only like one way people can go. Turn
around, walk straight, and you got to follow your teammates. Just follow where
they're going. This guy. You'll get to the enemy team. You're on red. Okay, don't
shoot him. Don't shoot at people on red. You're on red. I'm gonna shoot this guy. So get out
here. There you go. All right, fine. And then just, yeah. Okay, yeah. Oh, it's the blue team.
Oh my god. Oh, get old, you motherfucker. You're dead. You are dead, you shithead. I
No, no, no, no, no. Don't go up the stairs. I'll go up these stairs if I want to. I'm gonna punch this
fucking guy. All right, stop swearing, please. You're gonna get me in trouble. I'm sorry. I can't
help it. I grew up in LA. All right, well, just come down the stairs. There you go.
Who's that guy? Get that guy. Get him. I'm trying to shoot him. He's running away. Get him.
Yeah. He's dead. I did that. You didn't do it. Okay. So should I walk to this, well,
platformer. Take out your sandwich and eat it. If you go hit two. I'm gonna die. Two is your
secondary and that's, okay. Right now it's, there's a bunch of different items, but I'm not even
gonna pretend I'm, like, I can explain that to you. So just hit two and then eat the sandwich. What's the best
item in the game? Yeah, make sure you're in a spot that's, like, safe, though. Don't just stand still. Yeah,
but what's the best item in the game? I kind of want to know, because maybe I want it. All right,
fine. I'll eat it. As you guys can tell, it's really hard to play with him. Oh, yeah. Yeah,
okay. Says you, the hardest person to play with. No, it's hard to play with you. Any game. No,
it's not. I mean, it's easy. Especially a game like this, like, especially. Well, no matter why
am I playing then, maybe I should just quit and go back to writing my book. No. The title is not
written yet, so don't even ask. Okay. But I, oh, watch out for this guy right here. He looks like
he's pretty mad. You're good. You're good. You're good. So what's the best, I want to talk about what
the best item in the entire game is. What is it? Well, what do you think the best item in the game
is? There is none, to be honest. I think it's the Razorback. That thing looks really cool. No. All
right. Well, you couldn't be any more wrong. I don't think so. It really does. All the items are
good. I mean, I say the Razorback is not, but no, whatever. If you like the item, use it. It's all
about preference. You say a lot of dumb things. Well, I don't even have to, you're not going to
play this game ever again. So it doesn't, I don't have to tell you any of this. So just keep playing
and just, I don't have to explain this to you because you're going to forget in like five
minutes. I am not going to forget this in five minutes. I already forgot what you told me five
minutes ago, but it doesn't mean I'm going to forget what you just said five minutes from now.
What do you think this is? Some kind of game, even though we are playing a game. I'm telling
you right now, I won't forget any of this. I'm going to come on Team Fortress tomorrow and I'm
going to play and I'm going to be the best damn sorcerer anyone's ever seen. And if you don't
think that's true, then you can, you can stuff it brother. Oh, all right. That's fine. Yeah.
Just, you know, you can play on your own now. I'll let you play on your own since you don't
need my help and you don't think anything I say is worthwhile anyways. So I don't need your help.
I'm going to leave and hopefully you can figure it out on your own because I'm not going to sit
here and baby you anymore. Cause obviously you don't need that, right? You're a baby, not me.
So anyways, uh, take care guys. I'll see you at the live stream Saturday. Big birthday party.
Hell yeah. Let's do it. I'm going to be there. No, you're not going to be there.
What? No, why would you be there? Because it's you're going to be at grandma's anyways. You're
going to be at, at, at Jones. Oh, okay. Yeah. So, but dinner sucks over there. You're doing family
dinner there. Yeah, but dinner sucks over there. I want to eat with you tomorrow. I don't want to
be over there. That place sucks. Well, I mean, if, if you want to come to the live stream for like
a few minutes or something, okay, by all means you can come, but you can't hang out all night.
Cause why, why the hell not? You just can't be over. You can't hang out all night. That's it.
All right. Fine. So bye guys. I'll see you all tomorrow at the live stream. Peace. Okay. See
you later. And, um, I'll see you later. Yeah. Hey, just make check. Wait, how do I make a pitch?
Shut the computer down when you're done. Cause I'm not going to come back in here. What?
Shut the computer down when you're done. Oh, okay. I'll shut the computer off. All right.
See you later. I love you son or grandson. Oh God, I'm going to puke. So anyways,
I'll see you guys next time on my, on my grandpa plays with me today. I don't even know if that's
going to be the title or not, but it should be. Okay. Salute United States of America.
What the hell am I talking about? Okay. Bye guys. See you later.