What's going on? Why am I always late?
Because I'm not ready.
That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it.
That's the only actually that's the only explanation.
That's it.
Why are you not ready?
I'm just not.
I'll sit down at like 350.
Make sure like OBS and everything is working well and make sure I'm capturing the right things.
I have to I don't have a drink or anything.
I got a good guy.
I can't just like turn the stream on without a drink.
I need my tea.
And then I take a sip out of the tea and I realized that like wow, that's really moving me a little.
That's yeah, I have to go to the bathroom.
I have to pee.
I got to comb my hair.
Maybe that does my phone ring.
Is it mom calling?
I don't know.
I can't take I can't take mom's phone call on stream.
So it's okay.
I have to have a decision here.
It's either okay.
I see mom's calling at like 355.
Okay, if I don't answer this mom phone call, I can't talk to mom till like 10 11 12 o'clock tonight.
I got to talk to mom.
I got to answer mom's call.
I got to answer the mom's call.
Of course I am.
I mean mom didn't call today.
What's going on?
How are you?
Good to see you again.
We're gonna pick up where we left off last night.
Where's my okay.
Precisely.
Where's my chapstick?
I'll be right back.
See this is what I'm talking about.
Okay, I got it.
He fell in the toilet.
I actually did today.
Funny.
That was like a plant from chat because I was going to talk about that for a second.
It wasn't a big deal.
I didn't fall in the toilet, but I sat down on the.
Like the toilet rib cage.
Not the seat.
The seat was up and I sat down on that rigid part.
I was in a hurry.
I almost wish I had the audio from this this whole thing because I made this old man sound.
It was like, hey, it's like, hey, hey, because when I sat down, it just you don't you never you're never expecting that we as humans know the exact
distance from ass to seat and even one to two millimeters off your body goes into a panic mode.
Once you're not at that spot where you know, it's supposed to be all hell breaks loose and it's holy shit.
I'm going I'm sinking through the earth.
Then it hurts the shit hurt.
I mean, I don't know why I'm not just like ground pounding down on the toilet, but it kind of it kind of hurts your ass distance must be crazy.
No, it's not you guys know what I mean.
You hit that moment where you're not your ass is not on seat and you know, it's supposed to be and even if it's not even a tenth of an inch, you know it and
there's not you're already sitting down.
So you're screwed.
So we're going to play some demos.
We're going to do what we did last night.
Looks like the internet seems to be okay right now.
I'm glad that whatever route Twitch was Twitch was taking to my internet.
I'm glad it's fine.
It ended up being fine last night too.
So let's cross our fingers here maintenance.
Yeah, your mic sounds goofy.
It doesn't.
My mic does not sound goofy.
You got a goofy ass mic.
This is what is in my voice.
You're talking about now.
You got me all freaked out.
I am going to start with a gloom would I'm very excited for this game.
This is by I think the dusk Dev had something to do with this.
They said that company was it called new blood very excited for this.
They usually come out with very very good products and could we see a coveted
5v not 5v5 could we see the coveted 5 out of 5 we only gave one last night.
I got high hopes.
What was the second highest score I gave last night.
Please clear your throat.
Oh no, it says please don't clear your throat.
Well, dude, my voice is fucked up.
It was a four.
What did I give them?
What did I give that other game?
I'm ready to go.
Let's do it.
You should be able to hear it.
Let's move over here.
That's even going to work.
I hope so.
Hi, here's gloom would and here's me too.
I'm here.
You gave nine souls of four six.
What do they give that rhythm game that fighting kind of rhythm game?
What did I give that?
It's like a four or something.
I didn't give that three six.
I get a three nine.
That wasn't fair.
That's like a four one.
You hear you.
Can you hear this?
I was like coughing.
All right, gloom would I'm ready.
Here we go.
This is a demo for those of you don't know.
Steam is currently running this big event where a ton of upcoming games
that not out yet have demos that you can play right now.
It's a big steam event.
So this game is not out and it's not coming up for a while.
We get exclusive access to it as a steam community.
It's like difficulty.
Let's do I'm just doing half moon.
I'm not doing any of this other stuff.
Okay, brightness.
Just go full bright.
I can see both the moons.
Wait, what does it want me to do until the left image is not visible?
I always don't listen to this though, because I know that okay,
when the when the moon is not visible, that's oh wow.
It's really dark.
I always go at least a little bit more.
I just I can't I can't see anything.
You're gonna break the immersion.
Yeah, but I want to be able to see.
I think that's okay.
Just a little bit.
Okay, let's go for a second.
I thought that was way too much.
It was like I did way too much.
Put the screen shake up.
See I'm saying this is why I did it.
Can you how's the audio?
Can you hear it?
Well, is the audio good?
Oh, there he is.
There he is.
WSD.
Yep.
Turn off the lights.
It's the middle of the afternoon where I am.
It doesn't not gonna help.
It's not gonna do anything.
Tap F to pick up items hold F to manipulate items.
Apologies that I could not encounter you in person.
For now take this vial and find your way into the manor on
the Main Street.
I await your arrival.
Okay, in the manor on Main Street.
Use tab to open your inventory and health status.
Oh, okay.
It's kind of like a VR setup.
Okay, so I got a letter.
I've got a vitalizing tonic.
I don't want to inject that right now.
Tap F to open the door hold F to slowly open the door.
Your visibility is affected by light and shadow.
All right.
Hold space to Manta.
Creepy because you're cautious of traversing on loud surfaces
hold left shift to sneak.
Okay, I need to go in the manor.
An enemy.
Ooh, what's this?
Oh, it's a it goes across it hits multiple times.
Oh, that's cool.
All right, let's go.
Cane sword jailhouse.
This is not the manor but whatever doors locked.
I will have a sword now.
Can I sneak anywhere?
Can I break something?
Can I break this?
I can.
How do you crouch cheese?
What is this money dead end sewer cheese?
Yeah dead end bullets dead end.
What do you have a shiny nose today?
I don't know.
My father was fucking Rudolph.
Get over it.
Now that would now that was funny.
All right, so I need a key to get in there.
Wait weapons can be drawn and holstered.
Oh, okay.
This way some objects can be destroyed.
Why would it say that?
Oh, save your progress.
Okay, saved.
That's quick and painless.
I like it.
So there's guns in this game.
That's where I need a gun.
There's guns and there's also sprockets.
I get him.
Oh shit.
Okay, that's a dump this guy somewhere.
Don't I what I didn't want to do right mouse block incoming
melee attacks.
Where is he?
Where'd he go?
Weird.
Where is this guy?
Oh, there's the key to the jailhouse gone.
All right, you just shot that guy.
Yeah, I did.
All right.
I got the key.
You did nice stealth.
I stealthy shot that guy when he came down the stairs.
Can you throw stuff?
There's got to be a way right?
Yep.
Okay.
I let him give me one of these here the box.
Anything else in here?
Okay, so I have the key that that's goes to the jailhouse,
right?
So somebody said why are you acting like you're playing
Minecraft?
I'm I'm not.
Oh God.
Oh my God.
Now say the bullets just hide.
Did you see me?
I don't think you saw me right?
No, don't step on the grate.
Oh my God, he shot me in the head.
Okay, there's something in my nose.
It appears that something needs to be placed into this.
Dude.
I have I got these right.
Oh, no, it's an that's a the wrong whatever.
All right guard house.
This door is locked shit.
I didn't be pulled through fences and oh.
Okay, nice here.
Oh, what?
Oh my God.
It was I'm gonna die.
We're good.
Dork mic.
I'm sorry.
My mic is a fucking dork.
I turned it on stealth game.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know.
I'm not very good at stealth games.
I didn't think I didn't know the window is right there.
Oh cool.
What does that do?
The men managed to confiscate one of the seals required to negate
the dark magics blocking ladies Sylvia's doors.
We've reason to believe the foreigner is planning to take refuge
within the countess's high walls.
The seal has been placed in the jailhouse evidence locker.
Okay, seal house evidence locker.
Okay, so I got jailhouse got it.
I got my task.
I got I know what I need to do.
Lean against doors to hear behind them.
Really?
Oh wait, somebody was in the bathroom and it is not here anymore.
Because when I shot the gun downstairs, they they all came out.
Okay, so we need to go to the jailhouse.
I need to do I need a key for the jailhouse?
Whatever guard house.
All right.
I need the two seals.
Remember to return to the phonograph to save the city of
gloom would only gets more dangerous from here.
Oh no, I don't remember where the phonograph is.
Where's the phone?
Where's the phonograph?
This game goes hard.
Isn't it?
It's in here, right?
I missed a shotgun.
Did I actually miss miss the shotgun?
I did.
Holy, I thought you were lying.
Okay.
So now I gotta go.
I don't know.
Where's the where's the safe thing?
Way too dank.
I'm sorry.
I put a limiter on the mic too and I can't doesn't fix it.
We'll do some tests on it in a minute.
Where'd that guy go?
Oh fuck.
If I lean out, can they see me?
Can this guy that it's can that guy see me when I do that?
What I did a backstab.
Did I just do a backstab?
I thought I just backstabbed him.
Oh, it has to blink.
Okay, it has to blink.
I get it.
Nice face stab.
That was a backstab.
It just didn't register.
What can you do with the money?
Wait, hold on.
Did the dev say this demo is so old and crusty?
Did the dev say the demo is old and crusty?
What?
Wait, the dev came in here and said, oh God, this demo is so
old and crusty.
I think it's good.
It's an old build compared to what they're working on now.
I don't think it's crusty.
What do you mean crusty?
All right.
Here's a power station.
Can I do a force pull on it?
All right, power station.
Jeremy, you're old and crusty too.
Yeah, so it's fine.
All right, relax.
Hey guys, if that was in the game, wouldn't it be better?
Where's this person?
Trying to distract him.
Okay, I don't know.
Why do I even sneak?
But I even why would I even be sneaking?
I'm just crouching around shooting people with a shotgun.
Why wouldn't I just shoot them?
Just shoot them.
Is this a gun?
This is the third broken rifle this week.
It's a stealth game.
I'm not good at stealth games.
I don't some of you guys want to make like a big blueprint
before you get in the level and be like this is where I'm
going to go and that X right there.
That's where I'm going to stay for five minutes.
I'm going to go cook pasta and come back and then when the
guy makes his rounds, I'm going to go sneak behind him do
one tap on his head and then this exit.
No, I'm my brains too small to do that.
I can't do that.
The shotgun ammo is very rare.
Like so you guys have some of you guys are very meticulous
and you want to plan out your routes and that's fun and
that you can do that.
You can do that in your game, but I want to throw a bottle
at somebody's face point blank.
Oh shit and hey guess what do we both get to the end of
the level see me walking around going like this and you
like sneaking around and like we both get to the end of
the level it and we both get it.
We both get a passing grade.
I don't want to hear it.
Okay, that's what that's one another gun.
This is dual welding 2.6 GPA.
Yeah.
Okay, so I got that is the key.
What that what key is that for does it say warden court
key for the door near the jailhouse shotgun?
I got a lot of ammo cheese.
Oh eat this.
That's it.
I just ate five wheels of cheese.
Okay, so I now the door near the jailhouse.
I got one of the Resident Evil puzzle piece stones.
So the dev is here, right?
Well, when are you going to add the breadcrumb the golden
breadcrumb trail that goes of GPS to where I need to go?
I thought that was going to be in the game.
I was like, so I was kind of convinced it was I don't know
why it's not here.
I'm like, I don't want to die.
I don't really want to say I'm disappointed but I mean
whatever it's now whatever.
Sorry, I'm sure that they'll add it later.
I think that just scared the shit out of me.
I thought I was going to get zapped by Darth cities.
I just thought I thought a guy was sitting there.
We're just waiting for me with hands.
I don't know.
I just made it up.
Okay, let's put this in.
I need one art jailhouse.
It's back this way.
It's kind of near the beginning, isn't it?
Are you going to save the game yet?
I mean you might need save points.
I'm a hardcore gamer though and we didn't have save points
when you got to level five in the Lion King on Super Nintendo
and when you lost you had to do the whole game over again.
That's what I was used to.
Okay, let me go down here.
Wait, should I wait this is different.
Okay, I'm going to get this right.
This is completely inaccurate.
I'm not I don't look good at this.
You know what I am good at?
I'd walk around the corner be like, excuse me, sir.
How are you?
Oh, my name.
Can I please shake your hand?
I would like shake his hand.
We talk like I'm the guy that distracts the guards.
I'm not the guy that sneaks into the castle.
I'm the one that walks up and does like a goofy routine
and distracts the guards while I do like magic tricks for them
and then laugh and clap and stuff.
And then the main character gets to go into the castle
and then guess what I get to go home.
I get to go home after that.
I did my job.
Okay, they didn't see that good.
Oh God, it looked cool.
It looked cool.
He's a jester.
What do you guys think?
Okay back in old medieval times.
What do you think I would be?
I don't know.
Everybody has this thing in their mind.
No, I'd be the sword wielding hero.
No, no, I wouldn't.
I would be dancing around the dinner table.
You'd be dead.
No, I wouldn't.
I'm not going to be the guy with the, you know, the rape here.
Like...
Oh, please.
No.
Did you have a Red Bull today?
I don't drink Red Bull.
I'm just a fucking weirdo.
I think.
I don't know.
No, I'm not even a weirdo.
You're the weird ones.
Not me.
You're the town fool.
Is my head too...
Can you see me?
Copium.
I'm just kidding around.
Yeah, I would not be the...
No, I'm not going to be the hero.
Don't turn around.
All right, nice.
Cistern entry.
You want to relive the Lion King?
He walked by the save room like three times.
Nobody wants to relive the Lion King.
No one.
That was so off.
I was trying to arc that so badly that it was going to hit him in the head
and it was completely off.
Somebody's coming.
Somebody's coming in the room right now.
Despises that the Lion King is not good.
Where is this guy?
Did he not come up here?
The Lion King...
The movie is fine.
The video game was just hell on Earth.
What did you guys think I was talking about?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did you guys think I was talking about trying to watch through the
Lion King movie and there's no save points?
What am I going to go make?
Wait, what?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the Lion King, the video game for the SNES.
That's what I...
Wait, why?
I think you guys are getting confused.
I said game like three times.
Yeah.
Ooh, lantern.
Oh goodness.
Does this cost oil?
It probably does.
Fully visible to enemies.
Does that mean I'm invisible to enemies in the dark?
That's kind of what that means, right?
I'm fully visible, but not right now.
Is there a bottle?
Give me this.
I think a bug just blew in my eye and it probably was on camera.
How do I get him to open the door?
There's a little entrance over there in the wall.
Should I follow him?
If I aggro him, will he come out somehow?
All right, come on then.
Get out here.
Come and get me then.
Come open the door and come get me.
All right, where's he going?
Can I turn this off?
I don't know.
Huh?
Oh God.
These...
Oh, these are freshly fired.
All right, give me the shotgun.
What the fuck is that sound that I just heard?
What the fuck was that sound?
What the hell was that sound?
That was horrifying.
Oh, I hate this.
Was it in front of me?
Was it...
Was it in front of...
Was it right in front of me?
And it's just...
There was no light?
I think...
I literally think I was looking at it.
I think I was looking at it and it was dark.
Oh goodness.
Is it me?
That wasn't me.
That was not me.
Safe point.
I got it.
Storage.
Door control.
What?
What the hell was that?
This is a weird thing over there.
Okay.
There's the thing there.
It's like a fucking bird.
Can I kill this in one hit with a backstab?
I need a DEV confirmation.
Oh shit.
Will it see me right here?
It won't see me right here, right?
Will it see me right?
I need to DEV post on Twitter right now.
Will it see me in this dark?
DEV post on Twitter.
Will it see me?
Where the fuck am I?
Okay, right here.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Storage.
It's not coming over here, right?
What the hell was that over there?
There were eyes over there.
What the...
Relax.
No, that's not eyes.
No, no, no, no.
Get out of here.
Get the fuck out of here.
There's one in the room right now.
Is there?
No, just put it down.
Put it down.
2010 YouTuber reaction.
DEV said, yeah, backstab it.
It works.
2010, man.
I'm traveling back in time.
Is there two?
I think there are two.
This sucks.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
It's fucking 2010.
Okay, that wasn't that bad.
Okay, they die in like one hit.
They die in one hit.
Two hits.
Your mic sucks, dude.
I'm fixing it right now.
I'm pausing it.
You tell...
Look, here we go.
I'm fixing it.
You ready?
My mic sucks.
Hold on, give me a second.
I swear to God, this is gonna take two minutes.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Here we go.
You tell me when it's better.
Oh, oh my God, bro.
Oh my God.
Is that better?
Oh my God, bro.
Whoa, what the fuck is happening?
Better?
Is that better?
Dude, what the fuck?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Second one's worse.
First one better.
So this one right here.
This one, this is pretty good.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, easy, man.
Easy.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Better?
It's crunchy.
I can't, I don't think I can make it not...
I mean, I'm yelling into a microphone.
Nice fucking eye exam, dude.
Stop screaming.
I can't help it.
I'm an overreacting YouTube Andy.
Okay.
I, that's not going to change.
All right, let's go.
I think that's in a better spot than it was last time.
Let's go.
Let's go, go, go, go, go.
That's, that's better.
We're good.
We're fine.
Everything's fine.
This one's worse.
How is this one worse?
Dude, you need to get a blue Yeti.
I remember those were, those were all the rage back in 2010.
A blue Yeti.
No, a blue snowball was the big one, right?
Dude, every single person had a blue snowball.
If you could buy stock in the blue snowball company back in
like 2008 and just sell it in 2012, you, you probably would
have made a fucking shitload of money if that was actually,
if they were actually publicly traded.
I swear to God.
I think every human being that was in front of a computer
in 2010 had a snowball.
And let's be honest.
They worked great.
They were cheap.
They weren't that expensive and they just plugged it in
and it was ready.
All right.
What did I, did I complete my task here?
The blue snowball is still kind of good, but every single
fucking person had one.
Oh dude, when they came up with the blue Yeti pro.
Oh yeah.
Hey, I'm going to get that one.
I want to sound like a pro.
Yeah, I've used the snowball before.
It works great.
All right.
Am I doing this right?
I got, well, I can read.
Let me read.
Apologies.
Oh wait, I already saw this one.
So what is this thing?
It's like a crank.
What does this go?
Is there a crank?
Excuse me.
Do you remember the movie Crank?
If the guy's heartbeat of his heart rate went down to a
certain beats per minute, his heart exploded.
What a fucking hilarious movie.
All right.
Should I put it on here?
Okay, main canal.
Yeah, this is the movie.
If you guys, if you guys didn't know the movie Crank,
it's a movie about a guy who gets some type of like drug
or something injected into him or he has like a fake heart
or something.
They give him a fake heart.
That's like an electrical.
I don't know.
I don't even know what the plot of the movie is.
All I know is it's like the movie Speed where you know,
in the movie Speed, you have to go a certain miles per
hour on the bus.
This guy had to keep his heart rate up if it went underneath
his heart would explode and they made a sequel.
Yeah, insane.
Okay, where is it?
Can I use it?
How do I use it?
No, it's not going to work.
Does that not work?
That's it.
I need to put it right here, right?
Press the use button.
Oh my god.
Okay, we're good main main canal.
All right, let's go.
Something in my eye.
I'm loading my shotgun up just in case one of those bird
things shows up.
Main canal.
Pump room.
What the fuck?
Oh god damn it.
No, just go back back back back.
I can do it.
I don't know which side he's on.
He's right in front of me.
Nobody here.
Which side is he?
I got to keep my fucking heart rate up, mate.
I just keep punching people in the fucking face, man.
Are you fucking trying to tell me that fuck my heart rate
goes down under 14,000 fucking beats per minute, mate?
Oh god, I'm in trouble now.
I have to run.
How do I get out of here?
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot.
Joke was more important than playing the game.
Joke was up here playing game down here.
Way more important apparently.
I'm not afraid now.
No, I'm not even afraid.
Let's go.
Now, now I'm annoyed.
I'm not afraid.
Come on.
Hey, stupid.
Why don't you come up here?
But only come one at a time though.
What?
Where?
Oh my god, he's behind me.
I have to sneak.
I can't attack him.
I can't, I have to sneak around.
I just have to sneak around.
You can't attack them.
Attacking is wrong.
It needs to go.
It's a stealth game.
I know, but I, I can't do stealth games.
There are two things in this world that I cannot do.
Stealth adventure and a Tetris.
Or most math problems.
Who even saw me?
Thank god, there's no bullets in this gun.
I would have shot it and I would have, I gave my position away.
Oh my god, what are they doing?
They're sprinting around.
What am I supposed to do?
What?
Where?
Where are you?
What the fuck?
God damn it.
All right, turn it back down.
I got to get, I'm almost at the end of the demo.
I imagine.
I'm going to turn it back down to where it was.
Here.
See, it's back down to where it was.
That was fun.
Was that loud too?
Was that like crunchy and horrible?
Yes.
God damn it.
This part's hard.
I'm just gonna kill them.
Fuck it.
I'm doing it my way.
And that's stand right here in the light.
It is this three.
This guy's dead right now.
There's one.
Here comes two.
Where's two?
Here it comes.
Right there.
Why is there only one shot in this gun?
There's your second.
Where's the third one?
Let's go.
Let's do the piece.
Hey, hey boys and girls.
That would be a fucked up start to Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
What a weird intro.
He's kind of like a monkey.
Or I have to get out of here.
Where's the exit?
Okay, there's not gonna be another one spawning, right?
Okay, I got bullets.
Get out of here.
Go, go, go, go, go, get out, out, out.
I'm feeling to full health.
It's just a demo guys.
I'm gonna get to the end of the demo.
Oh, okay.
This is like a shortcut.
This looks wrong.
Oh, it's cuz I was cheating.
Okay.
Now that I was gonna go to that door.
I did it.
All right.
That was fun.
That's terrifying but fun.
There we go.
Hell, yeah.
Is there more?
Stanley?
Stanley walked into the church.
Very good.
That was good.
That was intense.
That was Gloomwood.
Uh, explore the early access August 16th.
I'd mark that one on your calendar seems like it's gonna be really good.
Gonna give that one a rating.
No, that's higher than this 3.9.
The demo for Gloomwood
was a four
point.
Hold on.
Don't influence me.
Sound design.
Five.
Length of the demo.
Getting right to the point.
Five.
Just right to the point.
Hey, this is what you're doing.
Here's a little tasks.
Just go play the demo.
Five.
Scare factor.
Four point six.
Stealth game.
Three.
This is a 4.7.
This demo with not this demo was a 4.7.
No, I'm not.
Well, hold on.
Whoa.
I'm not saying that like a this is me personally give this is me personally giving you a review.
Does that mean stealth games are bad?
No, that's just how I feel about stealth games.
I'm not very good at them.
I'm very bad at them and I can't play them very well.
So for me a stealth game right off the bat is like a two.
Okay.
A stealth game is a two right off right out of the box.
This one was really good.
4.6.
Let's go.
That's a skill issue.
I look okay.
That was phenomenal.
Right out of the box.
All stealth games get like a 1.5 for me.
There's no the game could be a 10 and 10 masterpiece.
That's a 4.6 out of five.
Yeah, that was phenomenal.
Very very well done.
I loved it, but I'm terrible at stealth games and I can never play this game the way it's intended for it to be played.
But I can still enjoy it.
I think what about Metal Gear?
I feel the same way right?
You guys have any idea how many times when I was playing Metal Gear.
I heard there he is and I would just go.
No, that was fantastic.
4.6 gloom would look actually look forward.
I'm looking forward to playing it because that I mean you got a Mickey Mouse scream out of me.
It was like horror and stealth though.
So that's that was awesome.
It wasn't just a stealth game.
Don't categorize it as that.
Okay, so now I also because we queued up another one for today as well.
Trey Pang that I remember I got that one last night.
I was going to try it.
Let's try that one.
Trey Pang 2.
Okay.
Let me get the game here difficulty normal video resolution.
That's a weird resolution that I don't have 1440p.
Come on, bro 90 FOV.
No motion blur, please.
You can't see sorry.
Okay, a field of view 90 gamma.
I think that looks all right.
Wait, is this a scary game to quality preset high audio?
All right.
This is important.
How loud is it?
I can't really tell.
Is it good?
Does it mean lower a little bit higher?
I can't see over here.
Maybe like a little bit lower.
We'll take it down to like 70.
How's that?
It's doing normal.
Did that just what's going on?
It's very far.
I was like, wait, when are we going to stop and it's going to be us standing there.
Wait, trepang 2 was made by trepang.
There was a trepang one and it was made by trepang studios.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go.
So this is a sequel.
Okay.
That was that scream.
Just shoot me in the face.
Am I all right?
What do you know?
He missed.
I he point he missed.
I missed.
All right.
I can't see fucking anything.
Hold on.
It's it's so dark.
Can everybody see anything?
Little lower this DPI on this mouse is seriously.
How would you ever have it this high?
Somebody correct me.
And is this weird to like I've never played a video game where this was ever higher than here.
Out of a hundred who how could you ever have a hundred is my mouse just fucked up?
Is it my mouse just weird?
I'm gonna say for the feels better.
All right.
So then now turn the gamma up a little is that cheating?
What about just like 10%?
I think that's okay, right?
It has to be an even number of freak out.
Okay.
Like I security is not responding.
That's the game.
What is going on?
What was that?
What happened?
Units were under attack by unknown elements.
Execute Operation Bright Star immediately.
That's something was running down the hall.
Okay.
There's something is running down the hall.
Is this stealth game?
It is still too high.
And I'm going 120.
We're going 20%.
And I need to turn this down to like two.
You know, I've been concerned playing games before where I didn't think even down at one.
It felt really bad.
And I was like, what am I supposed to do about this?
I have to like change the deep.
I have to go into the DPI settings.
All right.
Three should be fine.
Three's fine.
Yeah, that's better.
That feels good.
It feels natural.
This game looks really nice hiding the dark.
Is there a run?
I just pressed E.
What happened?
Oops.
Hey fellas.
Let me distract you for a second.
Would it work here?
You see I my car broke down on the road.
Can you believe it?
Right a mile down the road.
I had to walk a mile.
It probably just killed me.
That would be like a target sighted.
It was some kind of currency thing.
Do I have a flashlight?
What?
Who?
Yo, yo, I think I see him.
What's on the dings?
What's going on?
What?
Clown mode?
What's clown mode?
Get out of here.
What?
How do I run?
What is sprint?
How do you run?
Somebody tell me how you run?
How do I run?
There's nobody in the wall, man.
That guy's pretending to work.
What the fuck?
Clown mode.
I'm stuck in here.
How do I get out of here?
Is there a jump throwing flares in here?
Oh, wait, I see.
You can't get me up if I save area here.
Who would win a hundred guys with machine guns or a walking
clown?
How do I run?
I like this game.
This I think this game's got serious potential.
And I mean it dead serious potential.
Oh my God.
There's a gun.
Is there aim down sights?
Nope.
It's okay.
All right.
It's kind of like Counter-Strike mode.
Oh my God.
Oh, what the fuck?
Okay, let's go.
Should I go across?
Wait, what's in here?
Might be ammo.
Is there flashlight?
No, can't get in there.
There we go.
There's the sprint.
Go to we lost contact 106 stay sharp jump and melee to do.
Oh my God.
There's a kick.
Okay potential left alt is slide.
Oh my God.
Okay.
That's gonna be hard to do though.
Flashlight.
Thank you.
I got full health.
Would you I missed it.
What'd I miss?
Turn off the light.
You missed it.
I didn't miss anything.
What'd I miss?
Go back up to the way the body is where I missed lore.
Whatever.
It's a demo.
It's fine.
Running is clean by the way, if you're curious running is very
clean.
But what's a blue?
I tried to shoot two times.
What's that?
What is this?
What's this?
What is that?
We can't even hit each other.
What a bunch of fucking idiots.
The gun.
This is great.
This plays really well.
Don't miss any lore, right?
What's the game name?
This is called trepang 2.
Is there is there actually a trepang 1?
This is actually really really good.
So he's playing angry foot.
How does this feel?
Is this like?
Yep.
This is like an ammo crate or something.
No.
Oh, yeah, I'll take it.
I love shotguns like my favorite in every game.
Armor.
Yep.
Slow down time.
Shit.
Oh my god.
Oh shit.
That was so what an amazing game.
That was fear, right?
This.
Yeah.
This is fear.
Oh shit.
Do they do it still?
Come on.
I can throw him.
What do you mean grenade?
Well, this is out fucking rages.
Okay.
Where should I go?
Violent violence, Andy.
Jesus.
What the fuck happened here?
Oh my fucking God.
Wait, I didn't.
Did I do this?
This is me.
Wait.
Oh, I'm progressing through.
Oh, no.
No, I didn't.
I didn't do this yet.
I haven't been here before.
He's in a time paradox.
Coin holding the coin like this get you killed.
Can I have a sword?
Can I have the sword?
Sword looks pretty cool.
I don't think so.
There's nobody here.
What?
Don't move.
Don't you dare move.
Hey.
Don't.
I see what you're trying to do, but it's not going to work.
You're not going to get a good line on me.
I tell you.
Hey.
I didn't want to kill that guy back there.
No, I wanted to grab him.
Stop.
Oh, I need more shotgun stuff.
Locked.
Okay.
I love the flares.
I'm not.
Actually, this is probably better.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, that's does that.
I'm all right.
Person.
The inside of my ear is itching.
Does that mean that somebody like sneezed?
What does that mean?
That means something right?
What the hell was that?
Was that little shimmy?
No, it's if somebody sneezes that means they're talking.
No, if you sneeze means somebody's talking about you.
That's what it is.
Was that a huge kick?
What the fuck was that?
What just happened to that guy?
Oh my God.
I want this.
Okay.
Oh, ding dong.
Oh, what?
Who's still alive?
Who's alive?
Is it what?
I put a grenade on him and threw him back in the elevator.
All right.
We're good.
I got it.
This gun sucks.
I love it.
I'm just having too much fun being like an idiot.
Open, open, open.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
No.
All right.
Give me up.
We're good.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
Oh, I can't leave the room.
Okay.
I'm alive.
We're good.
That was insane.
Oh, grenades.
Where are they?
In here?
All right, G is grenade.
Health, got it.
Silencers.
Where is there a silencer?
Where's the silencer?
Where is it?
It just popped up on the screen.
Where's the silencer?
Oh, fuck.
Well, the game's physics just make a shitload of noise.
The game's physics makes a ton of noise.
What am I supposed to do about that?
Okay.
What?
There's another person here.
Get out, get out, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don't come near me.
You gotta shoot me in the shoes, man.
Why are you shooting right into the shield?
No ammo.
Oh, come on.
I don't.
Shoot him.
Why can't I?
What's going on?
That was weird.
We're here?
No, it's locked.
Shit.
Where did I go?
What the hell is that?
Do you remember you're killing them?
Yeah.
I'm playing a game where I'm there.
They're coming in with us with machine guns to try to get me.
I'm like it.
I'm this is I'm like an SCP.
I don't know what's going on.
Yeah, no shit.
I'm yeah, I'm this is of course that's what's happening.
Oh, shotgun.
You're killing them.
What?
Did I get him?
Oh my goodness.
Customize weapon.
Laser and a suppressor.
Holy shit.
Yeah, cool.
Can I customize this laser?
Laser.
Yeah, the game is so loud.
I thought you guys told me it was good.
It's been this loud the whole time.
Wow.
Whoa, what the hell was that?
Whoa, don't walk into that.
Oh my God.
Don't don't don't don't don't don't.
What are you doing?
Don't throw that.
It's gonna blow the whole thing up.
Thanks, actually.
Oh shit.
I have three bullets.
This looks.
What do you know?
See you later guys.
Zero one respond.
Son of a bitch.
They're gonna come from this way.
Don't don't say move in.
I know they're gonna go on the elevator.
You're making this wheel.
They're making this too easy.
Zero two move in from the second elevator.
Sierra three move in from the third elevator.
Oh my God.
That guy's probably.
He's trapped.
I'm trying to get him out.
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
No.
He's.
I don't think he's alive.
I don't think he's alive anymore.
What?
Another Sierra team?
Where?
Oh, I'm invisible.
You can't see me stupid.
You.
What?
Oh my God.
Okay.
God, there's a lot of fire.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
This is a gug of the game.
All right.
He's gonna come in on his own, right?
Yep.
Okay.
Is he?
Oh, the baby's close.
This guy looks like he got a bug on the character.
What was that?
What happened?
Is he on me?
Why is he attached to me?
Get him off me.
What the fuck, dude?
What the hell?
No, I didn't like that.
I didn't like that.
It was horrible.
That was fucked.
Are they stopping me?
Wait, these are bad guys?
What?
What happened?
What's going on?
Wait, these are, I thought these are the enemies.
These are friendlies?
How?
These guys are what?
We're gonna, we're gonna get you out of here, man.
I was like, why are they not shooting at me?
It was weird.
I need to know.
I have to know.
Okay, I'm not leaving you until I know.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
I really didn't.
I've been shooting at these guys in this armor the whole time.
I didn't know that I was being rescued.
I just see guys pointing guns at me and I was like, oh, there,
there he is.
That was insane.
Holy shit.
That's a five.
That's absolutely a five.
Wow.
When does this come out?
There's more?
It's not over.
Really?
Are you serious?
It's coming out this year?
Oh, hell yeah.
Oh my God.
Pleasure to finally meet you 106.
The Horizon Corporation had you locked away for a very long time.
They must be frightened.
Now that you're free.
Customized appearance.
So do we.
Who's what's going on?
Welcome to Task Force 27.
Oh, it's me shooting.
So what I do here.
Oh, we select missions.
It's kind of like a hub.
That was just pure.
That was just adrenaline.
I'm starting to understand the kinds of games that I really like.
It's just like the go go go go go go go go go go do not kill.
I'm not going to I know now that I'm not I'm not going to shoot anybody.
Don't worry.
We have a mission ready for you.
A raid on a Horizon facility similar to the one you escaped from.
When you're ready head to the briefing room and we can get started.
Intel.
Okay.
Well, they better be Intel in that computer.
You know I'm saying prologue and okay complex.
Pack in and download the encrypted data.
It's normal.
Normal is fun.
Did I do it?
Do I have to leave?
Launch mission.
Oh, I have to get on the helicopter.
Okay.
What is this?
No, no, no.
Oh, serum.
Of course.
That was a dual welding serum.
It's kind of weird.
Oh, oh, can you open the door for me?
I'll get it.
Customize change your clothes.
I don't care.
I don't need to change clothes.
I think I'm good.
BF bugleberry serum.
I didn't do that.
Don't blame that on me.
That was poor placement.
Okay, so I have to sneak in here and hack the mainframe.
Clean up how much?
Okay, clean up.
Armor.
Oops.
What is clean up?
Access denied.
Do I need to keep doing that?
All right proximity hack.
I'm hacking a coke machine.
Oh.
What?
What's going on?
Wait, this is a setup.
They were waiting for me.
This is a setup.
I couldn't find the gun.
Dual welding.
So it's just okay.
It's like a wave.
Can I do it?
Hey, stop.
Stop anti hacking me.
Get out of here.
Get out of here with that Norton.
I was shooting at this friend.
What?
Oh my God.
He's alive.
No, he's not.
Never mind.
Oh, it's done.
All right.
Now what?
Wave two.
Oh my God.
How long does this last?
I don't...
I want the...
Okay, over here.
Where'd he get this fucking Ghostbusters proton pack out of here?
What?
Where was that guy?
Where'd he go?
Where did that guy go?
He jumped over me.
Oh shit.
My God.
The hell is that?
Oh my God.
What is he doing?
Stop.
There's literally no need for any of this.
Just stop.
Stop.
Enough.
Okay, you still want...
I gotta clean up.
Wait, I can get in my own squad?
Oh my God.
They were just guarding it.
Oh shit.
I think I'm done here.
What is it?
2500?
Oh my God.
They're just collapsing here.
All right, that one's done.
Where's the last one?
Ow, my ears.
Can I pick that up?
I just want to see what the squad looks like.
And then I'm out of here.
Okay, 25 right now.
Let's get the squad.
All right, squad time.
Where's the supply thing?
They're just throwing grenades.
All right, squad incoming.
Where are they?
Oh my God.
That's a lot of people.
That's a huge amount of people.
Oh my God.
Be careful.
All right, move in, move in, move in.
What?
Grenade!
I'm so confused.
Get in there, get in there, get in there.
There's somebody shooting me over here.
Okay, I think they were, I think they moved in this way.
The source of the interference is right here.
It's you, you motherfucker.
All right, move in.
Are you up?
I didn't know if you were on my team.
All right, let's move in.
Wave five incoming.
All right, I'm too stimulated.
I can't do it anymore.
All right, I'm too, I'm overstimulated.
I gotta get out of here.
I'm over, I'm way too stimulated.
I gotta go.
Did I get on my team?
Oh shit, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Who are you shooting at?
There's no one even here.
Who are you?
If this is just chaos, I don't even know who's who.
All right, just kill me, just kill me.
I want to get out of this.
No, I don't want to resume the cycle.
I want to, don't want to get out of here.
That was insane.
This game is crazy.
Oh, are you playing Call of Duty?
It's not, I mean that, not Call of Duty.
Okay, let's keep going.
That was Trey Pang 2.
Were there any more that I downloaded that last night?
I'm trying to remember.
Did I, do I have any more of that from yesterday?
I think there was one.
There was one that we were looking at.
Which one was it though?
Because I'm up in the top here.
If you take a look, this is the, so I'm on the action tab right now.
This is action adventure.
Some of these look kind of cool.
Turtles.
What's turtles?
Casual, cute.
Should I do it?
Turtles looks pretty fun.
Action shooter.
Beat him up in D.
This one looks good too.
Gnome online.
Play turtles over going to leave.
I'll play turtles.
Let's do it.
All right.
I'll get turtles.
Let's do it.
The stream is going to F for five seconds while I do this.
Just to let you know.
Okay.
And let's open it.
Turtles demo.
Let's check this one.
So this is a prototype temporary assets.
Okay.
Turtles.
Let's just do it.
World one.
So these globes need to turn into turtles.
What is this?
Okay.
That was really loud.
Did I just pick these up?
Oh shit.
I'm messing this up.
Oh, I don't get stuck.
I like this is I didn't lose to a kid's game.
I'm still in literally first place.
Oh lost to a kid's game literally in first place.
Shit.
It's kind of like snake in a way.
I got everybody.
That's it, right?
I got literally every single person.
That was cute.
That was that I was really cute.
What was wrong with this?
That was it.
I like that.
That was really cute.
Okay.
Three stars, right?
Yep.
Okay, don't go in don't go down the hole because you'll lose
him if you go in the hole.
All right.
I get it.
There's a lot of holes.
New meta.
All right.
So I got to go up grab this one over here.
What just happened?
What?
Oh, I held it down too long.
Okay, be careful.
Let's go.
Okay, I gotta get them all down.
Pretty good, right?
Okay.
Now I'm going to have to spread them out a little.
Oops.
All right.
Get everybody into the wall.
Is that blocked?
Does the seashell block?
Nope.
Oh shit.
Hold on.
Oh fuck.
Oh my God.
I didn't mean to do that.
Whatever.
Just again.
I'm done.
I blew it so bad.
I blew it really bad.
I just like kind of went too.
All right.
Maybe one star.
Two stars.
All right.
Next.
No, not yet.
So be careful of the birds.
The birds will eat me.
Oh, I get it.
Okay, so you just can't be in that spot when the seagull comes.
Sounds easy enough.
I hope it's just that one spot.
How do I get away from it?
How do I do this?
I can't do it.
No.
I'm good.
Did I miss an egg?
Nope.
We're good.
Go back down this way.
Is there a time limit?
Why is the music getting faster?
Sounds like a time limit.
How am I going to get them up there?
What?
I have to do it like one by one.
Wait, I got it.
I got an idea.
Oh, no.
Oh my God.
Forget it.
Whatever.
This game is fun, actually.
I like it.
I don't have very many complaints.
What?
I really don't.
I mean, is it a kind of a simple little puzzle game?
Sure.
But can you find something to complain about?
No, fuck this game, man.
It's super cute and really easy to understand and challenging
and really just kind of fun.
And where's the blood, man?
Where's the blood?
How come you're not shooting anyone?
What's there something to complain about?
I want to hear it.
No, man.
The games are cute and like fun.
And it's like really looks like really anybody can enjoy it.
Dude, anybody can enjoy this.
Dad, tell that to the potion game.
That's unfair because the potion get this game is pick up
and play the potion.
It was a big story.
Oops, and the potion game was really cute.
What would you what would you complain about the potion game?
Pushing it was fine, too.
I give that like a I get that like a three eight.
What?
Oh, come on.
I mean for the fact that a lot of people say and I'll move on
a lot of you seem to be really, really connecting and really upset
when one of the turtles gets grabbed.
But you didn't care about this game.
I thought this was like a kid's game.
I don't care.
You do though.
You're rooting for these turtles.
You want them to succeed just like we all do.
See that move right there.
Guys, not every game has to have swears in it.
Not every game has to have swear words.
Oops, right when you hatched right when you hatched.
What I think I need to thin them out.
I don't think I can get up there all the way.
The seagull mechanic is really cool.
You know why because you can't just sit here and think it
makes you have to move.
I would call that that's a that's a brilliant game design
choice.
This game is moving into the force.
I just want you to know that 3.4.
Oh, I like it.
This is really cute and fun.
I don't have anything to complain about.
I wish I could I wish I could sit here and be like, well,
you know, I don't like animals.
Like, what do you want me to say?
I don't like this game because I don't like turtles.
I don't like reptiles.
It pisses me off reptiles piss me off.
I can't think of a reason why you would not like it and
excuse me community.
One of our favorite things of all time is a game called
Super Frog, which is far less complex than this game.
Oh, I got a big one.
So you can merge three or is that only specifically and
let's find out.
All right.
You got a new mechanic here now.
That's three.
Oh, no.
Okay.
The little ones ones with a smaller design game doesn't
have candy.
You don't know that yet.
We just started playing it and it's like Beach, you know,
wait, I can combine.
I need to combine.
Yeah, it's summertime.
It's nice out.
Somebody said check your CPU and GPU usage to make sure
this is not a oh, oh, come on, please.
No, that's it.
Things just can't be fun and simple with like a cool
mechanic shit.
This is gonna be hard.
Did I get them all?
I think it is right.
I did.
I got everybody.
Can I combine the big Turtles?
Oh, almost three.
All right.
Well, I think I'm almost at the end of the demo.
Let's do we'll do one or two more.
I like it.
Three big ones makes a bigger one.
Yeah, almost 90% of you guys like Turtles.
You'll be buying this game when it comes up.
I guarantee it.
And then a year after this comes out, you're still going
to be listening to the soundtrack.
And then your YouTube history will be Turtles Steam OST.
You can't fool me.
Get a game over before you stop playing.
Yeah, that sounds fair.
We do have a lot more to go through which we don't have
to do all of them, right?
It's not like, oh my God, we have to play every single demo.
This is just a cool.
I like this event a lot.
It makes it so stuff that I never would have even cared
about.
It's just I'm going to try it because it's just there.
It's just available and you can just get it and try it
and the games aren't out yet.
I would probably be less excited about this event if the
games that you could download were games that were like,
oh, they've been out already.
But these are most of these.
I think all of them are not out yet.
That's really cool.
It's like a little little taste like a little sneak peek.
I got to combine some.
Yeah.
All right, give me that.
Let's combine the big ones.
Shit.
Oh shit.
Fine.
Hey, what's going on here?
That's three.
That was three.
What happened?
I missed an egg.
I can't miss an egg.
Why did the three big ones not combine?
Oh fuck you.
I shouldn't even come back down here.
So why won't they combine?
There's three in a row.
Too big.
I thought the big ones could combine too.
And this is temporary assets.
So you tell me this game is only going to get better.
All right, this last one.
Oh, that's the pattern for the big ones.
I get it.
So it's got to be in like a triangle.
Yeah, games get scores for different reasons.
If I give this like a four three, which I'm not going to,
but if I do and the game I played before this was like a
four two or something.
Remember this is based on it.
It's like a four.
It's a four point one.
For the genre that it is in.
This does not mean that this game is better than any of the
more elaborate demos we've played.
This is a four point one in the category of puzzle fun kids
based children's type games.
You know what I mean?
Like entertainment E for everyone puzzle like kids can
play it old people can play it.
I can play it.
You can play it.
20 year olds can play it 40 year olds can play E for everybody.
I think I think I'm in trouble here.
Go faster.
I'm doing fine.
Yeah.
No, not even kids.
Not even kids game.
I'm just saying like an anybody can play it and enjoy it anybody
going to go this way.
No, I gotta wrap around.
I would rather just go crawl on the beach.
Yeah.
Okay, so go to the beach then.
Why?
Why is that?
Why do you have to have one or the other?
Nah, dude, I don't want to play this.
I'd rather go to the beach instead.
You can still do that.
You don't have to just not go.
What do you mean?
Why are you choosing to go to the beach or play this game?
No, I'd rather go to the art.
All right.
Let me make a big one a really big one.
Boom.
Nice.
All right.
I got a huge one.
How come I'm not seeing like pepe D's and shit really?
I want to see fun pepe dancing emotes because that's what belongs
here.
Yeah, that's what I want.
That looks so funny.
Like why would you be that excited to dance to this?
Everyone's having such a good time.
That's so cute.
I love it.
This is psychotic.
How is this?
How is this psychotic?
People are dancing to a fun song.
I'm so distracted by the dancing.
I feel like the dancing is getting faster when I look over here.
It looks like the dancing is getting faster.
No, oh God.
Oh, I can't see.
We're just fucking doing a move.
It is getting faster.
You're freaking me out.
It actually is getting faster.
No, get down.
Get down.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
I didn't do that on purpose.
I swear to God.
Fucking music is freaking me out.
Okay, now it is psychotic.
You guys.
All right, I got it.
I'm losing my mind.
I can't I honestly I keep looking over there and it's making it worse.
Get over here.
Okay, I'm good.
Nice.
It's 4.1.
This one's 4.1.
Absolutely.
Without a doubt.
Very cool.
There it is.
There's turtles.
Wish listable on Steam right now.
I just wanted to just fuck with you for a second.
All right, that was turtles.
What else we got?
Let's take a look.
Turtles with an exclamation point.
Turtles exclamation point.
That's very very I'm sure if you probably type in turtles, you probably wouldn't get it.
What else we got on that list of action games?
Let's take a look.
This is also open world stuff too.
Turtles.
Bloodhound.
This looks like another kind of shooter game.
Scrap Riders.
Is this a beat-em-up?
Less FPS.
Yeah, we've done a lot of FPS.
That's right.
Is this game is FPS but looks good.
No.
Okay, what about it's like another page.
What is this a cooking game?
Fribbles.
Crafting.
Agriculture creature collection.
I think I'm gonna I think I'm gonna click on this one.
Hold on.
Let's not go too hasty.
Westwood shadows.
Survival Horror.
This is FPS.
Oddworld.
There's a new Oddworld coming out.
Okay.
Astronite.
Looks pretty cool.
Sort of retro Game Boy style 2D game.
Play Slayers X.
Well, hold on.
I just want to take a look at a few pages.
Far Star.
Panic Porcupine.
This is like a Son of the Hedgehog game.
It says difficult.
Panic Porcupine.
Okay.
Ooh, parkour.
This could be fun.
I might puke though.
It's a 2D game.
Dread Haunt.
Take a couple pages.
Hold on.
Undead Pixelmonks.
Gust of Wind.
I see stealth there.
I'm not sure I want to click it.
It looks pretty cool though.
Kingdom Gun.
Zolotl.
Fight of Steel.
Whoa, what is this?
You make your own cyber fighter?
Maybe.
EXP War Trauma.
Psychological Horror.
Goodbye, Dr. Sanchez.
Mythic.
All right.
I don't want to get overwhelmed.
What is this?
Zombies and keys.
All right.
Let me go back.
We're going to do Flibbles.
Yeah, Flibbles time.
Let's go.
That's the one I'm most interested in right now.
You're going to get a minor F here.
And then maybe I'll go to...
I want this so much.
Why haven't I...
Why did I not do this for the last two weeks?
I was busy, whatever.
Now I'm going to be busy this week.
This like next six or seven days too.
A lot of stuff going on.
Not just in...
Kind of the stream world, but in my personal life too.
A lot of things I need to do.
It's very busy.
You look like Giga Chad today.
I don't think so.
Okay, we're good to go.
Flibbles.
Are you guys ready for Flibbles?
Whoa, this is actually weird.
Look at this.
Weird.
Oh, this is weird.
Okay.
Should I use the controller?
Let's turn the...
All right, settings.
Can I do it from here?
How do I...
How do I turn the audio down?
Oh, should the audio...
The audio is not coded into the game yet.
Okay, so I do have to do this.
That's better.
So I cannot change this.
It's probably very, very...
It's probably very early.
All right, let's go Flibbles.
I have really high hopes for Flibbles.
Come on, look at this.
This is perfect.
Come on, Flibbles.
Continue.
I didn't do anything.
New game.
All right, both headphones going for this.
This music.
Wait, I can actually hold on.
Interact?
How do I...
Oh, okay.
Forward?
It's a five.
It's starting at five.
Protect at least 50 tomatoes from the evil goo.
Fish three Flibbles from the fountain.
Finish the level in less than nine minutes.
Okay.
We're gonna do controller.
Escape.
Open task, move, aim, interact, jump, look around, throw, shoot.
Dash.
Interact with Flibbles.
I can dash?
Interact with the crates.
Where are the crates?
I can't, man.
Okay, interact with the crates.
Where are the crates?
Over here.
Aim with up and down.
Okay, aim.
Why do I have dynamite?
Why would I do that?
Craft dynamite in the crafting menu.
Dude.
What are you talking about?
Why would I want to make dynamite?
You've got a friend in me.
Got a friend in me.
To people.
Having one of a life and I have...
That's it, right?
Somebody post the lyrics in the chat right now.
I'll do it.
Post the lyrics.
I don't care if it's spam.
Don't give a shit.
Post the lyrics to the song and I'll do it.
All right.
I'm going off cam for this.
Give me the lyrics of the song.
Actually, can one of the mods do it in the mod chat?
Yeah, guys, you don't do it.
Don't do it.
I'll do it.
Somebody in the mod chat do it.
Just like copy the text and paste it.
Oh, hold on.
I can't see this.
I'm going to try.
Here we go.
Wait, I'll get on the next cycle.
Me, me, me, me, me, me.
You got a friend in me.
You've got a friend in me.
Where the road looks.
Rubber head and you're miles and miles from your nice woman.
You just remember what your old pal said.
But you've got a friend in me.
You've got a friend in me.
You've got, they say it this many times.
He says it this many times.
You got troubles.
I've got them too.
There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you.
We stick together and see it through.
Cause you've got a friend in me.
Yeah, you've some other some other folks might be a little bit
smarter than I am.
Bigger and stronger too.
Maybe but none of them ever will ever love you.
What?
The what though?
That's what he says.
The way I do.
It's me and you.
And as the years go by.
Our friendship will never die.
You're gonna see it's our destiny.
That laugh that lyric.
No one's ever gonna love you.
What the hell?
I'm back.
You're hurting us.
All right.
So I have dynamite.
What do I do with the dynamite?
Craft on me in the crafting machine.
All right.
Okay.
How are you?
How do I turn it on?
Wait, what do I do with all this?
What do I do with this?
I put it in the crafting machine.
Does anybody know what to do?
Use the diamond to fish for flibble shoot with left of right
trigger.
Do I light the fuse?
What do I do with this stuff?
Fish for flibbles?
You have to craft it first.
Didn't I just do?
Okay, so okay crafting machine.
So I put this in here and then one of these things here and
then it's going to spit out a dynamite.
Okay, I have a dynamite now.
Now I can will this explode if I throw it?
How do I turn it on?
I can go fish for where I fish for them into the phone.
Where's the phone?
This is GTA original Grand Theft Auto one that just threw
me back Jack is an emergency flip the land is in danger.
A purple goo substance appeared out of nowhere.
It consumes everything that comes in contact with it.
We managed to find out that you can use water to fend it
off and I beg of you.
People probably hate me right now.
It's all right.
I don't want to like it hurt anybody's head.
I have a weapon.
Okay, I need to craft a water gun.
What's going on?
Oh shit.
Nice.
Okay, I can put some I can fertilize that what happened.
All right.
I don't wait wait, wait, wait.
I got it.
This game is so cute.
I like this.
What does it need?
Okay.
I need like a handle.
Oh right here.
Put it in.
No, put it in.
Don't make me scream.
You've got a friend.
Oh my God.
That's how you get around.
Okay.
Now give me what else does it need?
Oh, it needs like a barrel.
Okay.
I just what just hurt somebody.
Oh, no, that was that.
I need like a handle.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
All right.
I got it.
Fill up your ammo with the fountain.
Dermot, will you smoke cigarettes on stream?
Somebody asks me that every day.
Why?
What are you?
What are you doing?
Oh, murder attack.
Defend.
Defend us.
Get him.
Attack.
They're eating my tomatoes.
See you in hell.
Give me the gun.
Shoot the what?
Grab the bag to shoot seeds.
You know what I'll say about this game?
It's super clean.
I it's so shiny.
It's so shiny.
How do you get the game to look like that?
Look at how shiny everything is.
These guys are like the graphics look really I like the graph.
Look at that.
Look at that guy.
When do they stop?
Who's that little guy?
They've eaten almost every single tomato on the farm.
Well, that was a huge birth.
Will you guys do something?
They're just walking around.
Did he kill my tree trunk guy?
Oh, these are flibbles.
Okay.
Did I get it?
I think there's a bug in my head.
How am I so bad?
What are you talking about?
I how do I turn off this thing that's shooting him out?
How do I close the portal?
Close the portal.
I don't have a farm anymore.
I got goofied.
This is scary.
I like this one.
We got that you got a friend and me out of it.
Let's do another one.
Rate the game.
You know what?
I think that I think that game is charming.
I think the game is charming.
Although I will say it was a little weird crafting dynamite.
Is it over or two?
I think it okay.
I needed to see more about I need to see more flibbles.
I think I did you see more flibbles.
I think I played that for as long.
I played that for a long time.
I played that for a while.
All right, let's keep looking.
There was one more here that I want to do and let's get out of action
adventure open world.
What do we got?
Floating life to Pirates Bay.
Oh my goodness.
Should I do this one?
Yep, I'm playing Pirates.
I'm playing Pirates Bay.
I want to give it a try and then I'll keep let's queue up a couple.
So let's keep that on here.
What about other open world project canopy detained the beat-em-up.
Whoa underwater space renowned Twilight's final judgment.
Okay.
Well, there's a few that I'm interested in contraband
police Frontier Hunter Master Key frog monster.
That's a shooter.
Okay, zappling.
This looks I might want to try this one.
Okay, we'll get frog monster.
What else Grand Theft Auto Grand Theft Gato vice kitty.
Okay.
I mean, I'm going to download this one.
All right, let's do let's get those two and then we'll have free to
do here Grand Theft Gato.
And what was the other one?
There's one more.
What was the other one?
There was two that was going to do frog monster there.
Okay.
These games are all installed now.
So let's start with what was the first one we got.
I already forgot but it's okay.
Let's just start with frog monster.
Why not?
Welcome frog monster demo.
I've had so much fun developing this game and I appreciate you
checking it out excited to bring you more in the full release.
Cool screen.
Okay.
All right.
Oh wait, you can't see but I got to turn it up.
Okay.
That's good.
All right.
This is frog monster new game.
Right click to lick and press escape to open whatever that was.
What the hell?
I think that's all right.
Escape is what?
Seeds.
Okay.
So what do I do?
Just go.
Left click is shooting hard reload.
The audio is kind of low.
The sound audio is low.
Okay.
Turn the master volume up.
That's a little better.
What should I lick?
Okay.
All right.
I get it.
Get the fuck away from me.
You can press F to use spells when you have enough mana.
What the hell?
Take this weapon.
Little big on you, but it'll do.
Okay.
Shotgun.
Swap weapons.
Interesting mechanic.
Can I eat the flies in the air?
Damage with spells to heal.
Oh, all right.
Mana that has not been picked up decays over time.
Oh, I don't.
Wait, I don't have any what?
I have no ammo.
Shotgun.
Bug.
Is that the villagers from Minecraft?
I'm almost dead.
Something weird in that water.
I'm not much of a swimmer though.
Something weird.
Let's taste it.
Tastes fine to me.
Can I pick it up?
What's going on?
Walk up and press E on pink flowers to heal.
Respawn point.
So this is my menu.
All right, let's go.
Whoa, okay.
All right, I get it up.
Shotgun shells.
Thank you.
That hurts.
I'm gonna die.
That's how much health Croft had.
Is that how much health he had?
Oh my God.
I got this.
I'm doing it again.
I'm in the wall.
Fuck, I'm gonna die again.
What is this?
I don't know.
I can't use a spell.
I don't have any mana.
Stop fucking reloading and shoot the guy.
That was fun.
Heal up.
Good.
Let's keep going.
You dropping anything else?
What game is this?
This is called Frog Monster.
Frog Monster.
Found a piece of mana upgrade.
I'll take it.
Okay, go back down.
Yeah, what's this called?
It's called, it's got stars with a V, right?
So cubes when you put them all together.
So the V of, I cannot think of it.
Voxel, yeah.
This is cute.
No, not virgin.
Well, this is pretty.
This is, this is nice.
This is nice.
These are kind of shrooms that you smoke.
But you don't smoke mushrooms.
You don't smoke shrooms.
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
You get to live.
How does he know?
Why wouldn't I know that?
Ooh, cool.
Shit.
All right, one more try.
That's it.
I'm done with this one.
One more try.
You suck at this game.
The game is kind of tricky.
One more try and that's it.
Environments are beautiful and the gameplay has a lot of potential.
Sound design and music need a lot of, need a lot of work.
I would agree with that.
But here's the thing.
And this is something that's really important.
It's if you really think about it.
It's probably less than five to ten people doing this.
So that's why all these games, right?
Well, most of them, right?
You are never going to hear me say like, oh, wow.
This game's fucking awful, right?
Like why would I do that?
It takes a lot of fucking guts to kind of put yourself out there
and do this kind of shit.
It does.
And if you only have like a few people,
like especially if it's only one or two people.
I mean, this is, this is remarkable for it being a small team, right?
Yeah, you got to, I don't want, here's the thing.
I think discouraging people from doing something that they, that they're
like passionate about and they think is cool.
And this is good.
This is actually fucking good.
I wouldn't be able to do something like this, even if I really spent time on it.
I don't ever want anyone to think that like, oh, my game's fucking bad.
Oh shit.
No, I don't want somebody to, I don't want to like rain on somebody's passion,
rain on somebody's, you know, way they try to make a living and everything, right?
I'm not going to do that.
Could this game use a little work?
Yeah, it absolutely fucking could.
But I think it's fun.
I think this is good shit.
A little bit more time in the oven.
This thing can be fucking fantastic.
Now.
Yes.
You've heard me say, yeah.
All right.
Hold on.
But like fuck Capcom is a little different.
It's not, that's not like three people making Resident Evil 8.
Okay.
There's not one guy didn't make Resident Evil 8.
If they did, holy shit.
That would be a crowning achievement.
Yeah.
This is, this is, this is a time for us to come together as gamers.
I'm a gamer.
Don't forget.
And celebrate all the cool shit that people are making.
That's a coming up, right?
So I'm, the rating system is more of a joke than anything else.
I don't, it's not actually accurate, right?
Cause this is a demo.
This is not like it.
It's not like this is the full experience.
Some of these games are a year away.
Just admit that you hate this.
What?
I don't.
Oh, you know, you didn't say this.
You said that you hate video games.
You know, I kind of do.
I kind of do.
Okay.
Same, same, same.
All right.
So we're going to, we, we agree then we, we agree.
Last try.
That's it.
We're going to actually try this one now.
Okay.
Hold on geeks.
Why do you have to be such a positive Peter?
I'm really not even a positive Peter.
You guys have been here for a long time.
I'm not really positive Peter.
He's a positive Peter.
Come on.
No, I cannot reliably tell you that a game is good or bad based
on a 15 minute demo.
That's impossible.
That's not possible.
I actually like what I'm doing.
This game is called Frog Monster.
One word.
Turn the music down a little.
There we go.
That's kind of the point of a demo to see if you like it.
Oh, yeah.
Don't die, please.
Smash, smash, smash, smash, smash.
All right.
That's it.
That was fun.
That was called Frog Monster.
It's somewhere in the threes.
I actually like the death screen.
I think it's cool.
I come in next.
We've got, uh, please do Slayers X.
I will.
Oh, cat, right.
Grand Theft Gato, Vice Kitty.
The graphics up.
I think this is good.
How does this work?
Press B to meow.
Good cats can navigate.
Press M to view the local map.
Holy shit.
This is a whole city.
Okay.
Hi, it's great to see you.
You can really get hungry earning likes and subscribers.
We're out of food again.
I'll get it.
The downstairs door is locked.
We're trapped in here.
Man is too tired to shop.
Maybe he needs some candy.
Okay.
Man is too tired to shop.
Maybe he needs some candy.
Okay.
Binding human ten candy.
There's candy in the box.
Okay.
All right, here's candy.
Talk to Ricky.
He'll go shopping soon.
Now there's a cat downstairs he wants to talk to you.
Let's go.
The fuck.
And what do you do?
WHAT?!
Get the hell away from me! This guy's going to kick me? What the fuck? Oh my god, I'm on his head!
What the fuck is happening? Get this guy out of here! Am I ready? Find the strange cat. Okay.
Ponzilla. Want some sick power-ups? Yes. Okay, ever heard of XP? It piles up as you do awesome,
but it's useless by itself. You gotta spend it, cat. Open your inventory and look at the upper
left corner. Oh, okay. What did I just do? Are those hairballs? I'm not big, but you need me.
Okay, what do I need? Ever seen your journal? It's how you avoid getting lost. Open it with J.
Okay. In your journal, you can manage tasks. Click a finished one to get XP. Oh, all right. Okay. Yes.
Love cheese, I guess. Beep boop wrong. You didn't use J to read the task. What? I can't stand this
stuff. Why is my name Mouse3 anyway? This world makes no sense. All right, let's go.
Find Trinikitty next. She will help you with your skills. Wait, are you ready? I believe.
Climb the bookcase over there, jump at it, left click and hold. How? What the fuck? I got the
candy. You gotta- I can climb anything? Okay, I can climb anything. Find the strange cat. You can
climb anything. Are you the strange cat? What does that sound? What? How much for level one melee?
Um, how do I- what do I do? How do I see that? How do I get that menu? How do I get to that menu?
50. Okay, got it. All right, I gotta find the strange cat downstairs. How do I get downstairs?
There we go. Malthus. Okay. Talk to my crew. They will show you the way to the outside world.
My crew is on the second floor. I can only give you the keys to the door. You must walk
through it. Find Mayor Mittens and your destiny. Open your inventory and equip the keys.
Okay. How do I get out of here? I'm out. Let's go. Can you drive a car? Can I drive a car?
What the fuck? You can drive a car? Why can I drive a car? Dirty whiskers. Sorry, you know,
this is the demo, but hey, what's the next best thing to owning the game? Wish listing it on
Steam because that's where all the stuff is coming out. Don't you want to do it? I'm not
going to click that because I think it might actually do it. I don't know. I'm afraid to
like click that button. All right, so where do I go? Oh, no, don't ghost ride the car.
Funk music? Did I kill that guy? What's going on here? Okay. All right. Well, what's going on
here? What happened? What's it? Diesel tools? Wait, maybe you can tell me. Give me fuel. Give me fire.
They're cheering on a race? Oh, okay. Let's go. You ready? Three, two, one, go.
The car I'm telling right now. Give me the controller. I think it's probably going to be
easier. Nope. I died. I can't jump. Oh, wait, somebody here. All right. There's Mayor Mittens.
Okay. Here we go. You want to work for me? Yes. Oh my God. A lackey of my own. You've made it.
Okay. Right. Work. To be my helper, you need wheels. There's a small car to your right.
Go take it for a small car. Okay. Hi Ed. W A S D to drive. Yeah, this is a why does it keep
cycling through gears? The car doesn't sound right. I'm not even holding the acceleration.
Well, to be fair, a cat wouldn't know how to use a manual. I mean, not yet. Oh, I gotta do one, two,
three, four, five. Okay. Two. Where's three? Where's three?
I know not yet. I'm trying to go over here. It's way too dank.
All right. The turning is a little slow. Don't. Okay. Four, five, six. Four, five, six.
No way. That was six. All right. What do you need, Mittens? Okay. We're over the big time.
I got some real work now. It's gonna be intense. Get ready. Person was making a tree for it and
now they're stuck in the tree. Crazy day, right? I need to go get them down. Fire cats are already
there to help. Jump, hold, attack the human's back and hold down the button. You can drive
him around like that. Okay. Over there. All right. Let's go. Where's my car? I don't need a car.
Why can't this guy get down? I don't understand why you can't get down. Okay. Let's go.
Oh, you're welcome. What game is this? The game is called Grand Theft Gato Vice Kitty.
Okay. Signed up my amazing helper cat. Your reward is a new toy. Maybe it's a gun, a pack,
a thingy. Okay. Works in a garage over by the apartments. Tell him I'm counting on his vote.
Okay. Let's move. This gets at least five letter grades because of the title. Oh, give me this car.
Wait, where is this? Oh, it's right here. Okay. I made something amazing. Cat pack 9,000.
Assemble the pieces. Okay. I yawned, but I don't want to be yawning on camera. Don't
fucking drive off the edge. I got another one. It's fine. All right. Find the pieces.
End of the stream voice. No, no, I'm fine. I'll go refill my tea. Wait, where is this stuff?
Wait, was it right next to me? T means he's going to go smoke a bowl.
Where is this stuff? Oh, it's up here. I don't smoke. I don't smoke weed. I eat it.
I like it better. You know why I like to eat it, by the way, if you have, you know, you know,
and you're over 21, you know, it's illegal in your area and you just be careful. All things in
moderation. When I smoke weed, I don't like how fast smoking weed hits you. And then it's just gone.
It's like, boom, it's an absolute explosion. Just and then it's gone in like 30 minutes.
I like the feeling of letting it kind of work up for an hour or two. And then you can stay in that
kind of mellow state, whatever you want to be in for a few hours. I like it. That's why I like to
eat it. 30 minutes. It's like four hours for me. Um, I don't have very much experience with smoking.
I'd rather eat it. So but the few times I've done it, it was just like, so I was like, too,
too much. And it just hit me like a truck for like half an hour to an hour. And then you just have
to come down. I feel a little I know a lot of people the opposite, where it's like, if you take
a view, eat it. And all of a sudden, you're you don't want to be high for four or five hours,
right? Because that's sometimes if you do a lot of edibles or whatever that can happen.
And I get that I get it completely. How do I get on the roof? It's also what your body's used to.
Yeah, that's true. How do I get on the roof? Edibles can really sneak up on you. Yes, they can.
That's why you should really be very careful with it. It really depends on the person. Oh, yeah.
If you like smoking it versus eating it. Absolutely. All right, I'm done. We're gonna
do another one. Actually, let me get some tea. I need to perk up a little. I need to pick me up.
That was Grand Theft Gato Vice Kitty. It was pretty fun. I think I like I think the music's
part of my favorite part. I'll be right back and refill my water. Get some tea with it. I'll see in
like two, three minutes, maybe five minutes. BRB. I'm still here. I just wanted to somebody mentioned
the so what the when I when I get tea, some of the time I get something called liquid IV.
And somebody said be careful those things like 100 milligrams of caffeine.
See, I do this. This is my tactic with it. I usually only do half a packet.
I usually do about it's about 40 milligrams of caffeine. Liquid IV is amazing. Yes.
It's got a kind of a strange name. Not 100 milligrams of THC. What the fuck are you talking
about? No, no, no, no, no, no. We're talking about two completely different things.
Let me separate this out. The powder that I use is green tea powder, right? This matcha powder.
And this liquid IV is the name of the brand or whatever. It's like a little packet. 100 milligrams
of caffeine is not that big of a deal. Cup of coffee is what 80 70 to 90. So that's not a big
deal. One cup of coffee is less than 100. A little bit less than 100. Something between 40 50 60.
Regular green tea is 30. Yeah, no, I am not drinking. Let me be really clear about this.
I really like these things. They've been I've been drinking a lot of them over the last few
months. Maybe like I don't do it every day. Maybe like once every once every three or four days,
once every five days. So once a week, twice a week. But here's the thing. You do one packet
over the course of like pretty much a whole day, which ends up being about the equivalent of maybe
two cups of coffee. But I like it a lot. I really do. No, no, no, no. Yeah, it's electrolytes too.
Yeah. Essentially, it's kind of like a Gatorade with green tea powder and caffeine in it.
So if I don't match a powder like green tea powder is only like 30 milligrams.
If I really need something, I'll drink one of these liquid IVs. Yeah, I'm talking about caffeine.
Yeah, no, no, no, no. This stuff is no. Trust me, I wouldn't drink this if I didn't think it was
any good. This is an ad. No, no, I just actually drink these matches. Not that high in caffeine
isn't the green tea is 30 milligrams of caffeine. Some people drink a bunch of monster a day. Yeah,
I always try to stay. I know I'm supposed to be leaving, supposed to get out of here.
But I really realistically, real talk, I've tried to cut a lot of the coffee I drink a day.
So I typically will replace coffee with one of these green tea drinks. And it's yeah, you know,
still has caffeine, but it's fine. And the company in general, too, I like looked into the company
too. I think they're at least what they claim. They try to be sustainable and stuff. So that's
cool. Don't leave. How is this not an ad? I'm not being paid to tell you this. This is something
that I literally do on a weekly basis. I mean, could it be an ad? Sure. I mean, yeah, I guess so.
Have you ever had matcha ice cream? Oh, yeah. I became a green tea Andy over the last six months.
I love it. You should email them thoughts on coffee ice cream. I got okay, I gotta go. But
yeah, sponsorships and, you know, advertisement type shit. You guys know that I'm
evolved is working on that stuff. So I don't know. That'd be kind of cool. I mean, I actually use it.
Get a matcha sponsor. No, no. All right. I actually BRBS in a minute. Wait, somebody raided? What
happened? Can I wait, wait, wait. Somebody actually raided. Who raided? I can't see it.
This is a big raid. I can't even see who it is. Who is it? Big balls raid. Big balls. Big balls.
Um, thanks a lot. Big balls. I appreciate it. Everybody coming over. Thanks for the raid.
Hold on. Are you guys making this up? I saw a lot of like big balls, big balls and like, hey,
we're here. I don't know. I don't understand. Hold on. Let me look at my dashboard. I got,
yeah, I got trolled. I didn't. Yeah, I seriously did. Yeah, that's okay. Yeah, there's no raid.
Okay. All right. I'll be right back. Bye. What's up? How you doing? The big balls raid was real.
Yeah. From beta 64. Oh, cool. All right. So it was real. Well, thanks for doing it. Welcome guys.
You pissed on a raid? What? No, I didn't. I even asked and I looked. What are you talking about?
You're so high. You keep laughing like Seth Rogen. Such a specific. I'm not even sure if it's an
insult or not, but in a specific comment. Okay, let's go. What else was it? What was the other
one I downloaded? There's one more. What did I have queued up? Pi. Oh, the pirate game. Right.
Turn that off. Get it open. Very cool. This game is very bright. It's very colorful. Just wanted
to warn you. Why is all this off? Oh, sorry. Okay. All this is turned off. I don't know why.
You guys ready for the pirate bay? Pirates Bay. Pirates Bay. Let's go. New game. You can roll to
avoid damage. Probably controller, right? Yeah. Control scheme. Change the controller. Okay.
That's jump. Crouch. Oh, F1. That's going to be different. All right. That's dodge. This is a
dodge roll or dodge roll. Use. Move. Hide. Change. Target. Aim. Attack. Oh, shit. That's block.
All right. We'll figure it out. Talk. A. Talk. Talk. A. A. A. All right. What is it over here?
E. What's up? I don't want to spend any money right now. No. Is there a sprint? Okay. Just
checking to see what happened. Am I holding my head underwater? How do I get back up? I just want to
see if he died if he jumped in the water. Where do I go? Where do I go to get up from here?
All right. Use ladder. There we go. Oh, yeah. That was quick. Okay. So now what do I do?
Put the sails up. All right. Let's move. Let's go for it. Can I steer? Let's go. Let's go. We're
going to that island right there. Open your sails. Oh, shit. All right. Now let's go. Am I steering?
How do you steer? Okay. We're going to do a keyboard. You only have one person on this
whole crew. I would be freaking out if I saw this coming into the port. How do you... Is there a
break? All right. How do you... So I made it this town. How do I stop the boat from moving?
I need to put the anchor out? Where's the anchor? There's no... There's no brake pedal, dude. Oh,
drop anchor. I got way anchor. Wait. Okay. I got to get closer. Why do I need a crew? I need... I
can't just do this by myself. I need to take a cigar out of my mouth. Be like, all right, hoist
the sails. Why am I doing this by myself? Oh, fuck. We're getting in... We're coming in hot.
All right. Stop. There we go. That's not going anywhere, right? No, we're good. This guy looks
like he's waiting for me. What do I get? I want a weapon. Is this a hostile territory? I have no
idea. Is this a hostile territory for me? I don't think so. Oh, wait. What's up there? Okay.
Oh, a pirate. Want to see my weapons and ammo for sale. Okay. You've got a saber, musket,
blunderbuss. That's actually a lot of weapons. All right. I need... I need like a thousand bucks.
Thousand bucks. I think it's like a quest up here. All right. What is that? See? 20 meters.
I'm going that way. Your boat is floating away. No, it's not. Do I need to kill this guy? Hello,
traveler. Have you heard of the legends of the most terrifying pirates of these seas?
I can tell you where to find them for a small fee. And if you beat them, your profit will be
much larger. Okay. Where is the rogue admiral? Thank you. Let's go get him. All right. Where's
my... All right. Where's my... That's such a scam. Oh, there we go. No. Oh, there we go. Okay. Over
there. 1,700 meters that way. Yeah. I spent all my money, but I'm going to get... I'm going to go
here. I'm going to get my... I'm going to kill this guy. Get a bounty for it. I thought that was just
rolling credits. I was like, we're getting credits already? Did I run out of time? That's not my
boat right there, right? That's not my boat, right? No, that's my boat. Brawl demo time, right? Yeah.
That's how I was like... Right over to the music. This thing's in sync, right? What's the game? The
game is called Pirate Bay. Pirates Bay. Part of the Steam demo week. Go check it out if you think
it's cool. You don't have... It's literally free. You don't have to do anything, but just install
the game. That's it. Okay. Let's go find this guy. 1,800 meters this way. All right. Full speed ahead.
I just... I... Somebody just talked about my beard. They don't like it. They don't like it.
Well, I'm shaving today, so... All right. Let's do it. Let's get him. I don't have any weapons.
How am I going to fight this guy? He's on this island. I'll just beat his ass. It's fine.
Self-overcorrecting. I've never driven a sail... a boat like... a ship like this before. Sorry. I'm
overdoing it. Yeah, there's rain too. There's weather. Okay. I'm going to... Here's my approach.
Put down the anchor. There's a campfire right there. He's definitely right there. Oh, shit.
It's a crewmate. I have no stamina. Can I take this guy's shit? All right. Give me your sword.
Can I loot him? No, I can't. Okay. What? This guy's naked. This guy's naked. Wait. Why is there a
naked skeleton? Wait. What's going on? The other skeleton. The other guy had clothes on. Wait.
Chest. Chest or chest? Right here. Come on. Give me a weapon. Give me a sword. Something.
A thousand bucks. Get the fuck out of here. Leave me alone. Where the fuck are you running to? He's
got so much health. He's got way too much health. I'm going to drown him. Oh, the skeleton's going
to fight him? I have an idea. Did they not go in the water? I'm trying to drag him by his feet.
I'm going to run him over. I'm going to run his ass over. He's got... Look how many people he has.
This is ridiculous. Hit X to pull a weapon out? No, I don't have any weapons. No, I don't... Wait.
What? Do I... Was that actually a sword that I have in my inventory? Let's go. Come on. Where is it?
Don't even... All right. I'm dead. I died. Where do I spawn? Am I still on the island? I do have... I
have a sword. How do I take it out? All right. Let's go. I think I'm on the same... I think I'm
on the island still. Is there a map? Yep. I'm still on the island. All right. This guy's dead.
Is that a foam Minecraft sword or what? Am I going to be able to fight him?
He killed me again. It's made out of aluminum foil. Well, I'll kill him eventually. I get to keep
going back. I'll just... Okay. This is a spoiler for a very popular Marvel movie that I'm about
to spoil. There's a doctor in it. It's a... It's a movie about a doctor and he's weird. Okay.
I can just... I could just doormar move this guy, right? Like, doesn't matter. I'll come back over
and over again. Oh, no. I'm dead. Not Morbius. Doormamu. I'm here to bargain. Doormamu. I'm here
to bargain. Doormamu. R1M? R1? R1? Stop it. I got him. I win. I win. I got 10,000 fucking dollars.
Who cares if I lost 600? Are you kidding me? All right. Get out. Get out. Get out. What if I
lose a percentage? It's probably 20%. Yeah. Fuck all these doormamus. I don't care. I'm out.
This is my boat. Is that my boat? It's not. Well, it is now. Never mind. Where's my boat?
Is my boat gone? I don't see it anywhere. I think it's actually gone. No, that's not it. Wait. No,
it's over here. It's on the map. There it is. I wonder if he had any items. There's probably
stuff here to take, right? Maybe not. Okay. Well, I can buy a gun now. I at least need to see what
the gun is like. I'd rather watch you eat a jar of mayonnaise. You'd probably rather watch me eat a
jar of mayonnaise than a lot of stuff. I don't think it matters what we're doing. I think that
you would probably put that higher on the list because that's weird and crazy and you don't want
to miss that stream. All right. Uh, I need to get back to, what do I need to go? All right. That was
fun. That was good. That was called Pirates Bay. That was cool. It's like a single player pirate
adventure game. Pretty sick. Pretty sick. What else we got? What's the one that everybody keeps
to? I keep seeing it in chat. I keep seeing people saying this one, this one, this one,
something with an X in it. Slayers X. Is that on here? What, um, what category? Is it action,
adventure, simulation, RPG? What is it? Platformer? There's like, I guess I can just type it in. Okay,
Slayers X. Is this shooter? No, I'm not gonna play this Succubus game. Why would I do that?
They don't even tell me I'm having problems again with this. Why can't I download it?
Hold on. Let me try another one. Maintenance? No, it's not. They did maintenance yesterday.
It's not gonna happen again. What was the other one? What, Celico? Let me try that one. What is
all this about? This is weird. Um, I can't download anything. My Steam is like, fucked up. Well, um,
I guess I can open up the Dread X thing again. That's weird. Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
no, I can't download anything on Steam. Oh, wait. Yeah, I can. It just popped back up.
I think this is actually working. Dude, your chin is huge. Yeah. And guess what? If I have like,
in a fucking street fight, I just, it's like a bird beak hitting you right in the fucking mouth.
No, nevermind. I think Steam's fucked up. It looked like I could download it, but I can't.
Um, I can open Dread X. Play a couple more of those. I was not fair to the Dread X stuff before,
because I had the internet problems and I was annoyed and pissed off. So we can try some of
the Dread X stuff. That's sad because I, this is like over soon. All right. Well, whatever.
You're the comedy relief character that gets killed off. Yeah. Although I know they keep,
they kind of keep the comedy relief character around long enough to make jokes for the movie.
So I'd last a little while, I think. I think I'd last a little while.
Please do some of this stuff for green screen. All right. I'll do the go away,
go away thing. Are you guys going to have me like get attacked by a bear?
All right. Uh, let's go play this other thing over here. That was, that was creepy. I like that one.
They were all pretty good. Dread X. I love this. I love these little like micro games.
The demo stuff I love because it's like only 20, 30, 40 minutes an hour. It's perfect.
Tries to be demo Andy for the rest of my life. Okay. Um, let's get out of here.
What's the, the one that I have downloaded is that sell, sell it go. Let's see if it's any good.
How much longer are you going to stream? Probably not that much longer. And I really,
I'm going to disappoint a lot of people here. Unfortunately, I have a lot of stuff to do this
weekend and into this week. I told you I was going to be kind of erratic with the stream schedule.
You're not going to see me for a little while. You're not going to see me for like five or six
days or something. That's why I was so pissed off yesterday because I wanted to stream yesterday
because I knew I wanted to do two days in a row because I knew I wasn't going to be around.
That's why I was so mad yesterday afternoon. And I know my voice is junk. I know I'm very aware of
it. Let's do this though. Let's play this. Sell it go. Hopefully it's not too long.
Disappointed. What do you mean? Um, I just, I'm really trying to do more than a couple times a
week. What is this? This is a little, let me see. Okay. So here it is. Welcome to the steam next
fest demo. It means a lot to us to play this little game of ours. We hope you like it. It's
been developed for many years and it required a lot of hard work to get here to a point where
you can confidently hand out a free demo to you. While the development of this game is a lot of
fun, complete do-overs for the entire game were frequently made. And it took a while till we
finally had something that we truly believed in. Something that made us go, this is the game that
I want to spend the next couple of years on. Very fair. Oh, it had a different name. Okay.
Game's unfinished. The demo has been significantly altered and that's it. Okay. It's a work in
progress. Yeah. Okay. I get it. Adjust the graphics. Be based on your heart. Please select one of the
answers below. I have a state of the art gaming PC. 3090. Oh, I thought the game crashed.
This is Celico. Press any key. Friendly reminder that you have previously set one or more graphics
to ridiculous. Please be aware that this setting is not optimized for any computer and may cause
performance and visibility issues. So maybe I should change it. I'll go ahead and change it.
What a streamer mode. Really? Wow. Reduce screen shake. That's a plus one for me.
Avoid compression issues. That's a lot of thought that went into that. That's cool.
I'm going to have to put, okay, yeah, let's do this. Let's put this on just high.
Where's ridiculous. Okay. Real-time ground ceiling reflections, mirror reflections. That's cool.
All right. Decal quality. High level of detail. Ultra. I think that's fine.
It told me not to do this because it's literally impossible for a computer. Sounding things in a
good spot. Dude, I got it. Okay. Let's give a round of applause. Having a shitload of options,
even if nobody touches it, is such a huge deal because they might be something that you really
don't like in a game that you can never take out. But when you have the option to take something out,
it's just better. Don't applaud it yet. You didn't try it. Hold on. Look at all this stuff.
Let's see some gameplay. All right. Let's see some gameplay. Let's see some gameplay. Fine.
Okay. Shouldn't these be the same? Shouldn't these be the same? Horizontal and vertical?
Not in this game. Really? Huh? Okay. All right. Let's go. Let's see some gameplay. Ensign.
Lieutenant. Commander. Well, new lieutenant. All right. Here we go. Just play the game. I'm
just making sure I get it in the right spot. Choose your play style. Well, just a traditional
rifle. Start each level with only an assault rifle. There's glowing eyes behind you.
Steam Dome for Celica provides an early look at the game while it's still in development.
Most story elements will be absent until a later demo update. When's the game actually come out?
Is there a date? Grab teddy bear. Notepad. Do I have a gun? Evade soldiers and locate a weapon.
Oh. Lock purple door. Add it to auto. What? Okay. Oh, this is fast. Anything in the trash?
I can jump? We're in space? All right. Cool. All right. Where do I go? Oh, right here.
Right here. All right. Go, go, go, go, go, go. Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I need a gun. I need a gun. I need a gun. Gun, gun, gun, gun. Right now. Gun, gun, gun. I need a gun.
Press E to pick it up. Gun. Gun. Whoa. That animation is cool. The reload animation. It's
like the FPS is low. It's weird. I like it. I like the reload animation.
All the animations are interesting. It feels like, um, I'm on just the normal difficulty.
It feels like, um, like Doom, but it's, it's like a 3D, much cleaner and better looking.
That's weird. Hard to describe. Oh, there's the key. This was, oh, this was a Doom mod. That's right.
Holy shit. I read that in the beginning. Data card. Codex. You can now use your wrist codecs
by pressing caps lock. Powerful information tool. Download a data pad. Contents. All right, cool.
Well, I think I need that. All right. Uh, one, four, three, two. This game is called
Celico. S-E-L-A-C-O. Add it to your wish list for the love of God. Whoa. Wait, wait, wait. Don't,
I don't want to use all my weapons. What's this? Um, oh, it's new info. Cool. So what's the objective
now? Incoming message. Slide attack. Okay. Nice. All right. Where's, where am I going?
Cool. All right. Watch out. Don't die. I'm going to, I have one health.
The enemies are 2D. Cool. Cool. Okay. Back here. More data. What do I do? Door unlocked. Oh,
oh, you need a cheeseburger. That's cool. Oh, I'm so hungry. Oh my God. I want a cheeseburger. So bad.
I need a burger right now. Can this open? Eat a whopper? No, I'm not into that right now. Um,
I went, I'm going backwards a lot. That's a long slide. Challenges. Okay. Cool. Armor lost. Uh,
this game gets like a five at a five for style. And I mean like a one for gameplay. Cause like,
how would I have died there? That's impossible. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. It's cool. Uh, this is
absolutely fine. I love the 2D, 3D. It's so weird. It reminds me of one time I was on family guy.
What these are slow down, slow down. You made my paper shredder overheat. Why? I didn't,
I didn't overload your paper shredder. You do up to six sheets at a time. Don't be dumb and do more
than six sheets. That's the thing that you did. And I know you did, you did like seven or eight
sheets. You said, ah, well, I don't feel like sitting here and doing six at a time. Fuck it.
And it went, and then you look like a fool. I mean, it was foolish what you did on lock.
Lockdown active. Where should I go from here? Somebody's shooting at me from her. This is
absolutely fucking insane to do. Jeezy doom. What's, what's Jeezy doom is it's just the doom
engine. Now, wait, wait, wait. Are we talking to the original doom? Just doom one, just doom
for the Amiga. What? That doesn't make any sense. That doesn't make any sense. This, this, this is,
how does that make any sense? That's crazy. Can I get in here?
I can go in there. Hold on. What about over here? I did this. I did that. I'm missing a door or
something. Well, that's insane. That's remarkable. That's really, really cool. Where's this door? I
know I'm lost. I know, I know, I know, I know. A key or something. Do I need to open it with
something? Wow. Where do I go? There's a light behind you. Yeah, I know. It's called a lamp.
Well, he's only it's this place is in lockdown. Wait, that doesn't mean anything. No, I'm fine.
What? It's in the middle of the room. Oh, got it. I thought I was just looking for a door.
That made that makes a lot more sense now that I'm playing this, that this is doom,
that they just have heavily changed. Happy birthday. Wait, that's who's that? That's me.
Jesus. Whoa, wait, what? Oh, dude, you should play frog monster. I already did. That game was sick.
All right. Where should I go from here? Oh, my goodness. I can't tell that was a bad or a good
idea. I think it was a good idea. What? Where am I? W. Do I have a flashlight? Oh, my God,
I'm going to drown. Wait, wasn't I up here already? No, I do have a flashlight. All right, good.
Come get me. Blue cake. Security level three. Camera feeds. It's a lot going on in this game.
There's a lot going on. That was just a Roomba, but I don't care. It was on the enemy team.
No. Crap. Use Z for med kit. Oh, my God. I'm dumb. Is there a map? I actually don't know. There might
be. Your room is really dumb. Yeah, because I was playing scary games earlier and here we are.
All right. One more attempt and that's it. Then I'm going to call it. I just, I mean, I need a
cheeseburger. It's so bad. It's like the only thing I care about right now. It's the number one thing
I care about. Perfect timing. I'm exhausted. Hopefully get some rest. Rest up. Yeah.
Get some rest. Why not? Those guys hurt a lot. Oh, God. I didn't know you were still here.
I got to go get some meat in me. I got to get some beef with lettuce. What's my special order?
My special order. Why am I still moving around? Lettuce. No, jalapenos, grilled onions,
A1 steak sauce. And that's it. Cheese, grilled onions, jalapenos, A1 steak sauce. Let's get it.
Oh, an A1 steak sauce. Let's get it. I guess I'm fucking tired.
Guys, I only put A1 steak sauce on a cheeseburger. That's it. It never goes on anything else.
I've never had A1 on anything besides a burger. Sometimes when I order a burger,
they just rename it A1 burger sauce because that's where it belongs. I don't put it on everything.
I don't put it on everything. No, that'd be gross. All right. That's going to conclude the stream and
I will see you guys later. Celico. That was really cool. The fact that that's done in a Doom mod
seems impossible. And that's what makes it so cool. A lot of fun games today. I like this. I don't
maybe even if it goes away, I might still do it. So you guys, the next time you guys are going to
see me, let me see. Let me check here. It's probably going to be, I just have, there's a lot going on.
I'll be back in a week. I want to stream. I really want to. I don't want to just leave.
I'm just like not stream for like a week, but probably the 23rd or the 24th. And then after
that, I can promise you that I will be back. No more seven day breaks. So trust me, I want to,
I want to be hanging out, but there's a lot of cool stuff that's going to be happening soon.
Stuff that I'm very excited for. Is there any IRL stuff? Yes, there is. I've got some IRL stuff
that I need to take care of as well as a ton of stream stuff. Baseball is in kind of crunch time
right now, but I'm going to have so much fun with that. That's going to be some of the,
oh, I can't wait. I've been waiting like two years to do that, but everything's good.
Everything's fine. Don't worry. When I say IRL stuff, it's not, it's everything's fine. Don't
worry. There's just a ton of things I have to get done. The baseball stream is going to be the first
first sports event I'm actually going to watch. It's going to be interesting. I will promise you
that it'll be interesting. Yeah. I'll see you guys in a week. Don't forget about me. I look back. I
promise. Thanks for watching. Thanks for the subs. Thanks for the raid. There was a couple of raids
today, right? Or hosts. It's late pretty much anywhere around the world right now. Get some
sleep. Take care of yourselves. Call your mother, you know, the usual. Have a great night guys.
See you soon. Oh, and by the way, when I, when I stream again, I'm going to have a ton of dates
for you guys to mark down. Green screen will have one. Baseball is locked in for the 20th,
by the way. I want to make sure I make that clear. July 20th. It's not July 14th anymore.
We had to do a bunch of stuff with the venue. So that's July 20th. It had to move about six
days later. I might even actually be able to announce the other project, which that would be
exciting too. I would love to be able to announce the other project. I feel like it's going to be
a lot of fun, but good night guys. See you soon. Have a good week. I'll be back. Take care. Goodbye.