Let's just go. Forget waiting for anything, man. Just move. Missiles, you know, screw
the missiles. Take them out when you can take them out and just move up the friggin' tower.
See the missiles are way far behind now. Stay ahead of the missiles. And then you can just
double smash them like... Oh! I thought that was a good plan. Turned out it was a pretty
bad plan. Don't make the screen go that far up. Just do it nice and gently. No, I did
it again. I did it again. Stop doing that. There we go. Okay. Mother. God. Please make
it. What does this asshole have to say now? Don't waste time. Stop floating around. Stomp
on those missiles. Okay, I can't touch those without doing the stomp. I'll be fine. Jump
up the sticky chamber. Perfect. All right. Where am I? That might be too risky to try
to get. I think that might be a little too risky. I never said I was going to gold star
every level. I never said that. Nobody can quote me on that. All I said I was going to
beat the game in like 10 minutes and it's been like probably 40. I don't even know how
long it's been. I'm just getting spammed with missiles right now. Look at all this nonsense.
I got to sit up for this. Sit up straight. Got to clear them before they become too out
of control. That's the theory. God. This is going to be a pain in the ass, man. These
missiles are going to be a thing for the rest of the game. I can already tell. Get out of
my face. Get away from me. I got the checkpoint. That's all that matters. I've got to stop
doing that. Why do they have to jump? Why do those things have to jump? Is there a reason
why they have to be jumping? Don't break your keyboard. What are you, Star? I only have
like one keyboard. I can't like afford to smash it into the ground. I'm not even using
a keyboard. I'm using a controller. Playing this game on a keyboard would be awful. It
would be mind-melting how hard this would be on a controller. This is not even that
difficult. I just need to slow down and stop being such a psychopath. I'm getting this
right now. Get out of here, you giant like fucking wildebeest. Did I touch the flag?
I touched the flag, right? I did. Good. Thank God. Let's get the hell out of here. Another
flag. Don't even destroy those. They're just to mess with you. That's the only reason why
these missiles are even here in this level. Just to mess with you. They're going a little
bit too fast. I did it. Hooray. The Pope. What did that say about the Pope? The Pope
has gone insane. That's too bad. Or been mind-controlled. Anyway, he wants to kill you. Pope wants to
kill me now. Guess you'll have to murder him. Oh well. So I gotta go kill the Pope? That's
the Pope? What's the Pope doing in this weird world? So I gotta go kill the Pope. Howdy.
Hi Pope. I'm the Pope. And I'm gonna fuck you up. Wow. Pope-tastic. What a dick. Is
this a boss fight? Alright, let's go. You think this is a spaceship? Alright, Pope.
You asked for it. I didn't know that was gonna be a thing. Okay. Here we go. Go. Oh man,
this is gonna be hard. This is gonna be hard. That dumbass screen shake at the very beginning
is really messing me up. Hey, what's like shake your screen? Like, look at violently
for like a second of... Whoa. I pulled that out of my ass. I like looked away from this.
This is... I don't even know about this one, guys. I don't know about this one. Fuck! I'm
doing something wrong. I'm going the wrong way. This is a bad route. I gotta beat him
up there. Let's go. There we go. Okay. Keep it going. I have to be way in front of all
that. Bull crap. No checkpoint flags. I don't see any checkpoint flags, by the way. Alright.
That was it. We built a spaceship. Jump in. Is this gonna turn into like a side-scrolling
shooter? Oh wow. It really is. This really is like a side... I can't believe it. That's
what this is. This thing handles like a slug. I can't move at all. Wow. Come on. You're
gonna turn this into like a bullet hell game? Are you kidding me right now? You've gotta
be fucking kidding me. You've got to be kidding me. Stay as far back as you can get and just...
I'm just tapping A right now and just weaving. That's all I'm gonna be doing. I'm just looking
at the bullet hell. Is that... Come on. He's almost got the shield down. Get rid of that
shield. Shield gone. Hit him. Good. Alright. Out of gas. Oh well. What the hell is that?
What the hell is that? I have a rocket launcher. Oh, alright. Yeah. Nice. Shoot him. Shoot this...
This is gonna be... This is gonna be a cake, man. I'm just gonna shoot this... Just shoot
him like probably like five times. Complete the level. Shoot the rainbow launcher at him.
Kill this mother... I can't call the pope a mother effer. That's not right. Kill this
bad guy. The pope. So he does a laser. He does rockets. You cannot get hit by the trail of
the rockets. Oh damn. Okay. I gotta go activate this one over here. Man. Just do it one right
after the other. See if I can... Fuck. This is starting to really irritate me. Can those
hit me? Hopefully... Too much stuff is going on on the screen at one time. I can't even...
I don't even know what's happening half the time. This rainbow colored nonsense is...
This is fucking ridiculous. Alright. Get it off. Get two off. He's gonna do the... There
we go. Laser. Three. There's the third one. Please arc over and hit him. Nice. That's
exactly what I needed right there. What is this? What? This might be the most swears
I've ever said in a video series ever. I probably have like sweared or swore like 60 times.
Oh, you want to like have a video where you like say swears like 75 times? Okay, great.
You know what? It's these... Is this like the last boss or is this like the first boss?
I have no idea. It's gonna be one of those things. It's either the first boss or the
last boss. And if this is the first boss, then my life is just gonna be over. I'm like...
My voice is getting all cracked up. I'm being quiet. I'm being totally silent to make this
happen. There we go. Please screw that up. I've been sitting here for so long trying
to beat this goddamn boss. Honest to God. This is just... This is just dumb. This is
just dumb, alright? You don't... See, I can handle this part. This part's not the big...
The problem. The problem is this part. Once it gets like the quad laser out, and then
you can't even like... You can't even do anything. Like I'm stuck in between these lasers and
he spins. So I'm like so screwed. And he's gonna shoot more rockets. What? Oh, he stopped.
He stopped doing it. Alright. I didn't... I had no idea that he did that. Don't do the
quad laser again, please. Is he dead? He's dead. Did I do it? Oh my God, I did it. I
did it. I actually did it. I'm so mad at you. Oh no. That was it? I just killed him. Okay.
You killed the pope. Congratulations. Dibs on his hat. Dibs on being the next pope. Dammit.
I wanted that. Anyway, good job. The game's not even close to being over.