Lakeside. One of the only places where you've got a guaranteed, okay, so as I was saying, Lakeside, you've got a guaranteed couple of snipers that just stand up here.
So the question is, can I kill this guy again? Oh, not this time! He dodged. He dodged. Oh shit. Oh god. Where is he? He's right here.
Come on. Come and get me. I have a free Uber. Somebody help me. Help me. I won't kill you. Oh Jesus. Just get out of here. Get out of here while you still can.
The thing is, you're just going to have to come down to... Forget it. Bait him. Here comes the bait. You want to see how you bait? I'll show you how you bait.
That's how you do a bait! Didn't even kill him. Didn't even die. Didn't even die. That's fine. That's great. I'm going to burn to death now. What a wonderful world. What a wonderful world.
I ain't got no beef with you. Hey, get out of my face. I ain't got no beef with you. I ain't got no beef with you either. My beef is with this sniper. He's freaking out.
Can he shoot me from here? I don't think he can. Holy god. There's another one. There's two of them. There's two of them. Oh god damn it. That should have killed him.
The goal in Barn Blitz is up here. If I just stand right here, some son of a bitch is going to come up here like this and walk right into it. They always move at the last second.
I'm like two mil... I went out the window. I was like hanging out the window by my underpants. You were like somebody was like hanging me like shaking coins out of my underwear.
You don't even know. You don't even know. Wish that was longer. Oh fuck. What? Are you kidding me right now? What's this guy doing? Are you really not going to like come after me?
He's not even paying any attention to what I'm doing. I'm going to get this sniper. My god how is this still happening right now? How am I able to do this and how am I missing? Please just...
This is the one. This is the... Yes! Free uber charge. Oh god. I'm going to have to use it immediately. Do it! No I don't have to do it yet. It's just a spy. Do it! What the...
Just going in with the saw. If I can get a taunt kill, I can get one. We're going to go for some fucking saw kills here. What are you... I got someone? Who did I get? I got the spy? How come it didn't hit him initially? He was just like stabbing me in the face. Alright I guess I'll take it.
Perfect timing. If I play my cards right... I'm real. I'm real. Don't worry. Looks like they're all backing up. There's a spy over here. Oh I just heard... Shoot him! Shoot him! Okay I had to pull out. Where are you going? Where are you going dude? Get out of here! You fucking...
Here he comes again. Here he comes again. Shit! He hasn't shot me yet. What's happening? What is happening? I can't believe that... I was hoping he was going to walk right into that. A victim! A victim! Okay well I had a chance there. I had a chance and it was all taken from me. Are you serious? What the fuck? What a psycho!
Dude that guy just came over here to try to hit me. What an absolute psycho. Alright well it's good to know. That was like Looney Tunes. That guy just kind of came out of nowhere. Oh well shit. I'm okay. I'm going for your medic friend. That's the one who's the real danger. Shit! I'm going to have to use this. Do I have anybody around? Is there anybody around? That's a spy. Alright well no there's nobody around here. Pop it don't drop it. Pop it don't drop it. I remember seeing that. PSA. You know what?
Pop it. I got you. I got you all. Don't worry. Everyone's alright. Now give me another free uber. Time for the mission to commence. If I get spotted I'm going to be very upset. Not so much. Wait till he zooms in again because he's obviously... And of course he just stares at me and turns around and shoots me. I should have went in. I should have went in when I had the goddamn chance. I should have went in when I had the goddamn chance!