Hey, what is going on everybody? It's Jerma here again with a gameplay commentary.
This time we're playing as the Sniper, the regular Scope Sniper. No Bizarre Bargain, no Sydney Sleeper, anything like that.
This is just the default setup, except I'm using the Shahansha and I'm using the Darwin's Danger Shield for the extra health.
As you can see in the lower left-hand corner, I have 150. And I'm gonna warn you guys, this is a complete utter domination as the Sniper.
I get mad headshots every day, mad headshots every day. I miss a lot too, but you know, when you're in this spot on Dustbowl, this is Dustbowl by the way,
when you're on defense and there's not a really good Counter Sniper, you are free to do whatever you want as a Sniper.
As you see, I get a couple of headshots here right off the bat, except that wasn't a headshot, that was a body shot.
And here comes a headshot right here that I'm most proud of. It is absolutely insane. I've never been able to do this before in my life.
Oh my god, headshot, did you see that? I'm gonna rewind it, we gotta see that again.
Oh my god, I've never been able to do that, never in my life. So that's the first time that happened, I'm so glad I was recording.
Also, I apologize for not coming out with a video the last couple of days. I've been pretty sick guys, I had a pretty bad head cold.
Wasn't able to really talk that well, so I'm okay now though, don't worry, I'm fine.
So here's an announcement for you guys, don't expect too much out of it, but I finally came out with a Twitter account.
So, twitter.com slash German985, if you want to follow me, that's cool.
Just don't expect me to, you know, update every 45 minutes or every 20 minutes or something like that.
So, a lot of people were asking for me to do a Twitter, so I have a Twitter now, so you can know when I'm eating like cheeseburgers or hot dogs or whatever I end up putting on there.
Back to the gameplay now, let's talk about some sniper tips and tactics.
The only real tip I can give you as a sniper, something it took me a long time to learn, and it's how to aim properly.
What you should be doing, to be completely honest, let your mind go.
Stop thinking about where you need to place the cursor, where you need to go, who you need to pay attention to, what you should be doing.
Counter sniper for the win. What you need to do as a sniper is kind of let go of everything and just aim and shoot.
It's kind of like pitcher and catcher. If you're familiar with baseball, a pitcher doesn't aim his pitches.
He doesn't say, okay, that's where I want to throw my ball, I'm going to throw it right there.
They know what they're doing, they already have their accuracy all pinpointed and everything.
You don't have to think about where you're pointing the cursor, just let yourself go and take the shot.
That's the only real advice I can give you as a sniper is stop worrying so much about, no, I've got to be so precise and so exact.
Because that's what I did when I started sniping and I sucked.
So once I started to let go and I started to kind of get the mindset of, you know what, if I miss, I miss.
If not, then cool, I got a body shot or I got a headshot, I got a kill.
That's what really helped me as a sniper is to just kind of stop worrying about everything and freaking out about nonsense.
Also, I have no idea what those white horizontal lines were on the screen.
They didn't show up in my game, they only showed up in this one particular five second clip in FRAPS.
So I have no idea, if anyone knows what that was, let me know because that was kind of confusing for me.
So here I go toe to toe with this Pyro, he gets me with a nice flare gun shot.
I end up getting away, nice little quick scope shot on that Soldier coming to replenish my health.
Can't get the headshot on either of these two guys, but it's okay because I got plenty of people over here to shoot at.
Also, keep in mind guys, if you know there's a sniper, if you've been killed by the same sniper like two or three different times,
make sure to look over here and throw something over here at me because people are just sitting ducks over on the right hand side.
It's almost a guaranteed kill, nice headshot right there.
These people are guaranteed kills if I can get the shots.
And this guy's taunting right here, I was like, I didn't even get him.
I got the wrong person, but I got both the medics regardless.
So look over here, come here, look at, shoot me.
Will you please somebody, will somebody please shoot me?
Nobody does.
So just getting all kinds of headshots all over the place.
I can't even keep track anymore.
I keep killing people with quick scope headshots, headshot, headshot, headshot.
I can't even tell anymore what's going on.
I actually fall down, I get so into it, I fall off the cliff and I'm like, doh, whoops.
But it's okay because nothing ends up happening over it.
Less than 30 seconds left here now and they can't even get on the point.
They start to push a little bit, but it doesn't end up happening.
That spy explodes before I can even get over to him.
So now this is kind of just a game of let them come out and let me shoot them in the face a million times.
I kill like four people in a row.
There's one, there's two, and here comes three.
I believe it's the heavy.
Oh, I missed, but it's okay.
Here it is.
There it is as a soldier.
So if you see, there it is.
That's the end of the gameplay.
One more headshot to end it right here, but it doesn't kill him.
Yes, it does.
Top score, but who cares?
That's not what it's about.
Anyways, it's all about fun.
Thank you so much, everybody, for watching.
I really, really appreciate it.
Getting closer to 2,000 subscribers, very, very close now.
So we'll see what happens.
I'll plan something really cool for that.
Take care, everybody.
Thanks for watching.