Wait, you put a wink in? I hadn't come on. I didn't even remember how to stream. Hold on a second.
All right. I just did the thing. And when you do that thing, that's how you know it's time to clean
your room. What I've done is I stacked a glass on top of another glass, because there's no room for
two glasses. So it's time. It's time to clean this room. So we have a wink. Of course we do.
In five seconds. Disgusting pigsty. No, no, I know this. It's not that bad. This just
documents all over the floor of all my personal information. PlayStation 2 games and glassware
everywhere. It's not like it's dirty. It's just stuff. That's one thing I want to make sure. I
want to talk to you guys about this before. I know there's a wink. We'll get it. Dirty versus
clutter. Your room, my room's not dirty. It's just cluttered. There's nothing in here that's
disgusting. It's just stuff on the ground. So why then? Actually, no, hold on. Never mind. That's
a lie. There's a... Fuck. I lose. There's a glass of coffee in it. That's definitely been sitting
there for like at least five days. All right. I lose. I can clean the room. That's fucking
horrible. I just looked behind me and saw it. But anyways, I had a good break. A lot of friends
came up. We had a good time and moldy. No, no, no, it's not. It's not. It's fine. We'll clean it
right now. It's fine. It's fine. No, it's going to be fine. All right. All right. We're good.
Watering. I went, we dumped it. The mold got him. There's no mold. Okay. There's no mold in that
cup. Hold on. I got a wink. This is a spoiler. You're not supposed to see this shit yet.
Hey, what are we doing? All right. That was the entire right side of a magazine. If you have like
the Cosmopolitan magazine, that was the entire right page for a fucking scent ad. You just
put text to it that says like stunning, daring, smells, and then like dot, dot, dot. Invigoration,
whatever the hell you think. A whole page ad. Fuck off with these whole page ads. You want to know
why nobody reads magazines anymore? Because the thing is 35 pages thick and there's 18 pages of
ads. That's why nobody reads them anymore. I winked. I winked like three times. Dude, I can't imagine
having a magazine company right now and the only people that read it are people that have
phones that are about to die at the doctor's office and they don't want to sit there and read
their phones. It's like, fuck, I have to read something else here. I forgot the Lord of the
Rings was in the background. Sorry. Hey, let me redo that one. You heard it. The only people
that read magazines are people that are bored at the doctor's office that don't want to fucking
know you heard it. I'm going to play Lord of the Rings Return of the King on PlayStation 2 today
and I felt it was appropriate. I'm returning to streaming after about eight or nine days,
so we're going to return to the king. Now it's too quiet. I'll fix it. Don't worry.
I'm going to explain why you are late. No, that's a pre-stream thing. That's a pre-stream thing and
now we'll find it'll be a now stream thing. I hate starting an activity where I know I'm going to be
long-term locked in, but it doesn't matter what it is. I could be going fishing for all that matters
and if I have a dump building, that's a bad way to put it. Let's be medical about this.
If I have to use the bathroom imminently, I do not want to do anything until that is taken care
of. It doesn't matter what it is. So I had to take care of that before I started my live stream,
because if you do not take care of that, if you do not let the process get started and finish,
then you are stuck. You are stuck needing to go use the restroom. You have to use the bathroom
at some point in an opportunity that might not be the greatest time. I hate that. No,
it doesn't happen to me. The reason why it happened today is because I ate food after 11
o'clock last night, which is like, come on, what am I thinking? That's how you make that happen.
All right, I'm going to play. No, I didn't even have a tweet. Hold on. No, it's because I had to
wink. Go back to the intro. We're not ready. Oh, we have huge bits coming in too. Bilactery gave...
Let me get the good one. Hold on. Let me get the good one out. Why am I... What are these pictures
on my phone? What am I doing? All right, hold on. All right, I'll be right back. I'm up.
Okay, this is funny to me because if you just browse your Twitter and you knew that I... Oh,
yeah, that's right. Durham has been gone. Durham has been gone for like 10 days.
The first tweet is, return of the king. And then a link to my Twitch. How many people might just
scroll by them and be like, really, dude? Like, return of the fucking king. Oh, wow. You were
gone for like a week and a half. You're the best. Yeah, return of the king. Whatever. All right,
what does everybody ask? No, somebody gave me money. Here's the worst part about when you don't...
Okay, I haven't turned my computer on for 10 days. So how many updates does your computer fucking
have to do? You just don't even realize just how much shit your computer does in the background.
10 days of no updates and no downloads and shit. It's so obnoxious. Anyway, Spylactery gave $50.
Wait, we losing friends? No, we're not. Why'd you say clocks? They say, glad you're back,
Jerma. I was watching your old Stardew Valley streams and holy shit, you were bad at the game.
You've grown a lot as a streamer and we're all very proud of my boy.
I'm not... It's all right. It's okay. And 15 community subs from Amferic. Thanks, Amferic.
Yeah, welcome back, everybody. You didn't forget about me. That's good. A weekend on the internet
is like three years real time. You know what I mean? I'm surprised everyone even knows who I am.
But thank you, Spylactery. Thank you, Amferic. This time. Lord of the Rings for the return of
the king on PlayStation 2. I'm ready. A little blurry, but what am I going to do?
We're not playing on hard. This is not going to be a 16-hour stream.
Lord of the Rings, return of the king. I'm not playing on hard. We're doing normal. Here we go.
Adventure MFDN 5 community subs. Thank you, Dan. Played on hard. Did you see how fucking horrible
this game was the last one? You don't want me to do this on hard. I don't want to do this on hard.
No. Why would I do that? I'm not going to do that. Here we go. Lord of the Rings, the return of the
king. We last left our heroes when they were having a good time. Of course, it's a fucking THX
at the beginning of the THX certified game. Good. Did it break the speakers?
You did the THX sound too loud. You broke the speakers. Do you ever think the guy in
the projection room during the THX sound is going like, oh fuck, oh fuck, it's going to happen?
Now what? Why is this so soft? Come on, Batman. Thanks for the 10 subs.
I think it actually did break the speakers. Why does this sound like tinny? Does it sound
tinny to anybody else? It sounds tinny. Why does it sound like it's coming down a hallway?
It's actually broken. I can't even hear this.
A hanostanet of the enemy is growing. What? Sauron will use his puppet son-man to destroy the people
of Rohan. My headphones weren't plugged in all the way. It's been a week, guys.
Here we go. Another old movie. Here comes the DM. No, don't DMCA. This is a cut scene in the game.
Yeah, this is when we last left our heroes at the Battle of Home Depot.
You know what's funny about this stream? I'm going to be really honest with you.
The only reason why I'm playing this is because I bought it. I didn't want to play this,
but I can't not play it. I bought all three of them together.
The wizard is never late, nor is he early. He arrives precisely when he needs to.
Somebody do it. Do it. Do late. That's the line right there. That's actually the line.
Screamer is never late, nor is he early. He arrives precisely when he accidentally forgets
to eat and might have a shit building up in him for three hours and can't start on time.
Seamless transition. Let's go. I get to play as Gandalf, too.
I already leveled up. I'm already in perfect mode.
Why does Gandalf look like this Star Wars kid? He's kind of flailing around.
That was kind of fun. What has Gandalf's staff made out of? Wood? Is it wood? Well,
I have to play as Gandalf the whole game. I don't care what any other character does.
Probably wood. Ranged. I'm gonna die. What the hell was I doing? Wait, blow it up from back here?
Gandalf gameplay, Resident Sleeper. You mean Gandalf gameplay, guaranteed victory.
I guess that is Resident Sleeper. Shit, you're right. I was wrong there. All right, what am I
doing? R1, action. All right, I gotta be careful. Did I get it? Did I not get it? I just didn't hit
anybody. What the fuck am I doing? What is Gandalf throwing spears at me? I have magical powers.
Why would I need to do this? Oh, there we go. Yeah, I gotta get rid of that. I'm gonna die.
Can Gandalf die? Give us Frodo. Frodo's not even in this game. What do you mean? No,
we don't give spoilers. No, we can talk spoilers. We can talk. You've seen the last two movies. We
played them on stream. Yes, I did. I played Fellowship of the Ring and I played two towers
on stream. We watched them. You... No one watched it, though. I mean, no one watched you. The skill
meter determines the kill rating. Earn higher ratings by swinging to get the successful hits.
Best song in the... Best song? This song right here could potentially be the best song that has
been written since like the 1700s. Fair ratings are the easiest to get, but generate the fewest
experience points. Good and excellent ratings are worth more. Yeah, I know how to do that. We've
seen the last movie. We already know how this works. Remember, won't read this comment? Well,
now you owe me a thousand dollars. Was that on the line? I don't know. Pushing the skill
meter into perfect will enhance your attack damage and generate maximum experience points.
Hey. Hey, welcome back, guys. It's been a while. How are you doing? I only got two perfects. How?
So we... Is Gandalf... Is Gandalf resident sleeper? I'm not playing as Gimli again. He's the worst
character in the game. Look at this. Oh, you can do it for all. You can do it for all. I know this...
I know this is... We usually don't stop the stream for the typical... When I say typical,
I mean like a typical like one sub or one donation. We usually don't do that, but I have to stop here.
Um, it's Marvash McGally says, it's good seeing you play one of my childhood games. I completed
this when I was 12. You better finish this. Thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents though. That's...
I had to read that because I've just been called out. So 15 hours stream. This is not going to be
a 15 hour stream. You know why that is? This is important. I haven't talked about this. I've...
I start physical therapy this week. If I lock myself in here for 15 hours today and I go to
physical therapy, I'm going to have to explain to the doctor that I... How long have you been
sitting in that chair? Uh, I usually six, six to seven hours. That's... Oh, but you do stretches?
Yeah, I try to. What about last night? 15 hours? No, I'm not going to the doctor with that info.
Just lie. Don't you know? What's that old saying? This, this three people you don't lie to? Your
doctor, your financial advisor, and your lawyer, and your wife, and your husband. It's a five.
And your mother. And don't lie to your parents. Uh, don't lie. No, just don't lie to anybody. Okay,
all right. I gotta pay attention. 6900 points. Orc Hewer. I mean, this is just... Everybody needs
this. X, X. Yeah, this is a standard combo. It's cheap if a Gandalf though. Yeah, I'm just playing.
I want to play with Gandalf. Wait, hold on. You can play as the hobbits? I don't remember that.
That's... interests me for some reason. I don't know why. Okay, looks good. Replay? No. How do
I get the hell out of here? How do I continue? I see continue down there. Do I have to go all
the way down? Shit. Play as Sam. I'm probably gonna get my ass kicked if I play with Sam.
I don't think I'm into that. I'll be honest. You want me to beat the final level?
The last free kingdom of men. His war on this country will come swiftly.
He senses the ring will draw close and the strength of the ring bearer will fail.
Oh, let me get this on screen. It's great. In the end, this war must be decided by the
smallest of things. Imagine somebody laughing at the Lord of the Rings movie like this.
The ring wanted to be found. Here's... Oh boy. The task began when I beheld it upon the floor of...
Sad story. Somebody's entire... Imagine watching Lord of the Rings in the theaters
when people were screaming and cheering and yelling at every fucking other line.
Somebody had their movie ruined, one of the best franchises ever, by being in the movie theater
watching it like on launch. Still questions needed answering. Secrets only Minas Tirith,
ancient city of men could reveal. The year 3434 of the second age who follows the account will be
Should I have to press a few beeps here to get this on screen?
It has come to me. The one ring. It shall be an heirloom of my kingdom.
All those who follow in my bloodline shall be brisk.
It is precious to me.
It was in this moment... This is the future of movies, guys.
I would weave a plan for a great war, yet count upon others...
In movie advertising. They're just not going to care anymore.
It was the destiny of Aragorn, heir to the throne, to lead this war.
Let me see that again. I once saw warriors of every race
fighting as companions alongside him.
This is good. I like it. Together we would spring a great trap.
All right. If I made this... Okay. If I made a streamer cologne.
No one's done that shit. People sell fucking mice.
Gaming keyboards. No, no, no. What if I sold a cologne?
People need to branch out, man. It's not all about your gamer chair.
It's about, like, a nice fucking eau de toileur.
For they, like us, will be in great peril.
Cologne that smells like me. No, that's strange.
I'm not... No, absolutely not.
It would be a cologne that I would think would... I...
That smells good. And that scent would be...
It would be a combination of a couple things.
It would be... Right when you pull open a green jolly rancher,
that immediate scent that hits your nostrils.
That'd be... It'd be in there somewhere.
Like, that green apple smell would be there.
Surrounded by a nice eau de.
And then wood. Like a wood smell.
Like a burning wood smell.
You know that when you have a campfire going,
you get that wood burn smell?
I think it would be pretty good.
All right. Path of the King.
I think... It's like a backwards level skill tree here.
Escape from Osgiloth.
Those of you guys don't know what eau de is.
OED. I'm dead serious.
People think... Don't tell me I'm crazy until you smell it.
Eau de is an incredible smell.
It's like one of the best scents ever made.
It's incredible.
OED. Smell it.
Path of the Dead.
Oh, is this the one... The storyline that Peter Jackson
wished he deleted from the whole entire movie?
Let's do this one.
Locked? Who are the other characters?
There are three secret fucking characters?
Why is Gandalf locked?
I just unlocked him.
He wasn't in that fight.
Oh, it's because you have the trial version.
This is the demo disc.
Okay, guys, sorry.
I only got like the first two levels and two characters.
Oh, by the way, I'm going to play through this
two level demo a hundred times.
Welcome to 1996.
Adam Sildur's heir received the ring of power
and also carries before him
the only weapon Sauron cannot abide
and the only power before which a dead king and his army...
I have to have my soul to fucking goddamn scent.
I got to look into this.
I'm going to look into this.
That's funny to me.
That's funny enough for me to set my eyes on it
and lose a shitload of money and do it.
Deep inside this haunted mountain,
they will face terrible trials.
They must overcome the wrath of an ancient, cursed realm
and summon forth its king.
Out of darkness, Aragorn must call an army
even Sauron's horde cannot withstand.
Call it Jurfium.
No, that's weird.
The living cannot defend Minas Tirith
without the fury of those long dead.
I'm going to call it Liquid Mold.
You think anyone would spray it near their face?
The dead linger on this path, but we must walk it to the end.
Hold on.
Just practicing.
Oh yeah, you have no camera control on this.
I forgot.
All right, I got to be careful.
The way is shut.
It is made for those who are dead.
Yeah, Peter Jackson wished he deleted this entire sequence, right?
He hated this part.
He was like, that's the biggest mistake of my whole career.
You know, he really said that.
He actually like talked about that.
I swear to God, he actually just hit me.
Oh, what?
I couldn't kill it.
It's kind of hard to see.
German knows Peter Jackson.
No, I just know of the YouTube video I clicked on
that talked about in the article
about how he didn't like this scene
and he didn't like this whole sequence.
Come on, land, land, do something.
Oh God, he never said that.
Yes, he did.
Jesus, this is very ugly.
Why is this uglier than the last one?
Am I misremembering things
or is this actually uglier than the second game?
It's the same console.
I feel like I'm watching a YouTube playthrough
of this game that was uploaded in 2007.
Is it not?
Why does this look so bad?
All right, we need some blocks.
Break this, right?
Nice emulator.
This is not on an emulator.
This is on PlayStation 2, slim edition.
I might actually turn it up.
I think I'm actually going to go
and do some adjustments.
All right, hold on.
It's because it's dark.
All right, you got that image, right?
Let's do some adjustments.
Okay.
All right, looking better.
A little bit more contrast.
How's that saturation?
A little bit deeper.
That actually looks a lot better.
Yeah, because this is where it was before.
That's why it looks so fucking wrong.
It's like dark.
Had bad contrast.
Look it up with an HDMI LOL.
You think there's an HDMI on the back
of my PlayStation 2 slim edition?
Can I throw?
Yeah, I can.
How do I throw?
You guys could like not watch me do this and help.
It's an upscaler.
It's on an upscaler right now.
I play all the old consoles through an upscaler.
So I think it's kind of an ugly portion of the game.
The first sequence didn't look like this.
Like the battle of Home Depot didn't look like this.
Killed.
It's the battle of lows now.
Come on, build up the pits and perfects.
This is perfect cheesing.
This is how you do it.
Just stand in the middle and just bam, square.
Break a shield.
You know what else it is?
They're surrounded by this ugly goo.
Yard sale.
No, this is not a yard sale brawl.
Why would a yard sale be in a cave?
Yeah, that's the problem.
There's no video game on the screen.
There's just weird pixelated green water.
They might unlock a move.
What's it?
It's X, X, A.
No, X, X, triangle.
Didn't I unlock it for everybody?
Did I just grab the ring?
All right.
Can I put one of you guys on this?
No, don't mind.
Just go ahead.
Go on, guys.
I'll just do fucking everything.
They just do.
They're just up there vibing.
Yeah, let's get the fuck down here.
Oh, God.
Ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly.
Let's go.
Build it up.
Did I get it?
Got it.
I can't even get over there.
I get it finally.
I can't even go over here.
Nice PS2 Slim Edition.
Don't make...
The PS2 Slim Edition is an amazing console,
which would literally fit anywhere.
You know the weird places I had to put this fucking thing
when I was in my bedroom?
This thing could fit anywhere.
The PS2 Slim Edition is as big as like eight credit cards.
It can go anywhere.
Can we move?
Did you put it in a Ziploc bag or something?
No, but you could stuff this somewhere behind like a bureau.
It fit everywhere.
You could go under your desk.
You could go on top of your desk.
What is this camera angle?
What is this camera?
I don't even know what's happening.
I think I'm winning.
Remember, please, stop you making chat.
What?
What are you talking about?
Is it clear on my end?
No, not at all.
Oh, there we go.
Finally.
Is it clear on your end?
No, no, it's not.
It looks like your end.
Bureau is French for desk.
Yeah, that's what I called it.
Am I weird for saying the word bureau now?
How much should I charge for the Cologne?
Should it be something stupid so nobody buys it?
No, I do have a combo.
I could do without it popping up on the screen every time.
Probably $20.
You don't think it should be like 80?
I'm only going to make like 10 of these.
You know, are you sure you don't want me to have articles written about me?
Streamer is such an egomaniac.
He has a $120 Cologne that he's selling.
I mean, that's publicity for the community.
Egomaniac.
I wonder how many bottles I could reliably actually get to manufacture.
Look, if you buy one of these Colognes, you'll...
They last a long time.
Guys, I've bought Cologne that I still have since high school.
I swear to God.
15-year-old Cologne.
More than that.
Try like 20.
What the fuck is going on right now?
What?
Am I dead?
I just got like trapped in the corner.
Nice Aragon.
Good job.
Good work, Aragon.
Or Legolas, whichever one of you.
Good job.
You're doing great.
Give me a break.
This is why we need you to be Sam.
Am I going to be the first person that beats this game as Samwise?
Does he even have any combos?
Does Sam have a combo?
I feel like...
So Triangle is Fierce Attack.
X is Light Attack.
Square is Parry.
Right?
Why do I feel like he's going to have a stab with X and then...
Oh!
Instead of any other moves.
Like it'll be...
I can make him say ooh.
Get in here and help.
There's a funny ooh noise.
Thank you.
Make sure you buy a Cologne on your way out.
They're only $100.
All fair.
Ooh, what's this?
What is this?
Is it a rock?
Oh, that's what we needed to do.
Cool.
I remember playing this level when I was younger
and having Perfect almost the entire time I played.
How the fuck did I do that?
That almost seems...
Like, not even achievable.
Dude, that was pretty good.
Dude, almost there.
Come on!
Oh, you idiots.
I had it.
Normal is easy.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, Jerma sucks.
Thanks for saying I suck.
Thanks for the five community suck subs.
Thank you.
Let me get out of here.
We're not down here.
I'll come down.
Thanks for the subs.
Oh, here's the thing.
Okay, let's say I make this Cologne.
I know I'm on the Cologne thing,
but you gotta give me...
Just give me a sec.
Let's say I make this Cologne
and it turns out like, holy shit,
it's actually...
What a combination of scents.
This is fucking fantastic.
This is actually really good.
And I don't know,
some celebrity gets ahold of it.
Do I just sell the rights to them?
Like a million dollars?
But they can just like change the name.
Whatever.
And then I can hire Danny DeVito
to be in a skit.
That's the long con here.
That's the long game here, guys.
That's the sellout move.
No, it's dodgy.
All right.
Come on.
Perfect.
It's like there's not enough of them
for me to get perfect.
It is on normal, though.
That's right.
Of course, another great point.
Or fewer.
Come on.
Give me perfect.
God, it's right there.
Come on.
Oh, you motherfucker.
Level up.
This is it.
Perfect.
Here we go.
Lots of fucking EXP.
Block it.
Good.
Nice.
All right.
We're good.
Just don't die.
Okay.
Please.
When I was a kid,
I used to think you could only use orc humor on orcs.
Well, I mean,
how old were you?
Were you over or under the age of 10?
I mean, that's not unreasonable.
I mean, can you,
either one of you two handle even one person?
You guys are worse than the last fucking co-op.
Is Legolas dead?
This game is awesome.
Yeah, they both really good.
The Lord of the Rings.
And the return of the king.
I keep looking over on the other monitor and just see that.
Oh, did you see that?
Oh, you didn't.
Did I block it?
Oh, it's just a cut scene.
Guys, don't DMCA this stream.
I didn't do anything.
How many purpose did I get?
Like five?
Mission rating.
Good.
All right.
Level three.
I...
Let's go.
I'll go over it all.
Final judgment.
I don't want to play as Gimli.
Rising of revenge.
You are Gimli main.
No, I'm not.
Strength of stone.
Permanently increases your health.
Lonely mountain lore.
Increase damage and get to perfect mode more quickly.
I'm doing health.
Okay.
Doing all...
I don't want to play as Gimli.
Gimli's not my main.
Did we get a T-pose right here?
I think we did for a second.
No, no, it was this.
Okay.
I never looked for that shit.
This is ever since I started streaming on Twitch.
I see them now.
I never even thought for a second.
But that was something to look for.
All right, let's go.
Who should put my points into?
Did you just say Gimli is your main?
I know, I said Gimli is not my main.
Game concept art.
Yeah, let's take a look.
We have to watch all of these.
No, hold on.
So this is the concept art for the game.
Not concept art for the movie.
Oh, that's bright.
Oh my god, this is horrible.
Something's wrong with the capture here.
It's really not right at all.
Fix the gamma.
No, it's...
Hold on a second.
I think it's...
Oh, oh, oh!
Whoa, hold on.
Something's not right here.
What's going on with this shit?
Why is it doing this?
All right, hold on.
I need to turn this off for a second.
This is fucked up.
I don't know what's going on.
Is that better?
By hell, let me go back in here now.
I don't know what's going on with this thing.
Did it make it worse?
The cables are bad?
How the fuck did that happen?
I've been gone for eight days.
What, did they rot while I was gone?
Hold on.
Is that better?
Maybe a little bit.
King of the Dead, the Southern Gate.
No, I gotta do all of them, right?
Yeah.
Road to Isengard.
Something's fucking wrong here.
Oh, I get to begin now.
That's like...
It looks a little better though.
So I took the cable and I bent it
and twisted it and pulled on it.
I'm not going to touch it anymore.
I'm being Gandalf.
Cable and ball torture.
It was not a chance that brought Maddie and Bippin to Fangorn.
Run, Mary!
It's talking, Mary.
The tree is talking.
Tree?
I am no tree.
I am an ant.
Inks have not troubled about the wars of men and wizards
for a very long time.
I love the word wizard.
Might be my favorite word.
This is pirate quality.
I really should just title this like Lord of the Rings.
Lord underscore of underscore the underscore rings underscore
like X2114 rip part one dot zip.
It does look like a torrented movie.
Actually does look better.
That guy got fucking disturbed.
That's being the first guy that runs alone to Gandalf
and be like, oh boy, you're done.
First to leave.
Yeah, what a...
I love the crisp loop.
That guy was running.
Smart.
Get that guy up there.
No, I just blew that guy's head off.
Gandalf, that was fucked up.
I'm trying to shoot the guy up here.
Let's just point blank that guy's head.
Hold on, can I?
Yes, I can.
Why would I even ask?
Here we go.
Let's get up here.
Come on.
Is that Gandalf?
I don't know why I thought that was Gandalf talking.
There he is.
Well, he's like, easy pickets back there.
Get him.
I was currently going and getting.
It sounded kind of like Gandalf.
And don't tell me I'm crazy because all video game voice acting is either we got the money to...
Ooh, hold on a second.
Come on, somebody.
I'm in perfect mode.
How dare you?
Come on.
No.
How dare you do this to me?
Fuck you.
Where am I?
What I was going to say is...
You either have the real actor there and you have the money for it or...
The guy from accounting does Gandalf.
He's gonna stomp.
All right, I need perfects here.
Get out of the way.
God, get the fuck out of here.
You guys are blocking the screen.
Gandalf's got a really good orc cure.
Come on.
Spring it, spring it, spring it.
Nothing.
Pick up.
No, get the fuck away from me.
I got this.
Leave me alone.
Oh, come on.
Ooh, there it is again.
Thanks for stepping on me over and over again.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Before they destroy all...
Come on, come on.
Let's go, come on.
Get this out.
Who the fuck are you aiming?
Star Wars wizard.
Is there any game that you can use?
Hold on.
I have to just get that nice and clean.
Should I play Jedi Fallen Order?
Somebody please tell me the truth.
I love lightsabers and I love Dark Souls games.
Like, how would I not like that game?
Is it really bad enough where you're like,
no, no, no, no.
It's like, suck.
That ticks every box for me.
Fallen Order is good.
One person just said it.
Did I believe them?
Wait a minute.
Did I believe that person?
Believe that person.
Okay.
Fuck that guy.
Don't...
Hey, come on.
You guys are sitting on the same train here.
You're not sitting on the subway
and somebody gets off at one at a stop
and you go, oh, fuck that stop.
Fuck that guy.
We're on the same train.
Shit, I didn't see...
This guy, this guy's like popped in.
Sitting on the scam train.
What the hell?
Is that health?
Ooh, come on.
Come on.
Oh, just excellent.
I might as well not even fucking try then.
Not even worth tweeting about.
Really?
Like, what the fuck?
Why am I supposed to go?
No, it's gonna do the camera change.
Bullshit.
All right, got it.
I'm actually playing pretty well.
Remember last time I played this game?
Like the multivitamins working.
I started taking like a little
volti vitamin recently
and I think it's working.
Voldemort gummies.
That's never getting sent.
I'll take a perfect.
I'll take a...
Will you?
Will you do that, Gandalf?
Gandalf, is that what you're doing?
Gandalf, is that what we're doing here?
I don't know.
I don't think that's what we're doing here.
I thought that just said overachiever on it.
I was like, why are you calling me an overachiever?
I don't...
What, I put the end out?
How do I save him?
I don't know what to do.
I can't hit it.
Oh, I just have to protect him.
I didn't even see the archers on my cell phone camera.
Sorry.
Gandalf, best character, seriously.
Why would I ever play another character?
Anybody else?
Take it.
Come on, go.
Sam.
But why would I want to play Sam when I can play as Gandalf?
Sam gang.
All right, I will play as Sam.
I will.
Did you get it?
Okay, I don't know what's going on.
I just started laughing about the cow throwing the rock.
And black and white.
It's happening a lot.
I'll be out to dinner with Kim.
And I'll just think of...
And then the rock getting thrown.
And I don't know why.
It's fucking crazy.
Do not...
Wait a minute.
What's this?
We have an important message here.
Let me see what this is.
Hey everyone, fucking listen.
For the love of God, do not buy the $5 Biggie bag from Wendy's.
If you purchase the standard 4th floor and add bacon, it comes to $4.50.
They're scamming you.
Instead, upgrade your fries to a large and your total will be $5.
I don't even know what that means.
I have not been to Wendy's in probably like six months.
I'm a McDonald's guy.
You guys know that.
If I had fast food, me and Kim.
Kim is the same way.
Kim's a McDonald's girl.
I'm a McDonald's guy.
Number one.
I'm sorry.
That's just the way it is.
McDonald's is dog food.
No, it's not.
It's great.
It's good.
McChicken is fucking perfect.
Number one is really good.
McDonald's is...
I like McDonald's.
I think when...
It's more comfortable for me to eat at McDonald's.
Wendy's might be higher quality food, but I like McDonald's better.
I don't care.
I like it.
How much did they pay you?
If you really think that McDonald's needs to pay somebody
to talk about how they like the Big Mac.
I mean, there's like 16,000 McDonald's stores.
They're doing just fine.
They don't need my help.
A McDonald's hamburger is sold every tenth of a second in this country.
They don't need to pay me for that.
The people are going to eat there.
All right, what should we do?
Final judgment.
It's garbage food.
You're killing yourself.
Do you have you ever listened to Benjamin Franklin's podcast?
All things in moderation.
He would have had a great podcast, don't you think?
I think Ben Franklin would have been the Joe Rogan.
Don't you think so?
He would have like the microphone set up.
He'd be bringing in people.
Okay, let me buy something.
I need to get this.
I feel like I'm wasting money.
Should I upgrade Gandalf?
This is...
Just do it for everybody.
X.
The dude came up with electricity.
I know what Tesla said.
Benjamin Franklin got struck by lightning first.
And he lived.
At least that's what the cartoon told me.
I'm going to get this because this is very important for everyone to have this.
It's incredibly important.
And do I have enough?
I have enough to give it to everybody.
Just give it to everybody.
I'm spreading it all around.
This looks good.
It's like a knockdown.
I'll do the kill.
X circle R2.
All right, that's good.
You sound like you're reading a menu at a restaurant.
We're picking skills?
Now, I know exactly what I want.
See, I pre-order at every restaurant I go to.
What that means is every restaurant has their menus online now.
I go find out what I want.
I know what I want when I get in.
I don't have to ask any questions.
So then it's not a question of sitting there for 20 minutes
while I try to figure out what the hell you want to eat.
I kind of have to watch this, don't I?
The world is changing.
Stand against the armies of Isegard Mordor.
What I'm doing today is I've been providing the voice of Saruman in the game.
I told you the power of stone.
Saruman the White was the head of the Order.
And he thinks that he can be the Lord of the Rings.
We must join with Saruman.
Power of Saruman lies in his voice.
Absolutely legendary.
Now we can attend with the will of Saruman.
He's not just a wizard who can do extraordinary things.
He can convince most unlikely people.
This is the impression, you see, that he gives.
All powerful.
What a professional.
What an absolute professional.
If you do the right things, you will beat me.
If you do the wrong things, you will lose.
Is Viggo Mortensen in this game?
I hope so.
All right, we can go to the King of the Dead.
No, we don't.
We have to do...
Wait, didn't we?
Yeah, we're going to go up.
Escape from Ozgaloth.
You know, we can do it all.
Whatever, we're doing it all.
That was violent for Sam.
Isn't Sam a chef?
Well, I guess you know how to cut stuff.
It's filled with both great hope and the success of our plan.
I must place the smallest of us in the greatest of peril.
Always the mighty tried to possess the ring and always they failed.
Fate has lent me a hobby, resilient to the ring's corruption and brave by his very nature.
I want to watch these movies.
You cannot stay in the Shire.
No.
Elijah Wood's awesome, too.
This is just an all-awesome cast.
Everybody is so good.
Start hard to bear the ring.
You will need paths into Mordor.
For all three of them are bound to the fate of the ring and to the fate of each other.
All right, I'm going to...
How many people are in this community?
Like a few hundred thousand.
I'll rent out a football stadium and we'll just put it on a big screen
and everyone's invited.
We'll do that.
What do you want this way?
You know the way to order.
Imagine.
Oh, that was like 40 million dollars to get the licensing to do that.
Into the very fires of Mordor.
Watch the Lord of the Rings trilogy in a stadium.
And they'll be captured and all hope may be lost.
I hire a...
Like a LARPing crew to do every scene on the football field while the movie is playing.
So you get two at the same time.
Make it happen.
Anybody have a hundred million dollars that they don't need anymore?
That they'd like to just have disappear?
All right, let's go.
All right, I'm just slashing at random people.
Are we supposed to be following you?
Can you block?
By the way, all you guys that said like minus two.
He's doing it.
That is the...
Oh, button for him.
Does he have Orcure?
Can he even have Orcure?
What is it?
It's a...
It's what?
X...
He has it, right?
Doesn't he?
It's...
It's X circle...
X circle R2.
X circle R2?
Oh, he's level one.
He can't do it.
Oh, all right.
Why can't we...
Okay.
Can we not trade swords?
Like this is just the...
You don't want to take it from your friend.
But if your friend has the legendary,
don't you think you should put it in the hands of the person that knows how to attack?
It's kind of...
It's useless in your hands right now.
It's soul bound.
Yeah, well, you shouldn't press need on it,
but I'm not going to give you shit for it.
Every time...
We can't talk about World of Warcraft
every single time we play a game with swords in it.
All right?
I'm not going to talk about it anymore.
I didn't even have to do anything.
How?
Oh, that was...
We just both hit each other at the same time.
Sam is the best character?
We'll see.
I'm not sure if I agree with that statement, but...
I mean, he did win the Academy Awards, so you're kind of right.
Actual Academy Award.
Dude, it was him.
You got it.
I didn't even notice the dragon.
Well, I did before, but, you know, I didn't know the dragon was still here.
Does this happen in the movie?
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
Come on, let's get Sam some perfects.
I need the XP.
This was cut from the movie.
That was a cool move.
Fire it!
He does have the orcure.
I don't like Sam...
I don't like Sam's orcure.
It's too fancy.
I don't like that.
It takes him too long to do it.
I'm not playing with him.
I don't care.
I'm playing with Gandalf.
Fuck it.
I'm leaving?
Really?
I can't even see who's shooting.
Gandalf hits twice with his orcure.
He spins around and swings once.
It's not very good.
Why are the hobbits as tall as the orcs?
Looks like we're going up the ladder to the cleric beast.
I'll take that one because that's an actual good reference.
I don't care what anybody says.
That was a great fucking reference.
One of the best I've made in probably the last few months.
I don't care.
You've ruined it.
I know.
That's the kind of...
Wasn't that kind of the point?
What?
What just happened?
What's the timer?
Oh, the dragon comes back.
I see.
Okay.
If it was a plus two, then you acknowledged it and turned it into a minus four.
Well, we'll see what the other judges have to say at the end of the boxing match.
I want the help.
There's always that one judge that's a real asshole.
Aragon is getting his ass kicked.
German, we all did minus two.
Yeah, but you're...
There's two other judges.
My mother watches these streams.
I'll text her later.
What do you think about that thing I said about the Clarities?
Honey, it was so good.
It's always a plus two from mom, by the way.
So, sorry.
Let me get some perfects.
Bring the bell.
Oh, is it again?
How many bells can I throw down there?
I have to help Aragon.
Is that even Aragon or am I...
Do I have this wrong?
No, wait.
Is that Aragon?
Hold on.
Why are there two Aragons?
You're a fake fan?
No, this is the same person.
That's the same character model.
Oh, look.
There's Aragon again.
Is that just like the default like human model?
It looks like Aragon.
That's a broken back.
Holy shit.
I hope you got the...
I hope you land the arrow.
All right, are we good?
Dragon's coming back.
I gotta go.
Where is he?
Oh, God.
He's coming back.
Is Frodo gonna kill the dragon?
You can't be up to...
Okay, right.
You can't be up top when the timer reaches zero.
That's not that far back, right?
It's actually pretty far back.
All right.
Well, now I just get out of the way.
It takes you too long.
It takes too long.
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna default swing.
It takes too long.
Unless I get to perfect, which I might.
All right, let's go.
All right, he's back.
He's back.
I gotta get out of here.
We go down.
Does this count as hiding?
I feel like he came over here before.
Right.
So if I'm over here...
So he's gone.
Okay.
All right.
For the love of God.
Gollum, can you fucking bite somebody's leg?
Stab him.
I'm trying.
There's health back here though.
All right, let's go.
Not this insanity again.
No, this is not gonna be insane.
No.
It's not gonna be insane.
I have confidence that I'll get...
I will get...
This will be a normal stream.
Normal.
My mother's watching.
This is her favorite movie ever.
You saw the notifications.
She texted me.
She's like, wait, hold on.
The movie?
Yeah.
She's like, my favorite movie?
Yes, mom.
I have to be on my best behavior.
Yeah, you guys...
You too.
You know she can read the chat.
Is there health over here?
Yes, there is.
When's the next crack stream?
I don't know.
You tell me.
When do you guys think you're gonna smoke your next crack?
I don't know.
I can't tell you that.
The game definitely looks better too.
I don't know.
I grabbed the cables and shook them so it worked.
All right, we gotta go.
Let's go.
Forget about it.
Just move.
I can't walk that way.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Move.
Well, I'm...
Go.
Go in, go in, go in, go in.
All right, we're outside.
Derma's dev is in chat.
That's clever.
That's pretty clever.
Let's go.
Three hits.
Does it kill?
Kind of.
All right, are we safe over here?
No, we're not.
Just go.
Just go to the next building.
Did you actually hit me?
I was ripping back and forth.
Wait.
You have...
Derma, you have a lot of moms.
There's only one mom.
And it's my mom.
And that's it.
Is there a ladder?
Where's the ladder?
Anybody see a ladder?
Can you say go down?
There it is.
You can play as Gollum.
That'd be awesome if you could.
Just keep moving.
Gollum gang.
I need health.
Otherwise...
Not what a good place I want to be.
I don't have a checkpoint so I can't focus up.
I'm gonna really focus here.
Okay.
I'm master.
I can do it.
I'm pretty good at that one.
It's real voice.
Derma, are you available?
Of course.
I'm available.
Really?
Block, block, block, block, block, block.
Swing.
Meet's back on the menu.
Ooh, full health.
Yes.
All right, we got a big guy coming.
What the fuck is this?
Come on, bring it on.
How many do we have?
Ooh, that hurt a lot.
All right, kill these guys first.
Don't knock me into the fucking...
God damn it, it happened.
I took them both.
I got him in the back, I think.
Holy shit.
All right.
No.
I can't even hurt him.
What the fuck am I supposed to do?
Heavy attacks.
Why did I have to...
I'm so fucking mad.
Why did I have to get knocked into the two healths?
It's two full...
And I'm all the way back at the beginning.
Was there a checkpoint at the bottom of the sewer?
Please tell me there was.
Oh, fuck me.
I'm just running.
This course is two healths and I'm just trying to...
This three guys stand...
I'm just running, I don't care.
I don't care if I get a zero.
I have to kill like a few people.
Fuck, why?
This mission sucks.
It's because I'm playing as Sam.
I could be playing as the most powerful wizard
in the universe.
But I'm going to be the guy who eats potatoes.
Remember when Gandalf went through Osgiloth?
I gotta get experience points for Sam.
You're being a Sam hater.
Well, that's okay.
What are my thoughts on the Hobbit movies?
People hate those movies.
I thought they were fine.
I mean, they stretched...
They stretched a book as big as a Goosebumps book
into three, four-hour long movies.
So that was probably a mistake.
But whatever.
I think that they're still enjoyable.
I like Smog.
I think he's good.
They're a little long, a little dragged out.
I could still enjoy them.
Do I love them?
No.
Would I choose to watch the Hobbit movies?
Probably not.
If I'm scrolling through Cable
and I land on the Hobbit
and there's 45 minutes left in the movie?
Yeah, sure, I'll catch the end.
Why not?
Please get out of my way.
Please get out of my fucking way.
Don't even fucking think about it, seriously.
Come on, don't even think about it.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
It's close.
Just let it cool down.
But no, I wouldn't really choose to watch the Hobbit movies.
But I, it's not, not like I hate them.
He does hate them.
No, he doesn't.
Hold on, let me get through this.
You just knocked him back up, dude.
I don't really, here's, okay, the thing about movies.
I don't really hate movies.
I don't really.
I hate video games.
Like, you know what it is?
Because I'm in control of the video game.
And I feel like I'm being personally slighted when I, as my avatar,
can't do something I'd like to do.
Right?
But a movie, I'm watching somebody else, I don't care.
Like, if the movie sucks, whatever, I had nothing to do with it.
If something bad happens to me in a game, I had something to do with it.
But I don't, I don't hate movies, really.
I can not, I can think movies aren't really good, but no.
There is no Surge 2 for me, or Surge, no, I didn't play the Surge 2.
There is no Surge.
That's not even the worst game I think I've ever played, either.
Like, why am I even saying that?
This feels unfair.
All right, can you stop getting on the ladder?
All right, I gotta pay attention, because I'm not doing this again.
The one time I don't swing.
Swing!
You're just waiting for me to do it.
Okay, just, I got this two health packs up there.
Now I'm gonna try hard as Sam.
Yes, I am.
Come on, don't.
Okay, all right, all right, all right, easy.
Oh my god.
I just tried to do a heavy attack, and he fucking, like, destroyed me.
Give me the health pack.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
This is, this is a little ridiculous.
Let's go!
Level up!
He's beginning to believe.
Yes.
This is the end of the level.
Yeah, that sucks.
Have you made a reward to end the stream?
Reward?
What?
150,000 channel points to end stream?
No, do it.
At a million?
No, I don't want that.
What if I have something big planned?
Hey guys, here we are on a big stream that took like a few weeks to make.
Oh, turn the stream off.
Okay, bye.
Turn it back on a second later.
Do you know how much that fucks up with notifications?
It would just be bad.
People would just leave and then I would delete a bunch of people
because they probably wouldn't come back
because they already got the notification.
It would screw, no, I'm never doing that.
10,006.
All right, what does, what does Sam get?
I don't even want to put up.
Nice.
Okay, Poison Blade.
Yeah.
Increases the time that a hobbit is hidden by using his elven cloak.
Warrior's Bane.
Parry, then instantly kill a man-sized enemy.
To everyone.
As opposed to a child-sized of hobbit-sized enemy.
I don't understand.
12,000 poison daggers.
Strength of iron.
Permanently increases your health.
I'm not level five.
Um, what do I got for all?
Level four.
I could get this for everybody.
Orc Bane.
Or, uh, probably Orc Bane, right?
Get Orc Bane for everyone.
It's so important.
It's just bang, it's instant.
Yeah, just get it for everyone.
You know what?
I got some points.
Let's do, um, people are going to be pissed off
if I don't buy at least one thing for Sam.
Uh, we'll do, we'll do the cloak.
Let's see, all the L1, R1, L2, okay.
An Orc Bane impression.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Nah, nah, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
It's not, I don't think that's gonna happen.
Escape from Osgiloth.
All right, now we're in the main story here.
But we do have Sam.
Oh, we have a Sean Astin interview.
Let's check it out.
Mordor.
The one place in Middle Earth we don't want to see any closer.
The one place we're trying to get to.
It's just where we can't get.
Let's face it, Mr. Frodo.
We're lost.
There's a lot in the movie where Sam is, the character himself, is very-
He's American?
He gets sad a lot.
He's, there's a kind of comic relief element.
Holy shit.
His goodness and his decency is what makes him heroic
and his, his bravery in the face of great danger.
I'm going to Mordor alone.
Of course you are.
Bro, spoilers.
And I'm coming with you.
But because the game is sort of an action war game,
the aspect of Sam's character that really comes through in the game
is the kind of heroic, heroic character.
Fighting Sam.
I get to really go and fight the orcs instead of having to, you know,
pull up from stabbing them because it's a stunt guy you don't want to hurt.
You really feel like you're inside the movie, driving the movie.
When I actually, for the first time, had a controller in my hands,
I was looking at a very realistic likeness of myself.
That's gotta be so crazy.
And it reminded me of filming the scenes.
It looked exactly like when we were filming on the sets
and it was totally interactive.
I think the game is-
You really feel like Sam, yeah.
That's good.
All right, let's do The King of the Dead.
I can't fucking believe I'm doing what I did last time.
We're going to get to a level where I'm stuck for like two hours.
And it was because I didn't pick Aragorn in the first level.
Boss?
Boss fight.
Wait, wasn't he just talking to Aragorn?
Ooh, I almost had perfect there.
Gimli sucks.
Oh, he doesn't.
It's just a little small.
All right, let's go.
Bring it on.
I need to get some perfects here.
What?
Come on, here it comes.
Perfect.
Come on, do it.
Do it!
Is there health anywhere?
Uh-oh.
I see what you're doing over there.
Why are you throwing it, Gimli?
I don't even see where that was.
Just-
He does that every time.
I'm going to have to fight him again.
Perfect!
You wasted my perfect meter, dude.
Oh, he's going to do it again.
I see.
Uh-oh, it's like Space Invaders.
He's already-
Oh, shit.
Dude, how many spikes do you get?
Dang!
Is he going to do it?
He's going to do the-
Oh.
No health.
I'm in trouble.
God, I'm so paranoid.
Health, got it.
Nice.
All right, let's go.
Bring it on.
New commentary for the day.
I fucking forgot again.
What's he doing?
Just another wave.
Oh, shit.
And there's archers.
Hey, he was off screen.
That's not fair.
How do you-
How do you do, fellow warriors?
That doesn't work here.
That was so stupid.
Why do they even read that?
You do, fellow warriors.
All right, I win.
This is it.
Don't go right in.
He does the-
Here we go.
I win.
What say you?
I need you to come off the boat
and be in the movie
for 10 seconds in a battle.
What say you?
Oh, Jesus.
No, I'm slow.
All right, if this is me,
I have at least 10 or 15 axes
that I have made for me.
I am baseball swinging
and throwing the axe off
and running with both hands.
I got extra axes.
You know what I mean?
Make sure you have at least
10 of these that are made.
I can't see shit.
Let me know where I am.
Jesus.
What the fuck?
This is fucking idiot over here
that's messing the whole thing up.
Who's winning?
That's a good question.
I think I am currently.
We'll see in about 10 seconds
if that's going to be the case.
Dude, Jeremy, it's your mother.
Please stop saying the F word so often.
My, I learned it from you.
Okay, this is fun, I guess.
Get the fuck out of my way.
Go!
Wink now.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, this level sucks.
I don't want to do this level again.
I'm going to try to get through.
No, no winks, not now.
No, no, no, no, no.
Four winks, you'll get it.
No, no.
I can't fucking see anything.
Give me perfect.
How the fuck do I not have perfect?
Right at the fucking end.
Give me a break.
Wait, is this even more of this shit?
I'm surprised I did that.
Six winks.
What?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
That's a triple perk.
The purple.
What?
Purple?
Why can't I say this?
Purple.
Perfect.
What happened?
What?
I thought, what do you mean?
I ran the wrong way.
What the hell?
What the fuck was that?
All right, Jesus.
I mean, I ran the wrong way.
Oh, come on.
Don't have to do this whole thing again, do I?
Oh, give me a break.
What the fuck?
That was playing pretty well, too.
How did I run the wrong way?
You missed a wink.
You ran into the wall instead of the door.
No, fuck that.
Come on.
Give me a break.
Winks are worthless now.
That was hard, too.
Not a bad start.
Except this stupid motherfucker in the back with the dumb bow and arrow.
I hate arrows.
It's so hard to see anything in this fucking game.
Let alone the guy shooting the arrows.
Missed another wink.
No, I didn't.
I did two extras.
I did two extra winks, so I'm covered for those two that I missed.
Damn it.
I don't want to do this again.
This mission is so dumb.
This doesn't even happen in the movie.
There's a cut.
It cuts to them being outside.
Get out of my fucking way.
Come on, give me.
I'm not even fucking...
Why wouldn't you put the camera like even 30 degrees higher than this?
All I see is green smoke.
Does anyone else taste iron?
That's blood.
You're tasting blood.
I don't know why you're tasting blood, but I would maybe figure it out.
Maybe you bit your tongue or something.
Just be careful.
All right, this time I'm not going to fuck it up.
Let's go.
I beat this game again and again when I was eight.
No, you didn't.
What the fuck is going on?
Why?
Come on.
Fuck this level.
Too slow.
I was...
I'm walking down.
That's not the wrong way.
I'm literally walking down.
What the fuck?
What did I do wrong?
I didn't do...
I just was walking.
Oh, that was stupid.
You know, these legs are too short.
That's probably like whatever.
Did I fuck it up again?
I mean, he's perfect.
Okay, can we please keep going?
It's happening again.
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
It's happening again.
What?
The Jeremy runs into terrible game design choices?
The stream?
Is that what you're describing?
Blame the player not...
No, no, no.
Blame game.
Only blame game.
It's never my fault.
Only blame video game.
Call Peter Jackson right now.
I don't have...
I don't know what Peter Jackson's fucking telephone number is
and he had nothing to do with this game.
We're good.
Nice frames.
They're actually not even as bad as you're saying.
They're only like 10 frames.
Sorry.
I'm just gonna just bam square because of what...
I'm just gonna get perfects by doing this
because there's so many people here.
And...
I can't even.
I guess I hit somebody with an axe.
Is that...
I guess...
Three come out.
And then I...
Okay.
Where's the right...
Where did I go?
Where's the right way?
Look at this.
Doesn't this break away?
This looks like it breaks away
but it's not this way.
This is down here.
I gotta get this right for when I need to leave.
Down here.
Left?
Like the way that I came in?
Like over here.
Your other left.
That is left.
So this way.
What are we doing?
All right.
Let's go.
I don't want to be...
More...
What's going on?
What's happening?
What is going on?
What?
What the...
The art that took too long?
I...
That was the last art...
Why are they even spawning?
What the...
Give me a break.
Oh, I'm actually mad about this.
What the fuck, man?
They're spawning the archer over on the right
where the camera don't even fucking look.
Does that...
What...
I can't...
What am I gonna complain about?
A 20-year-old game that...
Who cares?
Oh, sorry.
17-year-old game.
I have to pee too.
Can I skip this mission?
Give me some perfects.
I liked it better when Christopher Lee was talking.
That was interesting.
I can't even get that help.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
They always have to do stuff with this bullshit.
All right.
I'm gonna beat this one.
I'm gonna try as hard as I can.
Is it too early to be malding?
I hate timed missions, no matter what it is.
I hate scrolling Mario levels for the same damn reason.
Guys, don't put pressure on me.
Fuck off.
I want to play the game.
Lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock,
lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock, lock.
I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die in here.
If I die again, I have to go pee.
Pee your pants.
No, no, no.
Don't tell me to do that.
That's not a good idea.
What the fuck am I walking into right now?
There's nothing in that water, man.
There's nothing in that water.
All right.
This is it.
Let's go.
I'm trying as hard as I can.
Am I gonna save work?
Let's go.
is there still somebody over here come on man let's go out legolas get the fuck out of the way
kill him kill him kill him please for the love of god
every time it's right at the end oh slow down i'm okay i don't think it's mad about anything
i've i saw have we failed i said the word failed and i got very upset for i got annoyed for a second
10 perfect 14 i gotta pee you've hated every mission so far that's not true
i like the second one that's the comp for all
what should i do germa please stop streaming my friend won't play a game with me because he's
watching you stream um go play with your friend what's his name what's the name look just go play
whatever you're gonna play go play with them don't worry you're not gonna miss much all you're gonna
miss is me over the next three four hours progressively get more annoyed at this
playstation 2 game to a point where i hit a wall and i say i'm sorry guys i'm not gonna be able
to do this tonight because this guy i don't i don't like this game and it's making me very angry
and then we're gonna sit there for an hour on the same mission i'll finally beat it and i'll be
like wow what a good experience you're not gonna miss very much uh i'm gonna get it all you spoiled
the whole stream no it's not gonna happen parry then instantly kill a man-sized enemy it's just
do it for everybody is there can i do uh healing yet no i'm gonna save the points i'm not gonna
spend them all right it's time to pee let's go pee well pee if you have to but we're back i'll be
right back it was what's going on why is it doing this southern gate no uh concept art or interview
come on i'll comment here i want to comment on it says i wonder what the average day for a germa
viewer is i think i could have a pretty accurate statement of what that is when you get up in the
morning at 7 30 a.m sharp answer your 20 emails on the incredible time you're doing on the stock
market you're up at least two or three hundred thousand dollars i think total you're doing
really good trades you do technical analysis pretty good you get into your uh bmw on the way
to work you're a neurosurgeon do your first neurosurgery of the day check on the stream see
what we're doing see that i'm playing lord of the rings you're like oh that's kind of cool
i have lunch i'm only 23 dude that's real young to be doing the things you're doing damn good work
that's me that's me real wink hold on a second i have somehow tangled my headset i don't even
know how i did this like how did i do this i'm gonna hold this up because this is just this is
an oddity how did this happen what did i do to have this happen look it's even it has its own
gravity it has its own gravitational pull how does this make any fucking sense what is going
on right here it's standing up this wasn't like this when i left the room mega milk shirt no
no i'm sorry i'm sorry i gotta have to fucking make you stop that's this is a red red sock shirt
jesus mega socks all right all right all right all right i'm ready i'm ready i'm ready i'm ready
you guys ready here we go uh storm gc 10 10 community subs thank you for the 10 subs storm
great canadian fk club thanks for the five community subs thanks a lot guys storm actually gave 20
community subs let's get that right thanks for the huge amount of fucking subscriptions that
you've given to the channel and yes i'm aware that there was a there was a wink on the channel
don't look at that don't look at that come on what the fuck everyone's looking at it i can feel it
all right let's do the southern gate why is he locked puberty at 34 no it's called shaving
and having irritation come on 10 more subs from sculptor thanks sculptor
back i'd sit appreciate it sculptor thank you and then through gondor's southern gate here to join
the great battle of our time i actually remember this mission i'm gonna like this one guaranteed
this is a grim scene can smell orc even from well never mind you can't block that all right just
run back up i can't do a big swing just to kill it now use pyromancy yeah what the hell was i
thinking i'm dead stay back and cast lightning bolts at the motherfucker this is a grim scene i
remember this yeah i remember hearing this is a grim scene more than a dozen times and then
through gondor's southern gate here to join the great battle of our time this is a grim scene
every time this is a yeah i actually think this might be a hard one 20 hour stream no
won't be that long so do i have the uh the instant kill don't do i does he have it i think he has it
all right let's try to get this happening here are you bait him over there and then i'll
how am i supposed to get him he does that every time it's an instant counter
environment kill him or something holy shit this is fucking horrible i'm dead so one tap
run away but when i get close enough it's it's almost like you kind of can't avoid it one tap
run one tap run one tap run oh no this is like this this environmental shit over here hold on
gore thank you gore maggie for the five community subs a lot of community subs today
through gondor's southern gate thanks for the subs guys the great battle of our time
this is environmental shit over here hold on what we got i can like yeah i can launch something at
him can i yeah yep all right all right yeah yeah yeah okay so go go trigger the cut scene okay
so good throw that's who i wanted to throw my spirit as the guy across the game yeah that's
what i wanted to throw the fucking spirit like the sound guy all right give me he knows what
i'm trying to do here we go i just got fucked up i got really why won't he come over here come over
here god damn it you know what i could probably just do down here i could probably just get a shit
load of perfect why even fight the guy just grind okay here we go i don't
i haven't even fought the troll yet god oh god oh god oh god too many
i can't swing i can't even swing the axe i can't swing that i can't swing
can't do it how is the troll still at the door he is isn't he see he's still gonna be there when
i do this right fuck too many people too many people over here all right launch the other one
let's go did he get up there okay i'm dead i did two damage to him no i did more than that
this is gonna take a while this is a grim scene
but last lead him back to light city he shall head north and then through gondor's southern gate
here to join the great i remember this level i played it over and over will be all right i'll
get it right now this is a grim one run run run run run run oh yes i know this catapult
i'm also surrounded by people auto attacking me at all times launch it let's go how many
how many of the four all right i'll get it one two three four all right did it please get out
of my way are they with me are they running with me now do it do it r1 what okay now i need to go
forward to the gate i can't even fucking walk just please is one more catapult somewhere
i think i just have to the troll do i have to kill the troll i have to kill the troll don't i
i gotta kill this troll don't i oh yeah yeah oh boy all right okay all right i got help relax
okay anybody yeah how the fuck am i gonna throw a spear at this guy in the middle of all this
bullshit i how the hell is that gonna happen like what i'm the only guy on the field right now
i got how am i gonna throw a spear at the troll kill them all i think they did they eventually
here we go opportunity okay all right all right all right all right all right down to
what else now what else am i do i have to do i have to go kill that motherfucker right now
just on my own i can't kill this troll by myself is there any more catapults is it one more over
here it might be this one's not timed or anything no there's nothing over here
sorry that was like the script supervisor sorry i just have to get in there i think and fight the
trolls how the fuck am i gonna do this i can't get out of the please get out of the way so i can
throw a spear the right side didn't i've just i'm just over here wait actually i can run through
this oh look at how small that is i think i don't know
didn't know at least i didn't have to restart it oh my god there's a big one up here how do i get
rid of this guy what didn't i shoot up catapults at this guy oh dude he just like hit me over the
edge wait wait wait wait get um what dude okay i need health somebody drop health please
this is never gonna stop coming
okay i just burnt the orc it's full health right there i'm in perfect mode i'm in perfect mode
just hit him ow that hurts oh my god i just got double tapped fuck watch out watch out watch out
please all right help no i can't if i go in there and hit him he swings and fucking hit see
those two idiots do the same thing even the ai cannot avoid that hit i have to throwing axes
this video game does this thing where it auto locks onto somebody and i can't change it
i would love to throw an axe at him but it's gonna pick one of the random actors in front of me
i'm gonna run run run run run run run this guy's almost dead all right that one's dead
no not yet it's not gonna happen get out of the way just kill him all right go down i'm going down
i'm going back down just to get in the front door what the hell happens when you get through the
house okay we're i'm just gonna go back no we're going i'm gonna go back down can i either alive
but even get by him holy shit he's just get hit once okay fuck you i win all right i'll get now
we go we're good we're good we're good we're good okay
okay he explodes i didn't know he was gonna explode that was bullshit you didn't give me
a second man i was in a cutscene that's not fair all right you guys handle this well i do this
they're not gonna do that it's so unfair man am i still fighting up here i'm getting hit up here
i can't i'm getting hit what do you see how much i good thing i was spamming square because i would
be dead back down wait no dump the uh dump the acid on him okay i burnt him let's go good let's
go dude what the fuck that's gravy this guy out of here all right let's go back down through the
front door that's the best song ever there's no health down here how could there not be health
in here is at the end of the level yep that was tricky that was tricky that's a good grind level
yeah oh yeah absolutely we had big bits we had 10 000 bits from freak out wait didn't i ban you
i think i banned you from giving bits ever again or something didn't i for yeah this is the guy
yeah this is a ban because i banned i banned myself from reading this person's bits ever again
ban him again yeah yeah what the fuck what no this is the porn guy this is the porn codes
porno porno guy yeah i know i they struck out oh this is good use unpowerful foes to smash a
shield dock under the ground and strike yep give him a chance give him a chance give him a chance
give him a chance give him a chance give him a chance oh you had three chances that's how
baseball works you swing in this three times you're out yeah you already you already had
your at bat but you want me to give this guy a whole inning worth of outs a whole season
all right all right i'll give him a chance i'll give him one more chance this is it okay ready
this is freak out thanks for the 100 bucks is a lot of money that's you've given a shitload of
money but you've also been been banned from me reading them but i'm doing it anyways so
uh we'll get a try so stop me i'm gonna say this very slowly stop me if there's something wrong
with this message welcome to hell jerry we've been expecting you here are the wise words of
one of the great philosophers of our time gucci without the sauce stop you're gone okay uh a man
is lost but the same man can be lost in sauce at first i didn't get it but once i saw a bee
drowning honey is that another route for this guy not porn
encrypted porn encrypted i feel like i should buy something no i'm gonna save it for samwise i'm
not gonna play all right bye bye let's go oh here it is i want this i want everybody to have this
uh strength of iron i want everyone to have this too dark deliverance all right i got a new combo
though what is it what is it triangle no what is it i just did it didn't i just get it no i
didn't triangle triangle circle triangle yeah but thank you freak out for the 10 000 uh 10 000 bits
100 fucking dollars shitload of money it's a ton of money it's too much money but yes unfortunately
i will be screening your calls uh for the remainder of time that you give any money if you ever do
again that's just the way it works i've been to screen your calls now oh all right we're at
fields we're almost at the end of the game this shit hadn't been 11 12 13 hours i'm
i'm gonna beat this game soon this game's shorter than the last one that's interesting all right
let's do um minister at the top of the wall oh yeah i'm so happy i get to be gandalf who are the
secret characters you missed an interview oh shit i'll get it we'll watch it the last game included
parts of fellowship of the ring no that's true and saran learns that the ring is in the hands of a
hobby he will be drawn to it fate has given us form and he knows not who bears the ring your
favorite level this confusion is the bait i must place in my trap don't you understand
he thinks you have the ring he's coming for you then the war will come and rohan will ride to
gondor's aid striking from the north i'm checked by a now cleansed eisenstein
the mca caragon travels through death's shadow the elephant wave level is really really grim i mean
really grim like you can smell the bad design travel to minas tirith the envelope in which
we must beat saran's armies in our bids to buy frodo and sam enough time i missed a wink fucking
thanks for reminding me reached my ears of this aragon son of alethor and i tell you now ranger
from the north is there any hope kind of no absolutely not there never was everyone's going
to die will be before all these wars they decided what an outfit don't you want i want to wear that
outfit i want to wear this like the big robe and like the cool like pants why can't i be like a
cool magical wizard or something oh no it's no what hold on it's a ladder level no it can't be
it can't be they wouldn't bring this back how do i how do i knock the ladders down
no it can't be how do you kick a lot how do you kick them down circle oh my god okay uh this is
okay there's a ladder level and there's so much this like verticality launch the catapult and
launch the catapult
no anything but a ladder level well i'm i'm looks like i'm doing okay
it's not a total loss cause yet maybe this one's more forgiving it's not that's great it's really
good to hear this design the level is kind of odd it's it's this is all the way to the right
okay this is all the way to the right is there any health or anything over here that i can see
or need we're not safe here well what does the orc clock in the top right mean is that when it
gets full that means it's over what is this where am i going why can i go down here it seems like a
place i don't want to be or is it i don't okay whoa somebody drop health somebody drop health
thank you okay this is not as bad as the last one was the last one was unbelievably awful
let's go i see um siege towers something capitals yep up here watch out you guys know what to do
fire got it good right direct hit got it do it again we have to do this again
still here fire and okay the the i gotta go down here there's a dragon too all right uh hurry up
need help oh shit here comes another one excuse me is there another catapult or is it just the
one catapult catapult up here i hope to god there is hurry hurry catapult oh
fuck they've made it they made it they made it it's over what happens it breaches okay i mean
are they just gonna pour in oh i'll be fine now kill it okay that's good i think i was concerned
pretty much for no reason that's not even a big deal yeah come on where are they all why is it
they're all over here holy fuck there's so many okay i'm gonna lose how many there's not even
have any ladders up like dude i'm fucking going there's nobody even up here all right i have to
shoot the uh catapult no i don't fuck it let's go all right all right seriously when is this
gonna be over all right let me get this first try i don't want to do this again there's nobody
even over here okay there are people over here quite a few actually there's quite a few people
over here all right let's let's go no fuck you these guys just spawned out of nowhere
they weren't even here where no oh where is this no hurry right here
get this shit out of here all right now now i'm gonna go shoot the with catapult shoot the tower
that's what i'm gonna do i'm going go go go go go go go go go go go go hurry up hurry up come on come
on move move move move move move move move get out of my way what is this fucking tower i'm in
what is this this is not the catapult what the fuck is this why is this even here what's this here
for what a waste of time to be able to even go up in this tower why is here what i got i can't do
what i gotta fucking clear this out oh god what's this making me look up a random fucking tower
that means nothing and by the way the cameras are going to change angles 15 times ladder levels
not another ladder level and we let's go all right i'm ready destroy the siege tower i try i try to
just do it but we have cinematic towers to climb and another timed ass mission in this timed ass
game god damn it i can't fucking believe i have to do this again we already did this in the last
game this doesn't even happen in return of the king they just wanted to redo it because it was
easy to put it as its own level lord of the ladders god damn it man fucking even is anybody
get your shit out of here all right i'm gonna call that there's something wrong with your
fucking gauge there's nobody here why would that be at like 50 filled there's only one ladder
go all the way over here all right and then i gotta remember where the
catapulted nothing over here right no
dude this this this these camera changes make me want to throw up into my hands and use it to
wash my face it's seriously the most disorienting fucking thing ever what the fuck this is on the
same plane we've changed directions like four times you have a two link debt that's all right
i'll settle it up later two links in the sink god damn i don't want to do another ladder level
nobody wants to do a ladder push level here we go and there's already a bunch of people
up here and i have to shoot it twice fuck oh man oh man here we go here we go again
uh we're gonna go up here and we're gonna get this over with you can't why can't you just fire
without me i need to tell you when to fire just fire you're in the right spot why do you need
someone to tell you to do it just do it clean up some of this shit fucking flashbacks and now
i'm already overwhelmed i have to fire them i'm gonna lose hey idiots the what do you what are
you aiming at why is this not turning the other direction what why is it not firing in the
direction why would it not be firing into the right side no i'm very confused they only want
to shoot at the one coming in on the left side what the fuck is that they won't rotate it what
to shoot the tower yourself well what that what in the name of god is the reason to use the
catapult in the first place oh my god there's no nothing there's no reason to okay here we go
i'm gonna i'm just gonna ignore it somebody said that uh 80 percent well you know you could say
that that's that's accurate i don't think it's not 80 a significant portion of my 2020 streams have
been running around pushing ladders down that's true now how many hours have i streamed in 2020
anybody know do we have any do we have that data because at least six of those hours or so have
been pushing ladders down in the middle of the ring stage i mean it's got to be like probably
five percent six percent what the fuck hit me all right let's get that to 12 percent all right all
right i'm gonna stop reading chat and play the game you know what go down here it's probably
easier for me to hit these just go all the way around right that's the scrap anytime there's any
more than one in the middle where is this where's this thing tiny ass ladder die
we already did this i don't want to do it again i don't want to do this again i'm not even having
flashbacks i'm redoing i'm reimagining the same thing i did this is not a flashback
look at my fucking health too it's so bad move please there's another catapult for the other
side why doesn't it show up on the minimap why is this the only one that shows up on the minimap
so i'm gonna i need health too i'm gonna i might have to restart this one
because this thing's gonna get i need to get over here get out of my fucking way i'm painting the ass
is it dragging on our team is gonna make it isn't oh boy what a grim scene this one is
now please give me help can i drain somebody let me just take a life drain one of these fucking
guys oh my god it's too many so there is there is a catapult on the lower right corner here is
that what you're saying or should i just go shoot it with my own with my shooting i shoot it i'm
just gonna shoot it with my own arms i'm gonna shoot with my own arm it actually worked i thought
i okay but i can do that but i'm gonna lose anyways because uh i don't have a second player
who's doing the other shit while i do that look at all these guys in here go come on die die please
come on go go go go go go go oh my god give me a break move move move knock it down knock it
up all right i gotta yeah i gotta shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot shoot
come on come on come on come on go where is it it's here already it's here is it here it works
all right keep going go go go go go go what that was only that was on the minimap for like one
second that's gotta be scripted right it has to be scripted right dude please just get out of the
fucking goddamn way you're driving me nuts driving me nuts with this bullshit i can't just god damn
it how many of you have to die before i get a fucking opportunity oh good hit the wall
excellent work gandalf your aim is impeccable actually mad no i'm no i'm not half mad
they can't so what do we do go down where we're going where we're running to i don't know gandalf
doesn't have a fucking plan i don't know just fucking run get in the bathtub i heard that's
the best place to go when there's a tornado maybe it'll work here are we gonna get out
where am i oh shit get out quick oh oh my chest gandalf what did you do you just killed everybody
oh that sucked not as long as the last one though thankfully i hate those ladder levels are so
the worst i hate them i don't know what ladders the only ladders i want to climb are i said it
wrong the only ladders i want are the ones that i climb it's a lot of experience
did i buy everything for everybody let's see lightning bolt increased damage on the projectile
i want that i use it a lot what's this link what are you guys spamming here what is this
all right i like it let's put it on uh let's get what i what i want first which is i want the combo
effective for rapidly dispatching shielded enemies yeah triangle xx triangle triangle triangles
square i haven't even done this move i have a lot of points to spend oh all right i'm gonna i'm
gonna upgrade gandalf's shit this magic shield causes increased damage and persists magic shield
i have to do with somebody's special move for the love of god wink now no not yet and i'm gonna do
yeah better lightning bolt i already have this and fire yeah that's what i want i'm never there's no
opportunity for me to do with this shit yeah that's good enough here we go you want to wink
there i did i just did it it just happened i was i was in the middle of it when i turned off the
camera so you got what you wanted now what we have now there's another wink 20 minutes no that wasn't
at the top of the wall he and oh he and mckellan
quarters in england of ea was me doing the crack what the fuck is this
game which the curiosity of gandalf that there are many of us this is me but then when we were
making the film there was my double and there was the stunt gandalfs the ones who did the fights and
their twelves and then there's the digitalized gandalfs who are sometimes seen in the crowd scenes
in the film then there's the gandalf of this um this guy the gandalf is seven thousand years
old but he can do the most remarkable things and he's still got that's a long time and i only wish
that gandalf in the film had been quite as agile as gandalf the wisest of you will choose to imagine
being alive maybe the most of that long immortal character or something immortal if you can't be
in the movie you might as well play the game it's the next best thing i've been alive and being able
to see the dinosaurs become extinct it's too much info to have all right let's go on the other
let's go back to our to our hobbit crew seven thousand no i know seven thousand years is not
seven million i'm just saying if you if you were immortal you would just watch whole civil no i
wouldn't want to do that a thousand years would be fun though like you'd be able to live a thousand
years that's kind of interesting i would not i wouldn't want to live forever golem's treachery
may yet be the ruin of our plan but only guide frodo to his doom really won't live forever
we're trapped i'm pretzels dreamer you look like golem you look like golem he has actually
has your facial features you kind of look like him yeah i know that's funny okay some ways
mr frodo was counting on you to rescue him no matter what this is a maze level what i can't
step on them can i burn them you won't stop me at home all right what's it what's the new combo it's
it's triangle triangle circle triangle x x what is this x triangle x triangle xx he doesn't have it
he's level three god damn it right he's level three how would he have that this is embarrassing
just die just sam sam this is embarrassing you're embarrassing me say the line say the line say the
um okay well it's not i can't say it yet it's not not accurate yet what's his character's name
shilob damn all right where is he i just heard him say like sam help me use fierce attack use
fierce attack use fierce attack should i use fierce attack or should i use something else
oh my goodness works like charm actually no health away oh this is a grim scene
oh shit i don't know that was gonna do that all right let's go come here give me this
move i'm coming frodo burn it i'm gonna fucking burst if i don't hear that line in 10 seconds
relax that didn't do anything what how did that not do anything
get that shield off no pick it up oh got it there we go now get out of here
knock it over knock this over just who cares all right now throw this at him got him all right now
drink the soup in the middle can i drink this soup i'm all right bro i'm sorry oh shit
good strategy didn't kill spider why where are you bro no i want to throw throw throw throw throw
throw throw throw oh shit did i get it come on how are you on your fire you're just dead
just die that's a full health all right don't fuck around just get it whoa i hit him what with
the fire what is he okay this guy's freaking me out you're fucking freaking me out man
did the health disappear no they don't they disappear the health disappears does it
you gotta be kidding me it disappears health disappears i didn't know that i didn't know it
disappeared i can think disappears come on you deserve that no i don't checkpoint we're good
the giant enemy come on fighter fighter pick it up sam pick up the god you idiot i'm trying to
pick up the thing and he won't pick it up whatever checkpoints right there full health i'm just going
to break a boy's technique for the rest of the game he said if we can move on well you can do
whatever you want you can you can do whatever you want you're the ruler of your own destiny right
oh i've got itchy skin again r1 okay now excuse me r1 r1 r1 okay clear it again i need to do two
i don't know no i don't just walk around them i have to use the guitarro
talking about i r1 don't r1 understand r1 stand your r1
i don't even know what that means but it's funny here we go this way that's a spongebob reference
what a great show you guys like that show shit why can i throw the hey bro i'm gonna throw it in
here what the hell i can't walk i can only stand still i can't carry the torch i can only stand
still um okay well i'm gonna go the other way is this even fucking doing anything am i just stuck
here now wait you cut it i don't think i can no you can't just cut it get out of the way all right
i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good what happened here oh i gotta go up oh that's a pain in the ass
i gotta go all the way around and throw it over there a little puzzle i can figure it out don't
worry i don't need help keep looking to try to help me help nice okay go ahead back to it
fellowship of the ring all right what's the best lord of the rings movie and that's a real debate
for this chat here what's the best lord of the rings movie which one that's not what i wanted
to do really fellowship fellowship is pretty good it's probably two towers for me yeah it's
two towers for me the turn of the king is really good but it's it's two towers i think
at least for me shit there's so many here it's the best trilogy ever made oh absolutely
i don't think anything comes close what comes close what's the trilogy that comes
is it too late oh well shit here we go i have to pick them up all right what's the strategy here
block block block and then go in with a couple of swings yeah it looks like it's just block block
swing maybe not i don't think that's what i have to do okay what what happens in the movie doesn't
he do something in the movie giant enemy spider they're done okay good i just keep running we
should run forward i think it's just walk walk walk and fight i wonder if he does it he's like
shut she great she loved all right um what about this way no i think it's the fight it
i can't really run around should i throw he keeps backing up so fast i can't even i'm dead
i've got a lot of health trying to get her back to the yeah i'll try to get back to the wall
no all right you go this way back up here what are you doing what are you doing stop stop doing
that you're freaking me out back into the wall there you go no stop stop stop stop stop don't
what are you doing i'm just gonna wait till she does that she's gonna stop spin spin spin spin spin
spin spin spin like that no all right i don't know if you uh i think you're in a good spot
no you're not you didn't hit me this is stupid two one two why did you swing a third time
i'm not doing this right yeah there's something else i have to be doing is it going on what is
this image i don't get it i don't understand why why okay for a second for a second i thought this
was the webcam facing this guy and that was his webcam i'm like this is it no is
this i don't know what is going on in this fucking image you guys are freaking me out
who made this hold on hold on hold on this is i hate this is fucking so stupid oh my god
all right i'm gonna get let's go i'm too small to hit him my weapon is too short and i'm too small
i have to run behind i have to run back i don't know what i'm supposed to fucking do with this
i've got a throw it has to be a throw there's no way there's no way this is not a throw
no fucking way this is not a throw like throw this or something like hit this thing with a
what the fuck i'm definitely not doing this right i gotta do this correct i'm not doing this right
i gotta do this right does it get me something i'm gonna look at the environment as you do in
these games you check out the environment the environment fucking picture oh it's so stupid
all right what do we got around here sam's on drugs nothing with something over here
i don't know i don't think so do what i don't get it i don't get it i don't get it i don't
know do i just have to attack watch the movie to find out what they do do i just don't have
to pick up frodo no i can't pick frodo up wait use the cloak that somehow made it worse i just
stabbed it in the face it didn't do anything stab the butt i mean as hard did i don't think i can
do that she's con she's constantly moving around i can't like get around her what the fuck what
well then stab i can only use the cloak like every two minutes and she backs up she's like
swing swing back have you ever seen this movie yeah but this is not i don't know what happened
somebody i don't know what happens in this movie oh okay so um gotta take her down to about 30
and then she jumps up and then spiders spawn and it just all right i'm going for it let's go
she's gonna be very very careful come here stop please let me just swing at you come on spin
around do the thing that you spin around and you run around the circle and i can just sprint
into you like that because yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah let's go all right kill the spiders quick
it's triangle r2 triangle r2 triangle r2 not one of you dropped health how dare you come on whoa
what the fuck you are annoying you're annoying you're annoying you say what's your size
is
okay let's go again use the cloak that's not gonna help me right now
i need one of these guys to have health you're really pissing me off with this spider shit
i'm dead you're supposed to hit the abdomen is impossible i don't think that's actually
possible you can't stop me let's come on bring on the spider is full health but difficulties is on
normal now this game i don't think is completable on heart and once you have two people playing at
the same time and they've grinded a level a hundred times strange makes me want to throw up
why are you not grinding a hundred times oh my god we're just reading
now what are you up to not just reading fuck off give me some health finally you fuck faces
die have it be done please it's it over yet what are you doing what the fuck is going on
i don't know what to do swing run behind i don't know give me some help holy fuck okay all right
i'm in trouble i don't know i gotta move at some point here but it's gonna he's gonna body slam
she's gonna body slam me she's gonna body slam me god damn it i can't even move
oh what the fuck no way give me a break i'm serious i can't do anything i i could cloak
but if i have to kill them eventually i'm not high enough level for this what level is sam i
don't even remember i didn't block oh god you level five yeah but i mean this is the only
i probably have to grind another level with sam that's probably what's happening you're right
you can't stop me i should get it all right you just gotta you gotta kill them second that they
land if you have more than three people around you you just fucked all right watch over the
body slam let's go fuck children all right here we go ah no okay we're bad angle bad camera all
right now watch that she runs around the circle she's run great excellent game thanks for the
even tenth of a second to move this is it i gotta be good here
elf yes all right let's go come on let's go oh shit i just got baited so hard stop moving stop
stop this nonsense please no don't go up but not the top rope no not the top rope
oh you're making me want to fucking scream jump down so i can kill you please
please let me end this dude this please move the i hate this he hates it he hates it
i hated that i hated that yeah you know you're right you can say that here
the little filth will wake up and wish he'd never been born is there a wink take it back to the
fortress no there was yeah you're right i'm i don't i'm that's gonna be really annoying from here on
out the streamer that winks every like three minutes on stream yeah that's right i might
have to put the can on this one in like six months before i already got a buff so he can do a parry
now and he can do this combo finally it only took a million what the fuck happening right now
are you finished yes i am well not i mean strange still going but you know all right we're at the
final three levels of the game i i can't believe there's still more coming in the final four levels
see oh hold on elijah wood let's see what elijah has to say one ring never gets to join in any
battles in the film so i was always the kind of the one that was really weak and burdened by the
ring and in this i get to take photo on some adventures that he didn't actually get to go on
i'm a playable character that's cool yes photo style combat's kind of a little clunkier it's
not it's not as finessed as aragorn or certainly legolas would be potatoes kind of fighting very
straightforward i thought that was him falling down the stairs for a second to sort of be able
to take my character from the film and to be able to kind of implement that into the game is is
pretty awesome i shall take up this terrible task choosing photo you're also choosing the
ring bear so that's pretty cool i'm kind of biased nice all right here's kyrith kyrith tingle
black gate uh should i do the uh worst mission in the whole game or should i wait
i'm gonna do i'll do this one first we'll get we'll get sam's storyline out of the way
how long have i been streaming four hours just about four hours
damn just go in he's doing work better than gandalf what does this do use another combo
i don't think i could even use the other combos yet can i he's only level four
just kill me so i can do the way the game's supposed to be played 80 yeah that's gonna be
horrible this makes me want to play shadow war all right so i have a cloak
is there a way i can climb up or i guess i've been spotted probably
is there even a way i can get over her hold on let me look at this first
okay well that just let more of them come down cool all right they're fighting each other
they are fighting each other why are they fighting each other right now keep going i
need how are they dead do i have to kill everybody or just do i personally have to kill 80 i don't
get it really am i gonna run all the way via all these guys and not let me see can i
instant perfect mode for doing that holy shit all right these guys these guys are a huge pain in the
ass to fight did i hit myself in the head with my own weapon
all right so can i activate the
can i turn this on while i'm cloaked or no i move so slow when i'm cloaked though
can i turn this on when i'm cloaked all right okay that was all right that was all right
jesus jesus how i reliably take care of these guys i could drop the fire on them
come here come right here come over here the hell is this guy doing
what are you doing what is he just taunting get the fuck over here oh my fucking god seriously
what the hell are you doing thank you what the hell is that whatever i'll take it who's taunting
too roll around on the ground man uh can i look at the combos i want to look at the combos
can i see that joe upgrades there we go all right i can do final judgment balrog's gambits the
other one that's the one i'm thinking of x circle triangle there it is swing swing somebody swing
i'm invincible right here right all right no no no i can't i cannot fight this guy one-on-one
it's just it's instantly losing so i need to what the fuck am i looking at what is going on
oh my what's going on do it wait isn't this um uh okay i'm starting to throw it's all right
it respawned all right triangle was it triangle down here oh he's coming he's coming all right
what trying to do the orpane but it won't work i need health bad can i get hit by a stray blade
okay i'm dead i'm in trouble oh no germa you're doing this again well it's a different game
but yes yes uh for some reason i've decided that i was going to play this one too yep you're right
bern get in there come on give me perfect so i can get some help
um why does sam have a blue lightsaber um he i mean he kind of doesn't die
it's just finally getting hits on people oh fuck this is gonna eat
ass but your boy spoiling for fun get to the best spot
mr. frodo's up in that tower get myself up there i've got to find a way to beat all these orcs
do you really do you have to beat all of them sam fam you don't have to beat all of them you
don't have to slow down try two why is that not working block r2 block r2 block r2 doesn't do
anything my lord just get out of my fucking way oh no here he comes all right run run run
i just threw that out i don't even know what i threw that uh all right let's go
no watch out for the fat guy don't let him get you i got perfect right now come on
all right dump the dump the fire dump the fire fire fire fire fire fire fire fire fire fire
all right now let's sneak i don't think it needed to do that but okay um we're gonna dump this
oh got him let me get them all yes that's pretty good any help um okay just keep going
keep keep going i'm gonna just keep moving holy shit there's so many people um
i go outside okay we're going outside uh fire uh no no wait wait this is the time i can drop
something i'm stuck here forever until they kill each other so many fairies okay and then keep
carrying keep carrying keep carrying keep carrying nope that's not gonna happen but i thought it was
a uh isn't doing anything what's in here what's this holy shit wow that was cool did it do it again
i need help oh wait is this gonna refill can i just drop it again it's gonna recharge right
okay new plan don't move from this spot only fight from up here wait for people to build fall down
or will they did he miss okay keep it good but this is still a million people over here
all right now there's this guy here oh fuck you just blending in with the goddamn wall
need help oh lucky me lucky me there throw it good i want to throw it at this guy hi
burn see i see on fire right cut this oh that was a lot of whoa whoa oh oh fuck okay that's
what i wanted to do now we go nuts that i could even swing the sword almost there 10 more 15 more
nice throw through this way have it gone down here yeah oh dump it again okay somebody oh
that's right that's supposed to be okay there's people over here i guess i just go back out and
kill a few people who who is he talking about this is okay easy that guy's being blended in
with the smoke all right 70 need 10 more let's just all right i just have to go like this
okay this health here too i just don't even get involved one more get over here walk 77 come on
three more two more hey here comes 80 80 now what cut many down how many is many that's a great
question that's a really good question uh 2700 27 dollars is a lot of money how many is many
that's a good question uh this is from heartbroken samurai he misses his fan's bits well i don't want
to lose this and have to start over again 26 is not no it's usually 50 and i'm gonna be completely
honest it's usually like 55 5000 that's usually what happens right let's be completely real
that's why it happens to midstream stop it that's what we do usually i typically don't stop until
you know in the middle of the stream to do uh hits or subs or anything unless it's like something
i that's just kind of the way it is but i always let's read it i mean i've already started so
he only reads 50 dollar donations on stream well i actually don't read any unless they're something
significant like that it's just kind of the way the stream is run you guys know that we do it at
the end of the stream you guys all know this but why are we acting like this is some new thing
i've been doing this for like three years anyways uh heartbroken samurai i gave some money here hey
germa can you ask my girlfriend uh germa can you ask my girlfriend i'd watching your stream
she loves lord of the rings can you tell her congrats on school and ask her if i'll
hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on a second i mean it's like let me move this out of
the way oh shit i spilt it uh it's not codes it's not ask her if god there's a hold on hey
congratulations on school by the way ask her congratulations about school this is uh
congratulations on school he said ask her about school by the way uh ask her if i'll marry her
i love you christian i fucked that up pretty bad i'm not gonna lie i like i like knocked over a
battery i knocked over a battery you guys that's why you wanted me to do okay that's why you wanted
hey and what was it what was it
oh i'm so sad i'm so embarrassed and sad dude read those bits read i don't read those bits
what are you talking about it's gotta be 50 dollars oh this is bad oh this is really bad
oh my god um and that's why you guys are saying hey congratulations to you too let's go
pristine and heartbroken samurai hopefully you guys are happy together if if it worked out
hopefully it did i hey this is a great fucking stream welcome to the party everybody
oh shit and i knocked a bunch of shit over and i still i thought it was like
bait for a second all right hey thank you so much i hope you guys really enjoy each other
hope you enjoy each other's company hope you like each other hope yeah all right that whole
sequence was horrible i'm sorry for ruining your entire marriage no i just burned myself i just
burnt myself don't lose oh my god i'm gonna lose i'm gonna lose what i have to do what do i have to
do i'm gonna lose that full health help put on the secret okay we're fine no but for real if that
if that was actually for real good luck to you guys if uh hopefully you guys got it worked out
hopefully you guys are love birds and all that good stuff
i'm so like i'm so embarrassed
what is this oh fuck do it again that was fun heartbroken samurai uh thank you for the thank
you for the bits heartbroken samurai that was awful uh but she said yes yes yes it's she said
yes congratulations congratulations you two that makes me feel good imagine if i blew
your marriage proposal oh boy all right let me all right how many okay all right for future
reference all right hang on i have for future reference uh before i if you all right if you
want me to propose to somebody and write in brackets before like put it in parentheses and
say hey like don't read this but i gotta ask you something like don't read this part but like hey
you gotta let me in i gotta be in on it you'd read that out loud no no i would read the first
i would read the hey don't read this out loud part and then i'd go oh and then i'd stop wait
what am i doing oh maybe there's a guy up here that's huge no don't please what do oh my fuck
why is it why is a huge fucking guy up here why did they do this why would they do this i'm stuck
in the corner use it i want to do it oh he's chasing me he's chasing me he's chasing me
oh my fucking god thank jeez you made that more memorable you'll yeah you'll never forget that
you'll never forget it that was a good double leg drop okay what the fuck am i doing
okay i need to throw something at you or what am i doing here okay the shield is broken
not another shilob fight where you do this bullshit i'll throw another fucking i'm throwing
another one at you fuck off he's dazed he's dazed let's just wake him up what's going on
because i'm not supposed to do that oh i get it whoa i thought he was dazed where's it going
he's getting a shield oh oh that's not funny that's not funny i tried what i tried to jump
that's how you know how fucked up i am right now shit come on don't fuck it up here really
you're just gonna keep you to chase me around a fucking circle how am i what how am i gonna
do this this dude's always gonna chase me around a circle now like uh quick again i'm waiting
it's so scary when he just disappears on the screen oh he's running so fast
oh my fuck come on come on sam sam oh fuck you come on
he's getting me okay we're all right here we're doing fine we're good
video games are all fucking the same they're all bad i know the way out phylactery let's get
five thousand bits don't read hey chat i'm fucking huge go fuck yourself hey phylactery thanks to
the five thousand bits that's a lot of perfect you've ruined that guy's marriage all right cloak
of celebration what do i do oh it's just longer increases the time oh everybody gets that move
which is pretty big deal an attacking urik yep get it what else does he not have what's this thing
little six yeah just get it listen it sucks so much this is the move that no one ever uses in
this game i'm certain of it you have so many points just buy everything i mean i could
all right we're at the final three missions of the video game okay but
film production stills take a look stop pinging i knew that was i recognize that from somewhere
that actually is like a moba ping that's cool all right here we are we're at the uh the la i'm gonna
i'm gonna have to i'm gonna breathe in for a little bit on this one a few people have told me
during the course of the stream so far this level sucks you're going to hate this thing
i'm gonna hate this level you're gonna have no fun playing this so i'm just gonna just get ready
i'm gonna i'm prepared i'm just i'm gonna play whatever let's go it will require all my skill
and all of our luck to spring a trap lifetimes in the making in the end it will be decided here
upon the fields of pelenor and before the gates of minas terith from the south aragon will summon
forth an army from beyond the grave will against our stronghold the dark lord summons both man and
beast to oppose us army of powerful forces more terrible than we can imagine does this happen in
the movie i feel like some of these scenes i don't remember seeing rohan shall rise to war
and the world's ending here we go that song in the whole world they they don't actually
roger i'm up here again they seem to have taken into the desert of las vegas
no we're not doing that again it seems there seems to be there seems to be 5 000 more people
than before it looks like a big social media campaign must have happened for both sides here
kill this guy come on bang bang i don't even know what i'm swing it at come on knocking what
50 percent of my health i can't tell if these guys are on my team or not watch it watch it these
guys they look like they could be on my team come on block block it block block it block don't make
me angry go perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect perfect
that help give me the fucking help before it de-spawns or i'm gonna not stream ever again
that's been fun come on you're making me nuts here you're making me nuts
you're going nuts right now i'm gonna go fucking nuts look look i don't run he's telling me there's
no help over here finally what kind of video game doesn't have extra hp help
all right so we gotta oh i remember this part kind of my brain remembers this and my brain
remembers hating this right or something my brain hated this did that do anything what just happened
why is there only one i need to do oh right okay i thought there was like five oh it's um it's over
i fucked it up i actually got it okay did it okay here we go it's two here on this end
okay let's go there we go do i run should i run across do i run down and run across
should i go across this way okay i'm gonna wait for save and we're gonna enter down one two three
okay okay that's good okay okay not right uh incorrect apparently not right okay uh run down
no i i just no
do i have to go down why would they put me over here if i'm actually i'm supposed to run all the
way down no you gotta be fucking kidding me oh what a joke no that's not what i'm supposed to
do actually i try i tried to shoot the first one it didn't even hit you tell me this is gonna hit
i didn't even do anything oh how does that miss i don't understand that doesn't make any sense
didn't even hit i didn't even hit that was lined up right in the fucking back of the guy's back
wrong side of the map i can't even go down but what does mary and pippin even have a health bar
all right so how i go i have to go all the way down in a round or will these hit the second one
so go down but how the fuck do i even get down i think you made a mind just go down there
there is no go down i can't go down from here
do it can i go down here what a stupid fucking thing what an actually absolutely ridiculous
fucking place to put that well now i know where that it happens in the books then gimli and crew
walked by and down the 2d plane which actually is a 3d plane that switches the camera
180 fucking degrees the other direction dude read the books it happens and then lord of the
rings return of the king broke the number one fucking rule of all cinema breaking the 180 degree
line all right where the hell is this where's the way to get up can i go like up how do i go up
they're gonna die again can i go up where can i go up oh my god shoot it
remember he's just stand still i don't even know how i got up here and that was
i don't want to oh does he quick throw a wrench at him this is working is he gone i don't fucking
know is this dude gone we're gonna go back down what do we do these fucking things is it on the
same side as me is it on the same side or is it on the other side same side or the side same
side or the side what side is it on same side i think it's on the same side it's on the same side
i thought you guys are arrogant like this oh good to know those fucking things work
where is it down up here he comes again watch out watch out watch out watch out i gotta throw it i
gotta throw shit at him he's over here stay away stay away you fucking dickhead get out of here
all right all right he's gone he's gone it's gonna be the other way i'm assuming it's probably
gonna be another one on the other side it's just right across same side is he on he's on
the oh he's on this side he's still on this side i'm getting lucky here that was a really really
really lucky fucking super heal right in the head will one of you please do anything you useless
motherfuckers it's just standing around oh i have to play this game by myself this one person behind
me stop watching the movie you two fucking idiots you're in the movie watch out watch out
i guess from the next come on hurry move over there use this it's so funny no not this guy hit him
kill him get out of my way okay another one they keep coming
oh it's on the right side thank god oh all right all right all right all right all right all right
yeah that guy that's the guy we wanted to throw it at that's the guy that's right
oh and i missed oh what a fantastic pixel perfect shot and it didn't even fucking hit him
who loaded these i'm pain in the ass you got fucking kidding me all right quick get over here
so i can throw a couple axes at the witch king oh my god he's just already here no don't kill him
come on he's dead i'm staying right here i am i'm fucking going to that elephant come all the way
over here before i fucking care that elephant can literally come all the way over here fuck them
they're on the other side shit the fucking way
oh boom boom boom boom with the entrance over here there's a lot of people over here give me
better gaga gaga where's the entrance is the flag are they blocking the entrance how dare they oh
god damn it why did you have why couldn't you have pulled the camera back when i was walking
up here in the first place all right i gotta get i gotta get over here because i gotta get ready for
the uh which king all right this is it did i do it
oh thank god big cameo oh my god i did it yes oh feels good
only four perfects come on almost at level eight there we go all right that's better i'm late
so we've got what's killing zone first the amount of time during combat that you remain in yeah
also a new everybody gets the combo lightning strike and that brings us to permanently increases
your health which is good for everybody is there anything i didn't get for everybody
oh this is level nine and level 10 um permanently increases your health of him
i've given me all right that's good increases damage in perfect mode increases damage and
reach perfect mode even faster let's take it wait no i don't have money oh i already have it
no what did i not even buy this back at like level two no all right that's fine i want to
save the points for the last level teeth oh from diablo i see you mean all right teeth from diablo
yeah i see you saying okay we've made it the final two levels in return of the king or no we
have we didn't do the courtyard is this ps2 or emulated this is playstation 2
actual ps2 this is another ladder mission great ps2 slim
the enemy slays your people we must save everyone we count
200 so it's just reverse tower defense we want we want them to go in all right what's this new
combo i got x triangle xx triangle xx x triangle xx now he doesn't have it because he's not this
leveling system here we go what are they doing they're just running around in a circle just
perfect here we go die please everybody in pretty in we we good because oh here they come
give me perfect there we go let's do it fire just just grind perfect right now give me a break
somebody up here why are they firing into the keep wait okay well that was i guess
i made it did i kill those people too fast is that what's going without a problem
and here we go they're dead 200 got in anymore oh he's just running in okay whoops
and alf can yeah when you get perfect that's incredible give me that perfect
come on give me that come on it's right here it's right there uh-oh big guy no okay uh
i need help can you relax on the fire bombs it's getting a little they've been over here the whole
time just killing people they've just been feeding people over here and these guys have
been killing every single one what am i hitting the fucking statue all right i'm no i'm in fucking
trouble ah i'm working on it as easy as it looks lady hell somewhere this sucks glad to see you
gave this masterpiece another go oh this is this is the last one i beat the last one this is
return of the king we must save everyone we can okay okay where am i gonna get perfect there's
nobody ever fucking this swing out like defense against the school you got him
that moves really not that good it just takes too long barely hits anybody on the ground either
like i can't why is it hit him finish him on the ground like what the fuck
okay perfect let's go come on and yet again there's literally no one to attack
they come in waves of six here we go everyone stuff in the middle do one move and kill us all
all right time to look around nobody over there everybody over here
we did people are free to come in right from that way everybody safe okay i get hit by every single
fucking one of those it's just bouncing off this fucking thing can we why i need help good you got
the shield off you did a full four move combo catapult flame attack what does that mean i have
to do that take this the fuck out of here all right let's go let's go go go go go i just threw
that in person when he was talking shit i got a couple barrels here i gotta break that armor off
of him you know don't you just love looking through a telescope it's just like great at it
i picked this up when he was dead i'm actually getting slightly annoyed by this
it's just slightly annoyed are we all right everyone's fine right derma's full mooning
right now no no no no no no no no i'm not i'm you i'm not full mooning this is not a full moon
what are you talking about um why am i standing here oh no oh i killed him instantly why did he
die instantly why did he just die instantly that was ridiculous i think i just got like uh i think
i just got uh i think i got a uh all right slow down i need holy shit it killed him instantly
oh my god i killed him instantly okay everybody really
who is who oh please all right hold on wait okay well i need a barrel i need a barrel i need a
barrel as long as fucking 10 people going i need a barrel barrel over here as long as 30 more
people go across who cares just 30 of you run in you're going to be all right just get in
one more barrel here nothing even in there 172 all right here we go how did you get in here
why is there a troll at the door this is troll at the door uh it's blocking every
path okay so um just get in gone you'll be all right okay all right again though it's
oh my god
jesus man what the fuck is this drop health for me all right we're doing all right
all right
come on lady you can do it look at all these 185 185 we need to 186 186 187
187 188 188 somebody you got in one okay good only 10 more if you need to get in
10 more hopefully one of you can squeeze through 189
i ain't fucking doing anything i'm not doing shit i'm gonna stay in and just block and 200
if i'm gonna get it this is the lemmings come on you can do it you can do it 195
here comes a big batch right here all three are getting in 196 come on oh my god that was horrible
that was horrible
okay i'm gonna mute oh all right everybody relax you fucking asshole oh
as many as we can but the gates breached it is only a matter of dead upon all seven levels of
jesus my part in this battle uh our fate now lies in the hands of a hundred bucks came in from
cyclops parker 10 000 bits uh two or three minutes ago thanks for the huge amount of money they say
hey germans wanted to do some big bits to distract you from the game a little bit glad i could catch
the streamline thanks for the 10 000 bits man not in the marriage no that was ridiculous
the distraction technique no distraction technique not gonna work right now not when i have to do
18 minute long timed levels what do you got i haven't even used this i don't know what this
looks like i've used it once does gandalf have anything i don't have that was worth buying
what's this no i never i'm not gonna use it i'm really not i was my week off it was great thanks
for asking it's very good got to see some friends i haven't seen in a long time let's go i was
awesome all right let's keep going i gotta pee again everybody's up to pee pee before the final
two levels what do you think oh well i got you all here let me just uh go over this so uh tomorrow
we're streaming tomorrow but um i have physical therapy tomorrow so the stream tomorrow is gonna
start a little later it's not gonna start around like two three tomorrow it's gonna be probably
somewhere around uh let's see it's gonna be a late one tomorrow it's gonna start somewhere
probably around and it's gonna start probably around six p.m pacific if i'm honest i'm gonna
be honest that's really late yeah it is six p.m pacific tomorrow but uh this is the black gate
let's uh let's take a break and go pee i'll be right back should this probably be the last
p in the night i would assume i don't know two peas we'll find out okay herma smells with a burger
hey come on what am i gonna do to you betty you betty's eating baby food right now uh ding ding
ding what do we have for the winner shellwood people think i'm a liar i'm not that's just what
i do all right the black gate uh here we go there's absolutely no way i'm gonna do this
stand out my plans have ended in a day of great sacrifice gondor lies shattered in the greatest
battle of our age but the enemy regroups and our war is not yet won for the ring still survives
the last living men have witnessed the return of their king he has gone unchallenged long enough
and together we now ride upon saron's realm to create our final diversion for the ring to be
thrown into i shall give you a message for your master i will give you a magic trick for your
master i will turn into gandalf it's just like a brawl it's like germa rumble levels of
combat oh perfect oh i didn't get it i got on excellent
checkpoint hi all right wait a minute oh fight fight wait if i give me give me the boss now
i could really use some health here and be nice use it what the fuck did that do yeah no
this doesn't fucking do anything add a mana what did you run out of you can't even do anything
all right let's go i should have brought potions all right let's go come on this is gonna be like a
20 minute long mission i know i know
here we go it's too powerful i'm killing them too fast get in there all right watch it watch it big
guy big guy incoming where's everybody with the people on my own team i don't know where the
fuck are they um double team him come on eric are you is he dead okay this is getting a little
ridiculous don't you think guys let's go save gimli wherever the hell he is where's gimli
that is kill gimli no one's even attacking these people get home come here is this
help him am i healing him where where's legolas in this whole thing all right gimli's uh there he
is okay oh yeah they're good these have hurt him all right gimli where are you come here all right
let's heal gimli a little bit okay so far so good two out of six all right where's uh legolas where
are you i just mentioned your name and where the hell are you i'm just a healer all right are we
going where where there you are there you are good deal loved playing two towers two towers was a
lot there was a lot more in two towers it was not a new wave good what's the okay hold on what's
that what's a new move that i got triangle xx triangle okay i don't think i've done this yet
triangle xx triangle yeah that's dark deliverance all right i think orcure is just the best move
that gandalf has it's so fast i'm already in perfect mode that guy didn't stand a fucking
chance all right back it up anybody need heels what does that mean do i go left or right i'm
gonna go left i'm gonna go left did i did i go left what the stop what is going on
um what the hell is going on big guy fuck dude come on man what the fuck get the fuck out of here
where else over this way everybody healed up and good to go all right only two more oops it's all
right wait where's it going come on i need that guy where's he running this guy's running around
circles get over here get the fuck over here there it is health yes okay who need uh everyone
everyone what's going on here both of you healing both uh legolas legolas back over here five out
of six i don't even do anything oh fuck you're over here that's why good for you legolas there
it is i got a checkpoint right there didn't i i hope so dude can i get up i got a checkpoint
right there it's okay why couldn't i hit him i was bouncing off of him what the fuck was that
okay give me a break i don't even know what he's swinging his sword he's not even doing like you
know their weakness fire yes fire fire of course it's fire use fire fire of course it's fire
sometimes you bounce off sometimes you don't use fire holy shit these guys are worthless
compared to me oh i guess i did it this evil sorry guys i didn't realize that
my build is perfect for this sorry to steal everybody's thunder faces the final test
you invested everything into the fire tree must hold his gaze long enough
kind of unthinkable to become real for hope to conquer all from please cut the stream i have
not seen the movie it's like 110 year old spoilers at this point i'm sorry that's not on me at this
point this is like saying the dot that t rex was a fucking dinosaur at one point as this shit is
ancient history a lot of perfects all right we finally got triangle triangle triangle
helms hammer pretty sick triangle triangle triangle uh one more level
there's a lot to spend so i'm gonna save the points i wonder is this a level 10 scenario
or is the final level just mount doom i don't remember this is the end of the movie
crack of doom i have to play as level one frodo i've been playing as sam every time i had a chance
you mean i have to do level one frodo now is the final level of the game
and it's too bad he's level one seamless level one look at this i can't even fight back
get that to me i don't have any moves all right throw it in there throw it in there get in there
throw it in how did he just jump in throw it in throw it in dude go throw it push him
just sam if we push him at the same time we'll push him off all right push him push
it's just sam okay um hit him sam he's distracted push him push him push him
sam hit him all right that's what you gotta do he falls back it's scripted it's scripted
it's scripted it i'd step on his head what's what come on what i was trying to step on him
push him all right here we go why i just hit every possible button r1 circle x
okay hold on let me push him in push him push him okay
i didn't do it all right we're gonna do it like five more times all right i know i got it i got
it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got it i got to do i know
what to do just block until he falls back and okay sam get him i can't i tried to block that
all right sam let's do something good hit him there we go back him up back him up what the
fuck same deal all right come over here come on all right let's get him into the corner
back here again come on where's he going back up this way all right sam get in oh help all right
spin him around here we go now all right this way this way go go go go go go pick him back up
back up back up back up push him stab him in the head just give him the ring the whole world
ends if i do that it's not worth it all right spin around and push push him again here we go
come on fuck that push him get over the edge man you're killing me all right go on why is he
doing all these flips dude i can't make him do anything he just sits on the stage just laughs
and then all right now fucking go fall off the edge fall off the this what in the name of god
is going on right now i don't i don't why would he what the fuck what what was what the what what
what he's not standing on the edge he's just standing on the edge and he's just taunting
and i can't push i can't do anything but what i have no i can't do anything do i just have to
wait till he accidentally finds himself in the perfect spot to fall off the edge i can't push
him i can't hurt him i can't do anything oh so what happened with the other side what the fuck
jeremy you can't beat the joke character he is not the joke character all right i mean okay you
could say that golem is the jar jar binks of lord of the rings but he's like comedy and he's he's
got like he's he's like the comic relief and he's back how is golem comedy relief let me like say
weird things and they get like in little fights and stuff while they're traveling together and
he's like i don't like you and shit like that he's like a he's like a comedy character
they get in like little funny arguments like the three of them oh what my girlfriend heard
what you said and she literally got sad but that i said that golem was the comic relief character
as i compared golem to jar jar binks apologize two relationships ruined today but is it golem or
golem not this time golem it's golem right all right oh off edge what was wrong with that
this time can i throw shit at him give me this but i hear loud sticking noises back up back up
again back up back and unruly just get under the edge he's gonna do the he's gonna do the thing
come here come here come here come here come here all right back up i need health this game's plot
sucked uh take that up with uh five thousand people that now are going to be very mad at you
all right get him over there block him off block him off we gotta do like a formation here
good no no no no no between here go back don't let him all right here we go dive over here okay
turn around say him saying he was gonna do it say him block all right get him get him one more
that's it hey hey i'm getting stuck where is he where is he where is he where is he all right
get over here fall down okay you can fall now there you go last one bye do you let it go
that really wasn't that bad this is annoying the ring is destroyed and all that was done by that
power is passing away they do it those who were banned to the fate of the one are now free real
crowded now come the days of the king may they be blessed while the thrones of the valor endure
so do you think they're ever gonna do like the ring awakens do another trilogy after
secret fire of honor saron in his greed as saron mingled his own blood with the ring's gold so
did i mingle myself with my magic to live here i wove but a spell of trust and fellowship given
free but why was that yeah why is that in here it's finished that doesn't even happen in this
work of others we actually did just watch we watched all the lord of the rings on screen
we actually got to do it oh
oh
that's why they did that it was a it was a shout out for the dvd
three so i'm assuming you can build up how would you build up your perfect meter and then do the
last hit on him is that how you supposed to do that that would probably a huge pain in the ass
well let's uh go on a spending spree now i need to level 10 anybody level 10 what's the percentage
80% of what's gonna be like 85 86 who would win in a fight 1v1 golem versus jar jar
it jar jar it would absolutely be jar jar it would not be going it wouldn't be going
andy's interview will avoid interview
a lot of interviews here secret codes start press the start button press and hold all those buttons
then input the sequence uh there's no like big head mode i'm not interested at all what is this
one is this a secret level oh we can be sam frodo pippin mary or faramir these are great secret
characters i'm not gonna be able to do this with farmer no golem i what would his moves be we'll
do gandalf
and then i want to see the andy sirksey interview i shall free the minds of your servants and teach
them fear i shall render them useless to you perfect mode here we go i'm gonna have to kill 20
helms hammer uh how do i only kill one person oh it's the way it's waves okay come here come on
come on come on kind of slow but it does a lot of damage you're never gonna beat this no i
no i i don't plan on it bring it together come on lots of perfect what you still alive 2004 was a
good year yeah it was it really was whoa that's a lot of missiles can i block them all at the same
time and get it perfect and check this out ready ready here we go here we go and here we go
i thought it was gonna be way cooler than that but whatever stop what you all right you is that
really all it takes to do to get away from gandalf float backwards of two steps that's right prime was
i mean the 2000s the early 2000s like from 2000 to 2010 i mean do you talk i don't think there'll
be that rivals somewhere in the mid 90s the heyday of the super nintendo and sega genesis there was
some unbeatable games and then 64 think about the shit that came out in n64 oh man think about
the shit that came out of super nintendo in like 94 95 96 what a great what a great like
i was gonna say season he actually thinks the n64 is good um i mean super mario 64 and like
zelda games and we've got to be kidding 1064 i'm just talking about banjo kazooie yeah i think i
think you guys are messing around yeah you have to be what's banjo kazooie um i mean i don't
need should i even respond to that i feel like that's just somebody making a joke uh banjo kazooie
no i'm not responding so um i'm gonna lose here because i'm not paying attention anymore
i banned that person but not knowing what banjo kazooie is that's petty but go ahead and do it
come on one more get to seven shoot the giant egg that is it for me not even close to as hard
as two towers i played in the same difficulty too there's normal although i did get really
really really lucky at the very end of the um at elephant level easy can i get to 10 it's really
not even that bad it's actually kind of fun but i'm not gonna do it elephant level is the hardest
one yeah i got really lucky i i had one health pixel off from losing i'm doing the whole damn
thing again i'm running away that's cheap all right well that uh that you that has been you've now
seen all the lord of the rings trilogy on this stream thanks for watching did i unlock something
else what's going on oh i wanted to i want to watch the uh andy circus interview yeah this is
important what did they steal a major addict who who just needed to need yeah i compared him to
charge i think those nodding no i don't think that's correct because we're using motion capture a lot
um and the animators are watching my performance closely on screen and mapping
their animators keyframe animators are matching every expression it's called facial structure and
the way that his face moves is based on the form way mine does so it goes through three processes
i shoot on set with elijah and sean and we act all the scenes together this guy right here is
a pioneer repeating every single scene and then i do the final voice track yes precious the voice
was was really um born out of two things one was trying to find a psychological route into why he
speaks like that but actually in physical terms it it it came from i knew it we had three cats at
home and i knew it was a cat
what do they do
you know i'm getting my head back into thinking okay see you know this is great minds think alike
andy i agree all that through a game so it's actually quite nice to sort of visit where i'm
going to be going for the film it's probably you know an unusual way of doing it where you do the
do the voice for the game before you actually do the adr for the film that's kind of weird
and we be the master he did this first he had to do this first before they even did the movie
voice acting what's this one down here nothing here don't forget a perfect on every level
uh what about uh what about billy what about billy boy
thank you but not really you've just unlocked all these other characters like me one of them
being me so now you can take me and mary and anyone else to places that they didn't actually
go to like osgillia or paths of the dead yeah take pippin to paths of the dead let's see what
would happen if he went there okay let's take pippin to pippin to paths of the dead that's
pretty cool i'm just doing what the actor wanted me to do what would happen if it was in this war
it was made by those who are dead and the dead keep it the way is shut malice lies heavy in the
air the dead it's all right it's there's really no change here from behind there's no change
there's not a big difference here it's just another small guy i wonder what would happen
if if pippin were to be here the spirits of the dead pretty good actually pretty good pippin
not bad actually pippin's pretty good then no voice lines yet this should be more specters see
can pippin throw big things oh fuck he's pretty good that's not pippin yes it is
hello all right takes more than like three hits to die as level one um
why is he gonna play through this level right now does he have any lines he has to
when gimli talks he's gonna say something hey someone's saying currently reading the lord of
the rings books are you really nice star ever spoiling the whole series magic coming to the
stream and you're getting ready to read all the books and spend weeks or months reading all of
them you just watch what just happened with all of them i'm not gonna what i'm not gonna talk
about months yeah months it could take a long time to read a book especially the lord of the
rings the lord of the rings are huge you read like a chapter a night two chapters a night for
all the books it's probably take you it probably takes you fucking at least a few weeks everybody
stops fighting when i'm not here oh man i've read the books i've i just started a game of thrones i
love it should we tell them should we tell them that the the next two books are literally just
never gonna come out should we tell them i've been waiting almost 10 years for that fifth book
just want to make sure you understand that book's probably never releasing
i finished that i finished uh dance of dragons in like 2011 and it was like yeah here we go i'm
gonna know when's the winner is coming out like in a year it's been almost 10 fucking years the
book's never coming out i want to make sure you're aware that if you're gonna get into like the games
books you're gonna be with the rest of us for real soon and don't leave it to hbo like oh well
whatever i'll just watch hbo no don't do that be careful there it's uh we are trapped here
it's not tv it's hbo that's true it's pretty good yeah it became so yeah oh i don't i don't
really want to talk about gamers wrong or anything because i don't obviously don't want people that
haven't seen it or they're planning on getting interested or you know i don't want to be talking
about like well let me tell you about this part and this part of it no that's not we don't have to do
that but it's uh one of the big fans i wasn't a big fan pippen are you all right pippen you're
all right if it's dead okay uh now we know what happens pippen dies if he goes in there cool
all right let's get this one here we go mary what does mary have to say to us
very very well thank you a lot quicker than three and a half years to finish it excitement crazy
crazy excitement you've now unlocked two other characters what i have you can take mary or
pippen and you can go on any storyline you want i you could go and hang out with she loved for a
while what you could go with faramir and you know see what his journey's like that would be fun you
can hang out with gandalf because he's very protective and he feels like a father you can
do anything you want you can go anywhere you want with mary and pippen so this is now our
treat to you as a gamer mistake leave in the shire in the shire you know mary looks kind of
sweet and approachable as when he wears his war outfit he just can't think the people who would
choose all right so are mary and people mary and pippen the jar jar banks of that's more accurate
right highly intelligent people in the world no that's dead is the hobbit oh i want a sandwich
i want to have some no what are you talking about someone who you know comes to the table
that's more accurate than gauntlet physical strength but he's is wily and has a bit of
guile what about second breakfast yeah they say yeah they like kind of comic relief there are two
in c3po i don't think that's accurate either well i think we saw everything wait nope
we have one more interview with faramir was one of the few men who withstood the power of
faramir and boramir were brothers and it isn't beyond possibility that faramir went to rivendell
instead and if that happened faramir could have survived and returned to gondor you decide now
we're going to explore this fact by unlocking the character of faramir see for yourself what
else you might have done during the war at the ring good luck i mean it's i it's cool but
it's just you can just take the character you can i don't know it's for alternate time
game players should unlock faramir first because he's a character who is in possession of multi
skills he's a great swordsman great archer they actually get any different abilities or no
i think
high voltage gameplay guys it's pretty good
all right that's uh that's it
does the tree do anything though i didn't miss anything down here did i
you saw all the interviews all the production stills elijah wood on astin
game concept art film concept art hobbits on gaming this i'm glad we didn't miss this one
the best player would be elijah well this is where i get to to pat myself in the back i'm
definitely a better gamer than the two of them yes elijah has this insane ability of being able
to just uh grab hold of a console and go through a game i've actually made the the controller
float and without touching anything i've managed to play the game it's only happened a few times
but he's not even making that up it's probably real gaming now for probably years and he's doing
very well uh but i'm still a much more experienced gamer but i'm getting that i can be i wouldn't be
surprised if elijah wood could do that certainly a lot better he can do everything else he can
fucking sing he can dance he can act he can cook oh look at me go i'm on fire now he can like
lift big heavy fucking weights and shit i says okay give us a beat him three times in a row
billy's getting better but he's not great billy is awful one of the worst game players of all time
i think i do have a special gift for gaming you'll be playing a two-player game and you'll go billy
press x and he'll be like hang on a minute wait which one's x but i just haven't really opened
that gift yet and giving it to myself that was funny wait hold on no i got that one now we got
them all now we got them all all right guys i'm gonna call it here no vego interview yeah what's
going on there i guess they got him for the last one they got vego they got uh john they got did
they get orlando bloom for the last one too they were in the last one over the claw grip
did you give kim the 10 gifted fries yet no we have we actually haven't gone to any restaurant
that would even have them we just haven't we just haven't been there got a wink sure the last star
is hardcore mode but you have to probably defeat the game on heart but yeah that's a good place
to stop it we are now done with the lord of the rings for now that was good shorter than the last
one i thought we were gonna be playing this for a little bit longer but it's a good place to stop
so again tomorrow tomorrow i got uh some shit i gotta do physical therapy to do
but i'll be here after it and what game am i gonna play tomorrow what are we gonna start tomorrow
well wouldn't you love to know that's a secret only i know i think you're gonna like it nancy
no no no no lord of the rings we're putting to keep we did all three of the books well let's
be honest i've read the first 10 chapters of the first one and then we read the second and third
book that's fine not all the books oh yeah there's the there's the this is there's the
simulerian right that's it am i saying that right is that the sims currency or is that the name of
the book sim or the similar simerillian so well the simerillian is the name of the book in the
simulerian what's the sim currency what's it hold on what's the sims currency called
simoleons oh it's simoleons not simerillians all right i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll see what
we play we're gonna start again starting late tomorrow because of this we started at about
6 p.m pacific thanks for joining me i had a lot of fun it's good to play these old games and
i didn't not even a meltdown tonight i mean you might be disappointed fuck i thought he was
gonna like bite his controller tonight no not tonight but we'll do the uh bits and everything
and go from there if you take it up we'll see you tomorrow good to be back see you soon it's
the only time i get to use this music in like an outro i think it works pretty perfectly actually
all right i said i gotta clean my room too this is kind of getting ridiculous
uh is that music going is that music going can you hear that music
and music going there we go okay let me just change over here so i can actually see you what
you guys are saying all right let's go back to uh six and a half hours ago let's take a look
we had four dollars from pugil's thank you pugil say germy i recently watched elijah wood
through the google google auto complete interview with wired i don't know if you it was the withdrawals
from no streams or all the paint i've been eating but for some reason i randomly thought you and him
would get along well anyway glad you're back ps i'm gonna be getting the fireman plushie
the end of that question i have no idea i think everybody thinks they're gonna get along with
elijah wood he seems very nice he seems very approachable he seems very down to earth
i like anybody could probably get along with elijah wood he's he's got that energy to him i
agree i agree when is his game coming does he have a game coming on why is what is a game coming up
what is it really what is it elijah wood game elijah wood video game transference
is the name of the game wait wait wait wait wait really is is elijah wood making an fmv game
oh no it's vr it's like a vr fmv game when maybe not fmv that's interesting this is back in 2018 is
when they were talking about this that's cool that'd be insane actually i'm into it whenever it's
ready i would take a look no that's cool i did not know that he was doing that i look forward to
seeing it now what is fmv oh it's already wait it's out now wave is already out it came out in
2018 what is it on steam imagine an escape room set in a deranged mine experience a first-person
exploration game in a chilling new dimension shift between three perspectives of a family
and unravel the mystery hiding in this mind-bending psychological thriller it's apparently okay it's
got it's got mostly positive reviews it's got some negative reviews though apparently
somebody's the people are upset about uh ubisoft doing them let's see let's see
yeah it's apparently got some issues got some issues one of these reviews says don't buy
this game if you don't have a vr so what the non-vr version is not very good keep that in mind
is that ubisoft all right let's keep going espada escalata thanks for 250 hey germa
jav gaming here we're glad you enjoyed our videos enough to take a week off to enjoy them
more codes are on the way jav what is jav gaming what the hell is that blue pundit thanks for 300
bits i used to play this so much i love the nostalgia me too me too potion dweller thanks
for three dollars hey germa you've been gone for too long this week was painfully slow
glad to have you back yeah february is going to be a little messed up
i think it'll this is one of the busiest months in a while i've got physical therapy going which
i have to go to and i have to stick to i don't know how many times a week this will be going
i'm gonna assume it's i will assume i have to probably do physical therapy
maybe once or twice a week whenever i have to do it i'm gonna do it so i'm gonna have to bounce
streams around and try to get them in and do this too why are you doing physical therapy because i
have costochondritis and i know i don't want to gross anybody out here but um i lean back
and stretch my rib cage a little and sort of tilt and move my chest it goes and it kind of hurts
it's and then it feels okay i look for a little bit it's like just kind of popping
weird it's pretty crunchy down there so costochondritis is inflammation in your rib cage
i just i was told it would make sense because i have um the colitis problems are autoimmune
and i was told that you know it's not out of the ordinary that for somebody that has
ibd which is autoimmune which is i've had it for years that something like this could pop up too
randomly because your body my body's just stupid and for some reason wants to attack itself
because i'm my body's dumb and i got a low iq fucking dna i don't understand i have now this
is like two potential autoimmune diseases which like what the fuck but uh going on physical
therapy i've been told helps a lot and in some cases can make the problem almost completely go
away we'll see i'm gonna give it a shot uh lm man thanks for the 10 bucks germa choo choo you
deserve a chew is that a space channel 5 reference sounds like it thanks for the thousand bits
ibuprofen is good for inflammation yeah i'm gonna give you some of my personal
um personal thoughts and personal beliefs here on this subject i don't want i don't like
here all right here we go i can go get an injection tomorrow into my nerve of steroids
and nerve blocker and i it might be i might be fine but i don't really like the idea of doing
that first and i don't like the idea of taking ibuprofen every day taking ibuprofen or tylenol
every day it's not it's really not great for you and i don't want to get into the habit of taking
three or four ibuprofen a day and saying man i feel this i feel fucking great i'm just going
to take four ibuprofen every day and then you're i'm essentially masking a problem that could be
fixed maybe potentially if i just did it and i don't really want to just use painkillers
to just put a blanket over a potential actual joint problem that i have that i could just
fix it's the same reason why i don't i really don't want to go on any like prescription pain
medicine i know that that's been floated around before of oh you you have like osteochondritis so
you have like joint problems you have a joint disease oh well you're gonna take vicodin you
know just a small dose every day no no i know i'm not gonna i'm not gonna do that i'm not gonna
take i'm not gonna take i'm not gonna take one i don't want to even do that and that's what i've
told the doctor and the doctor also said that's a good idea just we'll see what happens with
physical therapy let's see what happens now in the event that physical therapy does not work
you know let's say i do physical therapy for the next four to six months and there is no progress
and if it get worse it could get worse i don't know at that point it's like okay i've done
physical therapy for six months let's do the injection and see what happens that's the plan
now it could take a couple years yeah but uh there's not a layer here and okay here's the
here's the other layer i you know i got stuff to do every day you know it's not just the stream
i want to be like on this stream and not have to even think about it i want to be able to
interact and have fun and do whatever i want to do and have it in the back of your mind that like
oh my like whole fucking rib cage hurts it's i you know i don't want to have three four years
from now like that it would get really fucking annoying and it would just sit in the back of my
head always so i mean i'm eventually here over the next six to 12 months i've got to have a
real solution for this i don't want this to turn into an issue that's i'm just sitting here and
hey guys i'm gonna go to the grocery store today oh my my fucking chest hurts but it's not an issue
that's life-threatening or that would really really debilitate me it's just annoying my rib
cage sucks that's pretty much it and i but i just really i also have to live my life too i'm not
gonna i am not taking any pain medicine i'm not doing any treatments i'm just gonna be in pain
here every day and um yeah that's what eventually i'm gonna have to do something
if something like physical therapy doesn't work but that road is very very very far in the future
don't forget to do the stuff the physical therapist tells you to do at home i'm going to be
i'm gonna follow 100 percent of the instructions no matter what they are this physical therapist
could tell me you have to eat lettuce every day for the next year i'm gonna turn fucking green
i'm gonna turn fucking green you know what i mean you don't do that already i mean i eat lettuce
i like lettuce i like romaine lettuce is bros romaine lettuce okay to eat no and they recall
every single romaine lettuce ever is this still going on january 15th 2020 outbreak of e coli
infections romaine lettuce this is still going on this is like three weeks ago i i ate romaine like
10 just keeps happening all right well instead of romaine i'll just i don't know i'll put i'll eat
i'll do spinach spinach is fucking better anyways adventure mf dan thanks for the five community
subs 15 from ampharic 10 from combat man 142 thank you appreciate kale i'm actually i don't
like kale i'm not a kale guy you put spinach and kale uh next to each other i'm gonna eat the
spinach every time every single time i don't like the consistency of kale it i don't it's like
it's like stringy almost it takes long to eat it it's like tough for me no spinach marvash mcgally
thanks for the 250 it's so good seeing you play one of my childhood games on stream i completed
this game when i was 12 you better finish this we got this in the very beginning i stopped the
stream for it uh you have no excuses okay here we go here's a prediction of your meltdowns let's
see if these were accurate prediction of your meltdowns getting trampled by an entus gandalf
okay that was um that no that did happen a couple times trying to destroy eisengard's dam no i that's
one for two here i was just confused trying to kill the king of the dead no i didn't have that
much of a problem with the king of the dead one for three trying to escape after killing the king
of the dead okay yes that counts i was that was i was not happy on that one uh the olefant level
yep all the ministerious levels and the final levels of the gates of mordor or at least these
are the levels that got me mad four for four yeah don't buy the other one right the four for four
the four dollar box whatever it is i haven't eaten wendy's in a long time being serious
eddie the penguin thanks for the five community subs in actually 10 eddie the penguin gave it
twice thanks eddie alec the bunny we had eddie the penguin and alec the bunny right next to each
other thanks for the five dollars alec germ i've been watching your stuff for a few years and
you've always entertained and cheered me up during bad days happy to hear that you enjoy being here
hope those bad hope those bad days turn into good days i hope you have more good days than bad days
it's the best you can do thank you for the five dollars a plushy bat thanks for the five dollars
my name is germa peed my pants they called me germa peed my pants because i'm germa and i've
in fact peed my pants a bunch of pogchamps sick all right thank you corn on the rob for the five
dollars 500 bits from corn on the rub germa today that marks the fourth straight year i've subbed
to you i've been watching you since 2013 i was in high school when i started watching you and now
i have a bachelor's degree hell yeah you might remember me as the kid that caught you off guard
for a selfie outside pax east 2014 you and star signed my scout poster i still have it framed
i just want to say thank you from the bottom of my heart for entertaining me for seven years
yeah happy you still think this is fun to be around this much time later did i just fart no
uh i did not what you probably just heard was otto otto is back here and he's just simply hanging
out being a good dog and having um some fun he's lying around just hanging out uh otto what's up
do you want to get out of here he's like get me out of here he's like get me out of here i'm i'll
get you out in a second just hold on i'll get you up he wants to go give me one second i'm just
gonna let the dog out hey uh let's keep going i don't want to get out of the room he was like
i'm out uh tar alecron thanks for the 251 bits thanks to 250 germa how have you not used up your
bottle of cologne in 20 years you do realize that you need to spray it on you for it to make you
smell nice right um because i don't use very much because i don't want to be the person that walks
into a room and everybody tries to find the smell because you spray yourself more you give yourself
more than one or two spritz as a cologne you turn into the person that then just drops smell in
room they go in and then everyone has everyone goes who's get somebody of cologne on who's who
is that oh it might be me yeah yeah that's you well i like that but oh yeah that's you by the
way i was in the kitchen and you were in the living room when i asked this question so i like to just
do you do a little bit you just like a tiny like just a that's it right under the neck i lift my
chin up like i put my chin up right on the deck down or if you have uh the one that's not a spray
you just take one little on your finger and right under the under the jaw like like that's it you
done you don't need very much how many sprays let's see uh how many sprays are in a bottle of cologne
735 sprays in a 50 milliliter bottle bottle so i don't wear cologne every day if i spray that once
even once a week or once every two weeks when i go out or something that's fucking 10 to 20 years
worth of cologne you don't need to use very much and sometimes and if you and by the way no that
is accurate that's very accurate because no you don't have one bottle of cologne i i have like
10 different bottles of cologne you use one for like a couple days week goes by use the next one
two weeks go by use the next one you you're always recycling colognes you don't do the same scent you
do a bunch you do like at least four or five of them to change it up who wears cologne i don't
this is my point my point is i wear cologne maybe once every like three to four weeks and i spray
one time so yes if i spray one spray a month that's 735 months what's the math there 735
divided by 12 let's see okay so i have 61 years worth of cologne that's not right what that's 60
yeah it is right okay i have 60 fucking years worth of cologne it's i don't know that's not
hard to understand you got to pass it down it's like whiskey you don't drink a bottle of nice
whiskey all in the same weekend i mean some of you guys might but fucking be careful for god's
sakes anyways where were we oh all right we're at germa sucks for five community subs thanks a lot
ancient sasquatch thanks for 250 germa thanks for the stream any chance we could have a few
details about the charity rumble like if there's any special you want to do for it or even an eta
uh there is no eta on it but it's going to happen at some point before april because the marathon
is in april so we would need to do it before then so it's going to happen before april isn't
that an eta yeah i guess it is estimated time yeah before april that's not really a time that's more
of a estimated time to end it you know what i mean that that that's like it could it could be
tomorrow or it could be march 31st that's a huge time frame yeah that's not like an eta that's a
big giant time frame call it what you will for real though thanks for the 250 i don't know if
you're aware but the vermintide devs made a rats reference i actually did see this i did see the
rats rats where the rats the vermintide to uh patch notes or something right whatever it was
news yeah yeah there is no it just the title of their uh dev update is just rats rats where the
rats they don't go into and by the way oh my god germa is so great it's just a one line actually
from i was reading a few threads about this and apparently the rats that rats movie and the rat
clip there's a clip going around that's that people know what it is but people might not know
that it's from this channel from my understanding the rats have turned into their own thing that
aren't even connected to me anymore it's just thing and whatever it's you know the student
becomes the master as they say it's just going the rats don't need you though they don't need
their they're going off to college they're gonna be their own rats they've entered meme hood yeah
that's fine whatever people can enjoy it that's why i did it that's why i said it in the first
place that's why i made the video so people could fucking think it was fun and use it and care about
it i think it was funny that was it so that good makes me happy sue them cease and desist so uh
you'd like me to cease and desist on the rats which is from a video game that i do not own
the rights to characters that were created for 3d movie maker that i don't own the property rights
for so i'm going to on behalf of me and and microsoft i don't have the i i don't have the
authority to do anything about that anthony bantony is on the case um no it's fine it doesn't
bother me if people sing the rat song what am i gonna trademark happy birthday you know what am i
i heard i heard somebody said the rat song um excuse me i i said that if i was in that person
and what am i what am i supposed to do like it's not like it's not like the vermintide devs made
money off of saying rats rats were the rats they're not selling that in the store all right if like
the vermintide two devs made a like downloadable music track that they made in house of the rat
song and they sold it for like five dollars there you go there's your opportunity at that point i
would get on the phone and be like hey what do i do about this no that's fair use that's just
that's fair use if they use yeah i'm saying if like they like uploaded my the my voice if they
just put up the rat song and have people buy it this is like a completely unbelievable fucking
not even real scenario yeah i don't i don't only fucking copyrights like this is i i wouldn't be
able to do anything he's getting upset over hypothetical lawsuits copyright that i can't
copyright the rats well i don't i can't do that that's not gonna happen making money off of your
like intellectual property you have intellectual ownership if they used your voice there would be
a case it's not case there's no cases there's no case there's no case no there's no this is not
this is not even real all right we're gonna move on like dude i think you should really like forget
it and get a lawyer at this point like dude if this is a case here no it's really cool though
a huge like eight minute uh pretend hypothetical fucking lawsuit later uh that's really cool i'm
glad that people think it's a cool meme and they think it's fun and i'm glad it's grown up
and moved on to meme college uh captain nemo thanks for the 500 bits jerma did you ever
hear the story about how christopher lee was an assassin you do christopher lee corrects peter
jackson wait what is this i gotta plug this in let me hear this you ought to see me with the 357
magnet when worm tongue rises up and comes up behind sam and to stab him um of course it was
my job as director to talk to christopher lee and to explain to him what i what i wanted so i started
to go into this long explanation about what sort of sound he should make when he got stabbed i seem
to recall that i did say to peter have you any idea of what kind of noise happens when somebody
is stabbed in the back and i said because i do what the fuck holy shit it's because the breath
is driven out of your body he proceeded to sort of talk about some very clandestine part of world
war two he used to be in the the british secret service whatever they were shit really he seemed
to have expert knowledge of exactly the sort of noise that they make and so i just sort of
didn't push the subject any further i just said well you obviously know what to do christopher
so i'm sure you'll do it great and he did that's fucking wild holy shit i didn't know that that's
that's fucking awesome don't fuck with christopher lee hold on auto uh now i don't want to come back
in he's like let me up let me in let me up let me in look at me hold on let me go get him hold on
give me a second okay he's like yeah that's what i wanted i love saying his name he's got a great
name auto show auto uh all right before the stream turns off i'll show auto i've got like
another 20 minutes hey gnarly thanks for the 250 jedi fall in order is pretty good as a souls
aficionado myself i think it's good now he he must align the pillow in here he doesn't want
it doesn't want me to pick him up he's doing the thing that dogs do and they just scratch
over and over again the same spot of a pillow or a bed there he goes pick up the pillow no
no imagine if you were lying in bed and somebody just opened the door
and picked up your fucking bed and shoved you into a camera you'd be like what the no i just
trust that would rule that would be epic oh yeah i don't think so anyways uh it's not as good as
sakiro but since you actually like star wars you might get more enjoyment out of it than me
maybe i'll play it i don't know it's been so long since we've played a new triple a game
outer wilds is the last game that was a new game it's been so long since we played a new video game
it's so slow though yeah i don't know i gotta play it off stream though i love star wars
i love lightsabers we'll see uh steve here coming at you thanks to the 265 thank you steve uh steve
is the one that warned us about the um five dollar biggie bag from wendy's said it wasn't
worth it that was steve coming out coming at you thanks thanks for the tip what am i going to eat
tonight eddie the penguin thanks for the 500 bits this stream has been dmca claimed just playing a
video game man that's all i'm doing just playing a game mavash begali thanks for the 250 okay turns
out this game is not just that hard like i remembered it 12 year old me was just bad at
video games i died like a dozen times trying to destroy the damn no these games are no joke
don't don't get yourself wrong there these games are tricky they're hard they're hard to control
they're hard to see yes these are these are tricky games they're very difficult bar broski
thanks for the 300 bits hey can you pause the movie i gotta pee uh hope you got back the movie's over
bone jackal thanks for the 500 bits germa hope you had a good week mine was pretty rough all right
hear that a group of rowdy bostonians uh this is just a made-up story a group of rowdy bostonians
came into the place i work and demanded dr peppo even after being informed we don't serve it later
the oldest member of the group jumped up his table and attempted to do the mario to impress
his friends and end up throwing up out his hip we called an ambulance and had to shut down the
strip club for the rest of the night not a fun day at all sorry to hear that sorry to hear that
bone jackal i'll thank you one ogan thanks for the 300 bits one who gan sorry thanks for the
300 bits hey germa certified vaude boy and first-time donator i've been watching your
content since middle school and now i'm in college it's so weird to think about that
it really is i'm mostly donating to tell you about a weird dream i had about you
it wasn't anything too freaky like you having sex on stream but anyway i was helping a school
throw out old textbooks and one of the textbooks was a germa 985 textbook it had outdated channel
memes and a whole chapter dedicated to explaining twitch chat also the textbook was tiny what an
odd book that book would not be very big the germa 985 textbook of what would okay the germa
985 textbook would be like a 30 page forward from me and then eight pages of actual content and 14
full page ads uh thank you noca for the 300 bits nice to have you back germa hope your break was
good it was good it's good to be back good to be back full page yeah a full page uh sent ad
remember there's a whole wiki for you yeah i don't know i've i've been showing it before
with samples oh yeah that's right they do the samples god about that hey mark melter thanks
for the 250 you mentioned fallen order earlier while i haven't played it i do recommend looking
into older star wars games public commando is an underplayed fps classic the jedi night series or
force unleashed both have some good lightsaber stuff in there for you you can never go wrong
with playing 2005 battlefront 2 personally older cult classics make for more fun streams compared
to hot triple a titles that are mostly cut scenes keep on standing out yeah i mean i don't really
play the old games to necessarily try to do something different i just remember these being
crazy and fun and ridiculous i remember playing a lot of these and when we get on a string of
oh yeah i went and i grabbed 10 ps2 games that i remember playing that was i thought were crazy
i get to kind of relive it which is interesting too for me it's not that i'm trying to avoid
big new triple a titles it's just nothing's come out that's really
want grabbed my attention and made me want to play it for more than a minute
there's been some indie stuff you know those small not triple a budget games that we played on this
channel over the last year the phantom menace game is really bad but i love it yeah i remember
some of those i'm a bounty hunter was pretty fun outer wilds is amazing yeah but that's not a
necessarily a triple a experience i don't know if one comes along and i think it's
worth playing i'll do it or worth streaming is a better way to put that i agree atro locks atrox
thanks for the 250 uh yellow well this guy thinks he's a tolkien fan tolkien fan i haven't seen the
movies in a long time it's been a while awesome alec thanks for the eight dollars awesome alec
um i don't know what this message is it's it's pre gay craig xxf
extra druid dudes just like sex sex a si whatever it's just in then a bunch of like clown emotes
just pornography or something storm gc 10 1500 bits big brain gameplay i got a pretty big brain
porn codes thank you storm appreciate it apple shift thanks to 250 thanks to the 250 bits hey
man my household's been pretty nightmarish recently it's been non-stop fighting and
screaming basically it sucks to some degree but it's escalated a lot these past few months
your streams and videos are my go-to when it comes to drowning it out the best i can
thank you again for being such a comforting voice to turn to you always are especially now
have a good one man hope you had a nice break we missed you i'm sorry to hear that that does not
sound like a good time at all i'm not sure how old you are but that does not sound like an
environment that you would want to be in i don't know the story here or why or what's going on
but stay safe hopefully you can get out of that scenario in that environment sooner rather than
later thanks for hanging out here though we absolutely welcome anybody especially anyone
that's trying just to get away from something but i will implore you this stream is a good
place to hang out but i do want to make it really clear that if you're having some kind of issue or
some kind of problem i hope you can find the necessary steps to solve it and start to go down
the road to fix it or at least try to because this stream can only be here to be a stream
and i know that does a lot for people but i really hope that you can also
take the steps necessary to try to get better or try to fix your scenario because this stream
can only do so much i wish you all the best stay safe hopefully you can take care of this
scenario we also had a bunch of community subs right uh there's been a bunch of community subs
10 from sculpert 10 from storm taff five from gore five from great canadian fk club
nice stream loser laughing my ass off i'm gonna go get high uh eat dust nice speaking of storm
thank you storm gc for the 500 bits no message just five dollars thank you peaceful hailey thanks
to the 250 yo germa how was your time away i hope all is well while you were away i streamed and
surprisingly like over 20 germa mites came we all had a good time be careful germa i may steal all
your viewers they're mine nobody can have them nobody they're all mine no one can have one not
even one thanks for the 250 though appreciate hey thank you hailey glad to hear it 3d compact
streamer doesn't like competition hey royal da we royal da we thanks for the thousand bits 10
dollars germa whenever you play an older obscure game that i really liked you seem to have a bad
experience with it all the lord of the rings games mountain blade warband halo reach i would like to
apologize as i feel i've cursed you to have a bad time with any game that i like what's matter oh
uh kim's home now he wants to get out he's like that's kim you want to get out yeah okay
okay yes all right okay i'll let you kim just got him all right watch out huh right okay
there he goes he's running down to see mama uh let's keep going but what we have is royal uh
don't we i would like to apologize i feel like cursed you to have a bad time with any game that
i like i didn't i don't have a bad time with these games a mountain blade war band it was
i think it was just overwhelming to me hey okay hold on let me i gotta i gotta rebuttal some of
these for you uh the lord of the rings games are just old and very very difficult just by their
nature so i'm gonna i'm gonna get frustrated at some points it's i mean doesn't mean i don't like
the game uh mountain blade war band overwhelmed me and uh i believe people in chat were calling me
like a stupid and an idiot and that i smelled and that my stream sucked uh so that was that one uh
i mean it was overwhelming a little bit halo reach was the worst stream of the year last year
because me and joel played it so i mean this is i didn't not hate these games
but i mean it's not like i would never mountain blade war band is just kind of not a game for me
it's a lot it's a kind of lot going on you have to pay attention to a ton of stuff at the same time
this it's like kind of like moving pieces on a big game board chat i you know that's kind of
just not my thing it's really really interesting and i i do love that people love that series
joel ruined halo no it really did i'm uh the honesty is the best policy let's use it here
i mean they like ruined all halo for me like all of halo not that stream but just that the idea of
that gap was that ruined every halo game i can't play halo ever again it has nothing to do with
it has nothing to do with joe it has nothing to do with joe he didn't do anything out of the
ordinary it's just like that stream i just like i can never play halo ever again it has nothing
to do with joe god damn it joe ps you should play warhammer 40k dawn of war one that's literally
my favorite rts ever made so you can have another ruined perception of one another one of my favorite
games of dawn of war one is my the tau was my favorite um that's one of my favorite games
that's my favorite rts ever that's probably the best rts i've ever played so how many
hold on call me out on this um oh fuck this is why i just i talk too much i talk too much too
often and i say this all up a lot of it what is he how many literally favorite rts's do i have
how many times have i said it we talked about rts's and i i literally tell you my favorite rts ever
and apparently i've said it like three or four different games three happened like three times
just got here who's joe you don't know johnny no no joe oh sorry got to put that there was an elder
took me a while to say it but no i i love i love that game you might see that game eventually
eventually not anytime soon thanks a lot for the thousand bits hey p flavor pif flavor hopefully
i'm saying that right thanks to the five dolls hey germa hope you you can say my name right this
time and hope you have had a good 40 days so far of 2020 here's your germa tax hope i got it right
i got it right let's put the uh we have a second here let's do the uh subs credits move away from
this one we'll go to that one theater is now empty thanks for coming and watch your step on the way
out let's run the credits it's been about a week and a half since we ran the credits thank you all
for your support even in my extended absence a shitload of people still stay sub to this channel
i even though i haven't even streamed so thanks for that all of you and this is what i'm talking
about i'm back in hundreds of fucking people so and thousands of you have stayed so even though
i haven't even streamed once in february until now essentially thanks guys anyways let's let's
keep going we still have a little bit more bits to go maybe like another five or six of them
uh darah dofok darah dofok thanks for the thousand bits 10 bucks appreciate it germa long time watch
your first time donator i've been wondering what do you eat to get your garlic honey intake
i don't know too so i want to know so i can too never age i love you streams even though i cannot
join in live for many of them i would donate more and sub to the channel but i'm only a mere
poor college boy don't worry about that keep your money save it use it for something good for you
take care of yourself first always but uh how do you get the garlic and honey um it's water too
drink a bunch of water always be drinking water over the course of the day try to get you know
cut out uh replace like three or four drinks a day that you drink normally with water helps also
stay away from cheese start cutting cheese out of your life i know that's hard and it's horrible
for me to say okay uh let me go over what just happened there um i started to almost choke on
the air that i was breathing and i had to make that noise otherwise i would have choked on air
okay just start stay away from cheese don't eat that much cheese drink more water try to eat at
least one vegetable group a day cheese is good but just don't do don't eat too much cheese that's
advice from the 1950s um eat less cheese increase your garlic intake and drink water is that's just
like hey you want to be a healthy motherfucker or not uh dr house even says don't eat cheese
dr greg house and that was a tv show is a really popular tv show and tv doesn't lie to you everything
you see on tv is it's true even tv shows every episode of every episode of that's so raven you've
ever seen happened in real life uh but yeah just drink more water water helps and moisturize god
damn it moisturize moisturize you know how many people don't moisturize when you get out of the
shower get a nice facial moisturizer and just put a small layer on and rub it in moisturize some of
you guys are dry get you gotta get some you gotta moisturize man king of the skincare says the sludge
streamer no you gotta moisturize right and yeah i'm a sludge streamer because i'm under these heat
lamps for like eight hours of course i'm going to be sludgy wow what do you want me to do i have
these like mcdonald's heat lamps pointing down at me to keep me fucking warm and happy anyways uh
thank you ebb bony for the 300 bits they say woo appreciate it sir canine thanks for the five
dollars very cool video i thought you might get a laugh out of and i love laughing but i don't click
links unless i click them first yes good thing i did i don't click links unless i click them first
and you want to know why because of uh links like the one you just gave me
that's i knew i knew what it was just proving it to you i don't click links until i click them first
pretty cool video hey chris bach thank you chris bach for the 600 bits okay germa thank god
why does everything have to come down to the last second with you what do you mean um i'm sorry if
there's a timer or if there's a period of time where i may allow to accomplish something it's
still i still accomplished it in that time that i needed to oh no the last second you did it no i
i did it in the allocated time that i needed to that's what happened worst noise 2020 why
is
holy shit holy shit holy shit that was it okay that was 30 seconds long holy fuck
okay you know do you guys know in futurama what's his name uh morris um
morris lamarche does this voice in futurama as it's an alien scream thing what is this
hold on wait wait wait the the the monster voice that that morris lamarche does
what does this exist
why does everybody make this video
oh no do this no it's a futurama thing hold on do you guys know what i'm talking about
it's this like i can't do it it's crazy he's incredibly talented what where is it
futurama alien like scream hold on i'll get it no not so i've worked on so that's that's billy west
oh he can do this thing not bender no no no no ah shit i need to find this here it is here
otherworldly sounds that he does i've heard you do some of the uh sound effects specifically
the belches for wacko thank you
okay
now you know the thing i'm talking about
drop it and go okay so now that you know what i'm talking about here it is
okay music back on oh that clip is on the internet forever and that's uh just the way it is
this is the worst stream on earth wait this one or or or like this channel sorry you missed
lord of the rings we've watched all three of the movies why does it have to be just earth
can't be more than earth this on this website anyways uh bulbous wag thanks bulbous wag desu
for the 500 bits i'm officially back from my vacation in japan but while i was there at night
i listened to your old tf2 commentary videos to sleep to i'm an old fan but i was wondering
if you could give us another hey what's going on everybody in that tone you had i've been feeling
nostalgic sure hey what's going on everybody germa here with the team fortress 2 gameplay commentary
and tonight let me rewind the clock a little bit and talking about the
and he'll never do that again ever thank you hey dove the bird thanks for a thousand bits 10 bucks
hope this helps pay off the lawsuits for using the copyrighted content i'll be all right i'm not
gonna get in trouble thanks though uh dove the bird another thousand bits 10 bucks from dove the
bird you're honestly a god gamer this game helped uh this game has helped me clearly see that now
yeah i knew that sometimes it comes out but yeah appreciate it uh pockets thanks for the five
dollars pockets hey germa i had to put down my cat last friday it's been a rough week sorry to hear
that that sucks but i came home that night and watched you play tony hawk and it took my mind
off everything just a little bit i want to say thanks for that and the streams and vids that
have been a source of comfort since 2012 wish i could give more hope your pt goes well i'm
thinking good thoughts for you thank you i hope so too sorry to hear about your cat
remember the good times you had thank you pockets and you've been around for a long time thanks for
watching for that long wish you the best uh almost at the end here we only have a few more we're
going to transition to the actual actual end of the stream thanks for watching guys we'll see
you tomorrow show on i'll show auto don't worry i'll show auto uh dog go good boy thanks for a
thousand bits a song of ice and fire being mentioned reminded me that even when we get
winds of winter roy dotrice won't be narrating it which is the most disappointing thing to me
about the whole thing hopefully someone can fill his shoes yes that's true the audiobooks by roy
dotrice were the best way i think at some point to experience those books they had somebody do
um he did what he did like three of them right somebody else came in and did feast of crows like
that he was awesome he did all the voices his narration was unbelievable yeah if we even ever
even fucking get wins a winner i don't even know it's gonna i think it's gonna happen i don't think
it's gonna happen all right put me on the list of people that i don't think it's gonna happen
i don't i don't think we're gonna get wins a winner i don't think so but anyways yeah thanks
a lot for the 10 bucks gold ruby production thank you gold ruby thanks the 250 germ this
month marks one whole year that i've been a part of the germa community in february of last year
was the very first stream i tuned into it was the meme funeral skit it only took me about 30
seconds to decide that i definitely didn't want to miss another stream again now it feels like i was
always here that there was never a day that i didn't have your streams in my life thank you
in chat for all the great laughs so far i love you chat comes up with just as many interesting
things sometimes more so than i could you guys collectively come up with some of the fucking
funniest shit i've ever seen or i mean that i look over i look over and just laugh at some of the
wild shit you guys write makes me laugh thank you thanks for checking the channel out when you did
and hopefully you stick around crack chat no they weren't crack chat tonight uh home homey lizard
thanks for the 300 bits germa have you heard momentary bliss yet what are your thoughts i
have not actually have not had a chance to do that i'll have to do that tonight that's the new
gorilla song right is that that's what you're referring to yeah it is all right i'm i don't
want to listen to it i have to literally put headphones on and just like close my eyes and
lean back in my chair and then listen to it like one more time but i have not heard it yet i'll
give you my thoughts i'm gonna do future gamer thanks for the 250 if you want to stream dawn of
war consider playing the ultimate apocalypse mod it adds a bunch of new factions hundreds of new
units map-sized titans and more i feel like i loved the original so much that i might not want
to do any mods maybe maybe maybe we'll give it a try oh fucks thanks for the 300 bits hello i hope
you're having a great night and that physical therapy works well i thought i was a new addition
to the community but yesterday i found out i watched your tf2 videos back in middle school
i'm now in college working on getting a biological sciences degree
oh yeah i've been having a hard time in school and at home recently and your streams in this
community have been helping me stay positive thanks for the laughs hope you feel better soon
biological sciences there's some there's some smart you have some smart cookies in here
there's some smart people in here biological sciences engineers pilots doctors a bunch of
fucking scientists hope you get through the hard times here if it has to do with school i know
school can be especially college can be pretty daunting sometimes just take it slow do what you
can and just do your best that's all you can do storm gc thanks for the five community subs
storm gave a shitload of subs tonight so thank you storm and then finally we have goo berry juice for
300 bits and j bong for 250 goo berry juice says oh hi yo yo some mass
i don't know what am i saying i was wondering if you could show off your amazing pronunciation
skills and just say these few words for me no i no no no no no no no i don't i don't i don't
okay is he's bad at least he's not bad words all right
just so you know if you mess any of these up even slightly in pronunciation
i will be drafted into world war three i probably should have read that part
that being said i know you'll do great thanks again well band show auto real quick j bong
thanks in 250 hey germa glad you're back i recently had to let my dog go due to complications with
her health sorry to hear that she was my best friend for 10 years given unconditional love
all the time it's hard to see the spot she used to occupy in the house and not tear up glad you're
back man your streams really help give me a boost missing you all the time bella oh my god oh they're
adorable this picture in particular is fucking fantastic hold on it's a wink it's so beautiful
that's tough though i've talked about the losing animals and being separated from animals before
and the way that i've dealt with it each time is you give yourself some time to grieve about it and
sort of try to remember but move on and then take care of another one take care of another animal
bring another animal into your life dog cat rabbit lizard don't matter keep the love going
on somebody else that wants a home right somebody else that wants to be your friend
hey look at this look at that amazing so cute sorry to hear about that thank you for sharing
that and good luck thanks for the 250 and finally we had 500 bits from allison j
the runescape pie vomiting sound is the worst sound you'll ever hear look up vomiting quest on
youtube and it starts out about halfway in what is a vomiting quest on runescape why oh my god
fucking ridiculous that's fucking insane this looks already okay all right that's enough
see you guys tomorrow goodbye holy shit it's unbelievably awful hold on i'm going to turn
off the audio for this and i can hear it myself warning it says hold on there's a warning in the
runescape text this says warning where's the warning i just missed the warning i don't care
i i just turned off the sound yeah i'm not loud i don't care all right see you guys tomorrow
remember 6 p.m pacific we're starting really late tomorrow because uh doing physical therapy pt
it's easier to say that way i know i know i know auto i know i know i know auto i know i know auto
let me see hold on i that's not auto that's not auto that's blue hold on just wait a second
oh no it's not even in the room anymore auto he went remember kim came and he left he's not
he's downstairs and i i'm i'll see you tomorrow auto's not even in the room he went downstairs
to go see kit remember i let him out okay we'll show him tomorrow i promise goodbye was there any
winks why i don't turn the camera on to say bye okay all right bye see you tomorrow get some sleep
good night