Now what, build the mannequin? Build the mannequin.
Alright, well the head, the octopus head definitely goes on the head.
That's very painfully obvious. Okay.
So what is the banana, is the banana my like dick?
What's the banana for?
Alright, the suit goes on here. Suit obviously, okay.
So what's the banana? Get out of the way, chair.
Get out of my, get out of my way, my god.
Here, take it. Oh. Okay, I was wrong.
I did it, mannequin complete.
I am the victor of the game.
Well now what, did I beat it? Did I beat octopus father?
Oh my god.
Why is my house on fire?
What is going on? Did this guy burn my house down?
Oh my god, what about my family?
What about my like kids and my wife?
I am not concerned about climbing this ladder as much as my like sleeping daughter that's like burning in a fire right now.
Yeah, see, I climbed your stupid ladder.
Get over here. I did it.
Now can I go save my family? That's in, whoa.
Gotta secure a grip on my face.
I don't know.
I got away, I'm good. I'm good like that.
You will be dead from sushi. I said that completely wrong. That was embarrassing.
Oh damn.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's the mannequin.
Isn't the house on fire still?
I don't understand. What happened to the house burning?
The house was legitimately just on fire and it's just not anymore. Okay, whatever.
So now what?
I don't understand what I'm supposed to do.
I don't understand.
Just gonna climb up this place.
Something tells me this is not supposed to be happening right now.
I don't think I'm supposed to be doing this.
I'm pretty sure I'm not supposed to be glitched into the wall.
And like sliding up.
I'm like one of those chairs that climbs down.
I can't even make the joke. This is too weird.
Get me. What's happening to me?
Seriously, what the f...
Get up the stairs.
I'm gonna have to restart the game.
Where's my left leg?
Oh, whoa.
Oh, hold on.
You can see my left leg.
I can see my right leg.
Whoa. Whoa.
Oh, hold on.
So you can actually slip on the banana peels?
Oh, whoops-a-daisy.
Oh, let's take a joke from like an 80s cartoon.
Whoa, look out. Is that a banana peel right there?
Whoa.
What the hell do I even do now?
Did I beat the game?
It didn't say like I beat the game.
It was like, oh, hooray.
You saved us from burning.
Bye.
Can I play pool?
I thought I think I can actually play pool.
Oh, hell yeah.
Let's go.
Let's play this pool game.
Come on, you...
No.
No, I'm gonna get a scratch.
I just scratched.
I'm really good at pool.
Yeah.
Well, I didn't want to do that.
I wanted to throw it.
That's why I said yeah.
Yeah.
Are you kidding me right now?
I'm knocking these things over.
This is how we play pool.
As a real man.
I'm like stomping grapes.
Anyone want some pool wine?
Wait a second.
Wait just one second.
This is a shovel.
Why would there just be a shovel right here?
Hold on.
Am I about to dig up this dead body that's down here?
It works.
Hold on.
Oh, my God.
This guy's dead corpse is gonna be down here, I think.
The real father.
Oh, that would be so crazy.
There's bananas.
Is this octodad or octodog?
Because who buries this many things?
Like, what the hell?
Half octopus, half dog.
Oh, I want to bury my toys.
Wait a second.
Get that out of here.
Get the fuck out of here.
That's a key.
Give me that.
What?
Is this like a giant like prop key or is that like a real key?
Pick it up.
What?
Pick the fucking key up.
Yes.
You found a key.
The key can be used to open doors of various lengths.
Okay, I've got to say this right now.
I've been walking around aimlessly with this key in my fucking hand.
In my fucking hand for like 30 minutes.
And you're telling me I'm looking at a keyhole right over there.
You see that?
You guys see this right here?
This is going to open this door.
Please come on.
Please tell me I was right.
Please tell me I...
What is this?
Open.
Open with your legs.
Does that not do anything?
Come on.
Open.
Yes.
What the...
Where the hell am I?
I'm in like an underground facility.
What is this?
And why is the chef back?
I am so confused right now.
It's not even funny.
I saw a panel over here.
Can I like open the panel?
I have to be able to open this panel.
It's the only thing I can do.
That was very easy.
Okay.
So what is it?
Is this like my like secret superhuman lair?
Well, I see big red button.
That usually means press.
Press the big red button.
Okay.
No.
Yes.
To the moon.
We are going to the stars.
Look at that.
Okay.
I got to beat this.
Push it open.
Push it.
Push the button open.
Push the button.
Go.
Come on.
It's a race.
I made it.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't get electrocuted.
What is going on?
What the...
All right.
I can beat this.
I can do this.
Go.
No.
Come on.
These don't turn off.
I have to step over these?
Are you serious?
Nice and easy.
Look at my bar on the top left.
Holy shit.
This is going to be so difficult to do this.
I got to get really close.
Fuck.
I just thought of a brilliant idea.
Let's see if it works.
It worked, but I'm so tired.
Oh, I'm dead.
You got me with your lasers.
Oh, I'm doing that on purpose.
All right.
So guys, remember, if you're looking for a technique to beat that really difficult part,
just like screw through it.
Who cares?
Oh, there's a zip line.
Oh, this is going to be so dumb.
Are you guys ready for how dumb this is really going to be?
Here we go.
Yay.
That was fun.
Oh, God.
I would play a game where you just did that.
That was like the funnest part of this whole game.
Oh, what?
Another laser room?
Oh, another laser room of, you know, fucking whole room.
Go.
Yes.
I am the laser room master.
Can I pick up one of these rocks?
No, no, those aren't rocks.
Those are like whistles.
Give me one of the whistles.
I got to coach my little league team.
I've got to be pretty close to being at the end here.
Okay.
There we are.
Elevator.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, whoa, dude.
What the fuck is going on?
I...
What the...
Well, the technique always works.
Fuck.
Fucking God damn it.
I don't want to...
I had this beat, dude.
I had this beat and the game like fucked up.
Great.
Why did it work the first time?
And I can't get it to work again.
You got to be kidding me.
All right.
There's that.
I actually have to like do it the right way.
How do I crouch?
Crouch, huh?
There's no way I can crouch.
Oh my God.
Just go through it, you stupid prick.
God.
All right.
Can I not like glitch into the wall this time?
It took me long enough to get back here again.
Thank you.
My God.
There's a present.
All right.
What do I touch?
How about the present?
Present looks promising.
If I could put...
Why am I backwards?
Why can I not pick up the present?
Oh.
I get it.
Okay.
I did it.
All right.
So that's beating Octodad.
Oh, I beat Octodad.
Thanks for playing.
All right.
What about the roses?
I can do anything with the roses?
Kind of.
All right.
Well, thank you guys for watching this Octodad playthrough.
Beginning to end sort of with edits in between.
Here's a flower for you because I love you.
Let me bring it to you.
Everybody watching right now.
Here's a flower for you.