What do you want to do? You want to go out there? Are you sure you want to go out there right now?
All right, how about this? We're we're all going out there. Curtin, get out of the way.
Fun in the sun, baby. Haven't seen sunshine in like three days. Oh, this is gonna be fun.
You want to go outside and play? You want to put the bun on your fat body?
The bun that like can't even go across your whole body because you're too fat?
Yeah, I got my hat. Yeah, you can't, well you can't be talking out here with me.
What? I just walked into the door. Why did you do that?
I kind of look like a dickhead right now too. Look at this. Come on, let's go. Come on, boo boo.
All right, can I be completely honest here? It's so bright out right now because the sun is shining
on the snow. There's laser beams shooting into my eyes. That's like how bright it is right now.
I don't need all these clothes. I can't even see anything going on on the camera right now.
I do not need all these clothes on. I probably look like such a dipshit to all the neighbors.
I could be out here in a sweatshirt. Like I'm ready to go like in the snow.
God, I look like an idiot. Otto, Otto, I like this little path I got for you.
Oh, look at this. This is so like hopeless. Oh no. Come on, Otto. You can do it. Come to me.
All right, well while you do that, let's see how boo boo's doing over there.
Hey, boo boo. You almost made it. Otto. Oh, come on. Oh, you can make it. I'm so overdressed right now.
Hey, boo boo. All right, I want to show you guys something because this is like,
this, dogs for some reason are obsessed with snowballs. For instance, ready, watch my dog.
Watch how crazy he gets when he finds out that I have a snowball in my hand. Ready? Look at this.
Oh, yeah. Oh, look. They love them. Oh, now he's like, wait, what happened to the magic ball? Oh,
jeez. What are you doing? What the hell was that? What, dude, why did it, did somebody just light
like a match under your ass? Like what the hell were you doing? Little Otto. All right, we're
going to play catch the snowball in your mouth. I figured it was going to be freezing. It's like,
it's like 70 degrees out right now. Some blizzard. No, this is like the day after. So a lot of the
snow has started to melt already, but I wanted to get out here. I wanted to do some like dog tricks.
We're going to do it right now. Dog tricks. Who wants to catch a snowball? Do you want one boo boo?
Here. Ready? Yay. See how crazy he just got? He just like almost tried to bite this out of my hand.
I told you when dogs see a snowball, they go nuts. Try it on your dog. If you've got a dog,
make a snowball. He won't even care until you go like this. That's pretty cool. So again,
ready? Watch this. Hey boo boo, boo boo. Look at, I got like nothing in my hand. Hey, ready? Crazy.
He's crazy now. Now he's insane. All right. You know what? I'm just going to go do like a front
flip into the snow right now. Hey, don't try this at home. Go get hurt. Oh, somebody help me. He's,
please. He needs your help from the two dogs. Oh, I'm sorry. I just made you do that.
Are you all right? He's stuck. Just get out of here. See you guys later. Don't do that at home.
You'll die instantly. Crazy.