Oh hello, how are you? Alright, currently in the middle of a game. We've got a big thing going
on here today, but real quick before we get started. Really quickly. Hold on, I'm hearing
two things in my ear at the same time. We're doing Midnight Ghost Hunt with a huge group.
Let me go over and do this real quick though. I know Shito is supposed to be on camera. Let's
go ahead and do that real quick. One sec. Okay, so here you go. Here we go. You guys ready?
It doesn't have batteries.
Alright, I ate it. Alright, we're gonna play it again. I don't know why there's no batteries
every time. Alright, I gotta get into the game. Welcome everybody. We're playing. There's no facecam
today. Turn it off. Alright, here we go. I'm currently live right now. I just want to let
everybody know that there is a live audience watching you right now. Hi. Okay, so we...
What's the... Oh, I'm not talking to them. Why am I doing zero damage? I have to hold the button
down. What? I will kill you. Can somebody give like a quick 15 second like how this game works?
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This proximity, I can hear you. I have to find out where you are.
Where are you? Stunning. I have no idea what's going on. Oh, I tabbed out and I died, I think.
What do you mean no audio? There's audio. You can hear that. How do you guys not hear that? Turn it up.
I gotta hit you, dude. What was that? You can hear that just fine. Can you hear me right now?
I can hear you, yeah. Okay, okay, cool. I think I died. You guys can resuscitate me if you guys
get the defibrillator thing. Sorry, yeah, I got distracted by several ghosts running around.
Yeah, I alt tab to start capture and... You got murdered? I got murdered. Okay, I got you.
This game is fun. Yeah, I'm liking it so far. All right. Oh, you're all screwed. Killer plant behind
you. Holy shit. Oh, I'm back. I got guy behind, guy behind. I don't know what I'm doing. I'm knocked
out. Neither do I. Am I shooting teammates? What's happening?
I don't have time, Ross. I'm sorry. No, you're all good, man. Okay, are we good?
Yeah. Good try. That's better. Okay, all right. That was a cool little warmup.
It's all right. Yeah. Now I understand how the game works. All right, so we got Vinny,
we got Criken, we got Ross, we got other people. I'm gonna end this lobby, hop back into the call,
we'll get started, and then we'll hop into a new one. Sounds good. Okay, sounds good. All right,
so that was the warmup. We're just gonna be doing a little introduction here. This is not Elden Ring.
No, it's not. Okay, so we had to jump into a little lobby. Remember, you're streaming. Oh,
yeah. Oh, I want to go over quickly. Really quickly. Uh, quick before I have to get in the
server. Oh, right. So tomorrow, the idea was I was gonna do DOS games tomorrow. We're changing that.
Wrestling Empire got a huge update, and we're gonna play it. I want a little bit more time
to curate the DOS stuff. We'll do DOS this weekend. Wrestling Empire tomorrow. There apparently was
an unbelievably hilarious update. I have to play it, so that's what we're doing tomorrow.
Are we using the same, uh, let me just confirm. Same code? So this game is kind of like Prop Hunt,
but it's like Left 4 Dead and Prop Hunt combined. Seems like fun. I did the tutorial. We're just
trying to do audio testing to make sure it works. This game sucks. I have eight minutes in the game.
Can we relax for a second, please? Can we just relax for a moment, please?
And you've seen, you've seen like us audio testing.
Okay, let me check. Is this the same code? I think we're doing a different code.
Why are you so tense? I'm good. This game is worse than Elden Ring. Well, not every game can be Elden
Ring. I'm sorry. Got a new code. Yeah, I, this is, I was gonna just wait to stream tomorrow,
but yeah, we're here. Good to see, uh, this group again. Vinny, Kraikin, these guys. It's been a
long time since I played with Kraikin. Or Vinny. Or Ross. It's been a while. All right, here we go.
I like how the game actually has like a lobby system though. So we don't have to have like
10 people at each other on Steam, which can always kind of be a pain in the ass.
Did that work? It worked. Okay. All right. You guys ready? How come you're so tense?
I'm a tense person. I went in for a massage like the other day and the person could not need.
They couldn't. It was like a brick. They were like, all right, that's like funny. Take off
like the cement jacket. And I was like, what are you talking about? My mic is off? What?
No, we're good. I just want to make sure that the lobby code's not here. It's not. All right. I can,
I can put it up. Can you hear me? I feel like that's been the whole stream so far for like the
first 10 minutes. It's like, Hey dude, can you hear me? Can you hear me? All right. So I'm on
the hunter team. The, our goal is to hunt the ghosts, just like prop hunt. People can hide in
chairs and, and curtains and all that shit. He's too tense. No, I'm, I'm, I'm a very tense person.
You're my favorite. Thank you. This seems fun. It does seem fun. Let's try it. I'm waiting for
players. So it looks like this, what do we got on this team? Vinnie, Liam, she says, I'm sorry.
Cricut. All right. So we're all right. This is a good team. This is a good team. Let's just start
doing yoga. No, yo yoga freaks me out because I get, I get even more tense in yoga because I
know I can't do the moves and I, it's embarrassing. It's like, Oh, put your leg over here and put your
head over this way and like raise your arm and leg up. And I can't do it. And I just ended up sitting
on the, on the pad like this until the next move. I just like, I don't want to do it. I can do the
really easy ones. Why would I even pay to do yoga with like a yoga instructor? If there's three moves
that I can do, I could just do those here and save whatever X amount of dollars it is to go
to yoga. You're inflexible. Well, yeah. The last like two or three years, you know, spamming
resident sleepers. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right. So I want to use, I don't have
any money, so it doesn't matter. Vacuum. Once a ghost is dead, you suck them up. I'll just start.
I'm just going to go with whatever I need. All right. Let's do it. All right. What do you say?
We say guys, there's nobody here. Oh, hello. Ready to catch some ghost. Hi team. We're,
I think we're only doing C. Sorry. This is Q. Yeah. Oh, you too. You can do load out and then
you come in. Yeah. Is that DMCA? I'm scared. Oh, was that? No, no, no. I don't think this is
DMCA. I'm sure it's fine. No, yes, it is. Yes, it is. Yes, it is. Okay. Audio jungle. It is?
No, I'm just messing around. This reminds me of the DMC five van. What is going on? Yeah. Then
where is the beeping? Uh, no, not. Oh, so drama. Do you remember the beeping when we last hunted
ghosts? I do. What did you figure out what it was? Yeah, it was a, it's a faulty headset that I ended
up EQing out. It's a long story, but it is, but you actually had a broken headset. My VR headset
was broken and came with bleeps. That was, that's weird that it did. You would, you're echoing now.
That was weird. In proximity. We're all like, I think it's ambiance. Every time you turn your
head, I stopped being able to hear you well. Like it's just, that's, we have to face each other
when we talk. Yeah, we have to face each other. Look at me in the eye. Does anyone of you spin
while holding down a note? We have to make eye contact. All right, let's do this. Let, let us,
let us hunt well. We have to be so close. Let us hunt fiercely. Yeah. All right. It's the rep.
Use, uh, remember your buddy system. It's the Tyrannosaurus. It's the deer. So wait, is there a,
should we not shoot anything? Should we, is there a downfall to do that? There doesn't seem to be a
penalty to, you know, we can, we can hit whatever we want. Like I'm going to hit Jupiter right now
because fuck Jupiter. There might be a planet. Is there a ghost in here? There's definitely a ghost.
If you are a ghost, say hi. Uh, guys, I don't think they're fucking in here. I was doing,
I was doing global. We agreed. We're going to do only global to start. And if it sucks,
we don't do it anymore. Oh, okay. I get you. I've been doing proximity the whole time.
Okay. Let's, yeah. Well, I'm sorry. Yes. Proximity we'll be doing. Yes. I think it's more fun.
That's in a weird space. That's in a weird place right there. Oh, where'd he go? Where'd he go?
What was it? What was it? I don't know, but it was, it was this thing. He's gone.
There's another duck. Yo, I just like duck. No. Whoa. Whoa. Did I not have shot the duck?
What happened? Was that, was it a ghost? I think that's a glitch, but okay. That's a video game
ghost technically. Yeah. This, I can't wait to be the ghost. Oh shit. Uh, uh, I'm going to go down a
ground floor. Oh, I think Vinny. Where are they? I think they're reading in this room.
Oh, that's right. We have a, uh, a reader. I forgot about that. How do you pull up the reader?
Uh, you gotta have it in your inventory and it's pressing number two on the, oh shit. Okay.
Oh, I thought that was just a bug. Oh, what was it? Oh, there's somebody right here. It was,
it was fucking Ross. Ross ghost. What? What? Why is he standing still? I got a vacuum here.
Okay. Great. Nice. Why would you just stand in there? Did he DC? I think he's, he didn't know.
I heard him though. See, since we're all doing, uh, proximity, Oh God. Yeah. Proximity is global.
So if, since we're all present, we give each other's positions away. Oh, it's kind of fun though.
Yeah. You guys see any,
Whoa, any ghosts around? I'm just friendly space, man.
That's a personal jelly. I was so focused on the reader that I didn't know you guys
were shooting a space, man. It's literally one minute to midnight. What's that mean?
What's that mean? Uh, at midnight? They can kill us at midnight. All right.
Into a vacuum can come back and still kill us, but they're weakened. I got a defib so I can oh well
I shouldn't have said that because then they'll single me out
Does anyone need help? I have a health kit. I
Think I think we're pretty good. There's only what two more. I'm going up. Oh, yeah. Oh you're one of these pots, okay?
That's what I would do
Really? I would have gone to one of those pots. So in 17 seconds, they're gonna attack us
Don't they build up a negative attribute if they stay still?
Yeah, Jerma, they build up ectoplasm and then they become more
Easily discoverable. All right, they still yeah
We we should probably stick actually maybe not stick together because then they'll kill us easier in group. Oh, yeah, we should
Oh my god, that was fast
Why is this what is the mammoth? Oh
My god
Nice good
There is
Jolly
God damn it plant. I can't we kill this I
Got him we do it. Yeah, it's just one. It's one left criken now one one. Yes, right
Right here plant plant plant
photo synthesize this oh
Yeah
Sorry, I'm good. I just got a way too excited. I'm so I'm out my parts beating. Oh look at us. So cool
Yeah, why oh man that's we look like
bootleg pyro
Like it's like a flash mob. Imagine being that excited
That excited over like the totally care about in this cheap pop ripoff. I leveled up
You suck is the first game relax
All right. Um, let's keep this team one more time and then we'll find out how to shuffle
Sure. Also remember when you're a ghost if you need to leave
That was very important info that we did not just get that was sounded important. All right, what do we got phantom?
Spirit I think I like this one this one
chill
See hunters through walls, sir
Okay, cool. What should I go? What should I go in?
Rock it out. Yep. I guess for this one probably shouldn't use the
What's the place where this wouldn't be? I have to build a scene. Yeah, I got to build a scene
How do I get out? How do I get out of here?
The proximity chat is so fucking low. I can barely hear you dude. It's it's yeah, it's very far
Like it's like impossible to hear you. So but yeah, I'm gonna I'm using that too
We all just gonna be the animals over here wait, I shouldn't say that out loud fuck no
I think you're okay cuz you're using the team speak. Am I I'm holding Q. Yeah, Q is team speak
All right. Listen, I'm gonna corrupt these pigs. Oh my god. I'm so stupid. I walked right into their base
Should we both be sitting here at the same time Liam? Maybe I should move should I move?
No, maybe I should move. I don't know. I'm smaller. I'm smaller. I'm smaller. I don't know, but you're a bigger talk
I'll move I'll move common courtesy. Okay, be careful. Be careful. I'm so concerned
All right. I've corrupted the pigs. So now if the hunters like attack them, they'll get like damaged
I don't belong where I'm building up. Okay. Oh, what's the deal with the generator? Do we do anything with that?
That's where the hunters resupply
Okay shit
Down I
Wish I could fucking say anything hold R. Yeah, I know you can or you can orient yourself, right?
But I need to move don't I when do they come out? Oh
Here we go. I gotta clear the
When do they come out? When do they actually start to come out? They they're they've been out. They just haven't been anywhere around here
Yeah, Oh
Scared this shit out of me. Just just role-playing
That scared the shit out of me too. Why am I so jumpy right now? Are they I don't like this
Should I go on the plant? I feel like I could hide that. Why am I a gigantic target?
Hey, oh that oh, okay. Good. Just make sure that was you. Yeah, I'm just
Role-playing as a duck right now. What happens if you get to red ectoplasm? Oh
Red ectoplasm means that their instruments can detect you very easily. So you got to like
Jump out of like jump around or jump out into different crops
Oh, that's a ghost that's a ghost right here right here
I
Don't get it. I don't I don't know what happened back. I don't get it
I don't know the head spectral or I don't know the spectrum. Are you bullshit? Did you get sucked up?
I got sucked up. No, you got sucked up. I had the ectoplasm. Okay
All right, if you survive, you can come back if we survived. All right, cool. Cool. Cool. I
Didn't understand the ectoplasm. Oh my god. My corruption is detonated. I would have stayed put
And I'd they're all downstairs wait you wait
Like blocking their way crash I was on the but I was at the bottom of the staircase Oh long way
Well, I'm walking their exit
Chasing me, but I'm back now. I freaked out cuz it was had a red ectoplasm. Whatever
If they come upstairs, let me know I can like just jump downstairs. This is kind of fun, though
I'm just trying to clear my ectoplasm, but I don't see them near you
She says I walked into him. I'm an idiot
Germa is in the same room as you but yeah, they they don't yeah
So what I can go look that is that cheating you you can you can cut fuck with them a little bit right now
Germa you're dead, but you have an ability. I think you can freeze them a little they're coming up to you any coal
Yeah, you'll never they'll never know if you want. I'll never know. I'll never know
She's got him
Children is it really down to me again? Oh jeez not yet. Oh my god
Don't worry guys, they're not gonna kill me in nine minutes. Oh, we good
Now we come back and we gotta kill her. I will be dead in three seconds
Suck him harder
All right nice job mammoth tusk wins
Three ghosts destroyed three hunters knocked out. Well nice work. I'm starting to get it
Okay, cool. All right, great. Yeah. No, yeah
Hopefully I think we get a new map now and I think maybe it'll scramble the teams if not we can do a
You will scramble. Yeah, whatever
Whatever works true true after whatever you got absolutely carried
Stop rocking back and forth. You look old. I'm rocking. Wait, what do you mean like this?
That's it. I don't know. It's just fun to do
All right, let me see this other stuff here. I have 1600 credit
All it replaces that I think I'll try it I want to try this thing and
Giving us the same team teams
Well, you want you want to do like three or four matches in a row at the same teams and then three or four
You know, I'm saying change it back to three or four or something
Okay. Yeah, that sounds good
I'm down for whatever this one
German, what's your chin exercise routine? Look up at the sky like this and you want to put your
like this and one two three
I'm gonna assume this is a DMCA
You go up with your job
No, also another one. Another good one is
Is that even real though? It probably sounds close enough to another song to get DMC aid
So that can happen. I mean I have like
6,000 or so videos on my full sauce channel and every day something new is getting claimed that that makes zero sense
Yeah, it's it's it's kind of crazy
Dude, I had crickets. I played the sound effect of crickets
Not like because I made a bad joke and the crickets got claimed. It's the funny face guy
That's unreal. Yeah. All right. So now that we who dared to claim that probably cricket
It was criken on behalf of crickets
All right, the ghost meter is actually pretty I would say like required
Yeah, I would yeah as long as what does anybody have a
Vacuum, I think we need at least one person with a vacuum, right? Oh, okay. I've defected
Just just look at all with your exercise. How hard are you doing that?
I got a ghost over here guys just warm up on me if you want to kill it
I'm making like a just don't don't let on that. You know, the ghost is there. Okay, never mind. What are you talking about? I
Didn't say yeah one into your room to the other while you like put your chin out
I said literally go like this. So technically the game is on right now and then we are like looking for them right now
It's not like a like a minute. Yeah. Yeah, this is as soon as the hunters join in it's on. Okay, cool
I'm on Ross's tail right now. He's a box. Oh, where'd he go was?
Now I see I'm so close picked up something over here over here picked up something over here. Okay, I have my ghost rail
Oh, yeah, there's there we got some activity in this room. Yeah, there is activity. There is activity. Oh
No idea what I'm doing. Hey ghosts
A little bit of activity over here. Wait, there's somebody in this room. Never mind up, dude
Got him in the room. He's a box. He's a studio stereo equipment box on it. Okay
Wait, what where do you go? What do you go? He's too quickly. What happened? Where'd he go?
Where did he go? Where'd he go? I don't know where he is, but he's here
This thing is so slow to shoot
Yeah, I thought I'd like the machine gun thing, but I don't
Well, I gotta go to resupply. Hold on. This thing is poop. Can I go up the ladder?
There's somebody literally right here the lantern
I'm not getting any readings. No, I think we got we just absolutely we got been had we got played big-time
Here I
Think I think he escaped
Damn it. Oh, he's right here. He's like he's literally in this room
He has to be the rate of the mark. The market is nothing market. It's not like a stock. It's going wild right now
What oh god right here somebody right here right here has to be right here
Good call good call
Jolly jolly, do we all have the melee weapon? Does anybody have a gun?
Damage
Shotgun I've ever charged
Gotcha
There's a fake me running around is that I it's dead now. Oh, it's midnight. Well, here we go right here
Criken is a pot our father who art in heaven
hallowed be thy name
Thy kingdom come will be done
heaven oh
God god
Dude, I'd love to revive you guys, but uh
Okay, this is in Christ. We have failed that melee weapon sucks
Yeah, yeah, I'm not using that anymore
So many of these weapons are like kind of
truce
Half of us are using the the little like a light stick
Need to level up arcane. I feel like yeah, it's like the combine weapon from half-life to it kind of is you know
Who's still alive? I am I'm just booking it. I'm just trying to like outlast. I guess I don't know what to do
I'm literally watching me when I asked that question for some reason. I thought that you were
Don't know why I thought it was a ghost. I thought we were ghosts for one second. Oh my god. Oh my god
Is this working out? They're just chasing you. I think I mean it's working, but there's
Yeah
I'm gonna play the wrestling game tomorrow. Should I just take the L?
You can do whatever you think is correct my brother and Geist
Perform an accelerated back off through the theater
Book it to the next QPU
Yeah, I will but what is that? This is what you see in Mario said in Mario 64
QPUs are positional universes fucking so that we need to talk about parallel universes
Why can they not get you does anybody do they have them a move? They're just running behind
Yeah, all right ghost moves, right?
Yeah, go team chair
The chair when oh my god ghost after this next round when the next map is about to happen
I'm gonna exit and we can all join a new lobby and we'll go into new teams
All right, I get it. I like I want to hide more now that I understand how it works. Nice straw. Sorry. I'm a very loud
No, but you're okay. No, you're good. It's a straw. Is there a problem with straws?
Buddy, why is your steam profile picture alone in the dark? I don't know. I haven't changed it since like
2013 or something. I don't know. Okay. This is important
Remotely charge up objects looks like a ghost charging up. I'm gonna try that. Are we playing this game?
Are we backing out? Yeah, we're doing this one. Yeah when it changes to the next map all ghosts
But then I'll make a new server random sound I found the ability that lets you create false radar readings. That'll be good
That's probably what was happening with us that whole time
Yeah
Apparently you can throw your voice
All you have to do is aim hold left shift and press C and talk
So like somebody's throw my voice like she says tell me if you can hear me in proximity
Okay, I did
Something really small. Yeah, I'm really far away from you. I just threw my voice to you. Yes. Oh, that's cool
I think I'm gonna go sit. I think I'm gonna go sit in one of those chairs
You do that. They'll never know if we find more buckets we can put them in chairs. This is too obvious
I don't think they're gonna look over here. Who's the piano? Can you just jump?
Yeah, you can fuck do your piano the Mario 64 piano I need to lean forward like the other ones are
That was probably a terrible idea. I don't know. I did that scan occasion. I didn't get it. I got the defense
Oh, no, did not about the scanner. No
They didn't get the scanner
They're far away I'm gonna go this way
I mean ghost hunters. I'm a ghost, of course. I'm gonna go this way
Something so humorous about German Tokyo drifting through the door there
Chair, oh man, okay. I get I can fake them out
Stop moving. I have to look at the ectoplasm buildup. I have to move I can revive
They're teabagging my shards
They're all in the first floor. Nope. There's one up top basically. Oh, yeah one just walked by Vinny
Oh
I'm watching this from up here
I'm trying to clear the buildup. Wow. Wow. I cannot believe that just happened. What happened? Oh, I just missed it
Why would there be a ladder here? It was already looking for Vinny and Vinny just kind of booked it over the balcony
Oh great. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I had like a gamer moment. I can't believe it. Well, not that kind of one
But I'm gonna save that for you so you can get a third-person perspective
Do you guys remember Iced for GameCube I do remember Geist that's what this is multiplayer Geist
It was on what happened recently Geist. Oh
Great show and yeah, I haven't been able to forget about it since playing this. Yeah. Oh man that game was okay
The very okay is game
I'm like a trampoline
I don't understand. It's too stressful. It's too stressful
I can't do it. I can't fucking do this. That's too stressful. This is too stressful. It's I'll I can't it's too stressed
I'm gonna lose it. Nice, you know, I don't I don't get it. I don't it's like I freak out
I think they can see me at all fucking sides. I think it's like too stressful
Yes, Vinny keep distracting. Oh, I don't know. I feel like they can see me
I'm just gonna keep jumping as a cat. Are you lying bagging my ghost corpse?
I think they'll laugh. So I think they lagged out now. Are they lagging or just tea bagging aggressively?
It's time
I'm a couch. It's time for you to pay
Yeah, I probably I should I shouldn't like
Yeeted myself down the stairs, but I don't know. I love to play these games. I don't know what like what it looks like
Fuck no
I'm trying I'm trying to hit him
We can if you yeah. Yeah, there you go
Good just various objects. Yeah like that. Good job. Oh
Come here
I
Almost got it. I'm trying
Ghosts if you want more speed you have to possess an object and right-click hold it and then you can like start
What are you doing?
Did you just like suck the ectoplasm out of that corpse? Yes
That's normal
Got it. I wish I would have seen that kill. Yeah
Yeah
Team chair, all right
Let's see how well you do teams with 12 minutes in a game in a genre that you've never played before
In a space that you've never been in before in a area that you've never seen before
You understand that I'm trying. Okay, relax. Relax. Everything's fine
Use a fee. No, I'm just kidding. I don't know. I never played prop on ever
I know this has been around for like alright, this is like I've never played a game
This is like never playing a game of Call of Duty in your whole life. Hey, I just I just solidified that game right there
I got the last kill. I think I did pretty good
Never played TF2 pro. No, I was always like a super contrarian and
Didn't want to play prop on because it was so popular that I was like, nah, it's not me. I'm not playing that
It's a popular thing I got a new code I was very much aware of his existence
You're a hipster. Yeah, you say that that's fine
You're in your right to say that is the guy who played Elden Ring 15 times in a row
What does that have to do with anything? Wait, I think maybe I did I play you a video of TF2 prop hunt. I'm pretty sure
Yeah, but like I don't it was like that was like eight years ago. I played it once I
Yeah, sorry, I forgot that I played TF2 prop hunt like nine years ago one time
What do you say?
How am I supposed? I don't know. I don't remember
You tell me what you had for breakfast two weeks ago. I bet you would you ever okay?
What did you have for breakfast on?
April 2nd
2022 what did you eat for breakfast? Do you fucking even know? No, you can
Dude, it was nine like eight or nine years ago, and I probably dude. It was I probably forgot it immediately after it happened
That's so funny, but what's a different game? This is completely different
Who knew how team can you hear me?
Are we on the same piece?
Yeah, it looks like only one person difference. We just we have Jolly now. We traded for Jolly
No, it's really not
It's weird because seriously, I can't find a way to randomize or change teams
Between people it seems like that just isn't an option
Hey, what did you guys have for breakfast nine years ago nine years ago to the day bacon egg and cheese almost guaranteed guaranteed
almost
Currently going back and forth with chat about a few things
Okay, sorry that took me off guard
Probably honey nut Cheerios, I mean lately this not that this is in any way relevant to the question that Jerma had asked
but lately
It's been bagel Vinny just shot Jerma's bit to bits. Did I ruin your bit Jerma? No ever?
Okay, so everyone's everyone's yelling at me over here because they're like, how do you not know how to play prop hunt?
And I was like, dude, I've never played prop on right somebody pulled out. We watch somebody pulled out an old video from like
2013 I was gonna say
Yeah, I don't know. I don't think they did laying. I don't remember playing prop hunt
So I'm like, what'd you have for breakfast two weeks ago on April 2nd?
Also crying bit if you play game
Wait the match already started he saw it he saw it
Does anyone have a vacuum? Yeah
So all me I just randomly shot a duck, okay guys
I just randomly shot that duck because I thought it would be funny and it was cracking dude shoot fucking everything
There's no downside wrecking. Absolutely. Yeah. Yeah, there isn't
Which makes no sense because usually there's like a risk reward
Yeah
Breakfast nine years ago and suddenly criken is dead. I feel a chill
We've got a ghost here where I am
What do you guys have you guys played like a game like that? You don't remember playing from like ten years ago
Do you know what I played last night?
Thank you. Wait, what do you found him?
Treasure chest
Like that you don't remember playing ten years ago, but you have played it. Yeah, we're saying oh
Probably any Call of Duty game from then you know how many steam games
I probably have downloaded that that I've played like maybe 30 minutes of and went well
I don't this game sucks and then never played it again and forgot. I ever bought it guys criken is haunting me
Hmm. It's probably because you shot a duck
Sorry, criken. I thought it would be funny to shoot the duck. I'm sorry. How is this happening?
And this is well, because I'm just looking for objects that are slightly out of place
I'm playing the video game, you know in a reading
That's a lot. I didn't mean that to sound so sassy. I apologize
Dare you not talk about breakfast that you ate something right here. Look man. All I'm saying is
Well Germans getting a lot of shit for this
I literally have played mods that I've got that I played like two months. I feel like them again
I don't know that doesn't make your shit inexcusable jammer. Come on. I mean, I've played a mod of
I played prop hunt nine years ago, and I don't remember playing it
How do you but do you not remember the craze on YouTube where oh, yeah, really? Everybody played it. Oh, absolutely
I just don't remember being a part of the craze
But like surely, you know a bit of this from osmosis like absolutely
To be fair though this this is this is a lot a little more prop hunty than usual prop hunt
It's actually not not to correct you but it's less prop hunt than prop hunt. Okay
There's nothing in the boat, okay, there's nothing I just I love that he's literally being a pirate in the boat
He was taunting me before
Now are there skeleton ghosts? Are we doing squid ghosts? What do we got?
I just watched what's the Caribbean?
squid ghosts
Watch the first two why can't squids have ghosts Charlie? What is this? Well, I mean they can but I don't think they'd be particularly cerebral I
Don't think there's much going on in a squid bat brain other than eat food eat food shit eat food eat
They're very smart. They're very smart animals cephalopods man mental. I
Thought that was octopuses. I don't know any better
Don't make me feel guilty for eating squid. I love just making stuff up it. Yep. So am I but
You know, he's chilling any readings at all down here somebody something down here. I found him. I found a piece of box. Oh
shit, okay, oh
Yeah, he's something else. He's literally in this room
The salt water is corroding your suit
What?
Where the fuck is he?
He's has to be right here somewhere like literally right here
Yeah, we got strong readings down here. All right, we're about to get fucked. So stick together run
He just fucking murdered him. Oh my god. Oh, he's so low. I'm knocked out
Squids are able to count solve problems recognize patterns and communicate
Dude squids can play video games
You think squids got kind of fell out of an alien spaceship driving across the earth and fell in the ocean
Just kind of kept going. I
Mean that that sounds like a good enough theory for me
being
non biology
Fuck oh, that's all of my health. I have six
You're so low, but I have faith you got this dude. I believe in you. No, just just just yeah, buddy
So how was Pirates of the Caribbean one in two?
Very good, and I will tell you this to comfort you as you die
But I will say that I like to maybe a little bit better than one
Really? Maybe a little bit just because I like the squids. They were pretty cool incredibly incredibly relevant point
I've seen all the Pirates of the Caribbean movies. I don't remember any of them
Okay, I'm cursed the black pearl is kind of a classic to me, but I
Thought dead man's chest was a little too long for its own good. I
Just got called out for having shit taste for liking the sequel like a little bit better than the first one
You I mean you could look at it like that. I mean, I mean you could Vinnie, but you're wrong. I
You know incorrect opinions are basically what I live for
There are four parts of the Caribbean movies, right? Oh shit. I'm about to fire like seven
That range was so all over the place. Oh, no, there are seven. No, there are five there are four
That feels like there are seven
Attention off to the third
That's what I'm gonna stop. I'm gonna watch the third one. I'm just gonna stop
Yeah, that was the last one that for Binsky
Directed then he went to do a Rango if you haven't seen that as a great movie. I've heard about that one. It's animated movie
Yeah, I didn't I think I've only seen two. I don't actually won the Oscar. There's so much fucking media nowadays like this so much
There's not there's only so much as one thing in our brains to be able to remember all this fucking media
Think of all the video games all the movies all the breakfasts you've had
Gemma, I just want to say I'm going from agreeing with you to maybe he has early onset Alzheimer's really real quick here
That's usually me
Like who remembers what they ate for breakfast who remembers what they did yesterday. I don't remember what I was playing yesterday
Who remembers movie? I don't remember movies
Yeah, but I mean, okay. I remember what I did yesterday, but not like eight years ago
Surviving their cheese. I was so I was one minute away
I've played so much Eldon ring in the past like I
Wanted to hear his take I wanted to hear the Eldon ring take you're getting I'm getting eviscerated, right?
Okay, I want to try it that good again
Yeah, I'm gonna try that point again is I've been playing so much Eldon ring that there's a good chance in a year
I'm not gonna remember more than the fact there were some dudes that look like foreskin
I've got that it's it's it's a huge game. There's so much to see it's just so much. There's just too much I
Can't wait for like two years from now when everybody decides to replay it at the exact same time
Yeah, what DLC you mean?
Yeah, pretty much so even though we're not playing Eldon ring right now, but any what are your builds? What's everybody's builds?
What did they run through the game? I've been doing a bunch of different things
But I do a little bit of int magic and mostly decks and like so I'm using
I
Do play blades based but bested this guy's bested for his build
All right, we just we're just gonna try all sitting in the exact same spot, huh? Oh, we're all here
Oh, yeah work good plan. No, I'm not over here. Yeah, I got a good spot. It's actually really good
Cuz I'm gonna corrupt these these crates
What does that do? I mean it crops them. I guess I got a really good plan here. So I'm just shaking off the ectoplasm
The good call I forgot about that you can press B to ding apparently the ding you can yeah, you can I think we I
Wonder if the enemy team can hear that and it like stops ectoplasm build up. Oh, that's cool. Yes
Remember to throw your voice that shift and then
Yeah
By the way, they can totally hear you going
As you're jumping up and down. Oh
Aided that does make noise. I will just have to be light-footed then. I mean, I'm a I'm a treasure chest, but
It'll work. Just ding ring the bell smash the link
subscribe
If you do 25 taunts in one game you get an achievement right here right here
My team I see him. Oh, yeah
Bouncing a crate. Oh, I can't go that way
Run German German was the one that ended up getting chased first
Yeah, and we're being complete assholes and dingy
Good harpoon. Yeah, now we got him
lads here the oh
Yeah, what button is that?
What would you would you press? I left my mark and so did Kurt Cobain
I wish I could how do I I don't want to certainly did
Here's I lost him by the way. Oh nice. Here's the problem with putting your spray paint paint down is that
It's not it's not prop. It's not prop what it's not proper because it's not like work
You know, we're giving away that we're props. You know what? Yes. Yes
Dinging in the jumping before which was totally inconspicuous. I think yeah, I think that was alright
I'm back. I just had to place my spray over there
Let me spray on the wall walk in the fucking door. By the way, hold on big brain move. Oh, no little brain move
spot
Why am I still alive?
You've been digging
Very well. Did you like my dings? It's a good round good round
I don't know how to respond to that. This is a really good round so far. Yeah
surprisingly good like I
Want to say it's not us it's them because I'm currently dinging repeatedly and the spray is right behind my head
They just don't seem to care nice
There they did there if they die, they probably had it coming
Kind of heartless, but correct. Why am I dying? What's going on?
already dead the
The seeing the hunters through the walls perk is fucking broke as shit. Where are they? I
Didn't know that was a perk. I thought that was a passive for everybody. Yeah, that that perk is in a book
We got a location on them. They're all hiding behind the at the back of the ship here the this part
Third
That also the I killed one
nice job
Salt damages ghosts. Yeah, that's some
Some I guess the boat phasmophobia. I
Don't see anyone in the boat, but on me back me the boat. We need a pence of them. Yep. Found one found one
Go to a gas can German German gas can get him. Oh damn German
Hold on damn dude. That was next round savage brain that consume its work
Only one left
So it just kind of becomes reverse hide-and-seek at the ends it kind of does yeah
Who's left is a crank? Yeah
criken
Where are you?
Probably like crouching behind something over here. I'm definitely getting that perk. Let's see through all as one
It's very he's on the top of the ship everybody
He's like I'm one of the masts. Oh my god. If I just looked up I would have seen him fucking hell
I'm an idiot. I almost made it demand your blood
Ouch still up top. Nope right here
Nice job. Good. Good. Good. Good game. This is souped-up prop on kind of is yeah
Box do you want to change up teams ready? We're gonna keep going
What do you think? I don't know. It's up to you guys
You want to shuffle again, I think it's it depends on who gets in first is the
First team I think
Okay, so let's shuffle. I'll exit this
Okay, that's fun. That's cool. That was your best game yet. Yeah, I mean I'm starting to figure it out
I definitely want that see people through Wallace thing cuz that's ridiculous. I'll put it on
I like to smash it into people you can throw your voice with shift plus C
Is that a perk or can I just can I just do that? It looks sweaty. I don't think so
I'm a little flush for some reason. I don't know why let's get in I
Want to take a good look at those perks kind of like the huntsman it kind of is yeah
Alright, let's do some loadout stuff
Alright ghost loadout this one here
See hunters through walls. Okay, I can I can unlock it. I definitely want that
Even before midnight that seems like why would you pick anything else?
Telekinesis is so good. I was able to live through that whole thing. I tricked the whole team for like a full minute
deadly
ghostly mist
Corruptor that's not bad either
Someone's a fake ghost. Oh shit. I didn't get to look. I don't know about these though
Flamethrower I mean hi Kraken. We're finally on the same team, which is nice
Oh, I don't know. I wish it was easier to like customize the teams. But
anyway, sorry about the duck incident incident
Apologize to me man. I would have done the same. I
Saw a duck I got excited man. I don't know. I just sometimes I
That was where the duck spawned though. Like I didn't even move it. I was like, this is perfect
He just fucking shot me immediately just went right in
Is the sniper any good? I probably not. Oh
You know, you know snipe a fucking box, man. That's true. They like make new songs for
like this game
Or did they like go to?
Yeah, is it is it new songs zero this might be a new song. Yeah, I haven't heard this one before must be new
This is a good one. Do you like it? It's our solo is fantastic
It's very very generic David Gilmore Pink Floyd waterlands music. It seems like adequate small talk on the way to a haunted mansion
We've been to this one yet. No. Oh, yeah. We have I think we you know what we did a practice
What?
What happened
sensitivity is way too high
Ghosts just hanging out in this it's better if you guys see a ghost, you know, I got a ghost
Where did I move that with my body? It's probably a glizzy. Yeah. Okay. All right. Hear me. I
Hate the word glizzy, but I can't stop saying it someone glizzy someone just dinged
What's the definition of the glizzy? Hello? It's Ross
A glizzy is apparently slang for a hot dog and I have no idea why this happened
Is that a New York thing or I
Think it was in I've explained this and this has come up on my stream like five days in a row
Like five streams in a row, but it apparently started as slang for a Glock in prison in like Florida
And then somehow it became slang for a hot dog
Really?
Down in the dining room. I'm getting some activity
Yeah, yeah table it's I lost it I'll check it up check this chair
My god, I got a chair
It was the chair. I
3c4
Nice why we were all at the boards because I got soft one. Oh really? Oh man. Oh, that's not
I thought you guys were just hanging out there. We were trying to get somebody's dingin in here redo or
That other ability
Does the ding mean all right, can they be painting the ghost of Hector Salamanca is haunting us. Where are you Hector?
Yeah, that ding was literally in my head
No, they're not upstairs. They're not upstairs. They're not upstairs
No, they're not they're not downstairs. They're not downstairs. Okay, I swear to God somebody is in this room
You know if you can be door
We're gonna look real foolish once we figure out where this person is
In the fire. I didn't bring my ghost detecting instrument. I should get that. I think something was just in front of me
Did I miss it? It's just where the fuck is this person?
I'm getting a candle. There's a candle on the table. There's a candle
Candles it was a candle on the table. Oh, I don't know where they went. I know I don't know. I have no idea. I don't
Oh
Just spray everywhere
Where was he he had several things
He was a candle on the dining room table. I was sitting on the table. It turned it
He was like table with sheet on it. Yeah, I was on the table
Myself yeah two seconds and then I realized yeah, two of those kills were just because you're in the lobby stuck
I don't know. How do we not?
Randomly spray you or hit you when you were on the table. It was hilarious. Honestly, I was watching you just walk over him
That's crazy
All right leveled up. I want to unlock new skin. So I don't look like
Candle was body blocking you
Have you seen arcane? What are your thoughts on the show? I think it's on the first episode
The only thing I remember from arcane was oh
the misery
Every single person is my enemy
That's all it's the only thing I know. I don't know anything else
And the song goes oh
Imagine dragons that they they have that formula down. They have that
Salt circle blocks your pet. Oh
That's good
And dude, by the way when that song comes on when I saw that intro like a warmth raises over my body
Like I'm like, it's like it's not chills, but it's like a yes. Here we go. I
Don't like this spot at all. By the way, I can what are you? You're the door
I've even moved the thing. Oh what I even moved. Ah, whatever skill issue. I was too busy like doing like
My enemies I'm
Radioactive
Radioactive every single person is my enemy
What's that stop? I have imagined dragons on right now
Well, I don't care. I'm not one of those banned elitist, right? I'm not gonna be like well, I
Have this indie band that I listen to that's better. I don't I don't care if you enjoy music good
I hope you do. I don't I don't listen to music. I don't really listen to it too much
I listen to like the guerrillas albums on repeat the Lost Odyssey soundtrack on repeat
Full metal alchemist intro and outro brotherhood
Maybe like a dozen times a week
I used to be able to recite the entire attack on Titan season 2 intro until I was like I probably should stop doing this
Cuz the YouTube algorithms gonna like I think I'm like a fucking weirdo. What was that sound? I cannot hear him
Are you making fun of imagine dragons? I just told you I didn't I'm just saying like that. Those are the two songs
I know I thought I didn't make I just said that music if you have different music tastes. There's nothing wrong with it
I don't care. Okay, I feel to say people used to give me shit about liking the Venom movie. Okay, look
I you know, I do let me tell you something about why the Venom movie
I don't I don't care if you don't like the Venom it's working cracking. I thought it was funny
I thought it was just like absurd. It was awful, but it was great at the same time. Who cares
Who doesn't matter?
Nowhere in that whole thing. Did I say I hate him? We're gonna avoid the clip
Nowhere during that entire segment. Did I say the words?
I never said this hate never said this imagine dragons never said it. All I said was I just I didn't say anything
I just went oh
I'm not gonna say it again
Oh
I'm not kidding man. I really thought something's wrong with my computer. I thought something was wrong
I thought there's something in this drink. I was like what happened? What did I just take?
It's like why the drugs in my drink what's going on I was like what the fuck
Feels like the screen is wavy too. I'm just like, what's it the macho?
All right, that is the most annoying fucking too much matcha powder I
Really think I'm gonna select it next time
It's like this side of it mother matcha powder
you know
The ghost hunt was really about the friends we made I died it wasn't so much about the actual ghost hunting
I was I was gone on the first probably five seconds
This thing's too big I'd like to dub this genre of game prop hunt with consequences. Oh
Shit I just bumped into you shit. Oh fuck. I was hoping Tony and physics would win out. I just kept missing
How do you even die in this we can get killed in the ghost?
Oh, I was bumping into stuff on that room was a bad place to do that should have left and on that map of all maps
We got consequenced. Yeah, I feel you guys should have had a real advantage to that true life consequences. I
Slammed into so yeah to ghosts. We smashed into it. It was too
Hey, I'm like these spooky ghost perk. That's just there to fuck with the other team. I
Just was trying to be annoying. I hope it worked
It oh trust me it worked. I it was soothing. I went to I went to
policing the attack on Titan intro
Now you're really gonna get like are you kidding me? I?
know
No way
No way not a chance in hell. No way
Hey, you like my outfit. Oh, it's a new that's how much does it cost?
1500 it costs you your soul because you have to cook meth and albuquerque to get it. Oh
That is a that is a Jesse out for you, right a little bit
And then just that's that's two references breaking bad tonight. It's just Jesse Jesse. Oh, yeah, it is a woman
I didn't realize that definitely a bit a bit of curves
I was play here. We got it. We want to strategize a little bit. We do two and two
Two and two and I think the high road
Okay, I'll take the the criken road because I want to atone for my killing of the duck
It looks like I'm the only one with a vacuum so I
Got it. I got a I have the radar
remember you can switch mid-round at the
Desk room have you considered singing as a career? You have a zoomer potential a meth cookie one
What does that mean? I saw you see that he was fucking running around upstairs. He's going up. He's going up top
I'll cover the down
Handle
Somewhere oh ding. I'm not getting I'm not getting a reading. Yeah, they bailed they booked it
Oh
There was something here in this room there he goes here, please make yourself known
Stone duck I see that you found your spirit animal
I mean notice I find the duck in whatever map we're in Adam right here on me. He's a barrel with candles
Oh, he checked he changed he changed he switched. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know
I don't candle but candle. It's that she thinks she says
Up top up top up top another barrel candles coming down all candles
Going to the under crop I'm down. There's all this shit in the way down down down down
Down his candles his candle
That was a headshot what they won't gonna back nice work somebody else down here at least it looked like it
Really
Maybe they went up. I heard I'd be up. Yeah, I think they might be up
Oh, this is just misery the thing is that they're the enemy though, so we gotta make sure we take them out
I think anybody can fucking hear me. I'm too far away. No more ding. I don't this had been on the roof
To left I'll check the Crips. It's just don't duck move
We still have activity in this read pretty bumped into me and yeah, there's a thing on the lantern over here
I don't know. I don't know something
Fuck somebody threw that at me. No way. Yeah, somebody somebody threw that at me
And it's pissing me off. Yeah, we we've got activity here and
Ding ding once if you're alive thing once
Yeah, I'm getting this activity and they be up on this lip is not the real she says gas can't help wait shoot this
Yeah, nice work on left
Crap 30 seconds if you're a ghost with the most just communicate appears press the V button
Ghost press the V button and that'll help you
This is this level is really good for for ghosts. There's a lot of room. Fuck. I don't know in life
Were you an animator?
Good night. I'm gonna stay perched
Fuck. Oh my god. We lost what? Wow. What? Oh
I was a statue in the basement that you guys walked
I knew it. I knew it. I knew is in the basement. It's good. Yeah, you were in on that. This is dog
I love the egg dog so much dog shit. Thank you fucking weapon is absolute dog shit
Seven damage that how do you do?
The tag I saw on the ground weapons dog shit. I'm just you great
Okay, and it just is your twitch avatar right thing. I'm a twitch. I hear your steam
Yeah, yes a bad craftsman blames the tools a bad craftsman blames a seven damage sniper
when the exploding splash damage the five per clip bomb weapon does like 30 all of them
Isary I won't do this. I think fly cuz you can fly that's yeah under that. All right. That was that was a good round
But let's go for it. There's some really good ghost skins like they're expensive as fuck, but there's some really fun ones
I gotta look at them. I like the
Grim Reaper one. I think I'm gonna be that one's cool. I just like the classic ghost with sheet America statue
Should I do door again? Or is that uh?
No way. It works twice. I think it will work again. Yeah, it's just
When the right mind would be a door for five minutes the person who likes the most fun gameplay
I like my spot
Also criken I saw you streaming something the other day where like chat was
Participating and they were like little avat like avatars and stuff. Yeah, what was that?
Cuckaroo was it good. Yeah, it's pretty fun. It's like it only uses your chat for interaction
So it kind of spams up the whole thing, but oh, they're gonna run Vinny. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no
Vinny's doing the duck
Self-report self-report. I'm beginning to I'm beginning to think I'm bad at this game. Can I talk or were they hear me?
You're good. If you press Q. Yeah, I
Do you do you see my 100 million IQ spot here? I'm gonna take a look guys
I accidentally sprayed my spray and right next to my door
Very that's cool. If they see it, it's a very clear giveaway
I'm the door
Just the door. I literally okay that put my own face on the door. That's a good spot
That's a good spot and it's stretched criken like a cross. It's really cool
Look, he sees it. There's no way they find me. Is he gonna this is riveting gameplay?
This is called winning gameplay because there's no fucking way anyone's gonna come over here. Like why would you come over here?
They really not you know, they didn't they just went okay the door I really hope none of them try to call my god
Good up to do that. Let's all right. We're good. Long time fan want to tell you that your title sucks
I don't know what the title is
I'm dangin
Here you do well you should have
They're never gonna find me no way
No fucking way. This is the best spot of the whole day. I think I can move a little
Clear the build up
my fucking god there
There's no way. No, this is no fucking way. They're gonna come over. I am in the clear. I am never going to be found
But wait, that means I have to kill everybody throw your voice. It was shift C should hold shift and press C
That work
Oh
Is that all right, all right, all right, all right, all right up I oh I fucked up I fucked up
This reminds me of bugs life when the ants stand up to the grasshoppers. It's like we're not as big a threat as they thought
Haven't thought of that in a very long time. The shotguns insane. We're still hiding from them down
Go gas can gas can you got this?
No, what?
No
How the heck is he flying like that?
My god. Holy shit. What a magnificent last stand. Yeah, I was trying to I
Was holding the button down. I felt kind of bad for him. I I was holding right click
I know you could throw your body at him hit him the fucking head. I do I couldn't hit him the fucking head though
No, you can like slash it people if you didn't know. Oh, it kills almost instantly
Does it really
I was trying that too, and I was not doing enough damage. I did 98 damage to me in one hit
I'm trying to hit him in the fucking head. I know you can fucking hit him in the fucking head
All right. Now that I know okay now that I know that I could do it. Give me this goddamn thing
So guys, how are you doing that?
local training
That's just what I could do that by a fucking sledgehammer
Secret vocal technique, I guess we'll do these teams
I'm sorry
Someone on my chat. Just said Vinnie annoys his friends all night
I don't think it's annoying. I think it's cool. I think you're great, man. I
Do frostbite this I?
Think that's great, too. You know, in fact, we're going to prom right now
That's pretty touching
Yeah, I think we're all each other's dates
All right, cool. Very excited. I'm gonna cook some meth at the prom
You guys can like place on fire. Yeah, you should spike the fruit punch with meth
Well, I don't know mr. White, come on Jesse
I'm happy I got Jerma to hear I got to hear Jerma do a Walter White impression
It's really easy just do Harrison Ford but say Jesse
Chewy, I mean Jesse
You got it. That was perfect
Think once for yes and none for no
Was moving is your name rubber Ross? All right, never mind. It's not Ross
Hulk says
There's somebody in the ballroom area
Okay, what the fuck I don't know
Percussion it's like oh like there's someone in the in the dance hall. Oh, he scared me
I'm trying to shoot him with the ice pellets. Well, we're all bad at this
I
Got science lab. There is a weird teleporter in here though. Oh, it's a bouncy pad
I'll see him. Yeah, she says your shit. Your shaggy voice is like unreal. Thank you. Here. Let me try one more time
Like swing scoop like we're at the prom
That's pretty good
Scrappy do and get banned. It's probably apologize
Yeah, you get banned from the server and which unfortunately it's in their rules now
Somebody's in here. Somebody's a chair or something. I
Think we have a ghost in the punch bowl. Oh, I hope we do
That's not the real cry
What what no
That was fake Kraken. I got to the first layer. Hold on
Thankfully, it's right. Oh, no a bomb in the lasagna. I am 100% being a toilet
Yeah, that wasn't Kraken that was Kraken. There's no way I'm not gonna be a toilet next room
There's no activity here at all zero zero Roger Roger
I mean my icon is Nirvana. So there's a song from Nirvana called school. Anyone know that song? Yeah. Yeah
That's this right now. So true
Interesting and I get some friends to come out of the stage, please. Oh, no, I couldn't find me squid game. Look an idiot
He's gonna be an idiot in squid game. He's a guitar guitar guitar guitar if you're
All we're gonna die. Have we tried in here?
Dude, I am such a okay. I cannot use this next time
I'm just staring at the meter and not looking at what it's pointing at
We got a ding and I I don't even trash he was trash it was Liam he was trash
Oh my god, Lois, I thought you know
Was jolly. Yeah, I just got sucks to
Damn it. Are there any weapons that are good besides the first one? I
Haven't found I haven't found one yet
Dang Liam, I thought it was jolly dinging the whole time
No, yeah, I was I was a trash can in the hallway. Well, you figured it out. Yeah, he's a shotgun
Yeah, I was and then I was a drum kit before then you walked by me a lot. I think also
my
Lads for tonight. My goal is for us to see every map at least once
So I think we I think we only have one more after this to be fit. Okay, this is probably a bad idea
But let's see what happens
Whatever people think I'm like a cringy annoying loser. Anyways, I'm going for it. This one's better
I like this actually way more I put shove hunter. Yeah to be fair someone was saying
Probably the other team
You guys don't all at the same time do a Peter Griffin impression that the kind of three
Yeah, let's do it. I think so. I think it's worth it. What are we saying? I'd love to see
Yeah, we're gonna say the same thing too. Yeah the exact same thing. Okay. What is it?
This reminds me of the time that I went to the school dance Lois
Yeah, you ready?
Yeah, and one two three this reminds me
Feel like I'm the weak link there guys, I gotta be honest. I couldn't tell because it was just a cacophony of Peters
That's like we all we all so badly wanted to make the same joke and we did it at the same time
I mean you told us yeah, but like but that's like it
Like out of context though like we all so badly wanted to make the Peter Griffin reference at the school dance
And all happen to say the same exact line
It's a very memorable quote. We could probably get Ross and his
To no don't be a guitar. That's so obvious animate it fucked. But yeah, I'm sure he would love to do that
Wait, I had not moved. I was too busy focusing on Peter Griffin
I'm the mic in the middle of the dance floor. It's not a good place to be
I mean
But the but you are an important tool of the dance without you. How would we hear the vocals? Yeah, whenever they come close
I'm gonna say um, Peter Griffin line. Okay. Remember you can throw your voice
I'm gonna throw it right behind them. They're gonna turn around and then I'll run
Yeah, how far can you throw it just as far as you can see?
Yeah, it's a little pinpoint when you do it. You hold control and see
So it's control and see what was that cool noise. It's not like Chewbacca
I hate that noise
Fucking scary
What you think of a bowl of Cheetos
Screw damn I'm a big man. Yeah, this is ghost Peter Griffin. Yeah, I'm staying right here you Stewie
You're not throwing it shift and see look. I can see it over there. That's what I'm doing the whole time
Look, you can see the indicator just see as I'm doing we're doing the whole time. This is now just spooky family guy
I'm over here. I'm over here here here. I'm over here here here
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I feel like I have the best hiding spot. Like I haven't seen anybody come over here
They all just like hanging out in the uh, the actual dance hall. No, no, no, no, no
Snake have you ever heard of the diaper chief?
I need to live I need to live
Come on you can't come on you fucking consumerists
C4
I got insta killed
I got one
Uh, it's just me. I forgot you can attack fuck
Why is it consumerists? I don't know
It's crazy to me. You can survive the entire round and then die in one hit
Yeah
I gotta I gotta remember to actually attack with right click. I've been trying i've been headshotting people with the furniture
I got
Yeah, and also in some ways less risky because you're going fast
Diaper chief stop it
How do you get that pose?
It's an emote
I don't know. It's a it's a victory pose
I don't know almost killed me with the sheer forces and launch. That was pretty cool. Yeah, you had 10 health left, right?
Let us exit the server and do one more map perhaps with one more change of team
All right, should we should we change the join order? Because that seems to be what the uh teams are
Yeah, let's try that. We can organize it we can like decide who goes
What?
consumerist
I don't know. We're like in all these objects like basketballs and like
Like keyboards and like computers. I don't know
I figured it'd be like what the fuck is he talking about? Like they're running around chasing this ghost who is a chair
And he's like you fucking consumerist. It's like
What are you talking about? What does that have to do with anything?
You're an object
Yeah, I know i'm like a piano
He's so high
You keep talking in team chat
Oh, that was the time that I played golf
This is fun. This is fun
Yeah, I was throwing my voice. I was throwing it all I that that was a really good round during the hiding phase
I think we're gonna wait till a couple people join so the teams are more scrambled
I think he's actually high. I'm I'm not i'm just having a good time
Don't ever bet on germa's team. We've won a few
All right, i'm gonna join now and joining. Oh that lobby doesn't exist
What are the animes that you've watched? I like the kind of mainstream ones attack on titan full metal alchemist
um
uh
Jujutsu kaisen
Although I don't think it finished that one. I've not seen jojo. No, that's pretty much it though
I've seen berserk a long time ago
What about mog? I don't think it's an anime
Brother hoodo the original i've seen both
One punch man i've seen season one of one punch man and i've been told just pretend that it ends at season one
Well mob psycho no cowboy bebop long time ago. Oh, I don't have the code. What about evangelion
I've seen the final scene of evangelion. That's it though. Maybe I randomly like on adult swim if it used to play
Okay, here we go
Please watch mob psycho. I don't have like a plan. I don't really have plan of like watching certain animes or whatever
Um, I just kind of catch them if I you know, feel like it one day. What about one piece?
Um, I okay this is probably gonna piss a lot of people off
We're not gonna piss you off but be like, oh dude, what the fuck are you doing?
I watched like the first like season I think of one piece
When the intro had
Yeah, yo, yeah, yo in it
um, so
That's all I know
the four kids version
Yeah, whatever one goes
Give it up. Give it up. Give it up. Give it up
Here's how the story goes. It's no doubt from the treasure in the grand line
It's no doubt. We don't want to be king. I'd be king of the island. He wants to be king. Yeah
Yo, yeah, yo
Don't give it up. Luffy. Don't give it up. Zolo. Don't give it up
Don't give give it up. Give it. I don't I know like most of it. Oh
Uh, dude, yeah
Whoa, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, there's a good bite of gum gum
And then yeah, yo, yeah, he spins around with his legs. I don't know why I remember this whole thing. I don't understand
Why do I know the four kids dub because like 15 years ago it was just on tv randomly sometimes
Sub or dub. I mean if it's the four kids version from like almost two decades ago, it's gonna be the dub
I keep forgetting you're not 20
That means you watched the four kids one in your 20s
Listen to me. I did not tell you that I watched i'm just telling you sometimes it was on tv
and like I'd catch the intro and be like, oh, okay, this is a show I guess and then like
And change the fucking channel
I I don't know. I don't know the whole series. Hi. Hello
Hello, I was ready to rock and roll
Let's do it. Hello. Yeah, you said you watched the first season
Hi, I mean, I'm when i'm when i'm in by that is i've seen episodes from like the first season because I got would be
Randomly be on television. All right. What's the uh strat? What do you guys want to do?
I'm gonna be a door
Oh, yeah
people
I'm 24 and I watched it on tv. Yeah, whatever
Because there's all sometimes a ghost
Sorry guys. I didn't come across one piece the four kids version when I was like fucking 20 and go
It was a fucking busted. No, no, i'm 20. I can't watch this like I just like I don't know
It was on fucking tv. My only concern is that I can't jump to reduce the ectoplasm
So I don't know what kids is for kids ding you ding
Oh, I ding I I guys I don't I don't know what happens in the show
I have no idea doesn't shake and the ding is way off in the distance for some reason
Oh, this is this is actually like this is evil
It's genuinely 24 and I still watch the care bears leave him alone
You browse television
Sorry, by the way guys, i'm old enough for when like I had to change channels to watch tv shows
I had to go like this
And see what the fuck was on tv
They have a footstep thing. I didn't open an app
I didn't open an application and just pick any tv show i've ever wanted to watch and watch it
No, we had to we had to scroll we had to scroll through our tv stations. Peter hates it
I mean, I guess we did kind of that makes no sense though. We don't even use our feet
That's true
Yeah, those of you guys that remember going to the tv guide channel
And watching the scroll the like one mile per hour scroll go steps go steps waiting to see what the fuck was on cartoon network
Ding ding ding ding. It's this guy ding ding ding ding
See you fucking later. Oh my god. Why did I what happened?
I made it
Oh, wow, there's an achievement for taunting 25 times in one game. Yeah, there used to be a channel on tv
Yeah
Did you guys remember that out very quickly?
Do you guys remember the tv guide channel where you had to literally there was the shit scrolled and you had to see what was on tv
No, i'm not 45 years old. Why do you ask? Whoa?
Because that guy
Used to be like that, right? You I apologize
My family had those tv guides like magazines. It was uh
It was a terrible time and you had to look through you had to find what was going to be on tv like on thursday
I don't know why this matters. Um, I who cares but apparently literally all it was was just for me to figure out
When reruns of the simpsons were on
Wow, literally the most interesting conversation i've had all night jama, so don't worry about it
Oh my
possess possess
One day they'll figure out that you can shoot the doors by the way, you can close your door
So just close and open your door all the time
What button is that? Oh fuck. Oh fuck. I'm going this way go back. Oh my god. They're coming up here right click
I need to get the fuck through this door now
This is awesome
Fuck I wanted to be that phone. Remember it doesn't clear your ectoplasm. So you also got a ding
I uh, I lost
Oh
I may have taken there. Oh shit
Oops, can I I have a ability but I can't area talk for some reason. Yeah. Yo, yeah, yo
I'm sorry
Hello hunters. Can you hear me?
Give it up luffy
Give it up solo
Give it up. Give it up. Give it up. Give it up. Here's how the story goes
It's no doubt with the treasure in the grand line. It's no doubt. I'll be king of the pirates. I'm gonna be king
I'm throwing it over there
I gotta get out of here though
Fell for it. You fell for it. You fell for it. You fell for it. You fell for it. You fell for it
I got a good spot
They learned
No, I hit them with a door. I saw that
And then they may have they may have become wise at that point. All right jerma, it's on you
I'll see what I can do. I'm going for it. Oh, never mind. We can all kill them now. Yeah, let's go for a quick kill
Jesus
No
Let's drop. Oh, no
Good game. Good game. Good game
Kraken I watched as a ghost objected you in the back of the skull
It was why did none of you attack the door?
Like I was hitting people with the door
I don't know. Sometimes they're useful
Well, I randomly like I just hit the voice chat button and I ask a stupid question don't let the door hit you
Breakfast let's do a peter griffin impression. It's like i'm like a
on the way out
Yeah, I was gonna say that as well
I'll be king of the pirates. I want to be king
I like that loadout. It's fun. Actually. No, I don't give me this regular weapon. All right, let's do it. Let's take them up
That was a good strategy. Hey, uh, hey jerma watch the floor
What's going on?
I'm spraying the floor. Oh, that's a spray show
Yeah
You use the z key
What is this? Is it spray your steam like avatar?
Yeah
That's what's aiming at the roof. It's just oh, yeah the roof
Oh, that's not bad. Okay
Alone in the dark
This is fun. I like how you had the basic strategy of just kill them fast and we did it
Yeah, just just just swarm. I think the swarm actually makes more sense
Just everybody can come out of their uh furniture and just go right click right click like let's just swarm them
Jerma, we're we're we're hunting the ghosts this round
Oh, yeah, but I mean when we are when we're ghosts
Oh, yeah, okay
But I mean we also die like crazy when people swarm as humans too
It's I think when your ghosts you're supposed to catch them
You're still supposed to catch them by surprise because if you're getting close you just fucking wreck them
Yeah, just like 50 damage a swing. That's kind of insane. Yeah
By the way, uh, if you have c4 use it in the final end like end round and it just eviscerates them it insta kills them
I wish we could throw our voices as the um humans. I think there's something up here
Oh, where are you at upstairs? It's it's like orange
Oh, okay jolly over by you gotcha. I'm coming to you
Got him in somebody back nice
I'll go get one
We only really need one person with a vacuum
And someone's got it. Yeah. Yeah, I got it. I'm like, okay cool luigi right now
All right. We got luigi upstairs seems pretty clear
For the moment for the time being we just did that he's a fan check it
Who was doing that?
It was like who was talking one of the ghost team like you shut the fuck up when you said he was a fan
I thought you were making fun of fans
Well, now he's a wheelchair like I don't want to make fun of wheelchairs and now he's dead do it do it
No longer a fan of yours. No, I don't think I will
Whoever on the ghost team is talking right now. You need to shut the fuck up
Someone someone's up. Somebody's up here. Ah, it's going crazy. You have the radar too jerma. I do. Yeah
All right. I see it too. I guess you just yeah, you're supposed to start shooting stuff. I guess I don't know
I would be the bathtub
It was me
This is like the reverse of that black mace of it there's something in somebody's in here
Oh, I think I found him. Yeah
There we go
I got the vacuum
Okay, I actually don't have the vacuum. I don't have a vacuum either apparently i'll get it. Oh, sorry. I was distracted
Should I guard this here?
Yeah, that'd probably be a good idea. All right, we're good. Awesome. You guys got any activity over there? I'm going back over here
Yeah, yeah
Okay, come on gwen really. Yeah, come on gwen. Where are you?
Okay, find anything jerma. I think there's somebody up here. It's going crazy right here
I tried the doors
Yeah the doors
Could be below. Yeah, I could be below. This is going crazy meat is going crazy. Okay
Oh, there's a whole basement. You should shoot guys a couple more times. No, where's it at?
In the basement
Ah, shoot, I should have known
Sorry, i'm not good with directions
Maybe it is the basement
Whoever's on the ghost team right now like just talking needs to shut the fuck up 49 seconds. He's talking about
Like don't think i'm annoying or anything like that
Imagine being like that pissed. It's like whoever on the ghost team
Where are you? I how can you be so clear but so far away at the same time? I don't understand
I don't understand. How could you be so clear?
Is that a real person? All right, watch out in the hallway bench
Now there's one uh in the hallway, dude
He just went down
He's a little fucking
Damn it. I didn't get out the door in time
Oh, he was a frying pan
He was so small
Hey, what was on the ghost team? Just shut the fuck up right now. Nice duck. Where'd you get a duck?
You got a duck what? That's a great duck there
Yeah, I got to duck him up. He's a fridge
I like the fridge
It didn't do me no good
Well, i'm just imagining
Being on the ghost team and hearing in the distance kind of footsteps and being like, you know
What was on the ghost team doing the fuck up?
It's just like wow
Psycho like real life if you lads would like we can do one more if not, I have no problem with calling it here
I'm down with whatever i'm having fun. I'm having a lot of this is great
Yeah, I can go another
All right, let me this is this is gonna be a good one here. I think I wanted to copy that sounds fun
Oh back at the museum level
I feel like the museum is hard for the ghost because everything's so
in such proximity
Jerm i have an idea follow me i'm behind you
Okay on it. So
These two birds
That's actually perfect
I knocked yours over. I'm sorry
Are we gonna make sure they are perfectly aligned?
Beak somebody said beak to beep
Wait, I shouldn't have said that
Oh, they can't hear us right now. Now if we're too close, it's too it's obvious
So if i'm in here and I do the um
genuinely
That like possess you do the pretend to be another person on their team. Do I have to be out of the
Object to do it. I think you'll automatically leave the object when you hit it. Oh god. Here they come if we could do something wacky
We could hold right click and aim at the same person and try to instantly kill them
Okay, right here. Someone's gonna come investigate in a second
For fuck's sake
Didn't work. I'm sorry. It didn't work
That's okay. It was a solid plan. They moved right at the last second and we couldn't get it
We're still alive though. So that's good
Yeah
Just like walking around
Oh shit we're blocking each other
Do it
Do it do it
Oh, no, please
Oh my god, I forgot that you guys hear that. Holy shit. I'm so sorry. I forgot that you're hearing that on the stream
I'm like just fucking with him like oh, he's definitely not the pig. I don't ever know
I i'm trying to do pig noises over there. So they think like oh he's pretending to be the pig
You know what I mean? Yeah, but you guys will hear it. I don't want to fuck with you guys
You good? Oh
Looks like bugleberry
But we still have up just one two
Two. Yeah, they got all four. All right, it's gonna be tough. I stayed in one spot the entire game. Did you really?
It was a cup of a brontosaurus dead
By the way, the shunt ability after you're dead is really powerful and i'm playing fucking soccer with the sun right now
Oh us pigs love to roll around in mud
Us pigs love rolling around in mud
Back here ow squeeze his hog
Oh, all right, we got it. We got it. We got it. Get him
I'm not gonna squeeze
It's very cramped in here
There's one thing that people hate. It's why I can't believe we lost like pig squealing noises. Nobody likes it
They hate it people. It's like dude. Don't like I hate that sound
That's a good game
Alone and alone in the dark illumination therma
Um, i've had the same profile picture for like at least five years or so
Okay, fair enough mine's probably since 2007 so I get you I kind of have this burned in my brain
Of hiding in team fortress. Oh, they can't hear me anymore
Uh, you'd change your profile picture and my name would be like fucking like inspector gadget
So people wouldn't know it was me. I gotta I could explain that i'm gonna ask you gemma why gas can
Okay, I I can give a really good explanation
so back in the day I used to make team fortress 2 videos, right and
I would if I was if I was germa
Like germa 985 in a team fortress 2 game with like a germa profile picture or something
People would see it and people would stand at the spawn and like high five and the whole game sometimes would get all messed up
So what I started doing
Is just starting making my name something completely different every single day and changing my avatar to something different every single day
So I could just nobody would even know it was me
Gemma i'm gonna be real. I was in the menu like the ready menu for 90% of that conversation
So I joined in until like the last two seconds of it
All right tldr
tldr
Uh back in team fortress 2 I used to hide so people wouldn't know it was me playing so like I could be I could get
Like a real gameplay that wasn't like five pocket medics and like five people outside the spawn trying to high five me
You got right pirate spy
Yeah, I I used to watch you gemma. I still watch you
Oh cool
That's cool
I'm watching you trying to act like a normal person
Fucking hilarious. Hey, I
I wake up in the morning like everybody else. I brush my teeth once a week
I
Wear pants sometimes maybe once a week
I'm a normal person just like okay. At what point do you clean up the blood of your last night's victim?
Yes
All right. Now I know I let you know. I know you watch now
I know you watch the channel speaks volumes
Now i'm good. Now. I know you watch uh, we got a jolly imposter over here, by the way
Hey, come here. Come here. What do you what do you want to go the word?
Do you do you want to go upstairs? What do you think they should be?
Wait, that's the real person. What? Hey, what's the emote button?
Post to fake people. Wait, how is that the real there was two jollies on the screen? Did I follow the wrong one?
It's v
Peace offering
Wait, why are there two me? Okay, somebody's fucking pretending to be me. I followed the wrong one
I thought you were the fake one
Geez, that's not me
Over here
My dick, bro
That's weird
No activity over here
creepy
I'm not getting i'm not getting any activity at all. Here we go. Somebody over here. No, they're moving. They're on the move
um
That's is this somebody here
He was the duck
Of course, he's the fucking duck
That spy is not one of us that heavy is a spy that sniper is a heavy that heavy
He's not one of us that one of us is you I made that joke like 10 years ago. God was it good
Listen, you didn't know I was the duck
You you had no idea
At this point you do the duck so often that like you aren't the duck now, you know what I mean?
I see the strats
Yeah
Uh
Did you find anything?
I am not getting anything
Just keep shooting
There's a little bit up in the run away a little bit in this room, but it keeps going up and down
It'll go down if they're taunting or jumping or moving in any way really?
Okay, so they so they can just move backwards and forwards
There's a ectoplasm meter on your right hand side when you're a ghost. I mean that fills up you become more
aware
Yeah, they can see you easier. So as long as you keep that low, he's totally one of these ducks
Are they all ducks? I could see that as a strap. I wanted to be all spacemen. The spacemen are fucking creepy
It's actually probably a really stupid spots
Just to be all be the same item and just be in the same room and spread out
Be like why would they ever do that?
Also, there's a little orc with the headphones on that nobody's ever been and I feel like that's a missed opportunity
In here in here trash can in here on me
trash can
plant
It's cranking. He's low
Got him. Yep. Oh, there's another one here. There's another one the triceratops
dinosaur
he's over here is a
zebra, oh
Nope, somebody's booted up that game boy
Oh, it's the smile go one
What the fuck rambert kite them don't stand still
I couldn't even fuck I got stuck on the stairs
I had my body was immediately died. Well, yeah. Okay. Good. Cool
I swear to god. I got stuck on the staircase. I couldn't move. I couldn't walk forward. No pressure. No pressure like I was
Pretend you're playing doom eternal
I said it just you call of duty zombies it
Yeah
Yeah, what was that like?
Chili
Somebody said don't come back to boston
I'm not allowed back in my in my hometown
Oh, that was amazing. I don't want don't come back here. I don't want you here
Like i'm gonna make a big announcement like boston i'm coming back i'm here what like i'm but i'm not annoying
Oh god, everyone's after you
You've changed I am the last one left
Would make sense. Yes
You're near the supply center if you can get there and kill yourself. No, that's that's bullshit
that's not a chance, but
Oh, they're they're on you. Oh god
That is so scary. Oh good try
That was scary
Nice. Nice. Nice. That was spooky. I love the bear
bear and astronaut there
All right, i'm gonna head back into discord and unmute and just thank everybody
Cool sounds good
Sounds good. Okay
I've unmuted
You know what that was pretty good for a bootleg prop hunt on tmachel. Yeah, it was fun. No, that was a lot of fun
Yeah
Uh, I think it could use a little bit of work in some spots and the balancing is weird
but and also the positional voice chat's like a little too low, but
Yeah, it was great. I enjoyed it
Yeah, I think that some of the weapons maybe need some uh tuning
But I think it was overall it was overall a solid experience. That's a lot of fun
Jerma, I I use a assault shotgun in real life
To defend against mosquitoes
And and they're expecting me to use that against ghosts
I mean it worked
I had well, I added the extended mag for my shotgun
So it had two barrels with three shots and that was just amusing the whole time
It also killed ghost pretty well too if you remember it's certainly my favorite gun. No, that was that was fun
Cool. Well, I appreciate everybody joining. Um, hey, let's do let's do this again. Let's do this again sometime. Absolutely
Let's let's get let's get a crew for another game whatever man what i'm down for anything
Yeah, i'm down for another game with the crew and also, uh, if you'd ever want to play phasmophobia again jerma
Anyone really here? Yes, i'd be totally down and I no longer weep. Was there a new update or something?
Huge updates. Yeah, many kraken. There's a vr update that has overhauled the vr mechanics of the game
Okay, i'm listening. I like the vr version but yeah, so it seems pretty kind of that's necessary but seems cool
So yeah, um
That was great. Thank you. Let me just give a quick. Thank you on my end to everybody. So it's kraken
We get jerma. We got jolly wancore. We got liam triforce rubber ross. We got she says and zam sire
This was a good group. I really really enjoyed this and I appreciate you joining. Yeah
All right, see you guys
Never fucking talking to a single one of them ever again. No, that'd be fun. Uh, it's been too long
So it'd be really fun. I like shit like this
You know, I know that look it's fun to jump in with like a group
Especially group haven't really hung out with in a long time
So, uh, let's not make it like three years this time check mod chat for the funny peter griffin video
Hold on the funny peter griffin video. Okay funny edit peter griffin. Wait, hold on. I can
What the fuck
I have to download this video. Wait a minute. Give me a second. All right, where's this file?
Did this is actually oh my god
Okay, let me put this up here. You see
We let's me on his team this year. I haven't been part of a team since I was with the four
Why can I not hear this
I
Let's be honest team this year. I haven't been part of a team. I can't hear this
Team this year. I haven't been part of a team. I was with the four peedish. It's for mine
We let's be honest team this year. I haven't been part of a team since I was with the four peedish
Okay, I can hear it I couldn't I don't know why I couldn't hear it before I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I could my OBS is fucking crashed right now. By the way. I can't close it. I
Something's wrong. It happened eight times. I don't know what's going on. I cannot even close over. I cannot close OBS
OBS is frozen. It was very weird. I'm sorry
Anyways, yeah, I couldn't hear it at first. Don't ask me why I have no idea. I don't understand computers
Alright, so here's the deal. Is it still playing? No, it's not right?
So here's the deal
It is. Alright, so here's what we're doing. So tomorrow I got I'm juggling up a schedule a little bit
That was really fun
To see all those guys again. We'll do that. Let's do it again soon. First of all, that's gonna be it for today. I
Wanted to do DOS tomorrow, but I want a little bit more time to curate some more
Because I have like 30 DOS games in Windows 3.1 games
I think I got a maybe get a couple more and shave some down because it's just so many
So we'll do that this weekend. But tomorrow tomorrow, we're gonna play wrestling Empire an update came out
That's apparently a ton of content and I really want to play it. So wrestling Empire tomorrow. We're gonna start not at 6
We're gonna start about 4 o'clock Pacific tomorrow and we'll get back into wrestling Empire
There's a GM mode now where you can just walk around town as the general manager of a league we're doing that, right?
Yeah, I'll be live tomorrow and then we'll be live on like Friday or Saturday as well
And I mean we maybe we'll do wrestling Empire again. We'll see but just a quick stream. I wanted to just go live
As Vinny was like, hey, you want to play this? I'm like, yeah, sure. It sounds fun. So just a quick one today
I'll see you tomorrow as always. Thanks for watching. We'll see you less than 24 hours from now. Good night
Goodbye 4 p.m. Pacific tomorrow. Good. I had a lot of fun. Hope you did too. The game was fun
It's my first experience really with prop hunt. I have to eat a shoe now. I did I I played Shido in the beginning
There's no batteries, but this is what that's what she'd have would have sounded like I pressed the buttons to play
It was just very soft because the Shido is out of batteries, but you can still very soft
You just couldn't hear it daily Shito. Okay, so who's still live from that group?
It's like Vinny or Kraken or Ross anybody still live from that group of people
Was everybody kind of taking off they're all still like let's let's go. Um, it's been it was very let's write Kraken
It's been a while. It's been a while since we have said hello to Kraken, which is cool to play with them
Okay, here we go. I will see you guys later. He's playing some kind of stream game. Oh, really? That'd be interesting
Hopefully I don't like
Ruin it. Is he doing like a stream chat game? Oh god
Be nice be be work well with others or I'm gonna be pissed. Alright, good night guys. See you later. Take care of yourselves
you