What is up guys? Jerma here with a gameplay commentary, but before I get
into that, I want to talk about the breast cancer awareness pictures that
you're about to see. Thank you every single person that wanted to participate,
that did participate. You guys supported an amazing cause. Thank you so much guys.
I was so happy that I filled the server a couple of times. About 50 or 60 people
were involved, so thank you so much. Here are the pictures. They came out great.
Everybody with a pink hat or a pink miscellaneous item painted. I heard a lot
of stories from you guys about how you're having family members deal with
breast cancer or you've had to deal with family members with breast cancer. And
it's tough. It's tricky for a lot of you guys and I appreciate the fact that
everyone came to that server and we all supported it. Everybody that's supporting
this whole thing, you guys are all awesome. Thank you. All I can say is thanks.
And you're supporting a great cause. So here is the gameplay. A lot of you guys
know that the Team Fortress 2 game engine is destroyed right now. So you
can't even play. I personally can't play Team Fortress for more than 10 minutes
without crashing to my desktop. So I am going to play Orcs Must Die which is a
new strategy tower defense hybrid game. Hope you guys enjoy it and hopefully
they fix Team Fortress 2 soon so we can all play again. Okay so here we are in
Orcs Must Die and I gotta tell you guys this is one of the best games I've
played this year. Haven't played a whole lot of games this year but this is
definitely topping the charts for me. If you are unfamiliar this game is a
hybrid of tower defense and strategy elements in the game. It's amazing. It's
really really great. So if you're one of those guys like me that grew up playing
Warcraft 3 and playing tower defense on Warcraft 3, you are going to absolutely
love this game. It is amazing to a million degrees. So basically what you
want to do, I only just started playing this game yesterday, so basically what
you want to do is you want to defend this thing over here. It is a little rift
area thing and you got this guy here that can protect it with you. But this
thing right here has to be protected and these doors over here if you look at the
top right of the screen, this door is going to open and this door down here is
going to open as well. What's going to happen is orcs, hundreds and hundreds of
orcs are going to pour out of those places and you have to defend them. You
have to kill them all or else they're going to take that over. So how do you do
this? One way is with your crossbow. You can shoot it like this. It has a couple
of little features too. You can do like a stun where it stuns them in place but
the cool part about this game and why it's sort of like tower defense is
because you have all these things you can put down. So I have started to
upgrade or I've already upgraded this poison spike trap and I use the super
boom barrel but I'm not going to use that right now because I'm going to use
the arrow walls but you can as you can see customization is really really
interesting in this game and look at how many spells you're gonna actually end up
getting. It's a whole lot of fun and yes you'll see what I'm gonna do here is
place a couple of spike traps over here. They're gonna come from this way too so
let's go over this way too. Bang, bang and this guy just got this guy. I don't know
what the hell he does. We're gonna put him right here though and we're gonna
put this guy rotate with R. Okay so as you see these guys are gonna shoot the
orcs that come down the hallway so let's unleash the horde and look at the top
right of the screen you can see where they're coming from. They're coming from
right here so let's get them. The cool part about this game guys is you can
string together combos and headshots and stuff like that. It is a very very fun
game. I gotta tell you right now like I said before it's one of the funner games
I've ever played and I've played a lot of games like this and this one is one
of the ones that takes the cake. It's awesome. Oh my god stun him. These
orcs are actually pretty sick. Oh they can get killed. I did not know that. I did
not know that. So yeah that's the first wave so as you'll know if you play tower
defense before you have multiple waves to deal with and you have a few
seconds between each wave so let's uh oh god put a couple more spike traps here.
Oh boy gotta go gotta go gotta go. Oh my god. Oh you know I'm gonna I need those
archers are sick. I need more of those archers. Oh boy this is not looking good
right now. I'm being really inaccurate. See if you look at the crosshair the
crosshair oh god stun him. The crosshair will shrink. It's kind of like in if you
know Team Fortress but oh they're killing my archers. In Team Fortress when
you are shooting the gun like with the ambassador let's just say for instance
if you have the ambassador. It's very very accurate on the first shot and you
see I'm collecting headshots right here. Bang bang bang bang bang bang me a bunch
of headshots baby. So it's kind of you get more inaccurate the more you shoot
and that's it for that wave. I gotta put some more archers down and the money is
in the lower right. So these cost 600. I'm gonna you know let's do this. They're
probably gonna come from the other side. Let's do this. You can't get my
impenetrable. Oh yeah they're coming to the other side. I'm gonna go. I'm gonna
have my archers shoot that way and I'm gonna shoot these guys coming around
here. See if that works out. Oh god the little freaks they run fast. Alright cool
cool. Stop where you're going right now brother. So there's a whole lot of
strategy and you can play this game a million different ways. I am selecting my
way I'm doing my own thing but you can do your own thing. There's endless
possibilities guys. It is a whole lot of fun. Highly suggest you pick this game
up. It is only 15 bucks. So yeah that is completely and totally worth it. So now I
have a break. I have a couple levels left to do. Let me pull out my you know what
I'm gonna keep this going. Let's keep these archers here. Let's do a ton of
archers. Oh baby. You think you're gonna get by this? I got my crew with me. My
crew are mad archers. Oh let's do it. Unleash the horde. Where they coming from?
Yeah I'll go I'll go this way again and they'll take out that other side. Oh let me
bang some headshots. Oh boy. Nice. Nice. How they doing? Okay they're doing
alright. They're doing alright. I better go over there and assist. No I don't
they don't even need me. They don't even need me. Okay yeah I might need some help
over here though. Unfortunately guys there is no co-op in this game. I really
wish there was. I really do. Because this would be so much fun with two or three
people. Oh my god. I'll be alright. I'll be alright. Come on let me let me just bang
some headshots on you guys. You can also pull out your staff or your sword
whatever it is. I don't have it equipped because I don't really use it to be
honest. And look at that. These archers. Oh they don't even stand a chance. So now
I'll put one more there and I'm gonna come over here and let's put a couple
this way because I'm gonna get smoked if I don't. Very cool. Let's do it. They got
it. They got that. They got it. I don't even have to go over there. They got that
covered. Wow this is awesome. So you're seeing I'm using the archers. I'm gonna
be using them a whole lot more. How's this side looking? Look that's alright. I
look good. Looking good. Freeze baby. And the more points you get after you kill a
group. Let's say see on the left there I just got a hundred points for stringing
together some kills. You spend those points you get skills and you can
upgrade your abilities which gives it like RPG feel to it. Oh it's just it's
fantastic guys. I gotta tell you it is fantastic. And here comes the final wave.
Let's go with a couple more archers over here just because I can. And let's do it.
I'm ready for you. They're coming on both sides. Little freak shows. Don't stand a
chance baby. They're good. Are they good over there? Let me shoot a long-range
stun. Oh boy. See some people just shoot violently like I like to be a little bit
more precise with it. Try and get some headshots. Get a few extra points. You
guys know the deal. Oh come on now. Oh what's that three in a row? Let me get a
three piece. Let me get a throw. Shoot. Oh this is looking kind of. No they're good.
They're good. We're good. It is game over. They got they got nothing. So I'll show
you the ending screen. He does a funny little dance. It's actually it's pretty
awesome. And here we go. Here's the dance. So yeah if you have not bought this game
already go buy it right now. It's on Steam. It is incredible. So I'll see you
guys all next time. Actually no let me let me show you this first. Got my point
see buy upgrades. See I have six skulls after doing a bunch of things. Oh this is
14 to upgrade and this makes it cheaper. It makes archers cheaper because they're
kind of expensive. But you get the deal and this eventually is gonna fill with
abilities and the replayability is just amazing. So yeah I hope you guys enjoyed
this and maybe I'll do more of this this series. Maybe I'll do more of this
because it's a very very interesting game. So I'll see you guys all next time
and take care everybody.