Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Nightmare House 2 for Scare Saturdays.
Alright, let me put my headphones in now, at least in one of the ears.
This is Scare Saturdays, this is Nightmare House 2. This is a Half-Life 2 Episode 2 mod.
A lot of people get confused sometimes. You have to have Half-Life 2 Episode 2 to play this game.
It is free, the link will be in the description, all that good stuff.
And it's fairly long, too. This might take me at least 5 or 6 episodes to play through the whole thing.
Probably a little bit more. We will see how this goes.
But, Nightmare House Prologue, I guess? Or should we just skip to Chapter 1?
Oh, we're skipping right to Chapter 1. Here we go, baby.
I probably shouldn't have done that. What if it was like, oh, this is the secret code you need to know to get into the first level?
I'm in my little cell here with my marshmallows on the sides.
Okay, it looks like the door. Is there anything in here I need to know?
Okay, Chapter 1 Rebirth. Should I just go this way?
This hallway is dark, so I'm assuming I just have to go this way.
Oh, my brain, you're hurting my brain with that. I can't open that door, let's just go.
Dive! Right off the bat, are you serious? The first second.
Oh my god, come on, dude. I'm not calm. I never have been calm, I'm getting out of here.
Is there a run? Can I sprint? Anything over here? A lot of blood.
Wait, I just saw like a twinkle. I just saw a twinkle. What was that?
Do I have like a flashlight or something? I don't. Security room.
All right. That does not look good. There's the flashlight. That's what I wanted.
Hey, you're looking at it. It's me on a webcam. A webcam-ception.
Am I locked in this room right now? What the hell? How do I get out of here?
Oh, okay. Like I said, just remove the lock. Good to know.
Hey, I thought you turned the lock off, you B-I-T-C-H. Locked in, it seems.
Is the kitchen over here? Looks like it.
Oh, damn. Oh, man. Chef Boyardee had a bad day today.
Anything else in here? I got it. I got the axe, now what?
Oh, god. Oh my- Is he dead now? Those bastards, man.
That seriously hurt my whole body. Oh, remember, I have an axe. Nobody can hurt me, I have an axe.
Oh, god. Which way do I go? I don't know where to go.
Oh, I don't like this game. God, no!
The bathroom is full of blood. That's disgusting. Can I break this? I can.
Any more cafeteria workers that are going to come out and punch me in the face?
Jump! Hooray. All right. Made it up.
I don't like vents. I do not like vents. Screw you, vents.
Something's going to just run right at me right now.
Don't look behind you. Don't look behind you. Don't look behind you.
Oh my god. Oh my god. I don't want to look behind me.
I did it anyways.
God damn.
Get me in this door. What's in here?
Hey, eat computer screen, whatever you are up there.
It's a button, I think. Come on, I'm pressing the buttons.
Oh, give me the gun. Give me the gun. Give me the gun.
Oh, for the love of god, please don't even tell me that something's going to jump through this door right now.
What the hell?
Oh, why did I shot the screen?
I shot at the screen.
Okay.
I'm losing my brain here.
All right, well, I'm going to shoot the absolute crap out of anything that comes near me.
If that guy comes near me, he's going to die. Hope he knows that.
Get me out of here.
Unlock the door. You said you're going to...
What the hell is that?
Where's my flashlight? Where's my flashlight?
Die, bitch.
Oh, god. Oh, god.
I just wasted like 10 rounds.
God, this game is tough to play.
All right, well, chapter two.
I think I might call it right here for this episode.
Oh, come on. I was about to say goodbye.
All right. Oh, my god.
Am I falling right now? Where am I going?
I need the axe.
Dude, dude, come on.
Okay, so how am I falling up?
God damn.
Okay, I will see you.
What the hell is going on with this frigging elevator?
All right.
So I'll see you guys. I'll see you guys all next time for chapter two.
And take care, everybody. I'll see you all soon. Bye.
Peace, love, resp...
Bye.