Dude, I think, uh, I think my computer's dying. Can you get it? Hold on, can you hear this? Do you hear that? It's going like
What the fuck is that?
Let me turn up the gain so you can hear it
This is freaking me out. All right. I'm gonna make no noise to make sure you can hear this
Do you hear that? No, not the fucking car driving by
I have to be careful because of
a ill-timed room
Will be horrible if I turn this. Um, I don't know. Anyways, my computer's making a weird noise
Uh, who cares? We'll just run it into the ground
Uh, hello guys. How you doing?
Hope you all having a good day
Hope you had a good holiday those of you that celebrated christmas. Hope you had a good christmas
Any other holiday that you happen to celebrate?
Uh, mine was good
Uh, I spent the last few days
Besides christmas, obviously the last two days in a row have been doing something very important
And if we could get a link, please
For the new year's eve stream 2019 nominations
The voting is live
Go vote survey monkey.com slash r slash germa nye 2019. There are there were
A lot of nominees
There are a lot of categories
they
Let's just put it this way
um worst noise of the year
I believe after combing through and removing some stuff that might should not have been there potentially and putting them all in
I think there were 24 nominees
And now I think there's like 20 or something. It's a lot. There's a lot
I couldn't remove them though
So many of them, I I can't remove them
But uh, they're available there's source clips for you to check it out source streams for you to see what the potential worst streams of the year was
That stream is going to be on new year's eve
so december 31st
Uh, we'll do pretty much the same thing. We did last year
With the only difference being I might not be in the studio this year because it might I don't think I can get the time
But I will be in my best suit
And we'll just comb our hair and i'm going to be in a tuxedo
Instead of at the studio, it's just going to be me in a tuxedo sitting in my fucking office
No budget this year. No budget on uh on the new year's eve stream this year, uh accidentally spent it all
Uh on the previous streams this year
small budget cut
Small budget cuts here and there but uh today
Um, let me tweet this out first
Today I was gonna play no more heroes today
For the wee i'm gonna play them both
I remember playing them a long time ago. I was gonna do no more heroes
but
I do I
I don't know. I can't get my wiimote
to connect
To my computer through bluetooth. I it won't do it. I don't know why
I've been sitting here for the last 20 30 minutes trying to get it to work
And I mean, yes, I am using an emulator. That's what i'm doing
Uh, I own no more heroes
I I
Not illegal not illegal. I own this shit
All right. The last time I talked about, you know, I like to use original hardware
There was a wave of like you fucking idiot just emulate it. What are you stupid?
And now that i'm trying to emulate it, what are you in a thief? I'm illegal get the fuck out of here
Put them in jail
Uh, I I did play on wii u on original hardware, but here's the thing about no more heroes
Uh, like I said, I own
You've seen me play on the wii u before
I own all this stuff. I own no more heroes the cd
Here's the problem
that game looks so
Fucking awful and plays
So awfully on the original hardware
It's you
No, I refuse to stream it on original hardware
That game runs at like 16 fps at 480p
It really does
And they did remake they'd made a ps3 version
But here's the problem
They didn't remake the second one. No more heroes 2 is only on the wii
I don't know. Why didn't they not do them both?
So what what would end up happening is I would go from oh look at the ps3 version. It's like hd and looks good
Okay. Now let's go to no more heroes 2
And it's uh, it's it's like 480p and runs at 12 fps
Play it who cares about quality. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, it's that game's hard
Do you understand how angry I would get if I played that on original wii?
I would be so angry
I would die like 15 times to the same boss because like the fps dropped to like 22 and i'd be like, where's the fps?
so, uh, i'm gonna get that set up i'm gonna try to figure out i'm gonna get a new dongle or something for my wii mode because
um
I just I don't understand like this. This is this is this wii mode is not broken or anything
Shouldn't be like it's a wiimote. It's like hey look, it's a wiimote
I'm trying to connect to your computer
I don't understand
He's naked. Did you replace the batteries? Yeah, this is brand new batteries in here
I think it's my computer. My computer's bluetooth just sucks
I figured it was just gonna work. But what a unit. Hey, thanks
If you ever want to play gta casino, hit me up. I'll invite you to my arcade. You can play on my machines. That sounds fun
Easy flexing sometimes
So instead of just scrambling what here's here's what was gonna happen
I was going to drive
to
Just go get a bluetooth dongle
But I it's like four o'clock. I'm not doing that right now. I'm just gonna what it's gonna do drew crew
We'll do it again tomorrow. I'll try it again tomorrow
And if look if for some reason I can't get it to work
Then we're just gonna play the original one anyways or the ps3 one i'll figure it out by tomorrow
So let's get drew crew on here
Uh, this is where we left off
I don't know what any of these really mean. Let me just make sure I say drew crew
So people know what i'm streaming
But all right, those of you computer, uh friends in here
Let me ask you this
Why would
So when I open up my bluetooth
And it's like
Looking for bluetooth devices
Why does it find a wireless speaker set from like six houses down the road, but it won't find my
Wiimote I don't understand
Is there something wrong?
Use the red button. Yeah, the the sync button
It's because bluetooth sucks
Wiimotes aren't bluetooth. Yeah, they are
Dude, the wii is like 20 years old. I yeah, but still
It's bluetooth device
Dude the wii is 20 years old
All right, I need to like I need to start streaming i'm actually kind of glad that we're doing drew crew tonight because
getting those nominations ready and
Bringing in editors to put videos and start like it's it's been like a kind of a two-day process here
So i'm glad we can just the wiimote is infrared
Yeah, there's an infrared camera on it, but the device is bluetooth. It's actually a bluetooth. You don't think I know my computer technology
Now let me just tweet that
Okay. What do you mean the wiimote is bluetooth?
It's a different bluetooth version
All right. Well, do I need to get like a special wheat like a what like a bluetooth 2 or something dongle?
Just get a wii. I
All right, I think this is where we left off
Jerma, why are you playing on original hardware? Just get an emulator. Jerma get an emulator
They're so much better
Why are you not playing on the original hardware? What's wrong with you? Just get away just go why use dolphin? What's wrong with you?
Oh my god, he's he's insane. I told him this long time ago. Why didn't he listen to me?
Don't nobody even remembers any of this shit. So i'll give you a quick
Look, here's a quick rundown of what happened to nancy drew so far
There was a crash somebody crashed
No, you can't hear it. No, you can't
No sounds
That's all good. I got it. I got it. I got it
Past when I was young. All right, let me try to give a as best as I can
I'm sorry to hear that for what it's worth. That's something we've somebody crashed the boat into the harbor
Or something. Oh, bye
All right, so I crashed uh, I crashed into the harbor and we're trying to figure out who crashed the boat into the harbor
Why somebody crashed into the harbor?
I don't remember any of this stuff. Okay, find dagny figure out the importance of the contents of the foot locker
Good thing they have this that's done. Got that one. Can't check that still have can't check. Yeah
Oh, yeah, that's right. Dagny ran away because dagny was responsible for all this shit
Man, let's take oh, that was a cell phone. It was a cell phone
Did we know what the password is yet? Did we figure this out?
When did this game come out?
uh
I have no idea
Password is puffed
Where would I get this info from? Yeah, she she knocked this over this way. There's a blood trail all the blood
These footprints they're huge
Only one guy in town has feet this size. All right, it's the guy with the beard
Go find the guy with the beard and say hey this footprints
Give me the password to her phone
All right. I'm gonna give you something strange that it's happening in my brain right now. This is very strange
I
Have I feel like I haven't left from last time
Like this i'm still streaming from the last time I streamed this
This is not a second stream. This is the same stream. That's weird
All right. I know what today
Do you know where uh dagny is? Do you know where dagny is the mink?
Missing I found a footprint near dagny's heater. It looked an awful lot like one of yours. What more?
I have nothing to do with it. Why would I take the mink? Where would I go?
My only home is here in the pub. I'll let you go
That didn't help at all. All right, so I have tiny key
All right, the souvenir is right. I have like I have toys and shit in here hook. I still want to figure out what to do with the hook
No, he no, he doesn't know. No, no, not at all. I like absolute zero
hold on like
I need to uh pull up the walkthrough for a second. I know drew crew. Don't worry
right now like
200 people's mouths just dropped. I'm not cheating. I'm just trying to find where we left off
I'm not this is not cheating
This is just finding where we left off
All right. Let me just go down to where we were
This looks pretty accurate
All right. Yeah, the guy the guy came out with a knife, right? He came out and he was like, oh and he tried to stab him
And then he walked away. That's what we left off. That's like the last thing that happened, right?
Okay
All right. Now we have to go
Uh, I gotta go to the crow's nest because I remember that he was like go to the crow's nest and I was like, okay
All right. Where's where's that cultural center?
Put on lipstick
No, I i'm not gonna say anything about anything
Here's the thing. I know I saw this in the pre-stream chat and it was actually kind of funny
Yeah guys, i'm not making any jokes until 2020
I'm not saying a thing
Because there's no more nominations. So this is just wasted effort for me to make a joke. Why would I do that?
It can't be used in this year. It can't be used next year either. I should just not turn my stream on until december 31st
That book mentioned this this is this is not canon. Maybe there's something here again not canon
We're in joke purgatory. Okay. Well, I just got this similar to that note. I found in magnus's journal
I can't I can't make it because if I say something if something happens, okay, let's just say
That like nancy drew
I don't know like drives down the road and like hits me with the car and I fall in the water or something
And like I climb out of the water and I talk about like a bulk of water joke
I don't know and then like people go. Holy shit. That was ridiculous. It's the most ridiculous moment of the whole year
It's like well, that's too bad
It's not gonna come up next year
All right. I need the history book
The crow's nest which stands in the center of the skip rot today adorned the original ship at one point
But was carted off to serve as a watchtower dubbed old stolka. It had remained on display in off limits to tourists for over 100 years
This is it solution is to divide into groups of six
No group touching another
divide into groups of six
What are you talking about groups of six?
Oh like that
Like that. Okay, so that's group six. That's a group of six
Somebody just said I just want to say fuck the drew crew
uh
I
I don't know what to say about that
because
They've taken over. There's nothing. There's not much I can say
Group six, right?
shit
Done got it. Wait, where's the last one?
This is a drew. This is a drew crew stream rise up
Wait, what is this groups of six?
How do I not have that?
Make one look on the right
12345612345
Divide the board into groups of six with no group touching another
123123123123123123
What I get wrong
You're missing one. I need to
Oh, I get it. Okay. Hold on. I have to so these can't be moved. Oh, I get you. I get you watch this drew crew
Can we get some i'm gonna get a fucking new emote called druze germa druze
Why am I like pandering right now? Like I played this I played nancy dru like twice on stream
What's the point of me pandering to you know, like this is like only the third time you've ever seen i've streamed
Like sakiro more times in this game and I don't have a sakiro emote. What the fuck am I talking about?
I streamed like red dead redemption 2 like seven times
All right, here we go. He's pandering panda to the crew
Uh remove all this this might be a while
No, if I go like this
I need to hold on. I need to fit one two more
Fuck. All right tennis ball noises. Uh, let me imitate that
No, I can't risk having a fucking best noise of the year. Are you serious?
That's all back loaded. Well, maybe I should try to do like a
Of really cool noise
And see if anybody remembers in a year
By not you could make this the worst stream of the year if I will if I wanted to
um
I don't know. Should I could I should I just like game everything? Well, because now you can't vote for it
Oh, no more dru puzzles. I got it. Don't worry. I got this i'm not gonna make this
We're just gonna start it everybody. It's been like 15 minutes
You are look how could this be the worst stream of the year you already got like a fuck the wiimote rant in the first 10 minutes
That can't be the worst stream of the year. What are you talking about?
true
All right, let's get him. We keep going
This is I think this is good. I think all this is good except maybe here
How did they ever expect?
I need to clean slate over here
I I definitely could not do this when I was younger
No way
I wouldn't have would you would you have done this?
No, you wouldn't have you would have opened up. You would have opened up like mario instead. You would have gotten this far and gone
um
I want to play ninja turtles
Because that was more fun for you. I would have just closed this and opened up turtles in time
Which is I mean, I think i've played that game 500 times from the age of like 13 to like 16
Do that right now?
I'm not i'm not gonna do that right what?
Am I gonna play turtles in time right now?
I mean, it is one of the best games ever made but I can't i'm not gonna do that right now
I'm not gonna do that right now
I'm not doing it right now. I'm not doing it right now. I i'm not gonna betray the the dru crew
I'm not gonna go get turtles in time right now
Do it later. No, that's like a whole stream. I could be I can do that game on hard by the way
Fuck. Okay. Hold on
How do I make this two?
He's so bad
You wouldn't have done this you would have you would have
You would have
Gone out and played tether ball. You wouldn't have done this
I know because I wouldn't have done it
And I still can't do it at 34. I want to go outside and play tether ball
Fuck turtles in time. If there was a tether ball court behind me. I would go do it right now
It wouldn't even be turtles in time. It would be i'm gonna go play tether ball
Wait, hold on. How do I make another little one in here?
I know this is right. I know it is
This guy actually went outside as a kid
Yeah, and I got hurt a bunch of times and now apparently i'm paying the price for it because my rib cage hurts every day
so
Maybe you should play fucking nancy drew. Wait, hold on bottom right doesn't need that upper dot
Doesn't don't I can't take that one off
The ones that are the one with the pegs on them are the ones I can't be um
Split the bottom right into two
This is not possible. I mean it has to be possible because an eighth grade girl beat it. It has to be possible
Hold on. Let me get let me do no no click maps. I'm doing this one on my own
No, this is right
This is no, no, no, no shit. Hey, hey, hey. Hey, I did it on my own
Now i'm just gonna figure out how to make these two
Oh shit
Yes
It's and he looks injured
In the ice pack
Uh, so am I gonna help him or am I just gonna say oh no
Okay, what was it? What was the point of that wooden gear?
All right. Let's go talk to him. Let's see what's wrong with him. You all right. Oh, um, hi
Uh, what happened? What happened to your face?
gunner happened specifically
Gunner threw a bottle at me. That's awful. Why would he do that?
Does he need a reason it's happened twice before
Now do you see what i've had to deal with all these years a lesser man than I would have practiced things
And quietly retired to a nice beach somewhere. I could easily take my work to Reykjavik. I don't know why I stay
Some you could but you want sense of hope maybe you have you've got a great thing going on here
You've got
Fucking a whole business here. I'll take care of that motherfucker. Don't worry. Dagny is missing. I'm worried something happened to her
Missing are you sure she didn't go for a stroll?
No, she's gone left a heater even once the entire time i've been here
that's
suspicious
Hmm, if she hasn't returned soon, i'll organize a search party in the meantime. Try not to worry. She's a tough woman
I'm certain she'll manage. Goodbye
Bye now you stay you stay here. You you you you got a whole thing going on here. Look at what you
You i'll take care of that motherfucker. Where is he?
Hey good day you throwing bottles now, why did you hit soren?
Hit soren. He said you threw a bottle at him. I did no wailing tailing thing of the sort
He's a liar is what he is and he's trying to make all good not look bad
Uh-oh, he said it's not the first time that's happened. It's not the first time this has happened between you two
We have fought before
I but this time he is a liar. I'll let you go
Why would I stop why would I stop there?
Why would I stop there?
Run along girl. Uh, why would I stop there?
Hey, did you throw a bottle at that guy? No, he's a liar
Okay
You sure he said he's he said you've thrown bottles at him like more than once
No
Okay. Have a good day
That's it
Yeah, run along girl. Okay
What there's nothing else for me to say here
Why would I have nothing else to say? I need this password
What do I do with this?
It's not one two three four
It's not one two three four. I know it's not
I'm 99 positive. It's not one two three four. It might be four three two one
But I don't think so. How was my christmas? It was great. I hope yours was good, too
Did you try it? No. All right, i'm gonna i'll try the damn one. All right, i'll try it here
If that worked I would have been so mad
All right
Let's go. Let's go back to the cabin
Didn't I get something? I got something out of a dog bed. So let me go there
Fuck this boat by the way
It's so easy just to turn around on this boat and i'm trying to go over here. I'm just trying to go the all right
Can you first miss boat? I was supposed to beat this before christmas
But I got I got so fucked up, you know, I have a lot of things going on
All right. Let's go to the captain's quarters
What what the fuck does what does this thing do I still don't know what this thing does
Not a single clue on earth
Uh zero one two three, maybe
Hold on a minute
I'm just looking up the watcher
I need to get to a fucking puzzle. We have so much stuff going on
There's so much stuff. I have so much stuff in my inventory. I haven't played this in like seven days
Let's just get on the right track
It's okay to be on training wheels as long as eventually you take them off
It's a shameless cheater. Call it what you want. It's I call it
Filling potential dead air
It's just for it's just to get us on the right track. You can take the training you can take the wheels off soon
All right. The password is the wacky digits on the back of your mom's credit card
Oh is this
Get it
Yeah, yeah, it's a bunch of crazy funny numbers. Go ahead and read them to me
God damn it
All right. What is this for?
That was the best chat joke 2019 that ain't even a category you guys can put that one as if you want
What is this?
I should be able to interact with this
I don't understand
This I should be able to click on this
the fuck
xd this guy sucks
Ow
I did so much of this shit out of order
You have to you have to have like been told to go to the bed frame for the bed frame to be activated
So I have to scroll back up this walkthrough and find
The note that dad left me for what's in the bed frame
You know what i'm saying?
I can't just click on the bed frame
He's using a walkthrough. I'm just trying to get us to his phone. We're all right
I'm gonna type in bed frame into find on this page
bed frame
Here we go. All right
Got it
There's a note here
Something about a bed frame with a bed frame note
Magnus's notes
Find all five pieces to really yeah in box pattern
That's the note, right?
Okay, slow down. I can't freak out here
I'm gonna relax
Because we're so out of order
Dude, I have to go back to when there was a struggle
I know I
I cheated how did I get it wrong?
I'm cheating right now. How am I getting this wrong?
scuttlebutt
It's scuttlebutt the password is scuttlebutt
enter
so
I have to read the clue
For what the password is if I get the password, right?
It doesn't work unless I have read the clue for what the password is
so
If dagny told me what her password is. Hey, I gotta I want to look something up. What's your password?
Oh, uh, it's scuttlebutt. Oh that didn't work
Oh here. Sorry. Let me write it down on a piece of paper for you and then you look at it
And then you can get in my phone
I'm getting anti-cheatable. Where's the note?
Give me the fucking okay
We did this so out of order. It's not even funny. Okay, we have to do
Uh dagny's note, where is it? Where's these notes? God damn it. All right, let's go drew crew assemble. Here we go
Imagine hiding gameplay mechanics behind finding notes in the world
What the hell?
Okay, read dagny's note
Look at the barrels. Okay, explore the hold of what?
Dude, this is back up when we did the crossword puzzle
Imagine cheating in a nancy drew game
Imagine needing to cheat in a nancy drew game. That's what you should be saying
Dagny left her suitcase at the cultural center. She also okay, so I didn't I already I have this note
Don't I have this fucking thing?
Hey, can you like go walk away again or something? Soran's using the desk right now
It's not even a puzzle. It's just you gotta like open the right container and find the right note
To tell you to click on the puzzle
What?
Why?
What what?
Where the fuck is this note? I'm gonna actually get pissed off at this game
Dagny's note, okay explore
What's the hold explore the hold
Go down the stairs at right enter through the door. Look close at barrels examine the middle barrel bottom
Dagny's note is in there. Why in the name of god would there be a note?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to get a closer look. I'll need a distraction first like this barrel here
Exit and go down the stairs at right enter through the door
Look close at the barrels
Wait, hold on like you're talking about like over here
This game is on drugs i'm definitely not on drugs
Wait, hold on
I'm not on drugs. I'm not on drugs
Look, I swear
I promise i'm not on let me look look
Look everybody i'm gonna use I I just downloaded this app on my computer. It's probably it's for the wii
You know, like that's the trashware that was on the wii store. Yeah, this is called
drug test
You know, one of my favorite calls is well, that's uh, that's like actually like a radio show
Wait a second everybody relax
Hold on. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. This is important. I'll be right back. Just give me a minute. This is important
Let me prove to you guys
All right. Everyone thinks i'm on fucking drugs
Bullshit bullshit. Let me put let me turn my fucking wig app back on to make sure you guys can we can see this
All right. Fine. Here we go. Let me
Okay, click that here we go. Okay, what's the first one?
marijuana, okay
I mean give me you gotta give me a fucking break. What's the next one cocaine? All right. I just I don't I don't do that. So
I don't do that. I swear to god. I don't what's this one molly
Hey, hold on
What's the next one on the list alcohol? Oh drunk right now
What's what's this what's this one
Oh, I gotta get the dlc I gotta get the dlc. All right, I guess what's this one?
P dlc
Hold on. God damn it. Do I really have to do this shit?
All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Let's let's let's open up the next one. What is it? I got the dlc
It was 15 bucks. God damn it crack. Okay, let's go
pain in the ass
Let me just take a quick sip of my water that I just poured
Oh
You can't nominate it for anything. You can't nominate it for anything. The ball is closed. You can't
Nominate it to anything. You can't nominate it. It's over. It's not nominatable. It's not on that list. You can't nominate it. Sorry
You know what? This is great. I could do whatever I want today
I could do anything
I could do anything and this i'll never be nominated. Holy shit. I got a free pass for whatever I want
What's going on?
What is going on?
I need to recreate the numbers written in the corner
Did I pee into the weed disc tray? I don't understand how that works. What is this?
Is it year a year and a date
I don't know re recreate the numbers written on the corner of the big oh wait 19
18 20
19 18 19 18
Fuck all right. How does this puzzle work? This is five. I don't understand what's work
The water stopped but the gate still shut
Nancy
Are you all right? You did this get me out of here
Worst joke of 2019 you can't nominate that for anything and I don't think I don't even think that's the case
Let's see. Damn it. Do I really have to do this shit?
All right, fine. Fine. Fine. Let's let's let's open up the next one. What is it? I got the dlc
It was 15 bucks. God damn it crack
Okay, let's go
Pain in the ass
I don't think I don't think that's that bad. I think that I think I would laugh at that if I was me
What are these images?
I
Is the best image of the year but it's too bad none of this counts like none of it counts
Holy shit, that's fucking hilarious
somebody please somebody please go to the next level somebody like
Like make me the same make me like white with like the
The like tan down the middle and the eye line the eye lashes and the hair, please somebody do it
Make me have orange hair
All right, that's fucking fantastic
Someone's trying to get me out of the picture. Oh, that's an understatement. It looks like i'm eating
I look like a gerbil or a hamster
Looks like that was the right decision. It's like a hamster with ice cream sandwiches storing them for winter
Here whoever attacked you dropped this in the hold
Okay, maybe it will be of help to you. Definitely. Thanks
I'm bad at the not getting locked in things aspect of a case. I'm not on drugs. I don't do drugs mysterious objects
Everyone has their gifts later. Bye now
All right
Can't check that still have to can't check that off yet
It's a metal crank. What was that for?
Hey, can I nominate this stream so far? It's the best stream of the year
Something about nancy drew. I don't know what I don't know what nancy drew does to me
It it I it's like I I go I go fucking crazy. I don't know what it is. You know, i'm saying what's what's with this?
Easy enough
Let's see. There we go. All right, what's the first i'm gonna do messages
Let's check on the bank
This is an automatic account text. Please confirm your bank account deposit of
2455 dollars
with a task message
for gulf coast treasure find
confirm
This is the automatic account text. Please confirm your bank deposit of 5500
From mr. Fallon for santa fe investigation results
confirm
$12,000 for from lure for petra extraction. Am I incriminating? Why is she just incriminating herself with her bank app?
Why would you put this in the notes?
Why wouldn't you just use code words or something?
Why wouldn't you say like this is for uh, cleaning up after the cat if you know what I mean?
Like oh, okay. Why like for lou for petra extraction. This is all illegal shit, right?
Yeah, there's an attack. I'm talking about the attached message not the bank
The automated bank app wouldn't be like yeah, this is for uh, this is for would you uh, you know
This is million 5.5 million. Whatever. I moved the decimal point. I don't care
I'm very excited for the maiden voyage. The deck looks darling. I put you into our festival donor section as ms
mrs. Dagny silva de soto
Uh, just dagny silva now. Thanks turns out my life partner wasn't so lifey after all
Alicia's returned to the states. I thought she was talking about how they were dead
Okay
I had no idea terribly. Tell you sorry to hear that condolences plenty of fish in the sea single and ready to mingle
No time like the present. You're an absolute gem, etc
All right, buddy fucking relax
It's fine. Uh, I always do i'll survive. Just leave me alone
Fuck out of here, dude
All right. What about uh magnus so magnus knew he was being followed something's following me closer. Lock everything down
Okay, mr. Melodramatic. Are we starting to just get a little paranoid? What about the dock pylon? Are you dropping that?
I'm serious
You'll have to wait on the final piece. We discussed
What i'm not gonna do accents. It's gonna be boris impression. You can't even look for it. So, you know, well fuck it
I don't even care. Uh, what are you where are you putting it?
Uh bed frame on the ship magic circles, uh venn diagrams. The key is the overlapping sections
There are five pieces. You have one. I have one. Where are the remaining three? How could they have gotten so lost?
You're not making sense calm down have a breath eat some eat a banana
All right. Now I can actually go to the bed thing. That's all I wanted
By the way, if you do have a strong opinion on anything
I recommend you go
uh, take a few minutes of your time if you feel like it
to vote for the
23 different categories for worst and best of the year for 2019
Check out that survey monkey link. That is a real link
Check it out
probably take you a
Because there's a lot of clips it's a lot to go through so maybe
Take your time with it. Make sure because that once you vote that's it and we will see the results on new york
Why are you still using survey monkey because uh, because the four hundred dollar yearly activation went through
Uh automatically three or four months ago
Because I didn't cancel it. So
That's uh, that's why
So I have but might as well use the damn thing
Yeah
Yeah, I know. Yeah, and guess what?
Uh, I probably will forget to cancel it again after this stream because it's I will be have been kind of over that stream
And moving on to the next stuff and we'll see you next year. Uh when I have not canceled my survey monkey
Ridiculously overpriced hundreds of dollars per year, I guess subscription
pictures of a blank wall
Either cancel it now losing it or I can't this is a clue i'm busy
All right, the back wall
All right, let's go to back to the captain's quarters
So now I can actually look at the bed
That fucking trophy picture is so funny
He's too busy to save four hundred dollars. Well, I already lost four hundred dollars
I can't get that back. It went through like four months ago
So I have like seven months to not spend four hundred dollars again
Why is it so bright?
This is this is droopy the dog like going to heaven
Droopy the dog
All right. This is droopy the dog like does too much molly
What the fuck droopy the dog does two smokes too much cracking that goes to heaven
What the fuck?
Oh
Hold on. Hold on
This is so fun
Well, let's try this one. Let's try this one
This is fucking fun. Hold on. Where is it?
Uh, I just saved it. Where the fuck is it? Where's my other droopy the dog image that just saved
You're literally an oblivion character
Okay, I have to fucking focus for a second
You need to do that as an emote
All right, everybody relax
It's it. We we're good. Let's go back to where we were going
Check out the bed
Just right here. This is the original captain's bed, then I should take a closer look
There have been diagrams this is gonna be great
Can't wait for this one
I'm just scratching my back
That's fucking really itchy. Okay. Okay. I got it
I need to place the numbers inside the circle so that they add up to the totals within the overlapping sections
Okay, so what place the numbers so that any total any total shown in the overlapping section is the sum of those circles individual numbers
um, okay, so
Whatever is in the circle
How is just so this would this would be seven? Okay
but
You gotta
Holy shit
This is easy
I mean
Oh, I don't nothing has to spin. Oh, wait, wait. No, this is this is easy. Nothing has to spin
Cool. All right. I thought I had to like spin these things around
so, uh
Let's see the sum
Of everything in the overlapping circles. This would be 33 what?
Total shown in the overlapping is the sum of those individual numbers. So like it it would have to be
We'd have to make 80 we'd have to make 23
So that would be
I still I don't I still don't get it. I still don't understand
I'll get it in a second
Uh
All right. This is the last droopy image for a while and then we're gonna move on
This is the final droop with the dog
This one's pretty damn good though
It's just droopy the dog hitting his favorite jewel
What do you mean? Not that one? Jesus
Christ
Oh my god, how do you do this this quickly this yeah, how do you even do this this fast?
It's not even possible to do it this fast
It's been like 12 minutes
This is ridiculous
This is now the thumbnail. I know it is
Right click set as desktop wallpaper
Here's one that isn't droopy
Oh my fucking god, what is going on?
This is just the Grinch. This is like the Grinch with no makeup
eating spaghetti
All right. That's enough. That's enough. That's enough. I'm done
All right, we're gonna do this diagram thing
Oh fuck
I don't know. I don't know. Um
I don't know
I'm not gonna lie. I don't know
If it were me, I mean it is me what I mean if it were me it it it is me
So, of course, it's me
What I would do? Um
place the
So, okay place the numbers
Any total shown in the overlapping is the sum of the circle of some is the sum of those circles individuals the sum
So I need to make
I need to make
23 here
What's 23 like eight seven and nine?
And we got a calculator
What is eight nine and seven? What does that do?
Windows has a calculator. I can't i'm too busy
He's looking at the answers on the other monitor. I know i'm not
Just look at the walkthrough. No, i'm not doing that. Not yet, you know, sure. No, not yet
No, it's okay. Here we go
All right, so that's 23
So now I have to make 10 here so I need one and then this needs to be 13
Seven
Wait, we don't have six. Wait. No, hold on a minute there
All right
This is actually pretty good. This is a fun puzzle
If you know every single puzzle in your entire game is based off of weird like logic math problems
Okay, now we need to make 10 first of all, let's get this is seven
So we need to make seven out of the okay
There's your seven
There's five
There it is
And if we get more of these sketches i'm fucking jacked up right now. I'm so
I'm so fucking excitable
Why I don't know why you know why i'll tell you why here's why really know why i'm so excitable right now
Because that new year's eve stream is the nominations are done and if it's votable
By the way, if you if you have some time if you want to check out those nominations
They're there and I can't wait. That's sure is gonna be a lot of fun
All right, let's go back to the uh, the thing where I can put the it's like to go back to the cabin in the woods
Very yeah
He's plugging it
Yeah, yeah, you come on. You gotta plug the stream. That is a big one
That's a big that's like the biggest stream of the year
Don't you want to know?
What sound was the best sound of the year?
Don't you want to have wait to find out which peter was the worst one?
That one don't count
Is like in a happy mood right now because i'm gonna play no more heroes tomorrow hopefully well
I was kind of mad earlier, but not anymore
All right, let's get these
What's three plus three times three? That would be
Would be six
That'd be 18. Thank you
I'm not stupid
This song where is it from?
That was wrong. That was actually wrong
Was it though?
What was the question again?
This looks like it goes
Okay
Oh, this is wrong
Looks like i'm still missing still missing a piece of this puzzle is stupid
North american education lol. Yeah. Yeah, you know, it'll be great if we could like
If we could redo our entire educational system
That's correct
We need it. We need better schooling. We need better
We need better schools in this country
See if I was a presidential candidate, I would get on stage right and during like the debates
Mr. Albertson, uh, so sorry. Excuse me. Senator Albertson
uh during your time and senator you you made very clear that you would like to have a
Educational reform can you explain why that's your policy?
And I would simply say yeah, I will tell you exactly why
I'm 41
And do not know my multiplication tables
I didn't know how to write a check until I was 20
And I still don't understand
At all and then I would stop and I would freeze for a second and my and my eyes would cross
And then I'd blink a couple times ago. Sorry. What was the question?
And even if I got fucking booed off the stage
It wouldn't even matter because then they would know like holy shit our education system sucks
This guy's get this guy out of here or i'd get a standing ovation. What a gaffe
Legit I have never wrote a check. Yeah, we we have like they can think of it like like our like our sex education, right?
even something like just
Just let us know some stuff. You know what I mean? Like
I let us know just some stuff
Every okay, there was health class
And health class did this thing where I know a lot of you guys probably had a similar experience and correct me if i'm wrong
health class
was typically
Some old lady that when we got to the point where we were going to do sex education
It was like, oh my god. Lol. Look at the lady. The old lady say the word penis. Isn't that so funny?
We weren't learning anything
Okay today kids
What I would like to do is yeah up and up to the page 20c to see penis and everyone would be like
Oh my god, she said it. We got to rethink how we're teaching our children
Otherwise, you end up like me. That's your fault
No, no anything but that
I would love
Just a simple. I don't know why they don't do this. Yeah, sure. We're going off right now and i'm going off
I'll tell you i'm hot tonight
Why don't we just have a simple life skills class?
What's the why don't why can't we just do that? Why do we have to why can't we just do a life skills class to?
This is gonna sound crazy
But I don't know i'm gonna get a lot of shit for this people gonna make fun of me. I know you are
But uh, but this is this even a life skill. I didn't know how to tie my shoes correctly until I was like 15
That is that a life skill. It might be a life skill. I didn't really get it
I just kind of mushed it up and and
And like did it wrong every time imagine. They just taught us how to tie our shoes. Do they they do
Yeah, they do when you're like four
But they should be repeating that information into like our early teens and early 20s
Fuck, okay. Let's go
No, but all jokes aside all fucking around
They we got to be told about like our tag tag system life skills writing checks credit
How many of you guys in this chat right now even know he's still what fucking credit even does?
It took me until I was like fucking 28. He's right manga s
Thank you. Derma. Your sex edit understanding is on par with goku
I don't I don't understand that reference
What do you uh, okay now I do wait. Hold on a minute here. Hold on
Do you guys still think that at 34? I still I don't know what like
Sex is
Am I do I just not know this?
I still don't know what it is
What the fuck
Somebody says to teach me
No, but seriously we like i've said this before
But I think we got we got to reimagine how we're teaching our children and bringing up our students
They got to be ready
And we're we're teaching them stuff that they're not we're not preparing them
Just play nancy drew mr. Comcast
No, this is important stuff
Do I still know what this does?
Your time is up. Mr. Albertson
That was just me talking the whole time as the senator
Uh, mr. Albertson, you spoke 12 minutes over what you were supposed to
And can you please stop doing the i'm crossing my eyes to make a point?
joke
Sorry. Sorry. Yeah going
My fucking eyes hurt
Haven't can't can't check that off yet a filibuster
They don't teach taxes. No, they don't
No, you're just you're just expected
to just
Hey, hey, you know like the the 700 pages of tax code. Did you know that right?
No
Oh idiot
Get good
Oh, you cannot treat something as important as as as tax code as like playing dark souls
You have to actually go to wiki pages and like and and government websites to find out certain thing. It really is playing dark souls
Taxes is just dark souls on paper
Oh, I um, is this is can I take that deduction? I don't know. Can you?
Um, I don't know
Look it up on the wiki
Oh, okay. I guess i'll i'll look it up on the wiki for every question. I have like yeah
Wait, yeah, you don't know that. Why do you not know that?
Uh, okay. I I don't know. I've never done that before
Holy shit, dude. I did I did it in less than two hours
Okay
Can I help why is everyone in your world an asshole?
Is it true that the town's in financial trouble? Uh
In the spirit nobody's nice in this like the universe apparently we've always had a bit of trouble everybody's horrible
No spas no ski resorts. We're a little uh
barren elizabeth
Bless her. Oh, oh, oh fuck. What the hell man. Come on, but it's just not oh, I hurt myself
How did this happen what is this and why do I have it in my hand the way the ship writes yes
Why are we playing with this back in the black of course
Where did I get that I don't know where I got that I don't know where that's from it just was here apparently
What the fuck that actually hurts?
Why was your glove found up near the volcanic caves?
My glove
I'm certain it was yours. Aha my glove. I
Lost it. Aha when I was trying to carry a bit of wood down from the hills. I was rather focused
I can get a bit
Adle-brained I found the most interesting carving you see in
Part of an old tree near the caves. It may even be from the 14th century or even earlier
Where's the carving you brought back? Oh
It needs to be treated before it can be exposed to the air again. If you'd like I can show you later on
Uh, sure. Have you always lived here for 12 years in total?
Two before university 10 after others seem to think of you as an outsider
gunner, especially
Oh for the love of him. I was born 10 miles away
And that means you don't live here to him. Yes, I mean to everyone. Yes, I don't I hate this game
I'll never be from skit brought because I wasn't born here. You know, I mean that
Upper secondary school was a nightmare with these people
I may not know much about skip brought but there are lots of unpleasant people in my line of work
Sometimes persistence helps. Oh, i've tried i've bent over backwards to put on this festival for them and yet
No one invites me out. I'm not welcome at the pub
Spending my birthday alone is getting to be a real downer. Bye. Bye
Well on with it
Bye
Spill your guts to me
All right. So fine. Still have can't check still have to do that. All right
I got that shit now. I have to do
What the hell do I do now? Oh, right with the bricks. Remember the brick walls?
Posture check it should be okay
um
Where uh, where was that? There was that room. I was looking at the wall
She's like, oh there's something behind that wall. I think it's back here, right?
Yeah, it's down here
And then there's a back wall
over there
Where is this wall?
With the brick. Yeah, there's like a wall somewhere right there. See
What's with this wall shine flashlight at the wall use the hook
What just happened?
Hope that shit i'm trying
I heard it
It was like a
Wait, I heard something else
Oh
Try the gear
Frank
No, what about the note?
No, this is pressure cooking. So this is this is how i've gone with his old thing. Well update gone on his head
What what's this picture for then? Where's her phone?
I don't think I can do anything with this yet. No, I can't do anything with this
Shit
Can I go back down here
All right, um
I don't know. What the what is this for?
This is for something too. I just don't know what
Derma darling be careful. I'm trying
He doesn't know. No, I don't know
I'm gonna go try to figure out this puzzle or uh open up the walkthrough and just and and lie to you guys and pretend
Like i'm playing the game
Which one do you think I should do?
You know what I mean? I wonder if I should be like, let's see. What was that one?
Three. No, that's not right. One two and then eventually get it even though i'm looking at the paper over here on the right
um
Six and then what was the last one? I think it was three five
Oh, no, that makes sense
Something within the ship must have unlocked elsewhere
He's bad at the game. No, i'm not
Nothing unlocked on the ship
What did it unlock?
Oh the wall the wall the wall
That would make sense, wouldn't it?
Let's see room back. Ah
It looks like it was concealed in the ship's lining. There we go. All right secret
Let's get in here
Oh, what's this? Looks like I need to press another math problem according to these numbers
Light up all the numbers by pressing the correct sections
It's like a dartboard
Oh, you can only do a certain amount of times. All right, over said
I'm gonna get these ones shit. Okay, why did that make like a you open the door sound that that made like a
Oh, it's just the boat is making all kinds of weird noise
All right. Hold on. Here we go. Someone dm me the history and origin behind germa walked
um
It's just the way that I walk man
All right. Ah
This is so easy a child could do it
That's fine. Is it so easy for a child to do it like me?
Here we go
It's a machine of sorts, but some pieces are missing
It's just an adjacent puzzle
There's more shit missing here
What the what how is this? I need two more gears
nancy
Egg
At least I get to dump some of that shit in my inventory
All right. So now I got that
That's all I can do here. Is there anything else in this room?
Not I don't know the secret rooms
There's jam a hook in there
That would be like a decent idea. I think what she says. Hmm. You're doing it wrong. Um, yeah
Yeah, I think so
You'd be right
Uh, i'm gonna go back up
Did I do everything I can in here? I think so
What am I missing
Dream crew he requires aid
Yeah, what should I look at now?
Although I I would assume none of you, uh
None of you guys will really know
You know, I don't think anybody's going
I i'm it's either it's it's me. I gotta figure this out on my own
You know what I mean?
Because even if you guys tell me what to do there get out of my pub
Enough already just leave me be I never asked for you to intervene just stay where I can't see you
We just got thrown out of the pub
To follow him. Where are you? Oh, wait, this is like I can touch his stuff
Elizabeth I love you so much. I feel like it's been forever since college
I wish you were here with me in Paris. The food is amazing. The skyline is to die for how's old moody magnus
Has he gotten that ship obsession thing under control?
Sorry to hear about the demotion and all that financial trouble with soren
the
Gag
The gag the guy sounds like a real weirdo
I'm sure it's got nothing to do with you. And besides you always said you wanted to handle the people side of the festival
uh more
More more of this. I don't need it
Got it
Hmm. There's a hole in the cellar
uh
Okay, I think I know where that goes anything else over here
I think that's it. Let's see check. Check it with a lock and a cup of roof. Can't check. Can't check that off. Yeah
Okay
Use the gear. Yeah, so i'm just gonna go back to the uh, well, hold on blast
What did gunner do this time? What did gunner do this time? I actually get some more coffee
And I can no longer bear it
A lot he just has a
Unconventional way of showing it. Do you know what he said? Why there's so many different kinds of dog food
Go to a pet store. Why is it like 700 different dog foods? I don't think that's which one's the good one. Fuck
Madness, but I know you
Untrue words still hurt
What if magnus is hiding from me? What if he doesn't want to be found?
Please leave me alone. I need time to think
I just talked over all that and it was probably important
No, I buy
I buy I did dog food elimination
Okay
You don't know what that means. That means when you have a dog and you go
I really want to take care of my dog. I want my dog to eat. Well, I want to make sure that I have
He's getting nutrition. And so so what you do is you you go to uh, you type in like best dog food
And then you need to scroll through potentially like 30 different ad pages that just put
You know, well this one's the best one because uh, somebody told us it was and paid us
Uh, there's so many different ones. Uh, you eliminate all the ones that are junk food brands
And then you have to go to the natural the good ones right this this quotes there's good ones
So after you eliminate the Doritos of dog food
Some of these dog food brands guys, holy shit
It is just crushed up Doritos water and cornstarch is pretty much what your dog is eating. Um
Grain free. Yeah, he eats blue buffalo
and it was like
The formulation is like grain free it's like meats and and vegetables and shit
Blue buffalo is good. Yeah, and it's and it's it's pretty well priced
I did some I you know, you look up all you find the dog food you want to use and you're like, all right
Is this dog food good and you look at like testing and third party independent studies?
Blue buffalo is i'm not gonna say that out loud
My vet says blue buffalo is trash. Well, that's what I mean. It's you how are you supposed to know anything?
Can somebody explain to me?
Why?
We have toothpaste
that
It's nine out of ten decades dead dead dead decktists recommend colgate for teeth
Why don't nine out of ten vets recommend the same brand of uh of dog food?
I don't understand
Is there a reason look there's like there's like five million different toothpastes and they all agree. Oh, this is the ada
Brand. Yes, that's good
The ada stamps are approval on that one
Why does every dentist
Argue what's a good dog food?
Well blue buffalo isn't very good. Let me tell you you go to a vet down the street blue buffalo is great
You go to another vet. I recommend the shit we sell at our vet. That's wicked expensive
Okay
Then you go to like the vet in the alleyway and the guy's like, you know
You could just you could just like give him a steak and cheese sub every day and you'll be fine
You're like i'm not going back to that guy
It's hard and there's other oh you dog really should be eating raw food just a raw diet
Should he though?
We have this refrigerated section with dog food
And the refrigerated section has a bunch of food that you need to keep in your fridge
And it's you you should be feeding that big salami stick that you've cut a slice off and put it in their bowl
It's a huge like salami thing. Is that good?
I don't know. My vet didn't tell me to do that
Yes, that's that's good. Actually. Yes
Dogs can have a little salami. No, don't feed your dog salami. Don't vote. Do not feed your dog salami
Do not do that
Bernie says they can have a little what are you talking about? What who's who's bernie? Who's bernie?
like
Bernie dog salami
Is bernie a vet?
Cats can have a little a salami. Oh today. I'm looking for some
Editor
Is this a react video but there's no reaction they're just talking about the thing that they're supposed to be watching I don't understand
dog salami
dog salami bernie
bernie sanders
What's the deal with the cats can have it's cats not dogs. What's the deal with the cats can have a little salami meme?
This is not even
Is it imger?
Elizabeth of bernie can cats have salami cats can have a little salami cats should only eat cat food
I thought it was a video. So this is what it is. Okay. I mean, I I don't don't I wouldn't feed any dogs
Uh or cat salami
I mean like you could have maybe a little bit of banana. That's okay. Just just eat a banana
Where's this image that I just said? Why am I doing this right now? No, no, no. No somebody fucked me up
They said go on a rant go on a funny rant and I was like, okay
What happened? Where are we? I don't even care about this image. Let's play
What was I doing? Get this off my screen?
Okay
Quick say do something funny
Not one thing funny. They're not not supposed to be funny. They're supposed to be real life
All right, i'm just walking in circles, what am I doing? Okay. Um, I have to find
Bananas have potassium. They're radioactive get out of here
It's a fucking banana. You're gonna be fine
All right. What what the what was I just doing can't check still still have to do that
Potassium explodes in water, you know, you need potassium, right?
potassium
Let me know what are you talking about?
Potassium is not bad for you potassium is radioactive
What are you guys getting this? It who cares?
It's probably like point zero point two percent microns or something for radioactive level
God my bathtub is probably more radioactive than 500 bananas
Who cares?
All right. All right. All right. All right. Oh, no, no the the disc the metal disc. Okay. Let's go. I'm so excitable today
You got me in one of those moods. Well, i'm excitable
Who did that? Uh, it's a secret room this way. There's one more
and
Who knows where the hell that is? Let's go back into the town
Imagine you could run this fast
Nancy is sprinting around this town
You know what actually a nice touch would be would you put this game in full letter grade?
Is if you click really fast like this, she's like
Let's go back to the pub
No, there he is. Hello
What happened with elizabeth what happened with elizabeth? She locked me out of the pub this time for good
It seems like she was pretty upset by whatever you said to her. That's not your business
Everyone tries to turn against me in the end gunnar always had gunnar's back
Holy shit
Every video game character never changes their clothes
If they're if you're like an npc in a video game, you don't ever you have the same clothes every time for every game
Maybe you should try to make up
No need for that woman no need for anyone anymore that blasted woman won't let me get into this skip again
His clothes are probably more radioactive than your bathtub a personal box
I did not get a chance to grab it before guys go walk down into your basement
If you have one special and take one breath in give you the only clue
I just consumed probably 5 000 bananas worth of radioactive material
If you help i'll give you the only clue I have. All right, i'll get the box. I'll get the box
But I swear if you're lying to me i'm being honest as the day is short
lancy
Please talk to you later
Okay, what does he want?
This thing oh, it's unlocked already
Let's open it
Is that picture of me?
She looks like me
Did he just make me go get a box of pictures of me and shit?
What does it say?
Police clothes drowning case of two women new. Oh shit. All right, hold on
Here you can have this
Did he not know what this was?
Here, I think this belongs to you
Thank you
Did did you open it?
Yes
I see it didn't tell me not to open it. I'm ashamed of the way I acted towards super ruse five committee
I have been angry and blind for too long
My daughter wouldn't stand for me like this no more of that childishness now
every day I wake up and
For one moment. I I think they're still alive
I reach over to my wife started a bed to hold her and it's all comes back
And I remember they're gone
They're both gone
And I am alone. Oh, he's right. I'm so sorry. Gunnar. It was a long time ago
I can see now there are still things left to live for
strong ships good festivals
new neighbors
But did he throw bottles at that guy at the cultural center at the misty skip after the tides change
I'll give you everything I have
All right, so let's go to bed
Welcome back. This is for you couldn't wrap my old head around but maybe you can make a head out of a tail
Oh, there we go
Hold on i'm texting somebody. I know I now put your phone down put your phone down
I know I know I know
I know I know I got my phone during the movie. I'm sorry make good use of it. Fisker
And don't fucking zoomer. No, i'm sorry. I apologize little lady hands
All right. Where do you where you saying this is a gear?
Let me do the puzzle piece first
I typically don't use my phone for anything
You can ask the people that call me all the time when I don't answer
Phones to me are like a pain in the ass
See back in the day
Everybody knew that you were not in constant communication
Now everybody has a cell phone in their pocket. So I know I know you're there. I know that you're getting this right?
So the 500 iq play
Is just leave your phone in your bedrooms on your bed
So then it's just like it was 15 years ago
Now you're always constantly contactable and what if you just don't want to be contactable
People know you have your phone because everybody has a phone
And then they added the shit that they have to read receipts thing
That's fucked up, too
What if i'm like out in the grocery store and somebody texts me and I have read receipts on and I look at it
Oh, no, I have to reply to this person right now
What if i'm like trying to pick like my favorite hamburger helper and it's taking me 30 minutes
Now we're gonna go back
Then problem
Look I understand like I understand like the cell phones are amazing because they've given us
a way for emergency
Contacts and always being in communication and if something, you know, if you're lost, you know, i've got my phone
I have access to I I have access to the outside world
All of your stories devolve into anxious paranoia
I don't this is the same picture
That's it. I think this is it
Oh, yeah, that's it
I've seen this design before
It's it's from the lighthouse. There must be something there
All right, we're gonna go to the lighthouse and find the star
Haven't can't can't check that off yet. Go to the lighthouse
I thought that was somebody crawling
Let's go to the lighthouse
She's the 5g killer
Don't give me another thing to have nightmares over tonight
Oh, he's actually scared of 5g
It's so new the technology is so new. It's so scary sometimes
Oh, there she is
Guys it took
50 years
For doctors to stop recommending smoking cigarettes
We've only had wireless technology and cell phone technology for like fucking less than
10 to 15 years and I have a feeling this is going to be a long one
I want to believe the best here, but you should stop doing that people like me don't deserve that anyways you me
town
So you faked that you'd gone missing, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, don't look at me with those kicked puppy eyes. I needed some time to crack the case without anyone catching on to me
All right, we gotta pay attention
You think that you've gone missing? Yeah. Yeah, don't look at me with those
Puppy eyes, I needed to crack the case. That's my job. You must have a compelling lead on the treasure
Otherwise knowing you you'd never have left the heater
Pretty passive aggressive. Let's pick that one. You must have a compelling lead on the treasure
Detectives
Okay
Fine. The ship itself is a map to the treasure. I suspected that
The problem is the original ship was torn apart many of the pieces of the original have been built into the town
I need some sort of key something to help me decode the map. All right, i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm going off
You know where to find that key? Um
Not even I but you know what I said, I think you do banana
And a bunch of people in this chat was so concerned about the radiation in a banana
But 5g I would like stand in front of a 5g frequency wave
Dude 5g is just it's like nothing. Don't worry. Don't eat bananas though
This is like this like point zero point zero zero zero zero zero zero zero one percent. Uh, fucking radiation in that soil that it was in
Sorry, I don't
Hmm a girl with principles. That's cute
5g is one one thousandth of a banana
Haha
If you eat a banana near a 5g tower, you're going to die
I don't want to believe you'd do something to magnus, but you're not giving me a lot of options here. Look i'm being honest
take this as collateral it clearly fits somewhere just
Not sure where I might be greedy, but i'm not a greedy kidnapper. I want magnus back safe or at least safe
I'm not a greedy grinner
By the way greedy grinner is one of the nominees along with uh shito clowns and um
shannon sharon
And the rumor for best character new character of the year, by the way
If you haven't voted yet, there is a way to vote for your favorites of the year
New year's eve stream. The poll is now live
There it is
Take a look
Maybe that'll help you if you decide to stop hating money. I'll be waiting
toodles
All right, so I have this lion token. What's that for though? Can't that's done?
Can't check can't check that off yet follow up on that. Okay, all right. I gotta go back to the uh tower
Now i'm not giving my opinion on any of the nominees
I don't want to sway anything
positive or negative
Not happening. I think it's time to find out what elizabeth's hiding in that deck closet. Didn't I already go in this closet?
I have nothing for you
I already went in here
Nancy stop don't go in there. Sorry elizabeth, but it's time to come clean. I know you're hiding someone in there
No, you can't
There actually is a person here
Why did you put a dog in there so much for finding magnus I guess you thought I was hiding magnus
It was really suspicious
Sorry, I pinned you wrong though
I
Guess it was a little strange
So I have to ask the obvious
Why are you keeping a dog in a closet?
Tumi wouldn't do well in a shelter. He seems to really like so he would do better in a
Three by three closet. I want to hate him so much
But I just can't
When did you manage to get to me just before magnus left to take the ship into harbor?
That's why I wasn't at the festival hang on so you knew magnus was going to go missing
No, but I knew he'd notice if to me did and then maybe he'd have to come looking for me for once
Yeah, yeah, okay
Uh, this is not elizabeth pet napping may not be a healthy way to handle this. I agree
It started off as that
But now that he's missing I feel like it's smarter to keep to me here if someone did abduct magnus
How long would to me spend in the cage at the borders?
Listen nancy just a little while ago. I realized something
When you told me my family's song I'm not paying attention because it is a love song
It's a love song for my family's heritage
the treasure
So the purpose of the song was to make sure only captain laurence's descendant could find that treasure here
Have this oh i've never shown music box. Maybe they've been the key all along I trust you to find out the truth nancy
Okay, bring magnus home bring magnus home. All right. Goodbye elizabeth
I'll see you when you return home to whatever fucking sims expansion you came from
All right back to the cabin
Talk to the dog
I can't you can't talk to the dog. No dog can't talk to dog
I gotta go I gotta go to the yeah the cabin
Music box
Here we go. All right stick it in there
This belongs to elizabeth's family and her song is a missing piece
I wonder if I can arrange these teeth to play that song
Fuck arrange the I don't know what this means
I don't make music
I'm gonna say i'm just gonna go for it. Let's uh
What is
Uh, let's try um
Uh, and then two in a row so it's
Like that
No, there's gotta be the same size
Are they all the and none of these the same size?
They're all different sizes
Damn it. I can't read. I of course. I can't read music
In order of height. Yeah, but aren't those two notes the same on the same line?
So wouldn't it be the same size?
Or am I am I overthinking this?
You're under thinking it
Yeah, it goes low
So
Just do shortest to longest
I I don't think that I don't think that's accurate. It's not shortest to longest
Is it?
I thought it would have to be
It's still going
Sorting algorithm. I don't think that was correct
lion
Um
The notes change. Yeah, why do the notes change?
Watch the dots
The game lagged for a second scrolling down in the walkthrough no i'm not i'm not
What
Fuck you. Yes, you are. Hey easy
Don't swear at me
harry potter
Oh
Can I actually get it to do that
This needs to be higher
This is be lower
I almost had it. Sorry. All right, let's see. What do I want to move? I want to move these guys gotta start like this
Big ones gotta be in the middle. I know that for a fact. I just do how do I know that you ask
I took two music classes another that we this is the crescendo. That's what that's called
Let's try that
Just try every combination longer bars make lower notes. Yep
This is just what happens when somebody tries to phonetically play jingle bells on a piano
Even if you get it wrong, you're getting the the timings, right?
Try that
Somebody said how are you this bad? I just did it
Tone depth. Oh my god. He's so stupid tough. I'll take my fish, please
I like this one. Why do I let me look at this a little bit more
nice
My i'm my i'm my eyes are ripping over the chat. It's cool. What what is that? Cool. What's that limit image?
Nice
All right. I gotta stop. Let's get back to the game. What's this?
Oh, that's like a little fish. It's like a like a little gummy fish. That's so cool
I just want to look at it for a minute
Cool. All right. What is this?
Part of a note or a book we succeeded we fought we captured the
Here lifcahede, okay
All right. So now I got the fish
Track down the treasure's location can't have check. Okay, there's that
I want fish gummy
I want fish gummy. I want fish gummy. You'll you'll relax. You're fine
relax
Cheating like this is why germa died to pinwheel
What's going on change obs to all screens to prove no guide
You know how easy it would be for me just to close the tab that has the walkthrough in it
Very easy
Oh shit, you got me
Uh, oh no. All right. Let's go. What's what's this fish wooden tile in token? Let's go back to the uh
I want to go back to that wall
Can you order me blueberries?
Now, how about you tell me what you want and I will order uber eats
And then i'll just eat the food that you were going to eat and i'll leave it on stream for you
And then you can just take the bites like mimic while i'm biting and be like
All right. Um, where was that?
All right, I gotta go back to the ship
Uh-oh ship alarm
What
Okay, the clues laurence left behind have confirmed that the treasure is not on the ship
He evidently suspected that the town would eventually turn against him and started to hide the treasure elsewhere at
this place i've been able to recreate the first steps and clearly
The caves run deeper than we realized there must be more pages from laurence's journal that will reveal the final steps to take
enter the caves, oh
Turn right at the red pumice stones walk forward to all right
What else is in here that's it who's up there got you
Uh, what it's the dog
Are we really? No, we're not we're not gonna get we're not I I can't is that a spoiler
Now i'm not gonna say spoilers
Okay. Well now I know so I'll track down the treasure
So we have to go to the cave
I gotta read this red stones
This would be a cool little adventure
All right, that's wrong. I want the location
Under the caves turn right at the red pumice stone
There it is
right
Walk forward to the high ledge with red stone
Okay climbing up and over then down past the yellow pumice stones
Okay
Continue forward till the tunnel splits levels go up
Okay, turn right at the cluster of five stalagmites and continue forward to a large cavern
Okay, wait, didn't I already get this? Is it the egg? I already did this turn right
Go up
Go up stalagmites are the ones that have five stalagmites. They hang
Turn right at the cluster of five stalagmites
One two, three, four, five six seven eight eight
No, stalagmites are one two three four. Okay, turn right
That's what I just did
And continue forward to a large cavern doesn't let I can't go forward there it is
I already picked up the shit that was down here. Didn't I?
Ice pick. No, that's not doing anything
Is the egg?
Okay, let's go. I'm going to the guide. What's the guide say? Okay track down the treasure
Yeah head into the right tunnel
Continue two steps use the hook on the wall
Isn't that what I did?
That's what i'm doing
Wrong wall
Okay, i'm in the cavern
Go wrong hook
What's the right hook?
What?
What do you mean wrong hook?
Give me back to square one. Give me back to square one back to square one. This this doesn't do anything
Back to square one
Just give me back out back up back up back up back up put this away
Give me back up just back up back up back up back up back up. All right. All right. All right. I've gone up
Turn around
Go up here we go
All right. Wait a minute. Okay turn
stalagmites
Continue forward to a large cavern
Left and right it separates
Head to the right the right tunnel
Go forward twice
Use the pick on the wall
Use the hook on the wall
I can't do this yet. That's the problem. I can't smash this wall
Because I haven't read the note about how I should smash the fucking wall
I'm not too good. I better have saved before that
That better have saved
Thank god
All right, get me the fuck out of here. Get me out of here. Get me I gotta go read like I could do something else
And read a note
All right. What do I what do I have? I have some stuff. I have to go back
To where where should I go?
This is what happens when you cheat with the drew crew
No, everything's fine. I know what I have to do. I know what I have to do. Check it out
Check this out
That's a lion token token to rotate these it's a clinko machine
Oh, this is actually kind of fun. All right
Reset it
They're all flipped. So it goes down straight first
Does it bounce over here? No, it doesn't
So it goes and alternates
No, it doesn't because it goes down straight doesn't it? I thought it did
What do we want drew crew that's here right now you get the drew crew's right here
All right, there we go
All right. It's so damn close. I just have to
Go fuck
Shit
Come on. No, I've said it
What was that boy that was left? Hold on. What's this? What i'm going to die? I just did it
I fucked it up. I'm just a little guy. I had it right
banana 5g brain
I literally just did it. All right. What's the guide say who cares?
I need to find I
He wasted so many lion coins
No, I had it. Okay, at least then go down here. That's done
Does it?
Didn't even need to cheat. I didn't even have to cheat on that one
final gear
I gotta go back to
All right. Now I have all the gears
It's time
Wait, that's on the boat. It's in the secret room
Head down here open that up back to the secret room
All right, get it on there done
What is behind here
This looks ancient. It's a pretty long game for a shitty dollar bin game
Yeah, I played it for like six hours last time too
I need to get this sliding shape over to that treasure marking
What in the name of god is this?
Move the sliding shape to the yellow treasure mark using your mouse or keyboard arrows
They did this shit in zoom beanies and it was horrible
Oh
So I have to be a red fish to go over there
Okay, hold on. Can I get to be a turtle?
Okay, I need to be red
blue turtle
Damn it. Wait fish
red fish
and then
Green crab or blue star green crab is right here
And then I have to be green
I could just be turtle
Should I just turtle turtle and then blue and then no
Oh shit, um
Okay
Well, I need to end up as
a red
Which is something green a star like a red star is what I need to be
So how do I get to be a red star?
Oh shit, okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait
I gotta be red go red
And then no
wait
star blue
blue fish
blue
and then
I'm gonna be a red star eventually a red
uh
This star
I'm still blue though blue star star star blue star red
Red
Uh grease lightning, thanks for the five community subs. Thank you grease lightning five subs coming
On each row and column arrange the pieces so that every row and column has one of each design
Can I put them anywhere wait, hold on why these in here then why these here
Arrange the pieces so that every row and column has one of each design
But this oh wait, wait, wait, wait, what do you mean you're talking like
But there's there's two of these in here there's two of these going down
This is this isn't well, I can't do that. There's two going down
I can cover them. Fuck. All right, I can cover them. Fuck. All right, blah so
So the boat is sinking everyone will be fine don't worry
There's nobody on the boat guys, but now this is horrible
So I gotta go let's just do this it can't be this one
I mean if this has to be there nothing else can cover that
Can anything else cover this?
No, this is wrong you have to have these the circles are huge you can't
Done, okay. Where's where?
Now I might need to flip this around I might need to switch it
Turn the sound down. Is it? Oh, is the sound really loud? Oh shit. I'm sorry
All right, so we're gonna do
Wait, what how could it be? How are there three of these?
Uh, wait, i'm confused. How would there be three of these? Oh it needs to be covered. Okay. Um
Um
What's this what's this coffee pasta?
There's a bunch of emotes and shit
All right, get that get that out of here get that out of here. All right, I can't read it
Okay, uh now we need um
This one
And then this one is that correct? We'll find out that's not correct
This has to be
Wait, what's underneath that? Yes
Um
Okay, what about down here?
Empty all right. I I get it. Oh fuck this is wrong. Uh
I don't know. It's going well. Uh kind of
All right, that needs to be covered. So what if I go like this?
and then here and then
That noise really is fucking hurting me
That's the last one
All right
So far it's working kind of
This puzzle is easy
Maybe for you
Let's just start putting shit in here and we can fix it later
This is still correct
correct
Why can I put that here?
Oh, no, I have to cover that
Uh-oh
um
Okay
Life is pain. It kind of is at the moment. This has to be a
This has to be this this has to be correct. So this is wrong
This is also wrong
Wait, that's wrong. Holy shit. This sucks
uh
Mods please slow mode or sub only or something. Please make it stop
I just like seeing purple in chat. Yeah, I still have to figure out what i'm gonna do with that stuff
All right. Everything's been covered
This is not right. Okay, I still need one of these
Is that done? No, what's wrong with this?
Okay, wait
Now hold on
That has to be covered there
uh
What am I missing this doesn't even have one of these
He hates us. What are you talking about? You still have 9 000 points. Well, I would save them because
Uh for like 50 000 points, you'll be able to like turn my camera on or something
All right. What's this last one has to be this right?
good
Is this this is still correct?
All right
Hold on. It's almost ready
uh
here
Yeah
Uh, this is wrong
Um, it's so close though
shit
What needs to change this has too many of these?
Okay, okay
Oh
I didn't cheat. I swear to god. I didn't cheat. I promise
Open the chest in the hold
Oh shit, there's like a skeleton back here
That's done
Catch that's done. All right track down the treasure follow the up on the image created by the sketches
I have to go back to the lighthouse
Who do you guys think did it?
I can't wait till we find out who did it. It's like
Who did it? Here's the big reveal
We walk up to the person that we think it is
and then you hear
You look down like a bloody knife dropped out of my fucking shirt
And then the camera changes to dagny's perspective and you start controlling dagny and it was me
That'd be pretty cool
Because a game I need a game i'm gonna make a game that does that spoiler alert for my future game
Sorry, you'll know what happens
Did you know that dogs can have a little salami? We already went over that
You're like an hour and 12 minutes late. Sorry
So where's the star?
right there
There's more
There are more puzzles in the world than than
Match numbers and have the sums of the numbers be next to each other. There's more
Puzzles than this that exists
Do I don't have to why is it because I have to be like this
This is just 700 000 games
All right, place the number so that one of each number is within each outlined large triangle
oh, man, okay, I
horizon
That each number has to be in each
It's it's just so it's it's sudoku
Yeah, I never played sudoku. I was a pick. Why can't they be pick ross?
Are you shitting me?
Look at these images and you tell me that these images were not made for pick ross
Why would you have another math logic place the tile one?
The true the drew crew lives for this
All right, let's go in a row. I said we have uh, eight six. We need uh, there's two in there
It was a three. There's no three in there
Uh, where's the four? There's no four in there. There is is there a five? No, there's no five. Is there a seven?
There's no seven
Okay, so two three four five six seven eight nine
uh seven five seven
What?
But this should be horizontal horizontal row and that I thought this is
Is that okay?
I don't know. So I didn't have played sort of
diagonals, you know, it has
Oh for the love of god has to be fucking diagonals
I'm using my lifeline
the lifeline is
uh
phone
Gamer boomers game boomers.com
And phone friend. All right, let's see what they say. He's cheating already. No, I don't want to do this
No, that's I don't like this one. I don't like that too many of these too many of these
Too many of these i'm sorry. I just you got you got to just call it like it is too many of these
Cheating not allowed that wasn't part of the deal
Don't you do we don't you want to see who did it?
He used game boomers last stream of this game
That's so funny that
This 38 or 37 nancy drew walkthroughs
on the game boomers dot com
that's so
Just so appropriate
Don't worry. I'm solving it
It's going to be so cool when you see the the actual solution
When there's too many numbers on the screen, I can't my brain hurts
like I want to like open up the container and find the key and like look under the desk and press the button and
Pull out the tray and and match and sort. I don't want to do math. I'm sick of math
Oh, so by the way, uh, I want to bring this up because it's something we're doing probably fairly soon early into 2020
We're gonna do an ipad stream
There are a shitload of games that have come out on the ipad
some of them just seem
Absolutely outrageous that we have to play them
I've been saving them. Some of them have come out some of them. I've been some of them are ad games
And what an ad game is it's a game that I was playing. I was playing a different game
and then
A 30 second take over the whole ipad a ad came up
And it was this game that I have downloaded now
Uh, it should be interesting a lot of them are ad games. So i'm probably gonna have to like wipe my ipad to factory settings
After doing this stream
Why i'm gonna have to this puzzle isn't hard. No, I know i'm doing it. I'm doing it
I just have a game boomer in my corner in case I have trouble
Malware, yeah, you gotta be careful with those games
My brother used to do these all the time
He used to try to show me
how it worked
And I would always get halfway through his first sentence before I trailed off
And don't know what he was talking about
Got it
Got it the final piece head into the tunnel continue forward two steps then turn left and take one step forward buried in the cave
Wall to your left be a chest
Containing a paltry sum should you be followed or forced by the town's treachery simply reveal the decoy chest
The true treasure lies beyond that retrace your steps to the decoys treasure location
You'll find another passage leading up from there follow it now recall the words i've sung to you many times
Press the images in the order they appear from start to end with those words as your guiding light
Let's go
Follow the instructions
And that was just oh, yeah, that's the cat. I don't know why that sounded like unzipped pants
Or zip up jacket
That was like zip up pants unzip jacket
It was one of those
Here we go. All right. Let's get where's the note
It was actually I think I remember how to get there
Yeah, you're just gonna go forward forward people said what about that hand?
Yeah, i've looked at it already
It's the guy's glove
All right. Here we go
Just gonna make it down go up
Up here we are
right
Right forward
Here we go. You're ready
There's a person down here. Did you just come to the wall madness? Yeah
I'm here to get you out
Are you hurt anywhere? No, but he's
He's coming back
Who is oh he is what I knew it his polite demeanor was all in act, wasn't it?
It's true
He kept me here alone at first
Tried to get me to talk. So it was a guy that got the hit in the face bottom
But when he found out I truly didn't know the treasure's final location. He
Grew angry very angry. I don't know what he's gone and done now or when he's coming back. I'm so sorry
This is all my fault
Have you been in decay for the last few days?
I don't think you had any part in this. I did though long before the festival nearly all my life
I treated so unpoorly just because I was told to we all did that would make anyone furious
Like everybody was just wicked mean to him and
Uh, it still doesn't excuse everyone else. He anything else he's done. You could have been hurt
Maybe sorry. I'm gonna be yeah, you could have been hurt
He explained this yeah, I know but I thought he was gonna make it up for so long do you
No, I guess I don't
Maybe this is a wake-up call for all of us. Come on, magnus. I promise elizabeth
I bring you back in one piece and I don't like to disappoint elizabeth. Is she all right?
I I need to talk to her. I made a terrible mistake. She's a-okay. Let's get out of here
I know just the girl to find us some backup
What is that i thought it was an animal
I'm somewhere inside the volcanic caves near skip rock. How do you have service down here?
And I think we're kind of in dire straits here
Soran's the one responsible for all this
We already know how to get out of here i've been i've been oh the cave is collapsing
It was me wait what
The treasure
Quick quick push him run ram him at full speed right now. His back is turned
He did not swing that thing. He's gonna lift it up. It's gonna be too heavy for him
What?
Wait, I don't know
Is it weird that if I think okay if he swung that axe at me and hit me
I don't think it would do that much damage
You still have to swing it and hit it hard. It might get me pretty bad
Maybe a little bit, but I think I could take them. I think I could take them
It probably wouldn't be that bad of a of a
wound
Not a chance right now
Okay, so we
Am I supposed to be running away from him?
Are you gonna are you gonna do anything?
You guys don't think I could take them?
Okay, bye. Goodbye. Uh nice menacing talk that we had
There's your treasure
East india company and the detail it's
exquisite at these years
I found it. It was all worth it
All right
That's just like a big it's like a playhouse like a dollhouse
I could take that hit I'd really good
That would hurt but it wouldn't do that much damage
You just killed you. No, I didn't that's done. That's done find the real treasure
Is another okay, there's an illusory wall back here that he didn't see
Sorry, dude. You missed the entire you missed the entire tree level
Sorry, soren
It's not a myth. These images are from laurence's final letter. You just need to press them correctly
Press the images in the correct order according to laurence's final letter
Is this it?
No, is this it?
Now recall the words i've sung to you so many times
What's the song?
Oh
I'm, sorry. Oh, yeah. Okay. Um, where's the song?
Oh, do you speak english? Yes little no, that's not lyrics to a song
Where's the song?
You have my song and where is it?
Here we go
foreign shore behind me and a hundred more to go
On stormy season starless nights caught on a cold wind's blow
So
So many years have put my battered bow up to the test
along just who cares
I have to put this I like my way better
What I did them all? Oh, wait, what was that?
What no your dog died. So you broke your heart. How is that not part of the song?
Holy shit, this is incredible
Nancy are you back there madness? I'm here. I found the I wouldn't say anything
Yeah, this uh, i'm stuck right here bunch of ice help go get help
Nancy you can take one coin
No one's paying you
You can take a small shoe box and rifle in
Just three or four handfuls of gold coins and just stick it just down in the front of your pants and just leave it there
You know what I mean? Like I would just put it in my underwear
Just stick it down straight down in the back of my underwear and then cover it with a big jacket
That's okay nancy to get you can give the rest uh someone tried to kill us
He's a danger to the town's safety
You got it ladies. See you soon. I think i'm calling this case closed
Did I win?
The secret of skip rot's famous treasure is finally put to rest and the case is closed
Soren was arrested the minute magnus and I arrested in the cave as it turns out
He was the one following magnus all along looking for his chance to take the treasure for himself
He followed magnus onto the ship just before ice jail
Knocked him unconscious and took him to the ice caves using his dinghy
When he realized magnus didn't know the final location he came after me
Luckily, I beat him to the finish line. The treasure is in good hands with elizabeth
Her family legacy has finally come full circle
Magnus apologized to elizabeth for having been so distant leading up to the festival
The two of them are doing well another case closed finally got that ship
He's always dreamed of he and elizabeth packed their things and left to travel the world and of course toomy went too
I just got a call from elizabeth. I think they're somewhere near thailand as we speak
Did they go with the boat skip pub and gunner's hands while she's gone
Gunner seems to be happier than ever
He's back on his feet and he even took me out on a fishing trip
He's still pretty cranky when it comes to tourists, but I think he'll get the hang of things
Dagny and magnus donated their exploration rights to the heurlic hide back to skip rot
The ship is now fully public property and is open to tourists at all times of the year
Dagny stayed in skip rock for a little while
But she split soon after she got her share of the treasure at first
She seemed to contend to stay but after a couple of days with no action
It seemed like she was itching to get out on the road
She didn't say much about where she was going, but I later found a note in my room at the pub
Catch you later friend. I gave ned the anniversary gift. I got him from the skip rot gift shop
Ha ha ha
Hey ned, I found like 60 million dollars in gold coins. Here's a souvenir from the gift shop
Which was not one of the waterfront shops
the heart of odin
We'll get I get to nominate with awards
the award
What what are you talking about?
No, how did it know?
Nice job on the game facts usage
You do know it only took you a month to solve the case put a little love in your heart egged time to make an omelet
Look out you're not afraid of heights compulsive spender or oh, yeah, because there's a sword. I didn't get the sword
Wait a minute the prequel to the last this one we did
Really important to me is in danger things are going from people are even saying she's some kind of witch
Hang the phone up and call the police your house is on fire
Join me venture. We already did that one
We already did that one
Play that one looks good
This is nancy drew singing
This is a real song
Nancy drew in the live concert
I could probably sing
I could probably sing like this if I wanted
to play ninja turtles
You still remember that?
People can be really mad
I already saw those
All right. That was nancy drew sea of darkness pretty cool
Pretty pretty cool pretty cool
Time to go play tether ball
Next is drew. I'm not going right into another nancy drew game guys
No, i'm not done streaming, but i'm not going into nancy drew
We solved another case until next time
All right. Let me uh, let me go pee
And i'll uh get us something else to do for a little a little bit
Vote on the poll if you haven't you got three days. I'll be right back
He's never coming back, is he?
He is he is
All right. What am I gonna do? What should we do? What do we got time for?
I just gave 50 dollars
50. Hold on
Vilemi
5 000 bits
It's a shitload of money. Thank you
Not going right into the next nancy drew game just proves that you're not really
Part of the drew crew
That's not even true though
That's not true
That's not that's not true
I am part of the drew crew
I've I originated drew crew
Well, I mean I
I didn't but I did
But I didn't
I was part of the I was in the same room
As the drew crew origination, you know what i'm saying? I was there. I was in the room
He's a true drewer
That's right
All right. I know that was a bad voice crack. All right. Let's uh, let me get this open
Okay
Looks good
No more tier list. I don't know what tier lists to do
I don't think there are are there
Yeah animals
Hold on a second
How wait wait, what I can't I I why
What is going on here?
Did I get the wrong thing?
I think I got the wrong program
shit
Uh-oh
Did I click on like an ad?
I may have clicked an ad
Fuck. Wait a minute. This is bad
actually bad
The ad is actually bad. Hold on. This is actually really really really bad. Hold on
What why do I look so I look I look strange today
Why?
You didn't notice that
I was muted the entire I was muted the entire time
How are you serious?
Okay, uh
Uh, it crashed so I said, okay looks like we're not doing that
Um the game fucking crashed
Uh, and and I I can't it's fucked up so and I and wait
Did you guys not hear anything I was saying when I told you I downloaded a fucking virus?
what
You didn't hear any of that when I said that like oh shit, I think I downloaded a virus
You did that. That's the last thing you heard. All right
You know what I could I could put on a medieval
What if I just open up? No, I can't do that. Fuck. What can we do right now to?
You didn't finish nancy dru. I didn't finish a medieval
Go back to jump king and do the jump king dlc
There is not a single chance in hell. I'm going to do that
Now, uh, all right, so here's what's gonna happen. I really didn't think nancy dru is gonna take three hours
That was gonna take like four or five. So
Uh, what we got?
What do I got right now on steam? Let's see
Because i'm no more heroes was supposed to be today
But I've had some trouble getting it to run
so
That's what's gonna happen tomorrow. No matter what
What the hell should I even do for the next couple like hour or two?
What do I have installed on steam? I got a couple of new games. Let me see what they are
Play gta
No, I'd want that to be its own thing
Ai dungeon, I can't do a I can't do that right now. I need to set that all up again
I have to go back to like the collab website and it's gonna take like 15 20 minutes to build it up again
um
See
Halo reach. No, i'm not playing halo reach
What do I have installed?
dos
I could do dos or
Or you know, there's another there's another game I have on this list that I haven't played in a while
And it's gonna piss off some people but it's gonna make some people happy
Let's see, let's see how many people we make happy and let's see how let's what's the over under on people that are gonna
Be upset right now. I don't
Anybody know what this is? It's not house flipper. It's not house flipper. You're wrong
Yeah, you got it. It's time to relax
I said it earlier. I said the word earlier
And now I just want to do it. I just want to play it now
What is this 15 15 by 15? Don't tell me what it is. Why is it giving me this solution?
I don't know what I don't want. I don't want to see that why it's showing me that
I don't know. It's lightning. That's a spoiler. No, I didn't already do these
Don't look at it
Hold on. Can I turn it off?
auto fade numbers
No, give me enable smart slide preview filling. No show buttons show time show theme
interface
english
Is it themes?
No show theme
See if that does it do the jump king dlc. No, I I gotta I gotta chill I
There we go. All right. Good. So that way if we don't I don't want to know what these are
So, I don't know what this one is. This is 15 by 15. Let's go get fucking get pumped up to
Relax and like go to sleep
All right. I gotta get like get back into this
Is this actually lightning? No, it's not
How many years goes 15 by 15?
Let's go
It's bedtime gamers
It's time to just listen to the music
Take it don't don't riot
Don't you dare riot?
One two, three, four, five, six, seven eight nine ten. I don't I can't determine
ten
middle five
Uh, then we do this we do these
math is hard
DOS do dos games
Yeah, I'm not set up for that though. It's gonna take even more time
I probably will just open up nancy drew episode fucking 34
No, I can't
I can't do that. Oh my god. I'm gonna do it
Is the turtles in time fucked up? Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right. Stop
What is it?
Nancy true the secret of the old clock
Fuck you do picross. Uh, I can't i'm sorry
I can't
You know why because I've I haven't done one of these in a long time. Let's open up the clock. Okay clock time
Fucking nancy drew why you like
Taking over my whole channel
All right, it's gonna be loud just exit out of here fucking my fate is sealed pic by the way
Picto pics is a great fucking game. I highly recommend it
shit
Secret of the old clock here it comes
The place the road to titusville where we find nancy drew behind the wheel of her blue roadster pondering this question
What what was the question? What was the question? What was the question? What was the question?
The year 1930 the place the road to titusville where we find nancy drew behind the wheel of her blue roadster pondering this question
Why did emily crandall a girl who nancy knows only through their mutual friend helen corning?
What what's the question?
God damn it nancy. Hold on. I have to
What is this happening to me? All right, wait a second finally, okay cap
The
Secret of the old clock this one probably sucks by the way
Nancy to drive all the way out to the lilac inn to see her the year
Game set up here. Can I capture this shit the road to titusville where we find nancy drew?
Why can't I capture this?
The wheel of her blue roadster capture this question. I can't capture it. It's like an old one
All right, i'm gonna try this. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. This should this should work
Can I capture this like its own window? Why was it this one? We're gonna oh my fucking god
Just play jump. I can't no i'm not playing jump king
That i'm not gonna get stuffed into a corner and play the dlc of jump king and like poo my pants
That's not gonna happen. No
No, no, no, no clock the clock nancy drew in the mystery of the fucking grandfather clock. Here we go
It's coming on screen right now
He's too afraid. No, i'm not doing it. Why can I not capture this shit?
God nancy drew i'm gonna just have to fucking install another one
Okay, like what there's no there's no windows even open apparently
Nancy's betraying us
Hold on. Let me try one more thing
See if this works
The year 1930 the place the road to titusville where we find nancy drew behind the wheel of her
Fuck
Where is it?
Give it to me
wrong
Got it. No, I don't
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I got it. This actually will work
We're doing i'm just gonna capture my entire fucking computer. Who cares?
Hold on. Let me just like take everything that's on the desktop and stuff it into a fucking folder
All right, everything's going into the folder. I don't even know what this stuff is
But like I have there's like a bank statement on my fucking desktop. Hold on. Wait a second
I have like like like my credit card info is right here. Wait, let me hold on
I have like six new folders
I'm gonna have so much trouble finding so much of this shit. All right