This guy has a sniper rifle pointing in the air and he's just like oh yeah what
is that oh yeah he's getting down I have never seen that before it's just
ridiculous yeah what you do is you crouch look up and you scope in yeah that's
what you do yeah all right I'm gonna play soldierless around what are you
doing actually no I'll just pocket you all right where'd you go where'd you go
left side so I'm going a stock rocket launcher shotgun and equalizer you're
going Kritzkrieg loot saga and the uber saw no I also got a request that we got
to try like legit battle medics where you have two medics you try to chain
uber oh hell yeah I've never done that before it looks very difficult it can
get pretty crazy because I mean you can you can end up having an uber for a full
two or three minutes on each side it's pretty insane all right grab that health
there he's just a little it's all right cap this point overheal everybody we're
going scout nice nice all right let me know when you want it oh oh oh oh I got
him I'll revenge you I'll avenge you not
revenge you oh god never mind I just walked right into a direct hit TF 2
double X Frank was not having any of that one all right double X Frank that's
a perfect name yeah nice good girl why would a pyro just be sitting there yeah
true they should be herping and derping
somewhere this looks like it might just be a GG right here yeah it's kind of
rolling through let's go take that last point slowly but surely got two medics
on you now oh we got a heavy I'm backing up yeah back off for a little bit I got
to heal this guy oh I got you oh oh watch out spy turn on guys oh man another
century in here somewhere oh god don't know from where damn all up top two
centuries up top is that medic still you guys still alive we both died or if you
don't I got I got a couple I got a couple soldiers in here I should be all
good yeah I'm gonna go second floor take up the centuries oh boy is it heavy in
here too oh god Gabe Newell I don't know he played with the fans of the game I
think his fingers would be too fat to use the keyboard he's kind of a big boy
oh he is very nice guy though apparently that's good when's episode 3 ever coming
out yeah I know you hear about the those protesters that were sitting on the
valve headquarters apparently there was protesters sitting on the front lawn of
valve like maybe like a week or two ago saying like where's episode 3 there was
only like three or four of them so Gabe Newell went out there and ordered him a
pizza so they could like eat and hang out there yeah and eventually I guess
somebody called the police and the police officer was a huge team fortress
2 fan so he like joined in on the protest nice I just thought where is
their headquarters located oh I think it's in Seattle no we just want to sit
in the rain all day oh stereotyping a city oh damn oh I got multiple this guy
this guy's got a Chris you're gonna get double dressed here oh oh give it to me
medic oh me and this medic oh god got one kill double pocket I don't think
I've ever had the double crits pocket that's oh man that would have been
pretty ridiculous yeah damn engineers with their centuries turtling up all
right I wanted I'm one to talk engineers like my favorite class yeah I love my
combat energy that's probably my second favorite class oh yeah it's just fun like
you just I don't know I don't know what's about it it's very satisfying I
will it is absolutely to work with a non-living object to complete an
objective of getting those wins I got like 50% where you at a second floor
still working on DJ set up mr. battlefield legend plans fortress yeah
still I'm on the second last point just healing people up over here yeah I'm
with Fox we're good balls can't take out that century it's so close 36 hell you
want me to watch change to over um probably this last point that makes
sense I got I got one more crits fully charged if you want it when you get out
you can just go to someone I'm on my way let's let's go cut down me and cut down
I'm gonna rip through people he's gonna cut down some people oh I think you know
he's a spy oh you got to be kidding me ubered yourself a nice little spy yeah
I just I just crits over his spy I didn't die though that's that's the good
part about this whole thing I'm just going suicide medic right now let's see
if I can kill him a little uh you know giving him a chance I got regular uber
we should be able to take this out on bone no I'm still we're still alive
somehow oh they got a heavy medic over on the near the second point second to
last point I got one of one two centuries down oh crap yeah Vega Bon
dildo with two L's laying oh no no no get me out of there get me out of it nice I
just got a pretty much a full uber by killing a medic with the uber saw do you
always go over saw nine times out of ten just because there's so many
opportunities to just hit somebody and get 25 free percent uber if I'm not
using the uber saw that I'm using the what is it called the one where you taunt
what's it called can't think about amputator the amputator yeah there it is
all right I got an uber all right I'm on the last point yeah I'm standing on the
second to last point right now all right behind you all right let's see if we can
do this do you have any suggestion which way we should go where's the century up
top yeah I actually don't really know fast lane that much oh god I just lost
you I'm sir all right let's uh all the kind sir that I'm doing it looks like
they got another century on point let's try to take that out at range and I
think this guy's got a crit screen as well so oh boy I'm all right I'm good
crap oh god I gotta back up back burner yeah that pyro just kind of ran in me
and Xbox might get this though oh bam oh they're in better factor they're in bad
water right now hot water oh god never mind you know what that century is in a
spot where you get out yeah we have to get pretty close it's right in the corner
yeah we're doing work me and X pocket doing work two centuries up here Jesus
you know maybe it'll be good and maybe you should uh switch the demo a good
point long almost got this all right these are two both down up here another
one below come on son really oh you know what I'm gonna I'm gonna switch demo we
got three medics right now oh son it's down it's down it's down nice one point
oh here we go another one no come on you're kidding me all right push oh we
almost have it looks like mr. pan slice are doing work go go go go go come on
shibs oh Gabe's doing work we got this we got this where's that century oh he's
trying to move it up top he's trying to move it up here oh no he's not gonna get
it okay there's so many guys oh wow this is an absolute battle oh teleporter
and centuries down oh teleporter was there that's weird we just got to get a
mass push and get on there oh this soldier is in this top room got him nice
so what they have four centuries I got something I'm up there too trying to
spam it down wherever it is trying to look and see it looks like it's in the
right corner oh yeah I see it oh this he engineers aren't even there oh son it's
like the game crashed oh you got a game crash yeah yeah I'll protect you coming
back all right we still we're still up here oh keep the hills up oh no Fox
McCloud Fox McCloud when AFK in the milk oh get out of here medic this guy this
guy's just kind of standing here too I'm on the point we're gonna win let's get
it we got it game over I think multiple yeah a lot of people just crashed I'm
looking at the at this everyone just kind of started freezing and standing
still so that's what happened everyone crashed