Okay, I am back and I am ready to play some Armored Core.
Somebody asked, is this your first Armored Core game? The answer is yes.
And I know. Don't play it like Dark Souls. I know they made this game. Don't play it like Dark Souls.
I know you're going to try and you're going to get frustrated. I promise I will not.
How does this look? So this is a controller game, right?
Everything I've read that this is a controller game. I still want to beat Final Fantasy 16.
I don't know what made me think of that. Oh no, my headphone plug is messed up.
Okay, keyboard is better. Controller, controller. I don't know. Let's try it.
Okay, let me see. Can you see it? You should see it.
Hey, there it is. I'm not playing online. I figured that's probably not.
I usually don't play any of these games online. Alright, new game.
That looks good. That's fine. Okay, that's fine.
Pilot name. I want it to be a surprise. I'm going to make sure you don't see it.
Because I want it to be a surprise. It's probably a cutscene.
Am I going to like this game? It's eating a lot of nos.
Open mind. Open mind, guys. Come on.
More Sekiro than Souls. It's very loud. You are so fucked, dude.
Yeah, I've heard all the people compare it. This is what I've been told.
This is a different video game. This is not a Souls game.
So I'm going to treat it like a completely different video game.
It's a completely different franchise. It doesn't have that From Software crispiness.
That we're all used to. Let's find out.
Looks really good.
Okay. Commence mission. Yep, move.
That feels fun to play.
Okay, so it's a toggle.
And that's a jump. And you hold to go up.
Got it.
How do I turn the gas off?
Okay.
Oh.
What's wrong with my weapon?
How do I reload? Is there a manual reload?
Okay.
Okay, so it's lock on.
Yeah, lock on. Got it.
Hold on.
I get it.
Okay.
Okay, so hold this.
Whoa. Okay, that's a slash.
Do I have anything on left bumper?
Okay.
What is that?
It just started moving. It kind of just started moving on its own.
Rollercoaster tracks?
I'm sorry. I couldn't see what you wrote. You were banned.
I can't read your message. Something with it.
Okay. I get it so far.
Okay.
Quick boost. Instantly accelerate in any direction, helping you to evade attacks or swiftly close in.
Alright, so it's X as a dash.
Cool. I think a lot of people thought I was going to die there, so I win.
It doesn't seem like there is a map.
Okay.
Oh, that's what happened. Okay.
That's what happened last time. I was like, why am I moving automatically?
Let's go. Alright. Gotta make it all the way over there.
I've never played any of these games before. No, not as of until right now.
Fun. Okay. There's no timer or anything, right?
No, there's not. He did play Metal Wolf. I did play Metal Wolf. It's true.
Oh, shit. I'm out of gas. How do I turn the gas off?
It's B? Okay. Yep. That's my favorite move so far. I like that one a lot.
The normal boost does not drain energy. That's good to know.
Okay. License code Monkey Gordo. License code extracted from an AC wreck
in the contaminated city. Contains the pilot's registration data.
Cool. So this is essentially a fast travel.
No, it's a salt boost. Right, right. You know what I mean.
Does everything reload automatically?
Yes. Alright, good. That's all I needed to know.
Alright, where we at? Down there. You can also reload it faster.
You can manually reload the rifle.
G7 Chakra. License expires in 12 hours.
I like the flying.
License expired. Somebody said you should
use the B type control scheme. It's way better. Is it?
I feel like I could get used to this. It's just personal preference.
Type B. Quick boost is right trigger.
A is boost. I think they're the same.
Okay. No, I much prefer it like this.
All the trigger buttons are weapons to me.
Alright, where am I going? Can I upgrade that?
First thing I'm upgrading. I want that to last much longer.
Oh, shit. That's a bad idea. It's all about moving, moving, moving, moving, moving.
30%. That's it? I didn't know that was ammo.
Are you going to get filtered by this game so hard?
What does that mean? I've not heard that term before. That's a new
From Software Armored Core 6 term that you're using. What is that?
You're going to get filtered. What does that mean?
Does that mean that I cannot? There's like a gamer filter on this game
where it filters out all the non-gamers because what if I can't beat the first
boss and I get filtered? Is that what it means?
I haven't even gotten through the tutorial yet. You guys are already
saying things that are going to happen on this stream before they've even happened.
You've already placed the bets already. I'm going to do just fine.
Vertical catapult. This game is harder than Elden Ring. I'm sure it probably
has a different category. Here comes the first tutorial boss.
I'm going to get filtered because I'm not good enough. This is definitely a boss
area. Look at it. Does it make the From Software bird noise though?
That's the main question. That sounds like the TikTok
filter. That sounds like the guy on TikTok that's the TTF.
I got filtered.
I get it. I'll get it this time. I got three heals now.
Here we go. It's all about getting up close. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Damn it. It's alright. Back it up. I'm alright.
I'm fine.
Second try. Is that alright? Did I do good? Did I beat it?
That was fun. Gamers are flipping their desks right now.
This is a raven? I can see how that would be really
difficult. You can die in one hit by those bombs if you don't avoid them.
Chat losing to a retired streamer.
Just because I'm a little older doesn't mean I still got it sometimes.
That was enjoyable.
I had a lot of fun doing that.
How come you sound so sarcastic?
Do I? I don't know. I'm just kind of chilling. I don't mean to.
It's a little low. I'll turn it up.
The whole point of this game is you upgrade and change out here, right?
I'm into that part
for sure.
You can paint it?
I took the idea.
Don't get tied to
one build. Always change it to adapt.
Okay.
Change the title? What is the title right now?
Design? Okay. Design.
Assembly. Oh boy, that's a lot of information.
Customize AC assemblies using the parts you have available at the assembly menu.
Maximum weight.
I like this weapon a lot.
I don't think I can change this. I can take it off.
Definitely don't want to take it off.
Oh jeez, that's a lot.
I'm going to keep it simple for now.
I can read those numbers at the bottom.
We'll stick with that.
I could spend all day here.
That means I'm angry.
Decals.
What do I have for regular decals?
You can just deck yourself out in a bunch of memes.
That's kind of fun.
This is all for another time.
Create images for use. Manage AC assembly appearance settings.
Save and load. You can save each one.
Missions. Training.
Check incoming jobs and sortie on missions from the missions menu.
This is $100,000. This is $68,000.
Destroy artillery installations. Do the training first.
Land shots on moving enemies.
You must pull the trigger while they are within lock-on range.
They have to be in the range.
They have to be in the circle.
Weapons with magazines will automatically reload when the magazine's ammunition is depleted.
Manually reload before engaging the enemy to minimize the risk that your attacks will be interrupted by a reload.
That's Y plus RT.
Missile lock.
To use missiles in other homing rounds, keep the enemy on screen until lock-on completes, then fire.
Missile weapons are capable of multi-lock.
You can cancel it.
Those all went over there.
Melee weapons.
You can charge it.
You have to fill up that meter.
I'm imagining some stuff does way more stagger damage.
The machine gun probably doesn't do very much stagger damage.
There's a Hitman 3 vision mode.
Melee weapons do a lot of stagger.
Slashing twice.
The new machine gun.
Less attack power.
I could put it on the other arm.
The bar is increasing.
I'll try it.
Is that it for the training?
Which one of these is a good mission for me to try?
Let's go to this one.
Let's go slowly.
I like in the middle of that.
Have a good one.
Destroy all Rubicon Liberation Front artillery installations.
I think I'm just good.
You get more money for more things you kill.
I'll just fly around and splash some stuff.
Destroy all the stuff.
Does time matter?
Time to finish.
Watch for the boost.
Much time is lost.
Easy.
This game gets very fun.
Especially when you upgrade.
oh excuse me excuse me that's a lot of shit over there all right I gotta be
careful that's too much stuff all right turn let's chill out for a sec all right
here we go oh ouch ow ow ow I'm stuck on the fucking thing what's
happening oh it's a good thought one more that's it right oh all right cool I
just win 120,000 so the missions are kind of snappy then yeah I that's my
favorite part about the game so far stuff is just snappy
registration number RB call sign Raven your return to mercenary activities has
been acknowledged restoring access to the it's got some from software
equipment a crisp crispness I can't even talk it does have that from software
crispness new training I who first rifle and gun sounds kind of fun bazooka
though all right back power huge on the bazooka Christmas in August honestly I
feel like that's the kind of weapon I would like to use there's only one how
many shots is it six seven hundred total rounds 105 I think I'm gonna buy the
bazooka oh there it is recoil this thing is probably just really good for
finishing stuff off I'm getting the bazooka well there's so much more all
right what it wait wait wait I need simplified info first rifle this is the
other hand the other hand right now has the slash on it I don't know if I want
to replace that although an assault rifle would be amazing mmm that would be
good too I think I want this I already have one of these though don't I all
right we're going bazooka on right hand oh I can't okay no back in it you need
one for each hand ah okay that makes sense I'm gonna get it I feel like
having a big bazooka and then having the be able to finish it off with the
machine gun is good give it a try I don't have a sword anymore but right
different missile launcher pulse shield another missile oh I can do double
missile launcher that would be awesome what about the shield what does this do
okay so just blocks a bunch of it just block all damage or it's a Perry it's
hard it's Perry I'll just do double missile launcher yeah let's go why not
this is a left bumper right okay there was some new training which I'm gonna do
because I want the item charge attacks oh wow okay this thing is disgusting how
many shots does this have four needs to be reloaded got 12 all right what about
what happened to my wait a minute what's going on here why is it giving me this
stuff oh it's gonna teach me how to do this attitude control system of a craft
can be compromised by accumulating strain from the impact of repeated
attacks so this is the stagger system so when you get that overloaded you get
into stagger yep that's what I figured it was doing during which time the
afflicted craft will be immobilized and susceptible to critical damage so once
you get that stagger that's when you just unload everything during stagger
all incoming attacks are treated as direct hits and deal much more damage
okay so you just there okay how long does it last for not very long honestly
yeah I think I get it oops uh ACS strain afflicted with it on enemies
resets after a brief interval but a portion of that strain will remain
weapons vary in the amount of accumulative strain they inflict with
explosive impact generally leaving the most okay that's quite the strain so
this is the boss killer that you need to do this to kill bosses surprise attacks
acts on enemies that are unaware of your presence will inflict greater strain
okay so they're off they're unaware of you oh they're not aware it does do a
lot more shield equipped to the left shoulder can be deployed to reduce
incoming damage from ACA ACS strain what's the charge on it so you can do
it pretty much instantly by doing it wrong it overheats shield output is
maximized for one to two seconds after deployment blocking during the initial
guard window can help to minimize incoming damage all right so it is a
parry okay so one two pop I get it cool although I don't have a shield on right
now they don't take very much damage in the front of their shield oh I skipped
that shit what did that mean I skipped that what did that say attack while
assault boosted all right got it yep I think I was doing that before though
attack well assault boosted gives you more stagger ah linear rifle let's check
it Oh just the regular rifle other arm though probably right no what is it I'm
gonna keep what I got that's the tutorial gun it's one you just used in
store okay I see all the charge one all right I actually really like that but
we'll test this out for now I like it
I think it's good it gets better and better down the line missions get better
and better how many okay so here's a here's a question how many bosses are in
the game are there like there's a lot cuz I love bosses bosses is my favorite
part about any of the from software games now I know this is not Dark Souls
I know I'm that I was told don't do that is a boss battles a big part of this
game yes okay play the game and find out all right let's go so I got a new weapon
sure let me can I test it it's one shot and then it reloads what about this one
it's just a machine gun I got the double launcher now it's just cool let's see
what happens oh that was a good shot shit I'm trying to hit him with there we
go all right cool cool cool cool cool cool I like doing the double bomb look
at that cool all right they come boost is still on wait for reloads let's go
enemy shields analyzed I can't believe I lost to this oh don't fall anybody else
oh I did it kind of reminds me of EDF a little bit is that accurate a little bit
when is the next EDF coming out it's out in Japan right now right
he's streaming tonight because he wants to advertise the you twos I actually
haven't even done that thanks for reminding me I just I like thanks for
the thanks for the reminder access log hunt you've been invited to join log
hunt one of all mines mercenary support programs okay I got more money and gone
on the right side now you can do double handgun wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait what is this pulse shield no I know what that is I can put
a different head on incorporates only the most essential functionality with a
minimalist build in keeping with the fangs stout tree slender branches
philosophy it's really loud light oh Jesus Christ I did not know you oh okay
it's not just it's everything I get it so you end up making your favorite
spore monster right you put the legs on you put the arms on okay but most
importantly what does this do for me right now if I were to do that lose a
ton of stability lose a ton of recovery lose a bunch of AP I don't think I'm
gonna mess around with this right now defense and speed press Y on it more
explosive defense scan duration is up anti-explosive defense speed boost is
better load better stop overwhelming him it mostly just means light yeah I'm
not gonna do that right now but I am going to do this I'm going to save my
money destroy targets destroy enemy AC let's do that transport helicopter one
the important part is actually the legs you can sell items for the same price
you bought them for anything you're not using I'm gonna stick with what I got
okay destroy targets destroy all the Rubicon liberation front logistics
helicopters I like this game because it's telling me just very direct
instructions kill that thing with the blue target on it I can do that you've
given me four buttons and they just kill that thing right there I'm gonna love
this game whoo very nice all right eat another chopper hang on for a sec you
watch out hit it yes ready to reload you do not need to change targets for
the multi lock ah oh I took too much damage there that was stupid all right
let me wait till my stacker goes down I'd let off steam or something I guess
flash damage to oops gotta go in the air oh oh all right I'm starting I'm getting
to feel for it I understand what's going on I think it's really hard damn all
right that wasn't even the target that was optional oh it's fun cool combat
logs give parts should I be looking for those I feel like I haven't scanned the
game once that's a new menu optional mini bosses like that give you logs got
you training I like that yeah I like you can replay missions as many times as you
want that's a good feature this might be really stupid but I'm kind of into it
I'm doing double bazooka I would probably use this very well the missiles
are fun to use okay I have enough to unlock a new head this one is more
stability more recovery this is the stir one right this is the one that stirs
playing with right now and then there's this one lightweight so I know I have
this down to the very very bare bones reduced menu but what is a P stability
and recovery I'm imagining is how I get that one what is stability in AP AP is
health and then what is stability armor Oh resilience okay resilience of the
part maximum load doesn't really help oh okay it's kind of it's like a tech
armor this is the posture so this is health posture and then healing
essentially poise our this is status all right that's a very simplified version
of it I definitely think I want the one that has more health I'm gonna do this
one that's a big increase we have a we have a germ a logo oh okay maybe I'll
put it on maybe yeah maybe I'll put it on that sounded so that was like a I did
not mean for that to come out the way that that did all right no I I think I'm
gonna keep playing this game although I did say that for Final Fantasy 16 but
you know we'll see I really I need to play Final Fantasy I really was into it
too I'm getting this one and I'm putting it on so this is heavier but it's a lot
more defense and in health is what I want the head is just for fashion to be
honest okay yeah I don't know much longer I'm gonna be streaming for I
planned on like three or four hours tonight
the Zooka strat is gonna go down oh it's not good for this we're never
seeing this again hi I would not say that I'll tell you one reason why I said
that for Final Fantasy 16 but let me give you a reason why I think that this
would you would say this again I can open a mission and be done with it in
ten minutes I can open up mission and lose ten times in a row and then move to
something else these are very digestible missions I'll go back to training I
already did him right what about the logo oh shit forgot about the logo I am
going to be decked out in decals the next time you see me play this I will
use that one I'm putting that right on my chest okay destroy the tester AC over
there end up as a NASCAR mech see that's funny too just have a bunch of okay like
sandwich chains all over me all right this is that wait a minute unaware watch
this wait you jumped out oh okay okay oh that hurt tried to be fancy there and I
was a mistake oh it's so slow did I get it or did I die oh I got it that's kind
of sad that was sad that was a student driver oh shit what's wrong with you
what I was told to oh am I on the wrong I'm on the bad team we're not on what on
the good team I thought we were good guys you have to ask am I on the bad
team you are on the bad team that's very true
you just want money that's it hmm new parts what I get something I want to buy
a new body oh that's I can get this new booster I'll get it where does that go
here this is the new one so this is a much heavier but I get a lot more thrust
I'll try it back the damn complex destroy the weaponized mining ship these
are very expensive this looks like a boss do the logo oh okay I'll do the logo
how do I do this image editor image downloader where is it decals in the
image editor okay there's a download tab don't see it with a black screen sorry
oh I'm not online I'll get it I'll get it for the next one I have I've okay now
I see why you wanted me to be online oops there we go I'm not online I'm in
offline mode go get online now I 100% guarantee 100% guarantee that you will
see this streamed a second time that is a 100% guarantee you said that about
Breath of the Wild I played Breath of the Wild again it's like Street Fighters 6
just like Yakuza 0 you said you were gonna finish Breath of the Wild by May
yeah May May of 2022 it was like May of last year wasn't it Wow
oh well it's okay all right attack the base destroy the infrastructure this is
for a lot of money you also said the three stooges were gonna be in fortnight
that was a good call though you cannot tell me what they've put in that game in
the last couple of years that I that was a bad call allies double missiles thank
you got it I get them both good shot dude I'm loving the double missiles
it's great I'm gonna up the up this way somebody's door is open in the car who
said double bazooka was bad show yourself last one both my allies alive
oh shit here we go all right get that stagger oh that was a lot of damage good
oh I'm out of boost oh that was a lot of damage nice
oh they all missed I don't think any of your missiles hit I'm on it oh that's
sad I want to get more money hundred and hey wait my expenses I have expenses
41 that seems like a lot that seems like a lot to spend on ammo you're using a
lot of missiles and a lot of bazookas it's alright I'll with that kind of
firepower I'm happy being broke that's okay emblem acquired did I unlock some
new stuff okay I can afford something now hold on how much at 149 I can get new
legs firearms specialization is that that's a huge increase what does that
one do prove target tracking performance okay actually might want that that's
kind of good right or what I have a double missile that's right all these
wait there I thought there was legs okay we're okay we're okay we're okay we're
okay I'll try this one out all right this seems like a boss destroy the boss
I'll give it a go okay
yeah can you yep can you yep can you
can you just put a blue target on it and I'll do everything else I don't need to
hear any other things give me caveman mode give me food mode this kind of is
caveman mode that's why I like it so much all right destroy the ship I
understand that first well that's big oh that's good tracking what does that
sound that was scary okay all right I see I see I get it I get it I see what's
happening that didn't work I thought I could dodge that is it a simple dodge
Wow there's no I frames okay all right all right be careful I don't have any
health fucking rock that's gonna land on me right that's much further away than I
thought it was I need I need boost all right no okay I'm fine I'm gonna go up
first what is happening something's shooting at me all right really that
does not want me over there it's one oh I'm not doing this right get up there
shit oh god damn it I know I'm or I'm so I'm too deep here though I just do it
just go all the way back I just didn't want to go all the way back this way I'm
too far away from that now I'll be fine just wait I got it I got it I got it I
got it I've never ever seen anybody fail this before well I was hey I'd beat the
first boss in two tries you didn't that that required movement and shit I want
the money I know it's expensive I don't care I want the money what the okay
plagued with greed I would have had it that last time it's just I didn't realize
I had to climb up the back of the fucking elephants legs or whatever the
hell it is okay here it comes all right all right all right here it comes I get
it now okay everybody relax we're good all right here we go hey here we go now
it's time here we go that should do it right all right now climb the back the
bigger they are the harder they fall hey I did it hold on let me get some juice
where are you who's shooting at me no no turn the boost off turn the boost off
it's flying me around there it is oh shit all right I got to get in there and
shoot this okay hold up right here I'm gonna go up oh my god oh that's a
fucking Sauron I oh my god I have to get the fuck out of here I have to get the
fuck out of here okay hold on hold on hold on oh is it alive shit just fucking
flew into the goddamn wall all right just one more it's underneath um where
is it though I'm gonna get lost oh shit no no no no no no no no no no no no no
what the fuck does happen what just happened okay okay
no stop moving for a second it's just I'm already in the air all right get me
up dude how the fuck am I gonna get over there okay I gotta I gotta be on
my mark here what okay we're fine what's up what's up bud am I doing any damage
wow it's not good oh god damn it this one's hard this one's hard because it's
a lot of traversing a ton of area and I hate that floating in the air to get to
another ledge in these games make it makes me want to throw up wait check
point oh that's better I'm gonna die right now oh no no no no I refuse
alrighty boost any boost back oh just die already oh my god I'm gonna die
here okay I might not have the best equipment for this guy but I'll get it
stay really close I think that's the strategy get back it close close close
close close close close okay all right we're good we're good we're good we're
good we're good that one was that one was pretty hard that was fun get me the
fuck away from this thing see you later punk or how do I emote all right two
hundred and seventy thousand dollars in pay with sixty two thousand dollars in
expenses thirty six thousand dollars all right that's where they get you they get
you with the repair costs that's fun though I'm surprised there's checkpoints
that seems pretty new to uh although this is not Dark Souls but you're gonna
need them later oh what the fuck Dark Souls guys made this I will say I feel
like the from software devs are so talented and they've done so many
interesting things do you think that when people say that all Dark Souls the
Dark Souls guys that's like when people come here and say that oh it's the guy
it's the sus guy and it's the ball up his ass guy I do more than that being
the sus guy is not like Dark Souls that was not a good comparison you just
equated yourself to from soft no no I am NOT even nearly as talented I don't hold
I don't have even a fingernail of talent on the from software devs but I can do
this I don't think very many people can do that that scared this shit out of me
all right that's uh that's gonna be it I'm gonna call it here only plan to be
in life for like four hours or so but I will tell you I wait this thing is
$200,000 and I want it it can charge we'll play again okay we're gonna play
this again that's it for today yeah let me let's let's uh let me shout out this
you twos one more time let me show you the boxes sure you will I will I will I
actually had a lot of fun playing this and I think I could probably get halfway
through so the you twos are on sale right now they're they're in pre-order
they're available for the next two weeks to pre-order after that collection is
going to close so you got just almost exactly two weeks from me saying this
right now about 13 and 14 days if you want them they're there and I can show
you here take a look they're very cute I must say not just because it's me on
there right let me show you yeah they are well here the here the boxes these
are the you twos boxes you got Jerma dollhouse Jerma and then umpire
Albertson Jerma put them on your reddit shelf you have one they're available
right now anniversary of the dollhouse and anniversary of the baseball stream
both in the last week that is you twos comm slash collections slash Jerma
pretty cool well I can show them one more time yeah available for two weeks
they're currently on sale right now they are I'll hold them buck I'll hold them
up one more time there check them out this is probably some of the last merch
you'll ever see of me like I told you as we do this kind of soft retirement arc
yeah thanks you twos for whatever partnering together or however you want
to say it it's more of a you're making it and it's pretty cool they are
available and they will be available until two weeks from right now and then
I think it's gonna take a month or so before they start shipping out I might
bring it up a week or so from now but you guys get it they're available you
can talk about it maybe a week or two from now when it's almost over they are
available see you later that is the end of the stream almost exactly no it's
more than four hours that was a really fun stream though thanks for poke thanks
to poke for being a good sport that was really fun doing the weird stream
inception thing appreciate it poke thanks for the game recommendation to
again was a lot of fun if you came over here from pokes channel during all that
maybe we'll see you again another time next time you see me live will probably
be later on the end of this week keep an eye on the sus I will come in probably
Wednesday or Thursday to update it imagining either probably Friday or
Sunday is where I'm thinking but not set in stone just keep an eye on the sus I
will update it at least a couple days in advance and we are gonna be playing
sorcery part 4 and to continue that playthrough whether it's Friday or
Sunday and then after that it's kind of up in the air we'll see times yeah good
times I know you're a game pass Andy are we gonna be playing starfield I will
definitely stream starfield at least once just because I feel like it's gonna
be one of those games that you're gonna have to play just because of how many
options of things there might be to do I would imagine if after sorcery I don't
really know what else to play we're just gonna play this I was a little concerned
opening it thinking hold on this might not be for me I think it is for me I
think it is very much for me so you are going to see armored core 6 again I had
a great time playing it I'd like to continue playing it I am gonna need your
help though I'm not gonna pretend like I'm gonna do this all on my own I'm
gonna be looking for help especially if I get stuck be feel free backseat when
when it's necessary what about Baldur's Gate 3 I think I'm gonna play Baldur's
Gate 3 on my own that's kind of a game I'd like to play just not being on
stream you'd love it I probably will Vinny is playing a duck game is Vinny
play wait is Vinny playing that duck game or a different one there's a lot of
duck games I'm not sure which one you mean Vinny's going to bed oh is he oh is
poke streaming still or no let me see I'll dump you guys on poke if he's still
alive focus okay yeah go say hi to poke say that was fun saying that say that
was fun you're a good sport with a thumbs up or a happy emote I will see
you guys later see you at the end of the week take care of yourselves see you
soon good night call your mother see you later