Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here with a Battlefield 3 video.
My first ever Battlefield 3 video and it happens to be with somebody very very special.
I'm playing with iPoneStar4Hire. This is all going to be a live commentary, just kind of us messing around in Conquest.
Just a small series of clips I put together all live, like I said, us just having a good time, messing around.
I'm a total noob at this game. This is like the first or second time I've actually really sat down to play the game.
So keep that in mind when you're watching these clips I guess.
The live commentary should be coming in right about now.
One down. Oh my god!
I'm just like, this is pretty much like Jerma follows PoneStar and watches him destroy everything.
I'm down for that. They do.
Whoa, is that us or is that not us?
I don't know.
That's not us, that's not us.
That's not us.
That is definitely not us.
I got the T-90, I don't even know what that is.
It's got like, pillows on the back of it.
Alright, do you want me to just spawn or spawn on it?
Spawn back to the cocktail. I'm going to fucking take that tank out.
He's coming behind us, behind us.
Oh fuck!
We got away.
He's still coming after us I think.
Bitch, let's go swimming.
Oh my god. Are we really going that way?
We're going swimming, man.
There's a letter over here, we gotta go capture our letters.
This game is ridiculous.
There's so many letters in the alphabet, I'm just used to seeing A, B, or C, or A, B.
They go up to F in Battlefield?
G? Are you kidding me?
That's cool.
You gotta go back and forth, it's like going crazy on these.
We start at F and we go backwards.
I gotcha, I gotcha.
I don't know how smart it is to walk prone backwards with your nuts on the concrete.
Should we be expecting people to come from one of these areas?
I don't know, I don't play Conquest.
I can't fly, oh fuck, what's going on?
I think I just stepped on a piece of wood or some bubble wrap.
Oh shit, it's happening again.
Where is he?
Somebody's shooting at us.
Dude, the bubble wrap assassin, where is he?
It's a sniper, it's a sniper.
I really am legit scared right now.
I'm more scared right now than I have been in Resident Evil.
Hold me.
Dude, he's gonna get one of us in a couple seconds and we're gonna be toast.
Oh shit.
Why am I shooting at it?
I'm just hiding.
Where are you?
I'm coming, I'm coming, hold on.
No, no, he got me.
Oh god, dude.
No, they're gonna take our G back.
No, I don't want to die.
Wait, it says I suicided.
I just got RPG'd in the water.
Wait, so what if I just shoot him?
What if I just shoot him over and over again?
I will save you.
I'm just literally firing at the tank over and over again.
I got my knife out, I'm gonna charge him.
Look here.
Hold on, hold on, I'm throwing a grenade.
Grenade, out.
It landed on it.
Imagine if it just took it out.
Stay alive, I'm gonna C4, I'm gonna come back in and C4 this.
Wait, I can revive you.
No, there's not enough time, I'm dead.
And you're about to be too.
I'm just gonna throw health at him.
You're gonna throw health at him?
Oh shit, I'm about to get ran over.
What are these guys doing?
Oh man, we're making the...
Kaboom.
Why am I climbing a ladder and there's nothing up here?
Look at this.
I climbed a ladder with nothing, you're climbing it too.
What is going on?
What is this?
Hey, the suburb.
Here's a little Humvee, you wanna go get in it and look like a boss?
Here, I'm gonna get in it and you get in it too.
You can drive it and cap shit.
Oh shit.
Just a good time to let you know I don't have my license.
So what, are we just like...
This is really uncomfortable.
I'm in the driver's seat, I look to my left, I see a flag.
I look to my right and all I can see is your crotch.
Grandpa crotch.
What? Yep.
Why are we the only one capturing flags?
I know, I mean really.
Look at the...
Wait, where is he?
I'm going the other way, I'm not going at it.
Look at the scoreboard.
Me and you are number one and two and we've done absolutely like nothing.
Besides like, well we took out that tank.
Oh shit.
Oh dude, it's bumper cars.
Oh come on.
Oh dude, you're gonna make me sick.
I got this.
Sit there and wait for him.
Wait, I'll back that ass up.
I don't think he's coming.
Are you getting points on this? Yeah, I think so.
I'll leave you here. Wait what?
Where are you going? I got you.
Get that guy.
How is he not dead?
I'm out of bullets.
Fuck you. I ran through him.
Oh my god.
Oh shit, here it is.
Watch this shit, yo.
Alright, I'm watching, let's see this.
Run like fuck.
Yeah.
That was awesome.
So where are you?
Where did you go?
You'll find me on the floor in pieces.
He's on a roof.
Who the fuck is on a roof?
There I come with the paddles.
You got enough? You got enough time? Hurry up.
Oh shit, he's on this roof up here.
There he is.
Smoke him.
Suck it big boy.
Up here they're taking our D flag.
Not for long.
I hear big guns. I don't know if that's ours or theirs.
I think we have a tank now.
I don't know if that's particularly ours.
Shoot the guy in the gunner seat.
Don't lure him.
He's dead. The guy in the gunner seat is dead.
Oh man.
That was awesome.
Where's my body?
Oh my god, Jesus.
You fell with the rail with your face first and grinded that shit.
Dude, that was like a montage worthy clip right there that you just did.
That is going to wrap up this video guys.
Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
Hopefully in the next couple of weeks I can get better at Battlefield 3.
But yeah, we'll see where that goes.
Take care everybody.
I will see you all soon.