Hey, what's up? How you doing? You guys tweet? Yeah, I'm tweeting. I gotta make sure people
pee. I gotta make sure people know what's going on. My fan's not even on. What the heck did you do
to me? You beaten Margit yet? No, and I don't know. Like once enough people come here, we'll talk
about it for a minute. This is Elden. This is like my 12th or like 14th. This is like at least number
12 Elden rank streams. And sometimes you just kind of have to understand the games like not for you.
I mean we're about like 100 hours into the game and I still have not. This is the first boss, right?
I just don't get it. I don't understand like the dodging and shit. And I tried to summon, I've
summoned like three people to come in but they always like die because I always just kind of
watch because I don't really know how to play. I don't know. I'm gonna try it one more time.
But I mean there's only so many times. I think I've died 1,600 times to Margit. I mean I feel
like that's not that like high. It's like a hard game. Only like 40% of people that
downloaded the game even bought that and killed that boss, okay? I've looked at the steam
achievement. Like 50% or something have killed Margit. So I mean it's a hard fucking game.
You got it this time. I'll try, I'll do it one more time.
You know where Newfoundland is? I don't know. I think so. That's a weird question. You're still
on the tree sentinel. You know though if you're okay if you are stuck on the tree sentinel for
like five days I don't even know if I would be too upset about that. That means you you're going to
be able to play Elden Ring for the next like five years of your life. You will get to slowly
experience this game for a half a decade. You'll be able to put it down and pick it up at random times
until you have children. And I'll be honest this game is so long I feel like if you just put
a few hours into this game every like four or five days or something it will take you a year or two
to beat this game. So that's that's just extra content you get to have because the game is good
as smite. Well I mean hold on I don't want to be I don't want to be like just handing out like
game of the decade awards right? We have to be careful because we have one.
All right let's go let's fucking go. I just spent the first like five minutes of this stream
I think I don't like gaslighting everybody I don't know why. There's no sound? I got it got it. So um
I might not be in the same position I was last stream because I was doing uh Polly's been playing
and we did co-op stuff. Something I didn't know about Elden Ring I don't I've never done like
co-op in any of Souls games. Um we we're getting invaded every one second after I we would summon
each other if you're like oh let's go explore like the lands between honey oh that sounds like this
person there and then just to kill us what the fuck we did kill a few invasions only happen in
co-op oh use a password we did I swear to god we did it was like okay here I am my summoning sign
I would like I would just barely phase into the world and they would be within 15 seconds somebody
else would be doing the same thing and then it's just like oh fuck here we go and you either get
rid of the person or you get embarrassed a password doesn't do anything for invasions don't use one
two three four what the fuck one two three four five is a secure password it's sequential it's
easy to remember it's very acable one two that's got to be I would feel I don't know I would feel
naked if I had a password that was one two three four five somewhere you know what I mean I would
feel awful every day every day wouldn't you feel awful I would just be like like especially if it
was like oh hey dude I bet you you won't go one week having one two three four five as your bank
password every moment of every second of every single day I'd be like looking at my phone like
dude nobody got it right nobody got in no fucking way did you play it as a me strong no okay then
you have to start okay then you have to start making new passwords because oh somebody just
said oh I usually do like a similar password and add numbers at the end so do you just do
one two three four five six seven oh no I remember one two three four five but like I got to add
something to this one two three four five six seven eight nine I would that would be so confusing
because if you do that enough times all of your passwords are a sequence of one through some
number and how are you ever supposed to keep track of that it's impossible anyways I played
a little co-op with Holly and we got invaded like five times I was like all right that's fun
it's cool though we did well it was one part we get to kind of walk around for like 20 minutes
was fun but voice is junk and I know that's the way it is but I was doing the giant area
there's a few things I can do that are not in the giant area what is it what is it what's
her character uh she I believe she's faith dex or faith faith arcane she's doing the dragon stuff
which holy shit those spells are fucking ridiculous those spells are insane
the big like dragon head that breathes like the dust that stuff whoa now that's cool
dragon spells are awesome man but anyways uh I was gonna continue this is where I was going to go
I know that I have to get the other half of the medallion I know I know I'll and I can I ask a
question thank you um peach teacher can I go to this place right here and not like end the game
yes cherubi you won't be locked out okay I got it because this looks like
that looks very important whatever that is so that's what we're gonna go we're gonna go to one
then we're gonna go to four and then we're gonna go to bar two very excited I feel like we're
getting we're gonna get some hopefully get some big deep lore bits it does change things you don't
get locked out of the game until the last boss well let's go let's go do it let's go to one
a little advice for elderly people you can hit the b or circle button that enables you to
run thanks appreciate it that's pretty cool uh that's pretty cool tactic let's go to one
yeah I looked at this area it was like these are giants that may have the red bar is your health
oh I thought that was my satan meter what's happening what's behind me
oh what I hear okay I know I did hear some what the fuck is happening
they're fighting the giant oh no do I help them I think you can handle it
I'm gonna help them I helped I'm gone oh god damn it all right I didn't that's a church
can I I think these might be the hardest enemy in the game what the fuck why do you have the
horse why am I off the horse this is the hardest enemy I think this is the toughest enemy in the
game I got invaded bloody finger this is what it felt like playing with Holly last night
yesterday whatever it was this is what it felt like volcano how about this fucking freezing mist
well bro without the r bye oh oh by the way by the way everybody you might have noticed some
spells I got some spells I all right shut up and play okay listen I went and got I fixed my spell
thing I had a bunch of useless spells I was trying to prepare for the stream I didn't play offline
well I didn't play offline I prepared offline these fingernails need to go because they're
fucking up I they're bumping into each other there's like a little too long and I might just
clip them on stream okay I cleaned up my inventory I didn't play off stream I prepared off stream
all right this time I'm not going to be an idiot and go attack the birds that are attacking that
giant prepare better I think I did I had 200 souls it doesn't matter okay here we go all right
invade me again this time there's not two or three giant birds attacking me they are probably the
hardest enemy in the game they're the tankiest they have the most powerful move set they're
crazy all right just do it let's go your headphones go to ice mist does this move do anything
like I mean I guess I kind of hurt him for a second damn it that fucking hurts
all right no I don't care about spells anymore I'm just gonna fight the guy nice dodge I haven't
played in a while all right I gotta get back into this I was busy getting invaded all right all right
let's go ice this sucks what a fucking shitty move it's coming off yeah I like I turn the
air conditioning on a little bit higher in one area of the room that's who cares that doesn't
do anything you're playing a bimbo ice mage build I know I'm not this is a bimbo ice build
come on guys don't forget to post who just had like a million health it's somebody just took like
5 000 damage what was that did you see that okay I'm not fucking around anymore we're gonna
this person eat the shit out of them here we go the more I storm god damn it this fucking move
oh my god I had him too well I don't why did I start doing swift glint stone it was to make
you guys think I was doing more than I needed to do I've asked me I'll be honest I was fighting them
perfectly normally and I was winning and then I switched to swift glyphs glint glint stone shard
and was like wham wham wham like I was doing a fucking like harry potter fight with this person
like don't I don't have to do that I don't have to like make like a scene like a cinematic scene
for you like ice stone shard like no fucking kill the guy I don't have to do that for some
reason my brain was like yo make it a little cinematic for him no I don't care I'm gonna kill
him I'm done with this I'm just gonna I'm going to attack them I don't care about the cinematic
experience I don't know why I did swift glint stone shard it was to be cinematic
use the swift glint stone shard whatever all right when I have I cast a spell besides
someone wears the ice storm this guy's tough oh get zoned oh somebody get zoned huh
oh David oh my god I gotta fucking kill this guy before this is my mind I'm I wasn't doing
that for cinematic purposes I was doing that because I thought it was gonna be able to cheese
it all right just fight him that was not for cinematic purposes that was for killing purposes
I gotta like I gotta get back into the game man I haven't played in a while I haven't played
like four days ago Jerma snoozes on this guy snoozes on him I'm telling you oh all right
this is a pvp player he played this literally every stream yeah but I haven't played it every
day well I like I took I kind of look like a Simpsons character shit look at over here as
I'm looking at myself I look like a Simpsons character why do I look like that I got my own
fucking move don't I god damn it dude don't fucking do it yeah look I look like a like a Simpsons
character I don't know why I just kind of do this is about rivers of blood best weapon and then the
mask that's the best sword in the game oh I mean I could have guessed considering it kills you in
two hits three hits with that move uh weapon of Okina swordsman from the land of reeds a cursed
weapon that has failed countless men when Mog really the lord of blood first felt Okina's sword
and madness upon his flesh he had a proposal to offer Okina the life of a demon his thirst would
never go unsated that sucks it's a bog type weapon uh I can't really use it because arcane
let's take a look at it that's that's pretty cool that's a katana all right very cool uh so
that's a mog like weapon it's fine I like I can't use it I'm sure it's great people said it's what
you guys saying pvp it's the insane and pvp arcane seems actually really cool I'm seeing a lot of
arcane weapons that I did not think were going to be in this game I thought arcane was going to be
one of those stats in from software games that just exists for no reason and like there'll be
like youtube videos of like I put 100 points in luck and beat the first boss right uh but it's
not it's actually that's cool okay oh uh where's my baby rattle you need to do the mog dance when
you fight him I mean well we'll probably think it's we'll probably think it's funny use a different
weapon use the darkmoon great sword it has cold damage yeah but I I have to respect and I'm not
respecting until I need to because I like this build I like the baby rattle the mog dance causes
a stun do I have enough these all right sacred tear do I have any more sacred tears very nice
very nice very nice I have plus 10 is that it I have a plus 10 flask now is that the maximum
amount of uh sacred tears in the game did I get there plus 12 is the maximum let's put on our
little detective shades here take a quick look around and I talk to uh usually you can talk to
what's her name bring out the frog detective plush oh by the way people people that would give me
shit people that would give me shit you see what's on the shelf right there you see that I got them
I told you that I was gonna get them see it's the it's the award yeah because I didn't I forgot them
you see it right here okay they are hanging out back there one of them is just kind of standing
on one leg it's broken that's okay by the way what's what's the formula for facecam size
they have there's definitely like a screen resolution scale for facecam because this is
too big right and this is way too small what's the goldilocks setting for facecam I think that's
fine I think that's good you don't want to be too you don't want to be too big because it covers
too much of the game we don't want to be too small because then you can't see my fucking fog
reaction right here you think I think right here's fine yeah that's fine about the size
of a postage stamp that's decent yeah I know I don't it's I don't want to be bigger it's it
takes up too much space that's all that's there so let's get on the uh horse it's a big head
all right so I mean it's very obvious at this point I think at least from my brain
these are gigantic skulls like gigantic way bigger than the giants that are here way bigger
than any giant we've fought in the game so far so like the fingers are they're their fingers
right this has to be like giant fingers nobody has hands that big right I think that's my theory
that there are like ultra omega giants that those are their hands right okay what's that
check the skull's mouth I'm safe in here all right I'm safe in here actually I can cheese you
that's what we're gonna do I don't think I've ever killed one of these
four thousand souls damn did they drop anything wait there's another one oh
where's the other one I heard it all right well I'm gonna take it what I take what I can get here
no you didn't get out you're fine falling I just want to go in this thing's mouth stop
leave me alone actually kind of terrifying so in the mouth okay I'll check it had to be so
cinematic because there's a legendary in here I would have walked by this ancient dragon smithing
stone oh that's a that's to get something to max level all right all right well thanks for I would
have just walked by that I really would have but that's to get a max upgraded weapon which I need
to make a few decisions here get these fucking birds out of here are the boosters worth it I'm
stuck getting one star yeah I mean if you're getting if you if you're constantly getting
one and two stars especially one star and all the if you have enough energy to play another time
I recommend the hammer because what it can do is it before when you go into the boss door
you know you have the bar that's at the bottom that's like hammer the glove and like the star
shards thing the hammer does is you tap it and it just the hammer comes down and when
go and it takes 40 of the boss's hp off which I think it's like it's a it's a really good
equalizer it is but they're expensive so don't use too many of them I have like four left I
bought the pack with like 10 what is this I don't have any boosters left I just buy some more fire
giant it's huge oh god he's like fucking flattened me um all right date the leg it's gonna be a fight
about patience shit I just broke his I just broke his leg his femur just came out what the fuck just
came out of him all right break both his legs the ultimate fat rolling oh shit I saw that in slow
motion maybe I'll get I'll get off the horse oh that sucks is there another bonfire or do I have
to run maybe I think I am gonna get off the horse for this now I guys I don't have any more hour
glasses I use the last one they're like a dollar 99 each I cannot freeze the boss for two minutes
I cannot I fucking well it's just our time that people love to say that I have not I don't have
any more is there there's a closer bonfire that's the boss door so oh shit this one right here he's
trying so hard to make it work I mean it's the title of the stream I need to try at least for a
few minutes I mean I have a VIP pass you know I will say for every time somebody says they hate
a joke a few weeks later people beg me to do them how many scenarios of like dude fucking stop
that that joke that's not funny and then like I read in my chat room oh dude do the lala dog
oh Aaron when can we get some more Aaron can't wait for a week from now when somebody tells me
to use the hourglass on the boss in a game where a completely unrelated game oh shit I just want to
see what he does he's gonna do it again boys jump you can jump over it watch out watch out boys watch
out he hit me okay all right all right all right all right we gotta break the shackles very clear
it might be tall enough to break the shackle get on the fucking horse you fight this guy
okay all right okay get on the horse just run around you lost 20k of whatever 20k I don't get
out of bed for 50 this is a run around and hit the boss's leg he's gonna fall down and
I'm gonna critical hit him in his face all right let's go we'll get the boys out why not
they might be a nice distraction you know you're fucking me get out of the way it's a huge area
let's go all right here we go the horse has a dodge I know I just did it and it didn't fucking
work god I don't like how honest to god I don't like I don't know when I can when I need to dodge
this motherfucker this motherfucker like his whole body fills up all the eye frames I don't know
like I feel like a dodge I'm gonna hit by the back of the plate have you ever played this game
before use the hammer what am I doing with my mouth all right come on I just run around him
uh all right no more fucking around that's not gonna break his shackle
oh out of the fucking way stay close dude I don't even know where his body is
somewhere over here Jesus all right there it goes there it goes get the other one get the other one
oh my god where is he all right get the other one shit let's do anything god damn it Jesus
this all right come on man like am I supposed to break that I have the right idea right break
both of the shackles and then or just oh no no no this leg's just weak now okay I get it I get
it I get it I get it I get it I get it I get it I get it I get it that leg get up get up get up
what happened why did I not oh my fucking god don't go near that shit my god that almost blew
open my face no he's gonna put it all around him right get it nice job boy great
now what am I supposed to do is this mogg do I have him in the eye
he looks like swedish from the muppets no I want to go to hollywood too kermit no don't leave me
behind we're going to hollywood well hollywood what do I hit him I don't know right here no
wait glintstone sorcery and what can I shoot him in the eye I think I could probably shoot him in
the eye like ice crack that's what I'm doing well that's ridiculous that was a little bizarre but
all right that's the that first phase you just got to just get in there and just whack the absolute
shit out of that leg get in there and beat up the leg and just keep beating the leg up don't even
leave don't run away I promise well dream of each sweetums in three more tries I don't know maybe
everybody's goku no I mean everybody's mr satan but if you go back and watch the old muppet movies
he does kind of talk like that doesn't he oh no kermit no sweetum fucking never making a joke
ever again last thing with the spells we didn't fall down dude you have so much health
oh
this sucks get him in the balls I tell you that like every time I think about that I just think of
it's like you know you have like four or five like like lock on points I don't know I just
like imagine like a whole like a whole like fucking warcraft party all like targeting
this like big dragons and it's just like get it out of my fucking head like a 40-man raid I
like I just think of like a huge dragon flying around it's like it's got like 10 targeting points
I hate it I don't why it's like all I get it's living rent free in his head all right now stop
it get it get it get it get it get it get it get it get over here fucking baby rattle is probably
the worst weapon for this fight by the way get that away from me where the I didn't even know
where he was I didn't even know where his fucking arms were dude from software can I have an opinion
here if you have an enemy that's 400 feet tall can you please give us a fucking power ranger power
but we could just grow as big as they are like they did that in the power rangers it's just like
they that was oh he got huge time to get in the mega zord and fucking fight the guy
this is this is a wash right here there's no way we're fucking three flasks you have to shit
me with a dead horse too it's a god damn miracle fucking baby flail that swings straight down by
the way I want to say this again it's cool dude right in the eye get him in the eye this is hitting
him in the eye not even fucking hitting him get out of the way I'm not even fucking hitting this guy
get out of the way fuck you what oh my god the fucking range is just like I cannot close enough
to fucking hit him I gotta use this no no no what do I use against this I can't go that close
get off your horse this is shit no it's not a shitty weapon oh my god I'm so fucking dumb
I didn't fucking turn on the starlight dude what am I doing am I fucking dumb
fuck out of here man like fuck you second phase is easier than the first phase is it
get off the horse dude when I get off the horse this dickhead jumps backwards and then starts
throwing shit at me no that's not what I wanted to do well in case I lose my way let's try you
you and me come on I like you you're my friend come on and do like the funny fucking thing that
you do you got a plan you look ready let's go off the horse wait just let him come to us fuck it
you know what let him come to us it's always our it's our we're on ho we're the home team
let's get this time okay because I'm not running out there because when I'm out there he's just
smoke he's so ready okay here he comes jump he's stupid get him I love that guy
okay dude this is the worst place to fight this guy it really is this is the stupidest
idea to fight him over here all right I broke his leg I'm getting back on the horse by the way
it moved oh my god video games are not fun why would I bring the fire surface to fight the fire
giant that's probably a bad idea actually kind of awesome though just get free and get up
hey hey did he fall off where's my circle oh god there's an edge get away from the edge I'll
fall off that edge get away from that please get away from the edge you you didn't even try to hit
me no come on the one thing that you shouldn't have fucking done and you did it and this thing's
gonna explode no I knew that was gonna happen all right keep going I don't need summons or
anything just go go that second phase is not a big deal he's gonna get in there hit him in the
eyeball or something I don't know do the wind move the wind can I jump on this and ride up his
body idiot your hand I don't even fucking know where the guy is man god damn it
yes I'd like to get on the horse make that toggle in the options farm software for the love of god
make it a check mark just a check mark in the options like oh do you want to confirm to get
on the horse no check mark in the options a check box a square that you check no I don't I know
I don't want to confirm to get on the horse after after it dies it's a check box solves that
hmm let's go boys all right do not summon them yet now something here we go
god it's so easy just to fucking have the camera spin around and lose track of the guy
walking on not walking on it all sucks Jesus man get out what do you fucking happen
oh damn it watch out for that explosion I don't die who died fuck out don't roll over here
the hands the edge was right there I had nowhere to go the edge was right I was gonna run that way
but the edge was right there oh no second I need to have what am I have for gear that fucking
kills you instantly fuck you what gears not gonna help um off the off the horse in the second phase
that's probably a good idea but fuck man like sometimes you just get caught like that you just
can't there's nowhere to go if I had gone forward I would fall off the shit I'm gonna get off the
horse in the second phase press L1 on the horse it goes I know it goes the other way I've been
doing that since I started the fucking goddamn video game I jumped over that I did I don't
understand I jumped over it that works that worked nine out of the last 10 times where is it
god no the fucking turnaround all right off the horse boys let's go summit get off
hate them out so they explode come on explode already I don't even the fucking camera is so
stupid how are you supposed to know where they are what the fuck dude how the fuck are you supposed
to know where those even go unlocked camera locked camera the guy fucking rolls around and
then the camera like how am I he's supposed to fucking know just get on the horse to run away
I feel like this probably if I just sit right under his like groin area that he probably just
can't do anything don't walk the camera I just don't how are you supposed to even know where
those fucking explosions happen you're supposed to guess just guess how are you supposed to just
run away from that or what I'm just gonna stay right in his groin on second base
such a piece of shit really is
come on more stamina give me a break damn it the fucking endurance this is why I need like 35
points in endurance not 10 get out move please no get off the horse god oh he's face explodes or
something oh my god where's my staff oh I couldn't see
it's a cliff
no get away from the fucking cliff dude
oh that guy sucks that guy sucks that fight sucks that guy sucks I thought I was gonna walk
right off the cliff oh my god I thought I was walking off the cliff that was happening to me
in real life by the way that guy was actually hurting me and that was coming after me in real
life I honest to god thought that I was I was gonna die in real life in a chair like when he
moved anybody did the elbow drop I was dead 180 000 souls are you shitting me dude you know what I
think I built up enough frost on him to do that chunk at the end that's what happened I don't
know if I win that fight without that oh my god that was ridiculous okay that was that was tough
uh is there a race here probably but really though give me a checkbox to check the fucking
horse thing I I just it's I will complain about that all day you're gonna bite your control all
right you know what I haven't been spoiled on anything but I just know that this boss
had a lot of people have taken like 10 plus hours to beat I'm all looking forward to that one
I might just turn around and walk the other direction Jesus is there a grace there right
there I actually bit my controller on that one really fuck I don't know bite my stuff
every boss from this point on is complete ass oh Jesus that's good to know that's great all
right dude 20 endurance seriously like that's why I can't do anything I think it just goes into
health 60 intelligence or get to 50 health I'm going home I feel like health is way more important
right now although I got a remembrance see the remembrances that was insane you're still doing
that okay what do you get for this giants red braid strength decks and faith hefty whip woven
from the flame red hair of a fire giant every giant is red of hair and radigan was said to have
despised his own red locks perhaps that was a curse of their kind flame dance or burn oh
flame 27 faith raises a series of flame pillars around caster can't really use either one of
these can i there's flame pillars charging yeah yeah yeah the fire giants borrowed from the power
of a fell god and still they were defeated yet their failure released them from their solitary
curse to serve as keepers of the flame for eternity I'll just break it look at how red
and sweaty I got in the last 40 minutes of that boss I go to shit so quickly something I've
noticed about myself I like I'll look good I look like great and then like after it after like 30
minutes or an hour I kind of just like it's almost like somebody's like crafted me out of clay or
something and then like I'm just gonna go to shit in an hour I can only show up to a function for
like two to three hours before like I go to shit and I start to like melt nice dad chapstick I've
because I want to like moisturize my lips because they're dry because I'm
fucking older and I get dry lips I get dry hold on how much is gonna get not that much
no that's not that much considering where I am in the game all right I need 87,000 souls but not
yet grave glovewort I want to get this I like this man serpent I need grave glovewort five where
can I get grave glovewort five one two three four six seven eight I'm missing five oh god damn it I
need a somber ancient dragon smithing stone it's not what I got that's I got a regular one
you drink enough water oh yeah I sit here all day and drink water you'll get a somber castle
over in the snow area I think I did it already right medallion all right all right all right
so let's get the medallion because I know I'm probably I probably gonna need it so here's
thing uh you said I I think I know where this is I think I know exactly where this is oh respect
mog drops glovewort five I mog already you have zero idea where this is no I I have an idea
because I actually saw Holly play this part like she stumbled upon this and I remember looking
over and be like what you up to and then going what's that I didn't I didn't really know much
about it but I just know I think I know where it is cheated I'm I look when I can't play elden
ring on my character I want to play through I wait look I was sick of going through limb grave
10 times I'm gonna be like oh hey honey what you up to oh Elden ring oh is that limb grave no
you're in a you're in this you're in Lunaria oh can I can I hang on to the guy watch you guys
don't understand I was only exposed to limb grave for like four straight days five straight days
I noticed whoa you're in a different place than limb grave what's how's it going can I live
I know it's like over here right it's over here somewhere stop bothering her you know
can I play it's like oh hey can I play I use keyboard and mouse sitting there with a controller
and I'm like oh I got a keyboard and mouse you know okay I know it's over here because it's the
only other place in Lunaria that I haven't fucking gone to how have I not done any of this zero of
this I didn't do any of this zero how you guys must have been fucking rushing me uh well this
probably uh there's probably a church here then there is a church up there I'm performing as you
in a play any tips uh you can't get up there oh but look at this I already get whatever this is
I am so powerful nothing no one can stop me oh I already got this I just wanted to check
can you imagine it's that guy again he's coming to look at our box he already took it
yeah just double check it by the great power of some more I cast all of you to your deaths
next time tell him to refill the fucking chest hey I had a hookah glintstone didn't open the
chest yes I did I'm in mock all right how how unreliable is it for me to get to mug
like is it simple is it gonna cause a bunch of problems it's gonna take like two hours
how hard is it to get to mug it's simple yep okay tell me how simple it is to get the medallion
okay all right all right all right
is the cocoa puffs bird still like crazy or did they is that still a thing they killed them off
I missed those commercials I think some four that's not what I want all right keep going
fell into he flew into a window and died that's awful that's awful so awful
oh not as tough not as tough as your big brother are you okay so where where is it from here it's
like down I didn't even do this urn tree did I even do this I've been here before
it just goes down here we went back to state prison for drug trafficking the grace here there
are two mugs so from here let's keep going this way let me just go let me at least do the urn tree
I have not even walked over her
no don't stop look we can do I was trying oh ever jail cuckoo's ever jail oh here it comes
oh it's me sonny the bird he just goes like just like freaking out and fucking
attacking you and shit he's like oh spin spin spin dash and he's got like those circle circle
circle eyes that go like circle circle circle circle circle circle and they're like green and
blue I have a lot of souls I'm probably gonna kill this really quickly carrion knight bulls
yeah I mean this is gonna be easy say that now but it is
it's probably would have been really tricky uh like eight streams ago
okay if I lose to this guy at level like 110
yeah see probably just drop magic all right what we got great blade phalanx
that is a sorcery but I don't really like those he drops mugs magic bidet I don't feel like
mugs bidet would probably like really hurt if it was a spell that's got to clean like a like 500
foot tall asshole that's probably gonna kill you okay forms a defensive arch of larger magic
glint blades and I can try it into troll knights I could try it I mean I'm not really a fan of
those that's cool all right mark that that is a sword means complete so let's just keep going
down here I need to do this or a tree we're just cleaning some shit up can I get there from here
well okay I got off the horse that means here comes an invader right revenger's shack edgar
the revenger okay you and I have like the same name oh you buried into it
hey what you rolled into it rolled into it shrubbery grape and banished knight's halberd plus
eight and meat dumpling plus eight did I already have one of these now this is golem's hybrid
now this one here I don't even know what that would be where is it oh there it is plus eight
kind of cool even the knights who weathered by misfortune or misdeed were forced to abandon
their homes most of these knights were sent to the fringes where they were forced to start anew
with only to spare for company and a lot of raw meat dumplings you can sort by new really good
tonight let's go do this uh urn tree thing okay the other half of the medallion where was that
just now right here lunaria western uh right in the middle western lunaria with them from the lake
this shack revenger's shack it's right here it's due south of cuckoo's ever jail the foot of the
four uh bell freeze is where you want to go down from there you go hey don't just walk off the edge
yo mog just followed me on twitter that is the urn tree there's a church i've already been up
there there's a dungeon over here yeah me strong will take care of it I got I've got a direct
mission here are you sure was it verified because there's a lot of mog uh imposters that think um
they like pretend to be mog and stuff I don't think I don't think the real mog even has twitter
I mean I have I got a phone number so we text and shit I don't think I remember him talking
about twitter there we go I'm gonna kill this pretty yeah how did I not come over here and do
this and you can even though I I could still die so don't be stupid all right more of those uh
flask tears what do I get durillian crystal tear and ruptured crystal tear where are those they're
like in a weird place in there causes concoction to explode in mixed physique a defective crystal
tear which possess absolutely no medicinal quality so lessons said to be learned the hard way for
some faith can be volatile matter after all causes concoction to explode so wait I drink this and
explode it's op what's the other thing I got stores half of total fp what do I have on now
eliminates all fp consumption and I don't think I even need why would I use that when I have this
this is just a better version of this I have like 10 to 15 seconds to cast spells for free
this just gives me half of my fp it does a huge amount of a way use explode with no soul loss for
homeward bone really does that actually work or are you just making that up that is actually
an error yeah you're right that's that's pretty early that's an early game boss you're right
this is one of these rises probably a memory stone oh did I get it's not a puzzle it's a
memory stone climb up erudition guide thee this is not a puzzle well first of all I got a little
bit of an issue here you have to have an emote emote which one light bow chat don't spoil it
oh well they kind of they kind of already did roval for mercy use the mug emote read the sign
erudition guide thee well what is what is she doing she's doing like arms out all the ones with
the arms are out wait rapture all right rapture the ring that one's called erudition
this emote okay this emote reminds me of like here ready
that's like what I see that's what I hear thanks for uh thanks for just telling me the answer
I've stuff like this whatever it's just one strand of hair over here this one
it makes me look like sweaty now I don't look as sweaty
okay it's gonna be a memory stone but actually it's good because I really kind of need
yeah I really need another one especially if I end up doing that moon spell it takes up two right
what does it take up one it takes up two doesn't it still I like it yeah who's getting a ton of
subs roshan is giving hundreds and hundreds of dollars that's insane it's a lot of money
thank you for the fucking insane amount of subs that's ridiculous I do look wicked sweaty
hold on honest to god what's going on it's the lighting in the room I'm I promise I don't look
like this I I don't know if it's like I'm just a shiny face my face is made out of like glass or
something I don't get it an item oh there's an item right there okay let's keep going it's because
of the starlight all right so from here I gotta go here right I didn't do this place I believe
it's down like here I believe I have it right oh to mug we'll do mug when I feel like doing mug
okay so now I kind of don't remember I just remember looking over it and that I saw that
she was here and then I saw what she was doing your face has enough oil to power my car for a
year you only change your oil once a year seems like you're doing a little bit more than that
every um three thousand miles I don't drive much all right I gotta break up enough oil for me to
change it twice oh that's more accurate then that's better what do I get over there do I have to like
drop down from here or something I mean this is cleanup like I'm just trying to get it no oh it's
my favorite enemy here comes this guy's still a panty ass I'm not gonna die here am I I don't
have a shield equipped and I can't go get one I've never killed one of these guys besides when
they were bosses get anything for it really I can see I can see twitch chat reflecting off your face
that'd be so funny you just see me like lines coming down all right so from here look at I
look I can go I don't want to die accidentally though here go that all right there's a bridge
right there here we go I'm hyper focused on your cheek village of the album or maniacs
the animaniacs it's you well what do you make of it what's happened to this village I just got
here witnessed a sight much the same in my infancy the oppression of the weak murder and pillage
unchecked a waking nightmare made by men but this time I'm a woman grown and though the
suffering cannot be undone I can still meet out justice justice to the oppressors let the scars
I carve remind them I am the felly Lou warrior oh right okay um but this time I'm a woman grown
and though the suffering cannot be undone I can push in class justice justice to the oppressors
I'm like 16 days ago I don't think I need to open those notes anymore this time though the suffer
well cool so this is dead the guy fucking died I can't even that's so funny didn't even get a
chance yeah syllabus had an entire other character arc it's like in episode two in the in the anime
of Elden Ring he gave the task to the character excuse me somebody just throw a fucking board at
me and then like 12 episodes later he's just dead and you what you realize is they there was
like a the director of the show just cut out the whole fucking part of like episode nine that was
like 14 minutes of content and she's like why did they do that it's just like well I wanted to
kind of see what happened why did they do that why why would they cut the entire half of that
episode's arc out it's like oh we weren't sure that people were going to enjoy that that part
of the anime so we just got rid of it right away this village is done for even if it's just you
old albus hide well and still your breath albus oh albus's shack they all they all kind of live
like this there are i've seen better bathroom stalls with more privacy right like this
like it's kept ridiculous like this is all these open fucking things i would hope so
i'm talking about the like all right let me tell you i've have i talked about this the slices in
the bathroom stalls i fucking hate it i don't understand why they have to exist it make it
infuriates me i know um yeah america america there are there's not there's no real privacy
in an american bathroom some of them are literally this wide so when you sit there
and you realize that like like you don't have any fucking privacy i don't know why it can't
just be walled why can't it just be walled why people not know what i'm talking about here
it's like these little slivers of area that nobody knows what i'm talking about it's because there
is this is i think this is solely an american problem from what i've heard but anyways yeah
it's so fucking dumb i hate it i actually hate it i avoid going to the bathroom like i avoid
shitting in a public bathroom because i hate that like you just open on all sides
it's the wrong way i was everyone avoids that but i i truly avoid it i actually don't do it
i truly do not do it if i'm going number two i'm waiting to like go home it we are we are that
dedicated sometimes you have to it's impossible i have not shit in a public bathroom in 25 years
i'm telling you i swear to god go back to vodz from like 2017 2016 i've said this too i've been
very consistent i swear to god i that i'm not making that up hit the glowing jar i wonder if i
should do that no secrets lie with me not a one please leave me be wait then does anybody i'll
talk about this
there it is please give it to her okay i have the i have the other half of the medallion
is the key that leads to the city it's only a quaint treasure for we who cannot make the journey
but for dear latina it is needed to fulfill her purpose okay my legs will soon fade and with them
my life this is the immovable fate of all albinorex
so a public bathroom stall right it's got like does anyone anyone in construction know why
we do that in america why did we do that in america but nowhere else on earth
anybody have an actual logical reason for it it's cheaper
i said i don't care dude oh god i don't care it's because of money but i was it's really cheaper or
i feel like is it to have the pieces of like steel or aluminum whatever the fuck they are
go an extra like quarter of an inch that can't be that that has to be like five cents per door
no not even it's probably less than that get over here oh i fought with one of these
i thought this would be the capital right yep i remember this god it feels so ridiculous to be
able to kill these animals it feels like i shouldn't be able to do that crucible not talisman
what is that reduces damage and impact of headshots so you don't run out of oxygen
headshots like bow and arrows all right i got the medallion do anything else here i need to do
we're doing our cleanup we've got both sides of the medallion that's it you need to fight
mog to get the middle part of the medallion to the left oh you need to find the find the girl
go to the lift to the lift to the left girl isn't needed yeah me strong will take care of that
all right so now wait is a dog read the description of the item is it a whole item now
howling tree secret medallion wrenching a medallion with a hidden path in other words
this secret medallion will guide the bearer to the land of mikkela's howling tree what the heck
was was that loud i'm sorry the land of mcdonald's all right let me go back to the
round table though because i need to live alone find the girl i don't need to find the girl i
guess like so okay what what is um what does he say now i have the medallion is he gonna say
anything the secret medallions are reunited ah the secret medallion glad to see my council has
borne fruit but the honor of the deed is yours alone you've made more of yourself than ensha
has both secret medallions are in your hands i suppose you'd like to know then what awaits
you on the path ahead me too my friend me too wait with bated breath this i'm telling you this guy
is going to come and kill steal our elden lord status i'm certain of it it's gonna be we're
gonna get killed still gonna do all this shit at the end of the game this guy's gonna step in front
and be like i'm the elden lord and he's gonna get like oh and get like wrong and then we have to
fight him that's like probably what it is because he's always like you and i want the same thing
oh we yeah you and i together i'll just go do all this shit and come back and tell me about it
this guy's full of shit all right here we go hello mr germa 95 i'm the albernaurk
woman will you be returning my medallion to me no i'm gonna go uh probably smash it on like an
anvil and like ride the lift or something oh you need to kill mogg please please tell a mogg
okay all right i'm fucking listening where's mogg where do i go for mogg where just tell me
because you know i'm never gonna you're never gonna let me do it go to the sewers go down here
don't go to the sewers sewer mogg is a poser we want the real mogg not the fake one fake mogg
we want real mogg there are two mugs real mogg all right i'm going uh i think i'm just going to the
lift because um i feel like everyone's just freaking out and i don't know what is happening
but we're gonna go where's the lift brand lift of roll okay there are two mugs i'm just going
here need to level up i i'm sure i will in a minute there are four mugs mogg champ okay
hoist secret medallion i'm very intrigued oh haven't seen that in a while please please adventure
be wary of the danger and the halid tree a century since we've seen that medallion
some halloween candy here we're going for two or three minus twos in a row if i can get a hat trick
prepare to mega mauled chill
now i'm talking about like i'm chilly hidden path to the halic tree i'm like
chilly like it was a cold chill not like a wow i'm this boss will retire you am i going to
retire after this beast eye quivers is there not a bonfire here anywhere let's say let's hang it from
the ceiling something's on the ceiling something on that ceiling that i don't like that at all it's
like upside down i'm not going that way oh they want to bump me too oh my god i hear breathing
chills no no oh ah oh it's one of these things good land octopus ovary
mugs these are not mugs i know what a mog like enemy looks like all right why does it want
me to jump from here very clearly it's saying hey go that way oh my god that hurt
holy shit yeah really come on nice good good good good what was that
hear that these guys are dropping a ton of souls i really hope this bonfire
that'd be so sad two freezing greases why so many freezing greases trying to tell me something
oh ghost gloveboard brave gloveboard nine holy shit all right i need one of those
thank god this bonfire thank goodness drop a glowstone on the broken edge are you telling me
that was a invisible bridge i mean i'm trying i i gotta try to get that full moon spell right
it's an it's actually an invisible bridge let's go find out if you're full of shit or not
oh god oh jesus you weren't full of shit i thought you were full of shit i was that's why i was
silent damn all right so what's this silver scarab that seems important raises item discovery
by almost a hundred silver scarab enhances item discovery almost a hundred that's ridiculous
anymore how am i supposed to get out of here from here this way how do i get out of here
i gotta go across that way does it actually just go that way i hope so it doesn't just go that way
it has to right it has to i'm dead you all right i thought i killed the guy behind me um
probably the grace right i don't know where the uh where was the statue or the way for the back
right beast eye quiver of course all right let's go and it's not gonna happen again i'm ready
you little shits yeah all right he's climbing on the ceiling i just saw him i i just saw you
where are you there's somebody climbing on the ceiling that he's seeing things all right
i can go down there is it just as simple as walking over there but he's walking over there
is this safe this is a very bad thing to do right now i'm okay oh i thought i thought i
fell too i gotta get back on track okay straight here i knew it knew it i knew you were gonna do
that another glove wart that's it and then i can go down there and i is that over there too
am i gonna die if i just jump from here no nice hero's rune there's even more what about over here
um i'm just gonna cast spells over here i can't really see i don't want to just drop down there
i'm terrified is that like a barney burp from the simpsons did you hear that that was like a
somebody in moe's bar oh my god oh my god just relax god he's freaking out he's freaking out
he's freaking out man freaking out for the person right here
Jesus all right let's take a second here there's a boss door it's not open though
old fang okay hey get that bullshit everybody else in there oh i'm out of juice
whoa it still hit me god i fucking missed you little shit just get over here
yeah all right root resin all right well here's the boss door this is gonna be interesting
because this is not the way that i was going is there a statue what is over here why is this skip
okay hold on you gotta have a reason to be here right no way no way no way no i mean like no way
right what's really actually that's there's no way well never mind that's not classic elden ring
where does this go i wonder if this is a uh a good skip to down here maybe spell drake talisman plus
two vastly boost magical damage negation cool where is this i'd love to fucking look through this
okay so can i is that a skip can i actually just get up there i don't think i can get up there
but that's not really that's gonna skip that's the exit well okay i'm just gonna run there again
the lever is back near the octopus i already pulled it all right let me do i have enough to
level up my might how much does this give like 20 000 right all right i gotta level up i'm just
gonna kill some stuff level up there's a bunch of stuff to kill here we revived all the enemies
yeah i want to level up i'm not going in there with like 50 000 souls i'm not going in there
with that i don't know what the fuck's down there my god oops okay sorry said you were gonna run
though i i have i need to level up once because i have 50 000 souls i just have to level up one
time and then i'm just gonna run to the boss forgot that that octopus lands on top of you
fine how does he read all the comments they're going so fast come on i'll tell you in a minute
how do i read all the comments okay i go like this and it's like i'm scanning each comment
and i pick out one sir no honest to god like something that you don't realize you're gonna
do when you start streaming is be able to just like that one it's weird it's uh it's actually
taking a long time to do that like actually read it all right almost there one more little
like group enemies and that's fine 86 000 how many 80 000 do i need i oh you know i also didn't go
up here so hold on before i do anything i didn't go that way what is that way
what it means is he looks for the one with the smallest of words
no no not this way i'm i got turned around didn't i not go in some of these doors because i jumped
down i remember doing this everyone that here is a paid actor do not fucking kill me how dare you
still alive hey cool almost there i promise we're not doing this for much longer i just don't want to
lose all these souls i just don't want to would you be a good mime that's such a fucking weird
question you know what yeah i actually think i probably would be a pretty good mime i do think
so okay so this is back here so i'm just gonna reset the area from the bonfire you would be i
probably could i could probably do it pretty well if i really tried that's such an old craft that
doesn't really exist anymore doesn't it right that's a very old crap it's not very many mimes
huh what about a puppeteer yeah those that too all right what do i need eighty eight seven
i'm almost there this last group down here will do it you can stop resident sleep ring
this from here i'll do it just this first group enemies just i gotta kill one more octopus and
i'm gonna run i'm done i'm done i promise that's it eighty there it is okay we're good we're good
go go go go go back to the back to the bonfire i see i did that was quick that was very quick
yo bro did i get some more green tea do i get some more should i get some more green tea
everything how long have i been streaming for flowers three hours yeah like two hours yeah
all right i am going to level up uh let's get this to 12 45 okay now i can assure you
i am on my way to the boss and i'm gonna just run and jump down there this run really sucks
i wish there was a faster way to get here so i need to kill this boss first try
where's the wait wait a minute and then this way you gotta run where's the statue go
i have to go down right is it no from here wait no down from here where have to go what am i going
where am i going where the fuck am i i have to go down is there okay is there only one way to get
to why is there a statue here if there's a fucking grace right there i said i can't commit this to
memory because there's no fucking i can't commit an invisible bridge to memory okay it doesn't
exist i can't commit it to memory it's shit don't exist how am i supposed to commit it
it's down here so it's over there all right okay so but can i just go from here
and i just like okay can i just run forward can i just run forward i have to actually run all the
way around that's such a pain in the ass i don't want to do this every fucking time and then it's
down there oh my god this is such a horrible i gotta kill this guy first try statue oh thank you
my god thank god okay stray mimicked here oh my god serpent get him he's using freezing mist he's
a moron all right 1v1 nice come on get him that using that move is cheating you can't use that
move i don't even have an equip cheater you get fucking 20% health gain oh that's so dumb
oh this is so unfair that's these member fights are so funny thankfully it's not a hard fight
black flame monk amon and some death root very cool all right oh yeah um where the hell am i where
am i where's that going i was going to like the halig tree and i ended up down there that's a
cratered snowfield okay so this is interesting show me the path oh gentle lights promise path
path to the halig tree all right so i gotta follow these what is the halig tree i guess
why ask that question when we're gonna find out probably in like two minutes it's like watching
a marvel movie it's like watching infinity war and just not seeing it for the first time you sit
with like a room of people like Thanos is going like this you lean over going hey dude is he gonna
snap his fingers no is he does he just tell me dude it's about to happen in one fucking second
just watch i just need to know all right let's keep going what are you guys doing out here
they're looking at something i had something in the mist that's so fucking rude i just swung back
he got that right in his face stray boys i know that was i'm sorry ah holy shit stop that's not
fair you want to play that game we can play that fucking game fine we'll play that game all right
these enemies suck uh they have a lot of health um i'm not following the lights anymore which is
probably bad i guess i maybe i should until i find a map fragment which i'm sure there is one
am i hitting something else oh okay go up here this is it no that's a fucking rock
somber spitting stone eight very useful i do need the other one though is this it why is it all
surrounding here now oh shit saint trina's torch what is that oh shit i lost the lights where are
they got a light i need a light saint trina's torch how's his sleep build up decks and faith
handles stand towards the burns with a light purple flame carvings depict saint trina but in
adult form somewhat unnervingly the light purple flame induces sleep okay i can't use it oh nice
i really need that considering how horrible it is to see here well that was i'm gonna help you guys
because like that was seriously pathetic how did you even get here dude you're so level one
how did you get here this was a lost player he doesn't he doesn't know where he's supposed to be
dude can i suggest east limb grave you're not you're way too low to be here i know you're gonna get
really mad because you're gonna get killed in one hit this is to teach you that you need to your
like you go go back to like the limb grave he warped to the end game zone and then he returned
the game to fucking target this game sucks i don't get it it's funny because i i have that
perspective of not understanding how these games are supposed to be played and not just not getting
it and being and just being like i don't get it like why are these fun what's the point if you go
to my if you go watch my dark souls prepare to die it was like 2012 i didn't get it i didn't
understand the game that was not me playing with any experience at all with any of these games it
was it was just kind of like oh this i know this released and i know it's like a hard game that's
it i didn't get it um it's actually kind of a stupid video to watch i don't even know why
i don't have it deleted like it's so bad i just walk around with a shield and talk about how little
the shield is like oh look at my baby shield and i was trying to block with the parry buckler
i fell off the clip a few times and then i didn't i don't think i even got out of the tutorial zone
like i don't think i even i think i beat the asylum demon and that was it i was like oh i
did it okay i played enough to make a video it's like dude that's like the first five minutes of
the game all right i'm kind of lost we yeah we we did rewatch this recently like a year or two ago
shit all right i gotta go back and look for those things there's a road here
how bad is the bit rate on the stream right now i'm curious actually good no way really
i feel like it'd be terrible oh grace you can actually see that's a good thing
that's it is that the same one that i got already i think it is you're so close
to mog i'm sure i am i gotta be careful because i almost have enough souls to level up again which
is crazy i've already gotten to 80 000 souls almost can i just spend them all right well
finally get the map is this the halic tree consecrated snow field this is probably right
here i think it's that i think i think it's that i gotta pee you're back pee time first pee of the
night i'm gonna get a refill right back okay i am back how do i how do i not startle you guys when
i come back i just realized this i you it's just hi what should i say what should i do should i
like tap or something because i have a little bit of compression on my microphone so it makes my
lows higher in my highs lower whatever right just whisper good all right so that took a little bit
longer i wanted to get a i wanted to get another uh drink i made another green tea drink but this
is very interesting because we just got pretty major reveal at this point in the game there is
another tree is this tree apparently this this is looks pretty big that's this looks that looks
kind of this looks like this looks big so there's the urd tree and then there's this other tree
i have officially revealed the entire elden ring map it's official look at that that's cool all
right so where are we going where's san andres we're going to this place here we're going to
this place we're going to this place and we're going to go to this place and there's also a
dungeon here a lot to look at we're going to start at number three at the little minor tree here
check your key items i don't have this room alice key sewer key fingerprint grape
onica forgetfulness uh what am i looking for you're looking for the fingerprint grape eyeball of
the night bike inflamed yellow seared with repulsive fingerprint burn akin to those that marred his
entire body if offered to the blind maiden it will lead her to the source of the distant light
allowing her to become a finger maiden eat this didn't i get i swear to god why were we talking
about mogg check my why is there like a key why are people telling me mogg is on the far left
it's mogg's shackle you got a reusable item oh it's not a key item okay find the accursed
people called the omen and these ones were made to keep a particular omen under strict confinement
though faint the shackle still retain vestiges of power and have to trap the once-bound mogg on
earth can't use it only for a short time all right well whatever i let's just let's start
over here let them ride just that minor tree here let's see what we got we gotta be careful
because i don't want to lose all these souls but you know whatever let's begin our exploration
god i'm treating these guys like a joke and i really shouldn't be what the fuck is throwing
at me why the guys do why they do it like look at me oh there's a rise up there
damn it all right i'm gonna stay the course here staying the course
jesus all right oh what a great fucking spell can i just be honest with you
what an amazing spell i'm ignoring my friends at my birthday party please say something funny go
hang out with your friends at your birthday party what are you doing go enjoy enjoy an experience
all right i have enough to level up but i think i can get up there without too much of a problem
1200 damage you get that hit that's so good what do you got up there it's mogg's birthday
what is happening hello i this is a prank oh okay it's up there strong blast the horse died
when all right that's this is weird is that a oh this is national war isn't it oh if you not hit
it somersmithing stone seven oh all right what's that that's kind of cool
do i eat oreos um yeah or is good i don't need too many of them though never a good thing to eat
too many all right wait no that's okay i don't want to go there yet focus on the urn tree or
whatever is actually up here yeah okay it is an urn tree well it could just be it is a tree like
what makes an urn tree an urn tree right like if there's a there's a halic tree up there
is a halic tree an urn tree or they just start as just a tree and they turn into one of these
things i don't everybody always talks about like baddie right like oh man sorry i'll just watch
the baddie video and i'll figure it all out and like can we like give baddie some credit here
a lot of it he has the monumental task of having to sort all this shit out for everybody
that seems like impossible i don't even like where do you even start like this is the world
is so huge and there's so much to think about there's so much to do so many pieces of individual
lore i forgot like half of it already yeah the amount of people that have to come together to
give knowledge to kind of figure out what the hell even just happened in the game there are
people still figuring shit out probably but when i used to do like youtube videos like all right so
the spy came out with a new knife that's i it does 10 more damage and um it has
it freezes people when you kill them wow that took a long time to figure that out
if i was if i was making elden ring lore videos oh my god i'd have like a spreadsheet that was
like 5000 pages high that'd be a lot harder you really should do the sewer boss i don't
i don't know what that means i'm closer me strong will take care of it this this is
for whatever it is i don't know i just lightning enhancements probably definitely going down there
without a doubt that's a cool it looks like the haunted mansion of disneyland
all right but am i going to get my ass kicked by this thing i'm afraid of this
it might be an avatar here i don't see a statue so i must i don't know is there a boss
maybe not like it would have spawned already something back there kind of what i gotta get
them oh no i don't just do this let's move the game even i offer a warp point here
i will absolutely keep so what's wrong with why is there nothing uh at this surgery
holding sunflower nothing over here or something behind it it's empty so um
what's behind it and what's with the tree these the phantom tree right it's weird like what's
with that they look cool you have to have a significance is what they do right what's over
here i don't really that's it i feel like i'm missing something i feel like it's not this this
simple oh what why are you abandoning your post we need to get out of this this is a weird place
to fight you oh that hurt oh frost really is really bad on these guys what are you standing
behind fuck off thank god jeremy don't do that one more that move is so fucking good 160 000 souls
thorny cracked here and ruptured crystal tier 160 000 they are really piling on the souls at
this point i'm just you know what i'm taking this right now i don't even care i'm taking one i have
30 i have 30 fucking just take it just take one i'm never gonna use it ever so what was that i'm
honest to god i just looked at that and got angry i have 30 of these i could use one of these every
10 minutes and it'll last me the rest of the goddamn game i have 75 and i don't use them
you just start using them what's the point it's plus five to every step oh it was here thorny
consecutive attacks go stronger in mixed physique i gotta rupture two of these but if i do both of
these is just do a double explosion what's the difference you just do an omega explosion i feel
like that do people all right do people just drink that in pvp and just like fucking run up and blow
up next to somebody i would assume it's probably yes so that's why they made that that's the only
reason all right cool i need to set out a bonfire so let's hope that there's one i'm gonna assume
that all right let's clear that so that's cool i am gonna check back here at three what's back here
i gotta go down i'm looking for a another bonfire going to that green uh spooky manner
all right this is where they this is where the lightning is we're gonna do this
like that all right i'm gonna assume i'm gonna go to one first because there might be a bonfire
here i don't see one here although there probably is one in there at least it kind of hurts my head
we should play fortnight now they took building out i'm not into it oh come on i thought that
was a bonfire that guy has a bone arrow i didn't want to hit that person oh my god i'm gonna die
these guys are fucking rough okay just you're just in the fucking way i'm trying to run forward and
i'm just like there is a thing of dog just in the way why does every single thing that has
collision in this game have like an extra five inches around it of collision
fucking goddamn rune ark is gone too take another one it's just like it's like the huntsman sniper
hitboxes everybody is like a gigantic cube that bumps into each other okay just go sit at the
bottom i don't want to lose these who is who dude let's go to tf2 to tf2 i look kind of do i look
like a little dark i look like i'm kind of like i think it turns up at this point i don't know
intelligence is cool but is it gonna get out of reach where i can't get to like 50 health
eventually here in a minute how much um i need 68 or 70 all right i can put the moon spell on
let's try it i'm gonna get rid of freezing mist because i don't think it's really worth it but
here is ranny's dark moon use the caster as a vessel to incarnate a cold dark moon and sends
it floating towards foes the dark moon dispels all sorcery that it touches temporarily reduces
magic damage negation for those it strikes okay i can now officially use this move let's see what
it does am i my moon in here does no damage it's pretty strong direct kind of contradiction
can't like if i go in there can they hit me you can still get hit you're immune from magic but
not physical hits okay oh yeah i'll try it i do want to level up one more time because
there's way too many souls yeah let's kill a few things it also reduces magic resistance of
enemies hit let's go test it on this group over here hi and that's like 1600 damage i can hit
more than one person right how far does it go damn okay that's actually pretty good all right i you're
very vulnerable in there though i wonder if there's any good use for that like a boss fight
shit these guys hurt a lot that's a lot of damage it really does a lot old sorcery is pretty fun
it should be enough to level up you use it once and then their magic defense is low and you can
spam the blade how long does it last about a minute oh so question for those of you that are
lore masters here is it worth me getting to 70 intelligence to go get the full moon
from ranala's resemblance is it worth doing that the dark moon is actually better so i'm
going to work on this now i'm going to get this to 50 and then we're going to do we're going to
split once i get to 50 vigor we're going to go mind and endurance 50 50 dark was actually better
okay let's keep going so the plan was to go up here you don't need 50 endurance no i was thinking
again it's like 25 it has not been a problem until the last hour so i'm imagining it's because of
uh it's kind of later in the game there's a lot more stuff you have to do a lot of more dodging
and moving around sprinting and jumping and there anything here this is like nothing okay
get it get it what are you doing pick it up what the fuck this game makes me so mad
yeah i just mean for the next five to ten levels not permanently all right let's do it let's do
the uh spooky green manner we're going double headphones by the way just a bomb or dina
liturgical town just a boss door okay um hello can't go in there over here maybe a lot of sealed
doors black knife hood armor gauntlets greaves hold on a sec where is that scale armor used
by the black knife assassins forge to make no sound muffles the sound of footsteps interesting
the assassins that carried out the deeds of the night of the black knives were all women
and rumored to be newman who had close ties with america herself really i'm not doing anything
like my hood what about this thing raises dexterity as it lowers focus well it's a good
deck summon uh i don't think i can get up all right i gotta keep going around another one of
those bell demons and one of these guys is here weird okay well let's go
hard to tell how much damage is doing but i feel like it's a lot
damn rotten doulas greaves and rotten great axe they're throwing so much equipment at you
bronze snakes eaten through by scarlet rot formed by gladiators who were driven from the coliseum
where it becomes slightly easier to target and where is it rotten axe x it's in scarlet scarlet
rot one of the few items in the game that has scarlet rot build up on the weapon that's actually
seems pretty good moon did 2000 damage to that guy yeah oh no i don't want to do that all right
well there's a bell demon um that looks like a america church so i know i'm gonna do that but
there might be a sacred tier over there so i'm just gonna go get it i'm dead
i didn't think it went down that far i thought that was maybe five feet below where i was
all right whatever it goes did you look go open up any of the red dead redemption two
streams all you need to do is open them up for five seconds if within within 10 minutes if i
don't crash the horse into a rock i i would okay no why am i getting off the horse why can't i
what's happening why can't i use my thing i can't use my spell why why can't i use it why is this
banned this is a banned move oh because my great room fuck i didn't know i had to use one of those
oh that's really bad no yeah all right will this person leave me alone
okay it's time it's time to make the ultimate decision do i get a plus 10 bastard stars
or do i wait to get a plus 10 regal scepter i have i'm i don't know because the issue that i have
with this i feel like in this late game here i've been doing way more sorceries than i were before
like two to three hundred percent more because i don't know you'll get more what do you think
there are a lot of plus 10 stones you're good how accurate is that though like am i going to run
into them soon i could do both okay there's a lot i got i have at least three all right very soon
okay all right well then i might as but i might as well make this as best as it can be there's
definitely no reason not to because this is a look at the 179 one that's so much more damage
i'm going for it but let's see what the pole says but i've made my decision what does pole say let
me like this webcam needs to brighten up a little bit i don't know why it's so low that's way too
much that's better there um yeah i'm gonna do it uh it's worth it it's worth it i need it
i'm definitely gonna need it done plus 10 baby rattle it's been done i want to upgrade this
serpent my snake friend so bad to plus like nine or plus 10 where can i get a glove warp five
i want to go do that right now i want that i want that plus nine plus 10 where can i get a somber
um not a somber ghost grave glove warp five i don't think they're in the store i'll check
though i have them i have all of them except for five i have a lot of all of them except for five
right this is ghost glove wart this is not the right one ghost glove wart do i have any bells
you need to get a grave picker's bell bearing let's get the bell clear the catacombs by the
giant bridge catacombs by the i want to i actually do want to do this real quick because i want that
snake to be like plus nine the giant bridge um like you mean this or in the mountaintops
catacombs in the mountaintops giant mountaintops catacombs did i find it yet or am i about to find
it it's this it's this right here that's not it oh missed it in the last area from over here
by the bridge so what like here here to start south of the giant narrow bridge so like somewhere
over here okay what's what's the best um probably this one i really i want it even though it might
take a little a few minutes i really do want it come you i have a plus 10 cat toy yes i do
mog wait mog is a banned word in chat right now you guys must have leaned into it way too hard
mog is a banned word not cool hey you have to relax you have to relax i see i see you fucking
all you i see you scrolling i see all of you bog bog bog bog bog bog bog yeah yeah yeah
bog pepe hands pepe hands bog bog i don't like my hair today aren't you microphone did you go
did it pick up no way minus two exactly that's the point that i agree with you do you understand i
agree with you i'm making i was making a sarcastic comment to somebody in the chat room who so badly
wants me to fart in my microphone i agree with you can i go down there so where is it is it like
here it's just south of the bridge they say wait hold on here wait i'm i'm way high up from the
bridge i gotta go down there shit maybe i should be down the other one from the other bonfire
i think i can make that i thought i could land on the statue or the tree whatever
it's worth a try i thought i could land on the tree like just and then be fine i can't believe
you thought that for a second all right i gotta wish i could just teleport out of here i need to
go to the other bonfire this one right then wrap around i'll get the comet i'm cold sorceress not
a comet sorcerer go learn comet azura i'm i don't want i don't need it i don't need it opium i am a
cold magic sorcery okay i don't want comet so let me try the other i need to get these souls first
so let me go down can i get that from here do i have to go to the other actual you might
as well get moon just use moon veil if you're going to get the comet i am telling you i'm telling you
now that i'm not getting the comet i just told you come on come on all right you gotta wrap around
you said it all right hey you're pointing towards a dungeon aren't you you are so here we go let's
go this way over here somewhere then it's an ice comet all right right here or like right here
is it can't be over there it's not an ice comet you know how i know it's not an ice comet
because two days ago it would have been non-stop spammed if people knew that i was doing cold
you'd all would have freaked out and been like go do this right now don't do anything else
here it is how big is your monitor um it's a 60 it's a 6000 by 4500 monitor um it's about the
whole size it's not a projector it's like it's 15 screens put together um i have like all stocks
and bonds and stuff up here but then like here i have like the game so if you notice
that when i look up here i'm looking at like i have like 15 different tickers i'm looking at
just to check i don't also have like every camera like i'll go around all the whole house
like command center you know like showing outside to see if anybody like for security purposes
every like window every like door just every every single thing bro a mouse can't fucking walk by
the left side of my property without me seeing it i used it already he has the price of usd on
his screen oh what how much is the dollar worth today i don't know price of the dollar go right
first it's plus 10 now come on i know okay so that was like a stupid shitty joke i made but seriously
uh i know that there are people that have one two three like four five six seven six or seven
monitors right like i know like like i'd be in flying like a spaceship or something if i feel
weird i wouldn't like it i'm not gonna go down yet i feel like i wouldn't even be in a room
i'm just surrounded by screens imagine how many different games you could have on it once
rave glove fort seven need that dream seven games at once we did that before i played all
the putt putt games at the same time and it was just no uh-huh why do they keep doing this
they keep doing this this is the second time in a row that they've done that
there's something up there in there come on did i really just do that god damn it i did didn't i
there's probably something right there wait what wait what just happened was this here
wait my brain is freaking out right now i wasn't paying attention oh all right that's kind of cool
oh my goodness gracious
oh fuck oh fuck that takes too long okay let me please whoa for a second
what i was still alive what happened i'm so confused what would just happen what just
transpired what just transpired there was something behind me got too chilly you forgot
to wear a scarf i'm just gonna fight it i'm more magical on this thing i'm way better with timings
on uh just swinging with the weapon oh it was that that's what happened distracting me fuck you
i jumped over him god damn it kill him freaking out i fucking panicked i fucking can't there's
no reason to pick like i i just got so angry that he did it three times in a row that i was i just
put the controller down you know what i mean like i just put the controller down because i was like
fuck you you know what i mean like fuck you i just put it down i was like i'm not playing
kill me i don't give fuck you that's what happened the cord off of me it's it's tangled up and it's
annoying like how does this even happen how does this happen i don't get it like everything should
be wireless get off of me get off of me this isn't even a boss i know and i i it's just it's i hate
this thing i don't even know why it's so easy i think it's simplicity is making me do terribly
like i'm just like oh for this guy's fucking stupid statue from all the catacombs i mean i
this will be easy it's easy simple it was so simple eight's nice it spawns when you reload
well that's i'm just gonna run by it okay i gotta be careful i don't even know how far that comes
out how far does that come up another eight you know about hitting the pillars i do i do know about
hitting the pillars just like that very cool nothing up there so we're just gonna go oh my
god okay we're not gonna go we're not going oh what's seven you fuck you this is how
i'm gonna fight you you're fucking dickhead i thought he was gonna get up does that hit me
i don't know if that hits me does it oh we're safe this guy's fucking dead oh fuck you oh my god oh
my god oh my god oh my god what are you doing very cool so what was what was all this for
fire monk ashes pretty cool so now what i guess this was the secret area there's only one good
thing about this weapon it's the weapon art you're not using it i do yeah i do i mean i'm
i do is your controller wireless i i do use it yes i do go back hidden wall go back behind that
statue i would just miss so much shit if you guys didn't yell at me every time i like left an area
you guys just scream at me when i leave an area and it's just like all right well never mind
my instinct was correct i'm just listening to myself all right so now let's go through
the actual dungeon that was cool got some new ashes god damn it guys do you really have to do
this to me you honestly need to you honestly need to do this i believed you again let's go back to
progress i have to hit it 50 times okay so now i this is the where the door is but there was no
contraption probably there's one down here that was just so that person um said fuck he does
do right right when i hit left trigger and i went he hit x he clicked the x and he was
fucking motherfucker i hate this guy i'm not gonna get swarmed i know everyone's saying don't do that
but what do you want to do what's this looks like a note what the fuck dude hey what do you want to
do just get killed by it great these things explode i mean these things explode i'm not
gonna have that oh hurry up and blow up that radius is fucking huge why are you shooting
it into the ground who that who somebody else is in here right come on fuck you what
i don't need to fight these just go these things take forever to kill anyways i thought alex
i said jesus fucking christ this chat sucks all right everybody settle down okay settle down
relax what's going on here what people have that opinion right now what are you guys up to what
are you doing i'm not paying that much attention over there what's going on over there the pot i
don't even use these but whatever so many glove warts all right um butterfly where's the thing to
pull i was already down there this fucking dungeon it probably is all right so well that's annoying
um how many people are in this room leave me alone i thought you were a good guy i thought
that was like alex what'd you just do why don't you just turn into metal mario okay i'm okay
i'll deal with you later nice there it is walked off the edge baby object permanence
just leave me alone baby object permanence i what are you talking i just came down here for the
first what do you mean all right i opened the door that's fine let's go kill this you probably drop
something drop like that thing i just came down here they all look the same look at the architecture
is identical it's designed to confuse you i need to actually go back to the bonfire i have no
healing i'm just gonna die to whoever this is is there a statue right here somewhere i need to look
at it's designed you're designed to be confused it's designed to be confusing um i i know i need
to go to the bonfire i hope it's this way nope i think i have enough to level up what level am i
like 110 150 120 122 i can't believe that you go that far in these games i feel like my dark souls
three playthrough i ended it so level like 70 like 75 or 80 or something not more than 100
definitely not more than 100 it's like three times as big yeah it really is okay
arc so three was around 80 to 90 yeah so i think i have enough to level up
golden rune i need i need 95 it's gonna no it's not worth it i gotta make sure i don't die
okay so let's go bang right on the elevator hey you are such a little turd you really are
that joke is so okay somebody just said hey germa i'm looking for my grandma's
ashes they're in a big antique pot if you live you see them let me know thanks why are your
grandmother's ashes down here in a dungeon like buried it deep in a dungeon with a bunch of
monsters and attack people attacking me i know i've seen you before oh doesn't like cold
oh shit bad get up dude get up oh fuck i thought this guy's so much
lovewort pickers bell bearing nice that's like the seventh sixth or seventh one i've had to fight so
far more death root and i got a golden seed too i also got a raid too for a raid from coney
thanks coney welcome everybody there's germa i'm a dark soul streamer he's playing an elden ring
for a few minutes uh thanks for the raid welcome guys so now that's that that was pretty cool
back to here yes okay time to get the snake to la to plus nine i have to give this bill
brave glove wart there we go all right grave glove wart five i think i only need one let's see
we're gonna have uh the boys are level nine and the snake is gonna be level nine too
i love how germa's a top 20 streamer but he's using headphones that look like they came from
the dollar store i didn't read please see what that says he's a bow's headphones where i took
you for dead matter it's all the same do you guys remember the bow's mall kiosks they used to have
where there would just be like four or five bows stereos in the mall just in the middle do you
guys have those where you were yeah yep they were these little boxes that you'd go over and they'd
be a demonstration where you'd press the button it would seriously be like this be like check out
the the real raw power of the sound i'm gonna mourn you i'm actually gonna do some sound here
so watch your headphones you'd go like this you'd hold the button so here's my finger be pressing
the button and be like this and it's just like oh my god it's getting way too fucking loud
and then you press press press press press press press take it down and like everybody's
fucking looking at you everyone's like holy shit dude what's wrong with you uh because it was it
was these little buttons that you held and there was no real there was nothing on the screen that
showed you the volume indicator it was just like it just got louder here we go it was the worst
day it was pretty it was pretty bad plus six plus seven plus eight plus nine snake friend is now a
plus nine unbeatable unstoppable spirit summon i still can't wait did i get i think i can do the
staff i need a nine i have an eight okay i love these things though i think they've been great
i've been using these headphones for a very long time at least like five years at least this myth
has dialogue so that was cool i did that now let's go and continue back already here i was
gone the girl has come along as ever time and technique have made her stronger it is good to
see an imprisoned monster does not deserve an apprentice the time nicely what she feels like
to me i've gone soft and it isn't easy
greeting uh i am not because we got the boys and we got the man serpent so i'm good thank you
though appreciate that was really good work you did all right it's time to go back to what we
were doing which was up here i have a few things marked the idea was to this is odina i'm gonna go
to this church first because yeah let's go to the church first because the church definitely has
a uh tier in it so might as well get it
it better summons what are you saying oh left side i'm gonna go over here
i will i'll do this whole area i'll do this i'll do that it's only like 8 30 so i think
this one's fine boys have helped us more times than i can count and the serpent does a funny
fire dance thing and it makes us laugh every time and remember sometimes that's all i'm looking for
when i get really mad at a boss and i'm like really not having a good time
and i just summon the funny serpent friend that comes out and is like doing this thing
it makes me not mad anymore and it's like this is as fun like that i think that makes me happy
again so like i i haven't been a good time again that alive you want one of the broken summons i
don't i kind of don't want one of the broken summons it's i mean it's cool but these things
attack i guess let's let's just start looking around are there enemies here i do have to watch
it i don't want to die with this many runes everybody have any dialogue no just looking
around just making sure i don't miss anything uh um that's sealed it's a puzzle what do you want
like the four figures in the ever jail any five
i'm gonna level up first i feel like this is gonna be annoying i was gonna kill like one thing
why do you guys have so much fucking health and armor almost like this is the last
was sewn in the game it's more efficient all right give me i'm gone gone gone gone gone gone
gone gone gone i'm sitting at the fire get away from me don't touch me how much intelligence do
i actually have without the rune 63 what the fuck man that sucks you see four i need 68
the rune is five yeah but i don't want to have to rely on the rune to do a cast of spell that i have
all right let's go do this hey content let me check up here first though what does this say
thing held shut by a seal so i'm assuming the seal is going to be this thing this is the oh
turn on light the fire is here in the ever jail your thing oh now everybody's real i get it
all the people we've seen lying around they're now gonna get up i get it that makes sense
all right light the four seals this illusion you can shoot through walls okay you can shoot
straight down you can literally shoot straight down through walls that's not that's fun well now
i'm coming for you motherfucker now i'm coming for you with my swift lint stone maybe just jump can
i use the horse in there i'll just jump up there um so they're on the roofs they're on the roofs
so on each roof i use the horse no no horse allowed there's one right here you can't really
get a lock on this one okay this is one okay um i got there the whole time dude so i'm gonna
just say okay this is not that big so i'm not that concerned but that was a lot why the assassin's
coming for me what did i ever do i know how to fight them though swing in a random direction
until you hit them and just don't stop swinging just going straight down assassin nope that's
i focus just came out of my nose i hope they're not on camera okay imagine getting like attacked
and just saying that saying the thing like the person that's attacking you out loud like i was
calling for help i was making a call out to my teammates that there was a black knife assassin
right here look at the blip on the mini map look at my blip on the mini map there's a black knife
assassin right here because even if i died two or three of my teammates would know oh shit all
right we're going there fuck oh it's you again all right they stay lit somebody said i just have to
run they stay lit okay yeah the play is run i don't who cares about any items i have a plus 10 baby
rattle and like the staff i don't do i really need another two rune arcs no just sprint don't
stop running and if a black knife assassin shows up just spam l1 over and over again and if you die
who cares okay go don't don't stop where are they there's one there's that one i got already
i'm just gonna go in a direction i'm going that way one over here give me the fuck away from me
how do i how do i get up there to go across there i see him walking into the snow what
where's his footprints i think i just bumped into him stupid oh my god it's so nerve-wracking
all right but hold on nothing changes in this dumb ass town i just go into the spirit world
so let me block out where i need to go so because the architect it's the same architecture
so i gotta go up there so how do i get from here to there to get okay this has a ladder that goes
up i got to get up on this roof in particular this one here now what's the way to get up here
on foot we're here here how do you get up here from the ground the ladder right there
is there a ladder ladder here how do you get here there okay so it's jump to here jump to there
and then go up and there's one right there all right let me just let me make sure i can do this
okay i can make that jump i made that one before as well i made that jump before double check hold
on what about on this wait maybe that's not a reliable jump what about over here
and get can i get up here any other easier way but this way maybe okay this is more reliable
so where is this mark this keep this marked it's right there it's this little spot right here
right on the edge so climb up there and i have access to the whole roof all right that's what's
gonna happen good luck trying to fucking remember my like two-year-old object permanence good luck
remembering where that is even with it's marked on the map in fact it came off it's over there
why is that so far away what are you talking about why is it so far in the distance oh that's four
where's one there it is okay so now let's go it's all the same like green and gray building
okay so from here from here i gotta turn it and just run straight that way right over there
okay can i can i follow me up the lot he's right there he's literally at the bottom of the ladder
he's climbing right now he's on the ladder right now right there on the ladder what do i do so is
they gonna climb the ladder i swear to god i thought i saw footprints it's two so from here
i can jump around where's the guy with the bow and arrow okay don't even think about it you
motherfucker don't even think about it where are you dude like okay god no no we're not doing it
like that oh there's another one shooting at me from another distance away from me
oh this is not gonna work oh my god i thought that was one oh my goodness just have to run
you actually just have to run i guess i could cheese somebody said with a bow but i got two
i just gotta run how are you reliably supposed to get how are you supposed to do that reliably
that's like a that's yikes how are you supposed to do that okay let's go i feel like with enough to
just running might be i think it's that's the way to do it run as fast as you can hold the shield
up if you need to and run and just jump and just pray that you don't get hit you can put on the
special armor i can use the terrain to block out the shots right for instance like i can just stay
right here and i won't get hit by anything so where's the route the route is run jump jump
to that balcony right there jump to that one and around the building go why am i fat rolling
what's what's going on why am i fat rolling what happened i'm dead he's gonna fucking stab me what
the fuck man how do i it's a it's a tiny little shield just stab me just kill me already i'm fat
rolling unbelievable this shield is made out of aluminum foil there's no way that it weighs that
much this thing is i'm fine relax don't i have a spell that makes it it blocks like a lot of
damage magic damage or something i wish i could use the fucking moon but i don't have 800
intelligence crouch crouch what am i supposed to do about this do i even have a bow okay can i even
equip this holy bow which one's better this is probably all right i got a bow on this is expensive
wait i think i'm safe oh i think i'm safe right here yep i think so don't move nobody fucking move
see you later okay um where's the other one there's another one right here somewhere i'm
gonna go up this ladder and he's gonna kill me i have to just run wait bait it out maybe
right there okay i'm gonna crouch by the chimney oh my god there's another one right there we're
fine um i don't think i can jump that yes i don't think i can jump up here can i not
oh my god oh my god this is gonna block it left go oh oh he's hitting me i'm freaking out i'm
freaking out i'm freaking out what do i do i gotta kill him i gotta kill him i have to kill him
how many arrows sticking out of my body this place sucks this place sucks it this sucks man
what the fuck where's the last one there's one more is it over there there how do i get up there
i do it out of your mind dude get up here from your ladder over here my god this one right here
the ladder right here please please please please please please please please don't shoot me
hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry where is he this is so vulnerable up here
no shots no shot god i did it oh my god the seal was broken in town thank goodness
so what did what did that do like there was a few places i couldn't couldn't see before
it was up there but wasn't there a few more there was like seals all over the town
it doesn't really matter i guess you broke too yeah the seals yeah the seals are gone
but did that help me i know these seals are gone up here but there was one of like big ones
blocking paths yeah i know about that one but they were two huge ones uh where's the bonfire
i am not gonna go over there without sitting at the bonfire are you serious i have one
mana flask can you show us how to do it again i was busy cooking steakums
um just run it sucks run and hide behind the little things all right well whatever this is
let's find out what's one of these well i'm going to assume this is about to take us here
i'm doing that oh yeah i'm going to this church over here uh because if there's a sacred tier here
there's no way i'm not gonna get it we will do that momentarily oh what do you see
i have one that's it did i already get this no very cool all right i want this because it's
gonna be a sacred tier god how come nobody's freaking out about this nobody cares it's raining
hell shit at least they gave me this
dude how the fuck do you get away from this fucking thing
what how are you supposed to do this i'm trying to look up and see where they're going and
thankfully i'm glad they just start you here did you like freeze my computer when you do this
tell us i must just go just sprint straight actually work hey hey it's still i'm sitting at
the grace what the fuck is happening i'm literally sitting down at the fire how am i getting hurt
i'm sitting down what's going on over here all right at least it's not aggroed silver
mirror shield friends alive what do i do wait that was that actually a shield field of radiant
silver astuned with amber and carried by loretta knight of the halid tree shape is said to imitate
that of a sacred drop of dew which inspired the absurd rumor that loretta herself was an
alberiniac they're like this is gonna leave oh i didn't do the previous part of the quest
well and there's no sacred tier here it was a wasted effort okay um i wanted to go down here
well let's just go look right i want to go see what's over here i hope i don't get trapped over
here um let's just see what's over here i'm imagine this is probably going to go to the tree
this could be a huge lore dump incoming killa's halid tree this place fucking sucks why have
you said that for every single area that's happened the last 10 minutes
20 minutes each new place i find people say this is the worst place in the game
this whole game is pain this is gonna be awful because i'm gonna fall off so many times okay
goal is just to get down the tree so what is this thing what's what why is this here
because there's the urn tree and then there's this other huge tree it's the halid tree
somebody gonna explain to me how this works am i gonna like walk in a boss door and they're
gonna like sit me down and be like look here's what happened there are two trees one of his evil
and i'll be like all right crazy looking though where even am i on the map oh fuck
oh my god shit okay so don't do that move that move is very dangerous shit okay we're fine
big gold rune that was dumb
i made it there are like bugs here my beloved dude god let's get out get out get out okay
we're fine don't oh i'm fine stop fucking jesus why is it like a cartoon i ain't going back up
there there's like a little town in here that's alive dude shit piece of shit i swear
stop doing that i'm gonna get it i just go i have the bubbles i can use them
jesus all right uh what about over here i'm safe right here very cool you could probably jump to
that that's a that's a tough call i don't think so there's a ladder i i see the ladder i know
there's a ladder there i was just seeing if um i could like jump to the top of the building like
it might be an item like on top i know i knew there's a ladder what are you guys talking about
i was like can i jump on top sometimes they put items on top of these things
all right so can you get the trumpet guy spirit ashes ah that's a good point maybe i don't know
the guy is a plant all right we're going in there we'll go up the ladder in a minute
i saw you you blended in but i saw you know what fuck all of you
oh hit him hit him hit him hit him hit him hit him hit him spitting stone eight
i could use a somber spitting stone eight that'd be swell or nine take either one i'm tired um
my god this is another one empty beast bones looks like a lot of ways to kind of go look around out
here you're probably all right there's a drop down yeah why did i do that why did i do that
why did i just do that what's the thinking god i i can't believe i just did that that was a
guaranteed death i don't know how i did that i can't climb that i can go that way go in the building
for now up this is tight this is tight someone's gonna be right here i'm gonna get knocked off
i can hear somebody breathing hell yeah i definitely have enough to level up use the super run
i need 97 000 to level up i should get it 67 80 90 should do it right okay i need
any three more intelligence i gotta pee again but i'm not going anywhere yet okay so from here i can
go that way which let me go back down over here oh it's one of those things okay easy somber
smithing stone eight is that what i needed to get the uh staff up or is it nine i think it's nine
all right i'm gonna i got a stun lock is there another one stun lock incoming two three
i thought i was gonna backstab okay oh please yes legendary here oh yeah that's two i have two of
the regular ones now yeah this spell is incredible it's the best spell in the whole game i need
another somber stone this probably one here i'm gonna go that way in a second really go live
use the cheap one just kill him please oh why do i think that's gonna work i don't know why i
thought that was gonna work it was stupid let me check over here first i can jump on this roof
i'm going this way so now that's a regular smithing stone
that gets you back out to the bugs just take your computer into the bathroom
you're so annoying i need a fucking god damn i need a shield to parry this easy parry move
catch you in this oh it okay so what were you hiding over here golden rune he's back why is
he doing what's he doing here why is he back what the fuck is happening why is he back little
shit it's you why are you still here what the fuck somebody else summoned them the hell they are
okay so where is this okay i'm just running fuck it i have no idea what this thing is
die i could probably jump from there no not quite big subs from freddy dread oh what's up freddy
it's a hundred fucking subs what are you doing there's been something there's been a lot of
community subs tonight there's been a couple people that came in and dropped like fucking
hundreds of them as well that's 150 something we had like 150 from who was it from roshan
you guys are crazy why why why why why just don't even fight these things this stupid
where am i going i don't know what is that thing i don't know i think it's one of those uh flying
things settle the fuck down please what's that blasts dude there are so many little like bits
and bobs here to jump to and fly to and stuff i don't i don't even know where the fuck i'm
supposed to be going cool i'm over here now heroes rune just kick them off knock them off
knock them off knock them off the edge christ who are these dickheads here holy fuck he blew up the
whole area see ya i ain't dealing with that shit what happened go leap before they get here oh my
god they're there too many bits and bobs there are way too many bits and bobs here i don't know
which way to go this way fuck that's okay that's okay that guy's low health they're close enough
you've got to be shitting in my face okay like let's be real here why you've got to be kidding
me you've got to be fucking kidding me what the fuck man you've got to be all right i'm going
the other way fuck you i'm going the other bridge dickheads i'm gonna go the other way
there are far too many bits and bobs all right what's in here i can go in here it's an elevator
get in the elevator get in the elevator jesus there are honestly way too many places to go
all right so where does this end up seriously oh yeah remember you just that literally just
spiked my allergies i don't know i'm not taking antihistamine man okay this this looks bossy
it is bossy and who's that loretta knight of the halleg tree can i get on a horse too you know who
i'm summoning let's go buddy level nine serpent get him oh shit we've got uh he's doing pretty
well nice he's so slippery put magic away for this i was i'm just gonna fight wait if i hit
man serpents pretty sick i'm not gonna lie no oh my goodness i'm staggering in the fire look at
that honestly great job we got to be real that was a that was a stellar performance
immediately holy shit oh fuck he killed me in one hit damn it he i know i just like every single
human and i just always say guy oh the guy all right i think should we try the boys you have
health reduction debuff i don't i don't have that thing all right we'll try the boys this time that
was all right we'll see who does better the boys will be more distracting that's for sure you do
have a debuff from what how do i have a debuff oh it's this it's this maybe i should take this off
uh for this fight put on something more defensive magic damage yeah just don't get hit it's the
easy way to do it i guess all right let's get the boys out here all right get in there shit
boys are doing pretty good too oh that was a little late i'm in trouble all right somebody
why don't you fuck that up because we could have gotten some hits in why don't you fuck that up
i'll be honest all right be easy you hit me what fucking enough swinging motherfucker enough
swinging i couldn't see anything the camera went like the camera fucking spun so fucking fast
i don't know what why did my guy just head just go like i think uh i think serpent uh serpent was
better your weapon sucks hello no the weapon's fine the weapon doesn't suck that was because
i didn't think i was gonna do that anyways try the nebula i feel like with another two health
potions i would have been fine the problem with the weapon art is it just it takes a long time
to work it takes a it's a huge wind up and he has these little spells he can shoot from his end of
his stick i see i know i know it's just a guy guy uh yeah well that guy that guy that guy that guy
all right here we go serpent serpent did actually really good here we go good
hmm very good oh my god i didn't think he's gonna go that way i don't know why oh good job
good job you took the whole thing oh yes good good good be a real pain in the ass good
oh fuck bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad bad i'm fine fucking face oh my god
oh my god oh my god don't kill me with those harry by the man serpent the man serpent is fucking
awesome the man serpent is so good oh red is mastery the fire on the ground
is such a huge pain in the ass because they'll go on top of it and it does the same shit that
does to you it's like that and you can't do anything oh it's so good all right that was cool
that was fun fight i have 200 000 souls oh yeah let me wait the weapon what was it it was like a
sickle war sickle int strength dex mostly strength and intelligence though
oh very nice is this a unique animation set this i think this is a unique animation set
that's really that's actually incredible and it's this yeah that's really cool and what was the
spell fire's four great hours from magic great bow at once 46 int to use it i'll try it
okay what's going on what's going on why can't i touch that it's happening it's freaking me out
i'm scared i thought that was a fake and that i was it was gonna be like a face too or something
oh i do here i feel like i need to use that that sorcery or like something like this one point
away from being able to use it without a rune arc i think i have a lot of these this is a hero's
rune no it's not enough well i need to get to 50 uh yeah i'll focus on that after this what is
this for thing over here down there it's too expensive the spamming great bow is better
are the new bow spell oh this goes down even further this goes way down doesn't it i gotta
pee this is a lot more there's more to do down here uh okay so here's what i want to do i am
going to rest at the bonfire what time is it 10 all right still got a little while left i want
to go back i want to go back here because i wanted to do this we're gonna do with this
i'm gonna go brb we'll go do this we'll see what time it is when we're done with this
and i'll be right back the sound stream is not muted what are you talking about okay so let's do
this area over here how are you so i wanted to see this spot preferably yeah this whole area
over here and this too why not all right two and five that was a suspiciously long urination
was it though i got filled my water back up well i got water at this time suspiciously long
dude can you please stop trying to spoil this game for me the last 12 streams
sorry dude i'm sorry i'm spoiling it for you i don't mean to okay two and five you want to
just go to mug and get it out of chat system sure where's mug what's the fastest way to mug
i'm imagining mug is probably five who is mug two and five are mugs well we're going to two right
now two and five are mug i have so many of these darts i don't even know what to do with them all
clear great i'm trying to listen invaded by sanguine noble
oh that sucked doesn't it oh my god he's trying to drink just interrupt his drinking every time
fuck no no get out of here what do you have sanguine noble hood sanguine noble robe and waist
cloth would have died black cloth featuring gold embroidery worn by the nobles who serve the lord
of blood known to strike from pools of blood these assassins are missionaries come to share
the gospel of a cursed blood say one of these two 83 focus the gray metallic pattern on the
shoulder is a signifier of the noble rank they intend to claim upon the advent of the new
dynasty they are working to install keep going to the direction that that guy just came from
like over here right this way oh shit so where does this go there's blood all over it it's
happening it's happening i was here oh here we go it's happening we're going to mugs hideout
we've been talking about this guy for like four streams yeah right i'm back up in the
mogwin palace come on mug come on what come on god jesus
raise the horse i can oh there's blood everywhere foggy you're kind of a slob all right well there's
a lot of these people all right i gotta go just touch the grace mog palace holy shit there's so
many people here there's 2 000 wounds each for these guys holy shit this is just like a farming
spot i need some blood fire oh my goodness that's a lot actually a lot you do this like two or three
times you'll level up i just want to see what the item is over here okay there's even more of them
down there looking at this like four just hanging out in the same spot damn anything else down here
besides this good all right i gotta go get more manna i'm gonna turn around
i just like i could kill these guys so much yeah just give me manna put some more flasks in please
all right let's do that again you have to go that way because you can't you just die if you fall
maybe i'll just level up right i mean why not what bird shoot the bird bird
what there's no bird what bird are you talking about shoot the bird
oh yeah i am gonna do i mean i'm just i'm just gonna level up once
it's aggro everybody it's aggro the whole thing manna manna manna manna 75 000 already
i'll be able to get my one more point intelligence and then we can go
i got up to level 404 here level to level 400 that seems excessive i don't i don't know what
this bird is that you guys are talking about but i don't i don't see it this would be good
ice okay go back right next to the grace i don't see a bird i have no idea what you're talking
about right next to the grace there's apparently a gigantic bald eagle that i don't see there's
apparently a big bird that i don't see you're talking about that what do you want me to do
that that thing you want to shoot that with a bow and arrow fucking edge dude drop an item
wait can you just do that over and over again is that the spot oh my god that's so stupid
i could hit the fucking thing that would be wonderful you don't really just reload this
and do 10 000 every time right that's so stupid that's so okay that's funny all right i can finally
use the moon finally well let me kill it now because i don't want to deal with it later
that's a good idea uh just wait till they patch that that's this is not going to be a thing for
that much longer i just don't want to fight that later because it's going to be there still okay
here we go let's do it you use the gold pickle thing oh yeah stop pretending that you didn't
already know about that this is the first time i've been here this is the first time i've stepped
foot in the zone how would i know that that was there i didn't think you could use the horse here
in there this is probably a rock ladies this is probably i can't probably can't stand on this
blood tax oh yep yep yep yep yep staff can go up upgraded this is just a mad item dash
okay the blood tax let me just look at the perimeter for a minute there's this is what
the bird was anything else here interest yeah there's a map fragment maybe is there is there
a map of this place smorma flies yeah this is just an item run i ain't stopping a fight like
40 people right now no thanks goodbye that smells really good all right i think i got all the items
except for this right it's the tibia mariner here was that person some
oh shit oh i'm dead i ain't no fucking goodness where's that item there's an item it's an item
somewhere over here i can't jump over the beam it's as fucking thin as a piece of
there was an item right in the middle and i missed it there it is sacramential butt
give me a break get the fuck out of here mogwin dynasty mausoleum map mogwin okay finally
that was absolute hell i can see where i am now thank god mogwin dynasty mausoleum what is right
next to me right here it's the thing i came in okay got what i want for spells and i level up
again i think so let's do it oh hell yeah i need 104 000 i'll get 100 and there we go
all right boys and girls i'm first to actually see and the item that i have
do i need to use this because this is something so i have this on briefly binds mug i put that on
like a bar or something i use it oh my god there's too many there's so many people here
i can't even fucking whatever fuck all of you
only hit one person what are you talking about there's like just five people standing here
hit them all okay whatever okay sprinting all right i'm sick of this
this is better crap let's look for a way to walk is that mog right there it's smog
i think this is mog right here this is literally mug i think
hey pop the bubble and i got out you all that cold they don't like the cold there all right
stop biting your lip stop i i can't help it i just do it they're a merchant in here why is
there a merchant down here what are you doing down here
why are you here okay how's this guy still here
lord's ruin that bog's room i'm just running because i can't i don't want to fight this thing
like five times oh my fucking god dude what are you doing great ghost gloveboard
oh my god he's so scary he's just like running through all the people
i need a great grave gloveboard not god i still have too many ghost gloveboards what's up
hey stop stop stop stop no he's right behind me fucking feel his breath oh my goodness how
the fuck am i not getting hit stop stop leave me alone oh sit sit at the thing so that was
lord's ruin no more lip biting i'm i'm like nervous that mog right there are they
summoning mog is that mog what's happening here what are you guys doing i'm taking this
it's just mine now that was it i need one of those where's mog where's mog at oh all right
there's bog i'll get an egg this made me need to pee i don't know why yeah there he is there's
mog i'll let him take the elden ring dearest michaela best to the love of our dynasty
serpent he's over there you and me right here right let's go right here you hit me in the
fucking forearm ow let's get him okay that's slow that's pretty slow
okay that's a huge overhead swing throws like blood at you oh that hurts that's good
gotta get that down ugly what is that oh god what's this he just he healed he heals at that stage
okay all right i think i'm gonna save the i'm gonna save serpent use the shackle
i'm gonna wait to bring serpent in because he looked like he started that was transition to
phase two hopefully the game didn't crash i feel like it did i think so yes it did okay well
uh i'll be right back i'm gonna reload the game please don't fuck up my save that's cool though
that's a cool fight so that's halid tree and i don't know what are they all what are they all
doing here so i'm what i'm gonna do try to get to phase two bring the serpent out and then
i'm just imagining you have to run i'm imagining that when he starts to do that thing when he the
bloody you just have to run the fuck away as far as you can all right yeah we're good let's go you
see i also could level up my staff to plus 10 which i probably i've read yeah i mean why would
i not do that this guy this guy's crazy apparently let's do that ancient flask um i think it's fine
for now this is very important okay here we go sombra ancient dragon smithing stone
we're at the maximum scaling on this weapon 321 so my moves are gonna be way better now and wait
didn't i get i need a great grave glove for it i think serpent is the call though i do i thought
that was gonna be way more expensive i just wasted that run all right uh over here are there any
romance options um i don't think so let's see if i can get them down to at least like 30 40 percent
on my own what's that i can send it back down i always forget to do this all right let's go
let's try it he's gonna send like five moons at him immediately the very beginning
pretty shit that was fucking incredible slow very slow way slower than i gotta hold on wait
i'll just do that fucking thing is so slow oh that was dumb i'll never it's gonna take me like
five more tries to get the like here it comes i'm just trying to get some ingredients do like a
fucking chunk on him all right watch out get out get out get out get out get out you're gonna do
the thing what the fuck how far away do you have to be how far away do you have to be
how far away do you have to be let's just hit you everywhere there's no you can't run from it
is unlimited range you just have really holy shit okay that well all right okay all right
use the shackle when he does oh that's a good idea isn't it i have the thing i don't know why
i'm not using it how many times can i use it all right i also have to first one not hit him
i i get i gotta take off some of these spells having to go tap tap tap tap tap like five times
to get the spell i want i gotta get rid of some of these fucking useless ones three hit combo or
is it a two greed is so real on this some of this shit i'm standing in this goo oh my god that's a
fucking wall behind me is there yes there is all right i think i gotta i gotta get rid of some of
these spells i'm never gonna use like star all right like starlight swift glint stone
zamora's wind store i just want three two spells i don't want to have to be like okay i did my moon
and now oh there it is okay oh oh got it you oh my god his fucking reach and timing suck
i gotta give him a phase two before i can even jesus yeah that overhead swing his arm extends
like five times longer than his arm actually is he stretch armstrongs his arm 50 feet in front of
him fucking piece of shit i can do two and that's it get two of these right that'll frost him
it literally did it the last time i did it actually did it the last time i just did it
why what the fuck happened oh shit don't get greedy all right here he goes here he goes
so i have to heal through this wait i have a shackle i'm gonna use the shackle let's see what
works yeah it didn't do anything it didn't do anything oh my god he turned and punched me in the
face dude dodge the attacks bro do you see what this motherfucker's doing on the screen
so much of the attacks dude what you really should try to do is dodge the attacks are you
sure i shouldn't shouldn't fucking run at him and stand still all right he's doing a shit
load of blood i feel like this guy's really hard i need some more help here what is he's doing like
blood damage what's like the highest immunity thing in the game is it worth putting this stuff
on the shackle only works in the first phase what about one of these headshots crits blood loss
wait what about that i i mean he does fire this is okay this is immunity you shackle while he's
casting it definitely you'll definitely have a lot of blood loss yeah raise immunity and then i'll
put on some immunity shit this is okay what about this give me something better like five
because that's killing me that's doing so much damage all right these are low immunity 44 that's
heavy load though i gotta be careful 39 44 i don't think i'm gonna see more than 44
um this is i think a good either way just has a lot read read robustness not immunity for bleed
oh oh oops all right well that's pretty robust that's robust that's robust that's very robust
that's what i had on 35 34 39 it's literally the same fucking clothes i just had on
all right so shackle only works in phase one let's see what it does i just curious what it does
what's going on all right shackle okay i mean that's how often can i use that
oh i can use it like a bunch of times in a row holy shit let's do this i use it like
can i use it you can only do it twice oh it's fire damage too all right i kind of
fucked this whole thing up didn't i can't do it more than once okay you can only do it twice
it's is it really even worth doing maybe not honestly i gotta get the timing to be swings
they're like markets just like sometimes it just takes like an extra second to swing down
it's actually been a while since i've been fighting an enemy like this yeah it's even longer
let me just try to get some timings down we're gonna do some practice runs here
somebody's so quick to fuck you
all right then he does the fire shit you got it back away from the fire all right there it is
okay that's a lot faster than than the other one is you throw that far just trying to practice
okay i got it down something he does three sometimes though he's got do i have to scream
it from the mountaintops that this is a practice run to learn the mechanics of the fight i'm not
trying to hurt anybody i'm trying to simply learn the mechanics of the fight gordon mr freeman
he started with okay is fine there's a whole second phase of different different moves
i know what look we got we can we got a crawl before we can run i can't i gotta reliably be
able to get him down to 50 you're the funniest guy on twitch what happened i didn't do anything
all right first of all i gotta do two moons what happened to them dude please like holding y and
pressing r1 sucks such ass sometimes god i gotta go to god damn bonfire this is infuriating having
to do that come on mogwin can i truly hit him during this how fast does he go i got startled
from the thing it does a second attack the fire on the ground is such poor shit it just makes it
makes like trying to fight him so much fucking harder he just puts it's just like that little
fire on the ground where you just like uh uh uh uh that was much better that was actually progress
oh i'm gonna keep at it
no i didn't want to do that that fucked the whole thing up that was such a great start too
i got it don't worry i got it that's a fourth attack sometimes you just don't do that
you just don't do that sometimes it's always so fucking annoying you don't do that sometimes
it's a lot weird right now i'm just so mad at this stupid bullshit moves
boys oh fuck boys so bad i i that was not me fucking around i really wanted to try to get them
out that would have been awesome i probably should do it right when he's done with the
heal though all right i'm making progress i got it i got it i'm making progress don't
worry check this out fuck he doesn't start with that usually dude oh my god oh give me a
fucking break he did the same overhead smash twice in a row oh this guy sucks ass
i no no here's what we're doing i'm taking all these useless fucking spells off so i don't have
to go one two three four five six to get to the next goddamn spell if i want to do the moon i'm
gonna do the moon if i want to do the slash i'm gonna slash i'm not gonna skip through seven
fucking spells get rid of them all i don't want any of them on the i don't want any of them remove
remove remove remove remove these are only two gosh darn spells that i need on this gosh darn
bar okay i don't want to sit there and do a move and then go okay i got it gosh darn it i'm getting
really really hated all right wait wait wait wait wait one of these should i do one of these
you're like driving with no shoes on and what do you what do you mean how is this how is this
driving without shoes on what's that supposed to mean you don't do the magic like i feel like
i know what you're talking about like it's weird to drive you know you can but it's not good like
i gotta suck okay drive with shoes on what i have a damage boost you don't really boost magic attack
what about one that boosts all damage no winged crystal tier i don't know what else maybe flame
flame one maybe sounds good do the exploding one i'm not just gonna blow myself up i think this
one's the best i think this one's good plus the infinite fp1 yeah all right we'll get here's what
we're gonna do you ready walk in the door drink flask moon moon moon it's gonna take out half his
goddamn health bar all right let's go yeah drink the flask go in the door just spam moons until he
gets too close that's the play it is and then shackle so moon moon moon moon moon shackle drink
drink drink i got it ruin arc not yet i'm not comfortable with i'm not confident with the second
phase yet i am barely 60 confident in the first phase we're not quite there yet not quite there
for a ruin arc here we go ready i can just spam it so we're just gonna fucking do it if he walks
into it he walks into it shackle didn't work how did the shackle not work that's a really good
opener though it actually is like the best opener i can do how come i couldn't shackle it i'm so
confused right now this is like fucking up the whole thing this is throwing me off so bad
how did it not work okay well i that just threw me off so bad he was in the middle of an animation
that was a good opener i just i expected him to go down and he didn't so i can't do it immediately
i have to wait till he's done and he's like attacked being hit animation and then do the
shackle just r1 i that's not gonna happen like that straight up isn't happening i don't do nearly
as much damage with an r1 against this guy it does i do like a fucking 120 okay here we go
good to go that's a good start you know what bring in the boys right now go go go we're throwing a
wild cardin i just got sucked into another dimension i got beamed into a fucking alien
spaceship somebody please edit that and you put like blue and green light all over me and like
to make me disappear from the chair please get the boys out quick get them out oh my god you
didn't even hit me you fucking didn't even try to hit me ah fuck there we go fuck the follow-up
swing too fuck you dude really what are all these new fucking moves you didn't do these poor
holy fucking shit the fire on the ground man i can't if the fire touch hits you i can't dodge
it's like it's a stagger fuck you man really holy shit it's like i'm ready to dodge and then my
character goes like out and i get hit yeah i i think i'm gonna it's gonna be close this is a
great way to start this fight and then we just get the boys up immediately i gotta get him i
have to get him in phase two reliably not hit him that didn't hit him well that's a bad start but
okay all right dude when he does the one two it's just you can't there's no way to know what his
third fucking thing is gonna be is he gonna follow up with another move or is he not two three okay
four he went the other way thank god dude let's get fucking weird with this one everything's on
fucking fire bro how are you supposed to fight this guy he burns his whole arena to the ground
god damn it that poor noble
jesus christ try to abuse another spell besides the moon okay if i do moon then
use the shackle i want everyone to just yell at the same time the shackle only works in phase one
everyone please type it in all caps everyone's getting fucking banned sorry thanks for being a
fucking distraction no god damn it no fuck how do i you no that's it no stop no stop doing moves
fucking jesus stop doing moves let me fucking attack you is it runar time i don't know man i
thought we're gonna lose immediately try the l2 it's i think that's way too slow all right let's
do it okay i think the l2 is going way too slow you got 30 of them all right hold on i gotta like
moisten my mouth for a second same plan come on ah oh shit we gotta get we gotta put the spells
away man it's too risky at this point dude you attack so many fucking times in a row it sucks
like the opportunity to attack is so fucking low like how the fuck am i supposed to close the gap
on this motherfucker it's so ridiculous it's like by the time you can get in there and attack him
it's like no no he's doing he you're fucked like waste the opportunity to attack him i need faster
spells all right we're going back we're going back i'm gonna put the ice thingy because i at
that second phase no fucking way can i get in there and hit him uh i and it doesn't do enough
damage i mean i'll last his ass this one here i can't wait to come here with pure strength
well that is going to be that is going to be very hard on nvu is it i know there's i know
there's like a laser beam spell but i i don't want to go i don't want to beat him with like the thing
that drink five flasks to kill him in one hit i'll get him i'll get him just everything has to go
right the rattles no the rattles don't you know i'll i'm gonna try a new tactic we're gonna change
it up here we go i'm curious how this works let's try it here we go much better tactic are you
kidding me what am i doing with my life what was i thinking this is gonna kill him in five seconds
let's be fucking ballsy let's go ballsy ballsy ballsy ballsy oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck get out
of the way boys you're in the way no oh that's a different move than the moment he slams what the
fuck holy shit dude i couldn't even fucking do anything right okay all right i gotta change
flask that's the that's the way i need i need like two more mana flasks that was that was good that
was the one plus 10 baby rattles shut up do you have great build that whatever uh i do have the
great lince the spell that goes further that's bigger uh but i feel like this does more damage
same thing applies let's go again we're going again we're good you can take two hits in the
phase change before you have to drink should i just go just wail on them with um with sorcery
and then just drink after the second one that's right let's go i fucked it up but i think i think
i'm fine get it in two hands you idiot i that's surprising to me i don't i guess we're doing the
serpent friend oh shit that range is so awful oh i fuck the whole thing up maybe i should do it
all right this is a wash but sorry i'm not going to do it all right get in there and fucking fight
him oh get his attention get him hit him do something it was so pretty i deserve to die
i deserve to die i deserve to die deserved it i just was like fucking spam spam spam spam
i got it i got it i got it i'm gonna get it i deserved that and i'll be very honest i think
he might be better i think he might be better i really do i i i i i oh fuck fuck you do something
help me nice drink two of those fucking things i swear to god i bet an audible shit this is a
panic run if i've ever seen one holy shit ah i can't see dude i can't fucking see through the shit on
the fucking ground man you can't just like oh hey hey do you see the boss he's over there somewhere
hey can you hey hey i know this like this like 50 gravestones but can you can you see me
i don't like this tactic by the way it's way too fucking slow way too slow
not doing that tactic god damn it bro seriously like i thought i could do it
a second i really thought that it wasn't gonna kill me i just didn't want to waste a flask
i'll get it i'll get it it's got everything the cards have to all
let i've got to get like three aces okay it might happen less greed more like intelligence
boys shit he's looking at me fuck on oh my god boys what are you doing
snake is way better he really is it's unfortunate it's true we gotta see you gotta you gotta say
what it's when it's real it's real and the boys kind of afraid of mog and um we need people that
have no fear that go in they drink fucking a magical flask and they cast 10 times in a row
and they're supposed to do like two i love the boys i do but come on gwen you piece of shit let's go
fuck come here snake please he's done that move so many fucking times in a row
and i'll be really honest he hasn't done the other one it's a little bit faster fuck you
dude you're killing me here i'm gonna walk where are we i don't know thank god for that
fucking snake friend
what the fuck dude 420 000 souls okay oh my goodness i do not those of you let me say a quick
prayer for those of you that are strict strength and melee characters oh dear you're in you you
have you're having that's gonna be a very hard thing to do uh snake friend leveled up on my
friends list uh all five of the boys just went down to till a little bit lower i've been spending
way more time with the snake it's not it's like natural to like kind of drift apart from other
friends right being the snake i've been hanging out a lot and it's like i'll call the boys
sometimes when i want to hang out but i mean i'm just i've been spending more time with the snake
oh my god that sucked and that's not even the hard one oh i did this first try i'm not kidding
you are a god some of those timings are so hard especially when you start bumping into gravestones
which by the way why are there so many of these up here it's just that all these gravestones
there's no places to bury anybody why are there so many gravestones it's just like
they're all your deaths yeah you made that joke two weeks ago you can't make that joke again but
you said snakes were unpredictable they are that's why they're so good at this fight because
mogg come on gwen it how he couldn't deal with it how are you supposed to deal with somebody
that just stands in the corner and goes like this it's weird it's like what you're doing is
weird so i'm like i'm kind of i'm gonna step back for a second all right uh that's definitely the
end of the stream by the way like i'm going fucking bad is there anything i can do here
that was a funny ending well hold on i'm not quite hold on a second i want to go see what that is
what else did i got i got his resemblance but i also i got something else too what was the other
thing oh the rune mogg's great room seek the divine tower of east atlas which stands beyond
the great bridge from lindell's eastern ward seek the divine tower of west atlas
okay at whatever did i not oh rykar's great run okay but let me let me go back to town
let's level up let me say every word wrong i don't know dude here's your 50 uh 50 vigor perfect
now let's focus on mind and endurance see we i want to i'm very i'm curious what we can get
should go talk to gideon i will what are these things gonna come back and talk
or are you just kind of stuck we sure that this thing didn't just like crash
augwin's sacred spear blood boon faith and arcane scatters blood flame before caster to set area of
flame mother of truth craves wounds when mog stood before her deep underground his accursed blood
erupted with fire and he was bestowed with the defilement that he was born into
frightened of mog lord of blood a sacred spirit that will come to symbolize his dynasty
as well as serving as a weapon it is an instrument of communion with an outer god
who bestows power upon a cursed blood mother of truth desires a wound well arcane and strength
is not this character at all use that instead of the baby rattle i would have to respect the
entire character respect to use this i don't think so whoa royal knight helm veteran's helm
anselm veteran's armor royal knight this this is good this is really good
is that better than what i have on i know that is but this is heavy though that's way too heavy
i'm not sure i can put that on lord of blood i might just i mean i have enough runes maybe i
was by this one's 15 what is it okay 16 14 how am i how is this compared to the scale scale armor
remember the beach hat the beach hat boost cold sorceries i need to use it
i'm gonna break this i'm not gonna use either one of the items so i'm just gonna smash it
bye see you later mog it was great but level up probably two more times what's with the stream
title oh i don't know is a like ipad game joke or something okay let me look at what is it 16 13
16 16 16 13 so this is better oh all right cool put this on royal knight armor oh that's cool
i'd lose a lot of resistances but i gained some more physical defense so how does it look
that looks pretty awesome yeah put it on heavy load royal knight i actually look kind of cool now
it actually fits it matches pretty cool all right let's do need a little bit more time is it
midnight what if i just said fuck it and kept going really a little while not that much not
that much longer just just long enough to all right i won't mind mind and endurance
i think i can do it again now let's do this lord's rune it's gonna be like 50k
okay are you gonna scream tomorrow um i don't know it depends on what i do today
i i can't i want to go see another one or two things i'm not done not yet i'm close but i'm
not here yet what are you doing oh so me and ludwig are gonna do what's today so on tuesday
all right so there'll be no screen tomorrow we're just gonna go for a little while a little while
longer tonight tuesday is uh bro versus bro me versus ludwig so that should be fun i get
to pick a few games i'm gonna tell we're gonna tell each other believe tonight or tomorrow what
the games are you better believe that i'm i'm coming with some real classics i don't want to
give it away but i'm telling you right now i think i have a pretty good chance of winning
very good chance i think all right uh what was i just doing i can put the spells back on because
i don't i don't i i kind of freaked out here didn't i i want to try this and starlight okay
i want to go talk to gideon i want to activate the rune talk to gideon because at this point
dude i got i'm it's me it's it's me uh here we go oh so that's where the so-called lord was
hiding himself there a fitting little squat for that deluded maniac to bleat about the revival of
his precious dynasty while he turns our fellow tarnished into bloody fingers let him stay there
away his delusions will remain as they are distant and unattainable but perhaps it's worth looking
into if what i've heard is right then maybe my apologies lost myself for a moment there
the information you shared is of great value that's promised your reward it is a wondrous
thing indeed you are a true fellow all i ask is that you remain constant
you gave me a cookbook fucking cookbook dude i have slayed every demon and every tarnished
every monster in this whole world and you're gonna give me grandma's meatball recipe is that
really what you're doing you're gonna show me that how to make fucking lasagna you don't have
a weapon under there that has a magical fucking juice on it or something that's unbelievable
a cookbook this better be this better be good where is it it is a wondrous thing indeed okay
what is it bewitching branch uses fp to charm pierced enemy here's a foe using fp to turn them
into a temporary ally but actually that is really good well what is it i see so nicola was with the
lord of blood after all that is some fine intelligence indeed it's pretty high with it
the far clue has been brought into the light what is it one of the last few pieces the round table
i need to put everything together as promised allow me to impart to you the last of the secret
rights normally to me close the door law of causality if he continues his slumber within
the cocoon it would be safer to destroy it nicola is the one thing that remains a mystery to me
well there are four more demigods yet to be located uh nicola of the hey i just killed him
it's twin millennia no i didn't the undefeated lunar princess rani and he has said so here above
you should learn anything i'll trade you fine oh as such okay so interesting if i go load that
area what happens to be dead there i need to turn these on right i have a couple that are just not
on one of them was an atlas right okay this is divine tower of west atlas divine tower of east
atlas easy enough oh okay already been yeah it's oh more gods okay the hardest boss in any souls
game i know i know and dude like i don't know hogs great runes so what do you do with this
grants a blessing of blood to phantoms it's a blessing of blood to summoned phantoms and
imparts a phantom great rune upon successful invasion hog and margot are twin brothers and
their great runes are naturally similar the mogs rune is soaked in a cursed blood from his devout
love for the wretched mire that he was born into what does this do makes you your summons to do
cool shit when they get kills pvp buff uh okay uh all right let's go to the other one the other one
was over here what was it west atlas stands upon the precipice at the coast southwest of lendell
that's right here okay how do i get there you go through the cave in here what is this
it should be a church okay i have a question for everybody that's played through this game and that
has knows everything about it if i cannot i can't go this way um if i go to that mountaintop where
the giants are and i go to that big scary thing am i going to lock myself out of doing anything
else oh okay what about no okay no you have to you lock yourself out of an ending you lock yourself
out getting some items that's okay i don't think i care i'm at this point i'm pretty locked in
not major you don't lock yourself out okay all right well let's i want to see it i want to know
what happens do we need to go i need to go this way probably better to do this
yeah i'm not gonna do everything that's possible i have second third fourth fifth playthroughs
eventually do that i'll do on my own and i encourage you to do different things too
because the game obviously is supposed to be played through a magnitude of times the area
after that that you get locked out of okay i did not come here minor urtree church
that would have been nice if i had had this because this is definitely a sacred tier
it's not a sacred tier what the hell is it golden order seal like a faith weapon
i look like a faith weapon yeah it is boost fundamentalist incantations fundamentalism
okay cool well how would you rate this game i really don't even know it's r2
okay i think it's probably the new standard for what people would consider like a great
unbelievable video game i think it'll probably end up being the standard if not a standard of
like video game it's not perfect i don't think by any means uh but it's pretty damn it's pretty
damn close i would say it's probably yeah i would say it's probably the game of the decade
it's sort of a culmination of okay well it has a thing if you don't like from software games
and you're gonna be like dude you're an idiot like this game's not as good as um skyrim but i mean
hold on it's gonna come back and go wrap around get off the horse i didn't i want to do so much
sooner than that i'm brain is just slow just tired here okay there have been times in this
game where i looked around and said it is too much to do i'm standing right here there's times i've
opened the map and i'm going like there's way too much to do i don't even know what to do
so when you get to that stage where each area and each place you're going to is so overwhelmingly
large with stuff to look at and stuff to do i mean there's no i don't i can't think of
a game that did that to me in the last 10 years where i was actually truly overwhelmed by the
video game truly like i don't know about this this is kind of this is so inspiring i don't
know what to do where do i go look at the tree there's a tree over there it's been an incredibly
long time am i not gonna be able to hurt this last time i had that feelings when i played dark
souls for the first time yeah but i this is better than dark souls i know people probably
gonna be mad at me for that i think but it is just isn't i'm so bad at this i can't even
comprehend why i'm doing this so poorly but it's it's unfair to say that because this is
this is just dark souls 5.0 did it leave the thing fucking left oh here it is
very full strike okay cool um because everybody needs to please be honest please be honest with
yourselves and with me and i'll be honest too this is this is just this is dark souls like it's just
the game is the video game not the world not the pieces not the individual parts the video game
here is dark souls it's just dark souls it's that's just what it is there is almost no difference to
how this plays to dark souls they're the almost the exact same video game so saying that like
dark souls 1 is better is kind of hard because or dark souls 3 or whatever is
they just made a better version here it is at least in my opinion right because
secura was a lot different even though it had the same kind of similar themes and stuff it was a
wildly different game i feel like i'm playing dark souls 3 right now like kind of like a better
version of it in a way illusion wall over here right here please destroy that baldkins blessing
do i have i don't have i don't have a blessing i don't have a baldkins blessing how does this
compare to half-life alex they're both like kind of huge huge like generational leaps of video
games for me because this is almost everything i wanted dark souls to be i loved playing dark
souls 3 i love bloodborne i loved i didn't love the hero but you know let's just say it we'll
just say because it's the whole family and we can't just say we don't love a certain family members
uh but what was it what was it going where was it what was it just saying like a one second ago
before that what was the last thing that i just said i actually fucking don't remember
what did i say half-life okay okay okay okay half-life alex is also kind of one of those games
that is just like a generational game that's the best version of vr games that exist because most
vr games don't do it very well i still think this is better i think this is better than alex
because it's more the type of game that i like to play i love upgrades i love character progression
i like real character progression not fake horse shit character progression
where your character's moves are not hidden behind a skill tree i don't like arbitrary dumb
stupid shitty skill trees i like real character progression item progression tons of it i like
when games don't kind of i like when you have to kind of figure stuff out like asking you guys how
to kill bog uh this is a game that i like more than a game that i like i like this more than
i like vr games let's put it that way and the here's the worst part about okay the worst part
about being a big fan of games like this is realistically there's really only one company
that makes it it's like the it's this fine wine that is so delicious and so wonderful that you're
like holy shit when they're done when i hope they don't go out of business for any reason
because that's my favorite wine and i'm never going to get it anywhere else then no one will
ever get the same flavor ever again people have tried right people make souls like games but
they're not even close they're not even close some of them have come kind of close have been
hold on there are some that have come kind of close they're they're fun they're interesting
but i just they just don't do it the same way for me and for all the things that i would say about
this game for all the things that i could say nobody really does it the same way every time
i've played one what was the point of doing that there's nothing there oh it was a stone
oh what kind of stone yeah fucking me strong we'll get it kind of want to try this
oh yeah when you see in golden ruin fives i can buy that thing in the store for probably a thousand
souls i don't really need it yeah nobody quite nobody quite doesn't like this and i know it's
it feels kind of bad in a way because like i i didn't like secure as much as i liked
like dark i like dark souls 3 i like bloodborne i the reason why i like dark souls 3
more than any of the other ones besides bloodborne i can't i bloodborne's like in
a grayed out area up here because 30 fps ps4 only but it's like one of my favorite games ever
but dark souls 3 the engine the 60 fps the animations are so much better the dark souls
one remaster it wasn't like didn't do it as much i wish that it was more like the demon souls
which i haven't played so what just happened died dark souls 2 copium
the newer animation style and the newer engine they started using since bloodborne
i find those games to be more fun to play i don't necessarily think that they are
wildly better video games i just think that they're more fun to physically play because
the engine is just better it's cleaner it's more fast paced it's there's more going on yeah
if you gave the dark souls 3 like demon souls engine to dark souls 1 we would have a different
conversation we're not having that conversation right now though it's a wall oh give me that
uh what a good time to get killed i want to do it let me do it the worst enemy probably
to test this on but whatever oh bounces everywhere you piece of shit really thank you for killing
dark souls 2 is bad dark souls 2 is not bad it's just messy dark souls 2 is not a bad game it's
just a mess and i had fun with dark souls 2 i didn't stream dark souls 2 but i played it i
beat it i did when they did the weird let's kind of just go into gmod and place enemies in random
places dlc expansion fucking whatever the hell that was um i played that it was all right
i thought it was fun i didn't hate it i liked how much there was to do in dark souls 2
and add good dlc yeah i did dark souls 3's dlc was really good as well i think dark souls 3 might
have dark souls 3 and bloodborne might be the best dlc of any of the from software games so far
are you still live i guess we're just going yeah bloodborne's dlc is number one and then
dark souls 3's dark souls 3's dlc is number two you like dark souls 2 i don't i don't hate dark
souls 2 i just don't think it's it's not my favorite dark souls 2 and sakiro sit down at
the same place for me sort of dark souls 1 i have to be honest i know a ton of people are like dude
how could you how could you say that dark souls 1 belongs down there it don't it doesn't belong
down there it is i mean you i you watched me play through all of sakiro i did the whole thing on
stream i did that's probably the maddest i've ever been in a video game on camera ever i feel
like i'm remembering only the bad parts of me getting mad at sakiro and not all the good parts
of me having a great time right this place is insane by the way sakiro is better than elden ring
no i just think it's the they just combined all their video games into one game and it's
just the best version of all of them now hold on though i am a big fan of a lot of content
right so i might actually going back and playing dark souls 2 i might have a different opinion
uh i've heard the complaints of this game of well when there's okay he's gonna explode
when there's so much to do and you level up it's very easy to kind of miss whole areas because the
character is too strong and you go back and it's like oh i guess i just kind of missed this entire
thing but i just like it's like i kill everything in one hit and it's kind of not fun right i
understand that aspect my only rebuttal would be just don't do it do it on a different character
and just keep going and progressive just do beat it and come back and do the other stuff you didn't
do what happened i have a feeling i'm why am i so scared of this thing i have a feeling i'm
going to kill it prime example coming up right here like i could probably just let this guy
hit me over and over again i could just probably spam r1 so like for instance that was that was
incredibly simple that was very easy right if i had come here 45 levels ago that might have been
like oh shit this is a this is a tough encounter i'm dodging i gotta watch out i just literally
slept through that um so that's what i mean by that i'm coming back and doing all this other
content that i didn't do yeah you know i don't have to be doing this right but when you have
such a huge world and um you level up a lot you're going to be way stronger than content you didn't
get to see that's the fun of it though you can come back and just wipe the floor with everything
no no it is it really is but sometimes you can feel like a few days ago maybe like a week ago
when i was streaming this i did an area that i had maybe was a week or two ago i did an area
that it was clearly like i was just wiping the fucking floor with everything it was not even
a challenge i was just walking through the area and just like hitting r1 and killing everything
um and that was like all right that's kind of cool it makes me want it makes me want to like
make a new character and just go do that and just turn around and go the other direction
like if i kill something in one hit and like i get surrounded by five enemies and i just go
like this all five of them die i'm just like all right i'm gonna come back here in another
character and i'm gonna see this content and i'm gonna see it well sometimes you want to
break from getting your head kicked in yeah no it is it's true and that's not even a complaint
that's just kind of i've seen a lot of people say that they're way under leveled for certain
places and way over leveled for certain places and when a game doesn't really tell you what to do
you can end up in scenarios where you're in one area when you're not supposed to be
way lower and then the next area you go to you're way higher um i've seen that happen a few times
that's unavoidable yeah oh yeah because there's no the game doesn't tell you where to go
but that's part of the reason why the game is so fun because you know the game's not like oh you
see that over there go there next by the way you this is all walled off you can't do anything
else why is the character such a fat ass because i have big armor on how many more of these things
exist stores hp upon defeating enemies it's good for like leveling better than auto scale yeah
scaling enemies is always a thing no i don't like that either i think they did a pretty good job
here i really do but it is a problem like this problem's for eat both things that's cool okay
i destroyed a lot of oblivion's fun yeah enemies that scale just kind of like you never feel like
you're making any real progress because you're just doing the exact same what was the point of
leveling up what's the point of having like a level system right there's no there's actually
no reason for it you just you're doing the same thing you're getting hurt and you're doing the
same amount of damage the whole game so it's actually really difficult to do a game that does
not scale that has this much content to do this is not this is an absurd amount of shit to do
so i feel like it's been pretty good so far and we're at the end of the game so you know all right
i got all the runes or at least the ones that i have in my inventory so before i turn off the
stream i think i want to see what's going on in this see this i want to know more guidance would
be better um if i'm honest um maybe but when you open the doors to limb grave for the first time
and you know when that i remember i think on stream i even said it i was sitting there going
holy shit when you understand that there you just are just go do something it's not a bunch of
indicators on the screen there's not a bunch of things telling you where to go it it hits a lot
different you get to experience it however you want and you know that the game has been crafted
to make sure that there's experiences in every single direction the grace light yeah but i mean
the grace light tip i'll be honest this is it's not this doesn't really tell you fucking anything
like there were times where i would go here like especially like i like oh uh where do i want to go
i guess down down where like there's something here did you want to show me this did you want
to show me that was it this that you were pointing to was it this it's not a great indicator or oh
my god don't fall off but yeah if you walk in that direction you will find something to do
just pick my fucking boogies out of my goddamn disgusting ass nose
at least i don't have to lose anything long-winded rant you asked what do i think of the game
i really it's been like a month i've been playing this game on stream for almost a full month over
a month i i do think it's probably one of the best games ever played without a doubt i have
some issues with it obviously you've heard the complaints but it is definitely one of the best
games to come out in the last 10 years at least at least gorge of the giants if we didn't have
gravestones it'd be a 10 out of 10 can i survive this no i gotta go like here
so what am i supposed to do with this thing so i'll walk around so this is interesting this is a
gigantic giant furnace what is why is this here it's also really cool because the game tricks you
a lot into pretending that it's way smaller than it is opening up the map in the first like 10
hours of the game and you only get this much to look at and even if you try to zoom out you're
stuck like here it's it's insane your brain cannot comprehend that was crazy every time a new fog of
war kind of was added to at the top left at the top right or whatever when i first opened up the
limb grid map i was like all right this doesn't really seem that big but i guess there's probably
a lot of content here right did not understand how big it was that was one of the coolest parts of
the game so far because they're kind of teasing how big their game actually was and of course
they're gonna flex let them they're like oh you think it's that big no take a look let them flex
let them i talk at this yeah i can talk okay here we go what are we doing i have long observed the
lands between this world is in dire need of repair and death indiscriminate are you prepared
to commit a cardinal sin i'd like you to wait i would like for you to wait that's that's like a
old are you better listen here uh now you better listen here you i'd like you to wait hey hold hey
hold on here now hey hold up here buster did we do it just do it very well let my hand rest upon
you for but a moment hey she fucking sapped us did she take all of our power we just gave her
like he touched me and she got like fucking old man hands you shall burn this is kind of sad
for the sake of the new lord i don't want to burn the tree he's just doing like the stuntman thing
like the the toddler walk thank you for guiding me here alongside flame shall one day meet the road
of destined death goodbye i'm gonna be so level one again it's like prestiging and fucking
call of duty i thought we just burned the place what happened what did you do what did you do
she summoned a goddamn tempest i don't want to go over there oh that's okay is that other is there
rumbling pharaoh azula you did this i didn't do this actually i just wanted to burn down the tree
i didn't want to summon fucking cyclone are those all those are all dragons oh a good thing
these are spinning strong i kind of want a race so i can um not fucking i'm i don't know if i want
to do this right now this area is so bad whatever you've said that every time i've gone to a new
place okay once an hour just baud watchers uh it's the worst area of any rub software again
okay yeah i do this is the worst area they've ever made i don't know why i thought i was gonna
see patches oh friend you made it how are you oh i see that yeah the cyclone's really spinning
really fast isn't it you did this didn't you you are such a bastard i'm like expecting that to
happen i really am that's crazy what do i go sitting yeah he's gonna be sitting there oh i
still selling things if you want to buy something still have fire arrows like bro if i jump into
this what happens i can't go this is like a secret mario 64 thing he's gonna go get killed i'm not
gonna get killed by the way wherever he is where he is in fucking hell he he was just like reading
newspaper on the toilet and he smashed into the ground in hell speaking just get this off what
i don't need that's kind of cool but whatever is this a speed run where okay where where am i
what is this i don't understand what's going what i'm looking at so this is all the way over here
it's a crumbling place yes it's gonna be some big reveal it's gonna be this like it's gonna be a big
reveal power was coming all along from the tempest and it's gotten out of control since you've burnt
the urd tree it was once normal it was once a fine it was a regular cyclone that gave us power
the tree connected to it but when you burnt the urd tree this is the urd tree's brain up here and
went fucking crazy i don't want to get too close to this thing one of these dragons is gonna come
down what is in here fossils i knew i knew a dragon was coming down here i just told you
shit dude serpent let's go he's so cute i love him i don't think i can fucking fight this
are you can you be frosted actually kind of yeah frost is good oh fuck don't land on me please
what's up how long you gonna stay in the air for he was up there for so long he's hovered
there for like five seconds things not worth killing let me try he that's an awesome looking
dragon though let's go i gotta get you in plus 10 i love him he's just going in no fear is that
gonna hit me oh that was actually a lot no it wasn't i was terrible seven thousand damage from
what i can't see anything where shit get out of here with this nonsense
ancient dragon spitting stone it was worth it nice job i need a name for the serpent
geico gecko did somebody say the geico gecko i did i read that wrong i might have but that's
like funny but it kind of looks like him a little lizard larry this is larry's no i'm not it's not
gonna be lizard larry no not gex you have something dance related like the salsa or something like
salsa but these are big the graves they got like jewels and stuff in them the smithing stone
mambo newt i'm not gonna name the snake newt gingrich so no no mambo i don't i don't i like
mambo see you yeah i like mambo lightning great bolt all right this shit down here this is an
elevator um should we take the elevator i don't know oh ancient dragon prayer book
oh that's the wrong question hey we're good i'm not in bed yet i want to know what happens
even if i can't beat a boss or something i just want to know i want to know what the
fuck is this place what am i doing here what what is that what is that up there that's the
first i've seen it there's a huge gold tree that's the first i've seen that i want to know what that
is i'm not gonna go investigate what the huge golden tree is that's the urge tree
imagine if you didn't know what the urn tree was at this point you just don't have no idea
that that was there you've what have you played the game like this the entire game just like
you've never once looked above like 30 degrees i need to go back and heal i should somebody said
go back into the halley tree all right let me am i gonna lock myself out of the whole game if i
keep going here then we're fine then everyone relax we're good damn pretty sick i'll go down
there in a second let's see if there's a bonfire where are they i know i have some go back to the
round table oh that's a good point yeah i will herbal bloom we eat none of those things
way too late it's all right it's all right i know but i just want to
i just want to play i want to play i want to play and i don't want to go to bed i'm not going to
bed i probably need to eat though it will stop soon not immediately but very soon oops these guys
are weird we had any oat milk today huge problem yeah why what where'd you even come from see you
later punk what crazy bastard is milking oats it's you squish them and they turn into somebody near
me is there anything that heals me or anything yeah stop what do you mean stop what are the grace
where i don't know where it is i know i'm it's how close am i in my clothes stop stop stop what
it's i don't know it's so far away go back up the elevator why can i teleport is that poison
well is that all i can do here i guess so you need to get you need to rest at a grace
there's no grace down here it's gonna die of poison i will not die of the poison
oh shit dog okay grace why why not there was another way i could go that way i guess i could
check it out time is it i gotta i gotta go yeah all right i gotta i gotta go i gotta go
let me go talk to the people at the round table though i gotta go it's late it's way too late i
will see you guys on tuesday in love we're gonna play stuff i'm gonna see what the round table hold
has to say about this oh very nice rovers bro it is it is a bro versus bro who lives here imagine
just having your desk over there just hanging out how are you how do you live here this is like
being next to the train tracks and a train is just always driving down the tracks always it never
stops uh we're gonna do 4 p.m on no oh god i have no idea i gotta talk to the lovely keep an eye on
sus tuesday probably afternoonish i gotta i gotta figure out i gotta talk to lovely keep an eye on
sus for the next couple days oh shit this is something new going on here wait the fingers
you don't want to talk still you still stuck
why are you still gone
don't you think that if the urd tree was burning do what you believe is that this this dude would
come back oh why are you still gone what's wrong with you what are you doing take a look around
table holders burned raised to the ground is this in the urd tree i don't blame you spirit tuning
just the same as before which is why i need your help persuading master hugh to leave i did this
his roots are so knotted in this place he was much longer if he stays here his shackles have
broken he's a free man now it's high time you put the round table behind him
oh you great great glove wart god damn it before you leave i knew you'd be back out your arms
why are you still doing this weren't you listening as i've always said
are you going to challenge the demigods and their god to slay them and as long as you do i will
always smith your weapons it is what i wish to smith a weapon for you to slay a god
all right roger the letter letter written in a trembling hand i forgot to tell you but it seems
d has a younger brother i heard he lies in a deep sleep in the aqueduct beside the eternal city of
nocron and said he stood before the prince of death not far beyond that spot roger there are
trees on fire um sorry i couldn't he's been dead for weeks have i just knocked on out
there and turned right he's been sitting there just rotting for a month he helped us he gave
us his thing all right dude i did it you burn table is soon to all serve to be needed to burn
for that i'll stay at the round table for a time i must learn all that can be taken from this place
and seal it into my memory how could i call myself the all knowing if i did any less
the pursuit of knowledge is without end for knowledge is never a thing complete
thus i maintain the mantle of all knowing you know everything perhaps the same could be said
of guidance it is to say whether we'll remain who we are once the fight is finished what do you think
as one of the spires to become elden lord
okay can i walk into the urn tree now no don't no no no
you're here for some spirit tuning so master hugue won't listen to you either you have my
thanks regardless i'll try and talk him around next time i know he was given this great entreaty
to craft a weapon which could slay of god but think of it as a curse a fearsome curse
that's the case i'm not sure there's anything we can do
i got some bells though when i hand them in the dung eater just still hanging out
okay rogers bell bearing we got smithing miners bell bearing two got somber miners bell bearing
four all right wow you really can do this great okay i need some great brave glove warts
uh it looks like we're gonna have to go another day pretty cool we're gonna have to do this
another time there's still some stuff left to do before what i imagine is i can walk into the urn
tree now we're not going to immediately do that
they have your arms i upset the girl she says that now my chains are broken i'm free
and if i stay here i will be ruined with the round table you survive for freedom now
i smith weapons to slay of god i have lived and will die doing so upon this spot is there any other
way well dude i've got some really good news for you i'm at plus 10 plus 10 man
use it take a vacation go i'm at plus 10 plus 10 on both weapons can't get any higher
you can leave i see that's it all right all right that's it that's it i see we'll pick back up wait
i just want to level up one more time 16 000
ah shit it's not gonna get there is it i can reload this to the grace oh okay yeah yeah yeah
still here okay okay all right that's it i see you guys later past time yeah we'll we'll we'll
do okay because we're at end game if i walk in here i'm assuming it's probably the end of the game
so i still have the halog tree i still have that i've got this area here and i i want to
i'm starting here by the way because i'm really interested in what the hell this is how big is
the map dude you have no idea you got plenty of content oh yeah rumble town halog tree end game
would be best yeah i'm most interested in this place here we did kind of half of the halog tree
there's still a lot more to do in here all right that was really fun did bog too we killed bog
all right goodbye good night take care of yourselves uh let's get the there were a
lot of community subs it was hundreds of community subs tonight thanks guys have a great night sorry
we went late again but this is kind of the way it is with a game like this i will see you guys on
tuesday for uh bro vs bro with uh ludwig after that i imagine that a day or two later we will
try to get somewhere closer to the end of the game i know that in one of these areas i don't
know exactly which one but i have i have an idea by what people were saying in the chat that i
still have one of the most unbearable encounters in the entire franchise history of from software's
all of your game library i still have that to look forward to so who knows that might be an
entire stream i don't know or i might go in there turn around just leave say fuck that take care
of yourselves it's always good to see you i'll see you guys real soon good night goodbye have
a great rest of your night there's not much left of it so good night