Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with chapter 2 of Sea of Her Meat Boy.
Gonna tackle the hospital.
Now welcome back if you just watched the first episode where I took on chapter 1, which proceeds chapter 2.
So here we go, the hospital.
A place that I don't like to go, cause that means you're hurt, or have some type of injury or illness.
Alright, where's my boy Commander Video? There he is.
All his glorious rainbows intact.
So I hope you're having a fantastic day.
I know Commander Video is cause he's gonna speedrun this whole level.
Woo!
Let's get A pluses on every level.
I forget these levels.
It's been a while.
Not long enough where I can't absolutely ace them though.
And that's how you do it right there folks.
No A plus, but that's okay.
Oh, I was also told to turn the music up a little bit, so I did.
Turn it up if you can hear it.
This is gonna be tough.
You might need Meat Boy for this one.
Maybe not.
Ooh, that's slick. Ooh, that is slick.
Slick. No, no!
I gotta stop trying to be like a slick Rick.
Just play the damn game.
Here we are.
It's all about moving fast. Just forget about everything, just go.
A plus.
And this is one of the things where you fly in the air.
Let's do it again.
Oh, I didn't hold down jump.
So that's the thing with Commander Video.
You gotta make sure.
In situations like this, you don't hold down jump for too long.
Stuff like that will happen.
Let's take this slow right now.
Ah!
This might be...I don't know if I can do this with Commander Video.
Don't!
But I wanna stay with Commander Video. I love him.
No, you know what? I can get this.
Ready? Here we go.
One, two, three.
Oh, you bastard! Last try, come on.
Ugh!
I'm gonna have to switch.
Sorry, Commander Video. I wanted to do the whole thing with you.
Do I give up that easily? I don't.
So let's try it again.
Let's try it again.
Alright, meat boy.
Didn't want to have to resort to using you, but I have to.
God, I'm so not used to him.
Let's clean this up.
Come on, just do it.
Oh, god!
Okay.
Alright, we're good.
That almost just not gonna work.
I'm gonna have to do this again with Super Meat Boy.
Because he moves faster.
I'm gonna have to...I don't know about this one.
Oh, Band-Aid.
Give me that Band-Aid!
I said...
Oh, here come the swears.
Forget the Band-Aid, let's go.
Alright, come on.
Oh, that's how you skip that whole part.
Alright, now I can probably switch to Commander Video and be okay with it.
The question is, do I want to skip this?
What's going on here?
Why am I losing this?
I didn't even jump and I made it over that.
Get out of my face!
Alright, going back to Commander Video.
Because he's my baby.
Oh, this might not even work.
I run into Fan over and over again.
I can't do this.
Oh, god.
Never mind.
Let's go.
Be careful here.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, man.
See, I gotta start paying attention.
I'm being like a real stupid bastard.
Land that, land this, and jump up.
There we go.
Just stay with me, boy. I'm having no luck here.
Ah!
Boop, boop.
I want to go back up that way.
No, I don't.
If I had Commander Video right here, I could float across this stupid thing.
Come on, you slug.
You know, I always say slug, but these really are slugs.
Didn't even realize that.
Oh, look, it's a slug, slug, slug.
Go, yes.
Just go.
You know, we're gonna do that again, but this time I'm just gonna go right off the bat.
Speed it up a little bit here, come on.
Speed it up.
That's what I like to see.
I can't go that fast, no.
No, I can.
God.
Oh, dear God.
Come on, no.
You gotta succeed on the first couple tries.
That's when you gotta really start to think about what you're doing.
Which is what I'm doing right now.
I forgot about this part.
You gotta jump up here.
Through there.
Over the slugs.
And that's the one. There she is.
She's the one for me.
Get out of the way, you giant slug.
Yeah.
Johnny's cage.
Give me the bandaid. How am I supposed to...
Oh, wow. Okay.
You know, this has got your name written all over it.
If I didn't...
Just hang out right here.
Oh, crap.
There we go. Got the bandaid.
Commander video, to the rescue.
Take the key, drop down, nice and easy.
And that's how you get a Thanksgiving turkey.
Oh, I'm too slow for this with commander video.
You can still try.
I can do it. I can do it.
Who am I kidding? I can do this.
Like that, and then you jump.
Float!
People want to see the deaths.
If I die a ton of times in a level, I will show the deaths.
Oh!
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go. Faster.
Go!
Oh, I didn't get the key.
I tried to get that key, that was fine.
I didn't get it. Dammit.
Get out of the way.
A+.
Oh, what just happened?
Okay.
I'll accept it, I guess.
Up with this one.
And then float, and then yeah.
Get the key.
Get the second key. Oh, you know what?
Screw the second. I'm in a lot of trouble here.
I'm gonna have to try and make my way over this.
Commander video.
Supposed to be my go-to guy. Let's try this again.
Up, slow, and then up.
Okay.
Don't screw this up. Straight in the air.
Get this guy out of the way. There it is.
And my queen.
I've come to you. Let's see some of those deaths.
I died like seven great times.
Or four.
Yeah, one, two, three, four.
There goes one, there goes the other, and it's down to these two.
Who's gonna win? Who's gonna pull ahead?
It's gonna be Sally, it's gonna be Jeffrey.
No, it's not gonna be either of them, because I'm skipping it.
And let's go.
Warp Zone. Warp Zone, give me.
Give me the Warp Zone. I forget which one this is.
Super Meat Boy.
This one.
Probably not gonna do this, I'm not gonna lie.
Actually, maybe I will.
Maybe not. Went too fast.
Up. Now take your time with this.
Don't have to freak out here.
Unlock her cage.
Go visit her family for Thanksgiving dinner.
Like you promised. Like that.
Oh, oh, oh fuck!
You know, I had that. You all know I had that.
I'm gonna do it again.
You know, okay, I can't screw this up.
I cannot mess this up.
If you're gonna go fast, you gotta slow down up here.
Like that.
I almost just jumped over the damn thing.
And I would've freaked out.
Simple enough. Simple enough.
Simple enough. Oh my god!
Sorry, Meat Boy.
But the green stick figure told you
that she's in another castle, which means she's there.
Floaty. Floaty McFloat.
Get out of... Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Whoa. Commander video.
Ugh. I'm trying to like sing to this beat.
Hold on, I'll do it.
Oh, come on. I gotta think some lyrics.
Commander video
is the best character in the game.
He's gonna beat the whole thing.
Then he's gonna have some cake.
Commander video
just land on her head. Please don't squash her.
She's the one you're looking for
in another castle.
Oh, I didn't even mean to jump over that.
I love the noise he makes when he lands on things.
Bunk. Bunk. Bunk. Bunk. Bunk. Bunk. Bunk.
Hey, yo. Blee.
Coolest part about him is I will definitely make this
because I can just do this. Ha ha ha.
Almost didn't make that. Getting close here.
Getting close. Oh boy.
Might need Meat Boy for this.
No! Go.
No, just hide in the stupid thing.
Oh my god. I am so dumb.
Oh my god.
What is the matter with me?
I'm losing my mind.
I'm starting to lose my mind.
No.
Oh my god. It's begun.
The freak out period is about to begin.
Okay.
I have to slow down here. Meat Boy.
Let's go.
No. I'm not going yet.
That's what I should have done in the very beginning.
There we go. Finally.
Don't die here. You'll never make it back.
I'm going to stick with Meat Boy for this one.
Oh, that is so loud in my head right now.
It hurts.
I'll be waiting.
Six feet.
Whoa.
Get out of my way. I'll take that key.
Open the door of
victory.
No. I'm not.
Just wait. Just wait.
Slow this down and I got this in the bag.
No.
Just wait.
I don't have to be too speedy.
It's all about just getting there.
And we got it.
Day breakup.
Jump.
That was close.
Was I going to just get out
of the way?
And this is a...
You know, I'm going to go down here.
Drop down. Jump up.
God. I'm so mad at that.
I can't believe I messed that up.
It was just...
Oh, my God.
This is the last level before the boss.
I know that. At least I think it is.
Maybe I'm wrong. I've been wrong before.
Get out of the way.
Jump up.
Around and down.
Now we got it.
No, not so fast.
No, no, no.
It's all right. We're good.
Oh, my God.
I got to stop doing that.
Okay, just jump.
Well, you just do it the way you're supposed to.
No, like, stupid tricks.
Let's see. Look at all these fools.
Oh, it's down to the two.
It's down to these two. Who's going to make it?
I go? I fall down?
Oh, don't worry. I'll come back.
Look, I'm right here with you again.
Oh, I'm so glad. Yes, we're friends forever.
We're both going to share the girl. We both love her forever.
Oh, that's so nice of you.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, and there he's gone. Oh, he's not.
When did I die with that guy?
Oh, right there.
And he makes it.
Time to close up chapter two.
Going against Chad.
Chad, if those of you do not know,
Chad is actually
in, well, he's actually the name of another
boss in Binding of Isaac.
Not, I guess, yeah, he is.
Press that button, I dare you.
I think it's a different look, though.
I totally forget if it's the same Chad.
I think it is.
Here he comes.
Yeah, he's in Binding of Isaac.
And the whole point of this is you're supposed to
outrun him and die
from the very beginning.
I can't even, like, talk. I'm just so, this music
in my ear is just making me so scared.
Alright, let's just wait for him.
Wait for him, wait for him. Okay, now I'll go.
Can I get out of, like, the first part of the boss, please?
Don't want him to hit me.
So just stay above everything.
That's electric, that's electricity.
Where's the, oh, the key's down there?
I forgot about this. Oh, it's over.
I can't even get over there.
Just kill me.
Alright, so it's on the right, it's on the right.
Both at times, it's on the right. I got you.
Let's move. Can't even go over there.
I just tried to jump over there, my god!
Alright, Chad, got about enough of this.
Oh my god!
Why am I so bad?
Okay, let's do it.
I, what?
What? How am I, how
How do I get up there?
I forget, like, what you do in this, in this part.
Um, hold on.
No, there's a way to drop down right here. I'm an idiot.
How do you do it?
Don't worry, I got it.
Don't worry, guys, I got this.
I got this taken care of, don't worry.
Super Meat Boy's in the house.
He's got this taken care of out of control here.
Oh my
god!
I'm starting to really get annoyed.
Let's see, I wonder how many die at times I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna guess, like, 30.
Because after this, there's some more stuff to do.
It's all about just dodging.
No!
I'm gonna land on him!
Yeah, go ahead, do your dumb thing.
Oh my god!
He keeps, I hate when he
Just do your
stupid thing, you big, fat,
ugly bastard. Get out of my way.
I'm gonna punch you in the, I can't even go up now.
Oh, you
You ripe, red tomato.
Okay.
This time, I'm not gonna just
jump down there, because he's gonna be there.
See? Told you. And I didn't even get the key.
Good thing I didn't, because there he is.
Oh!
I wish I could use command video,
but I can't!
Okay, if I don't do this this time,
I'm gonna put a hole through my
computer monitor. Take it easy.
Oh my
god! Oh my
god, I can't believe I did that.
I cannot believe, I'm
not even like halfway through this.
Son of a
See, once you start getting mad, that's when
things start to go downhill.
Collected, gotta get collected here.
You know, the screen is shaking too, that's why
it causes more problems.
Get me! Get me! Get the
Ugh!
Oh my
god. I wonder how many
times I've said oh my god, or oh my word.
Here we go again.
Alright, I'm in an okay spot
right here. Alright, we're done. We're done.
I just gotta get this key. If I, just get the
damn key, and just get it!
Just get the key! No!
Get out of my face! Get the key.
Get the other key. Don't even
worry about it. Just, just, it's okay.
It's okay. Get the
Oh my god, I did it! Oh!
Oh my god.
Whew!
That was the ragiest I've
been so far, and it's only gonna get worse.
So thank you guys so much for watching.
Chapter two. Chapter three
will be next coming Monday.
Every Monday is Super Meat Boy Monday!
Meat Boy Mondays! He still has my
girlfriend though. What's that?
Oh, it's little Chad! Hi!
Uh, hold on, let me look over
here for a second. We're going to go off!
No, I gotta, what are you doing, man?
I just, I wanna give you a kiss.
Uh, okay. Can you just like
back up for a second? Get out of here.
Oh, you killed me!
Dude, I'm wicked sorry.
Are you alright? No, I'm not alright.
Oh my god.
Whatever. Where is he?
Still over there? Oh, you threw my girlfriend!
Off with me! I'll get
that bastard! Let's go!
Chad? I still want that kiss,
please!
Okay, time to get out of here. This is
getting a little weird. I'm gonna have to just
put him out of his misery, and I just
why did I do that?
I just, like, voice acted that whole thing
as if it was actually, whatever.
So yeah, take care everybody. Thanks for
watching, I'll see you all on Chapter 3.
See you later, guys.