Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the soldier with the black box, the buff banner, and the escape plan.
This was actually going to be a one-life gameplay, but after watching it back, it was only like three and a half minutes, so instead of uploading like a three-minute video where I wouldn't even be able to talk about what I wanted to talk about, I just kept in most of the round.
I cut up a little things near the end. But anyways, we're gonna talk about something that I get PMs on a lot. Ever since I did my exercise video, I've had people ask me, Jerma, can we get some more details on your exercise life, on your nutrition life?
How should I be eating? How should I be exercising? I don't know how to... Where do I start? Et cetera, et cetera. So what I'm gonna do in this video is I'm gonna give you sort of what my daily routine is when I wake up in the morning.
My little nutrition plan. It's not really a plan as much as it is a story about how I was a really picky eater and what I have found ways to combat being a picky eater and still eat very, very healthy.
So let's go back to when I was a little kid, when I was like ten years old or so, eight years old. That's when I can really remember being a little kid. I hated food. I didn't like eating food.
I was a little string bean, skinny as a rail kid, and I did not like to eat. Like if somebody put meat in front of me, I thought meat was disgusting. I wouldn't want to eat it. I didn't like vegetables.
The only thing I would really eat when I was a kid was Captain Crunch. Now that's true. I only ate Captain Crunch at dinner for like maybe four out of the five days of a week for dinner.
I ate breakfast. The thing is I liked eggs and bacon. I loved breakfast food. And to this day, breakfast food has become sort of a comfort food for me because of my previous childhood memories with it.
And you fast forward a little bit to when I was in high school. I lightened up a little bit to the fact of eating meat and getting more different food groups inside of my body.
But still, I was still reluctant to try things. I didn't like to eat fruits and vegetables. I didn't like to do that. And that's so important to do stuff like that, guys.
To have a balanced diet is one of the biggest things. It's one of the biggest hurdles that you're going to have if you want to get healthy, if you want to lose weight, if you want to put on some extra pounds and get healthy and get strong.
Having a balanced diet with fruits, vegetables, grains, oatmeal, you need to have all that stuff because that's what fuels your body.
And to get to the real purpose of this video, I'm going to give you guys a very small recipe, which I think is a foolproof way to eat healthy every single day.
Now, are you going to cure every disease with this particular little recipe? No, but it will get you fruits and vegetables in your body. Well, fruits, to be more precise, in your body.
So when you eat that double cheeseburger at six o'clock in the afternoon, you're not going to feel like an asshole. There you go. So it's very easy. Very, very easy. This is what you want to do.
All you have to do is go to the grocery store or whoever is buying your food for you. If you have parents, just ask them for these items. Very, very simple.
Number one, it is required that you have a blender. If you don't have a blender, go get one. They could be pretty expensive, but you need a pretty good blender for this to actually work.
I've had blenders in the past that I've tried to do this with and they sucked and it came out like completely horrible. So you need a pretty powerful blender for this to work.
But that's the only requirement. Once you have the blender, there is no excuse for you not to do this. What you want to do, go to the grocery store and pick up a bag of frozen strawberries.
You can get those at the frozen food aisle or it varies on the different grocery stores. But you want a bag of frozen strawberries. They're rock solid like ice cubes.
Throw those in a basket, head on over to the fresh fruit aisle and pick up a bunch of bananas. Doesn't matter if they're ripe or not.
They could be unripened, just whatever the cheapest freaking bananas you can find at that grocery store. Throw that in your bin as well.
Then you're going to move on over to the yogurt aisle. And this is really important. Do not get any of those chocolate lime pie key lime confetti cake yogurt.
No, you don't want any of that. Those are all loaded with bullshit. You don't want to eat any of those. Well, that's a pretty big overstatement.
That's still yogurt, but they're filled with all kinds of sugars, all kinds of additives. You don't want any of those. What you want to get is just general, 100% pure, just Greek yogurt.
No flavorings added. Maybe you could get the vanilla kind because it's pretty easy to do that. But you just want the general yogurt with no BS in it.
Then you want to go over to the milk aisle. If you don't have milk at your house, just get a gallon of milk and that's it.
Bring all that stuff back to your house. Get it in the blender. Maybe a cup of strawberries, one banana, a little bit of yogurt, maybe like two or three tablespoons of yogurt and a dash of milk.
Blend the hell out of that stuff. And there you go. You drink that every single day. You are going to feel fantastic.
And it's a great way to incredibly easily fill your body with nutrients because you drink it. That's the thing. It comes out.
It could be a little thick depending on how many of the ingredients you put in, but I like it thick. You don't have to add any sugar either.
It's sweet enough with the banana. And because it's a liquid, you can actually drink this alongside of what you would typically eat for breakfast.
Let's say you have a bowl of Froot Loops for breakfast. You drink that alongside. Your brain is going to be like, holy, what's going on? Why am I so filled with energy?
Does anyone want to go rock climbing? Let's go rock climbing. I got homework. Anyone got homework to do?
You're not going to be on drugs. That's not what you're going to do. But it's a real foolproof way to get that stuff inside your body.
And for the longest time, I didn't do it. I thought, no, I don't want to get the blender out. It's too much time.
But it takes two seconds to rinse a blender in the sink. That's how you clean it up. That's it.
And I told myself for years that it was too hard. But my goodness, guys, it is the easiest goddamn thing in the entire world.
And I hope some of you start to do it. And even if you don't like bananas or you don't like strawberries, there are plenty of other little recipes like that that you can throw together on your own.
Like just make it up. Throw some apples in there, maybe some peaches, some pears. It really doesn't matter.
You could throw some spinach in there, too. Some broccoli. You can just go crazy.
Just go nuts trying to figure out what you think is the most tasty and most nutritious of all these different combinations.
And that's going to be my time, guys. Hopefully you guys got some information out of this video.
And I'll see you guys all next time. Pax East is coming up pretty soon. I got a video tomorrow.
Me and Orb are going to do a vlog for our final video before Pax. And I got plenty of videos scheduled to go up while I am not here.
So don't worry. There's going to be plenty of content on this channel still. And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.