Hello. Hello. How are you? That's good. That's good. Good. I'm good.
709. You're late. It's 409, actually, in my part of the world. Also, I- you guys didn't turn your
clocks back? The second- we have a few daylight savings times. You have to go back- you fall
back 10 minutes. You guys didn't do that? Don't be- I- you didn't do that? I didn't? What are
you talking about? Yeah, it's fall back. No, that's not- sorry, it's- it's uh- it's simmer down.
Summer, like simmer down, right? By 10 minutes. Summer down. Yeah, the summer simmer down.
That's not funny. You need to be funny. I got a whole book of jokes, okay? The joke- I have a
joke book. No, you're not gonna find every- all right, you're not gonna find every single thing
I say funny. If you did, if you- okay, if you thought every single thing I said was funny,
I would feel like you would just blow and smoke up my ass. You know what I mean? You're not gonna
think everything I say is funny. Otherwise, you'd- you might just be blowing smoke up my ass.
I have to tell you guys something. Um, I had an insane dream. Wild. This- this was wild. It was an
entire television show. It was a whole movie. It was fucked up. I- I'll tell- I'm gonna tell the
whole thing- I gotta try to remember it, though, because the thing about dreams is it- I wrote
the whole thing down. It's about, I don't know, I said like a full page long. And this one- I- you
guys are gonna think this one's funny because it has a really- it has a really interesting ending.
I will be- I'm gonna give you a warning here. It's disgusting. It's gross. It's really gross.
But I'm- I'll tell- I want to wait till more people- do I want to wait till more people are here to-
so more people hear this? Or do I want less people to hear this? So it doesn't- you know,
people don't think I'm weird. You know what I mean? Should I wait for more people or less people?
But then I feel like- I'll tell it in a second. Let me explain what we're doing. Let me give you
the kind of lowdown of what's going on today. We're gonna play a game today called Later Alligator.
Excuse me, Later Alligator. This is a kind of a puzzle slash point and click adventure game
with really cute interesting characters, I guess. It seems like- I mean, people have been requesting
this for a while. It's been requested for like a year. It's supposed to be really fun, just like
a chill game. We're gonna play it. If I get kind of over it and I'm done with it, I'm gonna play
a game called Webbed. We're probably still gonna play Webbed. Webbed is apparently really fun.
It's time for you to do a lot of voices. I think- isn't the- it seems like it's voice acted.
Is the whole game voice acted? I thought so. What is better, alligator or crocodile? It's
a different animal. Stop doing that. Stop doing that. Ow, my hand. Look what happened.
I just hit my desk hard. What the fuck? We're gonna have 15 different Bernie Sanders voices today.
I don't know, are we? Is somebody gonna talk like this? Is there gonna be another character that
talks like this? Yeah, probably will be a few. Do you want a barf drink or statue?
No, but I mean maybe. That sounds like kind of cool, maybe. Do you want one of those?
Do you like axolotls? Yeah, they're really cute. Please explain the birds and the bees. I'm really
confused by it. They're two animals. One of them's an insect. The other one's a bird that flies around.
The bees are literally gonna- that's how humanity ends, okay? The bees- you want to look into the
bees? Have we have issues here with the bees? That's how humanity ends. There's your birds
and the bees. Once the bees are gone, we're all dead. Don't you get it? When the bees are gone,
we are all dead. Wise words. Save the bees. What about the mosquitoes? Fuck the mosquitoes.
Insect-tier list. Okay, do you guys want to hear a tidbit of information here?
Uh, mosquitoes are all the way below F-tier. They're the worst insect.
Mosquitoes were part of the reason why I moved to Nevada. I was like, what's a part of the world
where I will never see one of those motherfucking mosquitoes ever again? Ever. I don't even- I
don't want to see them ever again. Nevada is one of those places where there just are no mosquitoes.
They do not exist. I would rather get stung in the mouth by a scorpion than be outside,
ever again, at like 6 30 p.m. in Massachusetts and look up and see the swarm of these bugs that just
want to suck all your blood out. That's kind of extreme. It is. I hate mosquitoes. Having to be
out there and to- look, look, let me show you. When you are outside and there's a place where
there's a lot of mosquitoes but a really humid place. Does this remind you? Does this- are you
aware of this scenario? Yeah, so how's school? Yeah, no, it's cool. I think one of the big
problems I think with the school system- you just graduated? Yeah. Yep. I don't like doing that. I
don't like fucking doing that. I'm so glad I never have to do that again. And everybody is doing it.
Everybody in like the group of people outside are all doing it. It's not abnormal to see somebody
just freak out and like reach elastic style around their back and be like, yeah, what time do you
guys want to go? If we want to get coffee, we probably should go at like six, maybe, maybe,
maybe seven. It's like this is normal. I don't- I hate it. You're a hater. Yeah, I am a- I'm a
mosquito hater. That was based. Okay, take a look at this. Ah, this is later alligator.
Do I talk about my dream now? Okay, this dream is fucking crazy. All right, let's- let me start.
Hold on. So I had a dream. I would tell you right now this is disgusting. This is a very gross
thing that happened. Your sideburns aren't even. I need a haircut. Sometimes when I shave,
I don't- I like- I fuck it up, all right? All right, this is actually a lot. That's really bad
now that I look at it. That's like- that's pretty awful. It's like so full. I don't- but listen,
I think it's- I think it's because I like went to- my hair has a weird growing pattern.
Is it that bad? All right, it is bad. But listen, my hair is a lot thinner here than it- look at
how much thicker my hair is here. You see? It's really- I have really thick hair here and really
thin hair here. I didn't shave this. Look, see? It's- see how it's better now? Because like this
kind of- it thins out. You're reusing the sideburns bit. No, I just don't care when I shave.
I- when I go and get my haircut, they get it to where it needs to be. I just don't care. I
shave my face and I go, whatever, that's close enough. Whatever, that's close enough. I just
don't care. I don't care. Like this is fine, right? When I go get a haircut, they take care of that.
I don't care. I do the same thing. I can't be bothered. See? Some of you get it. I know you do.
Okay, so listen. It sticks out. It's because I haven't had a haircut. They go
and they get rid of it. This is not worst hair. Stop that worst hair. I didn't do anything.
What the fuck are you talking about? My hair looks fine. My hair looks like good. Look at this. It's
like smooth. It's silky. It's been conditioned. Just because I have sideburn hair does not make
it worst hair. I'm not even putting it on a- I'm not even making it a category this year. Good luck.
It looks greasy. It's- what do you mean greasy? It's- look at that. Could greasy hair do this?
Nope. It's not- how is it worst hair? You guys are fucked. Whatever. So I had this dream. I had a
dream where I was- hold on. So I had this dream. This dream is crazy. I want to- I have to warn
everybody here, seriously. I'm going to probably, like, this is going to gross people out. I had
this dream. Why is my mic peaking? It's not. Fix your settings. Fix your settings. There's nothing
wrong with my mic. Okay. So there's enough people here. Whatever. Is stalling? This is- what do you
mean stalling? You just did stun locks. Fine. Okay. So here- listen to me. This is really important.
I had this dream where me and Holly were on a road trip. This is like two different dreams that were
connected for no reason. So me and Holly were on a road trip. We were, like, driving somewhere.
And, you know, in dreams, stuff just gets kind of stitched together and you don't really know why.
Holly and I- fix your settings! I don't care. So Holly and I, we went on a road trip and we stopped
at, like, a gas station slash, um, a gas station slash- I can hear her laughing already. I already
told her this, by the way. And she was disgusted, by the way. She was like, this is- this story is
fucking disgusting. Like, I- she- I- she's heard the story already. So anyways, uh, we go to gas
station and we pull in and it's a car wash slash gas station. Okay, cool. So the idea was, okay,
we're gonna get out and, like, and they're gonna wash the car and whatever. I don't know why we
decided to go get a car wash, um, in the middle of a road trip to some friend's house or something.
So we get out of the car and it's like, okay, take the car. Sure, whatever. Go ahead, go for it.
Take it and wash it. And one of the workers- this guy had, like, a clipboard here. And I, like, went
to go do something and Holly was, like, in the- kind of in the business or whatever. And this guy- I
don't know if he was, like, going to attack Holly. Like, I don't know why the employee was doing this.
Like, I come back out- I think it was, like, maybe I was outside for some reason. I come back in the
establishment and this guy's, like, going to, like, attack Holly. So I, like, got in the way
and I, like, fucking pushed the guy and he pushed me back and I, like, shoved him with the clipboard
and this clipboard, like, hit him in the face and I started fighting this fucking guy. I was, like,
fucking punching him in the face and we were fighting, just fighting each other. And the whole
time we're- this car is at the car wash, right? So, okay, what- the car is, like, at the car wash.
Splash! We're gone. We're not in the car wash anymore. We're outside the car wash.
I don't know how it's stitched together. And we're looking for the car. And the whole time,
like, Holly and I are like, that guy was- what the fuck was that guy's problem? That guy was a piece
of shit. Yeah, I, like, kicked his ass. Like, I fucking beat him up. Whatever, right? So I
kicked this guy's ass. And we're looking around for the car. We can't find it. We don't know where it
is. Um, eventually we come to the termination after walking around the parking lot four or
five different times. The car is gone. The car's gone. Somebody stole the car, okay? Somebody
stole the car. It's just not there anymore. So we had to start walking to my friend's house,
whatever it was, we started walking. Who's Holly? Holly's my girlfriend. So we- we had to walk. As
we're walking down the sidewalk, whatever, some guy in, like, a trench coat and these, like, big,
like, sunglasses. He was wearing these huge sunglasses. Comes up to us. He's, like, walking
kind of next to us and we're like, what the fuck is going on? And this guy walks up to us and he
goes, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, spray me in the face with this. And he hands Holly this, like, aerosol
can to spray him in the face. So we're just like, I don't- I- oh, I mean, you're gonna leave us alone?
Just leave us alone. So the guy- the guy's sitting there just waiting for Holly to spray him in the
face. So she holds the nozzle up like this and is, like, pointing at him and she goes
and sprays herself. It was- the guy was- it was a prank. The guy turned the nozzle the other way
and she maced herself in the face and she's, like, and I'm, like, what the fuck just happened?
What the fuck? And the guy starts laughing. So I start fighting the guy. I, like, start- I'm,
like, fucking- I fight this guy. I start punching this guy. I'm fighting this guy.
Like, I used to fight another person. I'm fighting another guy. Holly's over, like,
on the sidewalk with, like, these, like, welling up in her eyes. Like, I was like, I don't know
what the fuck it was. So I'm fighting this guy and we get to a point where, like, we're wrestling
around, like, fighting each other and there was a side- like, a drop down. We were on, like,
a sidewalk and there was a lip and then another sidewalk. Maybe, like, I don't know, maybe five
feet, six feet lower. This guy jumps down to, like, get down to the other sidewalk and I'm looking
down at him. He's only, like, remember, he's only, like, five or six feet below me and I'm, like,
I'm gonna- fuck this. I know what to do. So I, like, falling R1 the guy. Like, that was gonna work
in real life. So I, like, fall and, like, punch and I, like, punch him in the head and, like,
I fucking get him. Like, I knock this dude out. Two of his friends are, like, coming over and I'm,
like, oh shit, this is bad. This is really bad and they're, like, oh yeah, fuck him. He's a fucking
asshole, man. I'm just, like, what? Like, all right. Flash again. This is where it gets weird. This is
where it gets really weird and I'm gonna warn everybody. This is where it gets gross. We are
at our destination, right, after that happened. We get to the destination. We're at my friend's house
and I really have to go to the bathroom. Like, I could have been at that. Remember, this is a
gross story. Number two. So the bathroom is, like, I remember, like, this is stitched together in such
a weird way. I don't know how it's stitched together. So we get there. I go to their bathroom
and their bathroom is a bedroom. It's like a bedroom. There's a toilet that's, like, five feet
tall. The bowl is, like, up here and it's, like, a bunch of porcelain going all the way down,
okay? So, all right, it's, like, this is, like, this is, why is your bathroom a fucking bedroom?
There's, like, a shelving thing over here. There's, like, a bed over there, too, and it's just,
like, weird, like, why is it like this? So, again, this is gross. So I get, like, up on this huge,
like, high, it's, like, it was, like, a gigantic, like, high chair. It was, like, a big high,
that's all the way I can describe it. It was huge. Like, it was really high off the ground for no
reason. So I get over there, dude, I, this is gross. I take a huge shit, right? I take a
massive shit in this toilet and I'm done. Okay, that's it. I'm done. It's time now. It is time.
I told you this was going to be gross. I warned you, like, five times. So, like, I flushed the
toilet, whatever, and everything's fine, and I'm like, okay, it's time to, it's time to clean up,
right? So I look over at the material that you used to clean up, which is the toilet paper,
and there on this roll next to here was, like, right next to the toilet. The toilet paper roll
had this stain on it. It was a stain. You know what I mean? And I was just, like, I don't, uh-uh-uh,
I don't think so. So I kind of rolled it a little bit and the stain was there still,
a little bit faded, still there, a little bit faded, still. I'm like, I don't want to use this.
I'm not using this. So I'm like, what the fuck do I do now? Oh, I know. There, over on the shelf,
on the shelf in this bedroom bathroom was, like, of various sizes and shapes, different toilet paper
rolls. Like, some of them were kind of halfway undone. Some of them were wrapped up in, like,
the hotel wrapping. So I'm like, all right, the hotel wrapping over there. I, I, that's,
that's the one. It's a fresh one. It's brand new, right? It's wrapped in, like, that, that hotel
wrapping. So I go, I, I, I start to go up to go to where the toilet paper is. But remember,
I don't know why dreams are like this. Don't ask me why. Please don't ask me why. I don't,
I can't describe why this happens. I was in the water, up to here, like, like a fucking jacuzzi.
And I was, like, pushing up to get out of, like, the jacuzzi and, like, get, making it so my elbows
were, like, on the bowl and, like, getting up because that's how I had to get out. So I finally
get up, I'm soaking wet and I'm, like, out of the toilet and I go over to grab this, like, I'm like,
what the fuck am I gonna do? So I grab this, this wrapped toilet paper, fresh toilet paper roll.
Okay. I didn't fall in. I was apparently already in it. Dreams don't make any sense. I was
apparently already in this toilet and, like, up to here. Remember, this thing was, like, five feet
tall. So I, I get out, I unwrap the new toilet paper and there's a fucking huge stain on it.
It's a huge stain. Again, I was like, this doesn't make any sense. Something with the manufacturing
this shit. What happened? This doesn't make any sense. Why is it like this? I don't get it. What
the fuck? So I can't use this roll either. So I put that down. I, I go over the, again, there are
tons of, there's, like, five different rolls on a shelf over here and I grab one of them. That's,
like, kind of halfway done. But this toilet paper roll was, like, antique. It was falling apart in
my hands. Like, I would unroll it and it was, like, crumbling out, like, like, as if it was, like,
antique. I was like, I can't fucking use this either. What the hell is going on? So eventually,
eventually, I get to a roll that I have in my hand and I'm like, this looks pretty good.
There's nothing on it. There's no stains on it. It's not, like, weird crumbling in my hands,
antique bullshit. I start to, like, get it over to where, remember, I just crawled out of the toilet.
I get over to where the toilet is and, like, it's kind of, like, oddly heavy. So I, the toilet paper
roll kind of unrolls a little bit and then it unravels and hits the ground and starts rolling
on the ground. And there is rolled up in the toilet paper, like, 30 to 40 thousand fucking
dollars. It was where this person was, like, hiding money in their house. It was, like,
they were hiding money here, hiding it. I was like, oh my god, no, what the fuck? There was,
like, a hidden money spot in your house? What the fuck? So I try to, and then this is all this money.
There was, like, other, like, little antique shit in here, right? There was, like, little antiques
in it. There were, like, little trinkets, like, wrapped up in the money that was wrapped in the
toilet paper. So I start picking up these, like, this bundle of, like, just, like, it's rolled up
money. It was, like, rolled like this. And I don't know what to do with it because no matter what I
did, this was going to, I would never make it look the same way, right? Like, holy shit, man, this
was wrapped up so perfectly. It's going to be a mess. They're going to know that I did that,
right? They're going to know that something happened. So this is one. This dream is your
internal struggle with money and greed. Well, I'm not done. It gets worse. So eventually,
like, this unwrapped money, I, like, put it back on the shelf. It's all fucking crumpled up and
all fucked up looking. So there's no way I did, there's no way I didn't touch it, okay?
Finally, I get a piece of toilet paper, like, a roll that is fine and it works. I bring it over
and I realize that there's a gigantic window directly across from the fucking toilet,
like a huge bay window. And I was like, whoa, what the fuck? Somebody could have seen this.
What the, somebody could see me walking around like this. And like, who's, could anybody see,
why would you have a window like this? Why would you have a huge bay window here? What the fuck is
wrong with you? What are you, what's fucking wrong with you? So boom, I wake up. I wake up
and I'm lying in bed and I open my eyes and after this insane dream, I thought I shit my pants.
I thought there was shit in my, in my, like, asshole in my ass cheeks. So I'm sitting there
going, I shit my pants. Like, there's shit in my ass. So this is real life. Like, I'm lying there
in real life going like, yup, yeah, this, I, there's, I shit, there's shit here. I felt it.
I knew it. I was certain about it. So I get out of bed and I, like, waddle over, like, slowly.
This is the slowest I've ever gotten out of bed. And I walk over towards the bathroom and I go,
and I, like, go to get the toilet paper. And guess what? There ain't no toilet paper in there.
So, so I waddle across the fucking house, just like, god damn it, no, it can't be real.
And I waddle across the fucking house and I get, go to where the toilet paper is. And I get into,
I get into a private place and I, like, do what I need to do and I wipe my ass
and it's clean. There's nothing there. There's absolutely nothing there. It was fucking nothing
happened. And this probably, I probably, I probably, like, slowly walked around the house like I had
shit in my pants for, like, probably five minutes. Maybe, like, two, you know what, no, that's a lie.
Maybe, like, two or three minutes total. But still, that's, like, so long. And then I left and I was
like, well, that was fucking wild. And I had a wicked bad headache. I had a wicked bad headache
and I kind of still do. I don't know, man, like, I just have these dreams that just become so
fucking strange. And that was it. And I was like, oh, that was, like, ridiculous. And I wrote this
all down too. I remember, Holly was, like, out here, like, in her office working. And I was just,
like, it was, like, wicked early in the morning. Like, she was up working. And I was just, like,
I, like, walked kind of by her and I was like, hey, hi. Like, I probably looked wicked fucked up.
And she can literally attest to this. Like, this, this is real. I was, like, slowly walking by,
just like, hey, hey, yeah, I'm just, like, getting up. It was fucking wild. And I had to write this
whole thing down. I thought I should, I thought I should the bed. Because I thought, like, oh,
my God. Okay, I got to be careful because I don't, I, like, in my brain, I was going over every
single scenario, like, I hope don't come in, don't, do not come into the bedroom. Do not go in the
bedroom. Because, like, I may have shit the bed. Like, but how do you say that to somebody? Oh,
hey, um, hey, I just, like, woke up and I'm in, like, kind of a daze. But I may, I may have shit
the bed. Don't go in there. Somebody said TMI. I told you, I warned you over and over again.
This is a gross story. This is not, this didn't happen. This is not a real story. Let me be,
look, that didn't happen. This was in the dream. Oh, this music. This music should not have been
on this whole time. But I don't, okay, I don't know what it is about why our brains do this weird
shit to us. But when I woke up from that dream, I, I shit my pants. Like, I did. I felt it. You
know what I mean? Like, it was like, oh, no, no, no, this is bad. This really happened. I really
thought it happened. I actually really did. But why? Why does my brain want to do that? Why does
my brain feel like, oh, hey, by the way, I need to tell you something. Like, you really did that.
But like the first minute that you're up, I'm sitting there, I was lying on my back.
I'm lying on my back just going, oh, no, oh, no, this is not good. What do I do about this?
What am I supposed to do about this? It was like so much internal panic, like through that entire,
like I, I don't know, I fought like two or three people. I thought I shit my pants. You
just stopped doing DMT. I don't, I don't do anything. Anyways, we're going to play Later
Alligator. And the fact that I was in the toilet, why was I in the water? OK, I know that like the
people have like dream journals and people are like, oh, this is why you had that dream. I don't,
OK, if I told like somebody that was like a dream journal specialist or whatever that dream,
they probably would be like, you made that up. Like that's, that doesn't happen. I don't know
what the fuck is wrong with you. I have no idea what's wrong with you. This game is, OK, here we go.
Release the Armin Audition tape. That's what Holly just said. I'm not doing that. Not right now.
I'll do that before I like, I retire. And remember, this is important too. I know that like,
sure, me and Holly have a great relationship, right? And like, it's, it's very wonderful.
I like, it's a great relationship. It's fantastic. But like, it, I, I don't want to, I still like,
don't want to like fart like loud in front of her. So the prospect of, I may have shit the bed,
honey. It's like, whoa, you went from like, you are farting in front of your girlfriend to
you shit the bed. That's too hot. That's way too much. That's too fast. I'm gonna slow that down,
right? You're gonna slow way that, slow way down. What's an alligator? It's a dinosaur that made it
through the meteor, OK? Here we go. You guys ready? So this is Later Alligator. It's a puzzle game
and we're gonna have a great time playing. You and I. No company, please, thank you. OK? Latte
machine. Two earbuds? I thought about it. No, um, no ablo ingles, no ablo espanol, no ablos at all.
Not even one ablo. What's going on here? 48 puzzles! Do I have a knife? There's no voice acting? I
think there is. They said there's a voice volume indicator. Hey, I'm trying to lay low here, so
maybe can you move on, please? OK? OK? You got me. I'll come clean. Sorry for being so rude before.
I am just a little, well, I'm turning the cam off for this. I'm just a little on edge.
Normally I wouldn't tell anyone this, but you've got such soulful eyes that I can totally see the
eternity of. So I feel safe with you, stranger. You see, usually I love coming to John Johnny's
on my birthday like this. Staying in the hotel, floating in the pool, eating two bagels at the
Continental Breakfast, eating two soaps in the complimentary bath basket. Ooh. Why did I say
ooh? Ugh. I just burped. But this year I've got a problem. A real problem. A real, real, big,
problem. The thing is, I'm pretty sure the family is finally trying to rub me out for squealing.
I didn't mean to squeal, honest. I just see a pair of earnest eyes and the secrets just start
flowing out of my snoot. See? I'm doing it right now. Oh, cheese and crackers. What am I going to
do? I don't want to be rubbed out. Two Tantona even told me I have to meet him upstairs here at
H Sharp for the event. They think I don't know, but I heard him talking to Big Mama on the phone.
Well, family's going to come to really show me how it's done. What am I going to do? I don't want
to sleep with the fishes. I have shell physiology and I have my asthma accent when I get too
waterlogged. Wait a second. You're interested in me, right? You wanted to sit with me for
breakfast and everything. Do you think that you could help me? Since we're such great pals,
you could go out and talk to my family around Alligator, New York City. Find out information
about the event and report back to me. Yes, that's a great idea. Together, maybe we can collect
enough info to save me. You want to save me, right? Right? Great. I'll text you if I need
any help. How about you go there and start? Do you have a watch? Oh, you do? Great. I'll text a
little before 10 a.m. since it can take 15 minutes or so to get back here on the trolley. Make sure
you check your watch a bunch. If you happen to get stuck doing some weird game-like activities
while investigating, it could take time. I don't have because I'm going to have to, I'm going to
have to, I'm going to have a murder done on me. I'm okay. Think of the beach, Pat. Remember what
Dr. Duples knew to you. Anyways, thank you for helping me out like an alligator might be. I feel
like I'm just, I'm better just looking at your super kind invincible face. And be careful out
there. The last thing we need is two people sleeping with the fishes. We need to find a double bed in
this economy. See you later, friend. Stay safe. Ah, cam off. Hello, esteemed guest. If you're
looking to leave the restaurant, you'll have to use the exit arrow up in the corner of the screen.
We provide all our patrons with an exit arrow and complimentary pillow mint.
Feel free to use both outside of our fine establishment to exit and munch as you wish.
Just don't mix the two up since that arrow is vintage and known to contain harmful materials
such as lead paint, asbestos, and a combination of rat poisons and cilantro. Please feel free to
visit us again here at John Johnny's and have a Johnny of a day. What's up? Okay, that's his cute.
This is John Johnny's Cafe. New voice unlocked. Cilantro. Ew, cilantro tastes like soap! Shut up.
It is gross though. I love it. Hey, bub. Got a minute? Or perhaps three minutes? I ain't above
asking for five. I saw you walking out of John Johnny's over there and I said to myself,
Vicki, you gotta talk to that mysterious stranger. Vision and pinstripes, says. I ain't
trying to fluff you up or another, but you look like an alligator of exceptional taste. As well
as one who might like to dabble in high stakes games of chance and intrigue, if you feel me.
Oh, don't actually feel me. I got a skin condition. They call me slick for a reason. According to my
doc, it ain't going away unless I start using that topical cream at night. I gotta listen to
some jabroni with a smarty certificate, you know what I'm saying? All my spots on the street.
This is also where I got this skin condition and my impolite lower back tattoo. Whom? What about the
event? Oh, you know about the event? Ah, look. Well, here, bub, it's a real secret affair, you dig?
Ain't nobody supposed to be going and telling Pat about it. My lips are sealed just like they
seal when I wake up after a night of nose only breathing. Hey, who's Pat? You talking about Pat,
the alligator? Yeah, I know that dude pretty well. You see, yeah, he's my second cousin.
One time when we was kids, those guys got locked out of CCD after recess and missed juice and
cookie time. We only had one granola bar between us and good old Pat gave me the bigger half.
I'll always remember that. No, I ain't crying. I just spit in my own eyes as a display of my street
toughness. Name's Mickey, but everyone, you know, calls me the old king of the cops.
Well, that one guy did before he yelled at a fence to stop stealing his email password
and his pants fell down and he fell down into an open manhole. But I have it on good authority
from the paramedics that he only called three or five other people that. So by the way,
the old card king at your service. Oh, maybe no, just maybe if you play a little game with Mickey
here, my lips might loosen up a little. You can keep an eye on this flurry of fingies and find the
queen. Yeah. All right. Keep an eye three card Mickey. Yes, let's do it. Mickey's running a
street scam. Keep an eye on the queen and pick the correct card to foil his plans. All right,
keep an eye on the queen. All right. Get your peepers peeled because these hands are about
to become a hurricane. I can't voice act on camera. I have to do it behind the scenes.
See here. Keep your eyes on the lady. Where is she going to go? Where is she going to go?
I got it. It was easy. Oh, but oh, don't be feeling too bad. Ain't nobody can.
What? Wait, what happened? That wasn't even looking.
Ain't nobody can hold a candle to Mickey's slick hands and catch fire from the mystery grease.
Maybe I should start using that cream. I wasn't even looking. I actually, I actually wasn't even
looking. I was looking over here at you guys in the chat. I'll give you the win. Mickey ain't made
of stone. He's made of a series of tubes filled with a mysterious substance that may or may not
be slightly corrosive. What? I won? I did it. Oh, geez. Anyways, about the event. Well, yeah.
Ain't heard it from me, but I hear it's going to be a real affair to remember.
The whole family's been talking about it for months. That's really going to get here. You
know what I'm saying? Anyways, thanks for playing. Let me know if you need any of my city smarts
while you're out here, rookie. Try not to lick any trolley handrails if you can help.
Those dermatology copays are real kicking the alligator pants. You feel me? Oh, that was fun.
I did it. Trolley ain't here yet, so why don't you use go check out the arcade? Mickey got banned
for his slick fingers gumming up the machines and causing an epidermis epidemic. That ain't mean.
You got to suffer the same fate. Oh, say Goku. Oh, that was cute. Okay. Click and drag up and
down. Oh, all right. Where should I go from here? The arcade? What time is it? It's 8 30. I got to
be my what animal am I? Oh, I'm an alligator. I'm an alligator. All right. Where's the, uh,
where's the arcade? Go. Who is it? Um, hello. Is this by chance your first time in alligator
New York City? I mean, in the city city, not alligator Long Island or something. Who's this?
I thought so. Oh, you don't know me. I'm sorry if that's weird. I just thought if you'd like,
I could text you some tips. City is really big and has a lot of colorful secrets that I wouldn't want
you to miss on your first visit. Is it okay if I help you out from time to time? Lose this number.
Leave me the fuck alone. Oh, great. I'll be sure to text you again soon. Don't forget to enjoy
yourself. Okay. Oh, what's the street street kiter too? I got to play these. I just got a puzzle
piece. What's that? I got it. All right, let's go. Sweet Geraldine. Hey, up there in long arms. I'll
be back. Hey, up there in long arms. You got a sec? Nice suit. What's a fancy reptile like you
doing at the back of the arcade? I know what you're after. That's right. I've got you just by looking
at you. You want cold hard plush. Oh, you find the right alligator. And I've got a job that'll pay
for both of our retirements and poorly made stuffies. Auto. You might see a humble claw machine,
but this is a fault and we're going to break in. We can't just walk in. No, there's countermeasures.
Sometimes, normally the security guard comes by and says, I'm not allowed to put my con
chair into the aisle. Without the boost, I'm not tall enough to work the cloth.
He says it's a fire hazard, but most of the machines in here are. You see behind here,
that's one hailing power strip juicing up every one of these babies. One wrong move and pinball
and boom. This place lights up like my chemistry teacher's hair when I turned that Bunsen burner
too high. What? What the fuck? What do you know about the event? I love to tell you about the
event. I really would. But this is our first time on the job to get a Mac. You haven't yet earned
my unbridled trust. Okay. What about Pat? Pat is a Patsy, but not my Patsy. That's for sure.
It's related to some of my dad's friends. One time at dad's show, Pat pulled the fire alarm
because he thought someone was trying to set him on fire. Turns out he just had a warm piece of
pizza in his pocket. No one could find him for almost an hour until the firefighters pulled him
out of the concert hall's crawlspace. He was covered in spiders and had eaten the pizza,
but was otherwise unharmed physically anyway. That guy's pretty weird. That was fun voice acting
for like five minutes. All right, let's go. Me, I'm known around these parts as sweet Geraldine,
criminal mastermind of the claw machine. You haven't heard of me? Honestly, I'm not surprised.
I leave no fingerprints and Johnny Law doesn't have a clue. Or Johnny Boyer from my geography
class. At least that's what he said when I asked him to spring fling. Okay, so what do we have to do?
Maybe we can come to a mutually beneficial arrangement. Claw machine, it's a two man
operation. I need someone who's not going to rat me out for additional prizes when plush comes to
shove. You feel me? Low effort streamer. What do you say, old timer? One last claw machine
score. The big one. All right, let's go. Let's do it. Follow sweet Geraldine's instructions to get
the perfect claw machine prize. Click left and right to control the crane. When you're ready to
grab, click the center button. What do you mean? Here she is, the big quesadilla, the motherlode.
Inside this vault is a treasure trove of prizes. I've had my eye on a couple of choice goods,
but I need an accomplice with nerves of steel and hands of steel. A tall patsy like you can
push the buttons and see the prizes. So what do you say? Let's get some cute loots for our cute
snoots. First, you should warm up your tricky digits. Grab me any prize that catches your eye.
Go on, old timer. Show me what you got. I'm going for the candy. Right there? I want this. Got it.
I heard a prize. Let's check the slot. Oh, my dad says I'm not supposed to have too much candy
because I get hyperactive and prone to fits of father pinching. But I think he just likes
keeping it all for himself. All right. I got it first try. I got it. Real job begins. How will
you react when the pressure's on? This time you follow my lead. And you give me that seashell. I
think it's pretty. What's seashell? Oh, which one? There's two. There's three. They're all the same,
right? A little bit more. That'll get it. You got one. What is it? I wonder if I'll hear the ocean
if I put this to my ear. It said glacial melt is changing ocean currents. Whoa, dude. You're really
good at this, but it's finally time for the big score. I can see it in your eyes. You're ready
to get the ultimate prize. Get me the doll from the best, most awesome video game franchise of
all time, Final Friends City. He's the dreamy one with the spiky hair. This is it. The big one.
Which one? This one here? This one? Can't move it. It's gotta be that one, right? No, I'm not
gonna be able to get that one. You gotta go for this one. Stop moving. Stop. Is it puzzle piece?
Where? Oh, shit, there is. All right. Give me that. Oh, I fucked it up. The Onimon anime is a
bazillion years old and only weird grownups remember it. I bet you'd only get the reference
of it being here at all if you were totally an old person. I want that puzzle piece. Give me the
doll from the best, most awesome video game franchise. I think I screwed it all up. I don't
think I can get it. I have to clear this out, right? Piderman, you know, from that obscure internet
cartoon. Popcorn? Blue bullet, maybe. I'm Bobman. I'm Piderman. Here's another quarter. Could you
try again, please? I want the puzzle piece. Wait, I gotta make sure I can get it first try. I might
be able to get it here. Batman, Piderman. Do I go straight down through here? Through the middle?
I think I'll get it. That's it, right? Wow. Dirt. Wait, did you put dirt in there? I only have two
more chances. I think I might be out of luck here. I have to make sure I can get this one. Let me try
to... What? Did you get the... Oh, no, I didn't. Yikes. Even looking at this guy is like walking
under a bazillion ladders or yeeting a shattered mirror into hyperspace. Wait, I can get this one
over here. This one over here. I got it. Can the claw go that far, though? I don't think it can.
I think I just lost. Oh, I got it. I got the puzzle. You can have this. I get the feeling
it'll come in handy later. I got it. That's a Nintendo Switch sound. Bad news, old timer.
That was my very last quarter. I'll retry in 30 minutes. Oh, it makes... I thought it was timed
out. Okay, 30 minutes is gonna go by. I get it. All right, let's go. Oh, I got it. I got it. I got
it. That's the punishment. All right, any prize. Doesn't matter. Let's just get one. What's this one?
Try to get the key, too. A big edie bar. They stopped making these in the 90s. This is just
like when my science class dug up fossils. But when I found my old retainer under several strata
layers of anime wall scrolls. What? I want the ducky. The key is gone. How am I supposed to get
the ducky? What's this anime? There's only one ducky in here. Is this one easier to get or is
this one easier to get? Probably this one. There it is. Got it. Thank you. Thank you.
Last year at recess, this girl in my class, Chrissy Baraducci, she got her snoot stuck in
a hole near the swing set that was full of bees. Anyway, she looked kind of like this after. So,
I think I'll give it to her as a gift for her beeversary. Okay, you're ready for the ultimate
surprise. The doll from. Okay, the spiked haired. Okay, there it is. Should I get the key?
I get the key. No, I don't want Batman. Batman, I haven't seen this guy in a while. I come over
the house. What? I know you want the doll, but I want the key. Just smash the glass and take it.
What the fuck? It's gone. All right, whatever. I need to get it. One more try. Just go one,
two, three, go. Okay, I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. I don't want to mess it up. I can't. An hour can't
go by. I got to do these mini games. It's like 50 mini games. I got to do them all or a reasonable
amount of them to complete the games program. Right here. Got it. Those sounds are so loud.
Oh, jeez. I can't believe you got the dreamiest anime game boy from Final
Friend City, Claude Stripes. Claude, his hair is almost as prickly as his social interactions
with women. This is exactly what I wanted. Thank you so much for helping me. Claude. Okay.
I can't believe the big score. Thanks to you, we had a clean getaway.
Family member badge. All right, go. I'll tell you what you need to know. The event is a secret.
I'm a gator, not a rat. It's a birthday party. It's a birthday party. It's literally a birthday
party. It's a surprise birthday party and everyone's invited and he thinks he's going
to get killed or something. This is a birthday party. That's the birthday party. That's right,
a classic double cross. That's the calling card of sweet Geraldine master criminal. All right.
What else we got here? Joanne. Oh, Joanie. Hey there. You up for a real challenge?
I haven't seen you here before, stranger. Alligator New York City is a big place,
but we tend to have regulars, you know? Little Rocco and Bonnie over there. Those two are here
every day, but you, I remember such a visible face like yours. Look at me being a real jerk.
I don't mean to be giving you a hard time or nothing. I've just been a little frazzled since
last night. I had a dream that I was a ski ball and some sticky fingered kid kept throwing me
into the 10 point hole. Over the 50, dingus, I tried to yell, but being a ball and all,
ding dong couldn't hear me. I woke up in a cold sweat in my kitchen, systematically throwing
individual oranges from the window into my neighbor's terrarium. Vitamin C would have
helped me shake it off, but all I had for breakfast was black coffee and a half a can
leftover candy cigarettes. Well, I got a dream for you. How much time do you have? How much time do
you have? All right. What is the event? Look, I know you're here spying for Pat for whatever
reason. That's fine, but I can't tell you family secrets. You feel me? If you haven't been filled
that hot, you'd have to really impress me. All right, let's go. What do you want me to do?
It smelled weird. It was a dumb kid. All right. Pat's my cousin and also the most genuine doof I
know. So you better be nice to him, you hear? He smelled it. I don't know. The thing that popped
in my head was like the drain commercial with the guys puking. I wouldn't want to have to pop
you one. I'm told I got a mean left hook and a moderately insulting right hook. A kick that
could benefit from some anger management courses. I tried to sign up for some calming hot yoga
at the YACA, but it didn't go over well. You ever get kicked by your own leg? It ain't great, bud.
It ain't great. My name's Joni or Bologna. If you're my fourth grade bully, come back to fight me.
You're not, right? Damn. Anyway, I work here at Adelaide's Arcade, sweeping floors and keeping
all the games running smooth as a baby's balmy behind. I used to work as a greaser in a shop
downtown, but I left to be closer to my gaming hobby. But let me keep the leather jacket though
and the company hairstyle. All right, what are we doing? So what do you think? Can you roll the
ball, old timer? I'm talking pinball, the old pinny B as I like to call it. It's the advice of both
of my friends, family and the supportive therapist I see on Thursdays. I got the highest score on
lizard wizards. You're eight months running, but I'm always looking for a real pinhead to
put my skills against. What do you say? Care to take on a pinball lizard like me? I didn't mean
to make a joke. I take this very, very seriously. All right, let's go. Pinball. When the ball is in
play control by clicking L and R or the keyboard, beat 5000 points. Absolutely simple. 5000. I'm
going to beat this right now. I literally just destroyed it. Has anybody played to beat your
score? I just annihilated your score. It was, it was embarrassing. I think that's so stupid. I hate
pinball machines should not have this. There should never be a way for it to fall down the
left and right without you doing anything. Cause that's not user error. It's designed failure,
which is like, come on, like that's stupid. I don't know what pinball machines should be like
completely redesigned. Mad because bad. You can't control that if it goes down there. There's
nothing you can do about it. What if I get a million points? El ballo. You can influence it.
What? By like picking the machine up and turning it around? That's illegal. It's illegal. You can't
tell the pinball machine. You get thrown out. All right. I destroyed the score. You're the annoying
kid in the arcade spamming the buttons. What? Cause I like the sound. One of the most amazing
sound effects of all time. They go in this order, running water in a river and pinball flipper sound
when you press the button. Number three would probably be, I gotta make sure I get this right.
A perfect swish at a basketball hoop in that order. Opening a can of soda is probably number
four or five. Hey, it's been a long time since I seen moves like that in front of the lizard wizards
here. Got that ball hitting all the do what's and who's it so fast. I could barely keep up.
Releasing a big fart. No, that's not a great sound. That's like a gross sound. It's been a real honor
to hang with us. Another student of the pinball arts. All right. I got a puzzle piece too.
Well, the event now, this might be just a rumor, but word of the street, there's going to be some
sick games there. It's a birthday party, not pinball per se, but you know, he can take what
you can get. That's all I can really say. I'd better get back on the grind trying to beat my
last high score. Thanks for showing me your supple wrist and head. Catch you later. All right. Let's
go. Time is it. Hey, it's me, Pat, the alligator, one with the hat, iPad. It's almost 10 can
you come back? Someone came over to my table and threatened me. Well, they gave me a coupon and
told me to have a nice day, but that could mean anything. Nobody came to threaten me.
One free tomato soup, best in New York City. There's a coupon I got last week. If you come
back, I'll give it to you. No questions asked. All right. So I gotta go back. Am I on like a time
limit? An actual time limit? I got some info. I don't bop me. Oh, it's just you, my new friend.
Sorry, I saw your shadow over me. I thought some kind of restaurant assassin was descending
from the rafters to take me out. It's a birthday party. Just do what everybody else fucking does.
And you act surprised even though you know what it is. It's a birthday party. Relax. You're going
to walk in the door, you're going to walk in the door, you're going to go like the coat off, lights are going
to come on and you're going to go like that. Just like that. Those of you guys that have ever had a
surprise birthday party that you knew about, don't get loud because that means you knew about it.
You have to go like this. You have to have like a bag in your hand or like a coat in your like under
your arm. You have to go, what the, hey, if you go like, oh, it's like, you know, you played it up.
You have to have like a bag in your hand, like a, like a grocery bag or like a briefcase or something.
You have to like be holding it up like this and act kind of surprised. Thanks for the tip. Yeah,
of course. Don't you, don't you, didn't you have to dare me when you were in elementary school?
You know, dare, dude, assassins really exist. At least I think that's the acronym.
I was absent a lot due to my nut allergy. It was tough times for Pat at
Willie's Peanut Butter Factory Elementary School. That's funny. Anyway, did you find out anything
from the family? Well, yeah, I know the sound. They sound nice, but they just might be fluffing
you up, you know, buttering your bread roll to throw you off the trail. All right, I've actually
just been sitting here mainlining complimentary bread rolls the whole time you were gone.
I'm a burger boy. We were at, I think we were at, where were we? I think we were at like Outback
Steakhouse and we ordered like, there was like three or four of us, we ordered entrees and there
was like this big loaf of bread there, like the, like the free bread. And he didn't like order
anything. He wasn't hungry or like didn't want to like, he didn't have like any cash. And I think
we were probably offered to be like, and he's like, no, no, no, I'm not that hungry. But I don't know
why he like didn't think it was free. I think the waiter came over and he was like, hey, is that free?
They're like, yeah. And he just goes, oh, nice. And he picked it up and like started eating it.
It's like what, of course it is. He could have asked us that, right? Hey, hey, so bread, is that
free? Yeah. I think the waiter was like, yeah. I just kept walking. I don't think everybody
at the table was like, what the fuck are you talking about? Oh, so funny. All right. Sorry,
I've actually just been sitting here mainlining complimentary bread rolls. And the bread from
Outback Steakhouse was actually fucking unbelievable. You can say whatever you want about like some of
these chain restaurants. I remember that it was, okay, it was like this little loaf. It was like,
I think it was like pumpernickel, right? What is it? The bread from Outback is like the best thing
in the whole restaurant, like the whole restaurant. They gave you this kind of butter that you really
had to really stick the knife in and really move it around. I mean, literally everything else at
Outback, I don't remember if it was good or not, but that little, it was a tiny little loaf. Oh,
it's awesome. Yeah. The bread is unbelievable. It's really good there. Is it actually, or is he
insane? No, no, I swear. Oh, there's a time limit. All right. And let's loggy with bread. Let's go.
Yeah, there it is. Yep. Yep. Yep. Oh, and the butter too. That butter's perfect. Yep. This is it.
Hold on. That's it. I think that's exactly what it is. This is the bread from Outback. The only
thing I remember. Look at the butter too. Yeah. The butter was so good. Like, is it weird that I
would want to go to Outback and just order like an appetizer and just be like, uh, I would pay for
the bread, right? Like if, you know, it's like, oh yeah, do you want like more bread? They'll do
that, right? They'll come back. You want some more bread? But I almost kind of want to be like, hey,
can you just like, can I just like mac and cheese and just, you bring out like five of these,
I'll pay for them. Like I pay for whatever you would think they would cost, whatever they are.
I'll pay for it. Bread tier list. That's how I feel about Olive Garden. Breadsticks from Olive
Garden are actually really good. Steak houses have like really banging bread. Yeah. You can
order it to go. Really? Bread makes you fat. So what? All right. My safe place. Find the code to
Pat's abode. Help Pat remember his room code. Thanks for protecting me. It really helps to have
someone walk me to my room. The wallpaper in here is a little intense. That makes me feel like
something is staring at me. What am I going to do? My heart can't take 10 more hours of waiting.
What's the event? What did I squeal the beans on? Cheese and crackers. Am I going to finally
catch this for the first time ever? Come on. Every time I think about it, it just doesn't happen.
I'm ready if it does. Since I was so worried about getting super murdered today, I did the
smart thing and got a special lock for my hotel room door. Just a little something I picked up
at the hardware store. I was worried I'd get so nervous that I'd forget the lock's passcode,
so I saved it on my website, www.allocator.com. I even made a button you can click for it.
I'm really glad now I took those all these specific button making classes at my local
community center. Okay. It's a virus website. This is Pat's home page generated by Geo Scalies.
Warning. Don't click Pat only. About me. Sorry. Under construction. What is that? This is the code?
About me. I'm Pat. Okay. Don't click Pat only. If you're not Pat, you're breaking the law. This has
been reported to the computer police. 91619. Okay. I got it. I got it. How do I say I got it?
91619. Let's go. All right. Here we are. Let's freaking go. Let's freaking go! This is for sure
my room. You can tell by the unobtrusive lock I installed. Can you go to my website and grab
the code? Okay. Let's go. 9 for the code. How do I enter the code? Oh. You did it. Thank you so much.
Whoa. I can't close it. What's going on? Help. You gotta help me. I don't even like pink. What?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Back up. I fucked it up. It's getting on my feet. Enter
anything. Oh my gosh. Hello. My word. This is quite the mess. Who are you two and why have you opened
my door? Oh my. I'm Pat. This is my hotel room. I installed this lock because my family's trying to
rub me out. This is my door where I've installed the lock because my family's trying to rub me
out. But if that's true and my password still worked, is your lock code 91619? Is your lock
code 91619? We have the same code and our families are both trying to kill us.
This is very funny. So long stranger. Perhaps in another life we would have been total best friends.
Like ships in the night, Mr. Pat. And if you don't tell anyone what you've seen here or I'll come
for you endlessly. That sure was a string of unlikely coincidences, wasn't it? I hope that
guy's room is OK. That stuff kind of smells like brimstone. Do we actually have the same code?
This is awkward. I'm not saying anything. All right. If you have pink stuff in here, it's going
to be wild. All right. Here we go. Thanks. I never would have remembered that on my own. Come on in.
I'm so glad we made it inside. Now I can really try to relax. I'll try to distract you from the
investigation. I'll text you again when it gets closer to 4 p.m. So don't forget to check your
watch. You know, in case you do get distracted doing a collection of menial tasks, formatted
in an enjoyable manner. Something like that. All right. Bye for now. Do I have any minigames? Wait,
who's that? God damn it! It's nice about sitting by yourself in a restaurant with a good book.
My girlfriend's coming to pick me up after work. I'm so nervous. What's in the kitchen?
That was so scary and loud. Oh, puzzle piece. Puzzle piece. Oh, wait. Sound effect number five
in the top five list is coffee pouring into a mug. Yep. Hey, bub, you're just in time for the
trolley got here a minute ago. OK. Why don't you go check out the city? Bring Mickey a hot dog,
maybe, or some protective handware. I'm gross. OK. But hold on, there's people here.
Who's this? If we eat a John, Johnny's here, food's all right, but that bottomless chowder
bowl was a disaster. I picked that thing up and bam! Chowdered pants the rest of the day.
Classic work of comedy. Classic comedy. Oh dear, I think I may have left my scrapbooking scissors
at home on accident. Oh, I found my scissors must have been your approach that gave me good luck,
stranger. Hee hee. I'm gonna try to go outside, home more, since I had the new baby.
Nana is watching her today, so here I am, out in the world.
A little nerve wracking to be away from the nursery after those months, to be honest.
Oh, I already miss all the new baby smells. Well, not all the smells. We all know more things come
out of babies than just sweet fragrance of their cute little heads. Well, even that stuff is a
little cute. Hee hee. I'm Maria. It's wonderful to meet you. I was heading to the local YACA
before I ran into you. I'm taking a class there today on scrapbooking, but I'm a little early.
I meant to wait here in the lovely weather until their class on mom yoga and self-defense ends.
Eat, pray, shove. Hee hee. Do you mean my son Pat? Oh, I'm just so proud of him. It's his birthday
today. Did I fucking talk with you? I told all of you. Why is he not doing voices? This is depressing.
What? It's his long game. It's a birthday. It's a birthday. I told you it's a birthday.
He's so funny with how he treats himself to a hotel stay every year on the day. He just
loves that continental breakfast. Voices or riot. You're going to make me get up and sing?
Oh, yeah. Jeremy has a really good voice. Don't you, Jeremy? Why don't you get up and sing for
us? Twinkle twinkle little star. I don't want to do that. I don't want to do it.
I do get concerned he eats too many of those, however. Sud shouldn't be coming out the snoot
of a boy that age. What about the event? It's his birthday. The event is why I'm taking this class
today. Okay, so what do you need? Help a mom out. Trying to put together a family tree to bring
tonight. Yeah, I don't have everyone's picture. It's so hard for all of us to get together in one
place these days. I don't think anyone would like me to use their photos from the early 2000s.
We all made some questionable wardrobe decisions back then. Since you're already going around town,
would you mind snapping some pictures of the family? And you get to and you get and bring back
a foot in the family tree. Maybe if you get them all, something good will happen.
Oh, I see you already have one there. Can you put it in? Let's see how much you learned so far.
Okay, what do I know so far? Click and drag the alligator portraits in a position of the family
tree. Come back any time to see your collection. Oh my god, there's so many people. How many people
are in this family? It's like the Elden Ring family tree. Like there's a fucking million people.
I don't know anybody. Can I take your picture? Where's my camera? Ain't nobody can follow these
ferocious fingies. Where's my camera? I want to take a picture of these people. You already got
her picture, but now I take pictures of everybody else. All right, let's go to the fun district.
I'm in the fun district. You got them from the mini game. Oh god, unknown. Again, you're a friendly
city guide here. So I was wondering, have you been finding any puzzle pieces around? I'm going to
write in all capitals, stop, unsubscribe. I thought so. You can find a lot of fun things you might not
expect in the city by clicking around. Puzzle pieces, secret baubles to look at, interestingly
shaped sewer rats. It's a real menagerie. Maybe if you find enough pieces, you'll be able to do
something good with them. Like unlock something. Maybe make a small blanket for a family of chilly
squirrels. The world is so bright. Have lots of fun looking around. Oh, there's all kinds of, wait,
I sell bugs. Bugs, bugs. All right, I'm going off. You know that there's like an old person
I'm going to do this, right? Bugs, bugs for sale. More than one even, unlike what the sign implies.
Yeah, I sell bugs here. No, not for baiting, for eating. We're alligators and we eat bugs,
which is something you know because you exist here, canonically.
Anyway, get bug buying or goodbye, kiddo. Ain't got all day. But I got to sell bugs to feed my
family with different bugs, which I buy with an alligator currency. What do you know about the
event? The event? I'm not quite sure what you're talking about. I have a selective memory disorder,
you see, and that I forget about things I don't really want to go to. What do you know about Pat?
Oh, did you say Pat? That's my grandson's name, but also the name of the nurse that comes to
massage the kinks out of my tail on Tuesdays. Did you mean Pat or Pat? You'll have to speak
up. I'm hard of hearing due to a condition where I stop listening mid-sentence and think about the
war. Most people call me Capulli, but my real name is Mortimer Giles, Jr., the third and a half,
on account of my grandfather being perfectly bisected by a wheat thresher during the Great
Depression. Miraculously, he's survived, but his life wasn't without its problems.
That's just how it was hard to see him when he turned directly to one side.
Grandpa, where are you, we'd called, but you know Vail, he'd already slipped through a crack
in the decorative neolium. It's the last time we ever saw him, and also when those basement
sounds started up. Well, look at me rambling here to a youth about cellar screams and the like.
Perhaps you can jog this old man's memory if you help me out with a favor. You see,
the only photo I have left of my dear late wife, Martha, has also been the victim of a wheat
thresher incident. I can't seem to put it back together again. Oh, how I'd give anything to see
Martha's sweet smile again. Can I help this old softy gaze upon his love, lost love once more?
Sure, Grandpa, I'll help you. Get the pieces glued for this old dude. Make my wife please.
Like a block to slide it into the empty space would be a very simple picture to gaze upon
the alligator's beautiful wife. Am I actually on a timer for this? All right,
this is gonna go off. Fuck, I'm so bad at these. You have no idea. Okay, okay, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, it's close. It's close. It's close. I got it. I got it. Almost. I got it. I got it. I just did
it. I got it. I just did it. I literally just did it. That was in record time. That's it. I just did
it. Oh dear, it seems you've seen the other side now with my secret wife. Could you put this one
back together too? If not for me then for creepy old coot grandpas everywhere? What? Oh no. What
the hell? I don't know. This is gonna take so long. I'm not gonna be able to do this one.
This has got to go top left. Just get this where it needs to be. Is that the right way? I think
this is probably like that, right? This? I don't know. What? It looks like you're not very good
at this. No, not taking this. Okay, that's correct but I gotta get it over there.
All right. Why are there two? Why are there like three people in this picture? Who is this?
Where does this go? Somebody in the front? Whose head belongs on here? I don't get it.
Whose fucking head goes on here? All right, it's that one and then there's three people in this
picture. Oh, leave me alone. This is here. All right, wait, wait, wait. Okay, so he's all the way
to the left, right? She's in the middle, right? Right? Fuck. This is hard. That's not right.
I'm so confused. Is it? Wait, wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Bring everything down. Bring everything down.
Bring everything down. Shit. I can't do these. This is too much. This is, this is correct but
I don't want to touch this. Damn it. This is down here. Fuck. Chat, please be supportive. Dude,
it's hard. You're nearly there. I know. I'm almost there. I just gotta get it correct. All right,
this has got to go up there. Let me just get it over there. Okay, that's done. This whole side is
done. Don't touch it. Fuck. It's close. So close. Come on. All right, don't touch this one. Can I
do it without touching that? I'm melting. I'm doing it. It's so close. I'm almost there.
This has got to come over here. All right, I just got to do this.
Stop making fun of me. What's it doing? Get out of here. I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do
it. I can't do it. It's like, it's too, it's like my brain cannot do it. My brain can't do it. Even
if I sit there and think for a second, it's just like, like that's all I hear. All I hear in my
head is the net. There's nothing with that sound. Ah, I can't. It's so easy. This is harder than
millennia. I beat millennia. Look, everybody has a left left brain and a right brain. Okay.
My left brain is this big. It's this big. It's like you'd have to go under a microscope to look
at it. My right brain is so large, it's swelling up my skull. You get it? It's like, oh my goodness,
it's swelling up so much. I can't, it's so much. You have to go to a microscope to find the other
side. A microscope. Left brain, right brain is a myth. Yeah, but whatever. You could like,
whatever. We can speculate. We don't even know. Okay. We don't know how the dinosaurs died. We're
speculating. It was a meteor. Yeah, we don't know that. We don't know how they died. They could have
something else going to happen. They could have like eaten each other. There could have been like
an explosion from a volcano. Not a meteor. Who knows? We don't know. A big rock, you don't know.
A big rock could have hit it. Yeah. But also, there could have been like a volcano that erupted
a huge one. A super mega volcano. Right? Nobody knows. All we can do is we can look at fossils
on the ground and go, that was a meteor. I think. Yep. We don't know. Nobody knows. We don't know.
You don't know. You don't know anything. You don't know anything. This puzzle is hard. You couldn't
do it. All right. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Bro, there's like one thing I
can't do and it's these fucking sliding puzzles. Break up the right column. I, who cares? What is
the, who cares if you can't do a sliding puzzle? Does it really matter? Does that really matter
that much? That doesn't matter. Oh, you can't do one of those. Oh, does it matter? Oh, I can't do
it. Oh no, I can't do the sliding puzzles. I can't, who cares? Oh, I got it. What if there was a
life-threatening situation where there was an escape room and you had to get out within 10 minutes
for that? Or like, no, I'm dead. I'm just dead. I'm going to die. I literally die. I literally die.
One of you could have said in the chat, hey dude, I'm going to give, um, 50 million dollars in bits
if you do this in 10 minutes. I wouldn't do it. I actually wouldn't have been able to do it. I
would have been like, oh my god, I wouldn't have done it. I just wouldn't have done it. I got it
though. That was fun. Oh, Gertie, good old Gertie. It's been years since I've looked upon your sweet,
curly hair and your man-breaking arms. Thank you so much for your help, stranger. Thanks to you,
I'm reunited with both my lost loves. I just have like this red image sitting here.
Far the past years ago, but Gertie is just in witness protection, you know, from all the
man-breaking. What a firecracker, that gal. On full days, I could still feel the phantom
broken body pains she left me. Hey, a vent? Oh, you mean tonight's a vent? You young folk love
staying up late. Me, I've been bed by six nightly after a modest dinner of soft bug puddings and
four to seven episodes of soft flutes on public broadcast. Anyway, kiddo, thanks again for helping
me out, or should I say helping three out. Yeah, don't tell my grandkids. And look, here's a little
something for your trouble. All right, no more slide puzzles and we'll be fine. The breeze,
the practicing quartet, what a perfect day to be a live alligator. Sleepy pants. Oh no, the snipper.
Are you here about joining the resistance? Come to the front door, but don't let the feds tail you.
Password is the only thing worth fighting for. Justice Absolute, which is also the name of my
favorite Mark's Leaning Ska Band. Yes, I said favorite. There are more than one. There are two,
as a matter of fact. Their first single was about putting a potato in the tailpipe of a
crooked alligator governor when he tried to join their mailing list. No GMOs. That's no
governors may opt in. Which event? I have four events to go to this week alone. Like tomorrow,
it's Minestrone Monday at the soup kitchen. Then it's onto Taco Tuesday at the women's shelter.
Wednesday doesn't have a funny name, but everyone does get those cupcakes with the white squiggly
as an extra at the alligator food bank. If you're talking about tonight though,
you might as well go act like a cop somewhere else, officer pinstripes. I don't rat out my
comrades. My name is bolted up so tight the count of Monte Cristo has spent years trying to escape
from me while plotting his vengeance against those who wronged him. We just finished reading
that book in my Tuesday Lit class. Pretty baller to be honest. I love revenge and breakfast.
What do you know about Pat? Do you mean Hat Pat or do you mean Bat Pat? No, no, you probably
mean Hat Pat. Bat Pat is my high school neighbor that used to pick me up for DSA meetings on Friday
until he got grounded. He'd apparently broken his nice favorite set of extremely fragile and large
eyed porcelain deer with something. A club? Well it's not important. We'll spring him eventually.
Yes dad, I mean legally. Anyway, Hat Pat is an okay dude. I barely know the guy but he still made
me punch proof vest to wear to protest out of Dr. Soda bottle caps. He's a stand up alligator.
Maybe he drinks too much soda though. Doesn't he know what the government puts in that stuff?
I tell you but the CIA agent that watches my cell phone would probably delete my
chumbler in vengeance. That's where I keep all my pictures of day one. Okay. I'm Mona but you can
call me by my online handle for safety which is kpopangel85 but I can have other interests
besides the cause. All right what do you what do you what do you want me to do? Listen I'm not
trying to give you crud about Pat or something. I'm just a little stressed out. I don't have to go
all first world probes on you bobs but I have a design due to be scanned tomorrow afternoon.
If I miss this deadline it won't get printed in time for the indie comics annual people with
bangs convention this weekend. You know how long it takes to staple a stack of these zines? At
least two full episodes listening to gator crater a true crime podcast about the world's most blown
up alligators. Yes dad I also have Algebra 2 homework. If you know we put some of these pictures
together maybe I could give you the straight dope about the dope. Get ready to join the resistance.
Okay make paper words salad because your voice is valid smells like
zine spirit. Mona's zine needs to cover three topics evenly choose a clip to add to the zine
and click the page to glue it in place because some clips cover two topics at once.
So check it pinstripes I've already done all the hard zine stuff like picking the clips and
cutting everything with semi-straight lines. I need you to pick a good selection then glue them
into place. Sadly ever since the stickening of 2017 I'm not allowed to use glue myself
or glue sticks or rubber cement or large stickers or small stickers so you're gonna have to be the
hero that sticks the pics. This sign encompasses of course the most the three most important most
ziny things possible. I'm talking about social issues indie comics and k-pop obviously. These
three topics go together like peanut butter jelly and a third comparable thing that escapes me at
this moment. That doesn't mean we can lean into any one more than the other. My zine has to be
balanced or people will think I'm biased. That means no page space for anything more than the other.
So pick up a pic and get ready to stick careful though I have a limited selection of content
and my glue is forever just ask my hamster. Grip in Valhalla goopy the third 2015 to 2017.
zine for god's sake zine what magazine oh a magazine when you're done we'll ask the
editor if it's ready to scan so get pasting okay so what was it cover is really important
as to portray the essence of what's on the inside really choosing what ironically humorous t-shirt
to sport at Rosh Hashana that'll really unsettle your extended family wait what no I didn't want
to choose that heat it wibbly fin this will get him cancelled for sure I don't know I just
clicked on the first one don't forget to balance the topics okay I wouldn't want anyone to accuse
me of political bias or standing bias okay so we already did wibbly fin right this one guys together
forever together forever okay what's this one is it a meme all right oh well I'm going to send this
to everyone I know and some people like don't if you type random numbers into your phone they
have to go somewhere right Jesus do we really want someone who eat do we really want someone
who eat a sad lunch for another term in office oh my god I mean that's fucking crazy that's so
like sad to be honest this one kind of mondo bums me out I didn't win the zine award last year
last year's calm but I did place third in cool bangs Joshua Ransom oh okay wait this is a
like celebrity or something I didn't really get an interview this is just what I hope he'd say to me
ah I love you JR hope you read this this is balancing it out right question oh okay that's
okay I love you what type of girls do you like oh any kind but most of the kind that are like you
on the inside this one's a real exclusive I can't believe we got it last inside page is a hard
hitter you have to really leave them wanting more like really actually more like maybe they'll give
you a couple more bucks to pick up a few more for their comrades this is lois she feels wibbly fin
is an inadequate mayor balance the budget he can't even balance on this log in his own yard
nonetheless all right yeah this is particularly damning but I pride my zines on delivering
health care or public restroom chocolate fountain wibbly fin would rather save the scales
on his back than weigh in on what matters we are but no it can't be too we can't be too political
we can't be too this is we've already got political well I will always be so alone I
just need to be on my own at least this guy misunderstands is still streaming final season
this one really taps into the deep well of the soul we're almost there just paste on the back
cover and we'll be done mayor wibble fin uncompromising hair partisan teeth he's got an
okay hand cherry mandarin fingers embezzling tail mayor wibbly fin would make a terrible
addition to the k-pop group eight guys and therefore we should examine what type of
politicians we really want to hold office in our beloved city as you can see from this photo
he just doesn't fit and therefore the case is made that he's out of touch despite his effort
to not look out of touch and looks gross here in this photo okay I don't like it so it makes
me feel there's a really solid case you're all done hand it over I said fair and balanced but
you're clearly favoring one topic over the others I should have known better than to ask an outsider
what I got it wrong what oh my god all right it's this three topics let me just get it right
shit all right not more than one or the other okay okay okay okay okay I the the mayor ones
which is kind of funny all right we're gonna start with the mayor exposing the mayor okay
expose start with a mayor then not too much mayor so we're gonna go with this is the band
eight guys so we have one for the mayor one for eight guys now I need okay this is like a
little comic book or something meme okay so I've got one of each sad meal we have two mayors and
one of the others two mayors this is also because we have two eight guys and two mayors okay now we
need something that's not the mayor or eight guys is this one no no shit this is three eight guys
two mayor one of something else this is three mayor nope wait hold on oh here we go yep all
right this is like a comic book we have three eight guys two mayor two right right it's a comic
book all right so we're almost there just paste on the back cover so now we need another uh comic
book right is that gonna be all right this one right that'd be three two three is that two three
two will that be enough is this eight guys oh that's eight guys no I didn't want to click I
wanted to put it over it okay whatever we do again we're gonna do it again we're gonna do it
whatever whatever whatever I wanted to switch it I just click paste we're gonna another hour is
gonna go by all right fuck okay help me retract shit I wanted to move it okay okay okay okay what
do I start with I'm not gonna start with the mayor there's too many mayors don't open with the mayor
open with um this one I'm gonna open with the comic book one right that makes sense
indie comic one now I can do I can do eight guys and the mayor okay so we need to do meme
and now we need a mayor there we go we're pretty balanced now right so that's two comic one of the
other ones okay here we go this is two comic two um eight guys right oh wait no no no wait
this is eight guys person this is both eight guys is this a comic okay wait so this is eight guys
yep okay so we have two eight guys two comic one mayor we need another mayor okay we gotta balance
this up what's this one we need a mayor eight guys the last one needs to be a comic and that's it
right mayor and comic I don't have mayor in comic do I don't I my only options are our mayor right
so eight guys comic no comic for the back cover you will have to have a comic term of two people
the last one can be mayor eight guys burgers and fries by the way keep comic mayor which I do
right now it's one politics two k-pop two indie comic so this would be two two two but fuck help
me mayor then comic book this is mayor now we get comic book and then the back cover is eight guys
and that's it that's it right I think back cover is comic book I think that's correct then we end
up with the comic and that's it we got it got it that's it no that's eight guys fuck did I get it
that's two three does this count as both back cover is mayor and this is comic though technically
right you the mayor one this counts as mayor and comic this one is mayor and comic right you
cringe I think that's good that should be it right this is mayor and k-pop mayor I need mayor and
comic all right this is gonna be the one what do I need comic was the cover this is this is it all
right that's it that would be three three three I'm just gonna write fucking down I'm gonna write
this shit down I'm I can't I've ran out of time I've run out of time I didn't I didn't know that
too they could be two different things fuck god damn it all right I get it I'm gonna write it down
I'm literally gonna write it down all right what are we doing okay cover needs to be comic we got
one comic some covers are two topics all right so we need the cover we need the comic cover
all right then we want may no eight guys be one eight guys I don't know which one covers all three
this one does because this would be one eight guys and then this is that's good now we need a
mayor one mayor which is right here fuck um comic this is too comic or should I do two eight guys
this would be too comic cover is all three one no this is too comic too comic well we have two
comic one eight guys now this is mayor that would be two comic one eight guys one mayor
okay and this is eight guys this is this is this is eight guys there'll be two eight guys
is that we two comic two eight guys one mayor am I doing the same thing okay that's
two comic two eight guys one mayor now I need um I need mayor that'd be two two that'd be two two two
this would be two two two this would be three guys three this is what is this two mayor now
and then putting this would be three guys two mayor um eight not three what this is one comic
one this is I wrote I wrote I fucking wrote something down I fucked it up right now I'm at
two two one so this would be I'm so confused because this accounts as two left brain logic
I'll dodge an axe if you swing it at me I I've lost I'm you know I gotta turn the music off it's
like literally fucking with my brain all right music off we got two two one right now this would
be three two two right three two two three two two if I put this here I'm just fucking doing it
I don't care I'll leave I'm leaving if I don't get it right three two two that's three comic two
eight guys two mayor now I need this would be three mayor I just need one eight guys on the back
and I'm done because that would be three comic two eight guys three mayor that's it I just need
comic on the back and that's it right I just need just comic on the back is it is it not possible
I need comic on back no comic is on the back of the eight guys what there are no comic on the back
there is none so if I do this this would be free I stop I have to stop writing shit down before
it happens so this is comic I'm just gonna look up the solution all the backs are two topics
there are no comics for the back so this this would get us to three comic right
both mayor no don't do both mayor what do I do comic now and then mayor it's a comic and also
eight guys is it this is eight guys no it's not it's a streaming thing I'm just doing it I don't
care and I'm literally now I'm literally not coming back okay two now I just need mayor
and that should be it right right or do I need eight guys this is is this eight guys in the back
this is it I did it right yo let's show it to the editor for approval
yeah sure we're good what's going on mayor comic comic eight guys all right what I was
gonna say is five guys went up to S tier for me looks like we're all set to scan and send to the
printers uh I've recently had five guys and it was it was way better than Shake Shack I don't know
what happened to Shake Shack but holy shit it fell off hard so hard you want to know something
fucked up you know I I was a Shake Shack fan I was an absolute Shake Shack maniac um I've had it a
few times and holy shit it fell the fuck off so bad the last time I've ordered Shake Shack the
burger's been like not good it's like the texture length has been weird and if you get lettuce on a
Shake Shack burger this is just my this is what's happened to me the last few times this might not
be your experience but holy shit it's been mine dude the lettuce is like one tiny little joke
piece of wilted like wet gross lettuce like this it was dog shit dog shit I'm not even knocking it
was dog shit if you open the bun of like a recent Shake Shack burger it fucking looks like this
and it's like just it's one tiny little pathetic piece yeah I had a five guys burger the lettuce
was fucking big and crispy it was a tomato it was a big thick delicious tomato burger was cooked
perfectly I have to amend the fast food tier list Shake Shack literally went down to like a B
maybe even lower it sucks literally was my favorite place I'm sorry like you you know I'm not a
bullshitter I it was up an S tier but but why was there tomato on it I just felt like it one day
I know tomatoes I don't tomatoes gross I just felt like it it was good I felt like it I felt
like it you fell off shut up I felt like it today I didn't eat it today you know what I mean I felt
like it like recently I felt like eating tomato on my burger I felt like it I had to test to see
how juicy and firm and crispy it was you know I mean I had to test it because if your lettuce
if your vegetables I get to check and see that because that's important I don't like lettuce
tomato on a hamburger but I had to try to see how well it was it's crispy it was juicy and
watery and delicious calm the fuck down dude you know oh that's pretty rad tagline if I had public
access channel talk show which is 100% of the cards by the way if I keep a B plus his second
term that would definitely be my sassy catchphrase anyways the event is a gross allocation of funds
if you want my opinion I'm fine what have you calmed down what are you talking about you know
that helium is a finite resource seriously I'll google it every balloon it's a party every balloon
at that shindig is basically a big heck off to the folks that really need it like scientists and
clowns that are down on their luck but have hopeful hearts I'll see you there tonight comrade
bring your favorite safety pin covered jean vest for righteous popping yeah five guys really took
over I feel like I was kind of unfair to five guys because when you order a five guys burger
and you get fries they just dump they just dump fries in the bag it's just it's like a joke they
just put like five servings worth in the bag and they're kind of like messy and shit and they look
they're a little greasy for me but the burgers it went up to esther I have to be honest I'm sorry
all right we got it we got the puzzle piece hello hello hello hello hey
oh hello we're the downtown quartet and we'll sing you a song not a very short one but it also
ain't long we'll sing it in the morning and we'll sing it past noon we've had a lot of noise
complaints and we'll be gone soon hit the solo maries to jail we can't tell you much but we'll
sing like a bird we're pat's aunt and uncle's he's our darling nephew that didn't rhyme
all except for louis who's just part of the crew take it louis oh baby i'm not related to pat no
nothing like that i'm just a guy they know that takes part of the show oh oh oh dude pull it back
sorry okay denise louise matrice barice we're gonna sing a song if you can help us with our act
we'll tell you all that we heard the barbershop upset play give them a solo without triggering
an oh no help the alligator quartet hit their solos when the scrolling bar shows a singer's
background point the spotlight at them sounds easy enough one of our vocal chords
give an eye on the scrolling bar at the bottom find the spotlight at the singer with a matching
background when the groovy disco pattern appears shine the spotlight at the disco ball and we'll
all sing together ready gentlemen ready maestro hey what's going on oh disco ball i failed
oops i didn't get it i didn't know what they wanted me to do i didn't i didn't get it i didn't
get it i get it now i didn't get it okay here we go here we go why are you so pissed i'm doing
it right i got it right what are you talking about you can this lady's not very good say that felt
pretty good what do you think fellas not enough patrice time patrice demands more solo time
okay one more time for patrice he's actually colorblind no i'm not what are you talking about
what are you talking about did i get it wrong what are you talking about that's correct what's
happening am i stupid am i stupid what's happening what's happening he's throwing i
i don't understand what i'm doing wrong you could have had more timber the singing word i'm a real
singer and i'm i'm gonna prove it okay last time all right everyone give it everything you got
that's right she just sounds bad like that's not my that's not my problem you just sound bad
preschool level color not i thought i did it right you guys are just fucked up
got it all of them did it come on man oh right sorry oh here we go you helped us with our song
and to improve our content now what we're going to tell you is very we're booked at the event today
thanks for your help now we'll see you in a wink unless we get arrested then please bring us from
the clink this game's cute hello hello your pal the city aficionado here just want to make
sure you know about this cool local place called nana roux antiques i'm already there i know what
you're thinking antiques are for grandmas and you're right the whole shop is run by a grandma well
a nana a nana roux there's a great local legend about the place that it's super haunted by like
five billion ghosts what's really haunting though is the prices raffle ha oof oof there's a little
shopping humor from me to you i'm not really rolling on the floor anyway nana roux is a much
of a card shark as she is a deal shark so be careful if you have time defo check out her colorful
shop it's tons of fun you're right we're here now check it out i used to be a porcelain doll but i
came to life because of this magic shop at least that's what i tell my ex-wife so i can come sit
here all day i've got a good butt groove going on in this shelf you're late i've been waiting
for you for an hour what do you mean you don't work here well it's not as if you can fault me
for thinking so but with a drab wardrobe and pathetic sunken eyes everything here is the
clear stink of death upon it oh except for me of course i'm merely a poor poor woman in deep mourning
not at all one involved in mysterious circumstances the police cannot explain
oh i can't even imagine attending the event unchaperoned only my poor dear husband had been
less poisoned i wouldn't have to suffer such horrific indignities will no one think of me
and my feelings i'm merely a lonely widow left behind for the great beyond by my beloved late
husband horace oh horace such a always such a wonderful wisp of a man even at his most poisoned
he forever remained regal kind and absurdly wealthy now in his absence i find myself trying
to take comfort in the metaphysical arts if only i could hear his sweet strained voice once more
ladies oh pat you mean the one with the ridiculous hat yes i'm aware of him terrible stain on the
bloodline that a poolie fellow created all sorts of nonsensical cousins for myself and my dear
children once removed at the very least that's a little comfort to me especially when i see
someone like patrick vault over a coffee table at the holidays he thought he saw the spider's man
but whatever nonsense the questions grow tiresome your questions don't you see you're riling up the
vapors what are you the lead detective investigating the mysterious circumstances around
my late husband's untimely despise i fucking can't read how dare you i've had no rest for the past
week whenever i close my eyes i'm visited by horace's specter reaching out to me perhaps
trying to send me information about some secret treasure he wanted me to inherit on top of the
rest of his vast estate will nothing stop his ceaseless haunting i don't know your heart to
help this poor widow i can give you the information you seek just use the spirit board to contact
horace and please find out what my dear late husband wants or what kind of evidence he has
you got it follow the ghost through the eye of the planchette he could get tricky the faster
you move the more suspicious the widow gets okay prove me you can contact my beloved late husband
or i shall out you as a charlatan to the entire mean ladies bridge club which one of which is
where the husband wait what does her husband look like i don't remember what do your husband look
like that him that's him where the where is this guy it does seem like my horse perhaps it really
could be him okay i get the suspicion bar right suspicion bar got him got it dude you sus guy
yeah i'll be at uh i'll be at uh comic con next year i have a booth a sus booth
not be like shaking everybody's hands though oh i got it this no i'm not i'm kidding that's a joke
that's a joke i gotta pee and i want some more green tea hey hey hey can i get you anything
well i'm up can i get you something hey can i hey hey can i get you something all right so
how many how many people have i met i must go tell the children at once and also hide some sensitive
items in the toilet paper perhaps wait i read that i just read that that was my dream i simply
don't have any more time to discuss the event with you today farewell my medium all right
well you what about you you have something to do i'm gonna nanoroo is where if there's ooze on your
shoes it's just because of the booze it's haunted as i'll get out in here sweetheart so mind the
ectoplasm been buying some antiques from me today doll face but he's got a huge new shipment of
designer grandma plates never meant to be eaten on a bunch of confusing teddy bears from the 70s
with realistic plastic faces i can get you a real deal on one of those if that's your fancy
that you fancy i know you kids are into weird stuff these days yes sir i see you over there
i'll be with you in a minute who are you well sugar pie as the sign may have alerted you
i'm the one and only nana roux herself purveyor of only the finest antique goods and the finest
antique store owners yeah come on honey tell me i'm looking good for my age alice stop harassing
the customers my sweet sweet patrick he's my absolute shortest grandson why it feels only
like yesterday he would run about the shop squealing about ghosts trying to eat his kidneys
and hiding in humorously oversized vases as you can probably tell by my expression that actually
was yesterday you guys are wicked funny that boy might not be playing with a full deck hey hey you
be careful that vase is expensive oh so pat's inviting his little friends to the event isn't
that cute he's such a darling that boy i'll be closing the shop early to get over their own time
tonight i'm doing that i'm doing that what i just stopped for a second to look over here
it was one more okay it was like it was like one full second you had to it took you you typed that
while i was playing it it took me took you longer to type that sentence he's gonna get stun locked
no i'm not no i'm not i'm trinketing out of this conversation sorry pumpkin looks like i have to
stop yapping about the event and take care of a customer unless you defeat me at a round of cards
please say let's do it yeah how do you play old main on your turn click to take one of nana bru's
cards then she'll take one from you any matching pairs will be removed the player left holding the
old maid loses how do you play how do you play this let's go fish oh so i gotta see we gotta
get pairs what here we go i'll get you next turn i know it you seem nervous what do we have the
same cards but what if what if she am i gonna lose or do i win the universe wanted me to make
a pair so now what i won oh that was easy that was easy i wouldn't you beat me fair and square
holy shit look at his mod chat for a second i had another dream uh oh dear perhaps it's one of the
worst stories he has ever shared on stream was it though all right you see my older sister constance
around you should try to coerce her into playing around with you with an adult like you we get a
real kick out of it i had to warn another mod about it was bad how was it bad if they're at h
sharp okay something will get knocked the boy something will get knocked off the boy we'll
make sure of it hey it's me again pat almost four and i could really use your help oh shit
it's almost eight we have to we stopped this at eight do i have to do something before eight
you know anything about shoes and the wearing of them yeah perfect could you come meet me at my
hotel room just make sure you aren't followed by any shifty characters or college age canvassers
in cargo shorts that baby they give me like gas i already gave all my dollar bills to that guy
pretending to be a statue outside fourth street i'm on my way with a blood jesus christ i want
to know that guy's story good evening to you fellow traveler have you come to imbibe some
ales after your long journey as well how come bet just your finest novelty wine based on a popular
sci-fi television show i sued i like dabbling in a little bit of cosplay myself by just last year
at alligator comic con i dressed as a character of my own creation the errorless great wizard of the
north my brother mickey helped me put it together though he did get it a bit slimy yeah it's a party
but am i not supposed to say that i'm telling him it was you that is my second cousin as well
as my second favorite person to play dungeons and dragons with first being my internet friend carl
whose dad got rich white coin mining that's a bard so you know pretty party useless
great singing voice though he can really wail on that juice harp i'm dary known as the terror of
the east side in most magics happening card game circles on campus i'm known as a terror of the
ap bio lab or the one with that haircut bald coin is still an emote wow it's still there i never
deleted it okay you're leaving already safe travels my fellow traverser of the mortal plane
after we'll meet again in another realm or on an internet forum for role playing
what are you doing over here hello esteemed guest mr pat asked me to inform you to come straight to
his hotel room upon arrival can you update your emotes i don't know i mean i i have no i don't
think i haven't updated my like paid sub emotes in like three years yeah it's true okay let's go
i want you to knock first in case he was wearing pants all right i don't forget what i just said
and come with me i'll walk you to mr pat's room at once okay i can drag this hallway oh my how
embarrassing please don't tell the internet we've had a biohazard internet again can't read okay
thanks for your patience esteemed guest we've now arrived mr pat is expecting you please just knock
in case he's have a johnny of a day welcome back i was just trying on some nothing i was doing
anything actually have you talked to more of my family found out any secret plans you think
they're throwing me out oh no you're totally wrong about that i would definitely know if they were
doing that because it sounds a little far-fetched don't you think you can't pull one over on old
pat on his birthday that's what i always say if you guys want to hear the best cat puke sounds
those like asmr eating like kind of what mukbang videos i don't know what it is about these i like
i watch a lot of stuff right but they'll they drink usually they drink like a big soda at the
very beginning they'll always drink a huge soda like oh well today before i eat this big meal
i'm gonna drink a giant i'm gonna drink a huge soda and it's just like it sounds like the
microphone is inside of their throat it's just like cat puke cat puke cat puke and i say cat
puke every time please minus two i don't watch these every day i'm just saying like that's where
you can find the best cat puke like you would want to find them i don't know i don't know like
what do you mean stop what what's wrong with you mods deal with this guy mods deal them you lost
500 viewers for that i didn't lose 500 viewers and i lost 500 viewers because i'm playing a puzzle
game grima is disgusting today i'm just i'm i'm telling what all right well i say it sometimes
like once a year what stop reading the one guys huh you're gonna make me throw up i just i just
said that if you watch those eating videos they have cat puke sounds what i'm not allowed to have
an observation about video content i've seen at some point in my adult life you know what's fun
there's no don't end never mind i say i always fall asleep with autoplay on and when i wake up
i see what's there i don't know i don't know it's like weird like i would love to just kind of be
like you know let's see what we get and then i'll open up like i'll have my ipad usually sitting
right there and there'll be something playing sometimes i wake up to cat puke's i wake up to
the like eating videos and i'm just like what's that oh that's where we are and i just go back to
bed it's kind of like a mystery you don't know what's gonna happen in the meantime though i
actually called you back here because i needed your help it's no different than leaving the tv
so let me ask you a question do you guys leave the tv on in the hotel room you guys fall asleep to
the tv how's that different you don't like put the tv on to fall asleep to the tv on some random
channel and just shit you don't even know what's gonna be on there is gonna play what do you mean
no zoomers don't do that am i out of my am i out of my fucking mind people don't like leave the tv
on to sleep to some like a lot of time pauli said the last two weeks he's almost made us puke twice
from nasty food videos all right listen i almost puked last night because i was watching this video
with this guy it's a gross thing that's not that's that's real yeah i all i i almost puked last night
i almost puked for one second because when i say we were watching i was watching i don't know so i
just i want i want to have tons i want to have tons of knowledge up here i want to be like informed
about everything you know what i mean so like food videos and and like halloween conventions and um
like infomercials and i want to be all knowing i have to be all knowing i need to know everything
you know what i mean like that i i need to know about all these subjects i have i just need to
like absorb them sir gideon i don't know a shoe related problem i don't usually wear them but i
figured if i did tonight maybe i'd have a better look at it put it out of the event safely so
sometimes when you when you want to be all knowing you might watch a video where like a guy is like
eating like a big like thing covered in cheese and makes you almost puke and you go all right
i don't want to see i'm done with that i have that knowledge now i don't want anymore the loathsome
cat puke her the issue isn't my usual shoe all right let's move on what what's the weirdest
infomercial you've ever seen i don't infomercials aren't usually weird they just kind of background
noise last week by nanaru gifted me an antique arm war from her shop as an early birthday present
turn your noise get up higher i heard the fart stop it it's a big spacious practical and so super
haunted that it's leaving a weird stain on the park way flooring just by existing i haven't been
able to find any of my shoes and whenever i open a draw weird stuff happens why don't you see for
yourself okay peruse for shoes find a pair of pat's favorite shoes by clicking on those suspicious
draws be careful the packet's too scared they'll give up on shoes forever after each round the
contents of the draws will shuffle around spooky i can't believe in this generation of people that
consume media all day that i'm the weird guy for watching tv at night huh huh help me find my shoes
player let's go what got it that's a shoe no that's not sure that's a sandal right gross stuff
oh second chip oops it's a matching game you don't think i relax shoe gameboy advance is
the second one but what the fuck was that true oh it wants me to do it in succession
oh okay i know all right all right all right all right all right all right that where's that one
that one was like over here somewhere i don't remember i didn't know was it okay wait so where's
the other one where's this one right here i don't where's this i don't fucking know i okay here this
one here i didn't know that's what that usually would stay open and like in a memory game they
would stay open if we like go find the other one it stays open i look i get it now start timing
people out for a year if they continue to be mean to me okay that's top left see i thought usually
in a memory game that's the card stays flipped over the thing stays out a year what a tyrant
where's the shoes no no there's a shit okay there's one right below it pick the same one
again that's not how it works i got it i'm fine you got all pairs of shoes go bear flipper like
i usually do sorry i'm just so nervous i'm not thinking straight sorry i made you come back
here for nothing but i really appreciate that you did all right oh geez i'm so glad we met today
you're the best pal i've had in a long time see i'm getting all mushy you get back out
there and dig up some more dirt we only have a little bit more time onion ring uno giorno
city pal here did you know that's how they say hello in italy at least that's how what it said
on the back of my crisp pricies box today see there's a lot of different alligators from all
over the world here in alligator new york city that's why they call it a melting pot not because
of that strange smell the sidewalk gives off in hot weather as i originally thought
if you want to meet any interesting people during your stay maybe you should start on
the trolley since everyone used it you never know who you might strike up a conversation with out
there who might throw a bag of hair at you and then run away that's the big city for you full
of surprises a bag of hair okay where have we not been to how about the um the unsavory part of
this weirdo again hey did you say something i see you over there i in my cards youngin
but i ain't giving him to you last time i was given cards away was long before you were born
and now look at me i'm old see what sharon gets you aging irreparably one day your skin is sucked
close to your skeleton and then you turn around and boom the jowls are hanging down past your
collarbone which are now hollow inside is that what you want hollow collarbones or the nest of
galley long legs inside then stop staring at my card moisturizer every day get a good just
light face moisturizer and do it if you do it every day after you get out of the shower dry off
it'll look like this i ain't telling you a kid like you nothing i have acne there's one right
here you never get a look you're gonna get little pimples and stuff but did pat tell you to go
steal his great aunt's cards because if you did i am going to give him his christmas present this
year which of course is a bag of oranges and a strange tin of popcorn from 1987 about 1985
when super mario came out that's only the business of me and the nurse that puts the ointment on my
back bees three times a week stop staring at my cards although you could blame me for the
information as long as you don't stare at my cards what do you say kiddo think you can beat the old
maid that's right okay so this is the this is the thing before was the tutorial for this
beauty before age my dear you go first play cards like an old lady i was going right in the middle
at 10 oh is that on 10 you just took the same card back wait that was the old maid
there you go i won't lose i can pick cards in my sleep sometimes it feels like the pairs want
to find me left that's the old maid all right so i just i have to end up with the old maid right
means no you don't want the old maid hey the old maid oh fuck okay this is hopefully this is 10
oh no did i lose oh go home with the tail between your legs baby and your mommy will wipe the tears
off your snoot haha haha back haha can't retry it that's just rng you can't be like good at that
game hey buddy your good old guide here oh my god i just like scratched your eyes i just wanted
to warn you in a big city the city so big there are bound to be parts of their little seedy
fucking seedy tough guys seedy tough guys who eat the seeds of things without spitting them
out on a napkin politely be careful don't go clicking around in back alleys or anything
you never know what you might find i just give it gps on my phone why do you know i'm here
hey what are you looking at trying to listen to our exceedingly private rooftop conversation
beat a creep hey you got a light no not from my cigarette i mean in general kind of dark out here
and i've got a spooky ghost allergy you ain't seen any right i say you there vagrant brother i don't
think that they're a vagrant they've got that suit on perhaps a hobo king you may be right sister
you there hobo king come here a moment honestly brother what are we even doing in this filthy
part of town even breathing the air outside the city watering hole is making my scales lose their
highly regarded luster i agree sister but you know as well as i that we had to find an unbiased
bonehead for our beneficiary so anyone at the estate was out besides you know how weary i
grow of literally everyone we know in the whole world shall we talk to the stranger with the
briefcase then yes yes as long as it's not someone that gives me the dreadful horror of being known
hey guys what do you know about the event well now you're going to have to be more specific
i attend lots of events you know balls galas exhibitions princes unfortunate performance art
shows if you're speaking of last week when i walked the runway for gil's fashion fishery
rubbery pants for moist alligators i'll have you know i got a write-up in the magazine spread
for highlights for children anyway if you're talking about tonight we have no qualms spilling
the whole secret to you that is if only you do us the smallest of favors do you guys know
pat why he's our second cousin that's like a cousin but thankfully a little more removed from
your gene pool the amount of dna shared between us is blessedly on the shallow side much like your
personality sister oh prince you're such a cut up much like how i cut up your invitation to the
met gala this year and fed it to the cat what but the theme this year was the monopoly mascot
and you know mittens the third is on a strict diet for her failing kidneys
yeah brother this nobody doesn't seem to be aware of who we are bless you indeed sister
perhaps with that pinstripe style they've spent the last 30 or so years locked in a storage closet
with their fingers in their ears and their other fingers in their eyes and fingers yet still in
their nose obviously since i've released that perfume this year obviously i am princess valentino
heir to the valentino fortune and this is my brother prince valentino he's also the heir
since we're twins i'm the evil twin they couldn't doesn't look weird when i do this on camera
they couldn't test for that gene and you know it prince you see our beloved daddy passed away
just recently from poison related complications you know the natural way we're splitting up our
shared inheritance but we could really use a mediator and someone to protect my beautiful
face from dear sister's punches it's true i punch super duper hard if only we had some help dividing
up daddy's precious possession i'm sure we could tell you the information you seek so will you help
us or do you have hobo king duties to attend to we need you i'm here use the checklist to assign
an item to each of the valentino twins can't leave until both wins are happy pay attention
to the indicator bar okay okay let's get on with this daddy's not getting any more alive
i'm already bored um okay how do i inherit the valentino inherit i must say and whatever
minx okay armor does that go to all right i gotta get these right the armor is gonna go to you
shiny damage and empty well it wouldn't be totally out of place with me i suppose
you take the minx stole too oh cozy just the kind of thing i like woman may throw the suffering of
another you can have the hat by the secret society hat i wondered if it'd been lost after
the swat race you'd have the wine too oh this really brings back oh didn't like that remember
when we walled up tipsy cousin cleo and the wine cellar after lowering her with the promise of an
even finer vintage oh how we laughed um you want the vinyl these are mostly complications of halloween
sound effects and scream so yes please give this to me what a weird thing what a weird thing
the sound halloween sound effects how do you record those right you need to record halloween
sound effects in a studio i don't think you can do that in like a home studio you have to be in
a place where no one's gonna no one will hear you it's a bunch of screaming and like oh please
like where can you even reliably do that would you guys buy it if would you guys buy a cd
if i made a halloween sound effects cd and sold it it was like like like three hours long of just
like background halloween sound effects all right you take no we don't like the photo
all right well i gotta even this out take the armor then i will be smashing with great
grandmother's clay more literally okay you can have the painting all right i really like the
painting it could have like a like an intro by bugleberry you're about to hear some of the most
horrifying halloween sound effects ever ever compiled yeah like an intro by bugleberry
okay maybe all right what about a sack of cash it has to be even right
ej's made of two parts endangered tiger one part great barrier reef daddy knew how to live
urn of ashes give that to you whoa okay never mind um what crystal orb halloween farts i mean
you understand the city is going to be just absolute horseshit right this is going to be
insane this is going to be just an insane like 25 track cd okay all right we need this need to be
even here you take the ashes and then you take the orb all right this is pretty good how about
the sports car all right we're almost there what about a blade no no it's not even all right so
what about the you take the vinyl okay that's that's it right there i got it shit does it have
to be full bro got four things well he's really happy about it what do you mean he's got tons
of stuff no you don't want to hurt okay you really like the photo you really like no you like the
sports car more you keep the sports car you like that armor more none of neither one of you like
this at all so you can take that back what about the photo all right you like the photo more
you like the hat more kind of you like the wine no no no no no no no no no what about the blade
all right you like the blade more what about the orb all right we're almost there you're full
shit no stay over there his memory is so bad they change they they change they change they change
urn of ashes okay they're so close the hat it's so goddamn close they change oh oh it's literally a
centimeter go back go back go back oh my god this it's something's one thing that needs to be
one thing what am i doing i just did it i just did it i just did it it's all of daddy's things
and i feel quite pleased with my hall and me as well i'm in such a good mood i'm almost feeling
feelings again here's a brother help pedestrian no please don't tell any of the servants they'll
start asking me for silver dollars or whatever they eat these days i guess we should thank you
bin stripes and tell you what you want to know about the event we won't the reward is our smiling
now get out of our car before we ring the police
i've been doing that why am i doing that i'm going like okay well that's cool
i still haven't pissed let's do that now i'm gonna piss i'll be right back
for you and whatever yeah i refilled my drink before i was getting a little dry
it's probably adding honey to his mint green tea no good hot chocolate all right let's go
there's a lot of first time chatters on this stream is it really what's going on how are you
welcome actually hi is it really a lot of people that are new we're just chilling this is a chill
stream just playing later alligator i'll be live tomorrow too i don't know what i'm gonna do
tomorrow maybe we'll figure it out in pre-stream and play webs or something or what's what's come
out what's new did anything come out recently star child i can feel your energy from over here
i'd say that's what's harshing my whole thing right now play rogue legacy 2 good in a lot of
rogue legacy too is it a good game what about infomercials this week uh i don't know maybe
let's see solid all right well let's let's keep going with this i say it's what's harshing my
whole thing right now but the truth is i've i i recycled some really gnarly bagels for lunch
today out of the dumpster behind the furniture store my mellow has been thoroughly pre-harshed
oh why would there be bagels in the dumpster of a furniture store oh throw pillows bummer listen
who among us um what's this what's the among us tune i don't know i actually don't know it
uh who among us hasn't woken up at noon in a van under a blanket felt it equally from stranger
lint and candy wrappers it's no wonder i got into the wrong dumpster if anything it's fate
going to the bar are you going to the birthday party tonight oh dude i'm sorry i really can't
tell you much i've been sworn to secrecy you know pat you say pat he's a pretty cool guy
kind of dresses like a preschooler though if i'm being realsies my little sister lizzie is
dating his cousin i guess you could say we're kind of like family you can say anything to strangers
really no one can stop you i'm aiden it's totally chill to meet you dot com dot org i sort of knew
someone would seek me out today i'm like a bit of a clairvoyant according to some sub forms i
visit online plus i own a somewhat unsettling amount of powerful crystals their potent energies
course through me in my inner core which is great since i spent the last of my dosh on some
suspiciously expensive crystals my inner core is super starving man all right what do i have to do
for you i could actually like probably tell you a few things if you do me a solid first you see
those suspiciously expensive crystals i mentioned earlier well those little mamas were also
suspiciously powerful from just three nights of holding them even when i had to get up to pee i
feel mystically charged enough to access my innermost self but in my tireless questing through
the crystal concentration arts i just don't have the time to shower or dust my pewter miniatures
besides bathing is a way for the man to keep us down you should be sliding across the floor on an
oil slick of your own creation like nature intended oh my aromatic scent keeps away a lot
of unwanted company like solicitors and my father but did invite others talking about flies these
little buzzing buzz kills keep harshing my mellow they're making it impossible for me to concentrate
on my inner light to do it inner right if you know what i mean if you could just swat them away from
me while i'm getting my medication my meditation on i'd be happy to do you a solid in return
will you be my spotter swatter let's go look on flies and hornets to attack them with the
fly swatter hornets take extra hits don't spot butterflies or aiden all right let's see see dad
i do have friends oops that was butterfly that's double that's happening the sub forms are right
i have to keep going these are loud
i can hit you right in the face with a fly swatter i'm feeling the cosmos
and i pick up wi-fi keep going i'm almost there that's kind of hard actually
hurtbox is huge yeah what time is it right now hello my star child through crystal channeling
and staying mod at least mod modestly hydrated like advised on social medias i've been able to
reach my most powerful form i'm still the aiden you've known and adored for so so long but a new
more powerful aiden as it were like how i haven't been paid in weeks i'm so hungry
oh just kidding i don't feel the human desire for food in my new astral mode hey did you hear an
ice cream truck no reason i just like the song the truck plays it's a real bop this is a twitter
what are you talking about oh i'm not crying i can now tell you a bit about the event since i'm
a being of pure energy and knowledge given form but also a being that's like extremely good at
keeping secrets man what little i can tell you is it concerns pat for a certain reason
that's really all i can say i don't want lizzie to get mad at me for spilling the beans
she's got those angry little sister hands even beings of pure peaceful energy are averse to
tiny sister punches thank you again for your spiritual guidance what you have done here today
will not soon be forgotten at least not for the 45 minutes of short-term memory i have
you hear an ice cream truck oh just go get a fucking ice cream and stop how is it oh shit
the party's at eight the party's at eight o'clock we got willing like another this is pretty much it
i'll say all jared oh hey didn't see you down there can you move about two centimeters to the
right the placement of my eyes is particularly wacky i'm waiting for a call but my phone has
been pretty dinked up lately i wonder if it'll even come in maybe i should ask the bartender
to use the phone here well that's not going to work since i stored the number i need here
in my broken phone how did anyone even get by before modern cell phone technology how did they
send each other messages or watch videos about people drinking a gallon of milk and throwing up
i guess i just have to write letters now and film myself barfing on vhs just like the pilgrims would
have okay oh you go into that too i tell you more about it but the saturated as i jotted down all
the deets in my phone here but the dang thing has been on the fritz for over a week now
yeah the song is good pat the alligator that's my little cousin all my cousins are little to me even
the older ones pat however is particularly small maybe that's why he's so skittish a guy that tiny
could slip into a crack anytime or get lost in a medium-sized mouse hole like a borrower or
something folks call me tall jared i don't really get it though honestly i'm not even the tallest
jared that i personally know yeah let that info sink in for a little while i can see your imagination
running wild in your extremely visible eyes all right remember you would like break core i don't
know what that is what is break core ever since i got back from that ghastly mansions of the rich
and dead before i did on my vacation what's really ghastly is the distribution of wealth among the
populace and the deadulous i don't know what i'm going to do my phone is my life literally
i don't have a rich inner existence or anything it's mostly all saved on here in the form of a
dream journal and pictures of good breakfasts i've had i don't know how much of a tech person you are
but do you think you could take a look it's okay it fixes cell phone what is break core
what is break for look up pac-man hold on this is like i'm not i can type this right
okay great someone said break core pac-man wait what am i putting on break core pac-man
i'll try i'll give this try oh no oh my god i i don't where is it i can't flip so go to youtube
just break core pac-man this is this one this one's called the prophet pac-man this one
welcome to the golden age of yoga is this the one you're talking about not this one which one any
break it doesn't matter oh just break core why did you want a book of pac-man this thing says cure
for adhd what this is a journey a journey which along the way this one dimension new values and
experience let's see if it works so our journey takes us into the field this is what's gonna work
four three two let's see if it works
this is crazy
i feel like i feel like there's a counter on the top right of the screen and it's at like one
minute left in an old video game and i have to hurry the fuck up and get to the end this is
great wow this is crazy what the fuck was that was a slap chop guy go go this is the only way you can
listen to this music that's like this is the only way you can listen to this music there's no other
way to listen to that there's only one way to listen to this music and it's like this
like i'm downloading all of the world's knowledge in one second like i'm downloading all of human
history there was there were the dinosaurs i just okay i just saw the uh i can't even talk
i can't even talk i'm downloading it's like matrix i'm gonna be alert i'm gonna like fly
okay turn it off that was insane there's other ones what if i skip forward a little whoa i feel
whoa all right there you are ready ready for this shit this is you like like mom comes in the room
this is all mom sees like you're at your computer let me see if i can line this up right like this
is the kind of music where it's just like whoa you're getting you're getting way too into that
i mean you're too close here i got i got you you're really locked in here and you don't know that
anyone's in the room and this person could literally just be in the room it could be like
your mom or like a sibling and somebody could literally just be like hey like you're ready for
dinner and this is all they see in here like kind of in through your headphones and it's gonna take
they're gonna have to go like go like this to your desk like imagine opening the door you just see
this like you can't get a hold of me you're never gonna get a hold of me put on this one that looks
bad what what do you mean stop what
i don't mean that like you don't come into the room he said you're listening to that
oh all right whatever what did i miss you didn't miss anything all i did was i was blasting a cure
for adhd and i just wanted to make it whatever this is wild though this is actually wild
it's so ridiculous i feel like after listening to this for like more than two or three minutes i
would just probably go like this like screaming put on what is this one that was intense but i
that was like really intense that was crazy parents walk in the sun break core circuit to
break core who is break core listening party break core is so good all right what is this one
this one's like kind of a scary album cover what's this one he's right this one what what
song should i put on you're opening my eyes i've never heard this before which one this is royalty
in break core is there a certain song there's a lot of songs here there's a lot of recommendations
here all right how about like this one's called ghost is this dmca is it all right this dmca uh
all right pretty sick all right i can see it all right i don't want to oh oh oh all right
i can play the goddamn game let's play the game where's this where's the fuck it stuck in my head
forever there's a crazy part right but like if you if you open the door and whoever's in there
can't fucking hear you but it's time for dinner like how are you going to get their attention
you like calling them maybe like a discord message right you're gonna like you're gonna
have to go through discord and like hopefully they go who's up you have to go shake them
i don't even think that would work flip the lights on up i don't think that would even work
like you're moving so much that like you like shaking them is like they're not gonna even know
you throw something at them like frisbee something into the room and it's like
like frisbees in and like stop stalling we're not stalling stalling stalling all these stalling
andies no no you know what that is that's just all the hardest difficulty on dance dance revolution
that's the one where you see the people that are standing with their arms holding the
they're holding the bar like this behind them and they're just like
like just a feet of fucking going crazy and you walk by and you're just like shit wow how are they
even doing that it's impossible that's what reminds me of you know i my brain is just too small to
like be able to do any of that stuff it looked like they're having a great time that was pretty
cool though i'll i'll i'll watch it off stream i'll listen to it off stream i'm i'm very intrigued
i've never heard of this before okay let's fix the phone i've never heard this before
all right we have to fix his phone and my notes are pretty personal oh dream journal i was in
the woods and i was running on all fours and there was a monster chasing me i'm at school and
everyone's making fun of me because i forgot all math i'm hungry look at myself in the mirror and
accept my father is looking back at me he turns into sand and now i'm holding two hams i have
fish hands is best dream ever you're violating this guy's privacy i have to fix his phone
error see i told you my phone was acting up error code 09590 a ghost all right grocery list
first crises large ham muffins paper towels cleaning spray dirtying spray good breakfast
sandwich bread peanut butter small ham it's a really good workout music i feel like that's
kind of music i would i would keep doing reps i wouldn't stop i would just keep going be like
that was 10 look we're doing we're doing 40 and you get to like 35 and have to go home
you know what i mean i'd be like ah i gotta go home now good breakfast okay i'm not working on
a video game i just thought these would be some cool ideas spooky game about three kids in a bad
summer camp cute game about a sweet knight who gets to escort four hot princes down a mountain
stupid mystery game about alligators in the city too much work dramatic game about mecha
pilots fighting over the fate of humanity and kissing okay what else we got video time when
i get really stressed i watch soothing videos it calms me alligator sensory meridian response
okay uh what about when train turn this is the third train schedule app i try but i'm still
late all the time okay pictures you're gonna look through my photos should i okay no i'm sure there's
embarrassing in there you want to look first that's my little sib joanie i caught them on
candid camera like food uh other do you look at that handsome fella i give myself compliments
every day it's like a workout for your self-esteem oh look at it when i found a a cute cafe how's that
did you do that with my phone turn off the flash jarrod well i would if i knew how
save my photo all right my vacation pics hope you're ready to relive some memories of me
hey my phone started acting after we went to this weird house oh it's this one delete that one
that was definitely strange all right you're gonna i gotta delete all the ghost pictures
it was nice being so close to the mountains all right we got all the ghost pictures
is there a ghost in this one no which one did i delete wait what is that isn't this a form of
anime it's from an anime don't mess with the spoiler i have a lot of pics that i really hate
to lose it's not the the camaraderie is important to me oh is that oh excuse me is that it wouldn't
happen to me uh go go what it's just so cool okay i don't care about those these whatever green
shots this code does something cool do you have a way to scan it i'm i'm scanning it i don't know
what that does in it let's get it i don't scan qr codes i don't know i don't scan qr codes no they
freak me out coward i don't scan qr codes they freak me out pictures all right internet splunker
i want to scan it no don't scan it who knows what it is it could be anything we'll scan it
what is it scan the code i i don't scan qr codes you're scared of ovens gas and qr codes
why don't you do it it's too it's too like algorithmic to me it's like i don't know it's
like too much it's like data i don't know i don't like it i don't know that's weird put it on screen
again oh i um there what is it it's literally just a barcode i know but it's it's weird like
why does that do anything why does this do anything what kind of alien technology if you
guys think don't think that we have alien technology that's alien technology you can you can what
that's a fucking ink blot that has data that doesn't make any sense well it's just it's like
a weird display of like data ink blot like pixels why can that give data it's strange
it's strange aliens created it i don't want it anymore
it's a video all right it's fun i'm not scanning it oh i'm not gonna scan it what happened to my
voice all right what's it like outside some people like sunny days some people like rainy days
i like the forecast one is just like this pretty good it's pretty good out 75 yeah i'd say like
78 to 85 is good okay what about like settings this screen this screen isn't helpful at all what
do you think ghost mode is what's your password don't look at my calls don't try to call anyone
either i'm sort of out of minutes i only have 22 seconds left and i still have to call my grandma
what's your password is it this i can't type it i can't type recent searches breakfast near
me breakfast many pancakes sleep sounds what's the best password ghost going to test the best
most secure password of anything is ghost you're welcome okay okay ghost uh ghost mode activated
a good good good ghost yes okay now i'm on ghost mode how am i on ghost mode good breakfast
i am hungry for a good breakfast okay all right what about like breakfast places don't delete that
one ghost mode no no no ghost here no ghost here don't see a ghost there ghost no ghost
no ghost there dude what no ghost no ghost i don't see a ghost whoa you deleted the mom and dad photo
oh i didn't where did my handsome swimming boys go no this is a nightmare get rid of it
oh god next time i go on vacation it'll be something safe like go-karting or at a nude
beach some more creepy old mansions with the dark legacies contaminated by the vengeful souls that
reside within i swear it i did it right that was terrifying can i have my phone back yeah there you
go why why are you assuming that that was his parents did you know that was the information
that those are his parents parents he didn't say that he didn't say that well he wasn't listening
i was no i was too busy fixing somebody's phone using telecommunications intelligence to do it
i was literally fixing his phone stop talking to me while i'm trying to fix your phone oh no my photo
so many memories all gone at least you got the haunted ones i guess nice to have a functioning
phone again it's like i'm reconnected to society take that actually looking people in the eye and
talking to them directly thanks random stranger or should i say random friend he deleted all of
his personal photos i don't know there could have been a ghost caterer for the event a lot of work
since the family is practically made of food allergies and intolerances but i'll manage
thanks so much for all your help i'll see you tonight by the way can you have wheat
not sure actually hey city pal i was just wondering since we've been texting a bunch
um have you heard of ninth street station at all oh yeah i didn't think so
it's uh well it's been closed for a few years i'd love going on there since then
still got some of the most beautiful architecture of all the underground shops in the city
i really like to go there actually i was just thinking um if you ever wanted to stop by there
maybe i could meet you no pressure or anything you could probably have to really help a conductor
out to even get access it's pretty underground awful okay i was actually on the floor that time
but i'd fallen unrelated to laughing anyway don't worry about ninth street you can forget what i
said if you want i mean i feel like i feel like i write like like bro dot dot dot relax bro
bobby blue eyes what are you staring at chump put those peepers away before i
yank them clear out of your skull oh you think you're a tough guy or something
you think you can roll in here in a pinstripe suit not dissimilar to my own and share a passing
glance with me well you got another thing coming to your belly and it ain't nothing good around
these parts i'm the toughest guy you're gonna meet i don't think you can slide into my bar and lock
eyes casually with me across the room you'll be sorry when i pull those babies out and smack them
into twin yokes i'll let you guess what the red sauce is but you're not gonna like it
what's at the event bobby ain't spilling family secrets pat oh that little jabroni is my first
cousin once removed kind of like how i'm about to remove your eyes as i previously in the
conversation mentioned three boys i'm doing it on purpose don't you get it don't you get it i'm
doing it on purpose you think the red sauce thing was too far maybe it was a bit too far
i'm testing out some new tough guy material tonight so it's a bit a hit or miss
eric cartman the name is bobby blue eyes and don't you forget it because it's going to be etched
into your tombstone oh wait on your tombstone it would be your name wouldn't it pal my name would
be hey it's because i got confused about our society rituals cow it is yeah you're right
doesn't mean you can look away we're having a conversation here all right what do you want me
to do unless you prove you're tough to me the toughest guy in alligator new york city
it ain't going to be easy though and i'll make sure that let's you and me play a little game
called three finger fillet or are you two chicken yeah let's do it carefully watch out bobby stabs
the table copy his pattern on your side be careful to avoid your fingers
oh sir looks like you've had a conversation with two fingers you ready for this tough guy
wow you did that four times that's impressive but how many more times do you think you can pull that
off shit but well five times let's up the ante bit shall we jesus whoa whoa what is that that
knife is terrific is a perfect for a tough guy uh let's keep going
so
not bad got all the way to six i bet you think you're a real tough guy with those increasingly
ludicrous knives you were weirdly having on your person edge check this out oh my finger
would you put a band-aid on it please oh ow ow got a blow on it blow on it
oh i said i don't want to play tough guys with you no more you ruined it by going too far and
now look what happened i may never play bass guitar again family badge you're a real tough
customer i'll give you that cow the event is happening the happy things will leave those
imposterous knives at home no go leaving my band-aid in my misery oh ouchy what time is it hey
are you there it's pat i know we haven't figured out what the family's totally nefarious secret is
yet well maybe if we walked there together i feel safer is that okay on my way all right here we go
we have to go talk to majima i don't know i i think i've beat the game did i who's that
fifth william the fourth well hello and pleasant evening my good chum i didn't mean to startle you
oh no i didn't mean to startle you not i you see it is within my very nature
skulk mysteriously around corners and the like in depth silence as my mother was a mysterious
slipper designer my father was a mysteriously absent are we ready for surprise here we go
three what time is it seven o'clock it's weird too we're early aren't we early we're early welcome
back esteemed guest i'm afraid our kitchen is closed early for a closed event in the hotel
ballroom tonight i provided mr pat with some complimentary stale oyster crackers and tap water
if you follow me i can show you to his room pardon me will we begin walking at your leisure
what beautiful wallpaper we have so rich and distracting i like the art i like the
kind of reminds me of um oh movies you're right please inform mr pat he can't have any more tap
waters after you knock are you ready to go to the party just been guzzling tap waters and stress
eating these funny crackers the waiter gave me even though i'm not going to wear them i went and
got all my shoes out anyways i think just for the company scary being alone in here now the
event is about to begin but maybe since you're here nothing bad will happen this counts as
something bad happening do you have a flashlight i'm scared of the dark and of flashlights but
slightly less so you found one do i look like that one video by alligator queen hopefully with
this we can make it through the corridors of the hotel to the ballroom where the event is safely
just walk really close to me okay we have no way of telling who or what is out in those twisty halls
oh boy hours out click and hold the guide path to the dark hotel
go this way no i thought it was a staircase at first we're good i'm huge a reminder of the
inevitable passage of time that will one day consume us all into the infinite also i can't
read analog clocks i didn't think i was gonna really just completely be level with this character
but i get him now completely get you man or either that or he's high as fuck one or the other
where do i go how do i go oh what was this staircase okay i was like i thought it was a
wall oh he's anything but marty that's actually really scary is he gonna chase us i'm gonna say
right so it's the weird guy from the uh train did you see it move i think i saw it move this is the
weird guy from the train or the boss or whatever there's just something unwholesome about reading
graphic novels in the pitch dark sediment of a broken hotel wall all right so this is the wrong
way silent hill oh i was the guy from the loading screen oh mandy i'd ask what he's doing here but
he's attracted to spotlights like a moth that smells like hair gel i made it here we go here
was a big surprise it was a birthday party happy birthday
oh everyone's here well at least the people that i talked to
it's just the people that i thought that i'd talk to that's cute look at this everyone's here
everyone's having a good time what's up old and moldy you down for another heist sorry to pull
you back in the game but with a cake like this how can you resist one last score this is the worst
party i've ever been to it's simply dreadful even worse than last year's even worse than the rap
party for the gucci modeling shoot i did that's gucci adult-sized baby bonnets for strange
alligators even worse than the release party where they found my ex-boyfriend the house music dj
run through with a claymore excuse me i for one wasn't anywhere near there of course but how awful
simply dreadful oh here's the singing alligators happy birthday to you you live in a zoo you smell
like an alligator and that is unsuspicious and correct oh we already saw you we gave her the
claymore oh that's right oh that because they're sitting across from each other all right what
about grandma first year it's been a dog's age since i've been to a swinging shindig you know
of any i've just kidding ha ha mostly on my way over i passed that abandoned miss poopledooms home
for spooky 1800s children with coughs they wouldn't you know it my phone stopped working again all it
does now is sing ring around the rosie in a slow haunting manner and try to order a stick and hoop
with my credit card so when when we got a oh there's more people well star child my interest
you in a flyer for my upcoming crystal yoga class we're going to stand on our heads and really give
it to some quartz there's also going to be free pizza in the dumpster outside italian tony's
cheese circles like bellissimo or whatever this is like happy good evening and good morrow friend
what an auspicious sign that we have crossed paths once more perhaps with some unknown star
designed connection or you really want to read about my zine about cool wizards check it out i
have a chapter dedicated to toad tapicus the groovy hey there i got worried you guys wouldn't make it
on account of the blackout that's scared of the dark and hallways and parties come to think of it
this usually doesn't end as well as this is what i'm saying oh i'm so proud of my patrick he didn't
threaten a coat rack shadow with a stapler and jump out a window or dump the punch bowl in the
toilet thinking it was poison this is already going so much better than his birthday last year
oh my god i'm gonna lose my aarp discounts being up this late they take a hard look at your
benefits if you do too much staying up past eight or rollerblading i'm not giving up my tuesdays at
roller world tell anyone about what you saw earlier and i'll break your kneecaps into enough pieces
that the old maids can play mahjong and thanks pal hey uh bitter there old paly it's time for
an old-fashioned handshake this is more the snail trail i'm told it's full of vitamins and helps
with drying and that it comes with my out my limbs and leaves you crying oh hey where you going
only a couple more of course and i have come to an understanding of sorts wherein he remains dead
and courteous and i don't call in a priest or buy any more poisons wholesale hey it's you comrade
pinstripes good news pre-orders on my blog for the zine are through the roof since five copies
are already spoken for i'm sure to sell out of all seven by the end of the convention with the word
getting out like this we'll definitely get mayor wibbly finn's resignation within the week or at
least he might take my petition about planting more trees an alligator memorial park more seriously
be better or those edited videos of him set to humorous fart sounds and kazoom music aren't
going to stop being posted to snootbook hold your local government accountable or they'll get in
memeing all right sure whatever all right and of course our esteemed guest i'm sure happy
i wasn't getting rubbed out i was getting birthday clout so nice to have my beloved family here with
me we're going to take a big family photo and everything that means you too that's okay
everything you did for me today it really meant so much to me you're a really special friend i
can't thank you enough oh come on everything is ready for the photo except for you follow me
so we're gonna see the face face reveal face reveal oh my god definitely this one or this one
it's it's of course who could have forgot me alligator birdie sentence i just really wanted
to try to bring people together is that good all right that's it why am i in the front this is not
my birthday party i should be like back here congratulations that's cute that was cute that
was really cute yeah come on the game has won the story and sweet but though it seems done has this
all been deceit what's really going on does our tale end right here the more family you come upon
the more truth will grow clear that was an actual that was actually a children's game
oh that was an e for everyone game okay it's e for everyone there's a true ending you got a 100
percent the game for a true ending do a bread tier list right now or i'm gonna be pissed do you have
a bread tier list for me to do is there a bread tier list that you would like me to do i'll do it
right now okay a bread tier list it doesn't exist you unlock pat game skip more mysteries await you
in alligator new york city oh jeez that was really cool quick find one i'm sure it doesn't it does
not exist do people actually have one you actually have one there's a certain character everyone
wants me to talk to so i'm gonna go do that first before everybody yells at me where is it okay one
of the mods grab one of the links are not allowed in the channel the credits were like a who's who
of funny web animators that's cool bread types tier list okay where's this character you guys
want me to where is it where are they they're in the bar okay where are they in the back
are them okay this this of there's so many of these this one looks fine okay i got i have a
bread tier list here we'll do this first the night leave me alone as you want a knuckle sandwich
seriously do you want it it was the bar special of the day but i ain't got the heart to eat it now
because uh nervous guts anyway what do you want i don't really have time to talk now i'm waiting
for somebody but maybe they're in no show okay you keep pestering me didn't i tell you i was
waiting for someone yeah i know pat who's asking oh you are right right sorry i'm a little socially
anxious right now basically all the time i've known pat since high school when the seniors
got paired up with a freshman buddy to run the three-legged race as the gym teacher tied the
rope around our legs pat flipped out and thought he was being kidnapped and running like a maniac
down the football field with my gym pants still attached to it it's how i got my other nickname
birthmark but since then we've been good pals despite it love that weird little guy
people call me the knife on account of my design containing sharp edges and how i poked my eye out
in a freak jack-o-lantern carving accident back in the fourth grade because i'll cut you out of
extracurriculars if i catch you in the hall without a pass i'm a guidance counselor for miss petty
snoot school for snobby and gifted middle schoolers my nickname is just there to scare the
pre-teens to be honest all right what do you what do you want to do i gotta be honest with you i
ain't really waiting for nobody i'm just here at the bar to practice being casual and meeting
other folks you know in a romantical like manner but i always seem to say the wrong thing and scare
the other gators off how was i supposed to know complimenting someone's bulging neck veins was
weird i have those look real cool anyways between work and my somewhat bad personality i don't get
out much it's so hard to just meet people in non-weird ways you know i wish i could just
practice or something wait a minute that ain't a bad idea if i could just find a buddy to practice
dates on i could be way more ready when the real deal comes along i know you're only talking to me
because pat set you up on one of his weird wild goose-like chases i ain't got a lot of friends
to tell you the truth so uh maybe if you help me practice i could help you out too i want to go on
a fake date with a rusty edge like me yeah let's go take a lonely lizard out on a practice date
but to decide where to go what to do and how you end the evening great how do you feel about a
change of setting let's head over to my workplace and you can help me out there all right what the
fuck followed calls of the alligator international school for gifted youths kids are on break right
now so it's only us lonely administrators me i'm the lonely one i need a big favor from you you see
i have a meat i have a meat cute tomorrow i don't know what to do or say or feel
my friend karen who works in the front office set me up with a friend of hers
sorry i'm not usually the blind date type she says she's he's really dreamy tall which i like
and big which i also like broad shoulders she says he's cool quiet type but he has a sense of
humor and a big heart and between you and me she said he's a real dragon in the dojima if you
catch my drift i wonder what she told him about me while this negative thinking is messing with
my mojo he seemed like the strong silent type and you're cute enough that it intimidates me
just a little please you gotta help me practice for my big date i need a boost of confidence
and i need it now yay i mean uh cool thanks karen arranged it all with my date
we're going on an adventure first then out to dinner then afterwards who knows
laughter so um what kind of adventure would you like to take me on remember it's me i would like
to take you to a trip to the beach great let's go well come on i can't pretend for going somewhere
if we don't go somewhere those schools empty don't worry hey the beach is pretty nice this time of
year that's a sweet idea i know it's not really the beach we're playing pretend remember it's
only our first date i didn't bring a towel or swim trunks for sunscreen i agree can i take that
again i do that take again plus we're going to dinner later am i going to be all sandy at the
restaurant oh you're okay with walking along the boardwalk well that's nice my mystery date
probably looks great in swim trunks though this is fine actually i'm glad we're doing this it's
been a while since i've been on a real date like with an itinerary everyone i date these days just
wants to watch a tv show on an old couch don't get me wrong i'm above staying in and getting cozy
but i think a first date should be really special you know hmm what's this you brought me a present
but i didn't bring you anything well that is a change old-fashioned button in a nice way
gimme gimme i got you a cute toy oh look at that thank you i'll have to find a nice place to put it
i'm getting a little hungry do you mind if we head to the dinner a reservation
should i keep going or people gonna hate me people gonna literally leave the channel forever
all right i need a mod to run a poll and post say are you going to leave if i keep doing this
but the answer is yes or no i guess it's a simple yes or no question let me give you a quick little
taste of what it's going to be like a reservation wow you came prepared that's just a quick little
taste of what you could expect that's a quick little just taste about okay 12 percent say yes
and dress to impress i see that shirt really brings out your eyes was that too much i'm trying
to roleplay but it feels a little silly you're doing great now so where do you want to eat i
heard you were quite the foodie somewhere cozy hmm quiet and intimate sounds nice i now am going
to pivot to every old man character and every anime that's ever released we'll really be able
to get to know each other it's so nice that you have a local place too i've been living in the
city for five years and i finally have my coffee place oh yeah it was a big adjustment the city
is always moving i was living across the river in alligator new jersey back then please don't
ask me about those dark times there definitely weren't any cute snoots in alligator oboken
not like you now we're leaving all right i will switch back to the protagonist
there definitely weren't any cute snoots in alligator oboken not like you hey let's head
over to the restaurant oh this place is nice i like that decor isn't too pretentious so do you
come here often you're so right i barely make it out of the house myself these days i'm so happy
to be here meeting someone new say now it's your chance give me a compliment you've got perfect
teeth thanks you have a nice smile too this is me role playing at awkward silence
come on my date's got to be more charming than that i'm going to pretend you said i was cute and
move on i feel like i can really be myself around you it's been a while since i've done this i mean
not a long while it's just hard for me to meet other alligators i know a lot of you said no but
i feel like a lot of you actually meant yes do i keep going this is gonna literally ruin my career
i think this is gonna end the whole i think it's gonna ruin my career stop laughing this is
precisely why i wanted to practice what i'm trying to say i'm having a really good time with you
if you don't have any plans after dinner want to come to the spring festival with me
i think i'm ruined i think my career is over if double down quick all right you're right double
down when in doubt double down you lived in alligator new york city for how long and you've
never been to the east river spring festival and then you have to come with me there's food carnival
games and the whole thing ends with a big fireworks show what do you say we split the
check and head over flag down the waiter then let's get out of here double down always sorry
i'm being such a kid even when we lived in alligator jersey my family would drive into the city for the
big festival thanks for indulging me as a reward you get to pick the first thing we do no no i've
been coming here since i was little it's your first time what looks fun to you i'm done i'm done i'm
literally done because like try triple down triple down i have to try i'll triple down
try triple down i'm gonna triple down let's play i'll triple down oh i love carnival games
jaren told me you were pretty competitive not like in a bad way i'll tell you what if you win me that
big platter of stone i'll definitely be impressed a reward with the game first buddy and then we'll
i was wearing a solid snake now what a night that guy in the beer costume and all the pretty lights
you know for a first timer you really seem to be warming up to the festival i'm done i'm
gonna quit i quit streaming i mean i actually quit streaming i'm relieved you had fun you never know
this i quit streaming i really wanted to have a good time to be honest i wasn't sure i was even
going to come out tonight i'm doing it my on my own a lot of people are scared of me would you
believe me it's not like i'm some kind of scary gangster roaming the streets at night and showing
up whenever repeatedly challenging the same person to endless street brawls while slowly building my
reputation as a mad dog who will fight anyone and anything relentlessly punishing all who stand in
the way of my personal goals hey it looks like the fireworks are starting come with me i know
the perfect place to watch i quit streaming i quit i literally quit today what i tell you the view
from here is incredible right i had fun tonight i hope you did too for karen's sake i mean she
takes matchmaking really seriously and she's been hounding me for months to finally meet you
oh why am i talking about karen right now come on go ahead just say the right thing
bod should i quit bod should i quit stream all right i guess what i'm really trying to say here
is i'm so glad to meet you you seem like a great person and i was really cool hanging out with you
we should do this again sometime oh god you should you should step tubble i failed
okay let's do a bread tier list i don't give a shit