Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as that.
So, in this video I want to talk about a couple of things, as we usually do in these casual commentaries.
Sometimes I do stuff like that and I lose track of what time I'm in and what is the area of the world I'm in, so that would just happen right there.
Anyways, fucking let's go, get it together. This video is gonna talk about my server. First of all, I'll give you a little story about my server.
Those of you that have been trying to play on it the last few days, the last week, it's actually been like two weeks. I don't know, who am I kidding?
Here's a story. So, I forgot to pay the bill on my TF2 server. If you have no idea what I'm talking about, I had a TF2 Team Fortress 2 server that I had there was no crit.
There were no ads or anything on it. It was just there for you guys to play on if you wanted to play some games on it, make a few friends.
I know there was a community behind it, and that's awesome that I would go there from time to time.
You've seen a lot of videos on this channel of me in the server doing weird, crazy shit, and that's how I like it. That's how I want to keep it.
I didn't pay the bill on time, and they deleted the server because I didn't pay it, which, whatever, that's fine.
I have now a new server. It's a brand new IP. The IP that you currently had, get it out of your memory, delete it from your brain.
I'm going to change it in all the places where it says where my IP is for the server.
It's currently getting up and running right now by my server administrator, so I don't know if it's going to be there right now.
In the description of this video, there's going to be the IP.
If you try it, it might not be up and running at this particular moment right now, but that's going to be the IP.
If you can't find it in the server browser or if it just doesn't work, you can't connect to it, then just give it a couple days.
There's probably going to be some lag issues because on new servers, there's always lag for the first couple of weeks when the server kind of gets its bearings.
So bear with me for a little bit while I get that back up and running.
And if you had no idea that I had a TF2 server, and you do now, so we're going to move on from that.
I just wanted to give you guys a little update on how that was coming if you were curious.
And the next thing I want to talk about is about the Team Fortress community.
It's about the Valve community, something ridiculous that was just reported on this last week on money.
If you don't know, Valve just recently in the first week of January paid out $400,000 to its various content creators.
I'm not talking about Valve employees.
We're not talking about like Bob from accounting.
We're talking about people that make maps, that make custom weapons for the Steam Workshop.
Really anybody that has made anything that's been implemented into either Team Fortress 2 or Dota 2 just got a pretty big paycheck.
And this is incredibly encouraging to me.
This is like the best, awesome, most unbelievable news because it shows that you can actually make a couple bucks on the side.
I mean, we've talked about this before in previous videos where I've said I love when Valve does this community-driven stuff.
People can get involved in their favorite games.
If they're an artist or if they're a map maker or if they're a designer, they can actually do this on the side.
They don't have to work for some company.
They can actually put time and effort into their favorite thing, the thing that they're passionate about, and make some money.
And not just some money, $400,000 in a week, the first week of January of 2014.
Are you shitting me? That's ridiculous.
Almost half a million dollars has been paid out to these people in one week.
This is not over 10 years.
This is not since the Steam Workshop has been implemented.
This is in the first goddamn week of 2014, 400 grand.
Can you imagine? Imagine this, guys.
Imagine in a few months what that number potentially will be.
Imagine in a few more months after that what that number potentially will be.
I can't even make the math. I can't even do the calculations in my brain because, oh my God, it's probably going to be millions of fucking dollars.
And I really, truly hope, guys, that these numbers that came up from Valve will show the companies that don't want to open up their games from modding.
Don't want to open up their games to their communities.
Don't want to show, hey, there's actually talented people in our community.
There's actually people that play our games that are incredibly imaginative and can create things and know what they're doing when it comes to design.
Like, I hope it opens up because we just keep getting proven time and time again that modders and community members are what push a game into a longer lifespan.
And rewarding those people, rewarding those that do these things, is just great for the overall life essence of the game.
It just is.
And these companies that close their doors to this type of stuff, you know, the two CEOs, the three guys that know the secret recipe to Coca-Cola,
who gives a shit?
Like, who doesn't know how to make Coca-Cola?
Pepsi does.
Sam's Choice does.
The dollar store does.
Do you really have to keep Coca-Cola as a secret?
Open up your fucking business to people and people will like you more.
The more that you put yourself out there and the more that you tell people and you show people that you're willing to accept what they're willing to do for you, the better you're going to be.
So give me the fucking secret recipe for Coca-Cola.
That's the end of the video.
I want the secret recipe for Coca-Cola.
Give me it!
Give me the secret recipe!