How is it going? What's up? How you doing? I got the urge to play who wants to be a millionaire.
I want to play it. I know that there was some thoughts of what would happen today. What would
happen in the next few streams. But I was like, you know what? I want to play that. Sounds fun.
Sounds like a good time. Why are you at the Red Bull thing? Oh, I've seen the clip a few times.
Also, off-brand was on that show. So I was like, you know what? Maybe I'll pop in.
Say hello. So off-brand was doing some work on that show. I was able to kind of peek in,
say hello. Are you the sus guy? Ban that person for like a week. At least. I mean at least a week.
Hey, good morning, kid. Hey, good morning. Good morning, wherever you are.
Get a load of this guy. Yeah. What's up? It was great to see Ster and Ashley. It's actually
been a long time since we've been able just to kind of hang out somewhere.
So that was really wonderful. Really great to see them. It's been a while. It was really great,
though. I got to go pee. Well, you got to. You have a few minutes. Go ahead. Hurry up.
Well, no, take your time. Whatever you need to do. I know you already played Monkey Island,
but you should play it on stream. Would you guys like a Monkey Island stream? Didn't they do a new?
Isn't there like a new game? They made a new game. I feel like I played it for a little bit.
Just jumping around on a only game pass or something, right? Of course it was on game
pass. Have you seen Barbie yet? No. No, I haven't. I've been pretty busy. I haven't really had much
time to go see a movie or anything. You should play Pikmin 4. Did I even play Pikmin 3? I don't
remember. What about Mission Impossible? What about TMNT? What about Oppenheimer? Yeah, there's a lot
of movies that I just haven't watched. What happened to Toontown? Heard on Stirstream that
you got sick. Yeah. So let me give you just a brief synopsis of that. So Ster and Ashley were here
and it was a great time. It was a wonderful time. I want to say the second day they were here,
I got food poisoning and it was just me. I was the only one. It was bad and I thought the whole
trip was going to get ruined. I was like, oh no, here I am up here going through it so bad.
I cannot wait to... Well, not I cannot wait, but I know I'm going to go talk to Ster and it's going
to be, oh yeah, dude, I got it too. Or like Holly, I got it too. Or Ashley, I got it too.
No, I was the only one. It was just me. I must've been the sorry asshole that touched the thing or
ate the thing, whatever it was. And it fucked me up big time for like 12 hours. After 12 hours,
I was immediately cured. So that's how I know it was a temporary food poisoning thing. That sucked,
but I'm really, really glad that it was just a quick, really, really fast turnaround. You never
did your smurfs homework. No, I don't. And I'm not going to. Give me an F in that class.
But everything going through my mind during that was, oh God, I'm going to, I don't want to ruin
this whole trip. I have to be better. I have to get better. And I was fine. So thankfully,
happy to report that I am completely fine. And I was completely fine after like a day.
A super F. Where? Not from my end. I don't see anything here. Hey, I can confirm your
tuna sandwich is great. I added eggs to it. So I hope that's okay. Spin it however you want.
Oh, F on homework. Oh, anytime I see F, I freak out. That letter has turned into just,
it's like, if I see the letter F, it's a pan, it's panic mode. Something's wrong with my stream.
If I see the capital letter F, there is something wrong that I need to go look at my stream setup
right now. I'll give you a grotto beast update. The grotto beast tabletop mod digital version
is very, very, very close. Keep your eyes peeled over the next week or so. Keep your eyes peeled.
Keep an ear to the ground over the next seven days or so. It looks great. The team is doing
an amazing job. I had the opportunity to see how it's going for a while and I like what I see.
Really cool. Should be a really fun place to hang out for those of you that just want to play it.
Rather than having to do it in person or somehow figure out a way to play with somebody that you
don't really know. I don't like the way that my skin feels. I don't know how to answer that
question, but good luck. Do we get a free copy of the digital version if we bought the starter pack?
The digital version, the tabletop simulator version is just free. It's just completely free.
No one has to pay anything. It's just a mod. Well, you have to own tabletop simulator.
It's just going to be a mod we fought with for a long time how to do that.
But it's like, how do we charge for that? Why? I don't think I want to charge for that.
Prado Beast was such a success. I don't think it's appropriate to charge for that either,
if I'm honest. So just a fun place for you to play it digitally. I have tabletop sim with
the Pepe hands up. Oh, nice. You're a terrible businessman. Yeah, whatever. You're built like
a shampoo bottle. I'm pretty sick. Can I take a loan out here? No. How come you have a mullet?
This is fun. Don't you have to pay people? Well, yeah. Don't worry. It's all good. Okay, don't
worry. I assure you, it's going to be fine. Why do you hate Steve Jackson's story? Hey, it's funny
you say that. We're going back to sorcery. The next stream. There you go. There you go. The next
time this stream is live after today, it's going to be sorcery part four. How do you feel about
that? And then get the trumpet ready. This coming weekend, not this weekend, but next weekend. So
Friday, Saturday, Sunday, 18, 1920. I'm trying to get the MVM group off the ground. So tentatively
trying to maybe figure out maybe next weekend, be like Saturday or Sunday, maybe Friday. We're
kind of trying to see if I can get the group that I wanted to have play play. That should be fun.
Looking forward to that. What about Baldur Baldur's Gate three? I don't know if I want to stream
Baldur's Gate three, because I feel like I would make a character get into the actual game,
throw a rock at somebody, get like arrested in the game, poop my pants or something, and then
be like, I'm kind of done. Because like the actual video game Baldur's Gate, I have no idea even how
it plays. I know it's like third person, but it's top down. But I don't know anything about it.
That sounds like a great stream. Maybe it's D&D. It's basically just D&D on computer.
I mean, it looks fun. It looks really fleshed out. Just everyone's talking about it. I'm getting the
FOMO. I'm getting Baldur's Gate three FOMO. I'm seeing holy shit. This is the greatest single
experience I've ever experienced in my entire life. It's like, holy shit. Okay. I should probably get
it. Do I get it? And you see like the characters people are making. It's like, whoa, okay.
All right. You can make characters and stuff. That sounds fun. So I'm getting Baldur's Gate
FOMO. See if it turns into anything. It's kind of that good, dude. It's sort of that good, really.
All right. Well, all right. Let's get started. I want to just kind of hang up.
Had a pretty busy week. Obviously, if you didn't know, Ster and Ashley were here. I had a wonderful
time. Besides shitting my brains out for 12 hours. But hey, hey, sometimes stuff just happens.
Life is going to throw shit at you. And you got to be ready to you got to be ready to adapt.
You know what I'm saying? What do you mean, huh? Your milk voice hurts my eyes.
Well, you're listening to it. You're not looking at it. You didn't say, did you say that you were
shitting for 12 hours? No, but I did now. Now you know. I like this creamy voice.
I got like this creamy voice. You played manhunt like a while ago. Hey, I still haven't done my
Smurfs homework. I just just know. You know, it's funny about the Smurfs homework. I assigned it
and I didn't even do it. I assigned the homework. I wonder how many of you watched the Smurfs movie
took a bunch of notes and were ready for class. And the teacher just didn't even bring the
textbook in. Yeah, you you kids go ahead and go go do this math assignment and bring it in when
you're done. Okay, I did the math assignment. It's three days later. It's a week later.
Yeah, we're not doing that shit anymore. We're moving on to it. We're talking about rocks today
and where they come from. You know, it's lava. It's lava. You know that? I did. I did. I'm the
teacher. I know more than kids. Yeah, lava rocks. Isn't that cool? All right, let's play who wants
to be a millionaire is going to hang out. I'm really into the hangout streams lately, as you're
probably well aware. Let's go. Let's see if I can get past $32,000 because it's definitely not
happening. Maybe it will. All right, let's go. I'm going to play as Pablo. Don't help me either. I
don't want any help. If anybody gives any help, they're going to get banned. Is this like an anime?
Can I skip the intro or people get mad at me? All right, here we go. Dude, this is a landmark of San
Francisco. I might just get this wrong. The silver porch bridge, the bronze door bridge.
Okay, it's gold. It's gold. The silver porch bridge. All right, that's 100 bucks. Easy.
Which of these is a cosmetic in cream or cake form used as a base for makeup? Foundation.
It's foundation. It's D. 200 bucks. Easy. What animal found when he was abandoned in the jungle
as a baby? Oh, okay. It's neither one of these two. Oh, wait, I can cheat. People in chat can
just tell me what the answer is. It's one of these two. Blue? I don't think it's blue. I think this
is it. I actually was going to pick that one. I even told you it's not one of these two. I told
you. I wasn't cheating. I actually was going to pick that one. Complete the name at the end of
the saying, meaning it'll be done immediately before you can say Jim Parkinson, John Tompkinson,
Jack Robinson, James Donaldson. It'll be done before you can say Jim Parkinson, John Tompkinson.
I have no idea. I actually have absolutely no idea who says this before you can say
James Donaldson. All right, I have to do this. Jack Robinson. How would this many people know
that it'll be done before you can say Jack Robinson? I guess it's correct. Is it British?
Okay. The offense of willfully telling an untruth in a court after having taken an
oath is known as treason, perjury, arson. Oh yeah, arson. That's perjury. Nice. $1,000 for good.
What is the common name for the decompression sickness that is a threat to divers? I don't
know. C? This is the one I was going to pick. C. No help. No, that wasn't help. It's not the curves.
The game. Llama is a title for a spiritual leader in which religion? Llama? Llama? I don't think
it's A. Give me a new question. So let's change the question. I don't know. Town of Telford is
named after Thomas Telford, who was famous in which field? This is even, this is even harder.
It's probably finance. I feel like it's finance because the, do you have like a bunch of money
and like, I'm naming this town after me because I have a shitload of money. Does that make sense?
How long ago is this? I can't reliably say. Let's call somebody. It's only the $2,000 question. This
is a disaster. All right. Who am I going to call? I'm going to call, uh, son, wife, sister, granddaughter.
Wait, this is my granddaughter. All right. I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll call Zelda, my wife.
This is who wants to be a millionaire and Pablo needs your wisdom. Well, I'm going to do my best.
Zelda, you're my last hope on this one, but don't put too much pressure on yourself. Okay.
Not too much. It's C. No doubts whatsoever. No doubt. Okay. I'm, I'm going to go with C.
Okay. C. Damn. Got it. 4,000 the furthest I've ever been to a good start, but you shouldn't stop
there. Okay. By what name is the writer Charles Lutwidge Dawgson better known? Charles Lutwidge,
Lutwidge Dawgson, Charles Lutwidge Dawgson. I don't know who any of these people are.
Okay. I'm going to see. Oh shit. Well, I'm dead. Oh, that's not something you should say.
All right. Well, whatever. That was a warmup. That's a warmup. It's fine. By the way,
this doesn't really matter because I have so, I don't even know how I got so many of these.
How do I have a million points? Did I cheat? Wait, how did this happen? How did I get a
million points? I don't understand how this happened. I really don't understand it.
I opened this and had the same reaction. I was like, what? Only do food? A million neurons.
Uh, okay. I, there's some of these, I just don't know if I really want it. I don't have like really
good answers to. Should we only do superheroes? Should we only do Star Wars and Disney? I guess
this one makes sense. Should I just do them all? Who cares? Superheroes and Star Wars only.
Whatever. You don't know much. Yeah. I mean, that doesn't really matter. Does it?
How did you not know the answer to Llama? I don't know. All right. Here we go. Here we go. I'm
ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm going for it. I'm going to get to at least 32,000.
Guaranteed. Guaranteed this time. Who's the main character of Breaking Bad? Uh, Walter Green.
It would say D. Nice answer. Let's go for this new eliminatory question.
What does a person use to prevent sweat? Antiperspirant. Ant, uh, I did not use any
of these sides of this one. C is the right answer. I would state my life. Antimatter.
Going quick. Moving quick now. Which Hollywood studio made the films Dumbo and 101 Dalmatians?
Disney. Yeah. See? On what planet do the Wookiees live? Oh, shit. I should, I need, wait.
I don't know. I think it's one of these two. I'm not looking at chat. I'm not. I'm going to be,
people are going to think I'm a fucking idiot if I get this wrong.
Okay. I had a feeling. I know there's no way to verify if I'm cheating or not,
but I'm sure you are not. Who directed the film Star Wars The Last Jedi?
Uh, that would be Rian Johnson. I hope I get three Star Wars questions in a row.
Oh, I know this one. I know this one. Bad chest. What name is given to a single gemstone and a
piece of jewelry? It's a, put it on emote only. Yeah. Put an emote only for a little bit. Just so
I can verify that I'm not cheating. It's a single. That was completely wrong. All right. Whatever.
I have a million neurons. You guys think you're smart? I got a million fucking neurons up here.
A million. I have a million neurons. You're curious about the joke of this is most humans have
trillions of neurons. So therefore having a million neurons sounds like a large number,
but it's absolutely not. It's a small number. Just want to make sure everyone understands the
comedic, uh, the comedic process there. Okay. Yeah. Emote only. Let's go. Emote only.
Why? All right. I see. I don't need any help. I'll get it. What is the plural of mouse?
Easy. Which word follows tug life and row to give three other terms? What? What word follows tug
life? To row to give three other terms. Wait, what is this? What's this? What's this asking
to give three other terms? I mean, it's boat. It's boat, tugboat, lifeboat, rowboat. I don't,
this question is weird to me. It's a weird question. I mean, I, there's a weird question.
What is the national airline of Ireland? Air shamrock, air shellag, aeroplane, air lingus.
All right. I like that. If it's not that it should be, uh, why do I feel like it's this one?
It's not this one. It's this one. It's, it's air lingus. It's air lingus. It's air lingus.
Yeah. Okay. All right. All right. See? Yeah. I'm not cheating. The Catholic nun born of Albanian
parents and known for her work with Calcutta's poor was mother who? Mother Teresa. Give me that
thousand bucks. Oh yeah. What is the name of the prequel to Monsters Inc? I don't know. Monsters
Inc 2? I don't know this. I actually have no idea. I think it's Monsters University. That sounds
the most correct to me. I've, I didn't, I never said I'd never saw this. I think it's Monsters
University. All right. Where were you at on the pyramid? All right. This is a thousand, a thousand.
I've got all my lifelines. I'm good. The names of how many U S states begin with the letter K?
Um, that's Kansas, Kentucky. A lot of states have the letter K in Alaska, Oklahoma, Nebraska,
right? I think this is why they're trying to throw you off here. I think it's just two Kansas and
Kentucky. It's two. Yeah, it's two. That's a trick question because a lot of states have K in,
in it. You see what I'm doing? The game is getting tougher now with this brand new question. What
American drag queen plays the main role in the Netflix series AJ and the queen? Del Rio? Paul?
Actually, I don't know. I don't know. You have to find the right answer. I don't think it's
RuPaul. No, I'm going to have to ask. I'm going to have to ask the audience on this one.
Okay. I apparently was completely wrong. We're going to go with RuPaul.
Oh, okay. All right. All right. All right. I'm at 2000, 2000.
We'll be asked a new question now. How old was Ronald Reagan when he was inaugurated as president?
I don't have any idea. 49, 59, 69 or 79. I don't think it's 49. Uh, I don't think it's 79 either.
Maybe it was. I don't know. I'm going to say probably 59. 59. I'm going 79. I feel like that's
right. No, it's not. Wait, how long ago is this? This was, I'm saying 59 and I'm going for it.
I'm not confident though. I have to call somebody. You decide to play the life.
All right. We're going to, who wouldn't know this? All right, Zelda. You're going to come through
again. I was going to say 59. Good evening. This is who wants to be a millionaire and Pablo needs
your wisdom. Zelda, you're my last hope on this one, but don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Okay. Not too much. But when was Ronald Reagan? I would have chosen C, but then again, I'm not sure
about it. All right. Thanks for nothing. Hang the, like literally hang the phone up right now.
Cause that, that, that I, I don't know. I was going to say one, this one or this one,
let's just go with it. If it's wrong, it's wrong, but I, I'm going to trust.
Okay. Good. Actually good thing. That's a good thing. $8,000. Let's go. I'm going to get harder.
Music theory. How many Quavers are there in a crotchet? We're just playing Mad Libs right now.
I don't even know what those two things are. I don't know what a quaver is and I don't know
what a crotchet is. So I, both of those, did you just speak in like old English to me?
Um, how many Quavers are in a crotchet? What's it? Can I ask what a quaver is? What's a quaver?
Uh, I, this is going to be a wild guess. So I'm just going to say new question.
Just do star Wars. I don't think you can pick one. We'll plate the female lead in James Dean's last
film giant. I'm gravitate. I'm gravitating over her. What, what does this sound? This is 8,000.
Okay. Please take away. Let's go. I'm going to try B. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. 16,000. We're almost
at 32. No lifelines, but it's all right. Recovered from your emotions because here is your new
question. In the 1963 film of the same name, what was the pink panther? Uh, with this detective,
but it's not detective. It's thief because the detective is, is the detective the pink panther
or is the detective going after the pink panther? I think that's, that's accurate.
The pink panther is a thief. I could be way overthinking this, but I'm, I'm, I'm sorry.
I think the thief is the pink panther. The detective is the one going after the pink panther.
What? Unfortunately ends here for you. This is not the right answer. Sorry. Oh, well it was jewel.
Oh, all right. We're going to take everything off besides, uh, super heroes. Okay. I have to
have at least four packs. Super heroes, star wars, uh, food. I'll, I'll destroy that. And
DC. No, I don't know if I know DC comics that well. Disney. No entertainment. No, it could be
like, Oh, who was this actor in this 1940s series? We'll go DC. Fine. Star wars, food,
superheroes in DC. See if I can do it. All right. Let's go. I do wonder woman's bracelets do
deflect rain. Okay. See, I thought I got it wrong. Trust yourself. Okay. What is Superman's
Kryptonian name? Okay. That would be Cal. Which of these movies is the oldest for its release
date in theaters? Um, Oh shit. Actually, I think it's the last Jedi. Wait, the oldest,
not the newest, the oldest it's Empire Strikes Back. I know my stop. Trust yourself and your
acquaintances for this new question. Which character does not appear in the movie wonder woman 1984?
Oh, uh, can we just do like mid 2000s to late 2010s? Uh, Marvel universe,
DC, please. I don't know. Shit. This must be easy for me. Aries. Whatever. Actually,
I'm sure of it. All right. No more mistakes from what Italian city does had net tone.
Well, judging by how I just pronounced that name, I definitely don't know who this is.
So, uh, uh, shit. This is the $500 question. This is a $500 question to me is like,
is Thanos purple? Yes. Yes. Yes or no. That's a $500 question. You know what I mean?
This is, this is a way harder question than $500. Um, give me, give me a new question.
When Grand Moff Tarkin asks Leia where the rebel base is, what is her answer?
I don't know. I don't know. I just went, I like when Darth Vader's on screen and he has like a
lightsaber and he goes like, I don't fucking know places. I like when Darth Vader puts his hand up
and somebody goes, I didn't pay attention to that. All the other lore. I think it's this one. It's
not Dan Tween. It's this one here. It's all it's, it's Alderaan, right? I think this is correct.
It's correct. Dan Tween is a real fucking place. Dan Tween. What? I thought it was Tatooine,
not Dan Tween. I thought that was the joke answer. All right, we're going again, going again.
This time. I don't know. I guess I don't know that much about these two things.
We're going lifestyle, TV, sports, entertainment. Let's go. Dan Tween. Dan Tween. I've broken
through emote only. Holy fuck. Oh God. That's really funny, but you're going to get tabbed
up for like an hour. I'm just sorry. I'm just telling him it's going to happen. I've broken
through. What planet are Superman and Super girl? Whatever. Super. I can't even say Superman. Why?
I think they're from Earth. Nah, dude, they're definitely from Venus. They're from Krypton.
Krypton. For those of you that don't know. Confetti is most associated with which event?
Uh, definitely. It's not a funeral. Wait, what? Where's birthday party? Where's birthday party?
Fucking birthday party's not on here. Not a christening. Not a funeral. A wedding? I mean,
what is a Hogmanay? What's Hogmanay? Hogmanay. What's that? Does that mean birthday party?
I don't think it's wedding. It's Hogmanay. I mean, people throw, you know, oh, like,
here comes the bride and groom. We're going to throw the stuff and is it, I guess it's confetti.
I don't, this is so, I don't know what this is. This is weird. What is this here? I'm going wedding.
Okay. Yeah. What is a Hogmanay? Trust yourself and your acquaintances for this new question.
Which of these is the name of the American Olympian who won gold medals in 1984,
1988, 1992, and 1996? No, I don't think it's Jerry Lewis. It's not Huey Lewis. Um, it's, it's D.
Carlos. Huey Lewis. It's time to move on to a new question.
Which of these hobbies is a kiln like Louis? Oh, that's clay. Pottery. Final answer. Pottery.
Final answer. Good. What is Wolverine's true identity? Uh, Logan. It's Logan, bub.
What? What? Wait, what? Hold on. Isn't it Logan? Logan. He's Logan. James Howlett? What is Logan
from? Why is it, why is it Logan? Why is his name Logan? Who calls him Logan? There's a whole movie
where Logan's in the whole title of the whole movie. The title is Logan. The movie, his name is
Logan. Take off emote only. What happened? I, I'm genuine. I'm curious. What happened? James
Jimmy Howlett, also known as Logan or by his code name, the Wolverine. What do you mean bro?
What do you mean bro, bro? What? Logan is the scientist's name. It's a nickname. You're a
fake fan? Yeah, I am. That's fine. I just, in big bold capital letters, I just remember seeing
Logan. I didn't stop to think, and now I've never seen this movie, so maybe that would help if I
had seen Logan before anybody screams at me. I know. That's the good one. I'm sorry that I saw
X2, X-Men United before I saw Logan. I'm sorry. I have to apologize. I know that's the good one.
I know that Logan's the good one. I'm sorry. Fake fan? Yeah. Dantooine. Way too much confidence?
Yeah, a little too much. I was on a roll there too. Can I at least get past like 100,000,
200,000? Put manga on? I'll do, I'll put manga on after this. Okay, no messing around. And what
would you normally stay overnight while on a camping trip? A phone booth.
Okay, C. Jimmy Dantooine Logan. Okay, what shape are samosas? God damn it. I don't, I don't do
shapes. I don't do shapes, guys. I don't. I promise you I don't. I don't do shapes. Hey, do you know
like if this is like a hexa octagon? I'm just like, I don't, I don't know. Ask somebody else.
Who is the father of Wanda Maximoff aka the Scarlet Witch? Okay, it's not Cyclops.
It's not Wolverine. It's not, it's Magneto. Wait, I don't, is it, is it? I think so. Yeah.
How many episodes make up Craig Mazin's Chernobyl miniseries? I think it's six. I think it's six.
It's not ten. It's not. No, it's six. What? It's five. God damn it. I didn't see that either.
Why is, why are TV shows on here? I don't even watch TV. Why is TV, I don't, I haven't watched
a full TV series since season two of Better Call Saul. That's the last television story that I
watched a full season of. Why, why would I pick this? I gotta think of things that I do, things
that I know. I know food. I know history. I know manga. How about Olympic games? I feel like I,
how about just general culture? Let's do it. See your own game show. Oh, I feel, I've been on a
few game shows. It was really fun to be on them. Okay, this is the one. Which punctuation mark is
found in the middle of the word isn't? Uh, it's an apostrophe. Which of these is an alternative
name for Santa Claus? Father Ted. Father Time. Father Christmas. Father Time. Alright, Father
Christmas. Is that wrong? Okay, I was like, no way. In Saint Seiya, from what constellation is
Shun's character the Bronze Knight? Um, constellation. I don't know. Why, everyone's laughing at me for
some reason. What is it, what, what's this from? What is this? Everyone's laughing at me. I'm looking
over here and I'm just seeing, laughing. There's a stadium full of people just laughing at me. And
I don't, I don't understand why. I, I'm trying to figure it out. Okay, what constellation? Okay,
a dragon is not a constellation. Is there, there's no phoenix constellation. What, this is like a
galaxy. What is it? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what this is from. So I'm, I'm going to
say Cygnus? Because that's a constellation. That's a galaxy. What? Saint, what does Saint Seiya?
That's like, this is like, Andromeda's a galaxy. That's not a constellation.
Oh, this is an, this is an anime. This is a, this is a manga. I thought this was, okay, I thought
that, I thought this was real life. I didn't think this was manga. I thought that was a real life. Oh,
and Saint Seiya from, I thought that was, okay, whatever. I forgot that we had manga selected.
Anime is real life. That's right. I forgot. That's true.
Andromeda is a constellation. I thought it was a galaxy. Dude, anime isn't real. What are you
talking about? How could you possibly not known that? He was just moving his hands and not talking.
All right. What name is given to a dishonest or careless workman? I, I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I would, I would, I don't know. I don't know.
What? I thought a cowboy was, that's what a cowboy is. I thought a cowboy was like,
you're a rootin' tootin'. Update the game? What? Leave me alone. You lost on the first question.
Some of these are weird. You didn't finish Better Call Saul? No? Okay. Um, which of these is a sport
involving horses? Show hopping, show jumping, show leaping, or show running. I feel like all of these
are correct, but I don't know what the actual answer is. Is that crazy that this is the second
one in a row that like, I don't, I don't really know? All of these could be correct. I'm going
to say show jumping because that's okay. That's, that makes, is that what it is? Yeah. These are
weird first questions. They're too similar. Too similar. We'll be most likely to wear a tutu.
Uh, a priest, a chef, or a mountain climber. Okay. When something is completely finished,
it is often described as done and done and done, done and driven, done and dusted, done and dropped,
done and done and dusted? I've never heard that term before, but that makes the most sense.
Which of these is an informal word for father? Uh, that would be pop.
Okay. Which of these is a brief outline of the plot of a play, film, or book?
That would be the synopsis. Nailed it. Doing well. Okay. That was really fast to a thousand.
All my lifelines. I'm ready to go. In which of these carry on films did Kenneth Williams not
appear? No idea. If we get to the thousand dollar question and they give this
amazingly specific question. We need some help here. Carry on Columbus. I'll, I'll trust them.
Okay. All right. No more lifelines unless I absolutely need it. I need to get to 32,000.
That's, that's my million. You're going, you're going to make short work of this new question.
Which musical features the song matchmaker matchmaker? I think it's this one, this one,
or I don't think it's either of these two. I think it's this one or it's Fiddler on the Roof.
It's, it's not either one of these. It's Fiddler on the Roof. Okay. I was half right. What is
taffetta, taff, taffetta, taffetta, Italian bread, shiny fabric, sailor's knot or green tea,
taffetta, bread. That's Italian bread. Final answer. I'm sure of it.
Shit. I was so confident that it was bread. All right. All right. All right.
Did you please play League of Legends trivia? I will not get a single question right.
You suck at this. Here's the thing though. This game, I sit there and I've seen people play this
and I'm like, man, like I definitely could get farther than that. And then you realize that
there's so many questions that this world has posed. It's hard to even get to the, you know,
a quarter of a million. It's really hard to do that because you'll get tripped up on a question
that is just completely out of your head. It's just never been there. You've never had this
information and you never will. When you get one of those, it's just over. But I like it. It's fun.
There's so many questions to ponder on this earth. That's right. All right. Let me get to it. I got
to get to at least a quarter of a million or that's embarrassing for me. I'm doing this for
me at this point. This is for me. I'm getting to at least a hundred thousand. All the person
is dumb as being long in the hair, long in the lip, long in the socks, long in the tooth.
Long in the tooth. All right. Speedrun it. Additionally, who was the assistant to the
bridge groom on his wedding day? Wait, wait, what was his word? Traditionally, who was the
assistant to the bridegroom on his wedding day? Okay. The smartest friend, the oldest brother,
the neatest buddy, the best man. Yeah, sorry. We got to figure out who the smartest friend is.
Question who lived in a mansion in Memphis, Tennessee, called Graceland.
Besides puppy dog's tails, what are little boys made of? According to the rhyme screws and nails
frogs and snails and puppy dog's tails. Is that right? What the fuck are we made of frogs and
snails and what and puppy dog's tails? I thought we were atoms and matter and shit. Like what?
I guess this would, okay. Frogs and snails. Which of these amounts is equal to a gross?
Hold on. Which of these amounts? So what is a gross? Half a monkey. That's not the right answer.
I feel like it's this. I don't know. There's a million things in my brain. I think it's three.
I'm going for it. I think it's either three or it's a dozen dozen. What the fuck does that mean?
Does that mean it's 12 12s? A ton and a half. I'm not confident. I'm not confident. I don't
know if I'm confident on this. I might have to get an opinion. I don't know if I can stay with
three but I don't know if I want to do dozen dozen whatever. God damn it. It wasn't even
close. Why did I want it to be three? In November 2007 a strike by witch workers brought chaos to
the US TV and movie business. Is it screenwriters? Yeah it was screenwriters. 2007 really? I remember
that was maybe it was 2007. What should Muslims do between sunrise and sunset during Ramadan?
I feel like it's I don't really know. I think it's one of these two. I don't know. I want to
say I want to say fast. Why is it pray? It might be pray. I think that's correct. Yeah it is correct.
Okay I think I'm doing pretty well. I want it that way was a hit single for which boy band?
Hold on. But was that in sync or the backstreet boys? Damn it.
It's in sync. Fuck I shouldn't have put my first choice. That was my first choice. Damn it. Just
because I thought of a different song doesn't mean that it can't be the same band. I thought
of a different song and I was like wait that's backstreet boys. This one has to be in sync.
God damn it. Only 40 neurons. All right let's change it up a little. We'll keep manga. We're
going to add geography, history, sports, keep food, and keep culture. Dude go finish Better Call Saul.
I know. I know. Trust me I know. Put it on easy. No. How will I ever train my brain?
Which of the following is not one of the mother sauces? Are they asking what's the first sauce
ever? Which of these was not one of the first sauces? I don't know dude. I don't know. This
I know what Holladay's is. Holladay's I know what Bacchamel is. Bacchamel whatever. I don't
I don't know. I don't know what these are. Mornay? I don't I feel like it's Mornay. No
Holladay's is you put on fucking eggs. It's Holladay's. It's fucking Holladay's. Holladay's
is what? It was Mornay. What is a mother sauce? These are weird questions. That's weirdly worded.
I don't know what that's supposed to mean. What the fuck is a mother sauce? What's a mother sauce?
I've never heard that term before in my entire life. You're a fake sauce fan? No I've never
been like. You know what sweetheart? Tonight let's just use a mother sauce tonight. You know
what I mean? Do you want ketchup? Yes I want ketchup on my fucking eggs. Yes I like ketchup.
I love ketchup. I have a baby. Where? Complete the phrase as cool as a carrot. Are you sure?
Which part of a man's suit is most likely to be described as double breasted? What spice is used
in speculus? Again that's another word I've never heard before. Speculous. What is speculus?
What spice is used in speculus? What is a food I've never eaten? I don't know. Um what? Who's
eaten speculus? What? Cinnamon goes on top of speculus. Take off emote only. What is speculus?
Dessert? It's a cookie. It's a cookie. It's a cookie. I don't know either bro.
Where would you normally place a holly wreath during the Christmas holidays?
Right on the front door. Around your neck. Uh I don't think so.
Let's move on to a whole new question. Who was the only 20th century US president enshrined on
Mount Rushmore? Oh god I'm gonna get this wrong. Um I I know it too. I did though here's another
thing about playing these games like trivia games. You're a fake American. I know but listen listen.
I know the answer to this question but when it's presented to me with other options I go
I don't think I know the answer to this question even though I know it's this one. Right? I for
some reason it's like wait these there's other options here. You're gonna get this fucking wrong
Jeremy. It ain't it ain't Roosevelt. You're wrong. You seem to be. But it's right. Question coming.
All right. Which of these is not a bird? A sand wedge? There's a club in golf.
Actually I'm sure of it. Yeah okay. I saw a lot of omega luls and I was concerned for a second.
Experienced contestants. You would have got that one wrong. Here's a new question that I hope
won't worry you. Yellowstone National Park covers parts of Wyoming, Idaho,
and which other state? I believe it's Utah. Actually wait a minute might be Colorado.
Wait wait wait wait hold on think this through. Think this through for a second.
Think this through. Yellowstone. I think it's Utah. I would my initial reaction is either Utah or
Colorado. It's Utah. It has to be. It's Utah. It's Utah. It is. I don't want to ask the audience
because I have all my lifelines. No I don't. Never mind. It's Utah. It's Utah. I know exactly
what you're doing streamer. You're trying to see is if there's more green or red circles in the
chat. I know what the fuck you're doing. It's Colorado then. I don't know and I'm not gonna
pretend to know. I don't. I gotta get it right. Okay we're gonna call. We're gonna call Theo.
It's the Colorado. Good evening. Your line wants to be a millionaire. Oh very good in good company
but we need your help. Yeah you're on who wants to be a millionaire. You're not gonna get any of
this money but you might be the reason he does. How does that make you feel? Montana. Really?
Trust you. It's Utah. It's Utah. Okay I'm doing all right. I have to get at least past 65 000
Which of these is a sliding effect in music? Um glissando?
Educating myself to not know the answer to this question.
Easy. Is it Cato? Decrescendo. I feel like it's this. I think it's D. Decrescendo. Decrescendo.
Sliding effect. Crescendo is. Crescendo is. So what would a decrescendo be?
That doesn't make any sense. Um what I just did. I don't think that's right.
Give me a new question. I don't care. Which company bought the website YouTube in 2006?
This is a $100 question. Least the pressure. Here's a new question. Who gave birth to a baby
boy named Sean Preston on September 14th 2005? Oh no. I don't know. Sean Preston. 2005. I really
want to say. I have no idea. I have absolutely no idea. It's gonna have to be 50 50. From now on.
Okay. I don't know. I don't know. Pink? My gut is telling me it's pink. That's what my gut is saying.
I think it's. I don't know. I don't know. Is it. Is it Britney? For me. I just did 50 50 again.
Okay well good. Well this new question is now waiting for you to be answered with flying colors.
Which footballer wrote the autobiography in 1966 and all that? I don't know. Banks. Jack Charlton.
I don't know. In fact I have no idea. I'm literally. I don't have any clue at all.
I have no lifelines either. 16 000. Um I have to guess. I'm about to click this one.
That's probably wrong. Um. Shit. That was 16. That was 16 000 too. D Crescendo was right.
All right. A couple more. A couple more. A couple more. I want to do a couple more. I didn't really
have any other plan tonight. Just kind of hanging out. Maybe we'll jump into a different game.
All right. We're going to take geography away. We're going to do entertainment. Arts.
Literature. Keep manga. Get rid of sports. Keep history. And we're going to add science.
Go. Just only do food. Dark and Darker is back. That's true but I feel like I want to
get that set up first because it's not on steam right? Don't you have to go
do a weird process to get it? Oh no. Science. Yeah. I'm in trouble. Maybe not. Okay.
Which of these manga is not classified in the shonen category? Uh it's it's Berserk.
I'm sure of it. Yeah. It's Berserk. I know that one. I I know the I know that one.
Good luck. Complete the name of the great renaissance artist Leonardo Da Pinky. Da Binky.
Da Vinci. Da Zinci. These are like these are the one two three hundred dollar questions
right? We've gotten some weird ones that were way too hard to be down here.
What's the name of the small indentation often found in the human cheek?
Uh a dimple. This is a three hundred dollar question. I think this is the run.
What's the name of Don? Sidekick.
Uh I don't I I don't want to get this so wrong that it's completely wrong.
I don't know. It's kind of it's um it's not either one of these. Is it is it Huckleberry Finn?
No it's not. It's this one. It's it's this one. It's not Huckleberry Finn.
It's this one right here. Complete the title of the 2002 film Bend It Like Beckham.
I would save me. Neither do I. Okay got all the lifelines. I think we all agree that we can move
on to this new question. How old is Bulma at the beginning of the Dragon Ball adventure?
Oh boy I don't know. I don't I have no idea. I don't know. At the beginning of the wait aren't
there like 10 Dragon Ball franchises? Is it like there's like eight of them. So just Dragon Ball
just like Dragon Ball 1. I don't know. Some of you are probably freaking out screaming this right now
but I genuinely don't have any single fucking idea. And the audience doesn't know either.
Um I'm gonna go with the highest voted option. Nobody knows this apparently in this audience.
It's 16. Okay got it. I would have not known.
Questions follow each other and are not alike. Oh shit and the manga
Gun? Gun? What is the heroine's first name? Why is manga on here?
Guys I watched Full Metal Alchemist and Attack on Titan. I don't know any of these. Why would I
pick this? Why would I keep this in? Blasting 2. All right let's uh let's see if Zelda knows this.
Are you a big fan of the of the manga Gun M?
I'm certain it's A.
Ooh confident that it's D. Confident does does grandma know?
I'm choosing D. Wow grandma. Grandma knows more about manga than you do. Damn okay.
The game is getting tougher now with this brand new question. Which meat is used in Katsudon in
Japan? Uh oh it's uh it's chicken right but no no no no no but uh Katsu Katsudon is pork or chicken?
It's pork or chicken? Pork or chicken? Pork or chicken? Pork or chicken? It's pork I think.
I don't know. I'm gonna say pork. It's D I think. Actually I'm sure of it.
I got a little excited. Good start but you shouldn't stop there. Here is a new question.
Which US president reportedly said the ballot is stronger than the bullet. Why? Who said this?
What is this? The ballot is stronger than the bullet. Is that was that Thomas Jefferson or was
it was it Lincoln? Yeah which of these US presidents was born? Leslie King Jr. in 1913.
Um Leslie King Jr. Ronald Reagan? Is it Ronald Reagan? I don't know. I want to say it's Ronald
Reagan but I'm afraid to press this button. Look at this. I have still have I have two lifelines
and I'm almost at 32. That's a huge deal. I think I'm about to just dump this question because I
don't know. I have no idea. Give me a new question. Just dump it. Diplopia is the technical name for
which visual condition? Diplopia. Diplopia. Diplopia. Diplopia. Diplopia. Shit. I feel like
it's B. Diplopia. B or well let me think about this. I don't think it's color blindness. Night
blindness. Maybe. I don't know what it is. I would I would take plunge and say that it's either
double vision or night blindness and I have to use this because it's unfortunate. Oh that's great.
Literally the two that I didn't help me at all. You did not help me at all.
So well actually that kind of does help because I feel like it's night blindness.
I think that's correct and I have to live with it so. Oh god damn it. I was right. This this this
don't give me multiple choice fucking questions. Just ask me. Just ask me because like I was sitting
there going double vision. It's double vision. You know I think it's double vision. Diplopia is
double vision but what if it's night blindness. I don't know. That's on here. It was really fun
don't give me multiple choice. Just ask me what is diplopia and I'll go oh that sounds
red. That sounds like double vision to me and I'll get it right. He is too. I know.
But then I saw it. I freaked out. All right. I'll get it here. I almost got to 32.
You're a fake eye fan. Yeah. Okay. I'm going to try as hard as I can. Let's go.
Oh hmm. Which one of these is not the mother sauce. That would be Mornay.
You were here last week. We gave you the same question.
Garth Brooks is country. Very good. Very nice.
Which of these is the title of a 2011 hit single by Lady Gaga.
Uh is I'm sorry.
What is denoted by the medical prefix germ. That would be skin. I'm choosing D.
According to Shakespeare a rose by any other name would grow as tall smell as sweet.
Roses don't get tall. What would I what do you what it's it's smell as sweet.
Rose by any other name would smell as sweet.
Popular children's novel by
Chrisida Cowell is titled how to train your how to train your dragon.
All right. Where are we at? I got all my lifelines right. What a thousand.
Two thousand now. All right. Beyonce was featured on telephone a 2010 hit single for what artist.
Katy Perry telephone telephone. I don't know. I don't know. I need help.
Lady Gaga would say D. Obviously. Really. I know.
Fake Gaga fan knew the first one.
All right. No more lifelines off to a good start but you shouldn't stop there.
Here is a new question. Which of these is a length of water or bank side allocated to an angler.
Length of water pitch pitch of a pitch of water. This is a pitch of water.
This is a patch of water. The cast of water. This is a beat of water.
It's a patch of water. It's beat. This is a beat of water.
I think the patch is right. I've never seen anybody complete this by the way.
I've not seen a single human beat this. I've never seen a person beat this.
Gaga sweep. Gaga sweep. I've never seen a person beat this.
Everybody gets to 16,000 to 32,000 and you lose every time.
They ask you a weird question like what is Logan's name in the movie Wolverine?
What? And you see he's got his hand over his mouth.
The founding fathers.
Which parts of the body are affected by fallen arches?
Um fallen arches. I think it's your feet right?
Yeah that's an answer I can get behind. Let's go for a whole new question.
I say shoulders. What is?
Okay I haven't spent this many years educating myself.
Consum.
Not know the answer to this question.
Is it consum?
Soup, meat dish, cold appetizer, hot dessert. I've heard this word before.
I've heard this word before but I don't I nodded my head when they were like oh and by the way
today for our consomme we have and I was just like I don't I'm I'm I'm busy playing
fucking video games on my iPad what I want chicken fingers please um I don't know.
This is the $200 question and I've never heard this word.
I probably have but like I don't know does it mean a hot dessert?
The restaurants I eat at guys I don't they're not like and tonight I would like to hear.
How do you feel about this consomme?
Soup.
Okay which of these words means the formal resignation of a king or queen?
I feel like this question was the last it was on the last time I streamed this game
like a year ago and I got it wrong then and I'm gonna get it wrong now.
I remember this question and I got it wrong then I'm going to get it wrong now.
They're all just like this they're all just the same word to me like
aberration ablation ab-abtion abtion abtion it's like I'd give me like a B or like a C word you
know what I mean?
That was a shitty one I the $200 question was a word I'd never seen before.
Okay the name of the treatment for which essential oils are aromatherapy.
I guess how did you not know that?
Here's the thing there's a lot of questions in here that I think I would say holy shit
how did you get that wrong and you'll get wrong.
We all have different things that we know.
Sorry I don't know what a ukelele is.
I don't know what the fuck that is is that you might know what that is I've never heard
of this before a ukelele I don't know what the fuck that is.
Oh shut up sit down everybody relax.
What is the name of the prequel to Osamu Tezuka's manga Blackjack?
I'm gonna say Blackjack Zero.
It's gotta be it has to be Blackjack Zero.
What the fuck?
Get manga get manga out of here.
I'm not gonna get any of them right.
It's been such a wall for this whole playthrough.
Get I'm not gonna get this right and why would I even have it on?
All right let's go swap off of Pablo.
Which animal's name also refers to a person using an experiment to see if it works or not?
Guinea pig.
Also another thing that's important to know during trivia nights I'm the guy
that doesn't really I'm not I don't work well under trivia pressure
so if I'm on a team with another two or three people I wait for somebody to start to say the
letter and then I cut them off and say the letter very quickly at the same time that they do.
So like Wolverine does not have which one of these powers and then okay let me see um oh
this no he doesn't have and I hear oh see yeah laser eyes of course he doesn't have laser eyes
and then we we high five and everybody thinks I know what I'm talking about I've never been
to a trivia night in my entire life so for all of you that are like oh my god wait what's wrong
with him I made it up made it up wasn't real we got you on that one we made it up we made that
one up that one wasn't real huh got you there it was made up what did Jack sell for a handful
of beans in the fairytale jack and the beanstalk uh he sold a cow uh Timon is a prairie dog wait
wait wait wait wait wait no no no wait a second wait a second
this is why I can't have more than one answer Timon and Pumbaa who is the who is the
the fucking pig it's a meerkat when I was a young warthog how does Romeo meet his death
in Shakespeare's tragedy Romeo and Juliet poison okay how many equinoxes are there in a calendar
year well I mean it depends depends on who's asked it depends on what kind of equinox is it a
fall equinox is it the winter equinox is it the spring equinox is it the summer equinox because
I mean that would be I just named four but very importantly there's only two there are only two
equinoxes there's the winter equinox there's the fall equinox and then there is that's it
because there's only two there are two equinoxes because the equinox only appears twice
okay I'm doing good now let's go to the next question if you don't mind uh salicylic acid
used in aspirin derives its name from the latin word the latin for which tree salicylic acid
salicylic I should know this I really should it's so annoying that like I don't know this
because I know this salicylic acid is uh I it's it's I don't I it's it's either tea tree or
sycamore I should know this I really should I should know this it should be so simple I'm
I'm the dickhead I'm the asshole that anytime somebody says oh anything salicylic acid is
ever brought up oh you know you know that's aspirin right and people go wow really yeah
salicylic acid is is that is used in aspirin aspirin people go whoa holy shit you're a smart
person you know that I don't go any further than that all I know is that yeah hey it's aspirin
plus five IQ for you and for your head just how you feel about how I how I am uh I'm gonna say
guys I'm at eight thousand dollars without a single lifeline I'm good it's tea tree tea tree
salicylic acid latin for tea tree let's go lock it in I it's not correct I'm not gonna do that one
I just thought that it was not a good idea so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna ask the audience
this question is worth it I should have just done it I should have did it it's tea tree I it's tea
tree it might not even be tea tree though it might just be stupid this is I had all of my lifelines
at ten thousand oh my god Romans don't have tea tree I fucking hate multiple choice
did anybody in the audience get it right didn't look like it
I don't have two brain cells is that what you said no you said you're losing brain cells as you watch
both of those statements are mean okay so I'm gonna be fine I just got to eight thousand without
a single lifeline when is the fall equinox I don't know guys the equinox is I feel like the company
that no that's that's no I got that that's completely wrong which of these describes
something which causes stress nerve-wracking I'm choosing B yes all right no fucking around
blacksmith works mainly with which substance uh they make pizza I'm not gonna let I'm not
gonna screw this up complete the first line of the popular hymn all things bright and shining
all things bright and natural all things bright and sparkling I don't know all things bright and
beautiful deduction what French confections were popularized by two Carmelite nuns who prepared
and sold them to pay for their housing during the time of the French Revolution French confection
popularized by two nuns macarons grapes Suzette Claire I feel like it might be a Claire I just
had a core memory unlocked by looking up salicylic acid I think it's eclairs I would say clear and
that's what I would say I'm gonna click it but it might be wrong I don't know this is the three
how is this a three hundred dollar question three hundred dollar question is what is super
Mario's fucking first name Mario I had it right the first time you I you guys are fucking with me
I said macarons and everyone was like no no no it's wrong you're an idiot and then it
fucks with my head okay name for a catalog of recordings especially by one particular
singer that is a discography Hank Pym has never been which of these heroes um what
Hank Pym is the guy that created the quantum fucking realm he's the one that created the
realm he I I found I found a solution to quantum travel that's Hank Pym who was he not what hero
was he not ever I mean I feel like was Hank Pym Ant-Man or no he was never Ant-Man he's the one
that found the quantum realm and Ant-Man became Ant-Man I'm not I'm not Ant-Man I just I'm the
technology guy I think that's correct you're a fake nerd he was the first Ant-Man I don't know
okay guys that when I watch a Marvel movie I don't have a notepad with a pen and he's like you know
I'm Hank Pym this is Ant-Man one welcome to I never even saw Ant-Man one remember I thought
Ant-Man one I told you guys that Ant-Man one they weren't even ants in the fucking movie I never
even saw it and I remember I was adamant that there were no ants in the whole movie the whole
movie's about how he can control ants I've never even saw the movie but my point is I'm not sitting
there taking notes like Hank Pym was the first Ant-Man okay let me get that down and really
Ant-Man was the first uh Hank Pym was the first Ant-Man never even saw the material
that's a family guy flashback I've never I never saw the first movie I was such a fake shit
Infinity War fan it's like oh yeah Marvel oh I love Marvel let's go I saw three of the movies
over 10 to 15 years I saw Iron Man 3 the first Captain America movie let's go for this
Ant-Man and the Wasp and Infinity War I don't know I don't know what the fuck happens in any
of these movies uh that's Saturday Night Live okay the only thing I know about Guardians of
the Galaxy is there's rock music in it I don't know anything else I've never seen any of them
which of these is a television network in the United States maybe I'm choosing B
it I might be full of shit though nice answer maybe I have seen a lot of them
I think I don't know I don't remember which of these superheroes was not an orphan when
they put on their costume for the first time what an orphan um I don't remember Spider-Man
being an orphan okay was it uh no Aunt Batman yeah Superman yeah Batgirl I don't know I feel
like it's Batgirl I think it's Batgirl it's either Batgirl or Spider-Man I'm saying Batgirl
it's Batgirl yeah I mean Superman was his own planet is a million light years away
a tremor is a small earthquake what is the main ingredient in Scottish haggis I actually know
this I know this no I don't it's I believe it's sheep stomach I am not even gonna give you a
chance to say that I'm cheating because I got it right yeah I did know that for this new question
in which US state was the first Disney theme park open that would be California
Disneyland in California how many US universities make up the Ivy League I don't know yeah Harvard
Yale uh Brown um Yale this is this is quite a few I couldn't give you the exact number though
so we're gonna do ask the audience they're eight
final answer is none is a type of flatbread traditional in which country is cooking okay
now this is tough this is tough because I love this stuff but where where is it traditionally
what country traditionally is it from Greece India or Turkey I think it's India or Turkey
I'm gonna I I eat this stuff all the fucking time I love none but like where was it original
what was the original or country of origin I'm gonna say India I'm gonna say India but I think
it's Turkey and I'm afraid to click this I think I'm gonna have to just go for it and just click
Turkey because that might it's keep saying go for it that's where it's really from and it was India
and this is why multiple choice questions just rip them up because I got I had the question right
well it's no big deal I still had a good time I had the question correct but then I'm just
sitting there going wait a minute where's the original origin is it Turkey is it India if you
just asked me that question if we just were sitting there and you said what country is
non-bread from I'd say India but when you give me four options that could be correct it's over
it's over you're second guessing well that's the whole point of a multiple choice question is to
like multiple choice questions throughout history have been the right answers here but we're gonna
fuck with you we're gonna fuck with you on this question because it's gonna be something that
could be correct but fuck you you're gonna get it wrong okay we have faith no more second guessing
we're going we're going for it what type of creature is Jerry in the cartoon series Tom and
Jerry oh he's a rhinoceros uh in the tv series the simpsons who provides the voice for Lisa
uh yeah that is Bart it's weirdly who has never played Superman in a movie
Mel Gibson it's definitely Mel Gibson I feel like but his multiple choice bullshit that's the right
answer but like but there was just one made for fucking tv movie back in 1982 where Mel Gibson
was Superman in Superman attack of the mutants I I'm gonna get this question wrong to this new
question a lot of these in a row who is the main spider-man in 2018 spider-man
new generation movie spider-man's new generation who's the main spider-man in 2018's spider-man
new generation movie is it miles spider-man new generation it's definitely not peter parker
I'll say miles new generation it definitely wasn't peter parker it was ketchup first created
in the United States of America I'm proud to say that we created it France was created in France
for those of you that like to know sure that it'd be ketchup was created in France we have faith
was it China no it was made in the United States of America Arthur it was delicious
I got it that's China well I think we actually game is getting tougher I think that's pretty
recently that I found that out new question in the human body which of these bones is not above the
wrist the waist which is not above which one of these is not above the waist clavicle is above
the waist the sternum is above the waist the patella is not above the waist thank you thank
you thank you that you've released the pressure here's a new question one of the seven wonders
of the ancient world what was the pharaohs of alexandria one of them it's one of the
wonders seven wonders um one of these two pharaohs of alexandria I don't know I'm not caught up in my
seven wonders of the world the only thing I ever know about the seven wonders is I just I get a
lot of stuff about Egypt in my youtube shorts uh it's probably temple I have on my lifelines
it might be lighthouse lighthouse sounds kind of correct but I don't know for sure
thanks thanks for making it real easy so how many of you put that here as a joke
because I feel like it's actually the right answer pharaohs of alexandria
when in a lighthouse it says a statue it's no there's no way it's a lighthouse
it's probably a huge statue whatever the audience doesn't know either so I don't know
it is a lighthouse but it's the game this is not the right answer that feels like the answer
that's just god damn it the lighthouse uh I just got an achievement I'm very curious about my time
played in this game in fact let's find out because you guys are gonna I this might be very funny
I don't know how what the what the site what the answer is give me one second let me open up my
steam I want to see how long I've played this game for a total that's actually not that bad
I just got a hundred my hundredth question answered correctly I've only played this game
for like four hours total that's pretty good how does that make any sense that's like impossible
all right we're taking superheroes off we're taking literature and entertainment off I'm
putting on geography taking history off adding star wars back adding general culture back and
we'll put the olympic games on there too why not no I'm not putting manga on there I'll get every
question wrong all right I feel I'm feeling this one wasn't gonna be one in which years were the
olympics canceled because of the second world war uh I mean it's gotta be here right I'm gonna
uninstall game okay I just I fucked up I fucked up big time I fucked up big time I fucked up big
time okay I can't even explain to you what just happened I fucked up big time there I apologize
let's just pretend you didn't even see that I fucked up big time American education moment
yeah and I'll say this again too I know yeah I know some of you guys might still be in fucking
school I haven't sat at a desk in 20 years I haven't sat at a fucking desk in 15 to 20
years I oh I can't believe you don't know this geography last weekend I found out where fucking
where where where the sleep cycle is I haven't sat at a desk at a school in 20 years which of
these is a word for a short sleep during the day that's a cat I didn't just learn these things
like a few years ago I probably didn't fucking pay attention either you're trying to tell me
the guy that paid all the attention in school not only was it 20 years ago but I was like doodling
in a notebook I wasn't I well did I pay that much attention I don't know okay which of these names
has rapper Sean Combs never released a single under I hippopotamus yeah right okay in the fast
food chain KFC is derived from what word Kentucky fried chicken I'm choosing beef which of these
is said to give you a very clear view of a sporting event binoculars because that's the
only way I was able to see that's okay yeah that's my answer the ringside yeah it's like
what is a mamba I'm not cut out for these games I'm not made for this I it's a snake
right a mamba okay yes I it's just semantics and weird you know what I mean in cooking
to what does an espuma refer espuma an espuma I don't know I put the oven at 400 degrees and
I put the salmon in and I take it out in 15 minutes I don't what is an espuma I put maybe
some dill on it I have a side of broccolini I don't know this I don't do this what is that
I don't know what that is supposed to mean I put the patty in the pan I wait a few minutes I
flip the patty I wait till the patties done I take it off and I put it between two pieces of
bread I I take lettuce tomatoes and croutons and carrot shavings I don't know what an espuma is
I'm too I don't know what that means who the fuck knows what an espuma is oh it's foam oh
yeah all that all that foam that I use in my cooking I finished my salmon off with a salt foam
name is getting tougher now and then the person I served it to
question pukes that was that rude okay that might have been kind of rude whatever
which of these words is derived from the name of the writer the marquis de sad marquis de se none
of you know this nobody here knows this I'm not the only one that doesn't know this which of these
words is derived from the name of the writer the marquis de se I don't know sadist these are hard
questions or not even a couple thousand bucks you have to tempt fate sometimes this is what
my gut says okay what type of food product is monterey jack cheese all right let's go
according to george bernard shaw which two countries are divided by a common language
divided by a common language scotland and ireland spain and mexico america and these all kind of
sound correct I feel like that's right I would that would be my first guess this would be my
second guess I don't know I could be wrong judging by all of the not like this I see over in the chat
room I'm right stop making me think I'm wrong who co-wrote raindrops keep falling on my head
for the film butch cassidy and the sun dance kid raindrops keep falling on my head but that
don't mean I won't be ruling surely that burnt back a rat fucking classic hey that's a pretty
big milestone it only took two hours to get there which I wish that was ironically me saying that's
not which musical features the characters rum tum tugger and skimble shanks that feels like
those feels like cats names I think it's cats that's a that's cats that's all right
I'm about I'm about to win we're at 64k I got almost all my lifelines I'm not fucking around
anymore look at this according to legend which flower is named after a boy accidentally killed
by the god Apollo I feel like it's a if I'm pressing a if that's a is what I would is what
I think it is I don't even there's no second guessing here I don't this why would I second
guess this I know this is the correct answer so I'm going to press it yes okay don't know I
stopped second guessing I'm at 120 fucking thousand k what do you mean 120k what was the
name of the spacecraft featured in the tv series and film lost in space danger danger danger
we're on mars 1 we're on mars 1 danger danger danger danger we're on mars 1 reaching home
jupiter 2 we're on jupiter 2 saturn 4 this is saturn 4 reaching out wrong this is mercury 3
mercury 3 reaching out jupiter 2 it is jupiter 2 is the correct answer that is the name of the
spacecraft in lost in space thank you for coming out thanks for watching the stream
thanks for hanging out all this time I don't know all right let's call grandma
grandma will know grandma was a huge fan of the show Lindsay is in a tight spot in her game of
who wants to be a millionaire do you think you could help her out thank you that's a pleasure
to hear but let's get back to the game please I see that Lindsay is getting all right we have 10
seconds uh I don't know if that's right I don't think it's d I think it's it's either a or b
grandma you're just completely wrong Mars 1 this is Mars 1 trying to reach earth
can anybody hear me can anybody hear me Mars 1 to earth Mars 1 to earth that's the one and
it's the one that's not capitalized so it has to be correct oh I fucking hate this game god damn
it that was 100 and something thousand well it's no big deal I still had a good time I'm sorry
but god damn it that was the one you played yourself um that wasn't a second guess I thought
it was Mars I think we got the perfect amount of uh questions now that was what $250,000 question
we can get there you should play wrestling empire you're much better at senseless violence
I just got to quarter million right there without any help not sure okay what is the name of the
platform that Disney launched to compete with Netflix in November 2019 in the U.S. Disney uh
Disney I believe in my god I'm choosing b are you sure you go for a whole new question the Jedi and
the Sith's fight with a special weapon what is it a Jedi pistol a lightsaber a titanium sword
or a rocket launcher okay we have faith yeah nice here's a new question for you which of these TV
game shows is loosely based on the game hangman uh will of fortune I think it's a so good which
state is home to Silicon Valley uh California excuse me what oh what animal is Timon oh we
gotta repeat this is perfect awesome we gotta repeat already get a thousand which of these
is a division of geological time as an eon an eon eons and eons ago
yep which of these means to turn upside down turn tortoise turn turtle turn toucan turn turnkey
upside down turn turtle turn tortoise turn turkey turn turkey toucan turn tortoise a tortoise to me
makes the most sense but this is uh this is messing me up right now I don't like that this
is here although turn toucan sounds the best this oh hold on let me I just uh you have to take a
chance okay D dude I just got wicked bad deja vu did anybody else get deja vu right there I'm
serious really really bad really bad deja vu too bad like this happened I think this happened like
two years ago the same game the same exact thing played out I think the same question
and I said turn turnkey I did the laugh and it was like there's no way and then I people
were saying it was turkey in chat I have actually deja vu I think this exact same
scenario played out okay this is them are you streaming until you win a million no but I want
to get to at least quarter million half million I was right there which category of plants are
Christmas trees usually placed in for greens okay Ridley Scott directed a film called
blade what a blade runner let's freaking go a secret service make sure I get a secret service
okay are you sure what is the nearest state capital to wakiki beach hmm I mean I want to
say Honolulu Honolulu but like that's the easiest answer but I'm gonna do it because
whatever okay okay before law manado in 2004 who was the last french gold medalist in swimming
this is like this is just the kind of question that not I don't think anybody knows the answer
to unless they just look it up okay um I don't know any of these names do you guys care if I
look it up okay we have faith you know it's funny I feel like this is one of those questions that
only appears in a trivia game pedicure is the french word for which professional
uh pedicure is the french word for which professional hairdresser fashion designer
chiro potest that where isn't a pedicure your your toes chiro potest uh I don't I don't know
I don't know what a chiro potest is but it's the correct answer in 2008 who released the single
womanizer from her album circus ergy womanizer I don't know I don't know yeah when you invite me
if I meet you a trivia game I'm just gonna be the guy that drinks and tells jokes that's what I'm
doing there I'm not there to answer questions I know I'll be the guy that knows the one weird
baseball rule that makes sure we get to a million but I don't do anything else I don't really know
music that well give me a new question in brother bear what is the name of the human who is turned
into a bear he would have had to have seen this movie the friendship tonight uh let's call a
childhood friend hello Antonio we need your help because Lindsay is stuck on a question oh I might
be able to help her but just maybe believe in yourself you'll see I'm sure that you're going
to be able to help our contestant good evening Antonio don't be afraid this is completely up
your alley just concentrate I'm thrilled to tell you that the right answer is B
plain and simple I trust you nice how many legs does an ibis have two I'm choosing B
what sweet dish has a name which means thousand leaves thousand leaves
I think it's been a that makes sense to me I'm gonna have an 8 000 dollars and I don't
this one's not this is not the one okay well shit dare to say see let's go
okay in november 2003 at age 21 which singer got a star on the hollywood walk of fame
um it's probably it's probably britney although I feel like all of these make sense
let's go with britney I no doubt all right we're at a milestone what do I got 32 000
what relation was the late singer Whitney Houston to warwick what relation was this was Whitney
Houston Houston Whitney Houston Whitney Houston Whitney Houston Whitney Houston my gut is pointing
me over here here I feel like it's either sister-in-law daughter daughter I think daughter
to me is I that's the one I'm gravitating towards right now I just don't know I'm going knee spinal
answer hey I got 200 neurons for that one and somebody's leaning into the machine I'm going
with this hurry this is painful um I feel like this game you don't win a million dollars like
ever I've sat around and played this but hey guys I've sat around and played this with five people
in the room and we didn't even get to like a quarter of a million so come on relax
which creatures make honey from nectar that would be
blue was the name of a piece of paper given by a seller to a buyer as an acknowledgement of
payment be a receipt I'm choosing b question coming was the name of the daring star uh that
would be lightning McQueen Luigi German would definitely play the slot version of this show
a hundred percent a hundred percent yes I would be super stimulated and engaged if this was a slot
machine and don't forget that slot machine has to run at like 20 fps it has to otherwise I don't
want to play it I don't want to sit down unless it's running at a locked 30 fps uh what object
a curling player is used to slow down or speed up a stone uh broom right yeah we have faith
back in what is the full first name of the spice girl known as Mel C this isn't one of
those questions I don't know I mean it's Melissa melody I mean melody I guess but
Melanie I don't know it could be any one of these Melissa melody Melanie I feel like it's Melanie
Melanie are you you fail fishing me right now there wasn't a time where I ever was like um
what is the spice girl's name what is giving what is all the spice girls names I don't they
would just they were the spice girls there's no way I'll ever get this by guessing so and again
the audience has no idea either but I was Melanie is what I would have said so I'm going to go with
it the audience also agrees we're good Harvard University is in which Massachusetts city I was
fucking Cambridge dude are you fucking stupid who played the title role in Sofia Coppola's 2006
period drama film Marie Antoinette Sofia Coppola and Hathaway and Hathaway and Hathaway Hudson
I don't know this is only the four thousand dollar I can get saying Hathaway I'm gonna say it
ah I don't know movies uh what do I do I have to call let's call your friend okay let's call
let's call Antonio we need your help because Lindsay is stuck on a question oh I might be
able to help her but so we already called this guy believe in yourself you'll see I'm sure that
you're going to be able to help our contestant good evening Antonio don't be afraid this is
completely up your alley just concentrate stop omega lolling stop omega lolling maybe it's the
most likely one I don't wait that I that was the least likely to me
Antonio if it's in Hathaway I'm gonna be so mad it's the end for you well it's no big deal
Kirsten really nice shot damn I never I didn't see that movie I cannot believe the streamer
didn't see the movie and doesn't doesn't know that one how how dare he not know that he didn't see
the movie why does he not know that answer I saw that movie he why didn't he not see that movie
Antonio helped yeah but he was like uh I don't know I could I don't know my ad is probably D
I don't that was not confident D to what or whom does the queen ask whether she is the fairest of
them all the king her magic bed according to the proverb how many cooks spoil the broth I've no
one's ever said this I've never heard this oh only but one cook spoils the broth this is English
this is British shit isn't it this is British shit oh but one cook spoils the broth never heard
this before this is not this is not American this is something this is British or English this is
European I've this has to be that's what I would pick because that's oh but one cook spoil the
no wait only three cooks spoil the broth too many cooks spoil the broth not enough cooks spoil the
broth I mean that's that too many cooks spoil the broth too many cooks in the kitchen that's the
American one I think we all look to this new question uh offering to buy something at an auction
as a bid you have to take a chance okay D you seem to be convinced that he is ready good luck
which of these words describe someone with a very pale face very pale face
I made a pale face why are you batch testing nothing even was on the screen
wait no it's I don't know stop batch testing you're gonna get timed out
what kind of transport would take part in a dog fight in what type of mine did the dwarves from
Snow White and the seven dwarves work a coal mine a gold mine a die it's a diamond mine right
I it's a diamond it's diamonds okay right because they have they hold up the diamond yeah
oh John Paul II was born in which country wait I think it's Italy Italy or Poland wait John
Paul II the pope now who's the pope right now is this the current pope wait who's the current pope
it's one of these two my gut is Poland but I don't I'm not confident but I should be because
it's Poland I'm gonna go with my gut it's wrong and I'm wrong all right okay go with your gut
you're good it's Poland which of these countries consist chiefly of a north island and a south
island New Zealand New Zealand's very small off the coast there I think it's New Zealand
times you have to take a chance okay D yeah all right going well going well going well
uh 8 000 all lifelines are intact from which present-day country did the normans invade England
I should know this I really should I want to say it's Scotland Scotland France I want to say France
France is probably the right answer it's definitely not Iceland or Norway it's France or Scotland
it's definitely yeah it's France it better be yeah yeah nor yep yep I had it I had it I had it
we're good we're doing good the wife of which of these writers shares her name with an American
actress okay hold on let me think this through because look at this we're doing great okay the
wife of one of these writers shares her name with an actress an American actress I don't I have no
idea this is the first account of my mind Charles Dickens but Charles Dickens is is the first thing
I think of but I don't I feel like this is like a piece of trivia that I've heard before
but I'm not confident I really don't know so the first time I'm going to ask the audience is right
no the audience isn't going to know this either but whatever okay I would not have gotten this
I have no idea I did not know this is did a single fucking person in the audience put D
I could have done better but hey I mean no I mean one single person in the audience
nice shot respect for playing the game it was really fun playing with you great player it 60%
of the audience got it no 98% of the audience got it wrong it was Anne Hathaway they asked the
audience only works up until like two thousand dollars by the way so we need to use it early
that was a good one too that was that was horse shit you all know it hi Jerma what the fuck I
don't know what what's up which of these is a type of bear grizzly a grumpy bear
it'd be great if that was actually like a species of bear grumpy bear uh jack black
have to tempt fate sometimes okay see let's go for this new eliminatory question
whose vineyard is a resort island off the coast of massachusetts bartha's vineyard
okay d george michael was the lead singer in which musical duo uh wham which 1986 film centers on the
vietnam war and stars charlie sheen uh platoon right yes yes that's platoon okay yes it is
yes what kind of food was limewald limewald what kind of food is limewald well lime lime
means citrus so citrus adjacent wooled wooled is another name for a crunchy
tart so i'd have to say biscuit because biscuit can have a little bit of um a little bit of that
malic acid apple has malic acid in it and it's part of the citrus family the apple is a citrus
fruit i would get it if you were like what does he talk like some people probably just leave the
stream when i say apples are a citrus fruit and it's the last thing you hear before you click the
x because you have something to do then yeah i get like why is he like so stupid i don't get it
just settle down what's just hanging out what's just fucking around i get it i understand it
though like if i say that and you leave you're gonna really think i think the apple is a citrus
fruit i understand all right in which james bond filmed in pierce rosden make his first appearance
is 007 it's not golden eye golden eye i think is the second time although fuck it might have been
the first tomorrow never dies and golden eye are the two golden eye i think was the second one
tomorrow never dies was either the second one or the first one i don't remember what order they
came out and i just remember burning daylight playing this on my nintendo 64 and that's the
only thing i remember i believe uh tomorrow never dies is definitely not it this is the it's this
one golden eye 007 it was a big deal he was the new bond at the time and it was a banger
tomorrow never dies is the sequel it's definitely i'm overthinking this like crazy it's a golden eye
i'm over am i overthinking this i'm overthinking this it's fucking golden eye get it do it
thank you i just stopped is that you got it uh the horror film the shining is based on a novel by
stephen king all right where we at 8 000 madame medusa is the villain of which disney movie
that's ursula cauldron i don't know i would say this one the fox and the hound i don't remember
the being i'm gonna say it's either the rescuers or the black cauldron do i have all my lifelines
i do don't rush me i'm thinking the rescuers the rescuers are the little animals right it's
the rescuers it's like a little the little um like mice and rats and stuff right it's yeah it's
definitely it's definitely it has to be no single doubt in my mind it's a
madame medusa snake yeah okay we're at 16k let's go all lifelines intact by the way
carrots are a particularly good source of which vitamin vitamin a beta carotene that's the 32 000
dollar question all right all lifelines intact all of them how many original patriarchs or gurus
of the seek religion were there original uh anytime there's just like a singular number
i think i'm just going new question which of these islands are not in the pacific ocean
shit not in the pacific i'm just gracious very in trouble here i think this is a phone call okay
let's get a friend on the line who would know geography cousin sister i i it should show their
profession like sister clown antonio dentist thomas uh teacher i don't know let's go i'm
not doing antonio again fine antonio we keep calling this guy because lindsey is stuck on a
question oh might be able to help her but just maybe believe in yourself you'll see haven't i
answered three or four questions out of a million i feel like that's worth at least 30 lindsey
don't be afraid payment islands i hope you're right okay we have faith is that yeah all right
let's go we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good we're good
64 000 which animal is a chimney sweep in alison wonderland ah it's been so long since i've seen
this fucking movie it's not a caterpillar that's the definitely not the chimney sweep the rabbit
is that i'm late i'm late i have a clock i don't know what i have to i gotta go fast
so it's either a lizard or a ferret i don't remember the being a lizard in alison wonderland
but i don't remember the being a ferret either chimney sweep i'm trying to picture it in my head
but this i don't remember a ferret at all a lizard could be there a ferret is not there
there's no ferret in alison wonderland all right we're almost there 125 000 we got to what two
lifelines one of them is useless because it's the audience what is a gorgane which appears in
some traditional quebec recipes gorgane i don't know ava bean a gorg gorgon gorgane lentil pea
i just know this from silence of the lambs or game i can't really take a guess i honestly just
can't so let's see what the audience has to say okay ladies and gentlemen okay there's no way
75 percent of the entire audience would pick the wrong answer how many people are in the audience
like 100 200 people 100 people there's no way that this mini got it wrong but is it just wrong
that's so many people to get this question wrong but did some of them get it right because i was
going to say b the last time i trusted the overwhelming majority in the audience it was
completely wrong i feel like a p is too simple i feel like that's not correct i think i'm going
to go with fava bean and be pissed because i didn't go with the audience that actually
got it right this time i'm sure that it'd be okay we have faith come on the most important
question thank you the audience is so bad you are so bad i'm never trusting them ever again
there's only two more questions which is the roman equivalent of the greek god of the underworld
hold on roman that's it's not balona kronos is it's nox it's nox we're at the million dollar
question with a lifeline we're at the one million dollar question hope you guys are ready let me
think about this one more time because it's definitely nox but hold on balona is not the
roman equivalent of the greek god of the underworld kronos was fuck i'm second i'm getting in my head
again i'm getting in my head this is half a million stop it's nox nox it's nox it's nox
it's nox kronos was what is dis dis shit i don't know i'm i've i'm all fucked up over this
but what if it's wrong what if i'm overthinking this but i have but i'm overthinking it for a
good reason this time because it is kronos but it's not what if it's diz i'll be honest with you i
don't think i've ever heard i i don't know about this it could just be dis
this chat i don't i don't even want to look at it but it's a mess nox is not the is nox the
underworld nox is she holds the candle she's got the three and her three is a dash forward
and it makes a big thing and and depending how many people you hit with your auto attack
that's nox right balona is you know you've got the sword you can switch to sword and shield to you
know um tanky guardian uh slash warrior uh i'm gonna go in dis finalizer i hope it's right
it better be dis or i'm gonna be very mad it has to be there's no other alternative
yes all right i love so glad i overthought that is that one million dollar question
i just broke my chair hold on this new question is now waiting for you to be answered with flying
in 2020 how many full length winnie the pooh movies had been released ever ever how many
full length okay there's winnie the pooh there's winnie the pooh goes to new york there's winnie
the pooh in the great muppet caper there's winnie the pooh in friends hold on there's
well you know what like we're gonna do this because yo fuck that it's a coin flip regardless
okay i don't think there's been 10 winnie the pooh movies there's nothing 10 10 10 winnie the
pooh movies there's no way there was 10 7 7 for a million bucks let me just sit here and think
these are all of these would have came out between like 1980 and 1995 i can't think of more than two
so there being seven is shocking to me have no doubt seven is already shocking give me the
million give me the million give me the million give me the million give me the million give me
the million give me the million give it a minute give me the million oh my god i that's not the
music that's not the right music too bad that's the game i was like why does it sound so fucked up
why is the sound effect so weird you didn't lose anything but anyway thank you ever so this 10
winnie the pooh movies what do you mean we told you you guys were all saying yay you guys were
all saying yes it was a sea of green lights it was a sea of green this 10 winnie the pooh movies
what the fuck even are they winnie full length winnie the pooh movies you gotta be shitting me
winnie the pooh hold on a second i can't believe there are 10 oh you guys fucked with me on purpose
okay that's sad i you didn't you're not gonna let me get a million dollars that was it winnie the
pooh is one of the most iconic characters in pop culture and these are the seven theatrically
released films about him ranked there were seven where are the other three movies okay how wait a
minute how many winnie the pooh movies are there winnie the pooh there are seven winnie the pooh
movies i win can i get a can i get like a recount there are seven winnie the pooh movies i want a
million dollars i win three were straight to dvd oh that's how they get you so that's how they got
you because everybody would be like wait there was seven but then they don't think of the
the ones at the bottom of the fucking bargain bin at your local video store that had three stickers
on it the first sticker was yellow and said eight bucks the second sticker was red and is two bucks
and it's on top of the yellow sticker so sorry i did not know about the other three i still take
that as a win i think that's kind of where i need to stop playing millionaire because i
i fake won the million but we'll do one more just be fun that was the run i can't believe
it wasn't seven it's so funny because you guys all googled it that's why you were saying green
light you guys googled it and saw seven that's so funny but that's worth losing that question
because that's really funny even google didn't help all right last one and then we'll do some
doubts for a little bit the abbreviation usa stands for united states of um the united sheep
of australia the united sausages of austria all right i'll be right back uh we'll do something
after like maybe like an hour or so i will be rb i'm gonna pick a game out of a hat that was
fun though i enjoyed that i had the itch to play it almost won the million dollars but we can just
pretend i did because we all got it wrong i'll be right back okay i know what i'm gonna do uh i'm
just gonna play for like an hour but i'm about to make like three of you really really excited
the rest of you are just gonna be like oh okay cool but for at least two or three of you you're
gonna fall out of your seat i'm gonna play neon white just gonna check it out play for like an
hour or two i'll be right back