Hi there, welcome. Hope everybody's having a good post-Christmas, post-holiday here.
Relaxation day. Do have New Years coming up in just a few days, but I had a good Christmas.
I did some FaceTime with the family, which is always good. Yeah, I miss them, but it was fun.
The house here, I decided to give a few gifts to each other. Pretty wholesome day, and then
I just sat on the couch, watched TV and played video games, and ate snacks. It was pretty much
my whole day. So today into tonight, we are going to play this game called Kenshi. This is a game
about survival. It's like a wasteland kind of survival game that has top-down RTS, RPG,
hybrid, squad-based. There's a whole lot of crazy shit that can happen in this game,
so I figured I would give it a try. This game is going to be too hard for you.
That's fine. I did read a few things about it. This game is designed for you to just lose,
so by its very design choices, you're supposed to fucking lose. You can read? Yeah, I just
learned. I got this book, How to Read, and I started at the beginning, and now I finished
the book and I can read, but give me one second. We'll get started. I got the game ready to go. I
just need to grab one thing. See you in two seconds. How did you read the book that taught
you how to read? I've read it. It was very easy at first. Starting off each page, it's about
a four to five hundred page book, and the first page is just big symbols of animals,
and you know, I know what that is. It shows you an elephant. I know that's what an elephant
is, and then you turn the next page and there's an E there. It's a giant E.
So, okay, I know what E is. I know what the letter E is, and the next page shows the elephant
again, and it puts E-L, and then by the time you get to chapter 10, you know in appliances
what they are and how to call them what they are. At the end of the book, the Great Gatsby
is in the book. They just put it at the end, so eventually you get there and you can read
the Great Gatsby. It's really cool. Let's get started. What do you say? Let's turn this
music on, turn this off, and here is Kenshi. So I don't really know much about this. All
I know is it's gonna be fucking hard, and it's gonna be a difficult video game,
but it should be fun as a character creator, and you know how much I love those things.
Let's go to the new game. All right, uh, choose your beginning. Wanderer, nobody's,
wanderer, the wandering trader, the holy sword, the cannibal hunter, the hive exile,
son of a captain, the slaves, rock bottom, empire citizen, holy nation citizen, guy with a dog.
Okay, I kind of like, I kind of like guy with a dog. Okay, difficulty is normal. I have, uh,
I have a source on Wikipedia for the amount of money that I have,
and the play style is RPG. A homeless and hungry drifter rescues an abandoned puppy.
It seems pretty useless. Maybe he will just eat it. Holy shit, that's the, I don't know if I want
to eat a dog. Okay, um, I don't think I want to eat a dog, but what else we got? RPG, RPG,
what are these other play styles? Action RPG, difficulty dodgy. I seriously regret coming into
cannibal territory. This is a stupid idea. Warning, you will be attacked immediately upon
game start. Not recommended for a first-time play. This is hard. I'm not ready for the
hard stuff. The wandering trader. No, I don't want to do a trading RPG. Nobody's easy,
easy and hard combination. Guy with a dog. I'm not going to do rock bottom. You've hit
absolute rock bottom. You are alone, unarmed, naked and hungry, lost in the middle of a harsh
desert, teeming with slavers, and you just lost an arm. Good luck. You want me to start
here after I've never played this game before. And you want me to start here.
We can only go up from here. All right, fine. Advanced options, hunger time. I'm not
going to mess with any of these. Yeah. All right. Here we go. Okay. This is called rock bottom.
Heavy inventory will slow you down, but it's a good way to hold the middle mouse to rotate
the guy. I have to make my character create your first character. Use the confirm button
when finished. Yeah, but I do. I'm all right. Idle stance. We can make him golem
the straight up standing. I kind of want number two. I like this one. I know everybody's going
to want me to do this one. I'm going to go with this one. This is fine. Height.
Just make it stretched out guy. I'm just going to take a squid. All right. So Frank
posture. I'm going to turn into a human bow and arrow. All right. I know that's too
extreme. Okay. I already love this game and I haven't even played it. All right.
But how do I shoulder set this so much here? What do you think? All the way back
or all the way? No, we'll just do this. I got a really bad nerd neck and all. I got
to change the leg length. Oh, we go. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
I like this one because this is just realistic enough. Shoulder set. I'm going to say
tight together. Uh, yeah. Down like this neck position. Let's see.
It's like a bird. How could you? You can't have a fully side. Can you make a,
if you're the developer of this game, can you pick a wrestling game?
You know what I mean? Like if you do have the necessary resources to make a wrestling game.
All right. Uh, leg length. Let's go with this one. He's going to be really tall.
Shoulders tight together. Arm bulk. Oh my Lord. Hands. You have big hands. No,
huge hands. It's too easy. Tiny hands. Does this affect how hard I punch?
Chest. No, we're just making a seahorse. Um, bring it down. Stomach.
How tall is this? How tall is he? I don't even know how tall, but this guy's like
nine feet tall. Just give him like a big diaper ass. All right. Leg shape. You need to have
him top heavy or bottom heavy. That looks pretty good anymore. There. Okay. This feet.
Those feet are fine. All right. Face. Holy shit. Oh boy. This. Look at all this. Really.
Oh neck. Oh, you could do. It looks like somebody's arm is up in a sock. This is a sock
puppet person. Neck width. This is just unsettling is what it is. Neck length.
It can be even longer than that. Jaw. Cheekbones. I guess we could go this way.
You can go either width. Oh, it just looks like, it's just like, like Greg House.
Wilson. I, uh, you know, I can't do a doctor house. Maybe I can. No, I can't. Is there a
character named Wilson in the game? Not the game. In the show? Yeah, there is. Okay. Looks
all right. Arch. Let's see. Oh dear. This guy's not going to survive. You say that. Just
wait till he does. What's the, uh, what's that animal from? What's the ice age character?
The squirrel. No, not the Grinch. Definitely has to have kind of mad eyes. Yeah, that's sad
and surprised. This is very upset. No, not that upset. That's a little too much for me.
Can have his eyes bugging at his head. Now he's very concerned. That's good.
Mmm. Two, no, right there's all right. It's kind of got the Homer Simpson. All right. No,
that looks all right. Eye height. Aye yi yi. All right, do we want him to have more face or
more head? I think more head. Didn't you already make this video? Yeah, but the only
difference is there are no mods on this. Eye size. This is just straight up out of the box.
Oh man, look at, you can go all the way in. What do you think? In or in? Yeah, it's got to be in.
It's that. All right. Wait, hold on. I did this other. What the fuck? Wait, hold on.
There's so many creatures. Why did I not know this existed? So this is the best game ever.
You're telling me that I can make other. Okay, hold on. Go back, go back, go back,
go back. This is really important. He's gone. Are you sure about that?
That was very surprising. He's fine. Oh, no, I can't have a guy be a butterfly. Shouldn't he be a
butterfly? All right. Guy, butterfly. Oh, he's the contortionist. This guy's going to be
one like America's Got Talent and try to fit himself into a box.
Okay. It can't be this. That's too much. He has to at least be able to stand. Okay. So
there are, look at, do you see how many people I can make? All right. Perfect. Hair. Hair. Haircut
four. I don't want to see any others. I don't think I should see any others.
I don't want to change it, but I kind of have to. Let's do it. Okay, hold on. What
about beards? No, it has to be the, it has to be that one little swoop over. That's it. 40.
Was it like six or seven? He just looks like any currently airing animated 3D boss of the
main character. And all those like 3D animated shows that are currently airing, this is like
the character's boss. Always. Okay. Beard. There's a lot of beard options. So hold on.
I love how this is just pasted on right here. That's clearly a fake beard. No, that's too easy.
That's all. That's too easy too. I mean, this is so easy, right? But I can, no,
I got to get rid of that. The way it was before. That's actually not bad.
Oh, you can do different hair color. Okay.
The Joker. No, I can't make him like a YouTuber. There we go.
Okay. This is like what happens when you dye your hair too many times.
So it looks good. I think that's good. Confirm.
Primarily from farmer cultures, they still tend to be an aggressive race and they're easily led
astray. The worst of them live in ignorance, knowing only greed and fear, reacting to
anything different with hatred and violence. But the best of them are some of the greatest
civilized scientists, engineers, and warriors in the land. Humans. Yeah, okay. What is,
what is that? I think I, I think we got our character. I'm ready. Confirm.
Naked dude. The great desert. Oh, this is elaborate. Okay. Basic controls.
You can move the camera with WASD to rotate your view. Hold the middle mouse button.
Okay. To zoom, use the mouse scroll. Okay. Where am I supposed to go?
I'm actually in the middle of the desert. Okay. The middle, the middle bottom panel shows
the character in your active squad. To select a squad member, left click the character on the
icon. Select the squad, left click the character icon on the panel. Okay. To give
a move order to your character, right click on the terrain. Easy. Double click on your
character icon to center on the screen and follow their movement. All right. So I can
hold. All right. Cool. You can hold it. Right click on characters or interactable objects
to interact. Hold the right mouse button on to get more available actions. Okay. So
I see. Why is it? Okay. I don't have a name. Splint injuries. I don't have a splint
kit. Okay. Basic controls. That's done. Move around like this. I didn't name him.
Okay. So we got that done. Overview. This shows your selection's current state,
statistics, and other basic info. Mouse over each item for more information. Okay.
Naked dude nameless. That's his first, middle, and last name. State normal, goal aimless.
No, no encumbrance. Martial arts? Minus nine. Strength zero, dexterity zero,
toughness one, dodge one. Okay. Interesting. So it's your dodge skill, your toughness skill.
Interesting. All right. What is this? Athletics XP. This is the rate at which your athletic skill
is increasing while running. Cool. This is the rate at which your strength is increasing. It's
zero percent toughness. Six times. Bleed multiplier. Head. Your head is okay. Your chest
is okay. Your stomach is okay. Your left arm, your limb is gone forever. Your right arm is okay.
Your left leg, everything's okay. And you are getting a little hungry. You're suffering from
malnutrition. Your stats and strength will be affected. You need to get some food as soon
as possible. Stat penalty is at times 88, .88. Okay. So now what? No jobs. To add jobs
holds shift when giving an order. Continue. This shows the selected character's current
health condition. Yeah, I figured that out. The arrow buttons allow you to pause and fast
forward the game speed. Pause. Got it. Okay. That's actually pretty cool. So this is just
like The Sims, but in a wasteland. This is awesome. Here you'll find your character's
current funds and the in-game time and date. Nothing. And this is the day and the time.
Okay. This opens the build menu. There's a build menu? Here you can place buildings
and start your own outpost anywhere in the world, but you should choose a safe area and
check availability of resources using the prospect button. You will also need building materials to
finish construction. Okay. So I need to prospect something first. Buildings. Small shack.
Building material? What do I have for building? Am I just going to make like a
fucking trash box? Should I just build a fucking cube? No, no, that's a bad place for that.
It's in the middle of the desert. I can't even get running water out there. All right.
That's the build menu. You can open your inventory. What is it? I'm in the build menu.
Shit. I got to get out of the build menu. Out. Okay. Here you can open your inventory,
skill statistics, world map, tech and squad management. For tips and tutorials,
make sure to check out the help menu at the very bottom. Character's inventory.
Oh, this is so cool. Limbs. Well, that's what I'm holding on my arms. Total weight.
Disguise. Okay. Status window. Toughness. Max carry weight. Dexterity. All right.
This is a lot. Look it up. There's a lot. There's an open world map.
What? What's that noise? I'm paused, right? Dude, this is, this is bigger than Northrend.
Okay, there's a city over here. Sho Bataille is over here. I got to make it over to the city,
I'm assuming. Okay. Well, there's a couple of cities. There's bark, sho bataille, heft and
stroat. Okay. Faction. Dust bandits, slave hunters, research, crafting. How to research
squad. Dialogue. What? Did that, was that, what was that dialogue? All right. I'm going to
make it to, okay. I got, I got the basics down. This shows the jobs and orders for the selected
character. Jobs. No jobs. The job is make it to the city. Your character is hungry, missing a
limb. What do I do? There is no linear story or mission to guide you in Kenshi. Be a trader,
a thief, a bounty hunter, a farmer, or even a warlord. You'll need to explore the world and
find your own adventure. Tap the M key. You can use the world map to navigate and
find nearby towns or points of interest. So M, right, is the key. Oops. There we go.
Is a true open world. First things first, you need food and funds to survive. To get
started, you can either scavenge the outlands for loot, mine valuable materials from iron
ore veins, or you can even resort to thievery after nightfall. To cash in your loot,
you need to find a store. Use the map to navigate to a nearby town and find shops.
Surviving alone in the world of Kenshi won't be easy, but hiring new recruits will help.
Check the town bars for mercs or buy animal companions from any of the farms outside town.
Remember, you're not special and you're not stronger than anyone else. Train hard,
pick your fights wisely, and don't be afraid to run like crazy.
All right. What do you say? Huh? I'm ready to get started. Let's just go find a town.
You know what I mean? Let's go.
Give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give
it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it a, give it
a, juggernaut. Ow. God damn it. Where's my health. I'm going the wrong way. Quick, Bangal- Bangal tilt. Come on, where is the town? I'm not close to a town. I'm so far away from this place. Chest. Stomach. Lee- okay, I've still got had a pretty good head on my shoulders though. This is actually kind of brutal. This is nothing I can do about this. Don't fuck with us. I didn't, you came after me. Naked dude has been enslaved. Jobs, obedient slave. Uh alright. Leave him alone. Right I'm trying
Do I get up? What is he doing to me? He's been doing this for a really long time.
Your character is hung, you need food to survive. You can grow food, buy it, hunt it, or steal it.
Your squad will automatically eat whatever food is in their inventory.
So am I getting brought into a squad? He's healing me. This guy just let me in his squad.
All right, you appear to be missing a limb. Limbs are useful things to have,
so you may want to get that replaced. You can buy various robotic limbs.
Okay, install new limbs using the robotics. Robotic limbs require skeleton repair kits.
Okay, he actually is healing me. This is great. Building gates and walls. When building walls,
you need to be careful not to place them facing inside out. The arrows you see show the outside
facing direction. You can use the and buttons to rotate before placing them. As with other
buildings, you can only place them when they glow green. Yep, once you're happy, left click
to set it down. You got it. What the fuck? How do I like keep centered on myself?
Where's the camp? Double click your icon. Okay, there we go. Right. Well, he folded me up
like a blanket. I guess we're just going to be with this guy now. Okay.
Oh, fine. I'll just read tutorials while you walk me around. That's good. Welcome to build
mode. Uh, boo. Yep. Select the building and get a building a small shack will allow you
to build a research bench. That's $50 that came in by and I can't even see because
the text is so small. I don't know what I did. Something from the Christmas Eve stream.
I'm unconscious. Well, look at where at least we're going 12 miles per hour. This guy can
run pretty fast. Uh, but first of all, thank you to soup set for the $50. Happy late Christmas
big boy. Thank you. You as well. Thank you so much for the $50. Wait, hold on. I gotta
pay attention. Wait, are we just catching up with me? We're just catching up with the other
people. What is that? Don't trip over that. Those are his buddies. This is his. Yeah,
this is the squad. Hey, what's up guys? Yeah. I'm the new squad member. I'm not really,
I'm not really doing anything. Am I just pretend it's an online game? Yeah. It can't
isn't it? Doesn't this happen in some of these online RPGs? Building a shack will
allow you to build a research bench inside. You can learn new techniques, new shoes,
where to place a building on the terrain. Yes. Yes. Yes. Rotate the position using
the and keys. Yeah. Select squad members and right click the construction to begin
adding materials if they have them. Right. Much quicker depending on the number. Just
like in Warcraft, the more orcs you put on the building, the more they could build it.
How to craft. You are injured. You are under attack. Use the spacebar to pause the action.
This would give you some time to think and plan your next step. When you're outnumbered,
it may be best to jump ship and flee. If you choose to flee, right click on the terrain
to move your character. Make sure you have your character selected. If you do choose
to stand and fight, select your squad members, hold right click on the target enemy and
select attack target. OT attack all from the interaction menu. Just right clicking on an
enemy when the cursor is red also gives you an attack order. Okay. That's, that's what I
thought. You can also, you can select more specific combat modes from the right side
command menu. Block focuses on defense over attack. Passive focuses on non-combat.
Chases focuses on chasing down enemies. Taunt focuses on drawing enemy attacks.
You've been enslaved. You can either live out the rest of your life as a slave or
you can break free and escape. Your character will automatically behave obediently to their master.
If you want to escape, you'll need to dismiss the obedience slave auto job by pressing the
X. Okay. Let's go. I'm out. You can then hold right click on your character to bring up the
interaction menu and unlock your shackles to escape. Careful even if you escape successfully,
you're branded a slave. Oh, I'm unconscious. Just unlock your shackles. All right. I think
we got it. You are KO'd. You've been knocked out. If seriously wounded, the unconscious
status will change to dying and the character won't get back up until healed by another character.
If they don't get first aid in time, they'll eventually die, which is what we saw.
Even after healing, a character will need time to recover before regaining consciousness.
Particularly bad injuries will enter the character into a recovery coma until their
vitals happen. What the fuck is happening? Is he using me as a weapon out of a it's
come on it's a jailbreak ghetto. Is there animals? What is this like a pig dog? Come
on. Come on. Break free. Break free. Come on. Where did the dog just go?
That guy went up into the sky apparently. What was this powerful? They did it. They saved me.
Thanks for the rescue. Hello? Uh, hello? You know, check. I'm still alive down here.
I could use some help. What was the point of that? So there's just another army of
raiders. What are these? Okay, hold on up. I'm still, I'm gonna be just fine. This is perfect.
Okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait. Why are they getting up? Why are they getting up?
No, no, I just don't, don't come get me. Come on. He's running. I think this is a
perfect opportunity. No, they're looting each other. No, I really don't understand. They're
looting the dead bodies. Are they just going to, are they going to forget that I exist?
Because I'm technically unconscious. 1700 more seconds. No, they're healing each other.
Something's going on over here. Uh, that doesn't look like it's very appealing.
Yeah, they're gonna forget about me. Let's fast forward. 1600. Hold on. Yep. Wait,
what'd he say? Wow, wow, wow. What'd he say? Walk right over me. Come on. Oh my fucking god.
It's like it never happened. Is this dangerous? I feel like these sandstorms are dangerous.
Well, I got another 1600 seconds. What? Wait, why is there a giant bunk? Hold on a second.
Get off of this. Hold on. What is this? Put me down. Why are you just standing there with my
body? Where did I go? Why am I still bouncing around? And with my daring escape. Did they
kill it? No. How did you kill this thing? Can I please just get to a town? How much more time do
I have? 1400 seconds. They forgot about me. This is my perfect opportunity to lie here and
just be dead. They don't care about me. I went too far. They forgot. They thought I died.
Perfect. Don't remember. Come on. Just keep going that way. No, no, no, no, no. No.
Just walk by my body. Don't come over here. It's too dusty. You can't even see anyways.
I think we're in the clear. I just have to sit here for 1300 seconds. All right. We'll make our
escape very soon. I can unlock my shackles. Nobody around, right? No giant bugs. All right,
here we go. I just need to wait this out. And then I'm going to eat that bug. I can eat the
bug, right? Bug is back up. How can I? I can't eat that. Can I eat some of these things? The
bug's not going to see me if I stand up. What's like the view distance? I think the bug died.
Is this dead? Wounded. Blood, head. It's slowly getting worse. Okay, this this bug is deer.
Okay, hold on. I'm not food, right? I don't think so. This is a long time to be unconscious.
It's going to be cold and I need to get to the town. I'm going to try. I got to zoom out.
So much dust everywhere. There's the bug. I got to have a game plan when I get up.
This feels... I think you would be dead by now, wouldn't you? If you were unconscious
out here for this long. What's a bug fighting? Some more raiders. I need to take... I need to see
the map. I'm so close to this town. I can put a waypoint here. I'm just going to bang right
a little bit in straight. It's down there. Oh, it's right there. Okay, I just got to get to
the town. Only like five sped up minutes before I can get over there. Can this sandstorm let
up so I can see? Almost there. Okay, hold on. Take a look around. I don't see anything. I'm
just gonna make a beeline for the town. 200 seconds. I gotta get food. I gotta get to work.
I gotta get armor. I need money. All right, here we go. There's a band over here. All right,
I'm actually kind of nervous because this is the first time I've had control in like 10
minutes. Almost 20 minutes without control. It's dark too. I gotta wait. Okay, almost not...
Almost conscious. It's morning. I'm okay. Here we go. Three, two, one, wake up.
Playing dead. If enemies are still nearby, a character might play dead in order to avoid
further fighting. To get right... to get up right click to move, just to make sure there
are no enemies around. Okay, all right, get these off. Unlock shackles. I only have a 23%
chance to get this off. Oh man. Is the chance going down or up? It's going up. Does this
use brain power? I don't think so. Oh, fuck. Here comes the bug. 24% chance. Come on. That's
one out of four. One out of five. I did it five times already. I'm getting skill up
and lockpicking though. What am I picking it with? Um, the sand. I'm filling the lock with
sand and trying to smash it open. So I'm branded as an escaped slave. I'm gonna starve
to death out here trying to get this off, aren't I? Oh, come on. Seriously? No, get up.
Fight him. I'm all right. I got it. Get me out of here. Come on. No, no, go this way. I can't
run. I'm so fucked up. I need to get to this town. My legs... my left leg is destroyed.
My chest is destroyed. I'm going so slow. I still have the shackles on. I... no, I don't,
do I? I don't have any first aid. Get there. Come on, shimmy grandpa. Let's go. I'm so close.
I gotta go to the front gates. Inventory. Boots. Prisoner shackles. Are these armor? Heavy
prisoner shackles. They stop you from running and doing a lot of things. They will trip you up
in combat. They are locked on. You need to pick the lock somehow. This item isn't locked,
but it can stop a sword. I'm good. All right. Run. That didn't mean... it doesn't matter.
I can't run. Do you see all my problems here? Do you see all my sim problems? My chest, right arm,
left leg, and hunger meter. I'll have to go to the bathroom really bad. My chest is going to
piss its pants in about 15 seconds. I'll get there. I don't see anybody, although I'm going
out... kind of going the back door here. Wait, hold on. I see people here. What do I do?
Towns. You've discovered your first town. Towns are perfect for stopping up on supplies and selling
loot. To cash in your loot, you'll need to find a store. Hold alt to show nearby shop signs.
Okay. I don't have anything. Be wary of entering private buildings. Residents often
don't like trespassers. You can find out whether a building is marked public or private
by selecting the building. Also, most shops are closed at night. Let's get these out of the
way here. Too much damage can result in a KO, crippling, and death. The green bars and the
health panels show your health. The red bars show bleeding damage. Bleeding damage will need
first aid. In order to heal, you need to get a first aid kit. You can buy or steal them from
stores in town. You are injured too. To heal a character, you need first aid kit in your inventory.
Hold and right click the target, then select first aid. From the menu or simply right click
the heal icon over the injured person. Yeah. Here it is. First aid. I don't have a med kit. Yeah.
I'd like to know the next step, but maybe it just assumes that I'm on the next step
because I can't- I don't have any of these things. I wish- I want to see like the other-
if I hit skip, it's gonna skip the whole thing, isn't it? Do I have to be unpaused
while reading it? Okay. I don't think so. All right. Just making sure that I wasn't
gonna skip at all. Alternatively, you can click the medic button from the right side
command menu. This will heal all wounded squad members within range. So this one. So I'm gonna-
I'm gonna get a band of merry men. Just you wait. The yellow areas of the health bar show
bandaged health. Over time, this will slowly heal back to a healthy green. Okay. All body
parts are each affected in their own way. Your head, chest, and stomach are your vitals.
So these are vitals. Head, chest, and stomach are vitals. If any of them fall below zero,
you will pass out. And if they reach minus 100, you will die. Well, all right. That's good to
know. If any of the limbs fall below zero, you won't be able to fight or walk properly. You
can use a splint kit on broken limbs to speed up recovery and improve the limb's function if
recovered. Okay. The blood stat shows how rapidly you are losing blood. Blood is slowly
recovered over time, but if it drops below zero, you will pass out. After using a first
aid kit to bandage your wounds, sleeping in a bed will help you fully recover.
You need to build your own beds and camp beds or stay at a bar in town for free.
Let's get in there. Where's the front door? There are people everywhere over here.
Come on. I'm a dying man. Are these storm wind guards? These have to be storm wind
guards, right? As they walk up to a storm wind guard and ask where the fucking train is.
Where's the tram? I keep forgetting where it is. Dust storm. Okay. Just get me in here.
Why is that? Why are you carrying somebody? Uh, I need help. Citizen. Is this a citizen?
How do I interact? Uh, bodyguard. Follow. That's okay. It's samurai. Can I talk?
Why is nobody helping me? This is an elaborate town. All right. Get in there.
I'm just like shimmying around. I need food. I need shelter. I need anything. Somebody please
save me. Well, what's wrong here? What was that? Attack a guard to get healed. Oh,
don't give me that. These guys are freaking me out. Why are you all running like this?
You're just going to bump into me? A dying guy that's covered in blood,
desperately looking for help. Nobody has done anything for me. Is this just supposed
to be normal? Please help me. This is the commander. Gate sergeant. Is there like an emote?
How do I? Can I just go in? Is this loud in the city? Um, no, no, no. I don't want that.
Jobs. Taunt. Sneak. Wave. How do I like say hello? Oh, okay. I can just go in. All right.
First aid. I don't have any money. Go to the bar. Quick. Help me please. I can't go on.
What? Oh, wait. No, no. Get off me. I have. Why am I unconscious? I don't get it. What happened
to me? At least he's going to heal me. At least I'm getting free heals. I passed out at the
steps of the town. This guy, the only guy in town recognizes me as a slave and decides,
all right, yeah, I'm going to go pick him up. He fell. He fell asleep on the walkway.
That's great. It is free heals though. Look, double heals. It's because this is a slave or
town. Oh, well, will they at least feed me in here? What the? Do they give slaves weapons?
That's a, it's like, okay, here's your, what you do and here's what you're going to do and
here's your, here's your knife. Is he taking me to the bar? Where am I going? Oh man,
when we just found our first few characters that are going to, we're going to join together.
Uh, I kind of turned into a t-shirt somehow. How to escape a prison. You've committed a
crime and been in prison. What crime? You need to wait out your sentence, have another squad member
bail you out, or you can try to escape. To escape a prison cell, you need to use your lock
picking skills. Select your imprisoned character and hold right click on the cage to bring up
the interaction menu. Select lock pick. The character must be conscious. Now you need to wait
for success. The speed it takes to lock, to pick a lock is dependent on each individual's
thievery skill. Once successful, hold right click again on the cage and select escape. You
may want to wait until any nearby captors are distracted. Am I, I'm in a recovery coma.
I'm technically kind of out of the cage. How long am I in a recovery coma? I gotta break out
and I'm gonna break out all these people and I'm gonna put them in my squad and we're gonna
escape. I'm getting up. Okay, am I awake? Use tools, use strength. I'm not strong enough to do that.
Unlock shackles and the pick lock is at one percent. I'm never getting out of this cage.
Just do it a hundred times. Yeah, I got it. Okay, get them off. All right, let's get this open.
I'm not skilled enough. I can't even do it. Escape. Now I'm stuck here. It's only been one
day. Okay, I'm not obedient anymore. I have to reset. Game over. Use strength and lift up
the cage. Well, I can't do that. So what, what happened? How long do you sit in here for?
Somebody will buy me? Do I get like a percentage of that money? Normal. Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay.
Whoa, whoa. All right, I'm not skilled enough. You're a slave. Don't forget it. I mean,
yes, I'm aware of that. Oh, it's good. I took the shackles off. You put the shackles
back on. Well, at least I got pants. So why would somebody want to buy me? How many
days do I have to sit in here? Take them off. Is he going to be mad about that? Am I like an
unruly baby? This is my life now. I guess I was standing there for a very long time.
How do I get out of here? How do I like act? When does somebody come get me?
Practice lockpicking. I'm just going to keep taking my shackles up and putting them back
on. This is a good practice. Thanks for the training dummy. All right, I got them off. All
right. Now pick lock still at 1%. Use strength. Escape. He's going to notice. He's
going to come over and put them back on. Yeah, here we go. Here we go. Put it back on. Give
me more training. Thank you. No, no, no. My training went, my sensei went downstairs.
I need him. It's all, it's nighttime. People are going to bed. How do I see my actual stats?
Status, window, combat, thievery. Lockpicking is at 9. Not bad. Why is everybody else just
standing there? Because I think they've accepted their fate. Not me though. I'm
going to practice every damn day to get to a point where I can open this door
and then I'm going to sprint punch that guy in his mouth as hard as I can.
Got it. What level is my lockpicking now? Lockpicking 11. The ability to pick locks,
open doors and safes. More importantly, however, it's also used to break out of
situations. Cages, jails, handcuffs. It's for those who have value freedom and don't want,
don't want to wait around to be rescued. Okay. Thievery is also here.
And I'm just going to wait to get the shackles put on again. Just put them back on myself?
How can I lock them? This is just doing the Rubik's cube. I can't like lock them again.
No, I can't. I have to wait for the guy to come out. Practice on the door. I can't.
I don't have enough skill to attempt the door. Save the shackles to sell them.
Really? How much are they worth? They're worth nothing. They have no sell value. Okay.
You can sell the shackles for iron. Eat the shackles. Speaking of food, when do they feed you?
Because it's been two days and I haven't gotten any food. And then unlock the other...
All right, here's what's going to happen. I'm going to unlock this door and then I'm going
to get put in this one. I'm going to unlock this one. I'm going to keep unlocking the doors
until I have 100 in lockpicking. All right, here we go. Here they come. They're going to
notice again. Maybe they'll have food this time. He's been playing for an hour and hasn't
done anything. No, I mean, hey, welcome to... Welcome to Kenshi! I hear anointed... I did
pick one of the hardest things in the game though. So, you know, I can... I should go
back properly eventually here and do one of the other scenarios. I'm going to... I'm going
to die. I'm going to starve to death in this cage. Uh-oh, he's learning. Shut it down.
No, I'm interested. I'm not giving up on this character yet. I still have faith that I might
be able to pull something off here. Do they feed us? When... How do we do anything?
There's a barrel. Can I do anything with the... Oh! Papa just got a new pair of pants.
How did I get caught stealing? Oh, what is... You rats. What do you mean got caught...
Where are they? I... Who took them? I didn't even get them. All right, stealing chance. 46%.
Get them. Got them. Oh, get fucked. Get fucked over, game. You've just stolen from
someone. Be careful when selling stolen goods to traders. You might just find yourself in
trouble with the law if they catch you. Oh, get fucking destroyed. You didn't think I had
as long arms. How to steal. Be careful. Yeah, well, that doesn't mean anything. I still have
to get out of here. Be careful when selling stolen goods to traders. You might just find
yourself in trouble with the law if they catch you offloading their allies' belongings. When
you talk to a trader, initiate the trade screen, hover over a stolen item, check the
chances of fencing success before selling. If the fencing chance is low and it was stolen from
someone in the same faction, you'll likely be caught. Your best chance of selling stolen
goods is to sell to a trader from another town and faction or find a thief in one of the
town bars. Thieves will buy any item off you risk free. However, their prices
are much less profitable than the official merchant. Careful trying to open locked
items and doors is illegal and could land you in trouble. Well, if you get caught,
as a rule, if the cursor shows red, then that action is hostile. Right. Like every other game.
Entering sneak mode will help reduce the chance of you getting caught while committing crimes.
You can find the sneak button at the bottom of the right of the UI. So like down here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, easy. OI! Wait, do I get out? Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on. Something's
happening here. Okay, cool. Hold on, I gotta put my new pants on. Where are we going? I
thought I don't have shackles on anymore. No, I do. Make a break for it. But to where though? I
don't have anything. I don't have any money. I just got a new pair of pants. I lost the group.
I lost the group on the field trip. I don't remember where I'm supposed to go. Where did
they go? I lost the group. Is this them? I lost the group on the fucking field trip. I swear
to God. I don't know where anybody went. I'm going out the front door. I got a pair of
pants I can sell for one cent. I'm gonna go to the next town. Get me out of here. No, don't touch me.
What if I just hide over here? Where's the sneak button? Sneak. Is this sneak? I don't know what
that means. What's wrong? What? What? No, get me out of here. Go down. Go down. Quick, I need
a bug. Oh, come on. I can't, I can't sprint with these on. I should have kept sneaking.
Where are we going? He's taking me up the slide. This is cool. What's going on up here? Who's this
guy? Wait, why are they all freaking out over here? What are you all doing? Oh, I have the,
I can do it now. I leveled up enough where I can do it. Did I get it? Okay, I got it set free.
Not yet. Unlock shackles. I'm gonna wait till it's nighttime and I'm fucking out of here.
I need to, I gotta steal food from somebody's house or something, don't I? All right, wait till
night. I can open the door. I'm gonna free the other, the other slaves too. All right, time for
night. Just wait till nighttime. We've got a little bit, we gotta wait and I'm gonna, I'm
gonna build a shack in here. This is my new home. Okay, let's go. Uncheck obedience slave. Not yet.
Nighttime. When everybody gets put up here, we're talked to. Hey, dude. No, that's his
naked dude. How do I talk? Outlaw farmer. I'm too far away. I'm breaking this guy out
and we're making a run for it. I can hear a bunch of noises. Hold on. Steal his food. He
doesn't have any food. He's in a cage. Move to the cage next to him.
So you tell, can I, all right, hold on. Nobody up here, right? Okay. All right. Okay, now I can
talk. What are you looking at? You want to get out of here, don't you? So what are you in
for? I'm busting out of here. Are you with me or not? You want to get out of here? He
says, yeah. Let's bust these cages open and run. Then help me get out of here. Let's make
a break for it. We'll have a better chance if we escape together. All right, let's get these
cages open. No, no, no, not right now. Wait till night time. My first friend, but I, he's
going to die because we're both going to die. I mean, I can pick the lock that I just got in.
Nothing in there. God damn it. Are they going to remember that I was in this cage over here?
I'm starving. I know. Oh, my first squad member. Hey, get me out. Okay. I think I just
have to open it. Pick his lock. Okay. Unlock my cage first. Yeah, I know, I know, I know,
but I, what if they come up here? Are they going to know that, use him as a distraction?
Just eat him. I'm not going to eat him. Okay. I'm not opening the door. I'm going to wait till
night. I don't want to open his door yet. Okay. Here we go. Shhh. Guards back up here.
The guard's going to see the shackles. Uh oh. Willy though? They're on. Is that enough to,
let me just get these out of here. By toggling sneaky or entering stealth mode,
in this mode you can perform stealth knockouts, kidnaps, and steal stuff.
The stealth cursor displays two icons, an eyeball and a sun. When the eyeball is red,
it means you are in view of nearby NPCs. When the eyeball is blue, it means that you are
currently out of anyone's line of sight. The sun icon shows the light level. When the sun
is shaded, you are at your least visible. Nightfall is prime for sneaking. Right click
on an NPC while sneaking. The percentage shows the chance of success. The higher your
assassination skill, the higher the chance of doing a stealth knockout. To kidnap
a KOed NPC, hold right click on them. It's like kidnap. How to research. To research new tech,
such as buildings, defensive weapons, blah blah blah. You need a research bench from the build
menu. Okay. So just a Minecraft bench. Either you can buy a house in a town or you can build
your own house outside of an NPC town. To craft items, you need to build a workbench
from the crafting menu. First things first though, you're going to need to research all
the necessary buildings, equipment, and schematics you need for crafting. Build a research bench
to learn new techs and crafts. Got it. I just want to get those off the screen.
All right. It's time of night. Not quite. Almost there. Enslaved the slavers that enslaved
you. I mean, they have full armor and weapons. We have to break out of here at night
and sneak out the front door. No, the back door. Are there back doors?
Don't slow it down. Well, I'm just, I'm scared that somebody's going to, they're
all going to run up here. You're still on board, right? Quick. Look for a way. Okay.
Yeah. I got the, it's in motion. The wheels are in motion. Activate sneak to train stealth.
Is that really? Don't worry. The town will belong to you in a few hours.
There's a ladder on the right. Ooh, good eyes there. Good eyes. I'm starving.
I'm going to pass out, aren't I? If this goes down any further. All right. Somebody
just got the shit beat out of them. They just fell down. There's fresh meat in the
cage and next to me. Let me scope this place out though. Cause we, I do need food.
I'm going to have to take the bread from somebody. Hold on. Let me, where is there like an
inn? Hold alt. Okay. Here we go. So this is prisoner shackles. What? Okay. There we go.
Right here. I'm going to sneak out. This is that those look like dumplings or something,
right? Well, like potatoes. I'm going in here and I'm going to take the thing on the front
desk and we can share it as friends. Ice cream. Here we go. It's time for nightfall.
Should I open up every cage? That might be a good idea. Or just stick with the plan.
All right. Open up every cage or stick with the plan. Which one? It's not technically
really night yet. That's what everybody's asleep. Open, open. No, not yet. The
people walking around all over the place. Save the game. That's a really, really good idea.
There's an auto, it's auto saves every 10 minutes, but there. So close.
Play the pink panther theme. No, that's too distracting. This is, this game's on, see?
Everyone that wanted me to go, there's a night guard right here that goes to sleep in like two
hours. I would have walked right into him. Here we go. When he goes to bed, it's time to get
up. Just go. I can't just go. Don't you understand? It has to be perfect. I don't have
any items. I'm starving. Here we go. Right, he's down there. I don't know, whatever he's doing at
night. Rapidly. Whatever he's doing, whatever he's up to down there. All right, is it time? No,
he's not done. He's not done yet. There's two people doing it too. I don't know where the
second person came from. Okay, but he's downstairs. I think he's done. Use the
ladder. He came back. I didn't know if he came back or not. I didn't, I thought, I thought he,
when does he go to sleep? It's 2 a.m. No, he's going back downstairs to like masturbate again.
No, he's gone. Let's go. Get it? No, there it is. All right, we got plenty of time. He's
got 65 tabs open. Let's go. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Where am I? Wait, where did I, where's my
character? Oh, go, go, Jeremy, go. Just go, go. I opened the door and he screamed. Is he
alive? He didn't even wait for me. They're all down there having a great time. Wait, hey.
No, why is this guy, he didn't cut his leg off. Oh, what the fuck? I can't get out of here.
How am I supposed to get out of here? I need to help him. Honest to God. Okay, he,
I gotta eat this guy. I have to eat him. How do I eat him? Why can they hear, I don't understand.
Why can they hear us? This, I was sneaking. Is it, every time, I'm unconscious. All right,
so when the door opens, they just run up here. I'm safe scumming. Okay, so let me,
let me understand this. So when I, I'm going to open his door. What, really dude, come on.
Give me a break. Turn off obedience. I'm on sneak, but when I open.
All right, will you get the fuck out of here? Turn off jobs. I'm on the sprint setting. All
right, here he goes. Here we go. One, two, three, obedience slave off. Sneak on. Jobs off.
Open door. Escape. Sneak on. What the hell are you doing? Escape. What? What, did I go back in?
What? Obedience slave off. Sneak on. Open his lock. Oh my God, he's back. Get out of here.
Shackles. I know, I know, I know. Wait till he gets out of here. Let the other guy out. Not,
not with this guy sitting right here. He can't see you. You can escape if you sneak. He's
not going to do that. This random party member. I'm going to open his door and see what happens.
Because every time I open his door, he freaks out and just starts sprinting.
Fuck him. Leave him. Look, see? Look, this is not my fault. This is his fault.
Can I like tell him to just not do this? Let's go to the squad tab. He's not here.
This is how to do it. I need my... What? Wait, wait. How? They weren't even here.
The ladder. I can't even use this ladder. How do I know? Because everybody in chat has been
saying I can't use it. I've seen at least five people say that ladder's a prop. Watch. I'll
tell you. Let's see if the ladder's a prop. Let's see if I'm getting baited here. Let's
see if the ladder's a prop. Take off sprint. Let's check the ladder. Hey, look. The ladder's
a prop. This is why I didn't try it. Oh, fuck. I'm out. Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. How am I supposed to get out of here? I can't sneak out of here. I can't even
see in the building. He's going to cause a distraction. I have an idea. I'm going to
open it. I'm going to sneak this way. Once I open it, I got to move this way quick.
I'm going to pause it. Floor button. Floor button. Okay. Ooh, fuck. Okay, hold on.
I can sneak by that. This guy causes a problem every time though. Watch. Good.
All right. Why is he sneaking now? Do you understand? He didn't do this before.
Go. Get over there. What are you doing? I didn't stop sneaking. Look. It's right here.
Fuck this guy. I'm leaving him. I'm taking him. I have to uncheck this box. What? This
guy causes a problem every time. I'm taking his stuff. Here. Like, you know what? Deal with it.
Here. You can have this. I'll just dress you. You can have the shackles too.
I can't manage him. What? What happened? What happened? What happened? What happened?
What happened? Did he just take the clothes? Why did he take my clothes?
He realized. Give me his weapon. Where's his weapon? I can't grab his weapon.
Still the guard's weapon? No, it's this. All right. I got a weapon.
Legally blind. No, it was like a weird stick. Okay. So, this guy ruins it every time.
I open the door and he just walks out. He doesn't wait. He doesn't wait for me. He just goes.
I can't control him. He just fucking walks away. He took you. I know he took the stick.
Kind of like hiding the barrel. Is this building on fire? What the fuck?
Okay. Look. So, we've got guy at the table. Guy over here. What is in there? I wonder.
Oh shit. Okay. Hold on a minute here. Will these guys see? I mean, what's their line
of sight like? Oh, I'm good. Just please tell me nobody comes over here. I'm going to loot
everything over here. Let's go right to the box. You gotta be kidding me. He saw me through
the fucking bathroom stall crack. He heard me. Wait, let me try this one more time.
Jump off the building. No, this isn't the game's fault. I'm playing on the hardest
difficulty in the entire game. I'm playing at rock bottom. So, we have to play rock bottom.
We have to deal with the rock bottom issue. Why did I do that? Because chat pia pressured
me into doing something once again. Oh no, that wasn't one guy. That was like two thousand guys.
All right. Let's try this again. So, is this what is this with the I don't understand what
this is. What is the is that everyone moves together or is that sneak? Is this there's
only this sneak is already activated. That's like fast run. So, there is no other option
besides this. Fucking god. That's not what I wanted to do. Why did he go? Well, I would have
walked into that guy anyways. It's for your whole squad to run together. That makes sense.
Use the ladder this time. Why? We already proved that the ladder is just a prop. It doesn't do
anything. Can I like walk over this? I don't think I can. Six percent chance. Not gonna
get out at six percent. Why is this one so much harder than the other ones?
You train your skills as a slave. Learn to fight. Learn to revolt. Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Everybody wants me to eat this guy and then jump over the building.
We gotta play rock bottom. Right click the ladder. No, there's no context menu there.
You must believe in the ladder. Everything you do makes you stronger. Losing and die makes you
tougher. If you keep reloading sage, you get rid of all that experience you've been learning.
Yeah, this game is about getting your ass kicked. There's another person over here.
I don't think you can go over here, but that would be pretty effective if you could.
All right. Shackles. I'm just gonna go naked. Stealth KO this guy.
Isn't that gonna make noise? Here we go. Watch this shit. Stealth KO that guy with zero
percent. That's not gonna work. What chance did you have? There's none. I can't hurt
anybody. I can't fight anybody. I have to just deal with it. I've got to get out,
have to escape, and I have to find something to eat. And then I'm gonna start over as like
a man and his dog. Climb on the cage and WWE this guy. No, I'm gonna take off the shackles,
unlock the cage, and I'm getting out of here. Once this guy goes downstairs.
I'm trying this one more time. I am on sneak. I am being very silent. No shackles. No,
I don't have any gear on. No gear. Turk off slave. No jobs. No range. Only sneak.
This guy's just... is that guy gonna see me? I mean, he's just sitting right there.
I can't sneak by that. Steal the gear from the back room. I've tried to twice.
I mean, I could... I can't just run. They're faster than me. Maybe... are they gonna... is
their AI gonna go in different spots this time? It is. Okay, good. Go. All right. I made it
around the corner. I'm not moving a muscle. All right. Get me over here. Safe. Oops. All
right. Here we go. He's gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. Quick. What's in the box? There's
nothing even in here. What a bait. There's nothing here. Why? What about the safe? You
don't have any money in your safe. Okay. What about this thing? Nothing. It's empty.
Pick the lock. 77% chance. This is what I get for practicing in the cell the whole time.
Got it. Oh, cool. There's a flip book in here. There's a notebook in here.
Wanted. Cannibal leaders. Leader of the entire known cannibal population. Actual magical
powers unknown. Reward 40,000 C. Sure, I'll... I'll take it. What am I doing? What? What happened?
Was that an alarm? Was the book... was the book alarmed? Did the book have a tripwire on it?
No, he dropped a bunch of frames. Yeah, we're good. We're back. It was trapped?
It was not trapped. I don't understand how it was a book. He's not gonna ever hear it,
right? Okay, so there's nothing in any of these. There's something in here. They can hear you take
stuff. All loot is alarmed in this game. Enemies for three miles will hear you. Oh,
it's because I was reading that out loud. Maybe I shouldn't have read that out loud.
What about in here? There's no stray weapon or food or clothes in any of this shit.
More books. They're gonna hear me take these books. Why am I Naruto running? All right,
I can't pick up anything. I just have to get out of here. I need to get that manga.
Now let's move this way. So here's the question. There's so many guards everywhere.
I don't have any shackles on. I just have a pair of pants. I have no food.
People are saying so much blatantly false shit about this game. So what you're saying is,
chat's trying to fuck me over on purpose. Blatantly false shit. How do I get out of
here? I don't even know if I can get out of here. I think I just have to be a slave.
You know what I'm saying? There's no way I can get out of this. Go out the back door.
I have to go. No, that's just more blatantly false shit. I have to go this way. I have to
somehow sneak by all these guys. This person is going to see me leave this door.
I think I might just have to serve my time. Yeah, I think so.
And I climb through windows. I don't think so. Look at all the guards everywhere. I can't even
pick up a book. They'll know I'm picking the book up. Wait, what's this? Turn off this light.
Auto haul. What? These guys have to get out of the way. Not that guy, the other one.
Serve your sentence. I can't stealth knock anybody out. That guy has the
weapon up there. I have to get that guy's weapon or get him out. Why do I have one
arm? Because I picked the hardest difficulty in the game. Because I think maybe 15 people
thought it would be funny. I can try to run. I can try, but I don't think that's going to get me
very far. Where's the quickest way out of here? I got so far to run. Look at how far I have to
go. If I just click here and do sprint. Oh fuck. Oh my god. I don't even know where I am.
No. No, there's no getting out of here. No, okay. This is fun. That was fun. We're going
to do a new game. This is what I've been on this whole time. I've been on rock bottom very hard.
Zero dollars. You've hit absolute rock bottom. You're alone. I'm naked hungry. You don't have any
stuff. You lost an arm. No, a man and his dog. And begin. Skeleton? Should I be a hive?
That won't make him look weird. No, there's only two. We have to have a human. I can't do
the weird hammerhead shark thing yet. So let's go. That's okay. It's you. Well, that's very funny.
Arm bulk. Legendary posture. Legendary posture.
This looks like I'm wearing one of those comedy sumo suits. All right. That's fine.
We don't need to spend that much time. I'm just making a turtle. That's what it's going to end up
being. Let's go like right here. Oh man. I like the raised eyebrows. I'm not spending that
much time on this one. I just want to get into the game again. Oh boy. Oh boy. It's perfect.
It's perfect.
It's Sephiroth. If they got crushed by a fucking anvil. All right. I'm happy.
Name. I need a name. Where's the name? Anvil Roth. Anvil Roth? No. Canned. Canned Roth. There
you go. I fucking hate it. All right. What about my dog? Do I get to make my dog?
There are other characters' appearance haven't been changed. I'll show you what. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. No, no, no. I do get to make the dog. Or do I? I think I can do anything with
the dog. What's Sephiroth's, what was Sephiroth's weapon called? Didn't he have like a scythe or
something? The Masamune? I can't change this. All right. I'm ready. I start as a man and his
dog. Here we go. Finally. I have a weapon. You've just hired your first recruit. You can
select different squad members by clicking on their icons in the squad panel. By using the number
keys or by left clicking and dragging them in the game. Yeah. Select your new recruit.
You can check your character's skill statistic by opening the stats menu from the command menu.
Okay. Yep. Everyone's got different stats. The dog is an engineer. Oh no, never mind.
All right. To perform first aid, exchange inventory items, guard, follow, and carry squad
members. Hold right click on them or on their portrait to bring up their interactions menu.
Right. Okay. So you can follow. You can follow you. Bodyguard. You can bodyguard. Okay. Bodyguard.
That's what I want. Staying close to Kandroth and bodyguarding Kandroth. I'm ready. Where
are we going to go first? There's so much here. Uh, where are the towns? How many jobs or
anything? Play as the dog. I'm not going to play as the dog. What do I have for a weapon?
Okay. I do have first aid. I have a iron stick. Let's do some scavenging. I'm happy now. This is
I'm actually excited. You know how prepared I am for this? What's this? What's wrong? Get in.
Oh, I just walked away. And from my first trick, I'm going to attach myself to a prisoner
pole and I'm going to escape. Welcome to the magic show. I love how I'm just like
three feet off the ground. Oh, something going on over here. Oh, something happening over here.
Just wait till I get these cuffs off and we'll go investigate. Go watch the fight.
Where the hell is it? Whoa. There's a there's an absolute battle going on over here. Come on.
This is the content. I need to see this. Get out of the cuffs. There's a there's a war going
on over there and I'm I can't go that far. I can only go as far as I can. Did I get out?
I'm out, right? All right. Escape. Let's go quickly. Big Fred Flintstone running away.
All right. Look at this shit. Where's my friend? Come on. Hurry up. All right. I got to be ready
for this. Let's get a good view. There's some major conflict going on down here.
Holy shit. Look at this. You want to know what the plan is? It's called let them all kill
each other and then go pick up all the scraps. Where's the dog? Get over here. I just found a
bunch of free stuff. Okay, here we go. Just be a vulture. No, they don't even care about
me. What? Why would they even give a shit that I'm here? I'm just gonna go start picking up
stuff on people's bodies. I have nothing to do with this conflict. It's just free stuff for me.
Oh, well. Oh, yeah. I'll take a fucking sword. That'd be nice.
Give me all your armor. Holy shit. It's like a rare. That's a rare.
I'm getting rare items. Well, thanks for the immense improvement. Can I even wear this?
Well, what's happening? Hey, I traded you all my shit. You woke up with my stuff.
Uh-oh. Got you. You got anything else on you? No. Next person. Come on. What's wrong with my head?
Pants? Yep. Give me these big armor boots. Not the Minecraft shoes. Stealing chance. 100%.
Was it a standard grade? No, that's good. I'm gonna keep that on. Do you have any money?
This guy has some other stuff too though. What is that? Holy shit. What's that thing?
Just take it. I don't know. Evil thief. All right. Hold. This guy's kind of hard.
Get him. Hit him with your sword. I'm gonna have to start running. Uh, can you not hit him? Get
him. Bite him. That guy has a huge cloud weapon too. This is gonna be like true Final Fantasy.
Does he look like a commander or anything? Is he? How you doing? Oh, shit. I gotta hit.
Give the sword to the dog. That's not how this works. Swing your sword at him. No, wait.
Why is this guy so much better than me? Can I see his health? He's almost dead. Oh my. He's
a soldier and you are a random idiot. Well, how did I take out the other soldier? Don't worry. I
might have been too heavy. All right. Well, let's just, let's get easy stuff. I'm taking
the one person and we're getting out of here. All right. Come on. Is this too big? No. Let's
go. Let's get out of here. Out. Out, out, out, out, out, out. Get out. Okay. Wait. This
is one. There's another sword over here. Get it. And then get out. That's a cool sword.
Take it. I don't know if this is, but take it too. I don't want those pants. Just go.
Am I too heavy? All right. We're far enough away from the battle. Let me see what else this guy
has. I can actually take a look. Attack bonus plus six plus six damage versus animals. It's
the same weapon. Armor penetration. I need to like, I need to, I need to go safe and look
at this stuff. All right. Dog is fine. Dog just has backpack. Does not have anything else.
All right. I'm good. Let us continue. Let's go this way. Oh no, that's the dog. Sorry.
You are on bodyguard and staying close. Good. We're both hungry. At least he is. You can
have conscious characters carry KO'd characters to safety. That's good to know.
Carry them to a bed. The rescue job will find nearby unconscious allies and automatically
carry them to bed if there are any in the vicinity. Interesting. And disguises. If you
have the complete outfit, you can use faction uniforms to disguise yourself.
Disguise success is dependent on the stealth skill stat. Your character status
will show as disguised when you are hidden in full uniform. Okay. Carefully you don't get
caught wearing a faction's uniform. Most people don't take too kindly to impostors.
You got it. So it's time to just explore. I'm thinking we go up to the north here.
Into the cold. That sounds like a good time to me. I need to make a house. I got a lot
of stuff to do. How many money? I got 13 cents. It says disguise blown. Somebody
he's seen through you. Disguise cooldown 60 seconds. We're going to be far enough away
from those people, but it's not going to matter. Whoa. What happened over here?
Something crawled as a person. Are you alive? Saber cutting damage 39.
52. Blunt 0.02. Blunt. This is better. Blood loss is just better. Attack bonus minus 5
plus 6. Indoors penalty. There's an indoors penalty on this one. Wait.
This is much lighter. Oh fuck this thing. What about this?
Metal plate. Blunt resistance 7. 17. It's actually better. Shirt. What's this? Cut
resistance efficiency. This is armor. Yeah. It is lighter though by a lot. No it's not. Yeah
it is. What happened to my boots? Did I just throw the boots in the ground? Where did my boots go?
What happened to my shoes? Did I- Where did the shoes go? I didn't- Oh right. Because
it- Okay. I forgot. I didn't save it till then. Let's check this other guy.
Blood loss 6.5. 13. It's actually better. Attack bonus minus 4 though. I'm not sure
that's better from what I have right now. More defense. Carrying too much stuff. Well,
I'm going to get- I'm not going to use this so you can have it in your
total weight. 38 out of 15. Oh shit. Okay. No, I am too heavy. Let's see what happens if I take
that off. 18 out of 15. 13 out of 15. That's all right. I got- That's all right. Use the
cloud sword. Armor penetration damage versus robots. 19 out of 15. Wait. What did I just-
God damn it. I mean I can't pick that up. Why can't I pick that up? That's fine.
Uh, I can sell this stuff though. How much does it sell for?
1700. I don't even care how much I weigh. I will slug my way to a ton. Weapon 2. No,
it doesn't fit in that slot. All right. Well, I'm going to be- I'm very heavy, but
where- having this- just wearing it? Is it train strength? So I need just to weigh down
on myself. Does it matter if it's in my inventory or do I have to put it on?
Click on the name of the item. So you hold alt. Can't pick that up. Well, I'll just keep
that here for fun. So I can't really move that well, but let's go up here. So I'm going
to bang them right- actually I can just go like this, right? Yeah. So I'm going to move
very slowly, but I don't want to walk across the battlefield. I'm not going to, right?
I mean I kind of am. Yeah. I'm untouchable right now. Don't worry. They're all fighting
over there. I just need to slowly- where's my strength? Let's see stats. Strength. 28.
28%. 29%. That's so- you actually have to strength train. I'm probably going to get
hungry doing this, aren't I? What's that on the ground? Popcorn? Got to hit the gym.
I do have to keep an eye out for a town. Ooh. No, that's a camp. But what is that,
though? I mean, should I investigate this? Probably not. There's nothing here. No bandits,
no slavers anywhere. That's good. I'm okay for now. I'm just going to slowly make my way.
Strength. This is the lamest thing. Click the building. Public. Hamlet condition. Small shack.
Doesn't say anything. Speed up the game speed. Yeah. I'm just like kind of walking slowly.
Okay. How close are we now? Not close at all. Can you build a car in this game? That's
interesting looking. Let's keep going. Discovered- wait, what did I discover?
Ravaged Hamlet. This is the zone? What's my strength doing? What is that? Ravaged Hamlet,
guard outpost, bast. There are four people that live here. 14 live in the city. This is
just nothing out here over here. Then what is that? Hold on. I have to discover. Well,
let's just keep going. Oh, it's dark. I need to set up a camp or something. Like a campfire?
I hear something. I hear something. I hear something. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. I heard like clanging. Was it me? It might have just been me.
What's that? Is that a new squad member potentially? What is it? It's a bone dog.
Oh no. I'm gonna say this game is huge. Food. It's food. It's food. I can eat that dog.
I'm okay though. We're not hungry. I can make it. I played for three days before I
saw a camp. Holy shit. Discovered Watchtower. Let's take a look at what it is.
Watchtower. What do you think? Should we check it out? Let's go to the Watchtower. All right.
This does, this feels so stupid. Okay, slow it down. I want to see where we are. There's the
Watchtower. The question is, what is in the Watchtower? I see a band of, I'm not sure what.
Are these raiders or hungry bandits? I don't want to cross their path for sure. Whoa! Go
this way. Go this way. Go this way. Go that way. Go that way. There's so many people right
here. These are paladins. Oh wait, no, no. This is fine. Paladins are not going to attack on
sight, right? Why would they? Yeah, I'm just going to avoid them. I want to go into the
tower over there. That's not where they're going, right? Holy Chosen. Holy Sentinel. Quiet.
Let's go. I'll get up there. He's five times wider than he is tall. They're going a really
weird route. I think I'm okay to run. What's my strength at now? Three. I'm doing a great
job just walking around with incredibly heavy armor. All right, we're good. Both sides. Let's
get up there. What's in here? Arm of Okren. It's finally going to be light out. Why is
everybody freaking out? Don't, don't, don't. Don't go in there. Don't go in there. Don't
go in there. Don't. Why? I can, I can have a conversation with these guys. Save it. I'll
save it. Fine. Okay. Conversation. Let's talk about what we can do for each other. I've got
some supplies. If you guys have anything I can trade. There is no, like I had a chat bubble.
Out of bounds. Get out. Who had the speech bubble? I can sleep in their beds. All right.
That's fine. Leave. Oh, all right. All right. All right. Relax. I'm leaving. There's the
guy with the speech bubble. Why aren't you leaving your trespassing? Get out. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Talk to Paladin. Blessings from the Lord of Light, brother. Okren's light
shines brightly today. A good omen. Any travel advice? Any tips on how to live more
wholesomely for an Okrenite newbie? Greetings. Are you free to discuss the word of Narco?
Sorry, I have to go. Any tips on how to live more wholesomely for a newbie? Study the scriptures
of light, meditate on them, pray to Okren, and respect his holy servants with an open heart.
Brother, this is the way to a pious existence. For darkness preys on an undisciplined mind.
As for duty, if you are blessed with the skills for it, you may carry out
Okren's retribution directly by bringing marked heretics to the Inquisitorium. Any travel advice?
Venturing on a pilgrimage, brother? Well, it's best to stick to holy territory. The
Outerlands are infested with Narco's heretics that will try to deceive and tempt you into
the darkness with them. But if you must venture further, above all else, you must avoid
traveling northwest. Only the most devilish monstrosities prowl there a hundred times
the size of a man with the hunger of a rabid demon. Isn't that where I was planning on
going? The foolish treasure hunters are the only travelers to delve there and never to return,
but how tragic it is. There's nothing worth searching for. There's no place for riches
if Okren is already in your heart. Thanks for the info. Alright. Hey, thanks. That was
actually some pretty good info. You have any food? What did I do? I saved the game!
They didn't like that I saved the game! What?! What are you doing?! Hey! I don't understand!
Where are we going? Why is this happening? They told you to leave so- I just had a conversation
with one of them! I was literally just talking to the guy for like 10 straight minutes
about Okren and thanks for the tips and advice. Time for me to leave. Goodbye. See you later.
Where's the dog? Uh, time- dog only. I don't understand. I- I don't get it. I was just
having a conversation with the dude. First aid. Yes, use it. Just run. Run and don't look
back! Get out of the cage quick! Get- pick the lock! Get out of the cage now! Alright,
I can- dying. I gotta go quick. Quick quick quick. Get out. Get out. Out out out. Okay,
set free. Escape. What am I- what am I- what's wrong with you? Why am I crawling? Get up!
What's wrong with my leg? Come on! What? You're there. You're not welcome here. Don't
make me ask you twice. I can't even stand up. I was gonna fucking leave! I wasn't- I was
talking to the guy out in front- in the front door. Like, I was standing right here having
a conversation on the steps of their house. Alright, let's go. See, out of bounds. Get
out. Like, but I- I- I'm gone. I'm gone. Bye. See you later. Thanks for nothing.
Having a conversation doesn't sound like leaving. Well, so if they want me to leave
so bad, why would that guy have a full conversation about like the Lord of Light with
Get out of here, you piece of shit! You're a scumbag!
Hey, uh, so the Lord of Light- uh, let me give you some tips first, Bob, by the way.
So go- if you go- don't go to the Northwest. There's some scary guys up there. Be careful.
Oh, if you want to- one other tip. Uh, make sure you have enough supplies and-
Kill him! Murder him and his dog!
You sounded like a YouTuber there. Alright, where am I going? Where am I allowed to be?
Okay, here's the actual town. We're going to the actual city. It's right there.
I have too much armor. Yeah, but I'm building up strength. The YouTuber voice.
There's shit going on over there. Maybe I- they told me not to go up here,
but that kind of makes me want to go up here. Because
maybe they're just liars. It's a dog. Come on.
Oh, we gotta match speeds here, man. I'm like losing the dog.
Come on. Get over here. Quickly. We have to stick together.
There we go. You're gonna have 20 people in your squad.
That's actually insane. Maybe I should just make a camp or something.
What do you need for materials? To run your own camp.
The dog is the only smart one here. Okay. I'm gonna build a house over here.
There's so much to explore. I don't even know where to go.
I don't know what to do. I'm so overwhelmed.
I'm just gonna go this way, I guess, until I find another town?
Wait, hold on. Now, these are holy servants. We're fine.
How's my strength? Minus two? For what? Because I'm hungry.
Don't have any food on me. Just build a house. I can't. I need materials.
Are these holy? Holy servants. Yeah.
Southwest is a good starter area.
Well, that's gonna take me a long time to get there.
Okay, hold on. Should I just bang a U-turn and go down here?
I'm gonna go down here. Hey, hey, you're going too fast.
Going too fast. Stay with me. These guys hostile than not, right?
All right. Any huts? Any...
Okay, there is a congregation over here.
Discovered farm ruins.
There better be steaks and sodas and shit, like canned meat and stuff.
And this is taking me up.
See if we can find anything in the ruins.
All right. I don't see anything over here.
This looks fairly safe.
Is this a campfire? There's a fresh campfire here.
But that means there probably are supplies somewhere.
Hold alt? I am. I'm holding alt right now.
Nothing at this fresh campsite?
How can there be nothing at a fresh campsite?
What am I looting?
No, I don't have any meat in here.
Okay, that's a nice nap.
No, nothing else in these ruins.
Wait, is that like a... what's that?
Nothing.
Well, that sucks.
How can there be nothing in here?
Hold up, traveler.
Speak with me. Speak... whoa, whoa, whoa.
Speak with me.
Hello.
Love and devotion, brother.
Welcome to your motherland.
The sacred domain of the holy Lord Phoenix himself.
Blessed be his name.
Evil lurks in all shadows of the land.
But Okren watches over you here, brother.
Where you belong as a pure blood.
Okay, thanks.
Blessings on you.
I guess you want...
Blessings... I'm going to play the part here
because I'm wearing their uniform.
Blessings upon you, brother.
It's easy to find danger and lose your path
when you journey away from the holy cities, my brother.
Remember to stay true to your purity
and take refuge in the holy Lord Phoenix himself.
Blessed be his name.
I agree.
Now you look starved half to death.
Here, take this.
You need these rations more than I do.
Be well, brother.
Thank you so much.
Hey, take a look at this.
Rations. Food pack.
So this is free stuff.
Ingredients.
Food cube. Dried meat.
So I need to eat this right now.
How do we split it?
Pick up.
No, no, no, no, no.
Put the dog down.
Why is he carrying it like this?
How do I put the dog down?
Okay. Jesus.
They eat, you eat automatically.
You do?
You just eat it automatically.
Oh, okay.
All right.
Oh, you do.
Okay.
Nice.
First victory of the night
and it only took two hours and 41 minutes to find food
and I didn't even find it.
Somebody gave it to me.
Somebody entered my Dark Souls game
and dropped like 20 humanities on the ground
and then waved and fucking disconnected.
Hey, thanks.
I appreciate it.
Right. Let's see if there's anything here.
Let's zoom in on the map a little.
I want to see if there's any towns, man.
Farm ruins.
There's nothing there.
I was told not to go this way because it's dangerous
so I'm going to go this way.
We'll go around and down.
Well, once we hit the lake we're going to go down here
so let's just make our way this way.
I'm still in Paladin territory, I believe.
So feed your dog.
The dog eats at the same time as you, right?
Are we not sharing this food?
No, we're not sharing the food.
Wait, why?
I got to put the food in the dog's inventory.
How do I keep them both open at the same time?
The dog can't eat from your inventory.
You have to drop it on the floor and put it
or put it in your backpack which you don't have.
Okay.
What happened?
Who ate the ration pack?
He ate it.
Well, why is he still at 130?
He ate the whole pack.
He ate the...
You ate all of our rations.
That's all we had.
What?
Of course, you can't like leave food on the ground, guys.
Yeah, just take like 20 sandwiches
and put them down on the floor
and your dog will just eat one of them.
This is the way I wanted to go.
No, I wanted to wrap around here.
All right, we're fine.
I wanted to go around this way
so I kind of went the wrong way.
Dog equals food.
No, that's not going to happen.
I'm not going to eat the dog.
You probably can't even eat the dog.
Something over there.
What's that?
Distraction.
Let's see.
Dog?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with it?
Oh, okay, you got stuck.
All right, let's take a look.
Holding alt, looking around,
seeing if I can find the items
in this broken down house.
Oh, perma jobs.
You can organize your squad
by assigning them jobs in the orders menu.
It's especially useful for farms, mines,
and other production jobs
since assigned characters will automatically store
and replenish raw materials as they work.
Okay.
Well, it's the holy servants.
To assign a job, select a character,
then hold shift while clicking
to interact with the object
or building you wish to assign them to.
Okay, hold shift while right clicking
and on an object.
Then you can assign a job.
You can give characters multiple jobs.
Top most jobs in the orders menu
will always take priority.
Okay.
You can remove a job at any time
by pressing it on the X.
So why did it tell me?
Really?
Can you do this?
What am I getting from this?
Am I going to get materials?
Do I have a progress bar?
I'm being a real dwarf.
Is this completely futile?
I'll just show this left click on the thing.
Output.
Copper.
Proper quality.
20.
Workers, zero out of two.
This is the progress bar?
I'm not mining them.
I'm mining something else.
Okay, that's the one.
I'm going to build a house right here.
I'm going to build a fire.
I'm going to build a house.
You are so stupid.
My two-year-old sister has a higher IQ.
What?
Because I didn't know which...
What do you mean copper?
How was I supposed to know?
Like they're all the same thing.
Look at this.
Like I don't even know which one
I'm standing in front of.
It's apparently this one here.
I'm here.
It's over here.
All right.
You need to like patrol or something.
Mine with the dog?
I can't.
He doesn't have opposable thumbs.
He can't do it.
Oh no, he's got the zombies.
Did I get something?
Why did I stop?
I'm doing fine.
I kind of have to get this, right?
Yeah, this is like the point of the game.
You just are a piece of shit.
You can't do anything.
You should find a town before mining.
Well, I almost have one copper bar
that I'm going to get ripped off of my person.
It's taking me almost a full day.
Come on.
Paladins were fine.
Which one is this again?
Copper.
Got it.
Average price, 100.
Thank you.
Yep.
Valuable metal used in high-tech machinery.
Get another one.
Mercenary plate?
Where did I get this?
Oh, right.
That was so pointless.
No, there's...
I'm going to get three.
Okay.
There's no room?
I can move.
I'm a Diablo II veteran, guys.
I'll make room.
You say no more room.
Where is...
Stalling streamer.
This is part...
I have to do this shit.
It's not like I'm just going to skip this.
Let's take a look at the mining level.
All right.
We got combat range, thievery, sciences, trades.
Is it even on here?
Field medic, laboring, laboring.
Okay.
Laboring nine.
I'm very good.
Scale of general manual labor such as mining
and using simple machinery.
Level 10.
Coming up.
Ways to train.
Work hard.
I'm making up for all the slave work that I did not do.
If I get this game, I can start the game as a slave
and work my way to freedom.
Yes.
You're not supposed to do anything good in this game.
You're supposed to be a aunt of a person.
And not only am I doing this,
I'm doing this with full armor on.
Did I say this joke sucks?
What joke?
This is the game.
This is the stream, man.
We're fucking mining for copper bars.
All right.
How close am I?
Got one.
All right.
One more.
I can get rid of this hat.
I don't need this.
Value 10 cents.
No thanks.
These things are like 180 bucks.
Please stop.
This is not a bit.
I'm mining for materials.
I need the materials.
I'm not doing like a look at how long
I've been sitting here for.
Isn't that fucking hilarious?
No, I'm trying to get three copper bars
so I can use them how they're intended.
To smash somebody over the head with them
because they're just big rocks
and then throw them in the trash.
Okay, we're done.
That's it.
I got what I wanted.
I got three dinosaur eggs.
My three dragons.
They're going to net you 10 copper.
No, look at the price.
194 cents.
The cave up here.
Put a face cam on to replace world's end.
Go south, not north.
I beg you.
Stop acting like an idiot.
All right.
Look, I want to make this really clear.
I don't know what's up here.
If you do, I don't have that information.
How would I have that information?
Because I'm going this way.
No, go this way.
I know what's down here.
I don't what?
I know that there's like evil demons up here
but like I can't go this way.
Why can't I go like over here?
I have to go down here.
Why can't I go over here?
They told me not to go up this way
but like I'm not going this way.
I'm going like this way.
I'm going from here to here.
You know what I mean?
Like I'm not like going up.
I'm going like down there.
That's the plan.
But I want it to like wrap around here though.
I want to like go this way
because there's a lake here.
There's like a river and shit.
I want to see what this is.
Look, I understand this is one of those games
where like there's no way I could know what anything is.
And if I'm going to stumble upon something fucking weird
that's what's going to happen.
I don't need to know like exactly where to go.
There's no information in the game
besides like when people tell you.
You know what I mean?
Look, his world's end.
I want to see what this is.
He doesn't know where everything is
because there's the guard post, right?
Pick up the dog and carry the dog.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, he's a holy servant.
That's fine.
All right, hold on.
So what is this?
This is all the way up here?
Am I going to scale this whole mountain?
Oh, hold on.
Important.
This is not going to take as long.
Put your face cam over the character's face.
I don't know.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't even bring it back now.
My hands are off.
I can't even do anything.
Oh, you got to be fucking kidding me.
Really?
I'm all the way like the edge of the map.
I can't even move.
Got it.
Okay.
Where was I running?
Did I get the material?
Oh, fuck.
I don't have any room for this shit.
All right, hold on.
There.
Better?
Are we good?
Why is that so funny?
I don't have enough inventory space for this shit.
Hold on.
What can I do with this?
I can move this over here.
Hold on.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
They stack.
No, they don't.
Fuck.
Okay.
Just scared the shit out of me.
I can't carry this anymore.
How much is this worth?
32.
No.
Why would I just...
What happened?
Okay.
This is worth a lot.
That's worth 1,000...
That's worth 1,700.
Backpack?
I don't have a backpack though.
Like, I don't have a backpack.
I can't put anything in my backpack.
I don't have one.
The dog inventory.
I don't think he can carry them.
What can the dog have on his back?
The dog is dying.
Feed the dog.
I don't have any food to feed the dog.
Oh, shit.
Okay, hold on.
I gotta get one more fucking rock.
All right, let's go.
Where the hell?
This is so far away.
Do I have any...
Can I eat anything?
I spent all the time mining and not getting any food.
There is a town up here.
Let's go.
Quickly.
Come on, we're gonna get you some food, dog.
You're okay, you're all right.
You're gonna be fine.
I just gotta get you up here.
Go on.
What was that?
I just saw something on the screen.
Put a picture of Otto in the dog portrait.
No, because if this dog dies, I'm gonna be sad
because it was supposed to be Otto.
No.
I feel like I'm losing my grip on the dog.
I need to eat too.
Bad.
There is a town up here.
Somewhere up here.
Don't tell me I have to scale the entire mountain.
How high up is this place?
I'm at almost zero.
I'm gonna pass out.
Should I throw off the armor?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm almost there.
I'm almost at the front door.
61, 98, we're good.
Just get me up there.
Throw away armor.
I'm right there.
Look at this.
I'm standing in front of the gates.
The weight is doubling your hunger rate.
But that's all right though.
It's giving me extra power, extra points.
I am persevering through this shit
and it's gonna give me more points in the long run.
Here we go.
All right, I made it, I made it, I made it, I made it, I made it.
These are tech hunters.
Okay.
Look, I got a fucking sick dog here.
Okay, what can I save it
just in case something horrible happens?
Anybody?
I can just come in here?
Okay, they're not gonna like
throw me in a dungeon or anything, right?
Perfect.
Got it.
Okay, quick.
Food.
Shop.
Because that's a men's room.
I don't have to go to the bathroom or anything.
Bar.
Okay, let's get in here.
Sell the armor to this guy.
Okay.
Talk to.
Let's trade.
Metal plate.
Here it is.
Value, it's 17.85.
I'm gonna get 4.46 for it.
Where's my money?
How do I sell it to him?
Got it.
Okay, how much money?
Okay, how much are these?
You're gonna give me 97, 97.
I mean, I gotta get food and shit, man.
I can't just not have food.
We gotta sell it all.
I need money.
And take this fucking dumb weapon too.
Maybe I should sell this.
What do you think?
I think I'm gonna sell the armor as well.
But I need food first.
Dog needs it now.
Let's go.
Okay, I need, I need like a general store.
All right, the bar.
This is so brutal.
I don't, the dog's up.
The dog is up.
The dog is okay.
I'm only unconscious for 15 seconds.
All right, come on.
Come on, just crawl to the bar and buy a fucking pretzel.
Go, go, go.
Get in here.
What in the name of God?
What happened?
I just clicked a fucking ad on a webpage.
All right, I need a bar.
Bartender, hello?
Where is, I'm just stealing it.
All right.
Yeah, hey, heading out of town looking to join up.
Yeah, it'll be 3,000 cats.
Where's the, where do I just buy something?
Right here.
Uh, show me your goods.
Here we go.
All right, bread, cheese, meat, tacos, meat wrap.
How much is this?
It's 316 for the meat wraps.
How much is bread?
This is so much money.
How much do I even have?
13, okay, hold on.
Meat and bread.
Okay, I just ate it.
I don't have enough money.
Okay, where's the dog?
Come here, dog.
Where's the dog?
Come here.
Eat it.
How do I feed the dog?
Did you get it?
You got it.
Okay, we're good.
You're three times idling right now.
They're both eating.
They're both hungry still, but it's okay.
I need to make some more money.
Now let's go back up here.
I gotta sell some more stuff, I think.
I can't like, hold on the alt key to steal.
I'm not doing that.
All right, talk to, let's trade.
Um, dried meat is so, so much cheaper than everything else.
And I spent 300 fucking dollars when I could have just bought this.
Hey, are you stealing my dog?
Why are you taking my dog?
What?
What's going on?
What's happening?
Oh no, the dog's not allowed inside?
All right, so they've eaten.
Okay, we're good.
Bodyguard.
Here, eat it.
Eat the meat.
Did they not want it right now?
I think they're okay.
So what, do you only have to eat just one time?
Eat for yourself, I already did.
I already ate earlier.
I guess, can you eat more than one time to speed up?
I already ate.
Load the game and buy all the cheap shit.
It was poisoned.
The dog keeps passing out and waking up.
I bought the expensive fucking food.
You can't eat until the bar stops.
Yeah, that makes sense.
All right, I got an idea.
It's worth doing.
I don't care.
There's so much shit to take.
Chew sticks.
Nobody can see me right now.
All right, we got Saki.
Took it.
Committing crime.
Oh, please.
I don't care.
Water.
Cactus.
Hacksaw.
Nobody's seeing this.
Chew stick.
Let's just see.
Let's go over here.
Red.
Chew sticks.
I can't pick that up.
Be too far away?
Am I visible?
No.
Chew sticks.
Why do I, what did I pick?
I'm going to go sell this.
This water jug is huge.
Okay, I got food.
Chew sticks.
Meat.
Saki.
Let's go sell the hacksaw back to the person that I just came here from.
No, actually, I can't do that because they know.
How many times does this dog keep passing out?
And waking up.
Fuck.
Nobody can see this.
All right, let me get up.
I don't have enough money, but I can't, I'm not going to sell to you.
Let's do business.
It'll say, right?
Stolen from you.
Fencing chance.
10 percent.
So, no, that's not going to work.
I need to get that huge, I feel so bad for the dog.
All right, let's go.
Still, the hunger is still going up though.
So, eventually, the dog will be okay.
Let's go sleep somewhere.
You know what I mean?
What do we got?
This is armory.
I'm going to sell, I have to sell this.
I have to because I just don't, wait, it's, everything's locked.
That's a bar.
We've been in somewhere.
Sell that guy the water from across the street.
I mean, I can't really do that.
It's a lot of bars.
Yeah, it looks like a weapon shop.
Tools.
Bar.
Where can I sleep?
Traveler?
That's a guy with a backpack and a walking stick.
That's like, travelers, welcome, right?
Okay, let's try it.
The bar, bars have beds.
Okay, so let me talk to who's in charge here.
I don't think either one of you are in charge.
You are.
What's the percentage chance that I can sell to you?
Why am I going this far around?
John, what you got?
Backpack.
Robotic arms.
Skeleton legs.
Skeleton arms.
Fencing chance.
20%.
That's not going to work.
I got to go to a different town.
I need more money.
Poor dog.
It just keeps getting picked up.
Leather.
Leather, but I can't carry this.
I need a backpack.
Splint kit.
Chain mail sheets.
Wooden bowl.
No, I'm just going to have to...
Here's what's going to have to happen.
I'm just going to have to let the...
I'm going to have to sleep in the bar.
And then hopefully when we get up, I'll feel better.
How much is a room at the inn?
Is it expensive?
Can I afford it or can I just sleep in here?
Don't idle in times three speed.
Was I?
Sitting pillow.
Okay, well I can't sleep in this, but maybe I can go upstairs?
Are there beds upstairs?
Where's the dog?
Dog spine.
There are beds up here.
Are they usable?
Everyone just got up at the same time as if they're about to all shout like,
Stop!
200 fucking C for a bed.
I need more money.
This is why I needed to mine more shit.
You just had to have those expensive sausages.
I just didn't realize that they were...
Everything was so expensive.
Like, okay, the scale that I had there was sausages
and the bread was fucking 250 cents.
I already...
Look, I already fed the dog.
I can't feed him anymore.
This is just going to have to do for now.
Can I eat these?
I can feed the dog more.
Yeah, what are you guys talking about?
No, you can't.
Oh my god, I'm gonna get caught for stealing this
because I just put it on the ground.
All right, I'm not gonna...
I know what's going on.
There is a cool down period when you eat.
So I just need to sit around.
I need to find a place to sleep or hang out
because I can't really go anywhere until this hunger thing wears off.
Yeah, I have to abandon the bread because I can't pick it up.
If I pick it up, this guy is going to see me do that and I stole it.
You don't need to sleep now, it's for recovery.
So that doesn't make hunger go up faster if you sleep.
Like it doesn't make it go up.
All right, I'm going to tell you just forget about all these jobs.
You need to hang out somewhere.
Just like go sit over here and relax.
I'm going to go out and I'm going to mine a few more times
and I'm going to bring them.
I'm going to just you hang out over here.
Just you stay.
I'm going to go and I'm going to take care of this.
Just throw the...
This thing's huge.
I don't want it.
I need room for fucking mining things.
Back to the mines.
Let's go.
He's going to starve?
No, he's not.
There was a mine right out here.
It was like right...
Where was it?
Out here?
Like the back door?
Side door?
Where was that mining thing?
There might be another vein just sitting over here somewhere.
Why do I walk so slowly?
Because I'm building up my strength right now.
The heavier shit that I wear.
So if I go over here, let's see strength.
Is that 17 right now?
It's because I keep wearing this heavy ass armor.
So let me take a look and see where that vein is.
There is the other side.
Wasn't it like down here?
Where was that vein?
On the side?
What the hell is this?
That's like where he is.
Okay.
I wish I could pull the camera out a little bit further.
Because it's kind of hard to see anything.
See how like the...
See what's happening here?
Just like...
The camera's like freaking out every time I get to like a divot.
All right.
I can't go any further.
Was it down here?
I think it was down here, right?
I hope that I'm...
I hope I'm clicking on this.
I'm not sure if I'm actually clicking here.
Or if I'm getting blocked by the...
No, it looks like I am.
Yeah, I got it.
Okay.
All right.
I need to mine at that vein that's down here somewhere.
The hell is it?
I feel like it was right here.
Maybe a little further back?
There it is.
All right.
Just let me mine here.
So give information on the richness of resources.
Prospect.
Zone arm of a green environment.
Wait, what?
Resources of water, iron, fertility, copper.
So this is just...
That's what prospecting does.
Just shows it.
Okay.
I'll get over there and mine it.
How's the dog doing?
Oh, god damn it.
The dog needs to eat.
What if I run the dog over the bread while I just sit here and do this?
I drop the bread right here.
Ready?
Is he gonna get mad about this?
I'm just a...
I'm a fucking dog.
It's right in front of you.
Just eat it.
Dogs don't eat bread.
Give me this.
I'm filling my whole bag.
Dogs absolutely eat bread.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna buy a bunch of those beef jerkeys and we're gonna eat like kings.
Throw away the cactus.
That sells for a lot.
This thing's stupid.
You think I'm kidding?
I'm filling my whole bag.
I'll be back.
Don't worry.
He's gonna be fine.
Mining music?
Uh, fine.
I'll put on some mining music.
I'm coming.
I'll get you your food.
Come on.
Just get a few more pieces of iron.
All right.
That's good.
Fuck off.
Let's go.
Go.
Hurry.
When I was doing this, somebody said you are so not funny.
That wasn't even my call.
That was...
People told me to do that.
That wasn't even my joke.
That wasn't even my call.
All right.
Get in there.
This should be enough for me to buy a bunch of food and then...
I don't know what the fuck I'm gonna do then.
Dog.
It's all right.
This dog has passed out and woken up like 30 times.
Maybe 50 times.
How far away am I?
Hurry up.
Get in.
All right.
Bar.
There it is.
Okay.
Quickly.
Come on.
Buy a shitload of those meat sticks.
Talk to.
Trade.
Show me what you got.
I got these rocks and I would like to buy from you dried meat.
And that's it.
That's all I can afford.
All right.
Dog.
Come on.
Where are you?
All right.
I need a reunion here.
Come on.
Eat, eat, eat, eat, eat.
I made it.
Okay.
Trade.
Here.
No.
Never mind.
Just gotta wait till you wake back up.
Eat that food.
Got it.
Okay.
Now, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna leave you with a piece of meat here.
So when you get hungry again, you eat that.
But I have to go back over there and I need to mine...
I need to mine again.
So you eat that when you're ready.
You just hang out there and eat that when you're ready.
Let me save.
This is just gonna be the rest of the stream.
But this is what you have to do.
It's about survival.
Where...
I just keep forgetting where the fuck I was going before.
All these rocks.
Where's the prospect?
Stone.
No, there is none.
Is there...
Is there none over there again?
There's so much more to the game.
There's more...
Oh, I know.
But you can't just go see it all.
You need to start from a piece of crap that can't even afford to bite dried meat leaves.
You can build your own cities.
Yeah, that's fucking awesome.
All right.
So while he's relaxing, I really do need to figure out where the hell I was gonna go.
Because I can't just run out into the wilderness again.
Let's go down here.
What is this?
Is there something over there?
Are you winning?
Not yet.
Strength is at...
Let's find out.
Strength is at 18.
Keep going.
Back down here.
Dog is still eating.
I don't know if mining is the best, most lucrative way to get money for your sick dog.
Well, it's the only thing I got right now.
Let's do it.
Now I can fill in my backpack.
Man and dog is secret hard mode.
You have to feed two mouths right away.
I didn't even think about it like that.
That's true.
I didn't even think about that.
Put on the mining music.
No, somebody didn't like that, so I'm not doing it.
One guy, yeah.
How much is in this vein?
I mean, condition...
The building is in good condition.
Iron quality, 100.
Can I have up to three workers here?
Efficiency, max efficiency.
I'm going to be iron rich.
Just build your shack next to the ore.
That's a pretty great idea.
Can I build my house right here?
Is the point of the game to be boring?
I don't think this is particularly boring.
I think the point of the game is you kind of have to very painfully start from zero.
You got to earn your place at the top.
By having your dog...
Did you eat the food that was here?
What happened to the food?
Did you already eat it?
What happened to the food that I put down here?
Did somebody take it?
Someone stole the food.
Well, I'll be back in a minute.
Why would you expect the game to have the dog auto eat the food?
I don't know.
I figured he would smell it and it would be in front of him.
I'm just going to get a few more.
Because I don't want to do this again.
I want to continue my journey going to where I wanted to go.
Hold on.
I can boot this.
I think that's full stack.
I can't even do a full stack.
It's like starving again.
I'm doing just fine.
Get a backpack before going.
Yeah, that's what I'll do.
I'm going to buy a few more pieces of jerky.
Give the...
The dog needs to eat again.
This really is just the...
The dog is becoming...
What is this?
Only two more and we're done.
The dog is draining you.
Look at the amount of work that I have to do to keep this dog around.
See how hard I work?
I don't want to lose him.
Abandon the dog.
I can't abandon the dog.
It's going to eat all my beef jerky but it's going to be...
Whatever.
I can't make the dog work.
The dog doesn't have any skills.
All right, let's go.
Get up there.
He actually did eat the food.
I'm at times three speed.
Let's go get it up there.
Make the dog have a job.
I'm not sure it's possible.
Hurry.
He's starting to pause the game while idling.
PogChamp.
Strike check.
Let's take a look.
19.
Look how terrible everything else is.
How do I get toughness?
I don't know.
26 and laboring.
I have to get beat up for toughness.
So people have to kick the shit out of me for me to...
Okay.
This should give me enough food.
This is going to be like one, two, three, four, five, six.
This should be about...
All right.
How much is a backpack?
Alt F4 from this awful MMO.
No, that's...
You got the wrong idea.
Look.
Just because I'm mining ore to feed my starving dog that's passing out every 30 seconds.
No.
There's not...
There's like...
Just wait till I build my own city.
Didn't you see the back of the box?
Where am I going?
I'm going the wrong way.
All right.
Buy more food.
Actually, I don't...
Yeah, I do.
Do I have any...
I've been eating it.
So food.
Get on in.
Let's do business.
All right.
I'm going to get 97 for these.
Give me.
So this is dried meat.
Is there anything else cheaper here?
Am I about to buy up the whole entire place?
737.
I need a backpack.
Full backpack.
I can't afford that one.
I'm going to buy up every bar of their fucking slim gems.
All right.
Come here, you.
Come with me.
Unconscious of 20 seconds and then eat that.
All right.
Ate the dried meat.
Good.
Now relax.
I keep...
I'm just treading water with this dog.
Okay.
Let's go to the other bar.
Do you have a backpack I can buy that's cheaper?
Sleeping bag.
You got like dried meat.
Should I just...
I don't know.
Okay.
Should I just buy a bunch more meat and then...
Or should I get a backpack?
There's a cheap backpack right here.
Sell pants and armor.
Buy traders backpack.
I did it.
All right.
Somebody said to do it and I did it.
I need the money.
I desperately need this money.
All right.
So I stole that shit anyways.
I can steal it again.
So I can get a sleeping bag, a scavenger's basket,
a cheap and useful backpack commonly associated with peasants and scavengers.
Get it.
You didn't need to sell the pants.
I'm going to buy some more meat.
Okay.
I'm going to save some money.
Don't sell the chest piece.
Well, I can't.
I did it.
I bought the shitty one.
Well, that's...
What's wrong with the shitty one?
It still works.
You put stuff in it.
All right.
It's actually a drum on my back.
I just turned into a different character.
Look at this.
We're just getting started with this game.
You see this?
Look.
Are you looking?
All right.
Let's go.
Dog.
I'm going to carry the dog.
You can stack in backpacks.
Let's go to the adventure shop.
I'm going to take a mechanic.
Let's go over here.
What's this?
Armorer.
Here.
You can stack in the trader's backpack.
Well, that's not the trader's backpack.
Are you looking at this?
Medium backpack.
Glorious holy map.
Small backpack.
Do you have any no trader backpacks?
That's fine.
I'm okay with my drum.
Cheap, useful backpack.
I'm just getting started.
I've just started the game.
All right.
What about standard first aid kits?
I have a basic first aid kit.
Do you sell basics?
Who ate that?
Did she just eat that out of my...
Who just ate that?
Somebody did.
I did.
Okay.
I'm going to say let's get some basic first aid kits.
What's happening right now?
Did the dog just eat?
Give the dog a backpack.
Small backpack.
I don't have enough money.
I need first aid.
I got to keep myself.
Okay.
Doggy backpack.
I can't afford it.
I have a 21% chance.
Why is there a bird inside of this building?
No, I can't do it.
I'm not selling the dog.
The bird.
What's in here?
Oh, come on.
Is there nothing in here?
Oh, fuck.
You give me...
What happened?
What?
Did that just burp?
I let out like a huge belt.
33%.
Come on, that's a third.
If I gave you a $100 bill and said,
there's a 33% chance that that's going to turn into $300.
But there's also a 66% chance that it's going to go to zero.
You're going to take that bet.
You are.
What is up here?
Look at all this stuff.
There's so many machines in here.
Gears.
What?
800 cents to skeletal repair the dog.
I need all the food I can get.
All right, let's go.
The dog's out of food.
Am I already actually out of food?
No, I got lots.
I got plenty.
Dog can be just fine.
I'm going to take a stroll.
I don't need to sneak anymore.
Very stealthy with a drum on your back.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Now, I got to pee.
It's been like four hours that I haven't peed once.
I'm going to piss.
I'll be right back.
We will continue the mission to survive.
That's the only thing we're trying to do.
I'll be right back.
See you in two seconds.
Ow!
Is he still a slave?
No, I changed because it was too hard.
It was like it was at the extreme of you start as nothing.
Maybe one day.
That'd be fun for me to do.
That's good.
Okay, I like this game.
Whoa, that's $100 from Flimflam.
Thank you, Flimflam, for the 100 bucks.
Aw, snap.
Is that a streamer that I hear?
It is.
Thank you so much for the $100.
That's five or six pizzas?
Well, no, that's five or six like double, triple deals
from Pizza Hut or Domino's or something.
It's like 20 bucks for two or three large pizzas.
That's pretty great.
But thank you so much.
That's a lot of money.
What was I doing?
But it is a streamer.
Or I don't know.
Just kind of a guy right here.
You found a blueprint.
Blueprints allow you to learn tech instantly.
To learn a blueprint, open your inventory
and right click it to learn it.
If you're wearing a backpack, make sure to close it first
so that the blueprint doesn't switch between your inventory
and your backpack, okay?
What?
Chew sticks.
I can learn how to chew on sticks.
Cool it with the slurping.
I know people like hate that shit up.
So I think just do it because it sounds fun to me.
What's the dog doing?
Almost okay.
Stop slurping.
It's rude.
Well, you know, there are some cultures
where slurping is actually a sign of happiness
and being well taken care of,
especially if you have like a restaurant.
It's actually seen as a sign of respect.
That's soup.
What?
No, I just know that information.
Well, I'm not saying that I'm going to do it.
Look, can I just carry?
I know that's true because I do what?
I'm not just making it up.
Noodles equals soup.
Where am I going to take my fucking dog?
Why am I still carrying the dog?
Because I want the dog to be able to rest
because the dog is currently starving and unconscious.
So I'm trying to do my best.
I'm not supposed to be idling like that.
All right.
Open up the map.
Continue with what I was going to do.
Remember this town exists because I'm going to keep...
I want to go to the river.
All right.
On the way to the river, I got some food.
The dog has just been suffering this whole time.
It's okay.
I got a box full of food.
I have a big college laundry bag full of snacks to eat.
So he can just rest on my shoulder and eat out of the bag.
Let's move.
I think I just break his neck.
Let's just...
Okay, hold on.
I thought I just went too fast and snapped his neck.
Holy shit.
All right.
I am no longer hungry.
Let's go back to running.
Okay.
Dog is still on cooldown.
Can I do anything else?
Anybody else that wants to trade?
Do I have any other people who want to join my cause here of surviving?
I don't think so, but I'm ready to go out into the wilderness.
He'll heal eventually.
I'm going to keep him up here hanging out.
Let's go to the river.
We got to save.
Auto-save is right here.
The backpack is bigger than me.
Yes, it kind of is.
Now, I'm starting to learn the ropes a little.
I'm this...
I'm...
This is going to...
I'm enjoying this.
I feel like this is the kind of game that you could just dunk 500 hours in.
Yeah, you put a lot of time into this game.
Can you train the dog?
I have no idea.
But the dog is just barely now able to not be unconscious.
Is the game worth it?
That depends on what you want out of it, you know?
Because take a look, right?
If you just want to walk around and...
There are no rules to the game.
It says it on the back of the box.
If you just want to play a game where your character sucks
and you can walk around anywhere on the map and there are no rules,
then sure.
Some people probably say,
I don't want to do that.
That sounds kind of boring.
And I don't want to just be like a useless idiot the whole game.
Well, I mean, then this game is not for you.
Would a fan of Fallout like this game?
The original?
Like Fallout 1 and 2?
Probably.
I would say that would make some sense.
Playing an NPC in a big world.
Yeah, that kind of is what this is.
How's the dog?
Doing all right.
It's like Dwarf Fortress or Rimworld.
Yeah.
Because you can build cities.
You don't have to do anything.
You can walk around with an unconscious dog
and look for weird shit to stare at.
Or you can build a city.
It's kind of just up to you.
You could go searching for demons in the northwest.
Well, you're now turned into a rug of a dog somehow.
Which is terrible.
Because look at them.
Breed the dog.
Let's take a second here.
All right, who just ate?
105.
How much more food do I have?
Not enough.
But it's probably enough to get to the next area.
You could be a slave for two hours, yeah?
That's exactly what happened to the very forgetting.
That character didn't even have an arm.
So it was even harder.
All right, let me prospect here.
What do we got?
Stone.
Hmm.
You guys see any stone?
Water.
Stone.
Hmm.
I mean, there's stones all around me,
but I don't know if it's worth stopping for.
Well, all right, we're going all the way up this discovered holy farm.
Can you fall off?
I should probably be really careful here.
Where am I now?
I'm up on the mountain.
Put on a chill OST.
All right, fine.
That sounds like a good idea.
How about, uh, what's a good, like, chill?
Not doom.
Earthbound?
Earthbound OST doesn't sound bad.
What?
That was not me.
I didn't do that.
That was the soundtrack.
That was the earthbound soundtrack.
All right, this looks good.
What do you mean sure?
Look, listen.
See?
Different things that I'm doing that.
I think I just crashed my browser by doing that too.
Oh, what the fuck am I doing?
Hey, there we go.
Let's go.
How you doing, dog?
Is this earthbound or is this toe jamming, Earl?
Nowhere.
Holy shit.
Where am I?
Where do I go?
I don't have much food.
I only have like three.
Oh, no, two.
And the dog's not even ready.
Oh, what's this?
Materials?
What can I do with this?
I don't think I can do anything with this.
I don't think I have the necessary tool for this.
No, nothing here.
Dog's not ready to walk on his own.
Oh, got to camp.
That will take me to Wizard, Wizard.
It was the river.
Let's head that way.
Kill the dog.
I can't just kill the dog.
You understand the last three hours or no,
probably like two hours of this game,
has been making sure this dog stays alive.
Let the dog go on a spy mission to camp.
The dog can't even walk.
So, that's not going to happen.
That's a long way down.
I'm going to get jumped over here or something, aren't I?
What?
What the hell was that?
That was weird.
Okay.
Some more materials.
He can walk now, but I don't want him to.
I want him to get to at least halfway.
I don't want him to use energy.
Let me use the energy for him.
Okay, a few more things to look at up here.
Prospect.
Never mind.
Ooh, what's that?
Something over here.
I wish I could just throw him in the basket.
No, I kind of do too.
How am I going to get down here?
I went up so far all the way to the top.
Why did I go on the mountain?
I'm not even ready for this.
I have to drop the dog to interact with things.
Oh god.
You're going to be okay?
Are you all right?
How come you're not walking with me?
With me.
Come on.
Let's go.
No, this is material.
Is it copper?
Copper.
The dog passed out again.
No.
Why are you not staying with me?
Get me a copper.
We consider any...
Oh yeah, that's right.
It doesn't have the job anymore, right?
I need to do a sign.
Follow.
Jobs.
Answer the door.
What door?
Okay.
Okay, good.
I actually remember this part of the game.
It scared the shit out of me when I first played it.
This copper is shitty quality.
The other one was too.
I don't have enough food to mine here.
Oh, fuck.
The dog ate the last piece of bread.
Or whatever the hell it was.
I gotta get out of here, you're right.
I gotta go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I guess I'll get one.
Go.
There's gotta be the kind of town here.
There has to be.
Come on.
Go, go, go, go.
All right.
We're out.
Take a town or something.
I'm in the middle of fucking nowhere.
I'm in the middle of nowhere.
The dog is so slow.
All right.
Pick up the dog again.
I'm sorry.
I gotta pick you up.
I gotta run.
Look at how much faster I am than you.
Let's go.
I'm not stopping for anything.
I just gotta make it down the other side of the mountain.
Is this early access?
Nope.
Game is out.
It has released.
This is a released video game.
Can I even get down from here?
Yep, I can.
Right here.
Down, around, and then come on.
Is this a house over here?
Something.
A house.
A hut.
A village.
A small group.
When did it get released?
10 years ago.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Dog's hungry again.
Although so am I.
Let's go.
Pick up pace.
We didn't even scratch the surface of this area, too.
It's been in development for 10 years.
Wow.
That's a passion project, for sure.
There was a camp over here.
Give me some points of interest.
Oh, fuck.
Who are you?
Holy servants.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe they'll help me.
Do you guys have anything?
You need rations?
I got a sick dog.
Anybody here I can talk to?
No, I'm going the wrong way.
I gotta go this way.
Past the river.
But okay.
I got...
I'm not starving.
I'm normal.
Supplies and stuff I can't stop for.
I was gonna make it to the other side of the river and I'll be fine.
No discoveries.
The hat...
Look at the...
What could be right here?
There has to be some...
Wend, okay?
The city of Wend.
Where's the dog?
Did I lose the dog?
Bounty.
What?
Knife.
Skeletons.
Heart.
Uh...
I'm just gonna keep going this way.
I know the music is clashing.
I'm in good spirits and I do have a weapon.
So I'm not...
I'm not afraid.
Something up here.
We're just gonna go right into the crater.
You wanna play Mongolian throat singing?
No, we got earthbound on right now.
I love this OST.
O-S-T.
This is soundtrack.
Is there a town?
Camp?
Discovered holy farm.
What?
No, I didn't.
I'm in the crater.
Fuck.
All right.
Holy farm.
If I have to steal, I'm gonna steal.
You know?
Look, there's a couple of houses here.
I'm gonna be friendly, introduce myself.
The dog?
Dog's all right.
Just hungry.
Okay, I'm about to pass the sludge river.
Be friendly, introduce myself, and then steal everything.
Well, what do you want me to do?
We're kind of desperate right now.
Are those...
What are those?
Dogs?
Oh, got food for days here, guys.
Okay.
Let me take a look.
This is easy.
This is like a pig.
Oh no, that's just another dog.
Can I trade my dog for this dog?
This dog's healthy.
Okay.
Anybody here?
What's this?
Outhouse.
Am I actually using it?
Is this helping anything?
Is that...
Oh, a bed.
All right, I'm gonna put him in the bed.
You just relax.
Stay there.
Stay.
Look good.
Lie down.
Relax.
I'm gonna try to find us some food.
All right, I'm gonna knock on the door.
Stormhouse door.
Open.
I mean, do I have to knock?
Is anybody even in here?
There's nobody in here.
Steal...
Oh man, look at the price.
Look at the price on these.
Look, it's the apocalypse.
Oh, hey, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Out of bounds, out of bounds, out of bounds, out of bounds, out of bounds, out of bounds, out of bounds.
Bye, bye.
See you later.
Out of bounds.
I just need...
My dog needed help.
All right.
Where's my dog?
Did you have any food in there?
If I get to a town, I can sell that shit and then make a lot of money.
I'm gonna keep...
Dog is gonna stay there.
There's another house over here.
I'm hoping to get some food.
Okay, let's start walking.
Sneak.
Get this fucking door open.
Texas, smash the door.
Kill if you must.
Only if I have to.
All right, it's daytime.
Someone's gonna come out of this door.
Someone's gonna open the door.
Wait, can I stand over here?
He watches my here?
No, somebody just said that.
Does anybody live here?
You can get this door.
There's probably a fridge in here.
There's probably snacks.
There's probably food.
There's probably water.
I just have to get the...
Okay, let's knock it out and not just walk out.
No, I didn't open it.
Somebody else did.
All right.
If I reset the intelligence, it'll think that I did...
You know what I mean?
So now...
Oh, I just came up here and the door was open.
Person to sleep.
I'm gonna steal everything from their body.
First aid.
Splint kit.
But was it even worth coming in here?
They don't even have any food in here.
They got meat.
They have raw meat.
They got fish.
Yeah, it was...
Fucking fit somebody.
What the fuck?
Am I honest?
Is this a move I'm doing?
How did you pick me up?
I thought I was doing that.
No.
What the fuck?
No, I...
I'm breaking in now.
You can call me a safe scum or all you want.
It's nighttime.
I'm getting in there and I'm taking the dried fish and the raw meat.
I'm breaking this door open.
They're sleeping.
It's not gonna be daytime.
I'll get it.
Get it open.
First try.
No, I didn't.
Did I not get it?
I just need to get in there, grab the dried fish, and get out.
Okay, got it.
Save the game.
Okay, get in.
It's not even in the same place.
Okay, get out, get out, get out.
No, I ate it.
I didn't want to eat it.
What?
Come on, dog.
We're gonna go.
Where am I?
Go over here.
Get up.
Pick up.
Let's go, let's go.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I gotta do it.
I need to.
Hold on.
We're gonna get meat right here.
Okay, here we go.
I'm getting fucking meat.
Come on.
We need this meat.
No, come on, dog.
I know you could do...
That character is so useless.
Where's the dog?
is my dog just a bloody pile on the ground it's all right i'll find another come here dog
ah what's in here what am i taking from them what is this a well i'm feeling i'm getting water
water jug okay got it raw meat i can cook this i don't know what the hell you're in but let's
go this door this is open now i need to fucking take i need food fabrics hacksaw gears fuel all
right jesus let's go i got raw meat that's enough i'm gone i'm already gone i did steal a shitload
of their bars though all right now let's go as holy farm let's keep going down this way let me
go way through here i need to set up a camp or something speaking of that camping campfire
materials doesn't cost anything no it produces dry meat it produces dried meat
says who what no it doesn't it produces dried meat from where from the roots in the ground
oh no i had the meat okay dog needs to eat this put you down dog you need to eat that
meat i don't did he eat it he did okay come back over here i'll get you is there anything
else i can do inventory um no i got raw iron leather copper i got these these are so expensive
you can auto arrange that's awesome okay let's go you ate we're just gonna make it to where
i wanted to go which is down here let's go to this little section in this way
he's gonna put the dog on the fire i'm not gonna put the dog on the fire
he's gonna be just fine we're gonna be best friends and we're gonna have plenty of
stories to tell it's a big rock formation isn't it apparently my disguise is blown
that wasn't where i was wearing a disguise skinner's roam i discovered narcos trap
okay i see a town i see a town let's go for it oh talk about selling shit this is
uh iron it's got a iron quality 100 i can carry the dog and just get a few i thought you guys said
i couldn't interact with things with the dog in my hand what the fuck was that did you see that
there's like an explosion over here am i sitting on the top of an active volcano that was like a
ironic voice that wasn't me doing one stolen from holy sentinel you had a lot of these bars
how's the dog doing okay we're all right we're gonna have money though we're gonna have money
i'm gonna be able to do what i need to do and i can get like the germa mustard emote off of
massamune forever and people are going to come into the stream and they're going to think that
i named the dog massamune i but i like didn't though you know what i mean like that that's
an oh yeah my dog's name is massamune no no it's because of supposed to separate off i
didn't like do this you did though but i'd like i did but i didn't do that the way that
you're thinking the way that you're describing that just look at look at these stats 21 in
athletics my max run speed is crazy 30 in laboring crossbow smith armorsmith science robotics field
medic stealth staying in dark and my special gear melee attack is one well so this is why
because i keep like you i was told a long time ago i need to i need to get hurt yeah i gotta
get knocked back down you know i mean i have to get knocked down before i can do anything
i have no sword skill because i keep resetting when i take damage
six hours in and no squad well i do have a squad look i'm just trying to survive
but hold on but wait wait wait but hold on a second two to three hours of that was doing
the hardest difficulty for a joke for like two hours this is like a pretty fresh run
from like two and a half hours ago you know what i mean please don't give up on this game
i low-key love it i mean i'm i'm having fun this is a i'm having fun if i wasn't having fun
you'd know very quickly only a couple more what does he mean by that well he means
that i probably would not be having fun and i probably stopped the stream or i'd be like
oh you know what maybe i'll check that out uh maybe i'll check it out like enough time
not another kill all humans stream what all right that's good look at all the stuff that
i have i'm ready next time we get to iron valleys this is like a city right here
there's a hut there's people here it's probably hopefully some kind of person i can sell to
the rain it's acid find cover damn i i'm getting my skin burnt this rain is acid
oh wait what all right i'm gonna get inside of the gazebo come on let's go hurry hurry hurry hurry
hurry the rain is burning my skin i'm losing stats come on hurry up how do i even get in here
stop them tainted woman wait what's going on new party member defensive gate the holy nation
all right hold on wait wait wait what happened free stuff holy shit free shit
is this stealing no he didn't have anything what's going on all right come on somebody has
to have something i don't i don't see a shop i need a shop these are all thank god for the
holy nation is this a store you're not allowed here leave it's no can i talk to somebody
nobody has a dialogue tree fuck the holy nation come on i'm a person in need how dare you
come on my like skin is still burning i need shelter there has to be somebody i can talk to
in here whether in the town behind somewhere up top nobody nothing a mounted turret can i speak
to you stool use the stool out of bounds leave ah fine cast me out i'll go walk in the acid
rain thanks guys thanks for nothing yeah i'll take take me and my dying dog and i'll go
walk back out in the acid rain unbelievable really you gotta be kidding me are you serious
are you serious no why i was already gone no don't kill the dog run master moon
where are they even taking me up in the wait a minute who's this where's the dog oh 1835
right there okay remember i can't no one's gonna help me in here i have to just leave and on my way
out they're all gonna come after me there's a hut over here might be some supplies anything
just shitty houses all right well i gotta get out of the acid rain and i don't know if i can
let's go over here i have lots of fucking stuff i have supplies i have money put on
animal crossing yeah it's been a nice we've had enough time on the uh bloody acid rain
we've had enough time on earthbomb animal crossing ost relaxing animal crossing music compilation
this is pretty relaxing okay let's go i'm gonna say down this way oh that's cool
that's yeah you can go here that's kind of cool there's like uh 400 000 planets in the
game this is just one of them they all have their own unique completely designed from
the ground up uh landscapes no i'm kidding that's a lie what there's a what's that wait wait
wait wait wait wait hold on there's a giant bug there's like a bug monster that way i gotta cut
across that way should i fight the bug do you think we can take the bug what's what levels the
bug old machine iron spider athletic 40 no no no no age attack 36 strength 36 dexterity 39 no way
look at me look at how much of a piece of shit i am minus four minus four 21 i'll die in
two hits looks like the agro range i don't know hopefully not that far no hopefully very far
hopefully no hopefully no hopefully not that far what not not that far what accent am i falling
into here what's wrong with the dog the dog is dog god i don't have enough food that's what
happened to the dog oh yeah where's the squad jeremy where's your squad members you're gonna
have 20 people in a party in this game it's so expansive and so cool oh what's that oh
so just what's that you've been carrying your only squad member on your shoulder for about
hour and 40 minutes nice work oh what what am i doing over here i gotta get out of here
that's the only way i can go is done with no i discovered the oaken shield acid rain the
dog's unconscious but it don't matter all right it's gonna sound bad and you guys are gonna be
not happy about this but i think i'm gonna like give the dog away because what kind of life is
this you know what i mean somebody else will feed and take care of this dog i'm like an
adventurer the dog can't handle this right now you know i'm sure there's some family
that would love to have this dog so this is somebody has an important message uh oh no no no
hold on this way this way this way this way this way this way don't see me
why am i going through the area where the super mutants are jeez okay uh so so demonic cucumber
said uh jeremy an episode of family guy uh that family guy show came on yesterday
and i was pretty surprised to see that they stole some of your jokes really how the guy
living next door came over and said hey beater one of your classic jokes just to make it
worse they also stole the poop and shit in your pants jokes you always make it's terrible to see
such a big company stealing from small creators uh no this is the guy and his neighbor comes over
bandits bounty hold on that guy has a bounty no i do wait the holy nation wanted for theft
those characters wanted by the authorities turned them in for a reward these characters
not wanted by the local faction i have a 2500 bounty on me right now and why is that exactly
turn yourself in and collect the bounty you stole a bunch of shit and ran yeah but they
didn't know who i was i never said it's me canned roth i'm here to steal all your bread
i'm a nobody it's that iron that's terrible iron all right we got settlement over here
you're the only dwarf on the planet that's not even true how's the dog doing bad what happened
blessings this is the holy nation i'm wanting i'm wanted by the holy nation i can't even go
over here this is like a new outpost i can't do this is this like a kill on site with me
why is the holy nation take over the whole game what's this guy got athletic 40s attack
why everyone's so much better than me i really am just a loser carrying around my father's
sword you know i'm not i'm not my father i have negative four attack don't mind me uh
just the guy with the 2500 dollar bounty trying to walk through to a different city
but look at how much stuff is in here are we sure they're even going to give a shit though
no one said anything so far i just closed the gate i just locked him all up
sorry i'm sorry i didn't mean to do that i the game's camera went up really high all right give
me a shop what have we got is that a store first aid let's go i got steel bars i got money
does nobody recognize me and we'll be all good i'm getting a lot of looks though okay
hold on talk to do you have any medical supplies for sale can you change my appearance
um basic first aid kits i need food fencing chance 20 it's all right i'll sell these
i got these fair and square wait wait wait wait hold on why do i have a 22 percent did
i take this from somebody yeah what did i steal it from the ore okay well i got i have plenty of
first aid which i can do um i need to talk to some people i need to get i'm gonna make some
fucking friends what are they doing i need friends and i need food i have money i need
friends i have money that's kind of a desperate thing to announce somebody fighting what's the
fight going on in here you saw that right what was that for oh no did supplies those are free
come on man you do it again
this is so pathetic i need to fight like a shitty character oh boy what do you got here
iron plates electrical okay there's a raspberry pea what i'm running out of space i need to
i can just sell these right now well the dog the dog i might seriously just
auto-arrange it not bad not bad say it no i can't say it because it's too it's terrible
this is bad i'm gonna have to eat the dog i'm kidding i'm not gonna i'm not gonna eat
the dog i need to rest save my dog companion let's keep going this way nobody has any food
i need a bar i need friends i need anything what's that big cube let's go can i get a mount
where did it come from oh my goodness just go go go go go run quick turn it oh
i needed to have that happen i had to get beat up i'm not gonna i'm not going to reset it
because look toughness two see i have to get my ass kicked i have to lose so that i
can know what it's like to lose all right i'll wake up in a second to gone i'm not dead yet
almost recovery coma god damn it no i tried i tried to save you what was i supposed to do
i tried to feed you i tried to take care of you getting jumped by bandits and
fucking bugs and snakes this is gonna get to minus 100 he's dead the dog's dead
the dog's dead no i tried i tried to no i'm gonna go back that's not okay
where is this i can't i don't want to eat the dog uh why am i dying
wait i'm about to die i shouldn't be dying right now i can't do anything i'm dead no i'm
already dead it's over nothing this is not gonna heal back up somebody has to come save me
check the check the other buildings instead of being a sand runner
all right i got this is 10 minutes ago all right this is right when i was outside
let's go let's run the camera here what's going on all right so we've got one two three four
i'm gonna go we'll start over here no plates anymore it's okay i need a fucking friend
i'm desperate for a friend somebody that can carry me i need to talk to somebody in here and pay
them 4200 gold medical supplies yeah sell all this shit yes yes these are stolen that's fine
now give me i got i'll take them i'll take one more basic first aid kit and then splint
kit maybe i might need one how expensive are these they're expensive but i need one i have
to have one okay all right now i'm gonna go to the other side don't be a sand runner i'm just
running across tatooine with fucking mini Chewbacca in my hands so there's this one
is also are they any other building this one's run down that was destroyed
we have uh yeah a few places here i don't think this is a bar
off limits i can't even leave i can't even go in here and now i'm gonna get chased out and now
people are gonna know it's my bounty is up see and now everybody's fucking running after me
this is a mistake i can't go in the other buildings see he doesn't get it that i'd left
already i gotta be a sand runner i have to there's one other spot over here
once i find a friend you'll know check the buildings i i know i know i know
but if i go in a building people freak out this guy's gonna freak out why did he not freak out
these fax machines small generator nothing battery bank battery bank loop nothing nothing
in these why is that what was the point of that nice foreshadowing what do you mean
this is like a barracks it's definitely off limits can i go in here
i don't know i have to do bad stuff no i gotta be a sand runner i have to
i could go back to that big town i mean the world's end was a huge town a lot of stuff there but
that's a long run that's a long way you can tell what buildings you can go into by clicking
on them open to public private okay be smited free stuff like a swimming holy fuck look at
the weapon what is this 1772 1770 love loss fragment axe okay you have any money you have
any food didn't have any food somebody dead up there has to have food look at all these
dead bodies this guy is single-handedly killing everybody in here does this think a boss
oh kill them all kill them all kill all of them and then give i'm gonna have a fucking
field day you know how much stuff i'm gonna get from this he's gonna kill everybody here
how to do a bounty this person has a bounty on their head you can check somebody has a bounty
on the status panel really to collect monies you need to take them to a police station first
knock the person up and pick them up and carry them to the police station pick up a bounty
hold right click mouse to bring up the interaction menu once you've found the
police station talk to the station's police chief this guy's got a bounty on his head
status where's it where does it say that all right i'm gonna go fucking hit him if i get
the last hit that means i win right yeah did he break my arm he just fucking broke
i can't attack him you can do it
oh my wait wait wait wait go after him hold on wait i can no i need to get the stuff on him
that was my bounty god damn it missed your chance to loot what the fuck
no this guy's probably got a bounty too hold on i need to fucking heal myself for the love of god
i need to use the splint first aid heal your arm splint your arm how do i use the splint i
just bought it i can't even splint this arm there's no splinting this arm what's
you have the same problem we both go to the same doctor
i'm missing the loot i can't pick this shit up no don't touch it
how do i fix this though for real i'm not gonna be able to carry the dog
i can't carry the dog with a fucked up arm it's in the process of being healed okay damn it
all right it's time let's i i i can't even pick you up man how long is it gonna take
put the medic button on the bottom right medic just save scum it let's go i have money
all i'm doing is deleting my progress my saves come i know it's stupid and i need to stop doing
it i need to like go find a little shitty guy to kill let's just there's probably something
over here i'm i gotta go run to the sand here comes like a scorpion but i don't know how long
my arm is gonna take i couldn't carry the dog i would have to go sleep go back go back
go back what do you mean wait wait get away from me wait i'll hit him i can hit him i can
level up oh fuck there's a skeleton got it come on i need to get no you're too hungry for this
i'm not gonna rewind it i needed to get hurt dog could probably use some training here
all right get up get recovery coma great i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead this guy's dead
he's not getting up it's minus 43 i'm not gonna recover really
dog does more damage than i do it's dog oh god what the hell is that
why is this guy doing push-ups oh no get out of here dog run what did he just pick up he's
eating he's eating someone he's eating this guy's leg whose body part is that
where are you going stay back here stay back here back here come on you can eat that here
just wait till i get up for my recovery coma okay rescue where are you i don't know
where he's going he doesn't want to listen to me okay i didn't i want to see how this
plays out where the hell is he going
they're both gonna die oh this is fucking hilarious well okay um i can't start a new
game i already have so much non-progress on this one i'm addicted to this game though i
have to keep going so i need a spot i know everyone told me to go down here
but i don't i i'll find it eventually i need to go to a bar this story is over
but i have to okay sunk cost fallacy no i can make it i can make it i'm just gonna go
i'm not gonna run through the desert again i want to look not that way i need to go
i'm going back what just i'm sorry i gotta go this way we gotta trek back where we came from
new game no i can't i can't do a new game not yet i'm too invested not yet
i need to go back here and then i'm gonna go down here you understand but i i'm not gonna
run through the desert i'll be able to make it through here back to the farm and then i'm
going down here this is i'm gonna this little green pasture here now we're gonna see the
conclusion of this i don't know if those are good guys or bad guys okay they're good
now just have faith just have faith i'll get us through this let's go dog is okay starving
but it's all right i'm gonna i got plenty of supplies we're gonna get up there we're gonna
go down to the green pasture there'll be a stable or something down there i'll make it
i'm gonna take a left up here past here through the holy farm song name uh relaxing
animal crossing music compilation see right up there didn't take very long see we're fine
why is it so much fun to be just terrible because i know eventually if i have some faith
that i will grow my character up so let's go down here down the river we'll discover some
new land there'll be a little town and i will be able to just discover holy minds take
a look at that all right blister hill you got it town new town oh okay thank you slow it down
for a second it's having trouble here we got a real town i got money i'm gonna get food
i got look at this i got an ore right here look at that it's right there i can smack into
the oh it's right outside the gate dog can rest hello there holy sentinel i come in need
somebody just did 351 what selling something bar oh finally all right hello do you have a
coffee with the holy flame do i show me what you got all right time to make some money
value 363 that's a terrible price and i can't even do it how much money do i have i just
need food what about you are you a patron that can help me all right let's go in the bar
i'm willing to pay at this point for a carry i'm willing i'm willing to pay for like a league
of legends coach anybody in here anybody in here want to teach me mid please who are you
everybody help smothering things over with traders guild you know where to find me okay
okay hold on we got a patron human mercenary i'm looking to hire some bodyguards i need some
mercenaries to guard my outpost i'm looking to hire some bodyguards 2000 cats per day one day
minimum charge and no refunds i can't afford that how am i supposed to afford that well
let's just don't accidentally grab i need food show me your wares all right please
how much of these things are too much money we got green fruit it's a vegetable does this
food or is this bullshit food cube oh dried fish here we go that's so much money
all right give me a dog you need this oh he ate it okay okay you stay here your job just stay
there i need to find some more stuff i need to find somebody i can sell to any of the bars in
this town it's not a bar it's not a bar he didn't eat it yeah he did look see the circle behind you
oh didn't just come out of uh it's right across from it all right come on where are you going
all right who in here is worthy griffin i had a dream last night the lord of light
oprah himself came to me told me that i would meet a wealthy wanderer from the outside
the wealthy wanderer will lead me to the truth will lead me to the origin of the first extinction
with this the land of the holy nation will finally find peace and you think that i'm your wanderer
yep oakland will show me if you are the one so wanderer i will follow you but it will cost
you 9 000 cats do you have the coin how about a discount the wealthy do not need discounts
that's way out of my budget what about the guy across the table
the lights in this bloody bar are starting to make my head spin work here is dried up big
time how about you you hiring yep 3 000 cats and i'm yours damn i don't have enough
sell your useless weapon show me what you got it's i'm only gonna get 186 dollars i need to
buy food okay i got some food i need to find a fence yeah but it's not in here
3 000 is doable i mean maybe if i take i steal it sell the steel i can't there's only
there's a 20 chance for me to succeed this guy's 3000 i could get it just save scum
until it works oh my god that guy had 100 oh he didn't 22 you got caught selling stolen
items hey that's mine oh is it now it's just kicking and punching
this dude paladin steve nice 3d movie maker kick i think i would i want to fight this guy one
on one i feel like i could level up on this dude i have negative three attack yeah i know
it's bad i need to like punch rats in the starter zone but there is no starter zone
it doesn't exist heal the dog that i there's only so much i can do he just has to eat
i just have to keep feeding the dog i mean the dog is doing just fine besides this
find a training dummy wait wait wait wait wait who's that
now it's another mercenary then i don't know find a training dummy in a police station
uh well let me see if i can talk to anybody am i allowed in here i didn't even check
got some people though one guy green fruit cup flower rough stone get out
told you it wasn't gonna work i'm the weird guy in town nobody likes
and you tell me there was the fence all right new music what's the new uh soundtrack i'm gonna
put up stardew valley age of empires age of empires ost this is a short one
fence your mercenaries the dog has eaten at this point check upstairs i will try oh no nobody
up here but there's nobody can see me come on get it open the lock how many times come on
okay i got oh fucking holy shit holy shit holy shit open it holy shit holy shit i'm panicking
take it take it all who caught me who caught me taking that what i i didn't sneak so me
me crouching and opening up a thing and picking a piece of fish out is different than me standing
up me me crouching let's try that again how much 3000 can't afford that me crouch they still
have shackles on is that the problem all right i'll get it this time so you're telling me
sneak like this and then open it i can get a horse okay nobody heard this what was that
just i was just curious if um what happened there someone's on the balcony who the fuck is
on the balcony there's nobody on the balcony 56 chance to steal i need the stuff in here are
you okay never been better i'm gonna open it and then let me take a look and see how hard
things are saying i'm so desperate for food i have to try to get these okay save game
this ain't gonna work that's fine okay so now stealing chance all 56 so what's the most what's
the best thing to take here probably the meat wrap i didn't get it that's three times in a
row i just flipped a coin three times and got heads three times f5 is quick save and f9 yeah
stupid whatever has the highest nutrition that's a good idea nutrition 50 50 25 20 30 it's 50 it's
a meat wrap really like that's four heads in a row i have to feed this to the dog f5 f9 uh just
get rid of the dog would you say that would you say that if it was your dog would you
say that if it was your dog got it that's okay it's all right what's this throwing my body into
the ground oh yes all right now i got i could get the fish too i mean why not just get it all
you know why not just get it all this is the way to truly play the game well hold on now
let me see what's if anything's worth taking in here i need let me wait till the game to
load um i'm gonna break the engine holy shit when did you come up here i got my hand on the
handle my hand is in the cookie jar right now and my face is covered with chocolate and crumbs
don't move i'm not gonna move that's freaking me out that was horror movie like head tilting
okay i'm good
this is the perfect crime the perfect perfect plan oh there goes 100 gold i need to
i just blew 17 percent of my money no it's i'm gonna pull it back and then i'm gonna just
hide look he's not gonna be on the same ai path okay nobody coming let's try the other one
90 chance that's what i like to see all right what's in here 10 000 wanted the red bandit
but is this there wasn't even a percentage on there there was no percentage chance to
take that where was it it was just a poster all right i gotta get out of here i'm out
let me try this one more time one more piece i'm trying to get one fish got it two fishes all
right i'm good uh we got good food down this food's gonna very nutritious gonna fill us all
up plenty of food i can leave i got how much what do i got uh all right let's get this
shit in the other bag very filling food lots of it and i got i gotta find a fence i can
sell these bars and you know the rest dog i'm coming i'm coming with really good food what's
this thing splint kit get it small emperor statue all right give me the splint kit these things
dried fish too look at this i got another fish perfect dried fish uh small emperor statue
okay any of that there's no i got more fish right look at that another fish i already got it
beautiful what's this worth all right let's get out i got food i'm ready to move frog is expensive
is it oh i thought that was just bullshit wow okay that's a lot of money that's a lot of money
all righty um well that's about all i can do here any other people that i haven't spoken to
that could potentially help me i don't think so wait two thousand for one day
no that's not even worth it what a waste of money let's go southwest dog i got something
for you uh when you wake up from your unconsciousness come on i'll pick you up
can i pick up pick it pick the dog up check the other bar for the for a fence i mean will
there be a fence in here how can i tell when somebody's offense gecko uh this woman hating
god damn city is driving me mad you hiring outlander promise i'll be good if you take me
with you what's your price what's your fee got any skills what's your price three thousand
cats i don't have enough change your mind i shouldn't bother you damn it are you still
three thousand you can sell to the other faction yeah i know but i have to find the
other faction you know i've pretty much only seen the holy covenant whatever they are
go upstairs see if we can find somebody upstairs there's nothing up here there are some beds
i'm ready to leave i have a useless weapon what about down here there's a bunch of
little stalls sell grog get cats hire muscle i gotta find somebody to sell to how long has
he been carrying around his dead dog uh the pretty much the entire game that dog is gonna
be useful though eventually let me check over here where all right bar oh we got plenty
of mercenaries in here for free thief fence got things to sell oh i do you bet your ass i do
stolen goods no problem that's that's a huge cut though 200 315 it's a fence what do you expect
2200 i still don't even have enough sell the sake i 2400 i don't have enough to do anything
25 i have to go steal i'm gonna steal more shit and come back to this guy all right hold on
remember where he is i'm just gonna go on a spree feed the dog dog is fed as long as the
dog hang out hangs out on top of me he will be fed every time he's gonna eat out of the inventory
all right what about up here well time to go take more stuff am i allowed in this building
yes it's public all right so uh hey can't wait to take all the shit in here upstairs
hopefully is worth something we'll find out weaponsmith okay maybe i should have sold the
sword to the weaponsmith there is a big box right here uh upstairs let's see that's a big
hunting party one guy two actually but there are a barrel right here safe scum it sell value uh
mercenary i guess oh shit if a store listen item at the front desk it's somewhere in the
store to steal that's cool where am i all right uh is this but i can't really do it without being
seen i can't in line of sight them now put the dog back up why is the dog going in and
out of consciousness because he has not been well fed for a long time there are a couple
barrels of chest back here 41 chance 413 you know what we're gonna do why is there a fat
weirdo sneaking around with a large rat it's my dog it's just this club that's all that's
over here 46 chance i'm assuming it's because he went away got it oh yeah yeah yes what holy
shit don't scare me like that that was terrifying i'm gonna need one of these
oh okay 47 chance you know what to do has nobody told them why has nobody told them how
to actually play the game oh they have many times it's all out nobody's in the store
is this an opportunity to go take things in the store the alarm just raised you shouldn't
be here oh what am i gonna do about this though what am i gonna do about this i've been safe
scumming all the way up here i have to stay up until morning i stayed up here till the
fucking store closed crap i can sleep in a bed can i all right if i sleep in bed will they
know it's me this isn't mine oh no i have to hide behind this until morning this is bad
this is very bad i have to get over here and have to hide behind this and then go
it's super speed i'm not soft locked not yet get out of sneak mode and run what are you
doing oh man this is very bad very very very bad i'm i'm i soft locked myself up here
i'm gonna get out watch this run ready i have in my hands the game crashed oh shit
no i need to uh shit that's not good i'm coming back coming back coming back coming back coming
back be there in a second learn the first floor through scum take the best stuff and run
new game no this is what we're doing tonight i'm having a good time i'm gonna i'm not done
it's only eight o'clock i got plenty of time which one is it this one right here you met the stream
was gonna end oh no no no i have to at least get somewhere i stole shit got some people made a
base got fucked over by raiders and realized i couldn't hold my own and then i restarted
all right time to run why did you just put his hands up like jerry seinfeld out out what
are you doing stop getting scared go there's a door they locked me in i can't leave i have
to accept my fate here wait do i lose all my items that i stole no what about money
i try i have to try this one more time just hide until morning i kind of can't
there's nowhere for me to go well the game crashed again load the save before it i was
like that was almost like 20 minutes ago wasn't it wasn't that a long time ago
it was 11 minutes all right new music no i already i did runescape not that long ago let's do
uh can you jump off the building i don't think you can does it has anyone ever even
uploaded the zoom beanies ost no this is one song make a new character no no i'm not making
a new character we're gonna start all over again and i'm gonna be even more useless than
i am now so dude this whole game is sunk cost fallacy you're supposed to be a piece
of shit you're supposed to lose over and over again you're supposed to have like a dead dog
on your arm all right we're leaving this town see he ate the beanies good i gotta go to
that fence all right the other bar was back here all right i can't like take this zoom beanies
song right now get the grog grog there you go okay i gotta get the grog which one was it
even in i was in the one that but the one i was just in upstairs it's in this one yeah it's up
here back to bed okay thanks for the grog let's go okay fence there was three oh the camera is
gonna kill me all right there's two bars here one two there's one back here this way right
there's no fence in here anymore upstairs there's nobody up here this is upstairs right
wrong building no that was the right building it was all the way to the end
wasn't it all the way to the end the last bar they aren't always in the bars damn it i had
them in the right spot too there's two oh there's three bars let's just see if he's in this one
um although where does this three of them where's the third guy weren't they hanging out
together god the three of these guys hang out together well that's not good because i
can't sell any of this shit without him here that was why having to reset and go back 10
minutes is the that's the problem now because now i have to track this fucking guy down
and i have no idea which building this dude's gonna be in holy armor trader no damn it
looking for the fence yeah i just i went in all the bars already unless like are there any
others are there is there fourth bar in this town that i didn't see i could have just sold
you stuff there and then i could not uh there's only a 20 chance for me to sell anything in this
town unless i sell to the ones to the one guy and i lost him in this reload leave the dog
i might have to just cut my losses and leave because i'll run around here for the next two
hours looking for this guy eat dog fun uh and all the food what happened to all the food
was that wait hold on a second what happened all the food that i stole
that was also lost in the quicksave oh fuck that's actually horrible no what didn't that get killed
in the quicksave i think it might still be in the chest i'm kind of running out of options here
because i have this i have no idea what this guy would be whatever i i gotta leave i can't
just hey welcome to the stream where i run around in circles looking for one guy to sell
items to no we gotta go uh all right dog let's go i have enough food here or the only other
option is i load the quicksave and just fucking run out try to just get out of the city but the
door is locked and closed because the store is closed all right come here all the dog is doing
is eating your food i had that plan too and that was going to go so well i just got locked
into the store because i went upstairs i had so much food i had money i have to try it i'm
gonna save it here but i like have to try i mean i lost so much like i let's i lost way
too much there now this is gonna be i just have to like try to get out somehow will somebody just
open the door maybe i mean just pick the lock really fast and like run i got it oh fuck it's
uh go go get out get out of the city i had it oh why am i up here with the store closed
just hide until morning i can't go anywhere there's a guy literally right here i just can't
go anywhere if i stand still if i stand still he's gonna see me wait how does this guy not see me
now he can see what i didn't even the starting valley music is not helping it's actually like
making me angry for some reason so wait so if everyone's telling me just don't move at all
no there's no way this isn't gonna work i won't believe this at all how is this working
this is not no it's impossible that's impossible all right so wait a minute wait
a second wait till that guy goes down the stairs and then walk towards so i'm gonna i'm gonna wait
to this guy go i'm gonna go over here once this guy passes this way now why do they see me this
time and the game crashed no i was so close to like doing getting money and leaving i was
upstairs for too long and i got locked upstairs there's no way to get down and i have to hide
and wait and oh i had it done it was done it was done don't burn yourself next time with a useless
dog well i did pick the man and his dog character if in 10 minutes i kill the dog and don't care
isn't that like why even play that character okay i'm not gonna touch anything now just wait
he's gonna walk down here this is like here's my chance i'm gonna scum this like crazy he
came up so much quicker why did he come up so much faster he doesn't he he can't it doesn't
usually come up that fast there's rng with how he comes up i crashed it again because i'm
full go all right i'm gonna do i gotta do a new character i can't i'm just so fucked in this
character but i've got put so much time into that character and it was fun and i soft locked
myself upstairs or i would have to run in like mine for 20 minutes just go to prison i'm
not gonna go to prison i'm gonna die yes what time do they open what time i don't know
when they open when they open say i did i saved over here because i didn't want to lock myself
if just in case somebody comes over and goes to sleep i will have so i'm so glad i did this
i'm so happy i'm not getting rid of the dog i'm not making a new character i got 25 fucking
100 cappies and i got food look at all the food i got shit load of food shit load of fucking
fruits i got i got flowers up there i got a shredder helmet i've got everything holy wait a
minute hold on wait there's nobody down here oh boy oh boy jeremy why don't you just leave the game
huh just leave make a new character for crying out loud i got it i did it holy shit there's so
many things to do what no i didn't think no which i'd saved it it's okay i forgot
everything's fine don't worry everything's fine i'm gonna get back to the spot that i just was
okay i'm gonna peer i can everyone's up there though i just steal the stuff that's in range
take the things that you know you can take that you're not gonna i really didn't get in
there though i have a bunch of anything that's worth money what's the most expensive thing
here meat armor plating armor plating fuel let's see how much it's worth pause the game
building material armor plating has a lot of money that's how like you pick up all of these
the holy flame what the hell is that oh shut up you guys what it's not even worth anything
armor plating i'm gonna have plenty of money now just clean this place out gears if i can pick
it up just take it we're getting close to time to wake up sorry well no fuck the balls
don't need them okay hide over here save scum the chest i'm getting a lot of good experience
though from this i got all night whoa excuse me i got all night to pick this just leave
the dog in the store they'll take better care of it no he's coming with me the safe behind the
counter oh there's a safe right there wow i can't i'm gonna get all this stuff isn't the dog
dying nope dog's doing just fine what's the lockpick on the safe seven percent all right
ee ee ee i'm gonna call this one uh chest is open okay 71 chance to steal these
and they're worth a lot of money that's a lot of money this is dog shit worthless get it out of
here what do i gotta uh this stuff is worthless no this isn't worthless um okay 71 give it to
me got it okay there's one i'm gonna name this one one sword has one just one um sword uh one
sword sword one well that's what's worthless here let's get out of here it's too big got it
what time is it oh fuck did i make it i made it right all right i got two weapons cell value
745 river nest 469 has been wiped out oh okay wait i'll accept something wait hold on
save this is called uh scenario one okay scenario one that's done saved i'm good to go
okay scenario one is played out don't touch anything wait till it loads
scenario one scenario two is pick the pick the safe see what's in there oh boy okay hold on i
got it save game this is gonna be called scenario two safe open what is in here what
i'm so overwhelmed what is this four thousand four thousand four thousand seventy-six percent
yeah i need to i need room i need to make some room pause the game i need a second hold on
no time but okay set which one of these is the best one to take i can take two this one
looks pretty good ring saber paladin's cross got it this one's a thousand cell value
definitely this one give me give me i got caught stealing did i get it no i didn't get it oh but
at least i have i got one just get the other one and then get out i have i got plenty of time
take it got caught stealing you can take three if you move around the meat no i got i already
have plenty and i'm gonna hire that guy because a range i no i can't come on this is
77 chance got it done hit f5 fuck no i'm not grab the stick it's no i'm out of here one two three no
let's get out and let's get it queued up to the door go just wait let's get the the store's
gonna open 6 a.m here we go walk out right at the front door open the store this is the real
timeline okay timeline has been saved okay i'm ready for my first party member
hey remember me uh where's the fence wrong one auto is eating that's not even auto so where was
the fence not in that bar the dog is not dead the dog is alive the dog is it what do
you mean the dog is dead where are you seeing this what are you talking about the dog is fine
look okay fence feed it look it's already eaten that arrow means he's already eaten
look i got plenty of food for that dog i need a fence bad check the bars sunk cost fallacy
sunk cost fallacy is it a fallacy now i just hit big i want to hire you can you tell me about
the first extinction uh happen again why it sounds like crazy talk keep looking for your
wanderer i don't care this guy's dumb are we gonna search for the fence again
yes cost is nine thousand dollars like for what no fence here we are again with this
bullshit bard and i say hey wiggle on over this way muffin i tell you huh i tell you i've
never seen someone so steamed so fast so i took the oh glass is empty sorry pal let
me some cash i'll make it worth you a while i'm looking for fighters not drunk so you
wouldn't happen to be a fighter would you i tell you what i'll sing you a song
i'm thinking about that pay me 3 000 cat tab and i'll sing you tales till the sun stops setting
get lost fence fence no hire that guy i need to sell the things that i just took
hire the bard if i had money let the dog walk around no i'm saving his strength until
he's at least 50 check up the stairs maybe sometimes they're upstairs
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah all right here we go stolen goods no problem so i
i want to keep one of these what's the what's the best one mid-grade refitted blade so they
got hacker class defense bonus indoor penalty damage uh cutting damage 52 this is probably
the best one yeah this one is 40 24 75 40 this is more blunt damage yeah this is more cutting
and got more blunt damage we got 78 13 oh that's pretty good i think this is the one
seven point seven eight cutting damage thank you take these off me
4100 bucks take this plating for all i care uh this stupid this book is though
every citizen has to have one by law uh i don't know what this is gears holy flame
fabrics don't want it all right what do you have here oh my god uh should i just take this
should i buy this from the store clerk is gonna get arrested no no all right i'm going
to get the bar arrange arrange just get rid of this book put this over here the meat over here
too we got food cooked vegetables some fish still that's all arranged nicely uh take the
leather as well and i'm gonna put this in my weapon slot very cool let's go 4600 bucks
this guy better be worth it but book book book book book book what do you mean book
what's wrong with the book what don't do it don't crash oh no where was the safe no i think we're
okay oh my god why i didn't do anything i walked back up the stairs i need to change
settings i'm running out of vram uh is that possible with the gtx 1080 what i need to make
i need more v bucks uh shadows will turn this down to how much money i currently have
40 400 1000 uh all right real timeline is this one here and he's up now it's gonna be different
because oh that's a pain in the ass i'm gonna have to find this guy again baby you can afford
katana and hire but i need the money for food the bard will do all the work i'm sick
been asleep catch me up on this game game about starting from zero your character is worthless
uh everybody's stronger than you you're a wimp and you can't do anything you have no money
and good luck and go enjoy the whole huge game this is just a giant open world you
can do whatever you want there are no rules have fun all right uh here we go let's go do
exactly what we just did again and find the bard not the bard the uh training dummy mark this
on my map because i'm going up there and i'm gonna train and i'm gonna be so much better
everybody wanted me to save scum leave the game let's see if he's up there he's not up here
isometric kingdom come um i mean maybe a little bit but this is not like quests i don't
think well this is the problem let's see if i can just walk around into bars again perfect
he's right here all right don't crash so again we've got i was gonna hold on to the
saber or this this this this all these keep book keep book keep uh i'm gonna keep the book
this time for some reason i don't need two of them why do i need two are you range and
4600 if i see another person writing all capitals sell book oh boy are you are you
trying to light the fire underneath me all right i think we're good let's get this over
here where it belongs splint kit and the meat range it nicely we're golden save how's the dog
doing pretty bad not bad so this is the real question do where do i who do i hire i had so
much money right now to hire somebody this is my first real friend i want somebody that's capable
not some drunk guy that's gonna make me laugh oh let's check the bars it's dead dog is very
much alive all right i can put the dog down because now the dog and i mean that physically
so you need to follow me you have enough strength now where we can walk around together
where's the bard that's the bard all right uh i'm looking for fighters not drunk to tell you
what pay me 3000 cat and i'll sing you tales till the sun stops how about a demonstration
before i go all in that once was a pixie above all the clouds she soared with the zephyrs gallant
and proud she went to the nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan crest and swam with something
something something her breast she went to do uh i don't remember but hey make her a queen
at the end so pretty good huh yeah you're worth it bingo oh we get to we get to make
them we get to actually create this character we get to create the character this game just
became like a nine and a half out of ten it became like a ten really that's fucking cool
that's really cool wow i'm so happy okay yes make another one i'm just gonna have a bunch
of weirdo dwarves except he's got like big baggy jeans on all right let's see idle stance
what it's constantly holding his stomach all right he's constantly has indigestion
leg shape yeah that's fine can you can i can i make like glue man i would make a glue man
if you know what i mean if i could just make him a frog sad eyes if you didn't think we
were gonna play this tomorrow oh you we're playing this tomorrow you better believe it
hair i like it no no beard clean shaven well he is a bard the bard has to be like a blue
hair or something why well because the bard is like a youtuber there we'll go with this
holy shit great canadian fuck club just gave 50 dollars thank you great canadian this kind of
looks like a Elon musk not from the side but from the front it kind of does all right i
i think we got a good one here but seriously thank you so much great canadian for the
50 dollars i love this this is so i'm so happy because that well this this i seriously
thought this was potentially like a 7.8 right guy was gonna give this like a 7.9 right i'm
having a great time it's hard it's interesting but once it became very clear that it's not just
oh you hire the bard and let's the guy that you saw the bar no you can have a band of
whatever the hell you want to make that bumped it up a full letter grid for sure all right
name traveling oh now it just needs a car no no i'm not no no no it's gonna be uh frog musk
no that's gross that's weird it's a bard and uh hold on i gotta think about this is important
because my main character's name sucks this is the new main character sorry you're gonna make
up my own storyline main character sephiroth oh he's terrible no no no this is the new
main character i mean frog busk is whatever that's fine that means the hair has to be
green i'm ready why why do they have to be the same all right we got wait see it's
Robin Hood and his band of merry men make sure that make sure you're following him follow all
right let's do it do you have items everybody has their own inventory oh dear all right let's go
where's the dog dog all right here we are make sure we're nice and together as a unit look at
this why is he so much faster match each other's speed please all right what time is it seven
hours so far almost like what we started pretty early so hold on i'm uh let me just save it i'm
not we're not gonna stop not yet training dummy we're gonna train and then we'll see where we
are in about like we're not streams on anything i started at like two o'clock pacific
so it's only like nine p.m we've got plenty of time so i'm gonna go to the bathroom grab
uh another drink and i'm gonna come back and we're gonna play a little bit more see you in
um sorry i hate to be the bearer of bad news but i actually do have to go because i have to take
auto outside and it's gonna be longer than probably like 10 15 straight minutes so
i kind of have to like leave i have to take care of my real dog i have to carry him
okay we can wait we can wait it's gonna be like 15 minutes straight no no no no it's let's let's
just pick up tomorrow i'm gonna start same time tomorrow we'll go for this we'll probably go
for another seven or eight hours tomorrow too let me take a look over here and the bits
yes so here's what we're gonna do with the bits because i he's like i have to have to take
him out so here's what we're gonna do i'm going to save you ready for this we're gonna
do a super a super bit reading tomorrow night because i'm gonna save all these we're gonna hang
out for like at least a couple hours after the stream tomorrow and yeah it's only 15 minutes but
i was going to end within the next like 30 to 40 minutes anyways so don't do the domain is
dirty all right well hey hey hey i'm gonna try to go for here well fine here's what we'll
do uh i'm gonna go take him out see if he'll go out give me a little bit well the stream
is over right now so i'll come back we'll do the bits tonight and i will see you guys tomorrow
tomorrow we're gonna do is literally gonna start exactly where we just left off on the first
party character i this i'm having it i love this this is like this my my emotions were
like so up and down during this whole stream but no not bad like not in a bad way it was
confusing i was where am i going who am i what do i want to do even if i have no idea
what the hell i'm doing it's been kind of fun just being a dickhead and just dying and losing
and running around and finding a party member so i will be back to do the bits just give me a
just give me a little bit i'm gonna go as fast as auto so as long as it takes
i'll go to the bathroom walk around for a little bit come back in and i'm gonna give
him some food too so yeah i'll see you tomorrow if you take it off same time probably
two or three p.m pacific and i will be right back hello there i come back i see
somebody says germ was walking his dog houses on fire 15 minutes
that was like at least six or seven minutes but at that point if you're gonna like if you're
gonna leave i already was doing the end of the stream voice and it was already like okay
it's time but man no i'll be back and then it's like auto has to go on and you're gonna
feed him and it's like yeah we'll just pick it up tomorrow uh rampaging scrub just
gave five community subs thank you so much rampaging scrub there's a lot of money tonight
a lot of subscriptions and more than seven hours of bits keep playing do something else
tomorrow oh no i want to play like this i'm into this i want to have a shitload of people
you may see this game for a little while here this is cool i'm i like this so what i'm doing
tonight main game this is a kenshi stream now no uh i'm gonna spend some time just looking stuff
up about character development and what did you know how to do things and get more familiar
with it because this is um i think this is gonna be fun at least for one more full stream
right we'll see after tomorrow if it's something that i still want to continue to do
so the seven hour was the tutorial kind of any plans for new year's eve yes i'll be streaming on
new year's eve we will have the ball drop on stream building a town and shit like this
this is not just find rpg guys and go on missions it's build a city together i'm gonna
have like 50 citizens in this town of all frog musks it's very possible but anywho let's uh
let's go back here and go through the bits same time tomorrow around two or three o'clock
pacific i said it before but you've been taking off thanks for joining us uh see you tomorrow
maybe if you're around hey both for us both for us thanks for the five dollars thank you for
streaming hashtag charity thank you for watching and thank you for the hashtag charity as well
sticks renegade thanks for the one dollar we got the wrong screen on that's the wrong
screen uh thank you sticks renegade you forgot didn't you i forget everything
always not possible but literally what you're supposed to do what do you mean can i not do
that i thought i could do something like that aggression cow thank you for the 15
dollars thank you aggression cow uh before i read it let me just save the game here
uh i'm gonna call this one a new beginning because i have frog musk everyone's here
save successful we're good to go come on punch it push it come on exit the game
because you'll heal the back the background noise all right so thank you aggression cow
for the 15 dollars uh hey germa some community members and i wanted to create something special
for you for the holiday season hope you enjoy it uh let's take a look this is called the 12
days of christmas the 12 days of germ's miss uh we i'm gonna hold on to this we're gonna save
this for the end of the bit reading we will watch this before we go let me just keep it
tab open here thank you so much for this i'm looking forward to watching it in about
20 minutes or so thank you for the 15 dollars as well thank you divas for the three bucks
hashtag charity thank you uh i'll hear it oh it's that it's the name that i fuck up every time
it's the name that i screw up every single time uh itres gara got it thanks for the one dollar
interest you're making good use of those tmnt sippy cups uh yeah i don't have one here now
thank you though thank you wonderful telephone for the five dollars just reached my first
year sub but i've been around since the mspaint starting soon screen i'm just less
broke these days love you bud also this is your first character but in real life
uh it's a guy like covered in peanut butter i don't even i don't i don't even know that i'm not
i'm uh i'm uh thank you thank you so much for the five dollars the yeah the mspaint just kind
of turned into this i'm probably going to change this by the way well i fucked it up
uh so that by the way in case you're wondering germa expensive is going to
become a base emote and it's going to be changed into a germa one guy that fits more as one guy
than it does as expensive in my opinion so that'll be that's going to become a base emote and
then i don't know what i'm going to do for the 20 the 25 sub is just like it's that's
a that's so much i'll put like i'm gonna put like an x there which one guy told you to do
that um it might even been in the discord maybe this maybe one guy said it in the discord that
it would be like good i don't know i'm sure one guy told me to do that don't worry hey duke duke
what's going on thanks for the ten dollars uh not gone yet and what the hell was i watching
germa just show auto and you'll get thousands of bits no i don't i don't need to that's
all right you guys know autos around he's he actually was behind me the whole time
sleeping in a little bed that i made for him but uh you were watching kenshi
it is a pretty wild game but one that i currently think is fun to do uh thank you so much duke i'm
not sure when you leave but good luck when you do i'm not sure what the date you're leaving
the link i sent broke well that's not good show us the dog no he's eating but thank you
so much duke much love to you and good luck and again thank you for ten dollars that's
incredibly kind of you smelly but we demand the dog vessel no i he's down there he's get
there's a piece of meat in front of him when he gets up from no now that's like a bad
never mind because i was that implies that he's like down there lying down
no because i was making a reference to the stream dog i told you i didn't want that
dog to be auto i don't want that dog connected to auto at all so that's not what's going to
happen the auto is doing just fine downstairs eating his dinner dog food thank you smelly
boy for the one dollar even given uh ever given thought to playing any of those combat strategy
games like total war sieve nice try or mountain blade uh would be fun to watch you try those
um not really not really mountain blade is something that's requested a lot total war
seems cool because you have 10 000 units on the screen at the same time might be fun to make a
custom map or something no those are not for germa those are not nice try he tried he wrote
of word here and he thought i was going to stumble over and just say it almost you need
fast paced games for this boomer what about the game we've played to the one that i was
just on tonight that's a fast paced game people were screaming at me when i was mining
i was trying to slow it down and everybody in chat is like excuse me sir would you please step
on the gas and hold it down until you touch the floor no i i look listen this this game
i know has like a lot of people that are big fans and that probably spent a lot of time in
it and it's fucking awesome because it seems like a great game i i get it i understand
but i need to like mine the dumb ore to make enough money to buy the dog food
you know what i'm saying but thank you smelly boy thank you keldos for the one dollar italics
did a great job with the effects hashtag charity oh yeah it's fucking i loved it so if
you're curious about that um i loaded up a shitload of sound effects and music files
and they were just on a button press and i'm like hey dude you have full just creative control
he's like you're gonna give me full creative he's like i have full creative control i'm like dude
yeah do whatever the fuck you want except obviously like the the voice changer was there
for bugleberry i mean both like voice changer as in like you know that's his real voice
what software is it it's a stream deck yeah the placement on a lot of those sound clips
fucking perfect explain that clip what's wrong with this one
i mean it's a voice changer so i'm sorry he pressed a button that was called like distortion
effect i would if you look closely we look at my mouth i say i say hey and for some reason
he pressed the button at the right exact time to distort it and added like a monster effect
to it i would hey yeah so i mean that's the explanation for that but if you remember
what the first time bugleberry was on stream that i didn't have a like stream deck i was
opening up random tabs to have scream noises and stuff so it was so much more seamless
for him just to have a fully loaded board with sound effects for him just to do it
whenever he wanted to so no i i watched that stream back and i had a lot of fun it was kind
of hectic though because we had to build up and take down essentially a random bunch of stuff
that we put in the way and we had to be out out at the lock out of the studio no ifs
ands or buts we had to be out at 9 p.m so there was no oh can we like stay no we had
to clean up and shit so if you're wondering why that stream had to be kind of done after three
hours is because of that boomer watches his own streams well i wanted to make i wanted to make
sure it went all right i mean that was you know it was kind of an ordeal how long did
it take to clean uh we cleaned up real real quick it took about three or four straight
hours to put it all up and then it took about when you get locked in just disassemble put
everything in boxes get it out it's probably like an hour and a half maybe hour right when
the stream turned off we got going but i'm glad people thought it was fun i had a lot of fun
i have a lot of uh because i wanted to see the chat too you know i didn't get to see
the chat for the most of the entire stream and it's fun to kind of go back and see what
you know i wanted to see what you guys are saying i think it's fun you guys are saying
some funny shit so but that's uh that's that uh thank you soup said again for the 50 dollars
happy late christmas hope you had a good one as well thank you for the 50 dollars
lots of money sly 161 thanks for the two bucks hey german did you hear that
uh mccauley caulkin is going to change his name to mccauley mccauley caulkin caulkin
is that real uh when are you going to change your name to germa 985 thank you peaceful
hayley for the one dollar hey james wonder what your favorite thing you got for christmas was
off stream and i recently dabbed for you those i i recently dabbed for you so you don't feel
bad about dabbing god i don't i don't feel bad about dabbing because i never did it
stop dodging the question what my favorite thing to press is off stream uh i got a nice
mug my mother sent me these great gold foil playing cards because oh you moved to vegas
here let's go and they're really really nice really cool really sentimental kind of thing
from my mother that was really nice of her and oh wait listen to this whoa here this one guys
remember when i talked about tile and i went off on like a four hour long rant about how i
hated tile so much the little beep things for your phone so you can find your keys and stuff
and i talked about how shitty they were and how it was the worst product ever because
you can't replace the battery you have to like get you have to like sign up for their
subscription program because when they die you can't replace a battery you have to like hey
give me some new ones send but i need to buy new ones now right uh um they have batteries
now tile now has batteries that you can replace i wonder who got that to happen
now i had like i probably had fucking nothing to do with it but uh tile now has a battery of
a replaceable battery so i got new tile for christmas you were the only person to ever
complain about that i i know right imagine if i was that much of like a fucking eagle maniac
that i really thought that that was why there are 60 billion people in america and like one
person that just has like you know a few thousand people hanging out no what if the president of
tile tweeted at you i'd be like um that your products are great they're really like i just
like flew off the handle one night because like i might i lost my keys and i couldn't find them
and the tile was dead and they say they have a one year oh up to one it's a one year
lifespan it was like six and a half months it was just bullshit two of the tiles that
me and kim both bought them and i think two of them would just gone dead after like seven months
and the other two lasted for a year but i digress i got new ones let's see i get i am
not gonna look i'm gonna hold my judgment i will amend my statement 750 of the world's
population is in america yeah there's four billion people in alaska there's i think i
think there's like 11 billion people in la 25 billion people in new york city and then because
like the you know that the heartland of america like the big there's only like 60 000 people
that live in those 12 states that go on like kind of the belt there and one cow into wyoming
hey hey you know from what i hear wyoming's like my name is not like bad it's pretty
great state from what i hear somebody told me like you know i was wyoming it's like
actually nice i was like really yeah okay that's cool well maybe one day i'll go there
it was one guy but that's fine hey thank you to uh g g doran thank you g doran for the 10
dollars no message thank you thank you genv for the one dollar hey junior go make me
my milky what i don't know if i don't know what that means but i'm afraid to read it
uh g doran again thanks for the five dollars on top of your tens i think for 15 dollars
uh sad vega thanks for the one dollar last day to donate to the charity
got bits left over so have some bits for the boomer humor you give us hashtag charity
i appreciate that thank you uh tickles the barbarian thanks for the 10 dollars
god bless you germa for playing this game it's my favorite i'm beginning to see why it does seem
like an immense rpg sandbox but thank you for the 10 dollars and i'm happy to be playing
your favorite game thank you i am monk for the one dollar i've watched so many ads recently for
these enjoy hashtag charity thank you for suffering through advertising for my sake thank you the
thought that somebody would do that is thank you hydra thanks for the one dollar hydra last
stream during the best clips part you played a clip from dark souls 2 and you only had one
estus flask didn't star teach you that the first thing you do in majula is get the flash
in the wall god you never learned never but that whole playthrough of dark souls 2 uh i went
back about 10 minutes later because i went the wrong way i went through um the hide knights are
you have to go through the forest of the lost giants and i went through the i mean that
that whole this that was there was like six or seven dark souls 2 streams but i thought
that was like such a funny moment when i like rolled off the edge but thank you hydra for
the one dollar thank you i am monk for the one dollar they say hi hashtag charity thank you
again for a dollar i am monk made you look debated hashtag charity you can make me you
could debate me all you want that hashtag charity there thank you mr sneak man thanks
for the one dollar and 50 cents activate sneak vessel ps what's your favorite stream of the
year so far pps are we going to get a new york's new year's rumble like last year
ppps haha you said the it's the the board the letter comes after oh twice but that's okay
favorite stream of the year very too many um i don't i can't tell you i have too many streams
this year that i really really was like holy shit that i had a lot of fun i can't really
single any out what's the worst streams of the year i could probably tell you um
so what even what's the worst stream of the year don't sit labo no labo would be like in
the top five for me sorry uh this one carazam was not even this year the second hotline miami
2 stream no i it stressed us all out too much but that's the point of that game
the bird house would that would be i liked that stream i had a lot of fun
bird house was pretty bad what was wrong with the bird house bird house was easily the worst
yeah but that was too recent what about okay but besides the bird house
vampire was the worst stream yeah but was that because that was the worst stream or was because
that was like the worst game you know do am i at fault for that when a game is not that
great yes game okay all right all right i'm gonna have to tell you game review portable
uh dalek says i don't know if i agree with you the game review portable stream was i mean
awful but i liked it everyone forgot about immortal unchanged because it was so bad
i'll give you game review portable though because like that was so the whole i couldn't
get it captured yeah i'll say game review portable is probably the worst stream i did
all year i own it in a technical sense just like technically speaking that was probably
the worst stream i've ever done i thought that's true i liked that stream that's why i'm not sure
i agree with the game review portable pick here for worst stream of the year the minecraft stream
was bad yeah but does it count well it does it count if i was drunk you know what i mean
like if i'm like drunk and gonna play a game like does that count as like that was like a
10 minute drunk guy joke because that doesn't count as a stream that doesn't count you can't
okay you can't take a portion of one stream where like drunk guy plays minecraft for 20
minutes that's naughty that's that's a portion of a bigger stream the labo streams were
torture local streams stays drunk to excuse bad streams i've been drunk on stream like
four times ever in three years come on that's bullshit what like drunk on stream
that i what you did three labo streams that got drunk during all of them no what are you talking
about i got drunk on one of those labo streams one of them i was i was i was having some drinks
but i wasn't drunk there's a difference between drinking and drunk you got drunk and ate
taquitos on your final day in boston yeah that's one of four times we had to watch
get drunk and build cardboard for four hours i can't wait till another labo comes out i'm
doing it i'm gonna do it again i'm gonna do it again and i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it nice
and slow i'm gonna take my time and i'm gonna drink tea when i do it but anyways moving on
thank you has name for the one dollar i left and cooked dinner for two people and you still
failed to achieve anything in the game i actually did not fail to achieve anything in
game i achieved a lot i made a dog friend that i kept alive and now that dog is gonna be around
if i left that dog six hours ago i wouldn't have a band of merry men that is three strong
the last 30 minutes of that stream was somebody yeah somebody just said it was it was incredibly
valuable i'm doing all right thank you sad vega for the one dollar make him look like you so
we can rpu in this world with auto at your side hashtag charity thank you i'm realizing
now that i have to feed another person that's gonna be interesting thank you sad vega again
for the dollar while you were scavenging the bodies he was mastering the sword
hashtag charity thank you druid of necromancy necromancy thanks for the one dollar you're the
dumbest boy alive i don't know if that's true i wrote pay i wrote a essays in college and i
forgot a's on them b's whatever i got my degree it's back there i got an a once
but thank you thank you freudian weapon for the three bucks no message thank you
for the three dollars flug boy thanks for the one dollar hello derma i have found coke and rum
and am on my 13th drink there's no more rum i don't know what this game is and i love you
and hope you had a good christmas my friend much love to you and kim and of course the true
emperor of the world auto little flug boy um thank you so much that was kenshi and i'd be kid just
be careful take care of yourself you don't drink don't drink too much otherwise you'll
like pretend to karate kick other streamers so just you know just just be careful you know
uh mr pigeon thanks for the one dollar i'm so drunk i'm fucking laughing at you hitting his
this dog for the past hour when did i hit the dog i did not hit that dog once oh you know what
the subnautica streams were this year those weren't bad what was wrong with those what was
wrong with the subnautica streams i thought they were fun but thank you mr pigeon drunk
hopefully you're uh hopefully you're doing all right take care of yourself don't drink too
much but i'm glad you had a good time thank you uh jay paul thanks for the one dollar 94 cents
please don't mine any more copper that was during the mining part the person told me i
wasn't funny and that hurt that did like that that like that stings you know that stung the
ego a little there it did i put on like the mining song and i was like pretending to do
like a dwarf accent somebody was just like that was not funny man like you're trying
too hard or something and i was like fuck um sorry but it's all good they're probably just
messing around and but yeah i did it made me laugh because i mean i'm like i'm sitting there
going like oh i hit the stone and find some more ore it's like dude that's what that was
terrible i'm just like oh fuck i'm getting food another hungry hedgehog thanks for the
one dollar hashtag charity thank you super seal thanks for the one dollar i am monk thanks
to the one dollar i've watched the same pocky ad 200 times for these bits enjoy them hashtag
charity thank you for watching 200 pocky ads that sounds like a lot uh toe pack thanks
for the three dollars merry late christmas keep the change you filthy animal thank you
i say hashtag charities well how much uh has been raised i'm curious it's like almost a half
million dollars something right almost half a million dollars nice that's awesome good
that's really good to hear c4g thanks for the one dollar do the mining joke again
oh right because everyone was yelling at me because they were saying no he's doing
the mining joke but the mining joke wasn't a joke i was actually just trying to mine so i
could make money there was no there was no comedy there and then i added i because it's
the mining joke i added the fucking thing with the by the dwarf voice and then a guy got mad at me
there was a whole spiral downward there but thank you for the one dollar thank you
grayfeld for the five dollars i've been depressed lately and your streams have been
awesome keep it up hope you feel better thank you for the five dollars and thanks for hanging
out durham don't let the one guy hurt your ego yeah but that would go against my one
guy policy you know what i mean but thank you uh thank you grayfield take care of yourself
hopefully we see soon sad vega thanks for the one dollar hey germa everyone's screaming about
a prospect button that may or may not do something hoping you notice this smiley winky face
i figured it out there's no manual there's no instructional manual there was just a few
tutorials welcome to dark souls you know what i'm saying welcome to dark souls gotta learn
you gotta die you gotta lose you have to have one toughness because you keep safe scumming
and you're not improving sorry the bard will have like 30 toughness and i'll just stand behind
him but thank you sad vega thank you dark star for the one dollar there is no feasible way
this stream will make it to second germo i disagree i think i disagree with that
i don't know does it did carrying the dog improve strength maybe it might have
it's different if the dog dies i don't care if canned roth gets hurt but you gotta protect
massive moon how long has it been since you edited your own videos uh three days
because i made those uh clips that were put on the christmas eve stream three to four days
yep uh thank you dark star again for the one dollar thank you garon for the one dollar germa
heart hashtag charity thank you flim thank you for the hundred dollars again thank you
for 100 gosh darn dollars thank you flim flim flam sad vega again one dollar i support
your efforts to be annoying and slurp asmr stream go i forget how much people just hate that shit
i'm sorry i'm just a fucking idiot i forget like i'm in my own world up here sometimes
thank you heartbroken samurai for the six dollars papa germ next week i'm going to japan
for a few months to do to a sushi school can you wish me luck i'm nervous here's some money
for some coffee by the way where the hell is whale lord and socks well first of all
going to japan to you're gonna be a sushi a sushi chef that's really cool
yeah like that's one of those things where i hope in an alternate universe i'm doing something
like that that's awesome don't be nervous you're gonna you're gonna knock it out of the park
you're gonna be just fine and where is whale lord fucking lost shipping you've got like
it was like a seven to ten day ground shipping and i got lost in the mail you know i got lost in
the mail anytime anybody says that it means that they didn't do it they didn't do the thing
that you know what i mean hey uh so i'm looking for um you were supposed to send
me a package oh yeah yeah that must have got lost in the mail what does that mean
like the mail like the mail lost it and i know that happens sometimes but it never truly
happens we have tracking numbers now you can't use that you can't use that fucking term anymore
maybe like 60 years ago when ups didn't have an online you could see every stop that the guy's at
with the tracking number hey i got lost in the mail oh shit okay so you have we don't have
computers so you okay thanks you're a liar but oh anyways um it'll be here soon thank
you heartbroken samurai i wish you luck in sushi school take care i'm not sure where you're going
from but if it's a long way good luck i'm sure you do just fine hey e dragon thanks for the 15
dollars is this enough to get you to play the spyro 2 ost yeah you know what that is
zero dollars just say it in chat and i'll play it we'll start with the spyro 2 ost
but thank you for the 15 dollars and hashtag charity thank you garfield the monday killer
thanks for the one dollar here comes uh garfield master of the baloney garf is here to say how much
i loved your earthbound stream it's way different than i remember and so and so forth
joke over how is your christmas pretty garfy i hoped the face of disgust you gave when
you saw garfield present was hilarious i didn't even suggest it i trusted the german community
to give me some garfin publicity and they didn't disappoint special thanks to italics for inviting
me into the stream here's some fun background info about that so um italics on my amazon
is the one that kim wrapped the gifts and italics is the one that made the order on
my amazon right so he made the order and i walked into the room after he told me yeah
you can come in i said okay hey so like i i'm like i wonder what's in there what kind of presents
oh some of them are kind of funny some of them are crazy i was like oh yeah i i can't wait
till the garfield costume comes out and he looked at me like what are you talking about
like yeah you know the guaranteed absolute definite garfield costume i guarantee it's in
there here's the funny story it wasn't in there that suggestion was not used that was
added afterwards that had to have that was added after the fact because italics talked to
one of my mods a couple of them maybe i don't know exactly who he spoke to but they came to
the conclusion that um that it was to be added so that was originally not supposed to be
there i added yeah okay so it was it was grump that's so funny so originally it was
not supposed to be there but it is a little behind the scenes of the gift process and again
i don't i didn't really have much time to say it but if you had a suggestion or if you were
part of that process and you wanted to say you know give a suggestion for something fun thank you
so many of these weird projects and weird streams a lot of it is from shit that you
guys will say and write and help and it makes it a lot easier so thank you uh thank
you to boss trash for the one dollar i consider everyone here friends and it means a lot thank
you hashtag charity well thank you boss trash i think we got a great community here everyone
likes to have fun fuck yeah i also added the feet exfoliation thing because because i thought
kim was gonna use it yeah that's that's the when i got home it was just merry christmas
here you go she was like oh nice so yeah you were right but thank you boss trash thank you
demonic cucumber for the one dollar talking about family guy and uh that the word that
the peter word thank you well i don't why am i drinking so much coca cola it's getting
like in my nasal passages okay thank you dingus town for the 15 bucks kisses hashtag
charity thank you thank you the 15 dollars and the hashtag charity thank you as well
hey plasma player thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents hashtag charity listening to
earthbound and animal crossing soundtracks is so calming but watching germa trying to keep the
dog alive is too stressful not like this thank you doubled thank you double d11 for the one
dollar what's up germa mites germa here for another game or giveaway type exclamation
point don't do any of this thank you for the one dollar double d appreciate it thank
you honey chain for the three dollars hashtag charity thank you no message just hashtag
charity demonic cucumber again thanks for the two dollars here they say hey germa just want to
thank you for making me smile in this shitty month i've been having i always smile when
watching your streams i don't know if you saw this on discord earlier but i made a lego glue
man all right lego glue man i'm planning to do more any rumble characters that you'd suggest
hmm hashtag charity thank you demonic cucumber uh hmm i mean there's mr sneak man yeah
that would be a good uh color palette a good outfit i think mr sneak man sounds pretty good
but thank you for that and also also you should probably do some streams with key wo
because she's been in chat and discord consistently for the last couple streams
and we're gonna start corrupting her soon hashtag charity are you here now i hear that
get in the discord let's go i'm i'm right here she ain't here
uh i've done a couple of streams i think before a long time ago
keep those nine hours ahead of your phone that solar system isn't accurate at all
that's imagining imagining that's the first time that you like you've is that the first
this is the first time is you just click on a random stream like it is the first time
you've ever been here because that like that's so funny i love it like how could you not
come in here and be like this person's fucking stupid this person has no idea how the planets
work oh you would think that this person was not to be trusted with anything the wording on
that was perfect too oh man hey welcome thanks for coming down here hope you enjoyed the stream
come back tomorrow we'll be playing more games uh but anyways uh like i've told you guys before
i have no rhyme or reason to people that i play with just sometimes it just organically happens
sometimes you say hey italics what are you doing tomorrow oh i don't know what are you
doing tomorrow hey star what are you doing tomorrow hey vinny what are you doing tomorrow
oh another bunch oh hey vinny can i like come like ruin your stream by like making you
play uh red dead redemption 2 but i keeps on disconnecting from me and i like waste a bunch
of your time you know like okay you want to like do something definitely not playing with
you tomorrow that's for sure his plans with me uh but i don't really have like any or i it just
happens you know sometimes you go oh i wonder what they're doing and then that person will
also probably say i wonder what they're doing so who knows mate like hey you want to stream
with this person stream with this stream with her stream with him i don't know it just kind
of happens i don't really plan them so maybe you'll maybe it'll be like oh tomorrow
no i'm not gonna even say that but yeah i'm i'm like i'm i'm a fucking weirdo guys you understand
stream with drake no i just know i mean what do you want me to say
german rejects a famous rapper that's not even them no i'm what i'm talking about is like
i don't that's if i looked at my cell phone right let's just say that all huge celebrities
have phone numbers that come up no matter what you are it'll say like okay my phone rings look
over it says drake doesn't even say a phone number just drake because he's so famous like
he just you need to know who's calling you know what i mean if i looked at my cell phone
tomorrow morning and i had a call it was drake the rapper like it was drake famous drake was
the name i didn't put that in it had to be real how early is this i mean is if it's
is it like before 10 o'clock in the morning because i'm just gonna look at my phone i'm
gonna go like this like i'm gonna go can you even see the camera here's the phone
and i'm gonna go fucking back to bed and then four hours later
mm-hmm now i'm awake and i'm making food by the fridge
i'm afraid to answer this now because now i fucking didn't answer the phone call the first
time and why didn't you answer my phone call earlier in the morning when i called you earlier
i don't know i don't know don't just say i don't answer six days later the phone rings
again oh fuck i didn't oh no it's it's drake oh my god i forgot to call him back like six
fucking days ago and now he's gonna be angry with me no no just don't answer it don't answer
the phone another four or five days later i call you i call i call drake hey dude what's
up man hey hey what's going on uh what's up how are you now i've been pretty good but trying
to get a hold of you yeah i've been real busy you know i've had a lot of shit going on a lot
of stuff happening and i you know i've had a lot of things to do and i haven't had the
opportunity and i've been off stream i'm a streamer i can't talk on a phone during a
stream i was making a sandwich the first time he called and i was asleep the first that i
was asleep the first time he called making a sandwich second time he called and the third
time he called i was afraid to answer that's the truth but no i wouldn't even i wouldn't
answer the phone and maybe one day i would answer it okay anyways where are we we are here so i've
said my piece sick okay uh bonjour thanks for the one dollar the great canadian fk club thanks
for the 15 dollars talked about it earlier but thank you for the hashtag charity as well
mostly lost thanks for the one dollar getting close uh speaking of kiwo she does some fantastic
green screen edits in case you haven't seen them i have she puts them all in one video
hashtag charity i have seen them they're very funny i actually i liked on twitter i did a
liked on i pressed like button on twitter she's done more
okay i didn't i haven't seen a couple of these i've seen at least four of them but this is nine
minutes here there's one with batman here and i don't know what it is so i'm gonna hold on
to this one i can oh this one looks kind of funny add it okay you add it to the new movie
night playlist yeah because we're going to do an encore night so this is definitely something
to add to that movie night two oh yeah i can i confirmed a movie night not two
encore movie night epilogue movie night encore movie night one was six and a half hours
movie night encore movie night colon encore will be probably like an hour and 20 minutes
maybe like an hour we need more footage for a movie night too that i would say that yeah so
more like four hours i don't know maybe we'll see but i did see a few of them already and they were
very funny i want to watch this one so bad right now all right let's just watch one we're
just gonna watch one okay i just want to watch one every so often you're gonna notify
that i'm streaming and i do lots of fun things on this stream like playing hitman we played
that last night that idiot's right there
fucking minecraft ad just one more all right it's like eating potato chips you can't have one
hold on i need to get this off the screen you should have acted they're already here the
elder scrolls told of the return their defeat was merely a delay to the time after
oblivion opened when the sons of skyrim would spill their own blood
no one believed believed they even existed and when the truth finally dawned
but this one they fear in their tongue is dovahkiin dragonborn
okay no no no no more we can only watch one more all right last one absolutely terrible the city is
in danger fucking costume nut jobs is taking city part piece by piece eat your vegetables and fruits
too you get to them the more you become a chance we have to stop them you're a scientist
i've ordered silver sable and her team to shoot you on such cities had enough of your vigilance
oh my god the spy crap something of a scientist myself it was perfect it's time for you to pay
oh man that was funny god okay you know that was it we've got to save them we got to save
them for encore night one more you got to do one more all right that's it
oh shit you see my underwear wait a minute hold on when i did that cartwheel
my just like underwear comes up oh shit wow okay oh god damn it yeah i saw that one i didn't
see this one
i'm not even in the right direction
oh man i'm gonna eat all right i'm gonna eat the whole bag of chips i can't i'm already
halfway to the bag you know when you look down at the bag of family-sized Doritos and
you're like wow i just bought these and i just opened them 20 minutes ago no okay we're done
i gotta crinkle up the bag and put them in the closet it's no no we got to save these we
got to save them they're too good to not come on encore night all right i did i have a chip
in my mouth though so i have to finish this one oh no i saw this one
oh god
oh my god
oh i hate that clip it's my least favorite one in the water water
fire and nations live together in harmony then everything changed when the fire nation attacked
what is this
digimon
feels
that was that was awesome hey man welcome to the stream my name is germa nice to meet you
oh i finished the whole bag god damn it no we're gonna watch those again i shouldn't have eaten
the whole fucking bag unbelievable shit whatever anyways uh that was um that was awesome those
are very very good that was in nine minutes of i've had probably like outro music playing
from almost all of them too we're gonna what we're gonna watch those again on the true
encore night you want to link absolutely uh key well if you if you're watching this
or if you get uh if you get wind of this stream uh that was great now hop in the discord oh hey
what's this gta night oh watch out what's up whoa you just hit that guy so let's finish the
bits so when is the encore movie night now that is a tale for another day after the new
year or perhaps let's think about this that could be a snap of the fingers there that could be
excuse me what do you want to do on new year's eve that sounds like a pretty good
night for an encore possible that that's very close it's only what one two three that's only
about four days from now that's like not even three full days so we'll see might want to wait
till after the new year but we'll see i'm not going to guarantee anything but should be a lot
of fun thank you again key well those are fucking hilarious uh big march thanks to the five
dollars frog musk for the next germa rumble hashtag charity i get a feeling you probably
see a couple of the characters from this game and another rump uh kraken thanks for the one
dollar just want to donate my last bits to say that you and your community always brighten my
day germa thank you germa heart hashtag charity for sure thanks for sticking around thanks for
hanging out and thanks for being part of the community thank you for your last bits also
thanks to uh i am monk for the one dollar tell the oreo story again i ate too many oreos
i was sick i threw up my mother's bed and i couldn't move and i threw up all into my mother's bed
that's the whole story thank you for the one dollar uh garon thanks for the one dollar again
hashtag charity smelly boy thanks for the one dollar again coming from somebody whose first
exposure to games was pokemon in the ds uh no auto saving and fallout new vegas frequent
crashing you need to get way better at saving your game before and after buying and selling
risky moves always jeremy i know you know you mean you're talking to like you're talking to
a boomer here i remember the days of no saving well you didn't get to save the game you just
lost and had to do it all over again that's i'm not admitting anything that's just what you
guys call me as like a fun thing to call me fun yeah it's like a fun thing that you
it's like our thing here you know it's our thing that we have here
let's keep going uh rampaging scrub thank you for the five community subs thank you so much
very generous of you we talked about it before but thank you gonderland thanks for the one
dollar while suggesting stuff for the amazon presence i found this 700 games uh sorry that
page does not work it does know that link no longer works but apparently it's a 700 games
version 700 games by viva media 700 000 games version 2.0 would you look at that
i wonder how many of these are just the same game ten dollars amazon primable okay well i
know what we're doing at some point works on windows 10 700 000 games i'm gonna yeah we've
got to play the part we're gonna play part two one customer review it's one star
doesn't work in windows 10 well i'll get it to work that's 1.4 million games in total
thank you yeah even if it didn't go through the christmas eve stream i feel like it'd make
for a long-awaited stream sequel to the original video that sounds fun i think we'll
do that some point in the new year definitely early somewhere in january hey thank you pug
ninja for the one dollar german nosebite hashtag charity thanks for the nose wipe
thanks for the charity what thank you for the one dollar par follow me thanks for the one
dollar that erizuka was like a child to me turn up in my nostrils it's coming on my
nostrils i hate soda stop drinking them it hurts thank you for the one dollar the erizuka
is amazing it's a great toy i recommend it highly i am monk thanks for the one dollar
these bits are just to delay the stream hashtag charity no they're not that fine
not by very much like 10 seconds uh fat boss thank you fat bossiant for the five dollars
hey jerem i have my whole family and i have been sick through all of christmas here to try and
get my mind off of it thank you also a clip hashtag charity thank you uh thank you fat
bossian for the five dollars i'm really sorry to hear that your family's all sick and that
you're sick on christmas that's never fun but thank you for the five dollars and here's the clip
that's kind of death wednesday january 23rd 2019 it's coming up in 43 p.m that's coming up i i
have to be here i have to be streaming and i'm gonna be in like hockey equipment people
think that's a joke i am going to be in like a football uniform i'm gonna be in like
gear and i'm gonna sit here with like fucking the pillows of surrounding me and i'm gonna sit
here and just scream until that's over but yes i am aware of this okay i'm not i'm not even
kidding on january 23rd i'm gonna like final destination movie my house that's true i agree
serious i just fucked myself i'm gonna board up the windows i'm gonna only drink green juice
from now until january 23rd 2019 i didn't i didn't do that i've had a lot oh no oh no
oh well well see you on the 23rd and it has to be the 23rd too like the day of evil
doesn't the 20 didn't jim carrey make a movie about that number and how it's evil
uh uh thank you rag are no way for the four dollars any possibility of playing metal gear
what's the cannon on you losing to pinwheel i still think you lost honestly hashtag charity
the cannon is i won first try it was very very very hard for me first try uh metal gear rising
i keep people really want me to play that game is metal gear rising that good of a game to
stream is it like a good game that you would want to see on stream should i beat metal gear
rising on stream because that's essentially what i'm asking yes probably yes yes yes yes yes
really okay you don't beat any games on stream uh well i'm sorry that i have news for you
i've got some news for you let's go ahead and just take a quick little look back here at the
backlog and um i'm just kind of having what's happening what's happening why am i talking
um that was weird uh but i'm really really sorry to say this uh but less than two weeks ago
i not only did i start but i completed hotline miami and hotline miami 2
some of the hardest video games that have been released and i've eaten both of them
last week that was last week i did that last week i cleaned up the i was the janitor i cleaned
up the house i built the bird house that was a completion hitman 2 i beat hitman i completed
hitman 2 that was a few weeks ago that was like a month two months ago i didn't complete
red dead 2 because there's a very very specific reason for that i streamed red dead for about
30 to 40 percent of the campaign and i was like you know i love this game i love rockstar i love
i wanted just to kind of sit there quiet with my mouth open on my couch and complete it you
know what i mean completed the labo completed all the labos all of them beat jevil first
try all right that's we're almost done with the bits let's go but maybe i will play metal
gear rising put it on the list flustered flamengo thanks for the one dollar germa this
christmas season has honestly been quite stressful for me just want to ask how you stay motivated
hashtag charity uh well i'm sorry to hear that sorry here it's been stressful time holidays can
do that i would say best way to stay motivated is to try try to challenge yourself because
you give yourself something that if it takes it's gonna take a lot of work might take some
time but that's how i do it i stay motivated by trying to challenge myself and doesn't just mean
in like work or streams just in general it's a tricky thing though try to beat hotline miami
2 on stream it doesn't matter what you're talking about but motivation can be very difficult
and i get unmotivated sometimes it's hard sometimes it takes a lot to stay focused on
something did he like kenshi oh he loved it he loved kenshi sadly what what do you mean sadly
sadly oh no like oh great he likes it thank you c4g for the two dollars uh please
explain the plus two minus two meme to me i have a small brain i don't get it
well it's a meme that was killed that was banned forever if you if you weren't here
a few years ago a couple years ago back in 2017 i deleted i banned forever all the old memes
from the channel if you set them then you were gonna get timed out and uh it was there was a
revolt then there was a revive stream and then there was there was a well one of them got
to live and it had of course it's like the cryptocurrency one that's like just laughing in
my face of course the one meme that get got to stay the whole bald coin crypto thing well
that kind of well laugh it in my face now ain't it whoa whoa what the fuck was that but anyways
uh it means it's me getting points and losing points for saying something that people thought
was either really unfunny or that they thought was funny and sometimes people use it even when
i'm not attempting to make a joke sometimes i'll say i had like fucking corn flakes for
breakfast today and i'll see minus twos in the chat and it's just like that's i just
told you what i had for breakfast and it originally comes way further back when me
and italics played kane and uh kane and lynch right and we had to beat the whole game in four
hours and if we had a funny joke we got extra time that was a fucking joke what that
was a disaster but that was one of my favorite streams ever me and italics were
actually desperately looking around for another co-op game that's less than five to six hours
they're very hard to find to do that again we actually did do it yeah after all the bullshit
it was minus 30 minutes for nudity yeah and there was a shitload of nudity
but that's kind of the whole story there you know tldr fashion hey shooshroom thanks for the
10 bucks hey germa i've been having a hard time with my bird who is dying but your streams
and positive attitude help me incredibly you have no idea how much you help me and others
keep doing your thing thank you for the 10 dollars shooshroom and i'm really really sorry
to hear that any companion any animal any pet any friend that's always that's always incredibly
hard to do i'm really sorry to hear that thank you for the 10 dollars thanks for sticking
around and speaking of birds i was actually sometimes when i am in the you know i go to
the pet store to get auto's food i see some of those birds that they have in the pet stores
they look like a lot of fun they do there was one big parrot that was at the local pet store
and this thing seems so smart and so funny and interesting so i can imagine how much fun
they are and how how incredibly hard it is for you right now shroom so thank you so much for
the 10 dollars i wish you the best thank you don't get a big parrot for your first one well
no i wouldn't do that unless i knew exactly what i was doing and i don't have the time or
the resources to be able to take care of a bird like that that big but they seem really
really interesting thank you interest for the one dollar no message thank you double d thanks
to the one dollar speaking of suggestions for streams you should build a huge lego set on
stream hashtag charity well just replace two of those letters add an a and then a b
you know just keep the capitals that's fine thank you thank you hashtag charity as well
cooking stream when um i i don't know i'd want that to be elaborate i don't want to just put
up a webcam in the kitchen and just say this is me this is me cooking um this is uh
tuna tuna fish and um i just make a pancake by hour and 10 minutes see you i'm not i don't
want to do that i would want to hire like two professional chefs to come and do like a
cooking thing with like two real actual professionals to teach you the three of us
well i yeah well i watch them and like get in their way and shit and like like
be really annoying taking food out of one of the bowls put my hands in like the shredded cheese
and it's kind of good don't have the money for a bird hey guys check out my friend
gordon ramsey no i didn't say money i said time or resources resources doesn't always have
to be money resources can mean a lot of different things resources can mean space to
have a bird that's right resources can mean who can take care of the bird because let's put it
this way right if i was up here for eight hours what what what what if the bird got out
of the cage you know i mean just flying around and you're gonna get a huge huge cage right
that would take up a lot of uh room that we just don't really have but they're damn cool but
anyways thank you to ike turtle for the one dollar fell asleep during one of the mining
jokes i don't know which one though because there were so many i woke up and i had a dollar
i in bits so here you go thanks for being you germa expensive thank you for the one dollar
thank you double d for the one dollar they say youtube link good thing i muted it i'm so glad
i muted it what the fuck what's this okay i know i had to hit back i had to get back
it went to like a dragon ball z abridged episode oh my god whatever i got it the first time that's
all that matters i just reverse gnomed myself with the it still worked hey mr pigeon thanks for the
one dollar let's go sicko mode on what is thank you franker z what let's go sicko mode on push
at tf2 they have franker z here and then hashtag charity what is it thank you and
trader for the five dollars hey sir i haven't been able to catch too many streams this year
i just want to let you know that you are a very funny and talented guy you never fail to
give me a laugh with the stream highlights looking forward to another great year of streams
also i'm not germa complimenting himself i'm a real person hashtag charity that's true
that is not that is not me uh thank you don't worry about not catching streams you don't have
to uh feel obligated to be here if you have time and you want to hang out absolutely i'd be
glad to have you but thank you for the five dollars and i'm not a chat bot hey the great
canadian fk club why am i not saying that word i say that word a hundred times a stream
because it's actually written out like that that's why uh finish the bag hashtag charity
that was during key was green screen video compilation thank you for the 50 dollars
great canadian great canadian i'm looking at the weekly here they're at 26,500 bits
that's 260 that's 265 dollars holy shit well thank you there's a shitload of huge bits this week
my god thank you germa did you get the joke i'm calling you dumb what that's christmas money
well thank you uh thank you to uh looney b for the one dollar merry hollymus hope everything's
going well for you insert wholesome comment i can't wait for the new glue man shirt hashtag
charity it's not a new glue man shirt is the it's the original glue man shirt but there will
be another new shirt so it's going to be the glue man shirt from before i just wanted to bring
it back because it's a lot of people a lot of there's a lot of new viewers over the last
three or four years of people that didn't buy it before that have been around for a long
time so there will be new shirts i promise but thank you thank you domana cucumber again for
the one dollar you should host a germa game awards with a bunch of fake ads and costumes
every award should just be the top banana trophy hashtag charity germa game awards
who would come to that what people in the industry could i ever get to show up to that
thank you 50 for the 50 another 50 dollar 5 000 bit donation here thank you fitty
hey eu guy coming in right at the end here i've been saving up these bits until i would catch
you live love you germs and love you chat germa heart hashtag charity awesome thank you
i was actually talking this morning in the discord about eu stuff and it's just
i would love to have more streams available for people in eu
so you don't have to stay up so late but then like nearly almost 80 percent of the whole
audience is in north america so catering to the north american audience and if you've you
know if i do streams that cater to eu then everybody that wants to watch in north america
might not be available it's just it's a it's a balancing act so it is it is hard to do
it is uh it is a thing can you name your next kenshi squad mate after me
uh no me no uh maybe maybe maybe that was such a quick maybe that was that was a beater
it was i'll that i'll count that even if it wasn't it wasn't even close to being the same
word i would give you that one but thank you too fitty thank you double d for the
one dollar hey germa just letting you know that drake was in the chat the entire time
now he's crying himself to sleep and he's going to write a song about you look what you've done
all you have to do is stream with him hashtag charity well i look forward to what the song is
and uh kirby apparently kirby had their bits eaten a few times but uh let's see it's a
youtube link it's a gnome link it's a gnome link okay well that's that was a lot of
and i got it and this time it's not going to be played again
uh well thank you kirby now before we go uh i'm going to play the credits
down in the corner here actually i need a different thing here or are you going to do
this to me come on we're going to play the 12 days of christmas video while the credits
run in the corner and i would really love if i could get the credits but a lot of things
were changed because i had the by the way if you didn't know that this whole computer
went to the studio i had to tear down my whole setup and put it back together again
let's see i gotta get the right widget here okay there it is this out of the way
okay so the credits are gonna roll and we will open that video so thank you everybody
for your subscriptions there are a shitload of you guys know so many people are subscribed to
this channel thank you let's watch the video and i had it open in a tab but i tried to i
desperately panicked and clicked out of two gnome videos so i don't have it anymore so
let me go get it here it is put this up here all right let's watch it
i beat that game
so
come on
what the hell
so
i have to see that like nine more times
eight
what was that what was that like milk
seven what's up
that's not five feet tall
is it doing what are you doing look at that short ass hair
so
how many times have i done the comb i thought i did like two times
shut shut up
holy shit what was that
okay you all know what the story is on there i don't even have to explain it
well thank you for that that was that was what a lot of work went into that that was
really really funny thank you so much for that gotta show the credits you know i've got of
course that you know who made it thank you so much that was the 12 days of christmas i don't
remember half of those things happening what was the thing with like i got smashed and
my car exploded i don't even know what that was but marty20k gave out 12 community subs marty20k
is the person who uploaded that video so thank you thank you so much marty20k great work
and thank you for the huge amount of community subs as well
rose road redemption oh my god i forgot about that game but that is going to take us to the
end i will see you guys tomorrow let's just make sure that didn't miss anybody i don't think i did
unless somebody came in right now which no that's it i'll see you guys tomorrow around two or three
o'clock pm pacific time more kenshi see you soon have a great one take care of yourselves
good night i'm sorry that was so loud i had to okay i fucked it up whatever good night