Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Facecam Fortress 2, playing, oh, bang, as the Heavy live stipulation match.
Come here. Come here. Damn it. Live stipulation match as the Heavy, as you can see with the killing gloves of boxing.
Dr. Pepper? Hmm. I don't know how well this is going to go, but I'm only allowed to use the killing gloves of boxing.
Let's see if I can't. Oh, come on. All right. I'm going to bait him. I'm going to bait him. Where'd he go? Come on. I got to bait this guy.
You just get in here. Come on. Oh, now there's a mini sentry. Give me some health.
Playing on Frontier, which is, I love this map, but no one really ever plays it. I think it's because it's really, really big.
Oh, this guy. No, no, no, no, no. I'm going to go up here. Let me eat. No, I don't even need to. There's a health pack. Ha ha.
Can I catch somebody off guard right here? Come on. Right here. Right here.
Say hello to my little friend. Hello there. No. Oh, come on.
Two guys blew themselves up on me. Oh, for the love of crap. You are not a spy. Let's just eat this right here.
No, no, no. Got to get another kill. We got to get like two or three more kills.
That scout right there is dead. I'm going to walk up the steps and I'm going to. Whoa, what? What is going on?
Oh, they're over the guy. Come here. Oh, good job. Good job, scout.
Let's get back in this. I've got people to punch in the face. Come on. What do I got?
One kill so far or three technically because those guys both blew themselves up. I don't know. I don't know.
I got to get like 10 kills. That was a bad number to say because I don't know if I'm going to be able to do that.
Here we go. Jump over the edge here. Be a heavy spy. It'll work. This sniper wants me so bad.
I'll get the sniper. I'm going to get this guy right here. That counts as one. Hey, sniper. What? Where is he?
Did he get killed? Oh, damn it. There's the sniper. There's the sniper. This guy's AFK. Come on, kill him before I. Come here.
Oh, no, I can't go down here. This guy's going to just shoot me. Here we go. Come on. Eat the sandwich. Eat it.
Eat it, you fat bastard. Sniper's right here. Where are you? Oh, hey, what's up, man?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Get up the stairs. Somebody's right here.
Where's this guy? Come on. He went down here. No, he's dead. He's dead. He's dead. We're good. We're good.
Oh, I'm so scared right now. I'm terrified right now. I'm going to wait for someone to drop down.
We'll just get on the cot. Come on. Get it. Get it. Oh, no, I fell off the cot. Oh, I fell off the cot.
We're going to win. That's a win right there. Two thumbs up right here. Come on. Good job, guys. Good job.
Yeah. I don't even know how many kills that was. What did I say? I wanted to get 10?
One, two, three in the beginning. Four or five. All right. I still owe like probably four or five kills.
So let's see if we can get them. Come on, boys. Let's do it.
Come on. 60 seconds. Time travel. All right. Here we are going to sit here.
I'm going to wait for them to come out. I'm going to attack. Not going to move. Don't move.
Play this like a spy. Don't don't move. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.
No, never mind. Hey, spy, get out of my spy spot.
Here we go. I am going to catch a son of a bitch around this corner.
We go. This is it. Yeah. Oh, crit sniper. Are you serious?
This this. I got backstabbed. Oh, I had that.
I would have punched that medic right in his mouth face. Oh, I had that, too.
I can't believe a crit sniper came out of nowhere. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it.
Damn it. I'm cool with sitting here. Come on. Push the cart. Push it a little bit.
Yeah. Yeah. Here you go. Come on. Come on. Push it. Push the.
All right. You know, let's just go in. We're going in for the. Here it is. Oh, yeah.
Somebody else. Get somebody else. Somebody walk right through this hallway and just smash.
No. Is that. I thought that was a teleporter for a second. What the hell? Heal to full.
I'm behind enemy lines right now. I got I got a good a good thing going on right here.
Oh, I think that guy saw me. I think that Pyro just saw me. Oh, crap.
Come here. Oh, no. Come here.
Oh, you son of a bitch. Damn it. I would have had him.
I would have had him. Where are we going here? Where are we going here? Come on. Oh, they kept it.
All right. Two more lives, two more lives. That's what I'm asking here. Got to get like one or two more kills in the next two lives.
Am I going the right way? Yes, I am. This is a good spot to be in. I can sit right up here.
I want to string together like three kills in a row. Oh, I'm sorry, engineer. I'm like taking your spot.
There's one. No, no. Another sniper. That's what it was a spy.
Come on. This guy's no idea. He has no idea. At least I got him.
All right. One more death. One more death allowed. How many kills do I have? Ten. I got to my goal.
I got to my goal. I got to my goal. I got ten kills. That was my goal.
Let's see if I can pad that goal a little bit here. Let's hope so.
Last life. Come on. Here it is.
Yeah, I knew it. I knew it. What? Oh, it's a pyro. Pyro spy. Hey, what's up, dude?
You want to do it again? Come on. Do the stair stab again. Oh, no. There he is.
Look at me. I got to chase this guy out. Oh, fantastic. Oh, please don't jump and backstab me.
Please don't do it. What the? What? I just got so freaked out right there.
There is a spy up here, man. I'm telling you. It's all right. Whatever. He's going to kill you.
I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do. I can jump over here, though. Oh, no. Mini century.
Yes, there it is. Eleven. Eleven kills. Oh, make that twelve. Make that twelve.
Mini century just annihilated me. Oh, and there it is.
Well, that's going to do it for this live stipulation match, guys. Thank you so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody. See you guys soon.