Ah dude, I just ripped out every single cord that was plugged into my computer.
I'm not even kidding. I don't know what the hell that was. What was that all about?
I'm sitting here completely normal. Like there was nothing wrong and all of a sudden I look
over and I clicked on the start menu and it was just just scrolling. I wasn't scrolling.
I unplugged my fucking mouse, my keyboard and I opened up Binding of Isaac and it was on two
monitors and the other monitor was going. What? I've been using this computer since I left.
What was that for? Oh my god. Anyways, hello. How are you? Good to see you again. Hope you're
doing well. I have returned from my absence and what do we have? We have a lot of things to talk
about. This is, this is a lot. Some of these things are really good. Some of these things I
do. Hold on. Let me just open up my thing. Ah, global power raid. Oops. Okay. Well, don't
monkey ass yet. You don't know what we're talking about. Shit. Can I move this mic? Hold on.
Is, am I delayed? What do I have for a delay? Let me change that. It's been a while.
All right. No, I got no delay. I'm good. Okay. So the first thing I'm going to talk about
now, where do you start? I have to, okay. I have a book report right now. I'm up in the front of the
class about to present my book report and it's different. You're all teachers. I'm one student.
You're all teachers. All of you. I got selected to do my book report in front of like the teachers
union because it was, it was so good. And I'm up here like, okay. Um, where do I start? George
Washington had wood teeth and he, uh, okay. So let's start. Why not? But how do I, what,
what should I put on in the background? Don't ask me here. Oh, I get an F. We're on do OST.
Now let's like, hold on. Oh, we're going to play Binding of Isaac because, uh,
holy shit. Repentance is out. That's very surprising. That's really cool.
Oh, hold on. Unrecognized game pad. Don't do this again. Oh God. The project, the projector
isn't working. I have my image that I got of the first image search of George Washington's on the
fucking projector and it's glitching out on me. George Washington. Okay. There we go.
Camera's not on, right? There we go. So, uh, what do I want to put here? Everything's going to be okay.
You're the one teacher in the back that realizes that I have like a lot going on. I got a lot to
talk about. Son, everything's going to be just fine. And I'm like, Oh, yeah, it is going to be
just fine. Thanks, Mr. Davidson. Mr. Davidson reaches in his pocket. He's got like a big flask
and he just like. All right. So let's just get started. I gave you a PR press release before.
Those of you that read it, here's what we have. Here's what we're going to start right here.
As of today, I'm going to go over the medical stuff. So medically speaking, the reason why I
have been gone for so long and the reason why I was gone a while back too is to take
my pain problem really seriously. And I've started to. I went in, I had six injections into my spine.
Well, not my spine. That's a lie. Into my like spinal muscles. It was like not even real.
I had six injections into the muscles around my spine. They're called trigger point injections.
They're supposed to alleviate some of the tension that I've been having
in my chest and back that could be radiating. I could have trigger point problems. I could have
myofascial pain syndrome. I could have costochondritis. I could have a hernia problem.
I could have. The list goes on. This has been going on for three years. Those of you that aren't
aware of this. So I did those and they helped a little bit, but it didn't fix the problem.
The problem's still there. It hasn't gone away. It might never go away from what I've potentially
been told. So what I have to end up doing now is start to really seriously treat this dead serious
priority number one. And I want to do that without having to stop streaming because I don't want to
just stop streaming. I've taken like these month-long breaks or these like, oh I'll be back in like three
months. It sucks. I don't want to do that. Obviously because I don't want to just disappear.
But I kind of have to do what I have to do. And on top of that, there's been some things going on
with my family too that I need to really pay attention to. So they're kind of just jumping
on top of each other. And I need to make the decision essentially to dial back streaming.
And like dial back my presence on the internet, I guess you could say. I don't take this decision
lightly. This is not something I'm like really, oh I can't wait to like only stream once a week.
But I have to really start to take this dead seriously. And if I can continue to stream once
a week or so, or maybe once or twice a week depending on what we're doing, I don't want to,
I won't have to take these monster breaks. I can focus on going to maybe more intense physical
therapy to try to work this out. Do more procedures. Get this stuff done and some of the
other stuff going on in my personal life too without having to do like a three month break.
And I think that's going to stay for a while. So this is not something that's going to be here for
a couple weeks or like a month. I think this might be a potentially permanent change to stream only
once or twice a week. And I mean, I've been doing this for like 10 years to let you know.
And if I have to change things to be able to do it the way that I know I can, the way that I'm
comfortable doing it, then I'm going to do that. I have to. If I wasn't going to make these changes,
then I don't know if I would continue to be able to like want to stream if I'm serious.
Having to like have my brain in like three or four different places and like come on and do
streams and stuff. It's just, it's something I don't think is going to happen. He's done. No,
I'm not done. I'm not done. I'm not retiring. This is not a, I'm retiring stream. I'm not,
my career is not over. All right. It just got started. It's just getting, my career is just
getting started. It says the guy in like the dirty overcoat that's like running around outside
yelling at like popular streamers. You're right. My career just got started. And I reach in and
grab the flask and I'm like, you know, who the fuck's that weird guy over there? He keeps like
running up and yelling at us. I think that's, that's German985. I've heard of him before.
Yeah, you better have. I'll always remember you. The plan is to not have to do that. You understand?
The plan here is take some of the stuff going on in my life really fucking seriously and
continue to do the thing I like to do, which is this. And I know people are going to be concerned
here. I know they are about money. Oh my God. If you, if you, if you stop streaming, if you only
stream like once a week or once in a while, what about all the subs? What about all the money?
I never cared about that in the first place. If I did, you would have probably known that by now.
Dropping like subs or losing like viewers or something. This channel has done so,
like the view counts have been so ridiculous over the last year. The amount of people,
the new people, the new community that this has kind of generated, it's overwhelming at times.
But I was never in the game of trying to kind of min max my Twitch stats. I don't,
that doesn't do it for me. I want to continue to have fun here and enjoy what I'm doing. And
recently, it's very obvious. I can't like lie to you guys. What am I going to pretend like this
has not been a problem? The last year or two, you've probably been very aware that it kind of like
hurts to like exist. Like my back and spine and chest, you've seen me with like the brace on.
You've seen me wearing like the boomer brace and the chest piece. And oh, I only stream for like a
few hours at a time. Get a standing desk. Oh, but even standing is kind of a pain in the ass too.
This is something that just hasn't gone away. I've been to the doctor a bunch of times. We're
trying to figure out what exactly could it be. Is this something that's so simple and so easy,
but nobody has fixed it yet? I don't know. But it's, I can't, I'm not gonna lie. So boomer pog.
And don't, I also don't want anybody to twist this either. I'm okay. I'm not, this is not a problem
that is necessarily like ruining my life. It's just something that's constantly there,
that constantly has to stay in the front of my brain. So while I'm doing anything,
half of my brain is like, hey, your chest hurts. And it's like, all right, well, fuck off,
shut up, leave me alone. And the other half is like, hey, you're doing this thing. And especially
with the increased activity that I've been doing recently, obviously it gets a little nicer.
And obviously if COVID starts to get more under control, there's going to be a lot of shit going
on here over the next four or five, six months stream wise. So I, I kind of have to be able to
do these things without having it be a problem. So I'm trying desperately over these next six to
12 months to really, really focus on it. And to lead into that, why don't we talk about something
else? Why don't we go from like, oh, once a week Andy, and now that's, oh no, he's retiring to,
hey, are you ready? Hey, what's he gonna say? What am I going to say?
What's the announcement? The announcement. Oh, I'm going to milk this shit out of this one.
Grotto Beasts is real. It's going to be a real collectible trading card game that you will be
able to buy. It's real. I have had to keep my fucking mouth shut about this for a while. I want
to kind of start to build some attention to it because eventually here, probably fairly soon,
you're going to be able to buy your own Grotto Beasts packs. And what does that, you will wait,
we'll give you more details when that is, you know, more in the front of the brain, right? Of
course it was real. It was made 40 years ago. Yeah. But it's real in the sense of this channel.
I cannot wait to show you more details of what that is. You're doing NFTs. No, cards. Like you
could get them in your hand, physical card packs. What did I miss in the last 30 seconds? Somebody
update that guy. Grotto Beasts is real. It's a real card pack opening game. Physical. We're
not talking digital. We're talking physical cards. Coming soon. And going to be probably
doing merch too. Grotto Beasts merch. I'm going to wear this shit on stream. Razzle Puss real.
Finally, merch. Well, I only do merch when it makes sense. And this makes sense. Sellout streamer.
Oh, I get it. Let me lean in and put my hand up to my mouth and lean in. I get it. He's only
streaming once a week and he's going to milk the fuck out of us for all of our money. Grotto Beasts
merchandise once a week, Andy. Fuck this guy. Omega-Lel True. No, no. We'll see. We'll see how
cool it is. It seems like it's going to be really fun. Take it all. But that's big announcement
number one. There you are. Now, the next thing I'm going to say is not necessarily an announcement
as much as something really cool. When I was originally going to come back, I was going to
show something that we're going to watch together right now. It is a video. This video. You know
what? I don't think I'm even going to say anything about it. We're going to watch it right now. Are
you ready? Are you ready for the premiere of the Rat Movie? Rat Movie premiere? What does that
mean? I thought you already did the Rat Movie like a long time ago. Bionicle. And joining me now,
Joe Biden. Go. Go. You're there. I lost him. He's not on the line anymore. Oh, shoot. He was just
on the phone. Kidding. Not real. That didn't happen. That's a fucking lie. Don't you guys
remember? I forget how to stream. I forget how to be a live streamer when I take three weeks off,
a month off. I'm just sitting here talking fucking nonsense. All right. You ready? Let's go ahead
and watch it. This is the Rat Movie. But unlike you probably have seen so far, a lot of work went
into this. A lot of people had a lot to do with this. Let's just go ahead and watch it. No more
stalling. Here we go. No more stalling, I promise. Just one more second. One more minute. What is
this? This is not it. This is a fucking ad. This is a Liberty Mutual ad. It's not a huge announcement
of Liberty Mutual. Oh, this game rules. How come I can't hear it? Wait, why can I not hear this?
Johnny on the spot air conditioning in his face. Where's the movie?
Where's the movie? Hold on. I gotta turn off Isaac. On the spot air conditioning. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Isaac is still playing. I'm really bad at this.
Okay. Are we ready? We are ready. I'm ready now. All right. In three, two, one. Rat Movie
Reanimated Collab. We're the rats. We're the rats. We pray at night. We stalk at night.
We're the rats. Fuck off. I'm the giant rat that makes all of the rules. Let's see what kind of
trouble we can get ourselves into. So sue me for being thorough. I want to know that you know what
the plan is. Look, seriously, mate, how many artifacts do we need to steal before you trust
me with these jobs? Well, I just want to make sure you know what's happening. We're going to
get the treasure. We're going to get out of there and we also have to sell it. We must get it.
That's the most important thing. So be on your A game. We go now. I got to drive the car today
because it's my birthday. No, don't let him get in the car. Please don't let him. Come on.
He's driving. Whatever. Bloody hell. Oi, more importantly, since when did we have a rat problem?
We don't. Get in. Let's go. Speed it up. Yeah, that's the speed I'm looking for. That's the type
of fastness I want. I don't even know where you're going at this point. We've been driving all night.
It's my birthday. Hey, you, you're just, you're running over a guy right now. Are you fucking
serious? Mommy, next time we do this, I'll get my nan to drive. Excuse me, sir. Yeah, you over the
dancing. It's actually $10 to dance in this building. You're going to have to give me some
money. Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, may I have the attention of the class? My name is
Dick Dastardly Richard and I'm here to take the treasure chest that's in the back room. Go get it,
boys. I'll follow you in. And let me tell you something, clerk. If you as so as move a muscle,
I'll make sure you stay buried in that ground there. All right, let's go. All right. Give me,
give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me. Is the treasure in there? Is it in there?
Yeah, it's all here. Oh, yes. Now that's what I like to hear. And now we are invincible.
Not so fast. You stand before Gerard, guardian of the treasure chest of the Mayan temple.
And I will make sure to grab it. Hey. Oh, fuck this. I'm off. Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, we're the rats. We play at night. We stalk at night. We're the rats. All right. Yeah,
that's cool. Yeah, I like rats. Nothing bad with rats. But let me tell you something,
over my dead body are you getting this treasure? Rats, rats, rats, rats, rats, rats. Look at that
flock of birds over there. That reminds me of my favorite movie, The Movie. Is that's your
favorite movie too, right? Yo, my favorite movie is Frozen. I like Elsa and Anna. Okay. Now I kill
you. Wow. That's great pick choice for favorite is movie. I wonder if I have to think that now.
Now I get to be the giant rat. Cool. Surprise. So you're trying to tell me that inside of this
building right here, there was a giant rat among other things, the giant pickles. Did he say
pickles? Or am I putting that in there by myself? Whatever. Sergeant Pickles is going to go in here
check it out. We're going to make sure everything's okay. And give me some candy corn too. That's a
weird request. I know, but just get it. You guys are going to drop it. We're going to be in big
trouble. So quit pressing around. I hear somebody coming. Hello, sir. Welcome to the rat cafe.
There's no rats here. It's just hamburgers. That would be real nice if that were true.
Except it isn't. You're a rat, aren't you? No, no. Why would that happen? That's not us. We're just
people. And I'm going to be taking you in. And wouldn't it be funny if this were real?
I'm just kidding. Be careful though. There's apparently a giant rat around.
You have a good day, officer. So you figure anything out in there? Nice clean. It's back to
the drawing board. Well, that's great. I don't know how to draw, so you're going to have to do
the drawing. Sergeant Scritchy Scratch of the Cat Police reporting in. You are now relieved of your
duty. Thank you for your continued work. Thank you. Your duty will not go unnoticed.
What's that on you? What? Are you wearing a rat on your shoulder? Why would I be wearing-
What the fuck? Boss, we got big problems. The Cat Police are here. Are you kidding me right now,
Cat Police? Get us the fuck out of here. Get us out. We're getting the fuck out of here.
Come on, gentlemen. You can't believe it. You just did it. I just did it.
Good job, Cat Police. You did it again. You saved the world. And that's what we do as Cat Police.
We make the world a better place.
Whoa. What the? What's happening? Where am I? Oh, that was awesome. That was awesome.
There you go. There was rat movie mystery of the Mayan treasure fully animated.
Reimagining of the whole thing. Let's go over who made that possible. All these people.
That was absolutely fantastic. This video is now going to be probably public
on the second channel. If you want to watch it again. We are all rats. Yeah, that was- I was
going to show that like last week, but some of the things kind of were happening. Had to delay.
This is my two- this is a 2,000 subscriber video?
You know, I forgot that Burger Boy Eats a Cheeseburger. That video is fascinating.
I forgot about that. I forgot the password. That's a funny meme. You know, that's a funny meme,
but here's the funny- here's the actual sad funny part about what you just said.
I have not logged into my German 985 account probably in so long that it would not register
the IP as being mine. It'd probably be like, alert, fraud activity. Somebody is trying to
log into your account from Las Vegas? Holy shit, this has to be a fucking hacker.
Yeah, but excellent work. Chestnut is the one that organized it and put it all together.
Good stuff. And that is that. The refinal like sus face. There you go. I think that might be
public now on the second channel. You are the sus face. But Repentance came out. I was going
to play The Sims 1, but I really wanted to give some time here to talk about everything and talk
to you guys. It's still premiering? Oh, well, you'll see it later. You're living what? Maybe
the sus was the friends we made along the way. But long story short, and also by the way,
there are other streams right now being worked on. Do not take me saying that I'm going to be-
And by the way, when I say once a week, I mean scheduled once a week. The same day,
the same time every week. So no more, oh, maybe it'll be on Monday. I guess maybe I'll see you on
Thursday. And then maybe Friday. This is going to be a schedule. Every time at the same point,
same place. Now, how this becomes something I need to work on is when is that going to be?
When should I do this once a week? Maybe one to two days in a row. Should it be Saturday?
Should it be Sunday? And I think the idea is to do one more of these on Saturday. And then maybe
do like some polls and see what you guys have to say. Maybe we can see when the most people
are around for that once a week. There's a hundred subs. Yeah. Holy shit. It was PQ.
P. Q. P. Quay? Am I saying that right? A hundred subs, community subs. Yeah. Saturday,
definitely Saturday. Yeah, it'll probably end up being on the weekend because the weekend,
obviously, is the most- probably the most people can watch anyways. And I'm going to try to make it
early enough so some of the EU crowd is not going to have to- Oh, it's Saturday. Can't wait
for Saturday at 4 PM. Well, that's the one time a week that it's going to be live and I'll never
see it. So most likely Saturday, not early in the morning, but somewhere around probably 12
Pacific. I think 12 PM Pacific on Saturday is a perfect place for it. There's 22,000 people here.
Holy shit. Well, what's up, guys? What I was going to say before I cut my- I keep cutting myself off
mid-sense. Just because I'm going to be streaming less does not mean that there's not still stuff
going to happen. It's not like, oh, here we go. Once a week. Forget about all the other shit that
I was going to do and all the plans I had. I'm just going to open up fucking Isaac for a couple
hours or whatever Saturday and then see you later. No, there's still tons of shit going on. There's
tons of projects, tons of interesting things that I think are going to be really fun. A few big
streams are in the works right now and they're going to happen. And I just want to take the time
necessary to make sure that I can comfortably continue to do this and still enjoy doing it at
the same time. And I just tapped all of my fingers. I'm tapping it on the desk like this. I'm really-
I'm at the podium giving you guys a speech. The Catboy is confirmed. Yes. I mean, just, you're
going to- it'll be on Saturday. Well, no, no, no. It'll be on a Saturday. It's just- you'll know.
With all that being said, let's continue to do some of the things I want to do today.
I want to play the new Isaac. It's been a long time. I've been waiting for this to come out.
I'm excited to try it and mess around. But I hope I could give enough details on some things that
you guys understand kind of where I'm coming from. Because my 10-year anniversary is coming up in June,
right? June or July. Not 10 years on Twitch, but 10 years like on the internet as like an
e-clown. And as we cross this 10-year period and I start to get a little older, I want to make sure
that- and the medical stuff continues to be a thing. I really want to make sure it's something
I want to continue to do and that I'm still having fun doing. Because that's what keeps me
here at the end of the day, is that. Am I having fun doing this? Do I still want to be here? Am I
still enjoying myself when I'm here? That has to continue to be yes or I'm not going to do it.
Got to be very clear. So doing this is the way that I'm able to do that. 70-year anniversary.
When are you going to do a Jeremy Elvertson face cam? Do what you need to do. Yeah. And
look, eventually here as the years go by, I don't have a plan, right? I'm going to keep doing this
as long as I'm still being able to and enjoy it and stuff. I don't have a plan. It's not like,
oh in five years I can't wait to be this, this, this, this, this. No, I'm just doing this and
I'm just here. So let's go ahead and pull this up now. Back to Binding of Isaac. I've been looking
forward to playing this. Volume up a little. I have not played one second of this new expansion,
so I'm looking forward to it. I hope I have the... Last time I played Isaac, I had a save file,
right? Among Us. He peeked at Among Us. I didn't peek at Among Us. I've never played Among Us.
Do you understand? I can't use the controller. There we go. Let's go. New run. Oh, he's annoyed.
I've never played Among Us. I was my, I was ripped into a meme that I didn't even know
was going to be a thing. And then I became the Among Us sus guy. I didn't peek at Among Us.
Like that had nothing to do with me. That wasn't even my face. That was manipulated to a point
where it wasn't even me. Everything. Kane? Uh, I usually do... Let's go Kane. Among Us peeked at
you. Oh shit. Um, wait, why? What's, what is going on here? Why is it, why am I the second player?
What? Oh my. Dude, how did I activate co-op? I didn't do anything. Is the controller fucking broken?
What on earth just happened? Do I have to? I can't play keyboard and mouse with Isaac. No way.
What? Hold on a second. This thing, it doesn't work anymore. Control disconnected. Re-press any
button. What the? I don't know why this keeps happening. There's something going on with the
slot. Oh no. This is the Xbox one, but it shouldn't be doing this. Stream cancelled.
I'll show you next Saturday. Once a week. I have no idea why this is happening. Have you
guys noticed? I swear to God, there's a fucking conspiracy here. I'm going to go off on conspiracy
shit right now. They have made all USB cables worse over the last five years. Do you remember?
I used to have the same USB cable, the same lightning cable for fucking decades and they
worked fine. These new USB cables, they, they degrade so rapidly. It's, they, it's on purpose.
I have not gone through, I've gone through so many USB cables the last year than I have in the last
10 straight years. What happened? And lightning cables, like iPhone cables. What are they doing?
All right. I hope I can find a new cable. Or can you do Bluetooth with, um, can I do wireless
with the Xbox controller? Oh my God. What a pain in the ass. Yeah, but see, I can't even get out of
here. Press any button. I'm stuck in, in this, I'm stuck here. Why?
All right. I got one. I got it. Okay. This is USB-C. Why do they have so many different USBs?
Just make one. Micro USB, mini USB, USB-C, a USB 2.0, a USB 3.0. Just have one fucking cable.
One cable. One USB cable. Why is this seven? Who, who's doing this? Fuck them. Get Congress.
Get Congress involved. Right back. Everybody hold on. That's literally right in the next room.
Oh my God. This is what happens when you just, he's mentally deranged. I'm fine. I'll be right back.
Okay. I found one. Found a USB cable and this one, this one works. Remember we went through three.
This is what it's like to get old. I think it just ran out of treadmill for like an hour.
Okay. Now what? What is going on now? Does it think I'm, thinks I'm, how do I fix this?
All right. Die. Wait, who am I? Am I, am I player two? Restart. New game. I want to be
Kane on hard. Dude, I just, what the fuck is happening? What is it doing this?
What the fuck is happening? Restart the whole game? I can't even hit any buttons. Why is this,
how many people can play together? Why does it think there's five people in the room?
What is happening? Why is it that I am now using the controller? Who am I controlling?
I'm multiplying, but why? Why am I multiplying? Why is it the three Isaacs? What?
Did I use this to my advantage? Start button spamming. Go into the menu. I can't even go
on the menu. Every, restart the whole game. Use one hand. But how come I can't even hit escape?
Just restart the whole game. Alt F4. Yeah. But why is that happening? Okay. Alt F4. All right.
Somebody help me here. What's going on? Your computer's infected. Isaac and Isaac with his
Isaac. This is what happens in Germany. It gets too high. Windows settings. Okay. Go into Windows
settings. The PC has encountered software. But why would it be? It's, you might've had, you, you,
you might've had two controllers plugged in, but you don't realize. No way. That's not even
possible. That's impossible. You were with the controls while the game was open. What?
Only press start with the controller you want to play with as player one. Yeah. That's what I did.
And I loaded into the game and then I was the player two. Be patient, chat. He's bald.
Blow on the cartridge. All right. Hold on. Enable, enable, enable, enable. It's not the USB. It's the
game. I had the same issue. Unplug your Xbox controller and exit the game. Okay. All right.
Let's go back in. I, I've unplugged it. I plugged it back in. Does it work? Okay. I'm in the game.
I have the controller in my hand. I, I, I'm using the analog right now. This is the controller.
Controller is now activated. New game. I am now playing as Kane with, I, this is the controller.
Kane. Okay. What the hell happened? All right. So this is the binding of Isaac repentance.
I'm already angry at it. I'm already like, I'm very upset right now.
I, that's all these new features. Okay. We're good. Please tell Jerma every time you want.
It's because you plugged in the controller after starting the game probably. No, cause I was,
did you actually have four players in the game or was that a weird bug? Did I just, hold on. Did
we just find a potential like speed run thing to do to be able to have like four Isaacs and just
somehow have a bunch of devices hooked up to you where you control them all?
The, the multiplayer was, you, you were a little ghost, right? No, you're not special.
All right. Let me get into this. I love this game. I have more time in this than any of the game on
Steam. So I had CF2. It's a fact. You want me to prove it? Take my word for it. I'm not fucking
showing you. I don't care. It's upgraded multiplayer. Oh, wow. That's awesome. Actually.
Is it online or is it co-op only? Cause it was called only for the longest time, right?
Kane's got better pills. No, he doesn't. He doesn't care about us.
That's right. It's got remote play. Okay. I guess it would be hard with lag to do this, right?
The music is terrible. Oh, that is Scorpio poison tears. That's pretty good. Stop. That's pretty
good. Stop. How can I go in here? You no longer need keys to go into that's a weird change. You
don't need a key anymore. Really? Not the first shop. Oh, wow. That's insane. That's a really
good. That's a good change. Although does it really matter? Cause getting more than 15 coins on the
first floor is pretty rare to do anyways, right? But I guess it's better. New coin noise. I don't
think I like it. But what I was saying, anybody know of the new stuff? Do I need to have beaten
the game a certain way a bunch of times to have the new stuff unlocked? Cause I don't know where
this actually sits. I know that I've beaten the game probably like 40 times on this save file.
That's the thing with Isaac. I have so many save files. I have this. I have a ton of time on the
switch. I have a ton of time on the PC. You got to kill something three times. Three times beaten.
You just have to beat the game 120 times to get the character unlocks. Cause on the switch version,
I have a ton of time. I've beaten the gradier mode on every character and stuff, but I don't
think I've done it once on the PC version. So we'll see what happens. All right. Let's go.
Wait, one more. Okay. Run on extra HUD. Oh, that's right. Why is that not on?
I just gave somebody an absolute heart attack by putting that on. Can you, can you imagine
that like just, just like the pixels changing from where the F is to where N is, right? Like
OFF to ON just cause somebody a fucking breakdown. Think about that. Interesting. The gamma up to 120.
Oh yeah. The pop-ups, active cam, extra HUD. There we go. Mini. HUD offset. Ooh,
I didn't know you could do this. Kind of want it like there. Found HUD. I thought it said garbage
bars. Is it too bright? I'd like it to be 110. 115. Found HUD on. All right. Let's give it a try.
Oh yeah. That's much better. Turn the charge bars on too. No, I like to guess. Die. Is it
going to get me through? Yes, it is. Charge bars show things like brimstone. Yeah. But for me,
they distract me. I'm not going in that room. And I know so many people are going to watch me play
this and they're going to say, Oh my God, just run into the boss room. Hurry up to go to the boss
room. And I'm going to be like, no, I want to individually go and hit the poops and look around
and stuff. People are going to say, Oh, just like, God, it takes me 20 minutes to get through this.
It's been an hour for him. That's what we do here. That's how you have to watch me stream games.
What would normally take you 40 minutes will take me two hours. That's just the way it is.
That's the way it is. And you're here. Don't leave. Don't please. I'll be, I'll go faster.
I promise. Watch this. Ready? One photo. Tears. Oh good. Tears up. That's good. Let's move. I know
people, I'm going to miss tinted rocks. I know Isaac is underrated. I don't know if I agree with
that. I think a lot of people love this game. What's this thing on the right? That purple thing.
What is that? A little purple hook. Did I pick that up? Oh, it's the curse. Okay. I love this game.
I know that Edmund, Edmund, I can't say his name. Edmund, Edmund Macmillan said that this is the
last Isaac expansion. He's kind of, this game is so fun. Everybody loves this game so much.
I almost kind of feel bad in a way because he's just like, oh, fuck, this game is so fun.
Everybody loves this and it's like an amazing creation. I have to make more of them. I have
to continue to make them. He said that he was going to make a two eventually in 3D because he
can, he can pull that. He could go to 3D, right? It could be like super Nintendo going to N64. We
could have N64 graphics with Binding of Isaac 2. I'm not talking 3D like now 3D. I'm talking like
Nintendo 64. Do I want the key? No. Still got it. I love the poison. Welcome back,
Gerber. Ooh, wait, don't use it. How is he not getting hit? I am a living demigod. Mom's locket,
you feel her love. What does mom's locket do? I don't know. Doesn't this open somehow? More
hearts? The locket opens, doesn't it? Opening things will heal you. Oh, okay.
Really? You had to make like the funny breathe in joke? You just don't get hit. Like I could
have avoided that. I had to do like the funny look at my breathing pattern. It was stupid.
Go to the shop. I don't have enough money. Ooh, rainbow poop. That's a full heal, right? Yeah.
I did, what hit it? You should be ashamed. That's why I said it. I am ashamed that I would
even attempt that. Use diaper, use stink. That's something to do with flies, right?
Remember, you're not streaming. You forgot to click the stream button. That's better.
Chance to get hearts when opening stuff or a poopoo. Remember the hearts? No, not doing that.
We can't see the game. That would take some serious discipline from you guys to not say that,
besides the one person that just did. Are you going to scream from the retirement home?
No, absolutely not. Another joke is made that, oh man, I'm going to stream forever.
We're going to be 70. No, I'm not. No. Guys, I will be long gone well before my 70th birthday.
Oh, is this the ghost pepper? Lame tears. Oh, nice. These explode though, don't they?
Why can't we grow old together? Hey, you want to hear something really sad?
When you guys are 70, I'll be dead. That's like really sad. Holy fuck. Yeah, guys,
you understand? When you're like 80 years old, I will have been dead for probably 20 years.
How old are you? We're at 20? 19? The most age group here is like 18 to 24. Did I miss
something? What did I miss? I'll go in the shop now. That thing halves all damage, right?
Don't put that on. Is that something that reduces damage? That's like when you die,
something happens when you die. Oh, they changed a bunch of stuff. I'm going to get the bag.
Nice. That's a good return, except it wasn't. They're going to be really mad about this.
Okay. Should I get it? I don't have an active. That's not worth it. I'll save it.
All right. I'm going to go to the boss. I am furious. 19 gang here. 19 gang.
Um, all right. Monstro. Sometimes you got to use a fucking nice, quick, utilized bomb.
Although I guess with default enemies, that was kind of not worth it. That does a lot of damage.
Does it stick on them? Holy shit. That's insane. That was a ton of damage. All right. This is a
luck up and keys, right? All right. And I got, uh, why are those blinking? Why are the black hearts
blinking? Oh, you never give one heart for, uh, for a little familiar. The new animation. Oh,
they explode. Let's go. Five-year-old Isaac two with N64 PS1 graphics. They're similar.
Yeah, that'd be, I would be okay with that. I think that'd be pretty cool.
Oh, we're not twenties. Not everybody here is in their twenties. 19. All right. Let's spend it.
Did they change the slot machine at all? All right. I'll take it down to 10. That's it. All
right. Blow it up so I don't get tempted to do it again. Perfect. Uh, that, uh, that one's really
good. That's the one that does your tears damage instantly when you spend a coin, right? That one's
awesome. It sucks. What do you mean it sucks? No, for fucking idiots like me, I just get a million
coins and I go to a boss and I go, and the boss dies. That item is trash. Whatever. Map is probably
more useful. Yeah. Excuse me. Mr. Green. Get out of here. Hey, uh, okay. Good. Cool. How many items
have they changed? And how can you be so certain that these items are what you think they are?
This is brand new content. There's a lot of nerfs too. Oh, let's go down. Remember you don't have
any new unlocks. Yeah. But I mean, won't, won't they show up? Items should show up.
Wouldn't the new items appear like in the pool of items? Yeah, they wouldn't. Who are you talking to?
Most new items are unlocks. Yeah. Not yet. Who are you talking to? That's right. Nice. That's my
favorite comment of the day. For sure. Cause if you really think about it, I am just speaking out
loud in a room. I'll, I'm by myself in a room. I'm not physically talking to anybody. My voice
is being transmitted through alien technology into your alien technology desktop. That's zoinked.
You're zonked. That's a new enemy. That's not. I don't know. I'm of the opinion that the fact
that your microwave works, we had to have been visited by aliens at some point. Right? The fact
that this is like a box that like goes and your food is ready to eat in a minute.
Like how did they, how'd you even come up with that? Why would you even do that? Why would you
even think to do that? Who fucking made the first microwave? It was like, you know what? Let's say
I'll put radiation in a box in your house and turn it up to like a million. What? It was Dr. Wave.
Just Google it. No, I don't, I don't want to do any research or Google anything. I want you to tell me
what it was. I don't want to actually figure it out. I want you to tell me anything and I'll
just believe you. Come on. Like typing in Google, like who invented the microwave?
It's like Dr. D micro. Okay. Yeah. No, but like you told me, just tell me it was aliens
that gave the technology to us. And then I don't, that's it. That's what it is. Use incognito.
Imagine how fucking paranoid of a person you would be to be like scared to Google who invented the
microwave. Why would you need incognito for that? No, no, no. I can't have anybody's ever seen this.
Nobody in my house. Nobody. I can't have Google though. Who invented the microwave? No, no, no,
no, no. Incognito for that one. Faded Polaroid. You feel fated. What's that? God damn it. Stop
calling me out. What does this do? I almost said faded microwave. Does a microwave get
like diminishing returns over time? But can it just generate radiation energy for forever?
Does it burn out? Does the thing burn out in the middle? What are you even saying anymore? I'm
saying like when your microwave goes bad, are you okay? Okay. I got to stop like fucking being
stupid. Oh, when a microwave goes bad, please God give me a conversation to hold while my brain is
in a different location playing Binding of Isaac. Hey, do microwaves go bad? Almond milk. Damage
down, tears up. You feel. Oh Jesus. I shouldn't have picked this up. Wait, that's going to make
way more fires, right? What's wrong with me? Why am I fading out for? What do all these things do?
Why am I? I'm faded. You're faded. What's my damage? 1.3. That's horrible. All right. Secret
rooms right here. Probably. Maybe. Fires are good. Yeah, the fires are going to be awesome.
No, let's just kill the boss. Whatever. I got money though. Should I go in there?
Faded. Yeah, I'll get the map. It's definitely worth it. I need to get more damage or this
run is over. I need at least five to six damage or this run is over. Over. It's not coming back
over. Oh, secrets. Like the almond milk and like the soy milk, right? Whatever. The things that
make you just shoot a million miles per hour, but your damage is terrible. I'm of the opinion
that if you don't have at least five damage by floor five, just fucking uninstall and come back
later. Right here. What is that? That's new. Oh man. What is that? That's like mega dog food.
That's a full dog meal. I need bombs. That's seriously omega dog food. All right. I need
bombs now. The dog feast. Bomb. All right. I'm going for it. They're all concussed. Is that
what the faded lemon does? Actually, nevermind. With the fire, this might be fine. I just need
more luck. Holy shit. That's actually awesome. The fire is amazing. Bomb. Shot speed up. I'll take it.
Shot speed up. And that's Guppy's caller. Eternal life. Imagine getting Guppy with this. Faded
brain. I need a bomb for this damn thing. Microwave fact incoming. Microwave fact incoming.
I think it was deleted. Yeah. I think you guys, that's like spam. In 1945, the heating effect of
a high-power microwave beam was accidentally discovered by Percy Spencer, an American self-taught
engineer from Howland, Maine. Employed by Raytheon at the time, he noticed that microwaves
form an active rate from an active radar set he was working on started to melt a chocolate bar
he had in his pocket. The first food deliberately cooked with Spencer's microwave was popcorn,
and the second was an egg which exploded in the face. It exploded in his face?
Was there no cover on the microwave? Wait, did he not, was it like a microwave convertible? He
just could look down and just blew up in his face? I can't get, with the bombs in the shop.
That sucks, but whatever. Let's go. I can't get that thing. That mega dog meal. I want it so bad.
All right, pestilence. Let's go. Am I negating his dogs with this? Okay, I was completely wrong.
This is really good. Bandage. No bombs, though. That sucks, whatever it is. Can't get it. You just
mulched that guy. That's a really, that's a great term. I've mulched him. All right, whatever.
Shop. There's no bomb in the shop. I was just in there. Just give me more damage. I don't care
about anything else. Just damage up. Damage up and shop. Of course I get two. Damage up and
tier size up. I missed a bomb? I don't think I did. What are these? This is new. Spiked rocks?
What does that mean? I'm not wasting the bomb. What was that? Come on, open, open, open, open.
Oh, I had a black heart, right? Oh, come on. Infamy. Blocked damage sometimes. Oh,
this is really good. As long as I'm facing the right direction. I like the Isaac music when it
goes. Stop pretending. You know, you could probably like program a chat bot for right
stop pretending at intervals of like eight minutes. And like a streamer, like I would just look over
and see it and be like, Oh, what the fuck? I'm not. That's the, that's the guaranteed way to make any
streamer be like annoyed for a second. Guaranteed. Even if it's, you just, maybe if you're making it
up, you're just saying it for fun. Doesn't matter. This guy's different. This is the same coin.
What's it? Coin bomb. What is he? Is this new? What'd he do? Charge. He's a charge bomb. Oh,
I thought it was, I thought it was coin C for coin. Well, what are, I don't, okay. There's more to
look at. Hold on. Microwave. Oh, they're monsters. They're monsters. Microwave.
Hey, they're putting utensils in the microwave. You can't do that.
Why are you doing that? I don't know. I don't think, does anybody get that? I don't think anybody got
it. Whatever. That's fine. All right. Last one. What are you talking about? Nobody? Oh, wow.
All right. What the fuck are you saying? I don't know. I was, that was the buff scene from Gremlins
2. I like that movie. All right. Should I, should I take the umbilical cord or the, the thing? This
faded a picture. I have no idea what the faded picture really even does. Just hit them with the,
what? The faded. All right. Give me something good. That's good. One shot. Got it. Yep. Why love?
Hooray. All right. Uh, I just wanted money. Baldi. I see that was a lot of message for something
I'm not going to read. So whatever. Ooh. I need bombs. Wait. No, I don't. Who has these bombs and
you can fly. Sorry. You just, you just like picked me up from my armpits. Like me deadweighting you.
You just lifted me up by the armpits. Leave me alone. Get away from me. Get away from me. Get
away from me. Get away from me. What the fuck does that picture do? That was quagmire.
It was quagmire. I can't even replicate it. I can't replicate it. I don't even know what it was.
Um, I don't want to take a guess. Why would I do that? Hi Jerma. Hold on. This looks like
an important message. Hi Jerma. New items will show up and stuff, but to unlock the new alternative
path and endings, you need to beat hush three times. Okay. If you've already gotten a lot of
after birth plus unlocks, you might not feel too bad just downloading a complete AB plus save
and starting repentance from there. Okay. Um, I, I think I've beaten hush at least once or twice
on here. Download a save. That always feels so icky to me though. Like I, do I want to do it?
All right. I had to do it to beat hush three times. Yeah. Hush is obnoxious. Oh my God. What
am I doing? Use cheat engine. Um, ah, maybe I'll get a save file. Watch out. When does this come
in a switch too? I like playing this in bed. That's everything, right? Yeah, that's literally
never be serious. I mean, literally never hurting my head, seeing that many things happen.
Mom's pearls range and luck up. I'll take the luck for the fire. That's awesome.
All right. What do you got? No, I'm not doing this beating using we shark to beat this game.
Take them, do it. No. Oh, get out of here. Get out of here. Those are the worst rooms in the whole
game. These guys jump. I don't like it. Good. Stop pretending. Tending to like be good.
I see that context can mean anything. It could be what I'm saying. Stop pretending to not know
what that is. Stop pretending to be good. We all know you're bad. Stop pretending to be bad for
views. That's another one too is how is he so bad? Oh, that one drives me nuts. I hate that one.
I don't I guess I could get some bombs. Oh, no, he you don't get bombs. You give them bombs.
Well, now you have to die. Oh, fuck. I'm not okay. Give him more bombs. I only have four.
I need them for secret rooms. How is he pretending this much? Well, I do. I hope everyone's doing
well. It's been a while since you've seen me. Those who that may have trickled in before will
go. We're going to go over some stuff here. We'll go over just quickly because there are a lot of
people here. So I got we got to reiterate some things. First and foremost, medical stuff is
progressing. I'm going I'm doing a lot of shit for it. I'm doing some treatments. I had a bunch of
injections into my back and I want these coins. The injections went into the muscle tissue around
my like spine and back area as a start. I might don't god damn it. I might do I might do more of
them. But the TLDR of this whole thing is I'm probably going to start doing more seriously
therapy work like body work, physical therapy, strength training back there. We're going to
try to see if we can get that area to not be as fucked up as it is for some reason,
which people still don't know why. That's the most frustrating part.
People don't still don't know exactly why this is happening. I've heard you have costochondritis.
What the fuck does that mean? That means you have your chest and your back rib cage hurts.
Why? I don't know. So now what? Well you can get a shot. Is that what I do?
Well you know it might not even be costochondritis. It could be the dehydrated disc you have in your
spine. What do I do about that? Oh nothing. What do you mean you don't do anything? Well
we could do like some trigger point therapy and okay. You know it also could you could be the
hernia. You have a little hiatal hernia. What do I do about that? Well nothing. Just like eat
different. That's just a change your diet so you don't get like GERD like acid reflux. Okay.
So now what? I'm not going to pick this up yet. So nobody there's been a couple of theories. Oh
you might have like myofascial pain syndrome. Okay. What does that mean? Well it hurts. Why?
I don't know. What? I don't know yet. But it's not bad enough where it's good. Look I it's not gonna
I can walk fine. I can sit. I can. I'm sitting here right now right. But it just it's just kind
of a problem constantly. And it's something that always kind of has to sit in the back of my mind
no matter what. No matter what I'm doing. And those of you that are in this chat that might have
one of these medical problems that isn't enough to really
debilitate you that much. But it's enough to constantly be a problem and you don't really
have an answer for it. I I feel you here. I do because it sucks. Is this new? What is this?
There's a can there be as tinted ground? That's a tinted ground. What? That's that's like a ground.
That means like there's something in the ground. Right? Look at that. That that's the exact thing
that's on the tinted rocks. Can I get a shovel or something? So I just want to make sure everyone's
not overly concerned about it or that oh my god what's wrong? You all right? I'm I'm fine. I am.
It's just a constant like three or four out of ten in the pain scale all day every day and it
doesn't stop and it hasn't stopped in almost three years. So it's I have to start to go down
some kind of path to figure out why the fuck this is happening. And even when I've tried to it's
become difficult. Oh more luck. Perfect. Somebody that's had uh chronic pain their whole life is
constantly told we don't know lol by doctors I feel like pain on a literal level. Yeah that's
that's that that sucks. It really does because I was really thinking that this is like two three
years ago. I was like oh man my like my like chest hurts and my back hurts. Um it's it's probably
nothing. Whatever. When it's when it's stuck around for like two or three weeks I went to the doctor
and it was like ah I mean they'll do like a like a CT scan of my back and they'll be oh you have
like this and it's like okay whatever fix it. When you when you kind of figure out that that's not
happening it's like oh no we don't really know why. And even the things that I've told them
um for instance some of them may be things that may have happened to me uh over the last three
or four years medically speaking uh mechanically speaking how do you sit how do you do this what
do you I've always kind of been told that well that might not be why you're having it it could
be something else so oh do I take that I break danced on the internet better pills are just
better how is puberty better what is adult oh I took puberty three times oh man chronic pain my
yeah yeah it's having no answer for why this is happening makes you like second guess everything
you ever hear too and there's a lot of times that you sit there and you go is this like am I making
this shit up am I just making this up somehow and then you like get in your own head you like
freak yourself out you're like no why would I do that that's not just no like very clearly like
it hurts like if I if I know it's painful um you kind of like getting your own head but it did it
just it kind of came out of it slowly over about a week or two got to the point that it is now and
it's it's never really gotten any worse but it's never gotten better that's the weirdest part
is typically if you have some potential pain problems right they either get better or they
don't and make it worse it's like do is do I have a small hernia is the hernia just constantly
putting pressure on like my uh the middle chest bone area that's what they thought it maybe like
maybe my they call it a xiphoid process it was like maybe your xiphoid process it's this little
thing that's just in the center of your chest maybe that's what's happened what happened to it
I've done everything let's go go to a chiropractor I have I have gone to a chiropractor many times
and it doesn't seem to fix anything in the sternum yeah I have radiating pain that goes
from the middle of my back through the center of my chest all day every day it has not stopped in
three years and at this point it's kind of like it's time to manage it rather than well I have
to figure out what it is I'm in like the try to manage it stage I have as you guys know I have
been to so many doctors about this and it's time just to try to manage it just manage it medical
physical therapy trigger point injections uh maybe some uh maybe like an intercostal nerve
block which is another thing to potentially do where they actually go in and they fuck with
the nerve in your like intercostal chest and back region I don't know get a tony starkheart
oh the white heart the eternal heart I just started talking shit it's okay I don't even need it
crutch I need to spend my money somewhere I have a lot of money I'm so mad I mean there's also the
theory too and I have to be honest right I can't just pretend like I don't have a pretty
sedentary lifestyle I try to move around but the worst part about it is when I do move around
it hurts if I do any type of real like kind of physical exercise or physical anything involving
my core oh I feel like shit for a week it's like I what's going on there well that makes it even
harder it's like oh maybe I need to like really work that area out and like and strengthen it but
when I do that it's like holy shit I can't even move for like fucking four days you think it was
when somebody in chat cursed you oh yeah I thought about that too oh I thought about that too yeah
I don't know I'm thinking like holy shit did I piss off some type of like warlock that was
watching the stream and he heard me say that like Pikmin 2 sucked or something and he's like just
put a warlock curse on me he's sitting there like in a bubbling cauldron he's got my stream open he
was like a fan or something and he was an old fan he saw where I put in and out on the tier list
and he threw like fucking frog's legs and like batlings into a fucking cauldron and just cursed
the shit out of me I don't know it's possible anything is possible at this point dude okay I
have to tell you a real story this is like this story is so uh I'm gonna tell it because
whatever I don't even care it's like it's it's the story sucks because I really thought like I
don't know if my brain started going oh my god wait a minute is this real so on Christmas Eve
of last uh two years ago I think it was I I woke up and I woke up and my back didn't really hurt
that much I felt okay it was like I feel I feel like I don't feel horrible right now is just
is it gone and I looked at the clock and it was like 1201 Christmas day and I was like wait a
minute Jesus God did uh did it did it Christmas miracle no way and I was like I feel okay I feel
like a little better and I like really thought that like Jesus like fucking blessed me like 10
minutes and then I was like oh wait a minute and I got in the shower or something and I
ended up being like oh no no it hurts no it must have been the way that I like stood up or
something and it was I was so sad and I remember I'm not even kidding this is not a lie I remember
sitting there and going like hey if that was you like if you're like if you're that's a real thing
like you know I'll be at church every fucking Sunday I'll be at church every week and I swear
to God I swear to you Jesus 10 minute savior uh and then they came back and you know here we are
it was Jesus who cursed you no it wasn't second hand what's second hand it was a free trial Jesus
blessing oh shit so I that was like his free trial subscription and I had to go to church to get the
rest of it you're right oh Jesus pro a Jesus pro subscription god damn it that no stop saying
that god no stop saying god after that I'm sorry I'm sorry I didn't listen to me I gotta get that
out of my vocabulary I gotta stop saying that is this worth taking over the faded dome what's
better what's this even do extended stat effect time let's go look around or the shiny rock this
doesn't this make um I guess I could have shiny rock makes us so you find coins and rocks right
that's not what it is oh it makes the uh it makes the tinted rocks blink right okay
what does the second hand do I need more health because this build is actually really good
that's a lot of luck a ton of fire I need more damage and I need more hp I need like the meat
bone thing Christian streamer arc yeah I don't know you know how many times I've like sat there
and been like how do I what should I do should I do something about this should I like maybe maybe
I should go to church for a while and just see what happens right what's the worst that could
happen I go to church for a few months every Sunday and like go there and actually really
participate what if it goes away what if it went away right like imagine going to church
and like talking to the priest or whatever the priest like oh so I haven't seen you at this
church before well I've what what do you do I haven't seen is there a reason why I haven't
seen you how long you've been here for now like I'm just doing like a trial to see if like God
will cure my back and then I'm done oh um that's he probably thinks I throw holy water at me
like that's like demonic yeah I kind of just want like God to fix my back and then I'm just
gonna go back to what my normal life I serve alcohol here pheromones oh keep them come on
oh this thing sucks yes during communion wine yeah but I'm talking of whatever this thing
opens up locked chest right and second hand extended stat effect time I feel like that's
probably really good oh I'm getting a shitload of dubs right now that was 69 from depth it was
also 50 from somebody earlier and I was in the middle of talking about like microwaving something
right people giving a shit thank you guys seriously funny number it is a funny number
tear blasts and five bombs I need the bombs thank you thanks for the 69 sub look at all these fires
coming up more luck and more money to spend school bag has appeared in the basement didn't have that
already what's that I hate getting greeted in the shop rooms it's the it's the most annoying thing
in the world any tears wait what well these are now pennies whoa and they're I'm shooting so many
of these it's gonna proc all the time I think the tears now make them uh drop coins right I wish I
could spend them somewhere I'm gonna pray to the Egyptian god uh whatever to heal your rib cage
well but don't do that okay but hold on a minute but don't do that either though because they come
with like consequences I don't know I feel like oh I guess I'm gonna have to pray to like some
old god from the six million BC I don't know don't you feel like that person's gonna want like five
of my fingers or something yes mr. Albertson I will absolutely cure you but you're going to use
you're gonna lose five of your fingers no I think that's all I need to do yeah let's go
come on mom coins everywhere spam spam spam spam I need more damage I'm not doing enough
how are you gonna get through the womb with this kind of like shit damage I don't know you're not
gonna yeah this is shit damage with shit I don't even have the negative I need a save file if you
had to lose five fingers which ones would you choose um let's see middle finger middle finger
and ring finger on both sides no middle finger on both sides no just one whole hand probably
because that I you know I think I'd be I wanted to be one hand yeah because it otherwise it
would be it'd be difficult um because five is a lot that's a lot that guppies tail I have a
guppy something right I need one more guppy item I look I only have two hearts this is awful
like I'm not gonna pick up the robes it'll kill me how can I get to the room with such
shit damage out of context sounds awful I mean there's only one context so that would make any
sense and it's in this game damn it I'm gonna die I'm dead no I'm not I got like it's just it's
it's it's just shit damage is what it is oh these are new I don't know what these guys do
what are they doing what are they doing I don't know what this is what was that they spit out okay
just restart I have to get over there whoa that's what those do me hp I'll take it
nothing hate those things to the worst I'll move you be careful what you say on stream Jesus is
listening Santa he sees you when you're sleeping he knows when you're awake he knows you've been
bad or good so be good for goodness sake yeah like Jesus doesn't like see you when you're sleeping
and stuff like this Jesus doesn't know when you're asleep or not right Santa's like has more power
he's a Santa more powerful than like never mind he is that's blasphemy I'm not look I'm not I'm
gonna go look I okay well look I think look listen to some of the shit I've said on this stream
I've said some pretty blasphemous shit on here I thought Santa was Jesus
oh no what is that thing you leave cookies out and carrots food like Jesus no I hate
fighting greed I want stuff god I can't even whatever 99 coins cool what do you mean carrots
yeah people saying why people saying carrots in question mark you leave the carrots out for the
reindeer you guys kidding me come on I'm dead okay you I'm so you guys have to be so shocked
right now I'm so shocked that people have question marking me saying the carrots are for the reindeer
that I just I can't even pay attention to the game that was a shit build anyways
intensifying tears what's that mean it's sugar cubes no what are you making a latte for the
reindeer no you leave cookies and carrots cookies are for Santa the carrots are for the reindeer
yeah milk you yeah you leave milk it's a ton of bombs oh my god you leave milk a carrot or
one or two carrots and one cookie and when you wake up in the morning you see that there's a big
bite out of the fucking carrot and a big bite out of the cookie and the milk is half gone
imagine needing to like how horrible that would be to just take a one bite out of like 500 million
cookies that would suck at some point you just break them in half and like throw the other half
away after the third house Santa's not eating the cookies anymore he's just literally biting
them and spitting them in your trash go look if you're on the pacific time zone the next morning
go look in your trash and see if there's like a crumpled up like spit cookie in there I have to
beat the hush once come on I'm so sad I didn't get any new items there 500 million global population
well no I was just saying like in like how many people did Santa visit in a night a billion two
billion 600 million 500 how many like realistic houses would Santa go to because a lot of people
that a lot of people don't celebrate like Christmas night right do you it's not everybody
celebrates Christmas how many people are on earth how many people are in he stuffs his cookies in
his closet like a squirrel and he has food forever well then why would he take one bite out of them
no he's taking a bite and mushing it up and spitting it into your fucking like bathroom
trash because by the way Santa's taking a shit in one of your houses I don't you're gonna wake
up at some point you're gonna walk around and like your house is gonna stink like a huge dump
you're just waking up in the morning and go into the bathroom and the seat is down and just like
this like dehydrated yellow piss is sprayed it's just all over the toilet you're like who did that
he's I mean this guy's in a rush he's gonna just borscht into your bathroom pull his
fucking pants down and just piss oh oh shit what is that thing he's gotta go this is a new item
I think I'm gonna it's like a top hat what is that I'm gonna take it battery pack instant energy
that's all that was that was 15 coins so now I'm gonna rage buy this top hat there are multiple
Santas it doesn't matter how many Santas there are in the sky at any given time one of you guys on
earth is gonna wake up with a really really like just destroyed detonated bathroom and
one of those reindeers are gonna stick shit on your house you're gonna be a look at like google
google earth satellite images and just see whose houses have like huge reindeer dumps on them
I feel like that would be something you wouldn't want to clean up though you wouldn't want to
leave it there but that increased the value of your house if it was confirmed that you had like a
reindeer dump on your roof that means that like you I don't know like your house was like
blessed by one of the dead god damn I gotta pay attention all right pay attention dead tooth
toxic breath is this cool two keys what that that door is different all right I'm gonna I'm gonna
beat at least the game once here that's pretty that's pretty useful rusty key what does that
mean don't you know that you're toxic okay if you left money out on the table where Santa was going
oh I'm gonna go eat the carrots and are you supposed to tip Santa what if this whole time
we've always been supposed to be leaving like $20 bills there and he's like fucking hates us
would the money still be there like would he take it if you left like 20 on the table with the milk
I don't think he'd leave it just going for the poison damage here we buy all his shit anyways
I thought you said your audience was 18 to 24 years old blame the chat I'm not blaming anybody
I'm just I'm asking a few questions if you left a $50 bill on the table would Santa feel like he
should take it the devil Santa doesn't need tips he's got that juggles the great money
I mean damn it I thought the other one was gonna kill him I thought the other tick was gonna kill
him you also notice how every toy that's made in Santa's workshop and every piece of media is made
out of wood why do they still do that people get iPhones for Christmas not like wooden horse
why they're not making iPhones in those in those like pieces of media I'm not picking that up again
that's a robot chicken joke it probably is reddit joke when I was little my parents left out a joint
when in Santa woke up and there was a roach there what does four do I don't know
oh that's out of that's like touching that's like getting me what does it do what is it for a dice
room do rerolls all pedestals well I don't even have any pedestals I guess the boss oh shit I
could have just whatever it's a roach and I am seeing an envisioning in my head right now
just like the end of that roach it's tiny it's tiny it just looks like you squished it down
it's all black on the edge it's rancid looking I have to get that I need bombs so yeah Omega room
right these are the ones that explode I remember it gets you off guard a lot hey unionize your
workplace thanks for the 50 community subs thanks a lot see the 50 community subs I don't think I
can't get that key unless I have a bomb sorry guys it ain't happening wait no it ain't happening
in versus baby plum hurt him this guy actually sucks yeah I hate this guy his move set is very
difficult to uh patternize it out damage and range up nice all right that's good so far
he hates him this doesn't don't you feel like this floor should be way bigger I thought the
x out floors were huge and easiest boss in the game should be very simple so easy this is new
booster pack collect them all whoa cool I think that's new the empress diamonds
stars death oh dude grotto beasts and by the way for those of you that were not here earlier as
well we'll talk about this one more time a grotto beasts is real it's going to be a real collectible
trading card game that you will be able to buy physical not digital physical packs that you
will be able to purchase uh with a ton more characters a ton more stuff that's going to
be available some time at some point soon that's a real thing now grotto beasts will be a real
product for you to buy I'm gonna just use and all these are kind of is this the item the shop room
or is this the secret room stars I think the moon is secret room right yeah take the diamonds
where can we buy them I will give you more details as we progress here over the next month or two
you I think it'll take probably about give me a few weeks to get some more details
but it's happening soon not like next year like soon within the next probably six to 12 months
I would say give it like give me like a month before I can give you some real definitive
information but it's gonna happen soon is it gonna be us only I let let me just get that
preliminarily figured out there's a lot to figure out I am able to actually announce that it's
happening let me get the details I'll let you know in the coming few weeks entrepreneur 985
not really remember 12 months is a long time no I just meant six like I don't know it's not
gonna happen in a long time it'll be it'll be soon don't worry don't worry don't worry I want
them to trust me come on what's with that like tracking EU fans are gonna get fucked no I don't
know that I don't I don't think that's accurate don't say that yet I don't know if that's accurate
you don't know that's a thing yet how could you oh annoyed that I used that bomb five seconds ago
gotta be kidding me new tooth and nail you feel prickly feel prickly whoa is there did I make
that happen somehow I always start blinking one two can I move when it happens am I invincible
I wonder if I'm invincible when that happens because if that's invincible that's ridiculous
happens every five seconds and you're invincible holy shit that's crazy wait that means I can do
this wow well this is a cool new item I don't want to screw this up
it's gonna hurt me if I go near time for all the cards to get scalped and all the
prices are gonna go up 500 percent and how way how how do you know what we're gonna how we're
gonna do that whoo it's gonna get scalped get the poop thank you limit production to a very small
amount um no I've just I've got I'll have details for you at some point soon it's a full health
right yeah all right don't touch that don't I want everyone to spam for me not to forget that
please don't let me forget that sir whoo shit bombs again thank god now I have I wait keys
I can open up this that's new whatever it is I don't know is that like a deca dream catcher
what is that all right I need to make some money two of diamonds yeah I don't want to use it right
now though if I can make a little bit more money before I buy anything you want to make as much
money as I possibly can or I um use it don't let me forget about that let me just test to make sure
this works uh don't let me forget doesn't he do some hold on I'm so paranoid I've been blowing
up in my face all right so we got box of stuff bomb oh god that's so much okay bomb
the eight power diamonds hearts judgment judgment oh man okay wait wait wait wait I think I can do
this all uh this is I think this is shot speed right yeah so let's do diamonds not yet no what's
in here I hate that item people are gonna tell me to get it but I fucking hate that thing I don't
want it all right so I'm gonna go I'm not done yet I'm gonna go explore the rest of the room so
I have to remember all this stuff in order fight hard I know I know I know I get it I'll get it
I'm looking to get as much money as I can because I want to give that guy a bunch of money I want
to buy the thing I got a lot to do I want this whatever it is obsessed fan follows your every
move okay that's me oh you know you're fine mom oh no more money all right now it's time to do
this in the right order is this broken syringe mystery medicine it's broken syringe better than
cancer probably not it just gives you probably a random syringe uh item randomly all right let's
go that let's double the money I'm gonna buy whatever this is sweet dreams no idea and then
we're gonna give these coins to the uh to the guy down here tells you what the boss and what does
it do during the dream in between floors you will see something whoa it's funny enthusiasm whoa
come on come on oh no it's just enough to kill you I'll take it hey it was worth it
all right do not skip the cutscene all right um and it's the fallen that's all right that's kind
of cool small ears up hell yeah and infested twice super pride these guys are always so easy
oh I don't I don't know what happened I like these explosive fire tears but they really do
suck sometimes they really are because they just blow up in your face like that
wag wire cool bombs I'll take them so I have a question for those of you that know this is
effectively this is anti-birth right I've played anti-birth a little bit how much is this how close
is this to being just anti-birth on me bombs homing bombs or did they change a significant
amount of stuff and by the way does this work in here if I go like this did I miss the timing
it's like anti-birth twice okay goodness paranoid for the explosions way more with the new endings
okay unlock these for free don't touch that I don't think I can take that off 25 coins all right I
can't that's a tick right I can't put I can't I can't pick that off because I burn it with a
matchstick the emperor I don't want to use this right now come on do I just guess and who cares
charged baby what's with all these what's with my seeds why do I have so much of this
I have so many battery items I need an active now wow itchy tasty okay no I don't want that
gooey gooey what's that gooey gooey nothing uh let's just kill him the ball and I told you
with the ball and you guys said it wasn't use me okay I thought he was dead I thought that was his
death animation missing page two evil up your enemies will pay that's different that's new in
this so missing page two what's that do it's a bad item restart enemies will pay no it's not new
and I'm sorry but the red socks suck whatever they just got smashed with two home runs back
to back by the orioles I know you're from Boston but come on dude sorry yeah well I'll try I'll
try harder next time in the next game you let us down oh I'm sorry yeah it's like a voodoo doll
if you're from Boston and it's like somebody a Boston pitcher lets up a grand slam we all
feel pain in our necks oh what oh what happened loser yeah when Tom Brady got traded to Tampa Bay
where we left to go to Tampa Bay I'm fairly certain collectively everybody in Massachusetts
woke up with like a stomach pain it was like oh I feel awful today
I feel like I'm gonna puke what happened did I eat something like collectively every single
person in Massachusetts like all called out of work at the same time oh with the pill yeah
oh speed up and tears up what else do I need here I know I go slow I'm sorry
I'm sorry collectively everybody is affected yeah when the red sox won the world series in like 2004
everybody in Boston had like a collective overheal for a week oh what's that I don't know if that was
I love how much I can yeah I love I love how much I can settle down dude what's what we're doing
how is that so sing songy I love how much I can holy shit that guy's a lot of help that's the
challenge heart that makes the game really hard but makes you do more it doesn't do anything if
you beat the game with the challenge hard on doesn't do something oh I'm loving these new
items I love these new items in this Isaac game sounds irritated do I I was earlier two hours ago
when the computer started to freak out for no reason I was like yeah I was pissed holy shit
they move fast I'm still low on hearts did they nerf the amount of hearts you get in repentance
I feel like they did I've not gotten very many any HP up items they did they did oh they did
they nerfed it's they nerfed hard mode hard so now is as hard hard hard oh I was wondering I
felt like I haven't gotten any like HP up items damn okay they make they wanted to make it hard
so is it yeah am I am I like a normie if I play the game on normal or did they make hard really
hard and make normal harder still normie well we're completely valid if you play on normal
I'm just gonna blow this guy up hold on wait no could I have oh wait could I have done that
without with the I think I could have done that by doing like this and walking into him shit maybe
not it's a stupid blow up tears I hate this shit exploding tears I have so much tears up I'm so
paranoid I'm gonna hurt myself but I don't shoot is this shielded tears these are all okay
now that's good you're fucked now wait no I am you're right because now they're gonna blow up on
projectiles that was a horrible thing to pick up oops run ruined not yet it's still doable
I any tinted rocks no activate fortnight mode I could just say I bet you guys haven't seen me in
a while of course I know the song yeah I sing it all the time all the fucking time it just it
just appears every day it never goes away every day I don't know why it's better than the original
song I you know I never really I don't listen to that much music anymore that original song
that it's sort of a remix of I listened to that recently I was like oh I really liked it the
fortnight song I'm maybe I like the original song it's not even close to the same thing it's a
completely different and it's way better the victory royale song is way better than the original
whoever who owns the rights to that song I would just make that the song I'd be like holy shit you
just took what I did in it holy oh my goodness it's incredible I think this is where I die double
trouble I'm gonna lose to that swipe down tomato town my friend just got downed I revived him
we're going southbound none of the park we're going south street none of the park we're going
park street I don't I have bombs I could do it I could look only oh first try and it's matches
who cares we got up that's the best part of the whole song it's we gotta um we gotta number one
that's another good part you guys think fortnight's gonna last as long as minecraft
what do you think that it's just the thing right now I did not think fortnight was gonna stick
around I thought it was gonna be a thing that people thought was cool for a little bit but
I did not expect it to be like this really I'm not gonna blow that one up out of principle
point is gonna last forever I don't know what can it be compared to when did fortnight come out
fortnight came out and it was like plants versus zombies base building survival game it took a few
years for it to be the thing that is now 2017 2016 I wonder how much time it has left summer 2017
like tf2 started as mvm and then they added player versus player it kind of I wonder how many stock
options they gave the guy that said let's put battle royale in this I did that guy get enough
stock options to like the rest of his life to like be taken care of juicy sack sticky babies
absolutely not I got a gift card but to where where where did you get the gift card to you know
that I I gauge how much I like appreciate a gift card or not this is this is my my kind of gift
card tier list as you will so if you go into like walmart and grab like an applebee's gift card
I didn't that's in favor you just grab the first one I gauge how much I appreciate a gift card
whether or not I've been to the restaurant in five years or been to the place the like store in five
years I got I got a chili's gift card oh I haven't eaten here in probably it's seven and a half years
that was the first one on the rack that you saw at walmart at least make it at least make it a
fucking fortnight card hilly's is perfect I haven't eaten there in a long time is it good
they still do the like you can get well come with a friend and get two entrees and you get a second
entree for like five bucks or something did not do that anymore they used to do that right it was
if you were two people you could get two entrees and the second entree was like 10 bucks or
something or like eight bucks it was two for 20 yeah it was if you have two people were in the
restaurant together they could get two entrees that was applebee's right but I mean I'm sorry
applebee's fridays and chile's are the same place in my head the decor inside the menu the atmosphere
I cannot I couldn't tell you what was on what menu remember applebee's had the riblets which I loved
with these weird like square rib things and they had a little tiny not very much meat on them at
all you had to scrape your teeth on the edges to like pull off a little bit of meat they're
called riblets I don't know what the hell they were but I loved them I didn't even know what
those actually were they were rats I have no idea I've never seen this before a little like
square ribs it wasn't like beef rib what was it what what actually wasn't though
okay stop you're hurting him I'm all right what were the riblets from applebee's
it's the same thing as a McRib no no no there was a bony it was a cartilagy
30% of the animal doesn't exist anymore I think I think they just cut ribs in half it was these
weird they were squares they were squares connected squares riblets google it in incognito mode
come on give me something kidding me come on come on oh no I want hearts so I can keep doing
this riblets are from spare ribs come on hurry up all right that's enough that's enough one more
that's enough I got what I wanted start the bomb oh that's the the poop poop
it's not enough I don't have enough range to make this work yeah oh shit Jared multiplies
everything in the room oh well damn it I could get to um give me this back I don't want the
poop poop it's not gonna be good Jarrah okay I don't want any of that stuff button ribs aka
applebee's riblets these are technically not ribs they're a thin flat strip of meat and round bone
perhaps a fourth inch thick about six inches long and one and a half inches wide cut from the sides
of boomer's spines from the behind the rearmost rib you may you've made up the last part but um
I think that's actually accurate which is not not really shit I don't like this
ah die from the poison how much damage do I have not enough abundance there's so much charging do
they okay did they buff batteries because I see them all the time now they had to have right
right am I just getting a weird rng or something there's smaller batteries that give less charge
didn't they across the board buff active items in the first place I feel like that's something
they did they did that active items are now good a lot of them weren't very good at all here's guppy
eternal life I made it I got really unnecessarily angry at that oh you're supposed to be the
easiest boss in the game make me look bad um what is this trash can thing
okay dog everybody look back compost gain more friends what I just do does it give me more
spiders whoa man this is a lot spider andy okay uh I'm gonna go down kill watch the explosions
oh come on I didn't see it on the screen no rusty I'm so rusty at Isaac I'm so much better at the
game uh that's eve I don't want it rusty crusty andy they did they did make hard mode harder to
be fair it does feel like it that's cool though it did get to a point where people playing
and just destroying every single time is this a new expansion Isaac is hard did they make it
like difficult isn't how are people reacting to it people saying I got too hard I don't want to play
it hard mode was no harder than normal mode well I mean with all the champions they added a bunch
of champions and lest um it was yeah like add these like purple and like green and blue enemies
right like champions weren't a thing that much in normal were they thought I can remember
champions yeah like the the monsters the monsters that are normal monsters but they're bigger and
green champion monsters elites or whatever you want to call them I don't know whatever those
keys oh that's what compost does okay right right okay makes sense does that gonna hurt if I touch
it gears up and yep okay and one of these champions are brighter now are they oh lord
oh all right get rid of this guy on the top left who cares about you I guess I get if I get a room
that's full of stuff I could jara and then compost and probably get a shit load of stuff
come on really mr fred he'll break off it doesn't matter stay stay stay further
you got up that looks to be new what's this super glue eye drops that seems really fast
that was a fucking disgusting boss why the tear cap got raised too did it really because I've
I've always I've always wanted that to be a thing why put a tear cap that always felt this is
infinite isn't it what we gotta just be happy that I was not streaming when that was a huge
thing that everybody was talking about for like of the for the week it came out my streams would
have been unbearable it would have been horrible did I'm not gonna cover victory royale I don't
even know what the song is called it's called chug jug with you what is jug chug jug is jug
something like a fortnight thing jug chug jug jug is I don't know what jug is
chug jug is an item oh okay all right here we go guys it's gonna be intense can I beat this can
I beat mom it lives I wonder give me your best luck here shielded tears doing good oh not enough
damage to do it in one revolution oh you unlock blast baby dude all right so where should I go
I don't think that no that's not new that's the thing that just flies around and if you
shoot through it right I don't want that you got the Polaroids that go up yeah I don't want
this thing tomato town you got it victory royale yeah you're about to get down 10 kills on the
board right now just wiped out tomato time like the face shakes and the eyes look up
what is oh god is there more of those hey look at this what no are you kidding me I ran right out
of there oh yeah ah oh it's because the spikes on the ground I didn't even see the spikes
oh crap what was that spawn you're so bad whatever how many victory royales have you gotten
in the last month probably not very what's this bag is this a sin heart bag
I don't really think I want this keep going I got more hearts
holy shit whoa that was cool that enemy's cool I like that new enemy eyeball did rocks I'm gonna
say down I hate these little guys weird like leech eyeball things it's so annoying super magnet it
pulls now I don't want that I want the speed like doy doy doy maybe I'll give you a doy doy doy in
like a few minutes maybe it'd be good though range is pretty bad too bad range
I'll give it to you I will but you have to be good do a chug jug chug jug doy doy have you seen
that guy before this guy's deal I don't know like a cross on his head then you want doy doy chug jug
okay
it's the best I could do all right Isaac time to die and then we go to the chest from here
whatever I have unlocked I don't know well they changed that oh did they make it so you can't
just stand in the corner and not get hit at Isaac anymore oh okay it's still there updated
animations and sounds though it looks way cooler do I have to end it here or can I keep going
if I've beaten the game on this save file like 40 times that means I probably have the chest right
I think so all right yeah oh what's this sci-fly and buoyant protector friendly ball
and I don't want that Ouija board spectral tears and Mr. Mega Jara Jara Jara Jara
rune you bastard everyone doesn't do anything oh no get away look at all this poison the poison
lasts so much longer on the ground it took hit like 10 hits I took so many hits the poison was
lasting so long that's new it doesn't usually last that long what you could have had eight items so
with Jara counts for chest I thought it was only consumable is any physical item in the game is
that new I thought Jara was just like consumable it's consumables and chests
what I thought it was just like coins bombs cards oh shit as long as the chest is closed
oh all right I didn't know that hate not knowing how much health I have that sucks
how many of you are in this room come on I already
oh what was that what was that it was like a drink it or something I don't know it's gone
whatever it is do more shoe something like that right got it never seen this guy before this new
enemy oh Aaron Aaron Aaron Aaron run away Aaron the fact that half of you guys have no idea what
that is it makes it even funnier for me is Aaron I'm not even gonna talk about it just whatever
fucking let me play the game I spent $15 on by the way I spent $15 on this hey did you miss me
hey did you miss me didn't even take one damage that for like five minutes oh don't
watch out these bugs these bugs are dangerous I've been waiting for you to say this please just say it
why have I ever made like a reference to that oh shit this is bad this is very bad
I'm gonna go one of you's gotta go please one of you's got to keep you waiting huh
that was for that one person I don't care it was really bad that was really bad but I did it for
that one person that I mean they probably hated it too whatever it was just for that one person
and they wanted me to do like a sonic uh snake that's sonic the hedgehog
kill him before he runs at you they both in the same smash brothers universe
fuck oh oh I think this is the end oh omega large hp up okay I need to collect as many hearts as I
can here what's the boss even here is a blue baby I honestly don't even know and I might as
well look for the secret rooms okay oh whatever I'm just gonna go for it if I lose I lose that's
all I've been it's I'm kind of rusty I haven't played Isaac in a while and they made hard mode
harder so it's like the game is actually way harder for me because I haven't played in a while
and I'm used to it being a little easier so that's Mike's yeah it was burped pain versus
blue baby shielded tears are very good remember didn't didn't I try to play beat the hush on
screen one time I beat the hush like twice or three times ever did it once on screen it's you
don't you have to have a stupid build to even try and if you don't have a build that's absolutely
just dumb you just just quit right that's what I remember I did it yay yay yay yay yabby j yay
I've done it again I did that like a month ago are you sitting in your own poop right now
um why don't we check I'm gonna I'm gonna get up and sit down really quickly and we'll see
I'm gonna sit up I'm standing and sitting down I don't think so let's try it again
oh I don't feel it doesn't feel weird all right cool let's go again uh I have to beat I must have
the voice too bad uh let's do Lazarus let me try to get to mom's heart in 30 minutes I mean no
no fucking around let's go you want to see how you play Lazarus I'll show you that's how you play
Lazarus my my ostosis forget me not I don't know what that does I thought that was a legitimate
mistake for a second no you you die as Lazarus you come back you get the stat increases you
use the pill and if the pill is bad you restart the game it's the Lazarus strat who knew this
would be a diaper stream every stream is a diaper stream what are you guys saying even the carnival
yeah oh let me show you the uh Samson strat my favorite character in the game is Samson
I find it to be the most fun bad strat what do you even know have you ever played Binding
of Isaac I bet I bet you you haven't the Dio I think this just rerolls it uh consumables
not a great start not a great start too worse that guy's huge repentance guy's huge come on
worry I mean you seem this guy seems off I mean like in general you mean today I don't know I
think I feel okay right now I'm on I think I think I'm on what would you consider off
on CBD no not right now you're not knocked that away he doesn't want to play this game
I really I really do actually I've been looking forward to this update for since it was announced
like two years ago or something the image and range up I like it oh no it's only one eye though
I had this item sucks after all that Santa talk you probably you have to be high on something
I don't think so I don't have the curse again oh nice five cents wait what if I
I could roll what I just do hey what does this even do I thought it rerolled consumables it
rerolls enemies uh okay and yeah you don't want to do that until the last floors if you do it here
you could get end game enemies and die instantly I saw it don't worry I'll go get it later in the
game Peter it's funny that's that's just a I can just say that and you guys will say end game Peter
like somebody will even if it's only one of you I really like that I want it disappointing I don't
like getting little Gish it's always a disappointment when you see his face tell me I'm wrong tell me I'm
wrong when you see that little Gish you don't go and want to restart I'm just telling you
all right let's see what we got good for Samson all right that's enough I think I'm at max
little Gish saved my run before um I'd rather have passive stats I'm a passive stat kind of
guy in Isaac I don't really like the familiars that can be cool but I like having interesting
passive stat combinations I don't really like the active items I don't really like the
friends like the passive items and that's it don't make me don't let me forget the red heart
imagine if you can reroll bosses I hiccuped after that that was not like a fake laugh or anything
what is this consolation prize plus one to the lowest stat no it's kind of terrible it's really
bad um I have money I don't want that what's this um purple saddle thing do get them both I can't
everyone doubles card effects oh wow that's actually really good I don't think I can get
both though arrow cloth temperance nice I need that how do I get that what do you mean wasted
there could have been coins in there and make me allowed to buy the card thing all right I
could pick this up and they could be two pennies in it how much health do I have all right I get it
double card effects incoming judgment times two is the little guy right judgments the coin bum
well I get two judgments that's a pretty cool build anything else I can get the eternal heart
where was that over here d d 10 some of the two judgments versus satan that do anything
you're so broke now with no bombs or keys I don't think that matters though if I can get good cards
if I can get like the hierophant once or I can it's been awesome look at this already I'm good
do a satan voice no you do it satan face yeah I hate when games do satan faces scary
all right somebody hit me I want more damage well I'll tell you what Goku got you say it right
oh my god don't die I had stop no that was so cool too I can't like play a video game and talk
like I have to pause the movie you know what I mean once I start being like oh
the movie has to pause like if you want to do if you want to do like a Jim Carrey impression while
we're watching ace ventura I gotta pause the movie god damn it that was a cool build too
pause Shrek stop getting hit no I'm doing it on purpose oh shit he's doing it on purpose
he's doing this on purpose finally we figured it out we got him he admitted it
don't ever pause Shrek hey you know they're like what was the last time you heard it Shrek is like
on the way out isn't he it hasn't been like a movie in a while like he's Shrek's kind of on the way
out he's losing I think popularity I'm not sure he's in with the kids now good key how fucking dare
you I know I love Shrek I love Shrek I'm just saying I think he might think he's I don't think
he's as popular as everybody thinks he is now he's lost a lot to fortnight I'm sorry
reusable knockback he has though if I'm honest he deserved it but you don't you don't like Shrek
what's your problem with Shrek I can't knock that up well let's go Samson versus the hunt
all right no more fucking around okay good good good good go go go go go dog food HP up move
wasn't their whole thing with people thought Peter Griffin was gonna be in fortnight it was a huge
deal what ever happened with that yeah people on Twitter it was like trending on Twitter that Peter
Griffin was gonna be in fortnight I'm not making this up I swear to god are we on the same planet
here that was a huge thing people were talking about I feel like with family guy I feel like
is the tide moving on family guy like especially Peter Griffin I think we brought this up briefly
before but everybody family guy came out everybody thought it was really funny it got cancelled people
begged to have it brought back they brought it back it was around for way too long it became like
really sort of trying too hard and unfunny like and then everybody knew that started talking shit
about family guy and then all of a sudden like the last few years Peter Griffin is now like funny
not Peter Griffin and family guy Peter Griffin just the guy is funny not Peter Griffin family
guy Peter Griffin did it flip is it that's ironic okay like the people that think Peter
Griffin is funny right now they're they don't watch family guy they just think that Peter
Griffin going like holy crap Lois I gotta get out of here and it's like a meme right
why did I take that I don't know this is cool holy crap Lois it's funny because he's not funny oh
okay I get it I know I genuinely think that Peter Griffin is funny but family guy is bad okay well
that's some more data we have now I wonder how many of you there are I only laugh at family guy not
with family guy I think this is a good combo with the orbiting tears well if I just would stop
speaking I would rather have Peter Griffin and Smash Brothers I'm not picking that thing up I'm
getting this oh what a stupid car to get hurt for who's fallen further from grace family guy
Simpsons or South Park um I don't know I don't think it's South Park it's probably the Simpsons
yeah it probably is the Simpsons I'm in trouble now did I check this wall I'm in trouble all right
I have to pay attention I'm no talking about Simpsons and shit here we go box of stuff again
yeah I don't um I don't know if the Simpsons is particularly like a worse show than the other two
but it feels like is it weird for me to say that like canceling the Simpsons
it's just like you can't it has to be on tv if the Simpsons is off of television and old
gods are gonna rise up from the fucking earth's crust and kill us all it has to be part of that
has to be why it hasn't been 30 something years I'm gonna keep the poop it must always be a
Simpsons it must always be a lich king and honestly I can't I can't even speak very much
to what I'm even saying oh the Simpsons isn't good anymore I feel like all of us say that but
when was the last time you watched an episode of the Simpsons I think all of us just assume the
Simpsons is bad and none of us have watched the show does any no but I don't think anyone watches
the show they just air I don't think people actually watch the show it just airs and everyone
just goes I don't think the Simpsons is good anymore I don't who's catching brand new episodes
of the Simpsons when they go on Fox oh it's on Fox the Simpsons it's not on Netflix or anything
it's on fucking old-ass like cable tv and how many people have that still not on like Hulu is it
is it on Hulu are new episodes airing on Hulu though they might have seasons but are new episodes
airing somewhere like on a week-to-week basis it's on Disney plus why on Disney plus but it's it's
a week-to-week basis the newest episode is about Homer learning the floss okay yeah but like they
can't I get what people say here where it's like oh my god it's about Homer and like doing the floss
and fortnight they can't just have every episode about him working at like a nuclear power plant
and like him reading newspapers and shit and strangling Bart yeah they have to be they have
to have some type of yeah they're gonna do something it can't just be the same thing every
time why not because it's been on for 30 years this was a horrible idea by the way to take this
you guys are right which is why they should just take it off they have to end it soon well they've
already broken the seven-year rule it's been broken any show that is on the air for longer than
seven seasons is not good anymore as as of the eighth season every time it is the ultimate
Seinfeld rule when a show goes past seven years it's not as good anymore now there are some
exceptions there are there are some exceptions but in a 95 percent of the time scenario more than
seven plus years of a tv show it starts to get a little tiring and what always sunny yeah but I
said there are exceptions that's like a god show how many years have I been on yep okay this is
season 10 of German 985 well no no no no no that's not fair I would say this is season like six
really season five maybe because when I was on YouTube I did my first like two years a year or
two on YouTube I was like experimenting with stuff trying to like see what I wanted to do
like the real German 985 the streamer guy the youtuber guy was like 2012 2013 I was making
pilots for a year and a half to come this is a year like six next year we'll see if you guys
still think this show's any good the seasons are arcs this is the current like this is currently
arc number four yeah I mean that sounds kind of accurate I feel the same way about a lot of movie
franchises too and here hear me out here once a show or a movie gets to be a point where it's
like more than 10 on 20 plus years going all the actors feel like they are doing parodies and
impressions of themselves it's not the character it's like the actor doing the impression of the
character perfect example is like when Johnny Depp was in the last part of the Caribbean movie
I saw it and it was like this is not Captain Jack Sparrow this is Johnny Depp in a costume
doing Captain Jack Sparrow once you cross a certain amount of time and a certain amount of I guess
age for actors and stuff it's just like it's almost it becomes like a parody of itself
and I can't suspend my disbelief anymore Johnny Depp in a costume
fucking Jack Sparrow wait was that what I said what did I say what did I say is that that's not
what I said right is how I worded it how did I say it it was the phrasing I don't think I said it
like that though how this is why you can tell I don't look at the screen there's your proof that
I sometimes just don't even look at the screen I'm looking at you this is the worst item in the game
did they buff it did they buff the worst active item in the game they did really is it better
now holy shit that's now the best item in the game are you kidding me that thing was so awful
before this game oh yep thank you hey man I can't get this stuff I don't want the robes you know I
have one heart you don't you have too much confidence in my ability you didn't take the
robes you know I don't want it robes give black hearts yeah and they never come back
and I'm gonna lose them you know me you've watched me play games before I'm not gonna
have three black hearts forever they're gonna go away any tears up I would solve every one of
my problems right here how the run spin uh the last one was all right the save file it does not
have I haven't beaten the hush three times on this save file so probably not gonna do that so I'm
probably gonna get a new save file I'm probably gonna talk like this I guess for some reason
what is putting out the fires do the fires sometimes a coin will be in them
sometimes a couple hits not from the big guy because it's a full heart does it are not Isaac
pros like me probably didn't know that if a champion hits you it is one full heart not half
a heart it's just it's absolute dog shit game design dog it's awful fucking video game design
is it I'm just kidding pretty good it's actually pretty good design if you think about being so
angry at the game face cam no I don't close on I never do I don't think I'm gonna kill these guys
I please die it's the equivalent of hitting a foul ball every pitch can something happen please
nice please restart no it's not over yet if I get tears up and damage up I can just be a spam
mobile and I should be fine oh hmm I want the damage from Samson all right no more
now dollar oh no why would a dollar be in here portable blood
okay give me something come on you can do better than that I know you can
no come on come on one more add the two diamonds the whole time continuum transcendent tears
wait don't these go through walls oh boy if I get range and tears up this it actually be really
good I just need a bunch of rent and I need uh the Ouija board I need spectral tears
and tears up and then range this would be awesome let me go back up here
oh mr me has appeared in the basement
being the simpsons that's the first boss from the simpsons game the guy with the underwear
that just popped in again simpsons arcade game to beat him up when you go go go go go go go go go
any pants go down he goes oh I already did show it a long time ago punch HP up oh two of diamonds
use it blood blood bag no let's kill this guy that was horrible order I know it was but look
I'm not in this to be the best I'm in this to be the greatest different all right forgot I had to
talk so um that's favorite uh kind of latte mine is a oat milk a little bit of mocha and what's
yours I don't know mom's key better chest loot and plus two keys it was worth it I donated like
soy milk I didn't say soy milk I said oat milk I said oat milk oat o a t not s o y
oat open your ears open up your ears for once oat god I think honest to god oat rude yeah whatever
welcome to the next arc we're in season five now rude mean germa oh no nobody thought it
nobody wanted to get like he didn't nobody thought this was gonna happen rude mean angry
pissed off rude germa no fuck how do we that actually might be one of the better
space bar items no booster pack diamonds oh my god diamonds again two clubs two of clubs
lovers it's hearts hang man I'll take this one what did I miss anything else can I spend any more
money anywhere I didn't see the call I'll go back to the shop rattle beast booster packs I'll donate
now it's 500 give you anything broke it all right let's go okay I like the part of the stream where
germa says okay it's really funny my favorite part I always wait for it mine too they sus oh no he's
a one-trick pony he says like weird sounds really good yeah that's wait this double the stuff in
chests now I'll take the damage I got plenty of hearts no more I take the hearts now no
I was looking at chat again wait wait emergency we need an emergency doi doi doi chat is getting
bored emergency doi doi doi did you hear that I'm just like this makes this even shittier
this just kind of gives me a headache this is definitely season eight
yeah oh we're in season eight territory boys and girls hey but hold on a minute
we had a really bad season in the middle of the show and then the show got better
later I will be at a net zero here for these bombs that was not smart I'm gonna no I don't
want bad trip there we go finally more nice starting to come together more more more
time to spend some money I don't know what that is but I'm gonna get it mama mega
what's mama mega do I don't really want to get rid of the um heaven beam use it I don't want
to use it right now um is that the boss and I'll pick up the other thing on the next floor
dick relax oh no is that epic hacker is that chemical peel if it's epic hack this whole
thing's over okay I'm gonna peel this damage up for one eye right okay watch out troll bomb
open where's the boss and we're down here ice room bounce over here come on get killed by the
spikes it was another game sound effect that I was thinking of the other day I was trying to
imitate it but maybe I got it wrong you guys remember the game yeah Joe and Mac when you
fight the dinosaurs we could side scrolling beat him up with two players what they were the cavemen
and when you hit the caveman with club you had a melee weapon for a club it would make the sound
and it was like what what what what what what what what what did I get it right what does five do
rerolls the whole floor I don't think I want that wait if I got all the items wouldn't that
be just free stuff yeah I'm gonna kill the boss and yeah let's get free stuff let's go
yeah I'm not gonna pick it up until I'm gonna use the bomb on this boss I'm assuming it's just a
gigantic explosion rock where what do you see a tinted rock wait save the bomb for hush I don't
think I'm gonna get to hush at this point do it on a fresh floor but then I lose my don't use bomb
you idiot I don't even know what it does but what this wouldn't kill hush it doesn't do that much
damage just use it on a new floor but then I lose my um feather just use it now it opens up hush
it does damage to every enemy in every room on the floor please German tinted rock outside
the shop fish moly okay well wait so are we ditching the feather and I'm gonna use this
after mom's foot to make sure I can get to hush and die to him and lose because this build is
absolutely not a hush killer it is not a hush killer at all it is not where where's this
tinted rock outside the shop it's hard to see it's hard to see shut up shut up it's hard to see shut
up it's toxic season seven of turbo 985 fuck up you fucking idiot what do you even know
you thought he was a nice guy no no no not anymore the dumbest fucking thing I've ever
ever heard anybody say this stupid fucking asshole join us for our ever 12 episode series
season five fucking moron ban that guy and fucking don't ban his ip fucking stupid piece of shit
what is this one toxic arc should I go get the whatever monstro too I got a bingo who's playing
bingo oh no it's crampus me the coal coal is gonna be awesome all you all you non-believers
oh that's so unfortunate that actually sucks coal would be so good with this that sucks
oh well uh so I'm just not gonna take the feather I'm gonna use the bomb
whatever I'll try it who cares no I'm not I'm gonna re-roll the floor get the feather re-roll
that was a great item jerma they buffed it so I have three really good actives then I feel like
the bomb is just a gimmick I don't want it I don't care what it does I don't care if it's
gonna show me hush I don't even want it it's a gimmick give me the feather or no it's quick
it's crampus's head even better than it was before it's gimmick I don't want it okay I'm
gonna keep the feather oh cool whoa free money the atm exploded whoa just go in every single room
well let's open up the secret rooms it does cool all right 50 off and lazy worm this is better
just give me tears up and this is saved ow it's time for you to rest it's time to rest flat file
no more spikes no I don't care that's kind of cool but I want this slow super secret room
oh diamonds oh what's what's a double of 90 oh okay thanks horrible super secret room five
every same one okay we've done all those why am I exploding every single room because uh there
could be items in a bunch of these rocks and secret walls and secret rooms and I'm able to
do this and walk around like this and move like this I don't need to do every single one of them
but you know enough of them no that was annoying the germa show used to be so good yeah now he's
just like out there it's like season eight season nine it was like funny for a while
but just like I don't know I just like feel like he's doing kind of a parody of himself
he's doing like the goku voice like I remember when he did that it was funny but now he's like
doing it all the time and it's like he's using it as a way to kind of crutch or something to
comedic purposes I don't know what's he doing get off me the hermit thank you
oh everything is free don't take that right no that thing that thing sucks I remember that
thing is horrible doesn't that if you take damage you teleport out of the room right that's not what
this one is it recharges an item on hit okay I was okay all right all right I thought this was the
thing that when you take damage you teleport out that's the worst item probably in the whole game
the cursed eye oh what is this dead eye accuracy brings power that's not gonna happen
this is the most inaccurate you can probably be although it lasts
I don't know I think it's working it looks really cool though I don't want the monkey paw get in
there I need tears up so bad this looks awesome what a cool looking build what happened to that
why did that hit me it's weird I forget to use the active right right right yeah I'm holding
on to it because I'm scared I'm not gonna have it for the boss you gotta be concentrated or
otherwise it's not very good I'm gonna burp hopefully not directly into your face
how many hours do you have in the game well in total probably five or six hundred
but there's a big but here it's like five or six hundred hours the problem is oh this is actually
kind of uh the problem is it's like five or six hundred hours over the course of almost 10 years
I play the game for a few months and then I stop playing for a year and then so then I forget every
single thing that's in the game and I start over again I've done that for the last probably seven
straight years I have restarted save files across different consoles I have a file on my switch
right now I've played a ton of Isaac on switch I have almost all the unlockables but this is
not for switch yet I would have played it on the switch and been ready to go but I'm seeing a lot
of stuff I didn't see in the other one that I played yeah I played usually uh but yeah this
is a big but how are you so bad at the game um I don't know I mean like I just told you I don't I
pick up the game and I play it for like a week or two and then I don't play it for like a year or
two and then I start over again it's I'm like I'm fresh starting the game again for the first time
it's all muscle memory and repetition guys yeah if I had played Isaac for like a year straight I'm
sure I'd be phenomenal why did I go in here I really don't like that room all right watch the
health here um no all jokes aside what's the best thing you've ever seen me do in a video game
no messing around no like oh yeah when you uh Jevil first try what what opportunity have you
ever seen where I did something that was unbelievable what was it how many of those have I had
it was probably Jevil it honestly unironically was Jevil what the fuck laying through Simpsons
hit and run I don't think so okay let's keep moving this way it was beating Jump King uh
I feel like that was not that game was a horrible pain in the ass right but I don't know if that
sits up there with oh my god that was the best thing ever a lot of people beat Jump King not a
lot of people be Jevil first try I know you did but a bunch of other people didn't oh friend zone
friendly fly another orbit that's okay um oh that's the Ouija board isn't it that's the it's
the Ouija board that's it I got spectral tears they're gonna go through everything wait spectral
does not go through that's piercing I got that wrong oh that's right they don't phase through
they it's not piercing shit I thought it was I already had spectral god damn it I thought that
spectral tears meant that they passed phase through it's piercing like the color is still good
but it's uh let's go oh no it's Guppy's head this counts that I picked it up right I just have to
pick it up from my understanding Guppy yes the guy called this guy the Guppy Cruncha it's better
I don't think it's not I like the concentrated damage
reap creep oh my god somebody said are you gonna watch the Irishmen on stream why would I watch
the Irishmen on stream no no no no just have them hit over and over you're good you're gonna play
path of exile no I can't play path of exile I have one problem with it it's a major problem I can't
overlook the can't the game could be a 10 out of 10 game and it could be my favorite video game
ever made gameplay wise I think I don't like the camera I wish I could zoom the camera out another
20 30 percent I don't like the angle of the camera and I don't like how close it is even at max zoom
it's not far enough it's the only thing that's keeping me back from playing the game and I've
tried to play it more than twice so I'm not just bullshitting you here I've tried to play what is
fucking hitting me can anyone what the hell just happened to me what happened what was that Gemini
I need more stuff to look at on the screen okay um I gotta be really careful path of exile 2 is
gonna improve zoom oh god fuck arts why did I do that what did that accomplish I didn't look for
the secret room I'm so scared get the fuck away from me health drink Diablo sauce on stream
oh no it's over no it's over it's over I this is I hate this place bomb the door ball oh wait what
everything's fine I thought I was far enough away finally coins I'm looking for hearts hearts
hearts hearts hearts hearts I'll sit here all day if I have to now what was that come on oh get away
from him not many bombs give me hearts no give me hearts give me a difficult give me a fucking
heart no give me a heart yeah give me another one give me that heart right now give me another
give me another one I will do this till I have full health watch me my little sister's afraid of
you why why is your little sister watching this stream this shouldn't that shouldn't be happening
right now does your little sister hate me now I've got somebody here come on over here it's me Elmo
hey Elmo what are you doing here well I want to teach everybody some sharing and how to share
your milk well yeah you should share you should share your milk you should share your toys you
should also share um your your toys with your brother and your friends and your sister thanks
for showing up and telling everybody that Elmo no problem mr. noodle that's not me I'm not mr.
noodle you fucking dumb puppet motherfucker she's 24 oh well when you say my little sister's afraid
of you I think of like a little kid like a blanket going like what is this wrong with this guy
my little sister's scared of you oh shit wait what am I doing I forgot oh what happened to him
what okay I am serious I am I'm not kidding what happened to that guy in there what happened to
him I don't I don't know oh you got that item right yeah okay my little sister's scared of you
let me do an Elmo impression these new guys suck these guys right here they put up the little
bugs yeah well why did I do like the fuck you Elmo motherfucker thing like that wasn't funny
I was just like me being like the toxic streamer thing again I don't know why I did that the lash
out aren't I of course oh my god I'm so pissed that he's in here that I'm taking damage look at
this he's kicking the shit out of me I'm so mad that I he's here I'm actually kind of in deep shit
here I need health and I need stuff oh my god the spider webs all right well is this mom right
awful come on all right we're good Polaroid again 56 minutes not 30 minutes keep gambling
you know I could have but I really just want to move on what am I possibly going to get out of
there I have 40 bombs I have five keys I have tons of money I mean maybe spirit hearts is horrible
this room's terrible not going this way you know when I killed mega Satan on stream and I had this
thing that just blew up the screen every half second that was really cool I guess remember
that season it was a really cool episode of that season let's just do the thing that shows do where
they just tell you to remember how cool the show was how cool that was this is the clip show season
these are new what are these oh my god what the fuck just happened I look I put the bomb
and walked over and looked at Chad because I thought it was safe I have 99 coins no
oh it's not over yet not yet almost now it is I'm gonna die what is that flat penny this is
not worth it it's the part where the streamer pretends to not know how to play and lose a 56
minute run okay okay I'm probably gonna die here though because this stuff's all new and scary
and they made hard mode way harder you didn't tell me that I know some steam store page what
the heck banana crew I mean drew crew oh I'm dead we get my build was cool yeah but it was
never gonna work out it was cool to look at I needed more tears I needed more damage it was
cool and I need to it was cool to look at though uh slowing enemies down nice cool I'm just going
for it let's go I'm getting to the hush and I'm gonna beat hush right now oh that's new that's new
that bug is named in the first game excellence it sounds like our real monsters that sounds like
just just background music in our real monsters that was weird all right where's that it's a candle
don't want it hurry up smells like up gamer in here what's up dude how you been I hope you're
doing well it was um there it is really hurry up don't bother with the secret room just move
I'll get there I'll get there watch this nothing in here besides these little slugs
not coming back down here for any reason you're not beating the hush yet I I don't think I have
on this save file maybe once you can you can check right isn't there a way to check which is which
is the hutch it's like the three dots right oh that's delirium joker card hell yeah fat protector
that's pretty good or use joker now give me this stars item room don't want it you still have a
hundred percent devil deal chance that's right just do the joker now it can take me to like that
weird error room right I wonder remember save it for caves one okay I'm gonna hold on to the joker
does the fact I do anything besides just block damage or is it just a huge fat guy it blocks
and does a little damage okay cool I gotta try to get to hush oh I've definitely beaten hush I know
I have at least a few times on this file I think our soap tears and shots beat up all right nice
wait I don't want to leave just yet should I just go I gotta go I gotta go we gotta move use the
joker now use it now oh that's dark bum that guy's awesome they nerfed him what do you mean they
nerfed him oh hey he's shitty now no he's not what did they do he was good like three years ago
really he sucks now counterfeit penny wealth of wealth I'll keep it I'm gonna go down drops lots
of stuff now instead of soul hearts oh whatever I remember a really cool run was if you had little
chad and dark bum it was just never ending soul hearts it was awesome why'd I go in this room
still a 40 chance for a black heart okay I am not dealing with this right now
hellum please huge huge room
double items though that's good so let's talk about something really quickly on the next stream so
remember we're gonna we're trying this new thing here I am going to play I'm gonna try to get the
sims one ready for next week if you I gotta say it one more time I'm gonna say it for the third
time just to make sure everyone hears it I'm going to be streaming at the same point at the
same time on the same day once a week with an option for a second day in a row that's sort of
how it's going to be for a while and even maybe even long term if you missed out with all the
updates but it will be on schedule scheduled streams are coming back no longer just up in
the air randomly in the afternoon pacific you will know exactly precisely every time when the
stream is going to happen and this is kind of weird hold on try pac-man 99 yeah pack that actually
looks awesome two bombs to blow that up right and I will have a lot more information about grotto
beasts over the next couple of streams you'll hear me talk way more about it just wanted to
make sure you know that that's a real thing oh god what does this do this recharges you can blow
the bottom up right oh fuck I thought it took you to that room with the item I thought it took you
down that ladder with the there's an item at the bottom oh it's only if there's a ladder on it
like but the games like okay binding of Isaac may as well be a physics textbook by now okay there's
like a thousand items there's like 400 room combinations I I'm sorry shit and then I just
deleted like four items this is a dead run now fuck I'm so mad right now oh I want to greed mode
with somebody I love greed mode it's like my favorite range and luck up now I'm used to
when I was playing on the switch greedier mode so this this should be easier for me considering
the last time I played this it was greedier greedier only greedier so I should be okay here
when's the cat boy stream now that is a great question one that I will refuse to answer
but I will say it was a very nice question and I will move on as if you never asked it
yeah but no in all seriousness you'll see it at some point soon that's probably the next quote
more elaborate stream that you'll see it's probably the next one my god you get so many
more coins in the regular greed mode it's insane what about the bionicle movie that's just not
that's not gonna happen there's no chance in hell the items kind of suck what is this eyesore
so it just randomly shoots in a bunch of directions sometimes all right that's pretty
cool you get so much more time too isn't it like 10 seconds or 12 seconds in greedier
this is so much easier itchy nose what did I do I'm dodging it too much god have I got hit
that many times in a row nightmare mode go I'm actually gonna die like the poop guy it's like
giant a pinwheel okay what is it I don't want that thing it's two hearts it's too much to take
well you just fuck off already get out of here rotten baby is good you get a demon heart take
the pact get it it gives you black hearts does this guy serious take it take both act will give
you hearts take it yeah but I have to take damage as Samson let's hope that's part of the deal
oh new new deal no no deal Samson Samson this is such a great game oh intensifying tears what
does it anyone know what that is I've gotten that twice I don't know what it is intensifying tears
you keep shooting in one direction in one direction oh okay it takes so I have to just
hold it here in one direction to just spam holy shit this is awesome although I can never stop
shooting left okay what do we got in here cat food maybe I'll get the cat food anything left
or right is better we'll get it up there pretty cool I'm just machine gun that it can only fire
in one direction okay they're really inaccurate though come on shoot behind hi whoa whoa what are
these I've never seen that guy before I don't think all right tuna supper HP up tears up I
can't go faster than that I'm at the cap right now I thought I could go past this the button
is the fastest you can what just happened why is there not a delay on being able to press that
button when you step on that button you shouldn't be able to step on it again for like two seconds
at least that's good for this guy baby proof the game no no it should be like a half second or
it's in one second or something you know how many times I've accidentally stepped on something like
that you have to you just don't refuse to admit you do very secret door open that happens to you
once a day once a week well that was not worth even doing the nightmare room um hmm let's get
it go are you alive yes I am the mulligan is this the thing that makes spiders um flies just come
out of me while I shoot because if it is that's ridiculous that should be an insane build now
stapler stapler sauce imposter guy are you you are yes me one autograph cool uh it was his passage
so it was his passage and it's two it was what do I do I think this just goes down to the next floor
right you can spawn a ladder or a trap door it's a trap door give me a ladder what the fuck all right
let's see how good this mulligan works I am super excited everything of down I'm gonna go let's do
down why did he abandon the first German channel that's season one season two is see this season
one season one through three is on that channel seasons four or six are on twitch and second
germo these are different DVDs there's a separate DVDs you can't fit every season on one DVD remember
you used to have to buy like 10 DVDs get these flies oh yeah I didn't even know they existed
I had to do it I feel like I can hit horizontally better than I can hit vertically
anybody else feel like that come on let's go ah come on oh come on hi vertical hits are hard
to line up yeah they are let's see what about this pink um eraser thing it's doi throw it
and erases one enemy from the run hmm I think I want to reroll this whole thing oh very nice
stapler stapler no the state doesn't the stapler make you only shoot half of half shots it's
literally the worst play I've ever seen I thought the stapler means you only shoot out of one eye
it's just damage up it doesn't it doesn't staplers new don't be mean to me let the
coal I don't think the coal will be any good here leave him alone he's having fun all right time for
the psycho room nightmare whatever it's called he has long range
he did that oops I keep getting this item creep shots and speed and range up and a secret room
oh no experimental pills speed up shot speed down that's not good bad trip game actually sucks
okay invested these are all bad too oh yeah all right just stay alive stay alive I'm good stay
alive the worst part about this is my tears are red the worst the tears are red my tears are red
their tears are red and the floor is red hello this is just one of those awesome cool collectathon
games check options to change bullet visibility really fuck I got greedy on that one oh you get
out of the corner I'm not aiming that way it's not fair beep fine oh it was on the ground
auto-tuned what I'm not using the uh I'm gonna save it the next floor I don't want any of this
hmm right give me an angel room oh my god no they slowed down the tears slowed the fuck down
in the creep and it messed up what I was moving all right one more god damn it what the fuck was
that that sucked why I had the diamond card too this game needs to be easier just kidding what
the fuck I really like I wanted to go for it it was the stupid creep shot stuff it slowed the tears
down that it lives just firing out and it just like was stuffed in front of my face that was
stupid stupid stupid I was about to restart I'm fucking furious just hit me hit me a bunch of
times I want max fucking damage I'm just do it hit me more more this is not even great I beat ultra
green with my fucking eyes closed like every goddamn weekend I can't beat regular greed mode
on stream huh I'm winning this one if I do not beat greed no don't say that because like it's
actually like pretty much like throwing dice in the air you'll get a decent build to be able to
get to like the last room I might get like mom's lipstick five times I can't like make a prediction
here remember your mic is broken what did I peek the mic to a point where it like you crashed
all right I don't know what that is but I think I'm gonna buy it this is pretty good start here
don't blow it that's tears up what is that this is a weird looking item actually pretty good that
one's really good it's good spore shot be talking to you whoa what is happening it's kind of like a
booger I remember the booger shots whoa that's actually really cool oh those are awesome all
right oh my god does it hurt with the explosion hurt me no it doesn't okay I really want that
that's tears up do I go in here and hope this coin's in here wait um what do I do
that eye is triple shot I blow these up blow up the beggar all right give me a dime all right
what is better right now triple shot or a bunch of tears probably the triple shot now I need
tears up oh shit I don't have any keys will I go for this and just get fucking furious that I die
from the nightmare mode damn it you get triple shot you're fine you say that I you better not
fine I can't get a key though all right well whatever this is the one this is definitely the
one I need tears up and this is the one don't play like a fucking fool lump of coal that's
even better don't be a damn fool keys tinted rock did rock tinted rock wait I don't want you alive
for the next one be a miss with a shotgun at point blank is it aiming at the ground uh explosive
poison shot is awesome is that new feels like it's new all right what we got I need keys
I'm going for key open this door I don't know what this is leprosy you're tearing me apart
lisa I don't know what this does so do I roll the dice and open up both the chests or do I get
the pajamas gamble with pj's pj's is health yeah go for the sure thing go for the sure thing battery
I don't really have anything to charge right now yeah this is the one this is the run I'll get it
this is really good I just need some damage and tears up and this is a guaranteed victory
grid spawn angel room yes oh dear I don't know which one the cross or the seagull
oh dove dove take it it's flight yeah right right right right right light and spectral tears
I'm gonna probably buy it I'm buying a key I'm buying two keys and we're gonna gamble here
hope it works yep not bad not bad doing it again bad buy car battery no I don't I don't want it
I was hoping I was gonna get a key in the chest go in the curse room first room
I'm taking another key first room is free oh because I can fly this is full health I blow the
bed and I blow the bed up I thought I didn't take damage what are you talking about what the hell is
floating around me oh only going in right right right right right right sinus infection booger
tears wait I have booger and the fungus that's really good okay now I just need some tears up
and this is guaranteed victory I got two things that stick very nice all right let's go see what's
in here oh a bomb free oh look the stapler I could use shots damage and tears and shit kind of this
is good but it's gonna be annoying it's too slow cover them in boogers bombs awesome look at that
this guy's jump I don't like it whoo get chaos chaos or stay what does chaos do
or the stapler I feel like the stapler is not going to be good chaos yeah chaos it's fun take chaos
chaos chaos here's up range down chaos chaos chaos isn't that devil I can do anything it says chaos
hey I gotta attach boogers to this guy the angel rooms that's what we want 50 50 chance
the coin you know just oh that's not what that does oops I thought that was mom's foot I got it
wrong I thought that was mom's foot stomps down oh lord um okay there's a spider box and then a
weird like gray remote control chaos both are trash just skip well I mean it's a free item
the remote is useless box of spiders it's a box of spiders it is this actually might not be useless
into all it takes is two spawns and this is I can do it again box is good ban that guy
I mean I look at this it's pretty good all right um I don't have enough for the stapler sorry um
stapler fans I really wanted to see it here it is move cricket I mean cricket spiders everywhere
um what's this circle of protection protect me from thyself crickets head damage up oh now greed
is guaranteed to die it's guaranteed hanged man not gonna need it at all oh sacred heart holy
shit sacred heart sacred heart oh that's the sacred heart okay let's do it let's go sacred
heart holy moly what's the sacred I do this is gonna be cool are we all gonna be collectively
happy about this I can just have infinite spiders here this is perfect should not even hit me I
don't get hit in these games it must be a fucking bug in the code all right what can I do now
sake the sacred heart and sacred heart homing shots and damage up oh boy I'd have 23 damage
shit I'm really sad that this is not on greedier mode because this would be like an
instant kill dude boss wow that's unbelievable that's unbelievable I'm sad that we're not gonna
be able to see for like in five minutes the angel room get rotten baby oh what is all this stuff
I don't want the fat thing that's luck in the middle what's on the right right is good
lucky scab take the eye take the eye get the middle one it's free is it yeah it's hp and uh
this one's hp right okay I don't know if I want that get it don't take the eye get the eye eye
sucks I don't I don't know it's too much hearts to give up I don't want it I can take one more thing
or should I say what's what floor am I in this is not the I have one more opportunity I have
an opportunity next floor baby is take rotten baby yeah I'll get rotten baby there's more flies
all right let's go you got the baby but not the eye well the baby didn't cost two hearts
what is that I'm afraid of that I don't know what it is I'm afraid of all this stuff sticky
bombs egg sack bombs knockout drops they pack a punch what the hell is that okay it's knockback
keys hmm I think this is new I've never seen that before there's like a silver bar I'm not
gonna touch the cat no I know what it is I played for long enough take the iron bar well we'll see
oh that was as good as you could have gotten except for that that's a terrible card iron bar
is a damage and stun well that guy disintegrated these people are fucking disintegrating
it's in the homing missiles too oh this is ridiculous whoa what is I don't even know what
happened okay we're good see if I can kill the boss in like two hits that's awesome oh it's so
good I never want to lose this bill this is like why I love this why can I just keep this forever
I want every game playthrough to have this okay is that lemonade because if it is don't you shoot
a million miles per hour I feel like that would be that might be run ruining I'm not sure any
of these are worth it the p1 what's the one on the left um no I'm playing it safe this build's
way too good I'm not taking anything I'm gonna kill this guy the one on the one on the left
rerolls your stats and no thanks iron bar damage up in concussion tears
26 damage the lemon is just no lemon sucks all right I'm not spending any more money I'm
gonna use it on the machine at the end let's go the cat no it's you get nine lives would you get
one heart what's that crack quad I'm doing it holy shit wow and I got spider baby
I'm gonna kill greed in like five hits into rock all right all right no more money this
this thing is ridiculous this is truly ridiculous so the seed um right there this is not greedier
by the way unfortunately I wish it was this is just regular greed mode they're homing missiles
too I just want to stuff all these projectiles into greed's face they've taken too much unnecessary
hits stop it just survive aim in any direction bring it on I just punched him off the screen
he didn't get his intro animation to play best friends forever all my buddies get to be bigger
does that include the spiders it does all right let's rain hell no doesn't um I'm done I'm gonna
just try to put as much money as I can into the uh machine what is this stuff what's that one what's
the weird ice cube thing the onion onion take the shard of glass onion ring take the onion ring
here's up doesn't it make you um isn't damage go down dps goes up let's go for it yeah that's
better all right let's move I'm done let's put the rest in the green machine I want to be so
annoyingly powerful get the almond milk I just fuck the whole thing up and get the almond milk
and just spam all right fine all right ultrak reed nobody in here whoa let's go kick his ass
so much damage holy shit look at all the things stuck to him he's got stuff just attached to his
body ow he's just covered in stuffed animals 23 a zero have I not on this save file have I not
beaten greed mode once on this save you unlock special hanging shopkeepers the one that I have
down on the switch has like 750 on greedier mode I love this build though this is awesome
wait can I blow anything else up because sure fake fan yeah whatever I might as well use the tower
all right cool not even 50 what a bad streamer yeah that's probably accurate but you though
hey all right and the last thing I want to do they added challenges I'm kind of curious what
they are where are they guardian brains which ones are they added challenges
people are fools commands the last page
is this like poop touching poop gives me little poop monster people I guess we just
destroy everything am I gonna eventually have a ton of these following me around
walk into the enemies hey why'd you tell me to do that Adam judgment you can walk into normal
enemies you also heal when you walk into normal enemies I am so confused right now why is this
happening do you heal when you touch poop fuck doy doy doy doy doy doy rock and hard to see
wait mysterious candy or the money just poop in every room get the candy Andy is what is
healing you okay yeah he's playing Pikmin again boring oh is it how did I get hit I was in the
middle of the crowd did it really go through everybody and hit me somehow directly in the
head far do I have to go do I have to go all the way to beat mom's heart and a boss is gonna be
impossible if I don't have enough oh just mom's foot okay hp the bombs are strong too it's good
to know walk into everybody this is another insane run uh this is a challenge I did not make this
happen just here it's on the game menu oh boy if only they was screaming in farts yeah I don't
that doesn't matter is this I think there's a certain amount that can be on screen
because I think I'm replacing them why would there be a cap and how is this a challenge this
is very easy am I missing something here it's just fun it kind of is just fun cool all right
let's go kill a boss mushroom hp up tears up shot speed down that doesn't matter I'll speak
so soon okay I won't watch out don't get killed I stomp on this oh oh what oh it's the poop bombs
I know those feel though everybody on the screen gets hurt right so uh the next stream we're gonna
try this uh weekly schedule here I'm gonna try to get the sims one to work find it I'll make
sure I can get it to run we will do a sims one night and we'll see what goes from there I'm
gonna try I'm gonna see how this plays out I'm gonna go for it it's sort of a little
trial here to see how that plays out I didn't feed once forgot to pee once the whole day
oh it's pretty rare get him is this the season finale it's not the season finale
did you not notice did you pee yourself no I'm good doesn't look like it we're good what do you
unlock for doing this because you unlock items this way right I don't even care about the items
I don't even care about getting any uh any money or anything I just want to get to mom max poops
are determined by your range stat okay but it's uh it's good to be back it's good to uh see you
all again I will not be taking another break like that ever again we're gonna change up how we do
things on the channel so let's see what happens the idea is having the kind of weekly show in
quotes will make it so I don't have to ever do that again because I really don't want to do that
again just get them power twice can't wait for the next month break in June and that would be
something now wouldn't it I don't even buy that wait can I not kill these how do I kill these
I have to use bombs I'm gonna say holy that's not good all right only one more HP up wrap take any
break you need man we can handle it I know and I have I disappeared for like three months back
in last year and then here we are again I disappeared for like a month again like less
than probably about a year later I really don't want to take like a month two three four months
off when I would rather just stream more uh like periodically and that allows me to kind of do all
the stuff that I need to do and there's other it's not just the medical stuff too there's all
I have other stuff going on too that I really have to focus on and I'm gonna stream for fun
and when I think it's fun to do there's lots of opportunities to do games and play different things
and come up with some new ideas and there's there's a bunch of big stuff coming that's
happening soon but I need to be in a mindset to you know feel like it and want to
I'm gonna kill him I saved the money yeah I might need it this guy stinks funny or no I don't want
that how come this guy's not making any jokes I think the screen is really self-explanatory
how do I add to this besides making fart noises myself you know I'm stealing material from me
usually I would be the one making like the poo-poo noises and like the fart faces and stuff
chop speed up and the empress no I mean hermit all right this is it what do we get when I'm gonna
get what do I get for doing this kill him whatever I don't care if it hurt me I don't even care if
it hurts you say right or left ah I'm gonna skip it I don't care down maybe make him hit himself
on the thing there yeah fortnight we about to get down can kill his board right now
I just got down I revived and then we're going southbound
stepping the gas we're going part three out of the gas we're going I don't know wherever it goes
all right what does this do this was kind of just running around killing stuff with poop
and all right let's go kill hope I don't die he's stepping on them and killing them
money spawn somebody and
all right wait what's this part got it dirty mind has appeared in the basement
I unlock any other ones no not yet all right I think that's gonna be it I will see you guys um
probably on Saturday we're gonna go Saturday next time I'm gonna spend the week here going back and
forth with some stuff and medical stuff too let's see how this plays out I'm I'm really trying to
find out if this is gonna be worth doing or not I'm I'm hoping it is but at least you know I'm
I'm not gone I'm here it's just gonna be like a weekly show maybe two times a week I'm not just
gonna close the door on let's say that it's every Saturday that Sunday they won't be ever be a
stream so there'll probably be lots of occasions where it's like Saturday Sunday Saturday Sunday
Saturday Sunday Saturday Saturday Saturday Saturday Sunday Saturday Sunday
that's what I'm assuming is gonna happen we'll find out I will be back I'll see you guys again
thanks for watching I know we've kind of just played Isaac but really looking forward to it
we're gonna do The Sims 1 next weekend take care of yourselves I'll have a lot more to talk about
next weekend as well and I would assume that because of playing The Sims 1 you can probably
assume a Saturday Sunday scenario because you can't get a whole lot done in just like one day
in The Sims so we'll probably do our first one too next weekend because I want to give The Sims 1
time to play it and have fun so we'll see have a great rest of your night lots of shit is in the
works I hope you enjoy it when you see it in the coming few months again Grotto Beast is a real
thing there'll be more info on that next week take care of yourselves there were a lot of community
subs take a look this is gonna fly then yeah there's a lot of subs when you don't stream for
a month you get like a barcode scan going by oh my goodness and I want to make this really clear
too but I just for people to just because I really want to say it I understand like I get it if if
you've been a sub or if you are thinking of subbing and you don't think that like four or five
streams a month is worth subbing don't I don't want you to if you don't think that's worth it
so I I'm dialing back the streams to a point where I don't want people to still feel obligated
to think that they have to stay subscribed if they don't think that paying for like essentially
optionally paying for like four or five streams a month is worth it so I'm not going to hold that
against anybody if they don't want to stay subbed to the channel even people that have been here
for a long time I need to make that really clear he hates his subs what about badge Andy that's
right I have to give you money you don't sub even harder no I I want you to think it's worth
watching whatever you're watching and if we slow down a lot it's all right this is ridiculous
though how many subs is it today I need to know oh Jesus it was let's get a good picture here
I think I think like you know you know and you know what no I'm not gonna say I'm not gonna say it
because I don't want to talk about that I don't want to be like oh hey wow
X amount of subs today awesome I don't think I'm even gonna say it I don't think it's needs to be
said because I think that saying it is almost like me inceptioning into your mind like wow look at
how many subs were today oh I mean see you next week when I mean I better still have them I don't
think I want to do that anymore so thank you though it was a lot and with that I will see you on
Saturday and probably Sunday too for Sims one we're going back to the original the scary one
have a great rest of your night have a great rest of your weekend we will see you real soon
and I hear Otto perfect timing just asked me for dinner he just said something to the door
raid yeah let's write somebody who's who's streaming right now he said Joel let's see what's
Joel doing who is streaming oh can I not go to my manager here there it is
hmm I can't see it my monitor is whole hiding haunted ps1 demo discs all right that sounds
pretty great I'll see you guys later have a great rest of your week and I'll probably have some more
grotto beasts information when I see you on Saturday good night goodbye take care of yourself
I'm gonna try to take it easy go say little Joel take care