Hey, look at that! Welcome, happy, no, not yet, not yet, not yet, but hello everybody, welcome to a grand, grand, hold on, let me make sure it doesn't play again, hold on, oh shit, it's starting again, it's starting again, hold on, hi guys, welcome to a very special, let's just go ahead and get the feet up on the, don't, hold on, I can't fuck, this, I just got done setting this all up, I don't wanna fuck it up, uh, welcome to the New Year's Eve, uh, spectacular,
if you can even call it that, this is, uh, this is a lot of work in the making, in two days, we had this idea like two or three days ago, and a shitload of people in the community are to be thanked for getting this to be a possibility, so, thank you to especially the mods, all of you, you took a, the nomination process, there were spreadsheets involved, it was kind of insane, uh, holy mack and effectator, holy shit,
you guys, uh, you guys knocked it out of the park, we were, all three of us were like trying to get these like videos done, and oh my goodness gracious, uh, but, it, it, I think it's all ready to go, and I just figured this out right now that I'm here, so, welcome to New Year's Eve, as you see here, got a lot of cards here, these are all categories that some of you guys may have voted on, or maybe you didn't, but you did, uh, we got worst new character is the first one, slow mode off,
it's New Year's Eve, all the awards will be given, top bananas, and yes, I'm very much aware that there are only eight bananas here, there are like 17 awards, I promise I didn't burn the other ones, but I got, hold on, there might be another couple of top, is my fly up today, yeah it is, wait a second, there is the most coveted award in the entire world,
it's the worst stream of the year, tiny Oscar, somebody's gonna be getting this tonight, take a look at that, six inches tall, the real one's only like seven, so who cares, that's gonna go right in the front, does it look good, no, this needs to go like higher up, can I balance these on the bananas,
Jeremy, you're not good at anything, I just have to touch it for a second and it's fine, so, uh, thank you for, this is my leg of that, this is such a wobbly fucking table, I don't even have, by the way, there are no notifications tonight, because I'm on location, so, I don't have access to any real dashboard stuff or stream labs, I figured we just would kind of just axe it for tonight anyways,
I do have my Twitch dashboard though, which is a good thing, and yes, I am stalling because, this is like the first break I've had, I'm serious, this is like, first time I've just been able to sit down and do nothing, for like three days, it's an award show, this is what they do, the guy comes out on stage and he like has a nice fucking suit on, and hey, I'll pick up my, hold on, let's see, did I even match my pants, should I tuck, do you tuck in a suit, should I tuck this in?
should I tuck this part in, so it's like that, hey, I'm here for the job interview, I get it, that's right, regional manager, that's gonna be me, fireman, yeah, actually this is probably the first time I've worn this shirt, it's just been, actually no, that's not true, I wore it once on the way over here, it's a really comfortable shirt though, I have too many shirts, I have like 14 Star Wars shorts, I have, I probably have 14 Star Wars shorts too,
all right, without further ado, what do you say we get started, how this is gonna play out is like this, we've got 17 or 18 different categories, you guys have voted, the votes are up, I've tallied them all, I got them all here in envelopes, we're gonna find out what the best and worst dreams, best and worst moments of 2018 are, I'm gonna put my headphones in because I'm curious about how this plays out, so without further ado, the first category is worst new character,
worst new character, why don't we take a look at the nominees for worst new character.
I do quality work, okay, I do quality work, I hope not, you think I'm just gonna not do quality work, roll over, let's make sure we can see the Hanes, oh yes we can, absolutely, he's perfect.
I don't, I hate drama, I really don't want to do it, but his audience and him have said some dumb things, first of all his name is grill master x barbecue, and the guy hasn't cooked any food on stream in at least, at least like two years, you couldn't even tell how fast that was.
Ladies and gentlemen, if I could get a drum roll please, if I could get one of those that'd be nice, ladies and gentlemen, the winner of the 2018 worst new character goes to, the what, with 28.4% of the vote, ladies and gentlemen, grill master x barbecue is the worst new character of 2018, he sucked, with nearly 28% of the vote, that's actually very surprising.
I was certain it was going to be bugleberry, and just in case it was bugleberry, I was well prepared to invite, invite bugleberry here to do a little presentation if he had won.
I've got to give the award to somebody, a worst new character who made him.
I did.
Thank you, thank you very much, I appreciate that.
First thing I want to say about, you know, when you make a new character it can be very very difficult, trying to figure out the backstory and where they come from, what's their motivation, how tall are they, how small are they, do they have, where are they from in the world, it's a tough thing to do and sometimes you fucking miss, but remember if you're a baseball player, if you fail seven out of ten times you're still a fucking Hall of Fame player, they'll take it.
That's the first award of the night, that's worst character of last year.
Hard work to make, it's hard work to make a new character.
I've got to get that off the screen, it's going to fuck up my vision.
Do you see these envelopes by the way?
These are the real deal, look at these.
Funny thing, these are wedding invitations.
Invitation.
I was trying to find something that I could actually use to be, to make it fun, but there you go.
I did not think he was going to get 28%.
I thought that was going to be bugleberry for sure.
Oh well, reuse it for a wedding.
Oh by the way, just in case anyone wants to know, it's going to get probably insanely loud because I am right in the heart of Las Vegas.
So this is New Year's Eve and I forgot about this so I was thinking to myself, oh yeah, New Year's Eve stream.
I think there's like half a million fucking people here right now.
Like I'm going to get stuck here.
Like in the heart.
I'm in the heart right now.
There's like half a million people fucking here right now, whatever.
What are we moving to the next category?
This next category is, no it's not beater, not yet.
This is the worst sweat category.
For those of you that voted for this one, there were a lot of weird options.
Some of them weren't even sweat.
That's fine, I will take the loss on some of these.
Let's check out the nominees for worst sweat of the year.
Now this includes, greasy face, sloppy hair.
No, no, no, no, no, no, worst hair is the next one.
Alright, I get confused sometimes because the worst sweat is sweat.
It's sweaty face, sweaty body.
I don't know why the fuck this is even a category, but you know what?
Now let me check out the nominees for worst sweat of 2018.
Satan's dream.
Whoa!
Why am I made out of plastic?
I swear to God I don't look like this.
I don't look like this.
And the winner of worst sweat for 2018 is...
With 33% of the vote we've got...
Plastic face birdhouse.
And do it again!
That wasn't even sweat though, that was just the weird...
I had a sheen on my face. Does that actually count?
What about right now? How do I look now, huh?
You don't see a drop on me.
I was thinking what would be kind of a funny...
A funny joke would be...
Do all these categories tonight and be covered in sweat.
Have terrible fucking hair. Make a ton of awful jokes.
Make a ton of great jokes.
Have every category play out right now.
And have a final voting for it.
But there it goes, worst sweat, plastic.
But come on, here's the thing about the sweat thing, right?
I'm sitting down screaming every day.
I scream. Right now I'm screaming.
But you don't understand, my normal speaking voice is this.
And for a long time it took a while to get the ability to talk louder.
But over time I practice.
And right now I'm screaming as loud as I can.
So when you do that, you build up a lot of perspiration.
You build up your...
I'll take the... whatever. I lose.
Thanks for the award. I appreciate it.
Because that was also me.
But you know what I mean though?
I'm under stress sometimes.
I'm playing video games.
And it gets too much.
You lock yourself into the seat and you just...
Whatever.
I'm already subconsciously touching my hair.
Because that's the next category is worst hair.
I get a lot of shit for this.
Over the years.
But you have to remember, when you get to be my age,
when you grow to over 30 years old,
you're not worried about your hair anymore.
Some of you guys that are in your 20s,
that are in your late teens or something,
and you're out there having a good time on New Year's Eve,
you got gel in your hair and it looks fucking great,
and you look in the mirror and you're like,
fucking nice, man.
I don't do that.
I don't do that anymore.
I just wake up, shake my head as hard as I can,
and then take a shower,
comb it hard too.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I make sure it fucking hurts.
Every day.
I don't do it anymore.
I don't really care about the hair anymore.
The hair is just on my head.
So it doesn't really make me that upset
when people talk about the nominees for worst hair anymore.
Oh, that was a lot of lipstick.
Here you go.
More on a journey
through verdant fields and Viridian cities
in a timeless west.
I can't beat Vaughn Faith Kim right now, by the way.
What? Are you serious?
Holy shit, there's a button. There's a B in here.
Oh, fuck me. Goodbye.
There it is. Holy shit.
My sideburn's a different length.
You know, I got a lot of shit from my hair.
People were saying like, well, you look like a fucking,
you look like a real villain.
I slicked it back today.
So I actually look like a fucking real like 80s movie villain.
Slick back with oil.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
I'm gonna need this later, but I'll use it right now.
Man bun.
And the w-
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What was wrong with the rubber band hair?
You know what I mean?
It was just up and poofy on the sides.
What was actually inherently wrong with that hair?
Wasn't a man bun.
A man bun would have to go all the way back up like this and up.
My hairline's really, actually really bad now.
I had a stylist coming in to do it today.
I'm in a goddamn studio.
You see it today?
Oh, bad hair, huh?
Take a look at that.
Stylist came in, took five steps into the door,
sprayed from like 10 feet away with his hairspray,
and then left.
She was $225.
Worst hair of the year goes to...
With 18% of the vote, it was pretty close, I will tell you.
It was the Burnout Paradise bathrobe hair.
Now, was that so much hair as it was I looked terrifying in that picture?
I think it was more so how I looked in the picture than I did the actual haircut.
18%.
It was very spread out.
It was one of the closest ones, I believe, if I can take a look here.
It was both.
Yeah, but was it really, though?
I don't think it was that.
It was the face I was making.
It was bad angle.
You had no hair.
What hair?
Actually, let me pull it up because I'm curious as to how...
Some of these were really close, so I'll just pull them up.
Now, if you're wondering, there was a lot of responses.
I was kind of concerned that having less than a day of voting,
there were more than 4,000 responses,
so that's pretty great for having it be one day.
Anyway, worst hair.
Yeah, so Burnout Paradise had 18%,
and then the closest one to that was the sideburns don't match with 15.3%.
Everything else was very even after that.
So, you know.
Hey, we're getting to some better categories now,
not just like how disgusting and ugly is Jeremy.
Who came up with these categories?
Oh, wait.
I forgot to take it.
Thanks for bananas.
That's another way.
And I explained the award.
I have to take these top bananas, and then...
Are we at Peter yet?
No, this is best noise.
I mean, this is also kind of a strange category.
How many bananas do you think I can fit in my pocket?
I bet you I could fit at least like four bananas in here.
All right.
Best noise.
This is the category that over the years
during stressful situations and during video games,
especially stuff just kind of comes out of my mouth,
and I can't stop it.
I can't help it.
There is a worst noise category as well.
So don't worry.
This is not just like, oh, we're doing the best one.
There's more worst than best categories for this broadcast.
So just be aware of that.
Best noise.
Somebody raided us?
Well, I don't have my stream lab,
so thanks for the raid, whoever you are.
Welcome everybody that came from that raid.
Thank you.
Hopefully you have a good New Year's Eve.
And speaking of which,
you guys are going to have to remind me
because already it's 1030 right now, right?
Eastern.
We're going by Eastern time.
So when the ball drops Eastern,
I'm tearing the rest of these up,
and I'm getting the fuck out of here.
No, I'm kidding.
So it is 1030.
We got an hour and a half before the ball drops in New York.
So I need to be ready for that.
I don't have, by the way,
I don't have anything special planned for that shit.
It was a miracle to get this whole thing set up in two days.
I was going to have like a ball drop.
No, we're just going to be like,
Hey, there it is.
Happy fucking New Year.
The ball went down.
So we are now on to this best noise.
And let's go check out the nominees for best noise of 2018
that comes out of my mouth or the come.
I'm already getting stuck.
It comes out of a, you know, my mouth in general.
Here are the nominees.
A bunch of kids like, oh, fuck you.
Look at them.
You just walk in and you just go like.
And they'll all go.
Well, you can't take any damage, guys.
Fuck you.
You guys suck.
Watching that back is like,
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me.
The winner for 2018 best noise as chosen by you,
the viewers is.
Yeah.
The didgeridoo beer with 24% of the vote.
Didgeridoo beer is the winner.
Well, it really wasn't even close.
So 24% do it again.
Do it a re-vote.
What do you mean?
That's not possible.
I'll tell you.
I'll give you the exact numbers right now.
Not possible, they say.
Here are the numbers.
So we have,
we have,
didgeridoo beer was 24%.
Coming in second place
was German snort.
And then in third place was the Dark Souls
screech re thing.
So there are your top three.
So with every best noise,
there is a worst noise.
No, don't look at it.
I was about to be like,
the winner is.
No, I have to wait until we see the nominees.
These are numbers.
These are the numbers, by the way.
Oh, the award.
Right.
How many bananas can he fit in here?
Thank you for the award, everybody.
I appreciate it.
Am I going to be drinking more coffee?
I wonder if I do.
Okay.
This has been my life.
Anytime that I want to get something done.
You know what I mean?
I just drink a shit.
No, this is bad advice.
I'm not going to give bad advice on my.
No, you know,
we'll give bad advice because it's New Year's
and New Year's resolution is get rid of your bad advice
and take in the good advice.
Right.
So bad advice for 2018.
Don't do this.
There's only like one more like hour for you to do this.
There's drink coffee past eight or nine p.m.
Don't do that anymore.
New Year's resolution.
No more coffee after like seven p.m.
That's now impossible.
Worst noise of the year coming up.
I think people are going to be really upset about these
because some of the worst noises,
I think should probably be in the best noises,
at least in my opinion and vice versa.
I didn't make the rules.
I just made the categories.
The nominees for worst noise of 2018 are.
I know.
Like this thing's so weak.
Yeet.
Crooked monster.
The mass ray.
Increase XP from defeating enemies.
Perfect dodge temporarily increases damage.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Get it.
Go get the gun.
I hate the sound of tape.
I'm sorry, guys.
This is like turning on an oven for me.
I don't like ovens.
I hate turning on an oven and it like freaks me out.
I like this like box in your house
that heats up to like fucking 500 degrees.
I don't like it.
It's weird and it's gas.
This is also, I don't like this.
I didn't press that button yet.
Why did it do that?
Anyways, there are your nominees
for worst noise of 2018.
And there can only be one winner though.
Your winner of worst noise in 2018 is.
With 14.9% of the vote,
this was, the jury was really out there on this one.
The Oblivion webcam scream is the winner.
The Oblivion turn the volume down
and peak your microphone until you break it sound.
It was the worst noise in 2018.
They were all there.
They were all real bad.
Play it again.
Why do you want to replay that one?
You guys want me to replay that video?
Are you sure?
You guys want to see that again.
What's wrong with my backdrop?
I don't know.
Maybe I should just get another one.
I'll replay it again if you want.
Okay.
I'm going to play it one more time.
Oblivion webcam mic peak.
Here we go.
Here's the other nominees.
By the way, the nominees for best,
worst noise of the year are.
Why am I replaying this?
Just play the Oblivion one again.
I thought you guys wanted me to play the whole video.
Why would I do that?
Only the winner?
That's going to be hard to do.
Well, here you go.
Here it comes.
Yeet.
Crookie monster.
The mass raid.
I'll mute the video until it gets here.
Increase XP from defeating enemies.
Perfect.
All right.
There it is.
There's your winner again.
Director's commentary.
I don't really have any director's commentary.
Go get it.
Go get the gun.
What do you want me to say?
I screamed this time.
I don't want to.
I don't want to see the tape one again.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not doing the tape one.
I actually fucking hate that noise.
Did I already pick the winner?
Yeah.
Okay.
What?
All right.
We're good.
What time is it?
We got a time check here.
All right.
We got about we got an hour and 20 minutes before the ball drops in New York City.
Well, I'm sorry.
It's been a long couple of days.
I don't know what the fuck this was, but I apologize for it.
All right.
We had to cut a few categories because they just there's one enough time.
So we're just going to do something really quickly.
The worst meme, worst new meme of the year only had two nominations.
So it was Boomer and Peter.
So they both they both went like I was going to do something.
I was going to have like a tug of war versus Boomer and Peter.
But they both they both fucking went like they come on.
What do you want to say?
There's two nominations.
How am I going to take one of these bananas?
This is like Jenga.
Have a live straw poll.
Let's get that fucking banana in there.
All right.
What's next?
OK.
Wait.
Oh, the mic is right here.
I forgot.
I'm on my laptop right now.
We have this category.
This category is worst death of the year in a game.
You know, whether I fell off a cliff or something happened to my character.
This is worst deaths of the year.
So why don't we check out the nominees for worst deaths of 2018?
I don't think I'm ready for this pinwheel.
Am I too heavy for this fight?
Maybe.
Oh, it's one of these stupid fights where there's a there's like a clone.
OK, well, I don't know what the fuck he does.
So the first time you see a boss, you can't expect to win.
I just don't know which one is real.
That's the problem.
And if it takes me 15 fucking deaths to figure that out, there's nothing even in this bottle.
Oh, what the fuck?
No, I'm not going to spend my souls because I don't know what I want.
I don't know what to level.
Brought these in.
This was a pain in the ass to farm these.
I read on the Wikipedia page that you can actually throw these at them, right?
And it hurts 135.
That's not even close to what I was doing.
I was doing like two.
You can't light actual enemies on fire, right?
135 is so bad.
Why did I farm these?
Why did I do this?
I should have been used this from the very beginning.
Like if I use this from the very beginning.
My hitbox is so stupid.
Oh, get away from me.
I haven't died anywhere else.
And pinwheel.
Worst death of the year.
And moving on, we've got the...
How many people are here right now?
I wonder.
Oh, I need a banana.
Oh, yeah, that's right, a banana.
Uh-oh.
I can get this.
Just wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll get that one.
I'll pick that one up later.
That one fell.
Thank you for the worst death award there.
So that gets...
Hold on, we're almost at the...
Hold on, let me just get...
Sorry.
So I can have some more awards later.
So we've made it to...
There's still a lot to go.
So don't worry.
We've got our best feeder and worst feeder are coming up here in just a moment.
What's wrong?
Collar?
Oh, fuck.
Right.
I'm sorry about that.
Oh, let me fix it.
How do you guys pick up on this shit so quickly?
That would have taken me like three hours at a party to figure that out.
Fly is down.
It is not.
We already checked that before the stream started.
Oops.
Let's just leave it on because here we go.
It's time for the best feeder of 2018.
How many people are here right now?
So there are over 6,000 people watching right now.
Bet you about 500 of them leave in the next 20, 30 seconds.
Because we're about to do the fucking Peter shit.
Which I think only like 50 people in this chat think this is funny.
And I'm not even one of them.
By the way, we were looking up shit about Peter, right?
Did you guys know that I've been saying this word for over a year and a half?
It's been a fucking year and a half.
I don't remember me saying this for the first time.
When did this start and why has it not stopped?
I don't know.
I thought I started saying this two or three months ago.
It's been like two years.
I think it's because somebody in this community's name is Peter.
And they've given a lot of donations and I've read the messages.
And sometimes I just go like, hey, thanks, Peter.
And they just went from there.
I have no idea.
But this is the best Peter.
This is the best Peter of the year coming up here.
Next category, best Peter.
Let's see which one it is.
All of the towers have been unlocked.
You guys are in.
This is the end game.
Peter, Peter, we're at the end game now.
Thank you, Peter.
Peter, again, for the one dollar.
Hello.
Hello, Peter.
Peter.
Hey, Peter.
Hello, Peter.
No facial hair.
Peter, it's Stewie Griffin.
Why am I making everybody from family guys?
Peter, you're a scientist.
I'm something of a scientist myself.
demonic cucumber.
Thanks for the one dollar.
Can you tell me the name of a cooking device specifically used to mix eggs?
An egg beater.
Well, that was pretty good.
Ladies and gentlemen, the best Peter of 2019 is with 26% of the vote.
That's a lot of people with a lot of clicks.
I'm something of a scientist myself, Peter.
26%.
Scientist Peter.
This was the best Peter of the whole year.
No, don't pull the action figures on back that far.
Don't do it.
That's over the recommended manufacturer's length.
Don't do it, Johnny.
Oh, fuck.
It's only supposed to go up to here.
Not say Peter.
I didn't.
I am a thousand percent certain.
God fucking damn it.
Who cares if I said Peter?
I don't give a fuck.
Why does it matter?
That shouldn't matter.
Of all things to matter right now, and I was going well.
And he said Peter.
Cronk, like the emperor's new groove?
Hey, it's me, Patrick Warburg, Cronk.
You know, I'm Joe from Family Guy 2.
Peter.
Hey, Peter.
Let me tell you something, Peter.
Peter, it's the soup.
It was the goblin.
What should I say?
Peter.
Oh, so bad.
The worst Peter.
One of them was from like 2016.
Worst Peter of the year.
Ladies and gentlemen, the worst Peter.
Hotline Miami 2 Peter Breakdown with 29% of the vote.
I was going to just start eating this, but I'm not.
No, no, no, no, no.
I've got indigestion.
29% of the vote.
Hotline Miami 2 Peter Breakdown.
And it made that make sense.
It does.
There you go.
The worst Peter of 2018 or 2016.
OK, what time is it?
We've got about one hour.
Change the backdrop.
Why don't we just check in on how you guys are doing?
How are you guys feeling out there?
You guys good?
You guys doing all right out there?
You sure?
Fucking idiots.
Yeah, keep fucking dancing out there and booing.
All right.
Nobody said change the backdrop?
Yeah, they did.
Everyone's having so much fun.
Booing Jeremy at his award show.
And I just realized what I was doing there.
Don't.
That's going to get cut into a fucking.
Ow, my fingers.
Take that award.
The Pneuma guy.
No, no, no, no.
I was.
Ah, put your hands down.
Is this suit too small for me?
Am I just coming to the realization right now?
Wait, is that supposed to happen?
Like, it's not supposed to come up this far.
If I go to like shake somebody's hand, my suit's not supposed to fall off, right?
But how does it sit on me normally?
Like, how does it sit on my body?
You know what I mean?
If I was walking down the street, right?
It looks fine.
I just can't ever like go like that.
Hey, how are you?
I'll have to go like this.
I have to check my fly every now and again.
All right, next category is going to be the best flavor of ice cream for 2018.
Sometimes your opinions change year to year.
Just want to make sure we got the correct one for 2018.
Here are the nominees for best ice cream of the year.
Ice cream of flavor of the year.
Why does that keep playing when I change my scene?
What do you mean no vanilla?
Vanilla's on there like three times.
The best ice cream flavor, best ice cream kind of ice cream in 2018.
Whoa, I forgot about this one.
I forgot how crazy this one was.
So with 45% of the vote, 45% of the vote, you heard that correct, cookie dough.
There was 4,000 responders and almost half of you guys picked cookie dough.
Cookie dough is a great ice cream, but is it better than faded lemon?
I'm not sure.
That's rigged.
I think you underestimate how much people love cookie dough ice cream.
They'll just click it when they see it on screen.
Even if they know that there's something better for an option.
Do a recount.
No, you know how I know it's legit?
Because I clicked cookie dough ice cream.
I remember like talking to at least two or three people that also took that poll.
They all clicked cookie dough ice cream.
We should have just removed it.
Confirmed rigged.
No, I just said, but you can't tell anybody who you voted for.
I know.
What?
So if somebody asked you, hey, who did you vote for?
You could say, like, I don't want to tell you.
That's fine.
But if that person says, hey, who did you vote for?
You go, I'll tell you who I voted for, sure.
Mike Malarkey.
I don't know.
Whoever the fuck it is.
Dean Dingus, like, for all that matters.
I mean, that's illegal.
It's not illegal to tell somebody who you voted for.
Speaking of literally none of the things we were just talking about,
best impression of the year?
I sometimes dabble in character work.
You know what I mean?
I sometimes dabble in doing character voices.
And 2018, there were quite a few good ones.
So for best impression of the year, let's take a look at the nominees.
And I know that each one of these videos is probably very loud when it starts.
So just be careful.
When you see the video, just drop your volume by 5%
and then I'm going to take care of it from there.
Worst best impression of the year?
Peter, I hear you're by the scientist.
Well, I'm something of a scientist myself.
Get that in a fucking Petri dish, motherfucker!
All right, man, if you think this dead body is crazy,
share this video with two of your friends.
Okay, guys, so that's going to wrap it up here.
We're going to have to check this out in the next video.
You know what I mean?
Like, we've got a detective work here.
We're going to turn into Batman.
Give that video a punch.
Shoot it to the moon.
And I'll see you guys in the next one.
See you soon.
Hey, what's going on, sinners?
Welcome to another video.
This is part 39.
Why would you raise your hand this high over like this?
That doesn't make any sense to me.
Like, the doggy paddle, to me, is a lot more efficient.
It just does.
Wouldn't you want to, like, go up and in like this,
wicked quick, like a chicken?
But, you know, you give and you take, right?
Just like the Lord does.
The Lord gives and the Lord takes.
And the Lord gives away.
Just like you would be to me.
I really need five dollars.
If you could just find it,
your godly heart gets given to me.
I'm going to put my hands around right now.
You just got to put five dollars in there.
That's it.
You're going to be out of your hair.
I mean, you won the opportunity for a lifetime.
And yes, you're going to get a Disney World trip.
But who cares about the Disney World trip?
When at the end of the day, you're going to give me five dollars.
I can't wait until Sans comes out here and he goes...
You should have gone with the head.
Because of this, I'm going to do two hands.
Everyone dies.
That means me, too.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, that means me.
No, no, no.
I did not take it back.
By the way, spoilers if you haven't seen Infinity War.
Everybody's seen Infinity War at this point.
No one's not seen it.
If you haven't seen Infinity War, I'm sorry.
But like, why haven't you?
No one's seen it yet.
No, everybody's seen Infinity War.
I don't know why I have to keep saying that.
Hey, by the way, if you haven't seen Infinity War yet,
here's another one.
You haven't seen it.
I haven't seen it.
You haven't?
How have you not seen it?
Infinity War is like, have you seen Star Wars?
Have you seen the new Star Wars movie?
I want to know how many people.
With 32% of the vote, that's a majority.
There was like 10, 10, 10, 32% is Sans.
Sans is the winner.
Look at them all there.
Oh, they're so happy about that one.
Sans wins.
Fireworks.
Where was the Yoshi clip?
It got lost in the...
Yoshi!
You know what I mean?
Wait, it actually might be on worst impression.
I forget.
You're going to start hearing like explosions.
This is New Year's Eve in Las Vegas.
It's going to be like crazy.
And we're in the heart.
Do the voice.
What voice?
Do Sans.
I don't think I can do it.
I don't want to like peek the microphone.
Let me see how this sounds.
I need to like listen to it.
Let me just listen.
I can hear it.
Hold on.
This is going to hurt.
I can't do it with you looking at me.
I've got to turn the fucking camera off.
I've got to just...
I can turn that off now.
So that was...
Did I do it?
No, this is worst impression.
Oh, we didn't even do this one yet.
OK, spoiler for Undertale.
Get out of here.
Like, get that out of here.
Spoiler for Undertale is a character in it named Sans.
And he goes, a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a a.
Really?
That's a spoiler.
No, don't peek at it yet.
The nominees for Worst Impression of the Year are...
OK?
He's joking.
It's the worst bane I've ever heard.
No!
George Washington!
Please someone listen to this gritty, gruffy man!
What if he talked like this?
This was his real voice?
Nobody knows.
It's not recorded.
I hope he sounded like this.
Where's the tape recording?
Wait a minute.
We've got a suicide squad.
Oh, you forgot to do.
Ah.
Leo.
The best Joker laughing I've ever heard.
That was terrible.
Delete that too.
I was at Target today, and there was episode in the front row in front of me
in the title checkout.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
And I said, hey, excuse me.
I was at Target today, and there was episode in the front row in front of me in the
title checkout.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
And I said, hey, excuse me.
Excuse me.
And what she said.
I swear to God, I'm not even kidding.
She had yaks up her chin.
Snip, snip, snip.
Another video.
Woohoo.
So the worst impression of the year is...
Do I need to try to do the drum roll?
It's like a second.
Good.
Okay.
The winner with 29% of the vote.
This was really close.
Too close to call, you could say.
Until I closed it with 29% of the vote is Donald Duck.
Donald Duck is the winner of the worst impression of the year.
The gnome was right behind, and I was kind of against the gnome being on the
pole in the first place because I just jumped in front of the camera.
It went like this.
You know what I mean?
This doesn't count.
You know what I'm saying?
All I did was this.
So that doesn't matter.
That's not even an impression.
Where's my...
There it is.
I've got to snip it back up.
Okay.
So I'm glad it didn't win.
Donald Duck is the winner with 29%.
It was like 28% for the gnome.
Congratulations to me again.
I'll take the top banana.
Thank you so much.
We're running out of pockets on the website.
All right.
I don't know why, but for one second, you hear this?
I thought there was like a Game Boy in my pocket, like a DS.
I don't know why DS just jumped right into my brain immediately.
I got a DS in here.
Why would I have a DS in there?
A Game Boy.
I see you said Game Boy.
New background.
Sure.
Coming up, we got some of the best, some of the best of the year.
We're getting down to the meaty categories now.
What the hell is over here?
We're getting down to the meaty categories.
This is the best gamer moment of the year.
This is a moment where I did something cool, did something crazy,
accomplished something that is almost unhuman.
You know what I mean?
Best gamer category of the year.
Why is this one frozen?
I have another one.
Where is it?
I actually, I have another one.
Give me a second.
Hold on.
That's not it.
This is not it.
That's fucking odd.
That's a little weird for me.
Hold on.
Wait a second.
Just wait one second.
Coming to you live at your campsite.
Hold on.
This is important.
I did like a, I was going to go get a fucking forest.
This is too much.
I'm going back to what it was before.
I can't do that one.
Best gaming moment of the year.
Let's take a look at the nominees for best moment for video game
wise of the year.
Here are the nominees.
Oh, my life.
No.
I can do it.
Get the fuck out of here.
Do I have to fight it?
Who's fighting?
Make it happen.
Come on.
Make us proud.
Okay.
He's fine.
He needs to get hit one more time.
Any chop, anything.
He ends it with his fucking signature move.
Knock him down.
And I got his fucking friend.
It's just me and one guy left.
One guy.
Where is he?
All right.
I got my last hundred dollar bill.
My last hundred dollar bill.
Here it comes.
Final hundred dollar bill.
I lost it all.
I got one more bill in my pocket and I just sat down at the first machine I saw.
Jackpot.
Shoot the car 60 times.
You ready?
Check this out.
So this is not going to fight.
When I was a kid, I beat a bunch of adults in a video game championship at Blockbuster.
I'm a Blockbuster video game champion, an actual champion.
1995 store championship.
1995 store champion.
Store champion 1995 Super NES format.
Fucking real.
I got three lives.
Shoot the targets and watch the fireworks.
Five seconds.
The winner of best game.
What a bunch of great gaming moments.
Why don't we talk about it for a second to delay install time to make sure we can
count the ball down.
You know what I mean?
I wouldn't have to say that, you know, actually, I don't have anything to say.
No, that that's the organ.
Okay.
I'm not a good elf.
The prompter is fucking slow.
So just give me a minute.
Go on.
Get it on there, please.
He's actually lost it.
So I'm just trying to delay a little because we got like what?
40 minutes.
Jeremy's going to regret that one.
Yes, I am.
I already do.
I don't need time to regret what I just did.
It's live.
What am I supposed to do?
Go back and pretend you didn't see that.
I was going back to the bullshit that I did earlier in my brain and decided it
was a good idea to say I'm not I'm I'm not a good elf.
When you see something thousands of times, it just puts it into your brain.
It's just it's just there.
And the whole like feet thing, like I was I'm dropping stuff.
Anyways, that's the origins of Jax.
When I did let me tell you something about that bonus game.
For real.
This is like me stalling but not stalling.
This is a real story.
I used to go to the arcade and I used to be I'd had that that video game
home at the home console.
I have never seen anyone do every one of those targets in the bonus game.
Never.
Everybody gets to one.
Everybody gets to one or two and the timer runs out.
I've never seen somebody complete that.
I did it on stream and that had better win for best gaming moment because
that's that is the best thing I've ever done.
The winner for best gaming moment in 2018 is with 31 percent of the vote
beating Jevil first try beating Jevil first try.
It was a sweep.
Destroyed it.
Mother the transition.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm sorry.
Just fucking hold on a second here.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Slow down.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Shmee.
Yeah.
No, that was that was hard.
It was very, very hard.
Doing Jevil was I there was two or three times during that play
through what I was like.
Hopefully you know when you're about to do something really,
really cool and you about you almost drop the ball.
It's like the egg walking contest.
When you get to the very end, you see the finish line.
You have the egg in your hand and you're about to drop it.
You drop the egg on the ground right when you touch the finish line
and it breaks and you lose.
I thought that was going to happen during the Jevil thing and it was
going to be such a disappointment because I was so close.
Worst gaming moment of the year.
So did we lose like we actually gained viewers.
I thought that during the Peter thing that we were going to lose
a shitload.
That's not an analogy.
That's not a worst analogy.
By the way, worst analogy had one nomination and it was and it was
the stupid analogy thing that I have not drunk this coffee in here.
Look, you want me to prove it.
Oh, there's nothing in there anymore.
Fuck.
I can't spill.
Also, I forgot to laugh at the fact that I'm wearing the same fucking
blazer that I was wearing during the green screen stream.
This is coffee.
It's not alcohol.
I just had a little bit of an issue there.
All right.
So anyways, I don't remember what the fuck I was saying.
I don't have one seat.
You don't need more than one suit.
You know how much it is to have a rack of suits in your fucking
closet.
It's like six grand.
No, this was like this was like two hundred and forty five dollars.
And I got a long time ago when I was like 14.
That's why you see it still fits me.
I don't got to get a new suit for what?
Anywho, we're going to do the worst gamer moment of the year.
And there were a bunch of best gamer moments.
And sure enough, yes, there were a lot of worst gamer moments as
well.
Way more worst gamer moments than best gamer moments.
But that's OK.
Let's take a look at the nominees for worst gaming moment of the
year.
Right.
The game that game called my spelling wrong.
Law.
The law and order game.
But you point at people and scream at them.
Objection.
What?
I don't.
I've never played one.
What?
Destiny's law.
Destiny's child.
Dear.
Oh my God.
It's a guy's first and last name.
It's called like Professor Layton.
What is his name?
It's the character's name.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.
A cat in the hat.
What is this?
All right.
Watch this.
You don't think I'm stupid.
What?
I'm what happened?
That's not a door.
What?
Why did this not open?
Why did the door?
I walked right into it.
I don't understand.
What the fuck did I just do?
No, no, no, no, no.
What?
What the fuck did I just do?
Did I just go back?
I just pressed.
No fucking way.
Put it in there.
You know, there's nothing.
There's enough stuff in these.
Where are the diamonds, motherfucker?
I can't get him in the gut.
Why is this guy so good at fighting?
Is this guy just really good at this?
Why is this guy so good?
Give me a knife.
Give me a, give me a.
I'm cutting his fucking head off.
He's gonna fucking kill me.
Uh.
Yeah.
Sure.
I'm so dirty.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
ho ho, ho ho ho boy.
I swear to god!
I've done dumb things before.
I fall in a fucking clutch.
I forgot just how fucking embarrassing that Red Dead Redemption 2, I thought the
The Stole Your Gun thing was, holy shit!
That's the first time I've seen that back since I think streaming that game.
Wow!
Anyways, the worst gaming moment of the year is going to go to, with 22% of the vote,
dying to a creeper in Minecraft.
Dying to a creeper in Minecraft wins.
I was shit-faced on one of the last streams at my old house,
and I played Minecraft for 10 minutes and I was looking at a wall and died to a creeper.
That's the worst thing I've ever done this year?
It's a creeper? Is it that? Is it that? That's a huge problem, apparently.
Dying to a creeper in 2018 and hearing the hiss and not doing anything about it.
I was shit-faced. That doesn't... What?
A recount. We can't do a recount now. It's too late.
We only got 30 minutes to go until the ball drops.
I've got to get a song ready. Hold on a minute here.
Here comes a stall.
Let me get a good song. What's it called?
Old Lang Syne?
I need to get a ball drop behind me.
Hold on. Just wait, wait, wait.
I've got to make sure I get the right one.
I've got to have a ball drop.
I'll get it. Just hold on. I've got my computer here.
I mean, you know that I have the computer here.
How do you spell Old Lang Syne?
A-U-D-L-O-A-U-L-D-L-A-N-G-S-Y-N-E.
There it is. Got it.
Okay, make sure we've got this queued up.
And then I need a ball drop in here.
So let's go with ball drop.
I wonder if I can get a ball drop.
Well, these are balls, technically.
They are technically balls.
But they're not the correct kind of balls.
They'll have to do.
Let me just get those queued up real quick.
We've got the best categories coming up.
We've got worst stream of the year.
We have worst category. We have worst breakdown.
Worst joke, best joke.
You're going to want to stick around for those ones.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
We've got 30 minutes.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
We're good.
Let me just add these media sources to make sure we...
You know, don't do...
Hold on. What is this?
I'm going to have a couple of doctors here.
Hold on.
Somebody's going to think these are real people here.
Look, I'm here with my friends.
I've got my friends here.
We're all doctors here.
Okay, prove how tall you are.
Oh, yeah. I'll prove how tall I am.
The name of this clip was called Six Foot Doctor and 5'11 Doctor.
You know what I'm saying?
Let's make sure they're in the right spot.
See?
They don't even come close.
Y'all go stand right next to them.
That makes me so much smaller.
I didn't think about that.
It's okay.
I'm going to put them over here.
They make more sense right here.
Let me see.
What the fuck are you working on over here?
What does it say?
January 23, 2019?
Fucking book.
I forget what I was even doing.
Oh, right. I was getting the ball drop.
Ball drop.
I can't have this play on screen yet, so I've got to be careful.
Hold on.
I'll just play this song for you.
Just listen to this for a little while.
You know what? While I do this...
No, I can't do that. I was going to play the worst sounds again.
There we go. Here it comes.
I just don't want you to see it yet because
it's the only ball drop I can get that's like a royalty-free ball drop.
That's in the right place.
All right.
Almost ready. Almost ready.
I just need an old Lang sign.
Just wait. I'm telling you, it's going to be worth your time.
There it is.
All right, I'm good.
The next category is worst category.
No, don't play it yet.
Don't play it.
It's not time for this yet.
Is this the right song?
Okay, that's the right song.
All right.
The next category is worst category.
This one's not going to take very long
because the worst category...
Let's take a look what they are.
Yes, I am well aware that this looks like
a protein bar company logo,
but that's fine.
You got worst beater, best beater, worst category,
best ice cream flavor,
worst overall stream, and worst hair.
Everyone thought these were the worst.
I would probably agree with you.
Worst category.
And the worst category...
That just scared the shit out of me.
I thought these were real people.
I thought they were real people standing behind me
and I was like, how the fuck did they get in here?
And the winner
of the 2018 worst category
of the worst category
with 33% of the vote
is...
this one.
Worst category.
That's the worst category.
It wasn't as funny as I thought it was going to be
What like filler
for the rest of the fucking stream?
33% of the vote, but
okay.
That's the worst category and I spent the time
writing on this too.
Take a look at that. Put that over there.
Like take a look at this one. See?
It's funny because it's meta.
Is somebody taking a shower?
No, that's applause. Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have come to the
meaty meat and potatoes of the award
ceremony stream.
Only got one, two,
three, four
more categories remaining. These are big ones.
So we're going to have to get a couple more bananas over here.
Somebody said hurry up!
Sorry, I tapped it there.
So I got four.
Why don't I have a clap
emote? Why don't I have a clap
emote? Alright, we got
just over 25 minutes or so
until the new year
eastern time. And let me peek at this one.
Ooh, okay. The nominees
this is worst breakdown
on stream. To give you a little
bit of context, worst
breakdown is any time that I actually got truly
upset or
not joking around, you know, like
oh, I can't believe I just got killed
there. No, no, no, like real actual
breakdown. Caught on
camera. Here are the nominees for worst breakdown
of the year. Yeah, sorry
I don't have 50 hours at
Mario Tennis. And you know what?
I ain't going to lose very much sleep from being
bad at Mario Tennis. I don't think
that's going to affect me very much. I don't
think that's going to be a big deal. I'm just
painting all day like I'm
fucking fuming right now. Like I
am so unreasonably
angry right now. I have to restart. I should have just
fucking, I should have just bought
Breath of the Fucking Wild.
What? Are you serious?
Holy shit, there's a button, there's a B in here.
Oh, fuck me. Goodbye. Tell me if it's in
here. I'm going to leave the room for like a minute.
Tell me if it's in here, for real. I'll be back
in like a minute. Tell me if it's actually in here.
It's real, it's real.
It's there, right there. As
stupid as this level is
and it's just like, hey, I have an idea.
Let's just like make it impossible.
It's the only level in
the entire two game
series where you can't
walk out of the door. In the whole
two game series.
Fuck that stupid item.
Do you see how many times I swung over or
through somebody? Like, oh my god.
Only use that for bosses. For any reason. Don't ever do it.
Ever. Only use this weapon because it's good.
This is a good weapon.
It doesn't take three seconds to swing and you go
let me swing over your head. Whoa.
Did you duck for a second? Let me just, whoa.
Swing around like a fucking yo-yo.
Oh my god, that weapon eats ass.
Wait, I'm alive.
I'm alive, I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive.
No, don't eat that.
He's confused.
So am I. He's like, I don't know what
you want me to do, dude.
Wait, hold on.
Hey, hey.
Hey, lights and camera and action.
I fucking need to turn these two off.
Uh, so
best breakdown of the year
is, you could have seen
this one coming.
Worst breakdown of 2018
with
30% of the vote, the Wasp encounter.
The Wasps.
Worst breakdown of, that's
yeah, I would argue
Mario Tennis was more anger.
I mean, which one was more of a breakdown
though, I wonder.
Mario Tennis is also, by the way, up for
worst stream of the year.
Just in case you were wondering.
30% of the vote for the Wasps.
Okay. Oh, boy.
Do you see what we got
here?
We've only got the last three
categories. We've got
worst overall stream, best joke
taking more than five minutes, worst joke
taking more than five minutes. We're down,
we're almost ready to count down the new year.
Add more doctors.
You know, that's important. Let's get a couple more
doctors. Now, is this the
only doctor that's on a green screen?
Hold on, hold on.
Doctors green screen.
Excuse me, doctors surrounding me.
What the fuck is this?
Okay, hold on. Oh, no.
Oh, no, this is not.
This is what we're doing.
There's so fucking many of these. These are like
character selection screen people.
You'll see what I mean in a second.
Are you ready for like choose your doctor
character in a video game?
Let's get this one, this
one. Let's get like four
more. That one's creepy. Let's get this one
too. And I'm gonna get like
a hospital in the background.
Why am I? No, this is an award
show. This is not like
Dick around for. Yeah, maybe actually kind of is.
Alright, let's get these ones
added. Alright,
color key them in.
Alright, you go back here.
He's huge. He's actually
kind of small now. Alright,
get a couple others.
You can be a little bit taller up here.
Where'd you go? Oh, right.
All these doctors are so concerned.
Actually, I kind of want to be like back here too.
Like there's some 3D space going on.
And put the. No, I'm not putting the tent up
again. I had a breakdown
from that one. Okay.
There's another one. We got one more.
I think I got one more doctor to put up here.
Wait, what?
This is the same doctor. Now I need one more
other doctor. Put up the fucking
tent. God damn it.
Alright, let me put the tent up.
It's the end of the night anyway, so
hold on. There's a couple others
here.
I hate this. I need a different
background. I gotta go get like a forest background.
Put the guy with the needle
in the front. Why do you want
the guy with the needle in the front?
I don't even know which one he is.
I have so many sources. You have no idea.
There's like 30 sources. I don't know
which one he is. I don't even know where the ball drop is.
No, that's an old Lang Syne.
I'm not ready for that yet. It's
Eastern.
Not yet. I need a
forest. I want one more
doctor in the forest. This one's
good. And then we're ready
to go, you know what I mean? We're ready for the ball
drop in the forest with a bunch
of fucking doctors. Why is
there a bunch of doctors in the forest? That's why I'm celebrating
my New Year's Eve party.
So where is that one?
This is called a handsome
friend?
Handsome friend doctor.
This one talks. Is he saying
anything? What's he saying?
Is he talking? Almost done.
He's inside the tent
right now.
Replace me.
Okay, this is getting fucking
weird. Hold on. I gotta
bring that guy up
a little bit. No? There we go.
Which one?
Where is this guy?
Where is
this guy?
Make needle guy huge in the front. I'd love to
find out which one of these sources he is.
Handsome doctor. Thoughtful
doctor. No?
I don't know where the fuck. I don't know where he is. What time is it?
Okay, we got 15 minutes. Hold on.
No, that's me. No! I need him.
There he is. Finally.
I'm just like back here.
Okay, I'm okay being back here like
hanging out. Okay, I need a forest
quick. Forest, forest, forest, forest,
forest, forest, forest.
Anyone of you guys know why you get a forest around
here? Forest.
Images. Whatever the first one is doesn't matter. Right here.
Does this have like a, I think this might have
This is like AccuWeather. What?
I'm almost done. We're so close.
Alright, I'm almost there.
Got it. Got it.
Got it. Right there.
Get it on the desktop. It's called got it.
Here we go. I'm ready for the new year. Holy shit.
That's such a tiny image. Why is it
so small? This just doesn't fit though.
That kind of does. I'm like the
head doctor. This guy
is taking up my fucking limelight here. Get out of
the way. That's better.
Alright, the nominees
for best
joke taking more than five
minutes to set up. We're getting close.
Best joke taking more than five minutes
to set up here are your nominees.
They taste like cotton candy.
I'm all over.
Gus, I got bad news for you.
There's only one sex. I'm turning this
off. I'm gonna fuck out of here.
I had to get rescued by two other balloons.
You guys know when you go
on a cruise ship
and the cruise ship goes around
and you get to the certain waters where
you can play casino games,
there's no loss up there.
When you get to 5,000
feet in the air, there's no loss anymore.
I got stuck.
Hold on. This is kind of
cool looking though. Look out there,
man. It actually looks really
good on the 3DS.
I ordered a few pizzas. So I ordered
pizzas. And then you left and you didn't
pick up the bill. Okay, and the bill was
$100,000 fucking dollars.
The U-Haul trucks show up full of pizzas.
Okay.
So this is what we're talking about now.
He wants the almighty dollar.
This is what he's here for.
He's here for money.
Oh shit.
Don't go to the top row.
Please don't go to the top row. I can't take it.
I can't take it.
Oh shit.
Don't go to the top row.
Kill please.
I'll do anything for the top row.
Oh shit.
Dad just lives in the walls.
Imagine if Mrs. Doubtfire, instead of
I want to get back with my family,
I'm going to dress up as like an old lady
and be their nanny. It's
I'm going to build a house in their house
and listen to them and try to talk to them
through the walls and stuff.
Wall dad.
Everyone keeps asking about it. I'm not going to answer that question.
It's very lewd and disrespectful.
12 inches.
Yeah.
I think it's truthful.
See.
I don't even need any more questions.
That's it.
Do you understand? Do you understand
I don't need any more questions after that one?
This time it wasn't
I had the headphones in. This time it's not the doctors
that started me. It's the fucking noise
that keeps playing every time I come back.
Best joke
of the year that took more than five minutes
to set up. There was a lot of
a lot of people went
into those jokes.
Why is a tent moving?
I can't even do a serious
like oh a lot of time went into some of those
and they were a lot of fun.
It's impossible to do like a
hey let's do like a heart to heart with
seven doctors in the room.
And two people in a tent.
So ladies and gentlemen the winner
of the best joke of the year taking more than five minutes.
With 22% of the vote
it is
I didn't say anything yet. Wait stop.
The hot air balloon to Las Vegas.
Hot air balloon
to Las Vegas.
22% of the vote. Clap doctors
clap.
Why am I getting booed?
I don't hear any booze. Do you hear booze
here? I don't hear any booze.
Do you? Do you hear booze?
Any of you?
Do you hear?
I don't hear any booze at all.
That took a long time
to do. It took a lot of patience
from a lot of people that had no idea
what the fuck I was even doing so
I'll take this. I'll take fucking two
of them for that. So with the best comes
the worst. The worst
joke of the year taking more than five
minutes to set up. Peek the mic.
I'm not going to peek the mic.
The nominees for worst
joke of the year.
This one. This one. This one. You can't
make that joke.
I haven't had enough time.
Look, at 12.01 Eastern
time I'm going to scream into the microphone so
you can guarantee you'd have something for next year.
The worst joke taking more than five
minutes to set up for 2018, here are your
nominees. The worst joke
of the year.
Do we have to start?
I don't want to break this. This is going to a
library, god damn it.
Let's get a straight track.
He just went like
this.
He just went like this.
Shit.
Facecam. Oh my god fine.
Jesus Christ.
That was fucking ridiculous.
I got
these bags though.
Whatever. No fingerprints, no witnesses.
Nothing. I'll let you know when it
turns up. Alright fucking bye.
Bye.
If I can't see where I'm going I will end up in
a vault somewhere.
Most people will never know
anything beyond what they see with
their own two eyes.
Awful movie.
Because most people will never know
anything beyond what they see
with their own two eyes.
I did it exactly. I didn't even need to watch
the movie. Somebody clip it
then. Somebody show me that clip
of me saying that and then we'll play them at the same time.
That's not it.
I don't think anybody has it.
Let me turn this up.
This is very important. It's an incredibly important
part of the story.
B clip. Alright never mind.
Wait.
Someone's got it. Not the clip.
We're not doing that again.
I can just do it right now.
Why do I need a clip? Why do I need
audio from in the past?
I can just do it now. Most people
will never know anything beyond what they
see with their own two eyes.
No. That sucks.
I'm not doing that. I didn't have effort in
that one. No.
Yikes. No. That's it.
That's it. We're going back to playing Spiderman 8.
To the right.
This is just like bringing a couch into somebody's house.
I don't want to have to turn it upside down.
He's out.
He's out. Okay. Let the games begin.
Don't want to get him stuck against a wall.
Oh this.
I didn't do that. Somebody got really impatient
behind me. What do you mean riot?
What are you rioting for?
560 fucking meters.
That was a good movement.
That was nice and fluid.
Try to get that again.
Good volley. Good volley. Good volley.
Oh. Perfect volley.
It's too dark. It's too dark. Better view.
We're going to wait for daytime.
Oh shit. He's going to fall.
He hits. Water hits here.
And what does it do?
Bang. Bang. Bang. Blah.
All over the floor. Oh that's great.
Splashes back. Gets all over you. Gets all over
your shoes. And then you're stepping.
Here's another problem. When you go
into a public bathroom and you walk up to one of these fucking
like tank urinals
you're stepping
in a dozen
people's piss.
Leg here and leg here.
This is somebody standing here. Right?
This
has a trough. Guess what happens
if the leak drips down here?
Oh what's that? It catches down here and it's angled.
Goes right down in the hole.
Not going down here. Not going on here.
Going here.
Hey! Okay.
Worst joke taken more than we
have less than speaking. I will do this
after. Ladies and gentlemen we got
two minutes until
these people are freaking me out. Two minutes
countdown until
New Year's Eve. New Year's Day.
1201. It is
currently just under
midnight. This is the last
thing you're going to see in 2018.
Are you ready?
Hold on. I gotta make sure I'm ready.
I gotta get bigger. Wrong
person
to make bigger. There I am.
Alright. Get me in the fucking front please.
Okay. Here we are.
Here we are. What do we got?
One minute. Where's old Langstein?
Where is it? And where's the ball drop?
Oh shit. I think. Is this the ball drop?
No. Okay. That's old Langstein. Where's the ball drop?
There it is. Okay.
That's gotta go up in the front. All the way.
Alright. How loud is that? It's gonna be loud.
30 seconds.
30 seconds. Not even.
Let's start the countdown. 10.
No. 20. 25.
20.
19.
18. 17.
Why am I getting. I'm like losing enthusiasm.
17.
10. 9.
8. 7.
6. 5.
4. 3.
2. 1. There it is.
Happy New Year. The ball's dropping.
The ball dropped.
Happy New Year.
What's wrong with this video file?
Oh. There it is. The ball dropped.
There it is.
Where's my source?
Oh honey.
Remember when we went to camp in the fucking woods?
And we watched all those golf balls?
Where am I?
There I am. Happy New Year
Happy New Year everybody.
Have a good one.
Happy. We have a shitload of community subs
just came in and I didn't even see them.
Somebody. Big fat mistake.
Gave 20 community subs. Happy New Year.
It is now
12.
12.01.
Incoming.
I just broke OBS.
Wasn't even loud? Hold on.
Did I get
drowned out by old Langstein?
Holy shit. That's going to hurt somebody's ears.
Turn that down.
That hurt my chest doing that.
Does this thing still work?
Merry Christmas.
No. I'm not doing it louder than that.
I'm sorry guys. I don't want to hurt anybody's ears.
It wasn't loud?
I don't want it to be loud.
I don't want to do that to people.
Now I'm in the tent.
What are you guys doing in here?
Oh sorry.
I put my fucking desk on you.
Yeah.
I bring my laptop into the woods.
I know the whole ruffin' it thing.
But man, I gotta check my fucking emails.
Alright.
So we had a category to do there.
I can hear fireworks outside.
I have so many fucked up sources here.
The winner of worst
joke taking more
than five minutes to set up.
With 39% of the vote
sleeping dogs
pushing a guy into the ocean.
39%
of all of you said that was the worst thing I did all year.
39%.
I actually thought that was fun.
What am I hearing?
What's this noise I'm hearing?
Is old langs I'm playing at like
minus 100% volume?
Yeah it is.
But let's get this one
off because we got one more to do.
Give me those bananas. That's fine.
Worst joke taking more than five minutes
to set up. We made it to the final
category. Happy New Year everybody.
Last category
of the evening.
Worst stream of the whole year.
We don't, we only get to do this once.
There were some good categories
on here. I'm not gonna peek.
This one. Oh this one.
Don't make me, I'll scream into that mic again.
Louder this time. And I'll put the, I'll turn
the volume all the way up and scream into it. No I won't.
Why would I do that? Why would I like make everybody leave?
There's a shit load of people here tonight too.
Thanks for coming. There is
over 7,000 people sitting here right now.
Thank you. Hope you
have a good time. This was just a
fun thing that I wanted to do.
Really really short notice.
And why don't we like get
real for a second. I know it's hard
to get real with like handsome
doctor behind me. But
let's be real for a second here.
Like come on. I love you.
Sorry. Alright that's fine.
But
I'm like talking to these two people
here and that's whatever. Keep the guy
with the needle. That was slowing
down. My frame rate was dropping.
So
we're on top of another
okay. Double
tent. This is the wicked
witch of the west.
Fucking Dorothy dropped a house on
them. Anyways.
2018 seriously
was the most my channel has grown
ever. And I'm talking both YouTube
and Twitch. And we
joke around like this and do fucked up stuff
like this. But just please know
I can't even fucking believe
there. Like for instance there are seven thousand
fucking people here right now. Last year there were maybe
maybe fifteen hundred
would be at a stream like this. Maybe
maybe under two thousand. The
channel has seen ridiculous growth. Tons
of subscriptions. Tons of money
and shit. And I just want you to know
2019 is gonna be fucking even better.
So I can promise you that.
Thank you everybody. That has
been a part of this community for as long as you have. Thank you
everybody for all the shit that you put up
with me a lot of the times. Thank you.
And
let's go ahead and do it. Much
love to everybody here. The nominees
for worst stream
of the year go to.
I've been
really lately I've been really into
dexterity type finger
cardboard games.
It's kind of a newer genre.
I'm the only Labo streamer.
And I will stand on top of this throne
and drink the mightiest of all
fucking wines. That was a scary
one indeed. Wasn't it boys and girls?
I promise nothing looks
longer. They're leaving. They're leaving. You don't have any
content for them. They don't have any
content they're watching. They're watching a blank stream right now.
You need to put on content
before they all fucking leave.
You've just created a perfect home for
chickadees,
nut hatches, and
finches.
Any of those in Las Vegas.
The only birds that we have here
in Vegas are scorpions. How much would you have?
Okay let's start it. Start the bidding.
Start the bidding.
Start the bidding at 30 cents.
So it's CVS and I fucking saw this
and I was like that's what I'm streaming tonight.
So that's what you get. The Gamer V portable.
Let me be. Hold on.
This thing was less than 20 bucks.
It takes three AAA. No.
Look it's not a seat. Look CVS
sellout. That's not even true. You can get everything.
You can get toilet paper at CVS. What are you going to sell out your ass?
Have you seen anybody
play Mario Tennis on live stream before?
I don't know. Maybe not.
I might be the
first guy.
I should have just fucking bought
Breath of the Fucking Wild.
Good job Nicholas.
Good luck in the first grade next week.
Those are some bad
streams.
How you doing under there? You alright? You guys okay?
So the worst stream
of 2018, worst stream of the year
in what some
would call an upset
with 23% of the vote
the Morphe's Law
and Mario Tennis
stream. The worst
stream of the year.
Worst of the whole fucking year.
Yeah. There it is.
Worst stream of the year.
Thank you.
Thank you everybody. Let me just say.
Yes.
Thank you so much everybody.
We probably should turn to this though.
So during that stream
I had a lot of problems
when we played Morphe's Law on the Switch
which was. I'll get
to it. Stop it.
We played Morphe's Law on the Switch.
Probably the worst game I've ever played.
At least in the last year or two.
I was really frustrated
the fact the game was laggy.
There was no. I couldn't even
play the game really. It was not what I thought it was.
It was fun.
I was already frustrated going into Mario Tennis.
So going into Mario Tennis
I was really bad at Mario Tennis
and I told myself never to play Mario Tennis
ever again. And it turned into
the worst stream I've ever done.
I got really frustrated. I made fun of people.
I was really rude. Some of the things I was saying.
I take a lot of it back.
But I will definitely accept the award
here for having the worst stream
of 2018. Moved on to play Binding of Isaac
and that didn't help because that's a hard game.
Why would you move on to Binding of Isaac?
The whole thing was about 4 hours of absolute dogshit.
So
thank you everybody. Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
Why is there like dust coming off of this?
I feel like I
don't want to breathe this in so I'm not going to break that.
Thank you for that worst
stream of the year.
Runner up by the way if you were curious for
worst stream of the year.
Get that out. Get that
away from me. I don't want that near me now.
It's in my head.
Runner up for worst stream of the year
was
Bugleberry's scary stories.
And I came prepared
by the way.
I thought
I was under the assumption that
the Nintendo Labo streams were going to win.
So what I was
going to do is if it won
I was going to build
the last one
in spite of everybody.
But I don't have to do that now.
So I was prepared for it.
It didn't come close.
I thought everybody had those streams.
Apparently not.
And Bugleberry, if Bugleberry
had won
you bet your ass you would have gotten
an appearance from Bugleberry doing a very
very lengthy set of
probably 40 minutes worth of stories.
No not that long.
But that
actually probably was the worst stream of the year.
Like actually
I like Bugleberry.
I know a shitload of people hate that fucking character.
I like that character.
I think it brings a lot to the table.
Play Mario Tennis now.
I kind of
can't do that.
But
there's all your nominees.
The big finale.
Bugleberry builds a Labo
with a tennis racket in his hand.
Bugleberry Tennis.
Ay yi yi.
But happy new year everybody.
Bugleberry plays Mario Tennis.
Should I just like take that
worst streams of the year categories and just do a stream
where Bugleberry plays Mario Tennis,
builds a Labo, and like eats a
birdhouse or something made out of fucking gingerbread.
I mean it might be worth doing.
I just saw somebody say no
please. So that means
it might be worth doing.
But that's kind of
the plan here. I knew this stream was only
going to be a couple of hours.
I didn't even think about this
until very recently.
I'm in Las Vegas on New Year's Eve
and
I'm kind of going to be
fucking screwed.
If I stay here in the
middle of Las Vegas
it is like
there's probably like half a million people
over there.
I have to like get out of here.
Don't show boogers on your fucking face.
It's 2019 fucking worst of already.
Shit!
Everything's fine.
Let me take my suit.
My bananas.
But I will say
end of the stream voice it has to be.
I kind of need to go get some rest.
And by the way
I do have
a friend and a girlfriend
back home that I would
really probably want to spend
the ball drop with.
So there's nobody's here.
It's just me.
So with that
really? That's what you want to do on Christmas Eve?
Build a labo.
Build the labo.
No I have to go.
I can't stick around. I'll get stuck here.
You guys are absolutely worth it.
How about this?
Here's a New Year's Eve
prize for you. Hold on.
But if you're taking off, if that's what you're here for
see you soon. I'm not going to be live tomorrow
but I'll be live the day after so I'll be live on January
2nd. We'll go back
to normal. This was literally just a last
second thing to do. A shit
load of people came together to make this possible. So thank you
everybody that even put an ounce of effort into this
from the nominations to the categories
to the people that were involved. It was
a huge community effort to get this done
in two days. So thank you so fucking
much all you guys.
It's going to be a $200
Uber. I'll fucking swim there.
So I'll give you
how about this? Before I go
let's have a little bit of fun with the screen
for Encore Night. Let's get
this up.
I kind of got to move this out of the way. Actually
I kind of can't. I guess
I can move it forward. I'm going to tip this whole fucking
thing over.
Hold on. Ah the immersion
is ruined. He was
sitting on the toilet the whole time.
In his green painted bathroom.
So there's that.
Well I mean I'm at a desk so
and
three, two, one.
You here for the interview?
No no just sit down. Sit down. Sit down.
Absolutely. What's your name?
Okay alright.
So what is it about this
company that you think that you can add
you know some
worth to? Well we're going to
need a lot of that so it's really
important that you understand.
I need valuable team members.
And what's that?
Okay well I don't think
the position is for you. The position
already has been filled. So
thank you for your resume
by the way which was awful.
It was a terrible resume. So please
get the fuck out of my office.
Loser.
Oh hey come on. Come have a seat over here.
Right here. You got the seat?
Go take a seat. How are you?
So I was looking at your resume.
And it
looks like you've got some. You went to
school? You went to
Harvard? Unbelievable.
That's really really great.
It says here you were a chef.
A chef?
Wow.
I wish I could be a chef.
So anyways also on the back here you drew
a couple of weird
symbols. It looks like
it kind of looks like
penile to me. I'm not sure why you drew
this on your resume. Must have been like
a funny mistake. But we all make funny mistakes though.
So it's okay. I've made funny
mistakes like that before like trying to mess with my
friends. You know drawing like little penile shapes.
And that's fine but I don't
know why you're doing it on your resume.
Now you know I'm going to take a chance.
Yeah with you. You're hired.
Nah I'm just kidding. You're fired.
You're fired. I'm not fucking hiring you.
I just invite people in here.
I invite people in here
to pretend that I'm going to give them a job.
And then when they show up oh fuck up the suit I'm
wearing. I tell them to fuck off.
Like I'm doing to you.
Sneakers.
Alright so this is like a little bit
of space right here. Casual
Friday. I don't know how to fucking
dress. I don't know how to wear clothes.
You guys think I know anything about this?
You know here's how it works.
It's called let me make sure I'm in the right spot
to get this explained to everybody.
Move this out of the way. Oh
no come on in. Come on in. You're here for the job
right? Yeah no take that
seat right there.
Just don't mind the wood. Don't mind the nice
wood. Yeah it's really
good wood. So I was
looking at your resume.
No no yeah absolutely.
You can say something. Before you say anything
I just want to make sure that you're aware of how strong
I am as your company manager.
This wooden desk you see
is 445 pounds
and with ease I can just get it.
I think I just ripped out the ethernet.
Did I? No I didn't.
Why don't you have a seat? No come on in.
Ethernet's right here. I can't fuck with that.
No come on in sit down. Yeah
somebody will just cut this together.
So this desk here
is made out of wood and you know before
I hire anybody I want to make sure that
they understand that I am a very strong
manager and I can lift up
this is a 450 pound wooden desk.
Just so you know who you're
dealing with.
That's who you're dealing with right now.
I just peeked the mic.
How loud was that? Can somebody clip that?
I'm serious.
I turned the mic down too.
Fuck. Did I actually just peek the mic?
Why can't I open this?
I want to make sure that they understand that I am a very strong
manager and I can lift up
this is a 450 pound wooden desk.
Just so you know who you're
dealing with.
That was really fucking loud.
Lost a hundred viewers.
Happy New Year. It's alright.
Alright. I gotta go.
I gotta get out of here.
I need to clean up and lock up and everything.
Oh I did.
You got access to the green screen.
The manager is strong bit.
What time is it? Yeah it's getting to that
point where I'm gonna get trapped here.
Happy New Year everybody. I'll see you in a couple days.
Thank you so much. I'm sorry I can't really go over
the subs and the bits
but a shit load of people gave stuff.
Let's see if there's any big big ones that I don't want to miss.
I have it open
somewhere. I think I have
ah that's a top banana for you.
That's a hundred community subs.
From the Great Canadian Fuck Club.
That's five hundred fucking dollars.
A hundred community
subs.
Holy shit.
Happy New Year.
You've been contributing insane amounts of
subs and money for a while now.
Thank you.
You did it twice.
Hold on you did that two times tonight?
You did that two fucking times.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Wow. That's fucking crazy.
That's unbelievable.
Thank you so much.
That's crazy amount of subs.
A thousand dollars in subs.
That's unreal. Thank you.
Two fucking hundred subs.
Jesus.
Great Canadian Fuck Club.
I don't know what to say.
That's so much.
Mod Kyle and Fuck Club.
We also had
fifty dollars a few minutes ago here.
This is where you bring out the champagne.
Right?
Yeah. Champagne kind of got lost in the
try to get stream on
on time.
Because I had to be fairly on time tonight.
I couldn't just turn the stream on.
Give me another hour to set up.
I had to be on time.
Getting all those videos compiled and
all them ready into the stream and everything.
Champagne popping
was not really on the list
of priorities.
But you know it's alright.
I'll have a glass of champagne when I get home.
For you guys.
Because this year was all about
you guys. And next year will be even
more. Even better.
Paul Masson thank you so much for the fifty fucking dollars.
I think that's all the big big ones.
Make sure I didn't miss any others.
Because this is from two hours ago.
I don't see any there.
Ones that I really really want to make sure I touch on.
Inspired by the
French excellence.
Are you going to do a traffic stream?
Now I've got to put something else back here though.
I don't know. That's the wrong thing.
That doesn't matter.
I've got no outro's. I've got no
outro screens or anything.
So happy new year everybody.
And all you guys that are on mountain
or central coming up here.
Happy new year to everybody in North America.
Happy new year to everybody that already passed.
All the Europeans
have all celebrated
already.
Everybody in Asia. Everybody
around the world. Happy new year.
I'm going to go drink a glass of champagne.
And I'm going to take a rest.
Happy new year.
I'll see you guys in two days.
I'm not going to stream tomorrow but I'll stream the next day.
And that's it.
Love to you all. I'll see you next year.
I'll see you next year.
That's the joke that everybody's making tonight, right?
Good night. Take care.
See you in a couple days. Ta ta for now.
I hate the sound of tape.
I'm sorry guys. This is like turning on an oven
for me. I don't like ovens. I hate turning on an oven
and it like freaks me out. I like this box in your house
that heats up to like fucking 500 degrees. I don't like it.
It's weird and it's gas. This is also, I don't like this.