What am I looking at here? I'm looking at the chat and I just see somebody's writing like pp and like pooh pooh and shit. Like what? Come on, guys. It's 2019. We're in 2019 now. Come on. We're not doing that anymore. Really? Not on my live broadcast. Not on my livestream. You know what I'm saying? You know what I'm saying? You know what I mean? All right. 2019 resolution. I'm going to stop saying at the end of every four sentences. You know what I mean?
I'll try. Other New Year's resolution. I am not going to say we did. We did the award for it. The word that is the it is the it is the first name. Not doing it anymore. That was fun in 2018. You know what I mean? Well, hope you had a good new year. Hopefully you're rested. Hopefully you had fun. Hopefully you were responsible. We're in 2019. So this is technically the first stream in starting in 2019 because
yeah, I streamed in 2019, but it started in 2018. Welcome to the first stream of the new year. And we're going to kick it off with a good one because this is Metal Gear rising. Revengeance. Is that a real word? How can you have vengeance be twice like a revengeance? Isn't vengeance just already something you do? So this is Metal Gear. Two vengences. Revenge vengeance. But anyways,
this is a game that's been requested a lot of times and figured because just kind of want to play something, hang out for the new year. It was either this visceral cleanup detail or back to Kenshin. We did a little poll. It was pretty close. So this did end up winning. Dermot, you need to learn to parry. You noob. Ha ha ha ha ha ha. I haven't even done anything yet. You can't make that joke until you see it happen. So what if I do really good with parries? What if I'm just
then you're going to look real silly in like 30 or 40 minutes, aren't you? Dermot, I just got banned from RuneScape for cheating. Well, why are you cheating? Why are you cheating in RuneScape? Don't do that. Come on. I just got, but cut that out. He learned from me. When have I ever, I don't cheat in video games. When have I ever cheated, truly cheated in a game? It hasn't happened. Safe scumming is not cheating.
Turn on the face cam or riot. My face cam is not even hooked up. It's sitting over here and not plugged in. So it's not going on. No, I'm not doing a face cam. Just pretend that that's me in like the fucking dentist suit. You know what I mean? The me with like the dentist thing on my mouth. That's me in there. I was going to say, uh, all right, starting off the new year. Great. We're going to start the story. This is like a four hour game, right? I'll blow through this and fucking free.
So I don't just give a hundred dollars, a hundred dollars from Collie Brady, 106 hours. If you're a bad, I'll do it too. Okay. Time me a happy new year. Jerma hope 2019 is a good one for you. Love from Ireland. Jerma heart. Thank you so much. Collie Brady. Thanks for your a hundred fucking dollars. A hundred. God. I didn't really touch upon on the New Year's Eve stream because I would just had to, I had to get out of there. You know, I got to get out of here, but totally shit guys.
You guys are fucking incredible. Thank you. So let's start metal gear rising. I've got a controller plugged in. Does that mean I'm bad? New game. Normal, easy. I'm not going to play it on easy. I'm not playing this game on heart. Okay. Why would I play on heart? No, I'm not going to already ruin the stream. Normal. Hard with a face cam. I'm not going to play on heart. I don't play gay. I don't do this on heart. The developers designed an experience and here's how people design video games guys from some
body that's in the industry. You know, I died. I've had my hand in it a few times. Normal is how all the developers, all the programmers on people like that are working on computers of the design. This is the game that they wanted you to play. They made this this way. Easy is all right. Like you, like it's, you don't have to like really worry about it. Just enjoy it and press X a bunch of times and you'll be fine. They made this for the super humans. Hard. This is the way the game,
it's like times two speed from my understanding. When you put the game on hard, enemies are at times two speed, times two health and times two damage. I don't want to do that. Bullshit. You just suck. Hey, I beat, I beat fucking dancer. First try dark souls three. I beat flame lurker. First try. I beat Jevil. First try. So excuse me. I mean, I did, I did lose to pinwheel like 30 times, but that's because I was like fucking, I had like a headache that day. I'm doing, I already did it. It's normal. That's fine. I don't, you can call. I'm playing on normal.
Look, if it's too easy for me, I'll go back. I'll go. I'm just going to play on normal. I want to, I want to enjoy the game the way that the violent the developers begin with a quick warmup. Shall we? All right.
Is it really that much different?
Am I a chicken? No, it's going to be fine. If it's too easy. Look, I can just go like this and turn it on. Look at, look at this options. Hard can be turned on. What? Right? Hard on. It's not that big of a deal. All right. Our right trigger is ninja run. This is kind of cool.
Swinging your blade while dashing, for example, or striking your foe. I know, I know. Everybody's already saying that that's me in the corner over there. And that's funny, but not really. That feels fluid. Is this one of those fluid games? It feels like a fluid game.
Why would I need to parry when I can just do this? Can I play through the whole game doing this? He's already bad. I just turned on the game and I learned how to run.
I just learned how to run. Can I have like even five seconds?
So bad. Oh my god. I'm so glad I'm not doing this on hard.
What is it? What button is it? Oh, I got hit.
He thinks there's a block button.
Oh, is there a dodge? See, look at this. Look.
Light attacks on your own in the same direction. Oh boy. Thanks for coming to the stream, guys.
I'll see you next time.
Push left stick in the direction of an enemy attack and press X at this perfect moment to use the HF blade to parry your foe.
Like, they're talking about like this, right? Left stick, not trigger.
I don't walk up. Okay, I see. In the direction of an enemy attack, so it can be left, right, up, down. Hold left trigger.
How long am I supposed to do this for? I think I got him. When am I supposed to stop doing this? Does he have a health bar?
Oh, all right. He's dead. Hey, put that guy in a stew.
This guy's fucked.
Carefully aim your strike. Okay.
Is there a dodge roll? Is it the Raze? Game of the Year!
All right, let's parry. Yeah, I got it.
Don't do that to me. Camera? Oh, what the fuck's with the camera? I heard that was a complaint in the game.
I want his brain. I want his brain. Give me his brain.
That's kind of insane. How am I supposed to do that? Do I get more points if I do it like 40 times?
Hey, somebody chop up that brain and put it in a stew.
All right, I gotta calm the fuck down. It's been like 10 minutes.
I'm gonna expel all my energy in like fucking five minutes and like go to bed.
2019 Jerma is not as good as 2018 Jerma. It's been 15 minutes.
You changed.
There he is.
So, Whiz Snake.
He's got a snake mouth. Does he open that snake mouth up and eat something?
There's gonna be a joke where he eats like a hot dog or a hamburger or something. He like unhinges his jaw and eats a big piece of food, right?
There's a joke that has to be in the game.
This is a serious game.
By the way, Mr. Lightning Bull is the worst name. That's like a child.
Making up a terrible superhero name when they're playing pretend in the backyard.
Mr. Lightning Bull!
Uh oh. Boss fight.
It's Snake. It's Snake, isn't it?
This takes place like 4,000 years in the future, right?
There he is.
Nah, I'm not even cool.
Everyone had like a face cam on when they played this game. My screen probably was like, whoa!
I don't fucking care. You're so cool.
I can't wait to see this snake.
Exit.
Quiet compared to video game audio file.
Well, it's because it's a cutscene.
The cutscenes are always way louder in every video game.
They pre-render all these out and then the guy that's making the videos has the map plus 50 DB.
And they just put them in. They don't even edit them. They don't even care.
They rendered this in Final Cut.
That's like a .mp4 and they just gave it to their boss.
Here we go.
Do I weigh 400,000 pounds?
He's just naked.
Turns out it was just a ghost. Ah, now that is what we call...
I'm not going to say the E word.
That box only costed me one dollar.
What did I get? What did I get? What did I get?
Oh, it's common, but it's okay. Cool.
I forget how to play.
You jump with A, right?
Here we go.
What if I do blade attack on somebody, right?
Gun?
I got a minimap in the corner.
Should I try to parry? Do I get points for parrying and shit?
Like, I don't understand. Do I have to parry and then...
That guy's a gun.
Should I wait?
Oops.
Alright, that guy's a gun. I'm just trying to tell me to kill him.
Cut him off! Cut him off!
You can do it, but why is it not coming off all of his body parts?
Got it. Parry.
It's going to be really easy to kill this guy.
Hold on. Stay right there.
I want to parry.
Now, does it do it automatically or do I have to hold it like afterwards?
I guess not.
Perfect parry?
Of course I did.
If you can't cut through the barricade, try defense, huh?
I don't understand how to get through this.
You can't... shit.
Nah, that's it. I'm out of here, guys. Thanks.
I don't fucking know how to do this.
What if it was just left...
Here it comes.
It's Mothra!
No, that's a Metal Gear, isn't it? That's Metal Gear...
Wait, don't tell me that's Metal Gear Rising.
No, that's the name of this game.
That's Metal Gear Ray.
It's Metal Gear Ray, right?
I know these. I've played these.
This is the gear check to determine if I can play the game or not.
I don't care.
I'll just let him go.
I thought somebody sucked him from the other side.
So you're Jack.
What do you want with the Prime Minister?
I want him dead.
Nothing personal, of course.
That's Winston's voice actor.
Africa's just getting a bit too peaceful.
What?
Business ain't been the same since they shut down SOP.
A clean break from the war economy.
Some of us like that economy.
How's an honest warmonger supposed to make a living?
This is your answer.
What does he say?
Science is the most necessary emotion of all things.
What's his dumb voice line?
I won't. Not while he's still useful.
So long.
You get back here. I'm going to one, two, three, one, two, three you.
I'm going to one, two, three, X, one, two, three, Y. Just you wait.
All right, I'm so pumped up for this.
Look at the legs.
One, two, three, one, two, three.
Got it.
One. I didn't get it.
I didn't get one, two, three.
One, two, three.
Okay, get out, get out.
Don't do more than that.
What am I doing?
I'm just making somebody's YouTuber logo from like 2014.
My logo.
The left leg.
Yeah, I understand everybody.
Well, that was his left leg.
I'm talking about his left leg.
What the hell are you doing?
That hit me. Stupid game.
Harry?
Can I actually carry his legs?
This is only for regular monsters.
All right, I'll try.
I'll carry this leg of Ryan, okay?
There you go.
What a game.
Oh, what a god of a gamer.
Not really. I'm going to really focus on that.
Like they do in the WWF.
I'm going to focus on the leg that is in the brace.
Maybe I should just get him bolted.
Get bolted legs.
Okay, but you keep doing that.
Turn his other elephant foot into...
Yeah.
Got this.
What? Yeah, I can just carry everything?
I'll carry.
Okay, I'm going to carry whatever he's doing right here.
Oh, I did get it.
Okay, I didn't.
All right, that's good to know.
Whoa.
I don't think I can carry that.
YB?
Oh, do I tap this?
Because the rock music...
Picking him up and swinging him around.
I just so longed him.
I did the so long Bowser thing.
I'm going to do desktop testing.
B.
It's always a B, guys.
Don't you understand?
Where's my level ups?
Any normal human B would have puked by now.
There, get him.
All right, it's a chase sequence.
Use your ninja run.
Probably, that's what I'm doing.
Oh, I did...
Just come on.
That would have been awesome if I accidentally perfectly timed that.
I thought it was...
I thought it was a climb up sequence or something.
You can't give me shit for that.
Actually, it would have been faster if I just walked up a part of the stairs.
Here's Ray again.
There, you cheat.
It still works.
Hurry up and kill the big monster so I can get some scales from the Monster Hunter World reference.
Do I block this?
Okay.
I have to slide underneath it?
Oh no, okay.
Is this a jump rope?
Do I have to jump over that?
I'm stuck in the ground.
What is this?
What the hell is this?
What?
What the fuck just happened?
Get it!
I get to see what he really looks like.
Perfect parry.
Just call me Perfect Parry...
Paul.
I was going to say something else.
I've got to...
Um...
What?
Hold the right trigger.
Am I supposed to be swinging at these?
What am I looking at?
What am I supposed to be doing?
Oh, ninja run.
Okay.
Whatever.
He starts fucking crunching me and my blood and guts are everywhere.
My legs are ripped off and I'm like fucking mangled and shit.
I was trying to do a thing.
Wait.
Why is title so close there?
I was just being a dickhead.
Lost on the first level.
I was fucking around.
I was like jumping.
Sorry, I've played...
Yeah, guys, guys.
Relax.
I've played this game on iPad like ten times.
This is the...
I'm sorry.
I'm playing the most downloaded free game on the App Store right now.
Oops.
All right.
So we're going to stay over here.
It's the next big...
Watch out.
It's the music.
All the way down.
That's not good.
My god.
Sell that iPad.
He even died three times and I got a B.
He's still running away with this guy.
B for bad.
How about B for banned for life from the channel?
Got him.
He's done.
That's what I would do with this all day.
I would just go to a giant open field and just slide around like that.
Until I was at the point of physical exhaustion.
I would do it every day.
That's what I would do for a living.
I was about to just run off the side and just...
I don't do the...
That's just 2019.
We don't make those jokes.
What?
2v1 fight right now?
Remember, this next boss fight is easy.
If you don't beat it, you're bad.
Just let me play.
Enjoy the game.
I was looking away for a second.
I thought they were just...
That's what was actually happening.
Good things more is done for us.
Why don't we ever hear speeches about that?
Jobs, technology, a common purpose.
I'm just so unenthusiastic.
You ain't listening.
If I got in...
All we're saying...
Give war a chance!
No!
That was crazy.
Okay.
Let's go!
That was a powerful swing.
Beat Sam or bad streamer.
I'm gonna try.
Just relax.
I love how it's like a game remote.
I'm gonna wait for him to do something.
We're both playing the same game.
He's waiting to parry me.
This is just...
Nice PvP fight.
I'm gonna taunt.
See?
God damn it.
I shouldn't have struck first.
Let's see.
That wasn't even...
I thought it was a cut scene.
I gotta parry more than once.
Okay.
It's like parry, parry, parry.
I gotta parry individually.
So it's parry, parry, parry.
I'm gonna try to get that right.
He's about to lose to Sam.
So, okay.
I get it.
We just have to actually just up the...
Okay.
I'm probably...
I got...
I'm .1% streamer.
Hahaha.
Losing to the easiest bot...
Well, I'm learning how to parry.
I don't even need my game genie.
There's my opening.
He's shooting.
Oh no.
He has one of those action figure things.
Yeah, I think he's supposed to lose here.
This is a joke.
You guys were baiting me.
He's supposed to lose here.
Everyone's talking about how bad I am.
Bleed on him.
Hahaha.
Imagine this is just an elaborate game over screen.
Oh, you're gonna raise the blade up too high
and you're gonna get caught in the ceiling.
Oh, you can't be outside
because it's right up.
Like Vampire, right?
Lucky devil.
Sit up a little too high
and get stuck in the ceiling.
He's just like...
Kept you waiting, huh?
That snake!
The snake's behind the wheel right there.
What a fun cameo.
That snake before the cigars.
This takes place like 400 years ago, right?
Is this a blind playthrough?
I...
never played this game before.
Metal Gear Solid V is the first one, right?
Yeah.
The story of Metal Gear Kingdom Hearts.
They sell a product that you can download
into your brain, though.
I tried to...
chat, I'm confused.
Which one is Snake?
Oh, well...
I'm sure that it'll pop up eventually.
So I got...
Chapter...
Difficulty Normal.
Chapter Combat.
BB.
Time.
BP.
Rank B.
Bonus B.
How many Bs are on total BP?
Alright.
A whole lot of Bs on the screen.
This is gonna be kind of a fun game.
Three weeks later.
Oh, I know what this is.
This is the lolly with it all.
Come on.
I make a Metal Gear reference?
While playing Metal Gear and I get a bunch of question marks and chat?
Huh?
Oh, nooooooooooo don't.
Ah, okay, we're good.
So which one of these guys is the secret bad guy?
He looks like a secret bad guy.
He just does.
Yes, enemy cyborgs should provide plenty of MCFC electrolytes once you slice them open and extract their fluids.
Alright, gain like 50 pounds and then do what Dr. Eggman costed.
And their left hands, if you please.
Nobody wants the Eggman haircut.
Why? I don't get it.
That combat data stored on holographic memory typically located in the left hand.
You know when I get older?
Yeah, I really want like the Eggman.
That data is very valuable.
The Dr. Robotnik.
You know what I mean?
So this is the guy you upgraded with?
No, fuck that, man.
See, I'll fold that hair up and put a bunch of grease on it and fold it over the top of your head.
That would look better.
Grow that out really, really fast.
Yeah.
Grow that out really long and then fold the whole thing over and then style it.
I mean, no, it wouldn't.
Only one person has ever made that haircut look good.
And it was Hulk Hogan.
If you are not Hulk Hogan, don't have that haircut.
Or Ben Franklin.
Only two people in history have made that haircut look good.
Hulk Hogan and Ben Franklin.
All right, I'm ready.
So stop the organization here.
I got upgrades from Dr. Eggman.
New suit.
New weapon.
Three weeks later.
The way we drop it.
I was about to do the da-da-da noise, but no.
It's not anymore.
It's 2019.
All right.
What do I get for it?
I got an A for that one?
Did I get S?
Let's go in.
Can I run up walls in this game?
No.
Return it.
Cut the tree.
Oh my god.
Relax.
Cut the tree.
Can I do it vertically?
Okay, cool.
I'm so glad you guys told me to cut the trees.
Can I cut?
Hold on a second.
Whoa.
That's cool.
Combat manual.
What is it?
Codec.
What?
Back.
Who am I calling here?
Kevin?
Looks like a war zone out here.
The palace cleared out quick when Dolzayev's men showed up.
The streets got pretty hot after that.
Destroy cat.
We're definitely going to see a few civilian casualties here.
Luckily, it looks like most of them got out of the city before things got bad.
What do you mean cut the cat?
They basically got control of the entire town and are using the refinery as their HQ.
And that's why we're hitting the plant.
Keep in mind, those cyborgs are contractors.
For most of these guys, this is just a job.
There's a cat on the beach.
In theory, once you eliminate their commanding officer, they should scatter pretty quickly.
Okay.
Good to know.
There's a cat on the beach.
I don't see a cat.
Oh, I see a cat.
So the joke here is you want me to hold L2 and cut up the cat.
Why would I do that?
Whoops-a-daisy.
Good thing you just dodged it.
Because I hit right stick.
Good dodge.
You deserve it.
I'm not going to cut up the cat.
Why would I do something like that?
No.
That cat lives.
Okay.
All right.
Get me away from that cat before I do it.
I'm not cutting up the cat.
No.
Somebody else probably did that.
And you want to see somebody else cut up the cat.
But I want that cat to live.
Because Resident Evil 4 taught me.
Protect the animal.
Protect the fucking animal.
What is this?
What the hell am I doing?
I just ripped out a spinal cord.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's a counterattack.
All right.
Well.
Easy as one, two, three.
That's how you eat.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
I missed.
How do they miss you miss this?
And your film eat with this body. I could take these guys with no eyes
Intel wasn't exaggerating on the cyborg count now. They didn't do this, right?
You wouldn't be able to talk like that if you had that on your jaw
The super justice like this
I mean, yeah
Like a new body. It's really really easy and cyborgs are still you
Thinking people way less risk of collateral damage than your typical UAV strike
And don't forget the PR angle nations start playing Frankenstein with their troops and the public goes nuts
PMC's on the other hand are off the ethical radar
Yeah, they still don't think I'm PMC's in official death tolls
What was the moving the cup SOP out of the picture private militaries needed a new edge on the market?
We got in a way cyborgs are just SOP troops by another name
So she doesn't spill it predictable
But it makes you wonder here comes a classic spill of John these guys
I'm not complaining. They're like walking vending machines
Vending machines full of blood
Easy there Dracula like I said, there's still people people who terrorize and take innocent lives for money
They sewed their fate when they took this job. Oh, whoa, I'm scared
Still that from Bugleberry
Yeah, he's still
Jump-scare into the camera from BF Bugleberry
You sure did
s
Storials now playable view of VR missions. All right head to the indicated waypoint straight up here
Are there any secrets? They're like secret cats over here
And it should be where?
There's got to be random secrets in this game, right?
Cut the billboard cut billboard cut billboard. All right, my god
Cool, you'll need to head inland. But first make your way through this building
Cut car cut car in half the coastline is too long and heavily gun. You must take the inland route
Cut ground. I don't want to do that
The whole the earth will cut in half
Right. This is Boris. Give me your status looks clear. No one in sight. Good. Let's recap the route
You will take as I said the enemy's HQ is in the refinery along the coastline
Dolce I have has been spotted there using satellite photography also on site
Mistral a desperado captain cut Boris
So I go through the city I cross the bridge into the old town
Then head down to the rear of the refinery keep walking
I think I'm gonna walk and be on the phone. We'll probably have a grand reception awaiting you at the old city
Do not let your guard down
All right, so I gotta get up there
Ooh chest plus one repair nano paste
I think I didn't just sprint through wait about anything can open the boxes
Oh shit, you can
Everything can just be chopped up. Thank god. I have a good cpu for this
Okay, uh, so I gotta get up there
No, wait, there's more boxes now. This is couch
It's gotta be perfect right down the middle cut
Fuck I didn't realize that was gonna happen. Right it if you ever get lost use augment mode to check your next objective
So now you can fit it through wait toggle ar using augment mode
You can see enemy positions and the direction in which you should head
Useful for when you cannot find your objective on the soliton radar
Hey, thanks
I probably would have been here for so long
All right, we got another uh chest here
What's that
Bp
I don't want to say but it's just so easy to say b and then p, you know what I mean from two days ago
Hostiles in the lower corridor. I see try to flank them or approach from behind
I'm not doing it. I told you i'm leaving that in 2018
All right, let's get over here and do like the fun move where you jump down and then splash them
Nice
Excellent raiden
What's out here this time i'm gonna deflect rockets and shit
Is this stealth in this game take that main thoroughfare?
You can use augment mode to see where the enemy is located
Your body analyzes radar and ir data to construct your ar display
Some civilians are still in the city. That is not good
When it flashes blue use blade mode blue blue blue black flat blade
Blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah. What are you doing? This area is off limits
That guy's crouching too much
Oh, nice try almost got me
Can I parry the grenade?
All right, who's left you
This guy's a little different
So
Okay. All right, whatever when they're up here
Sands high restart. I killed a civilian. I did not I did no such thing. Oh, it's one of the goat things
Dodge roll
That makes things a lot easier
That guy didn't even exist like I just flipped over into me and turned into nothing
Oh, I tried to do it
What?
Okay
What do I do?
Did I miss something? No, I got it
Blade wait, hold on. Wait, wait when they turn blue I have to press left. Okay
I thought you I thought what you talked about the blue up there when it was full or something
Blade mode when the symbol appears
change sub weapon
recovery
main
Okay, here's grenades
A small quantity of the substance found in cyborg and ug self-repair units that can be used to immediately restore raden's
A life gauge. Okay, so it's heads. He's a heal
And then this is a grenade
the latest in fragmentary grenades
Yeah, yeah
Uh, I get the mouse office. I just dropped the fucking mouse hole
Uh larger and heavier than a conventional grenade requires cyborg great strength to throw it
all right, so
Lb is
Equipped. Oh i'm holding it now. Okay, uh throw it
Where is it?
Well a great place to give me the tutorial for that
Okay, let's go
Oh, that was long. That was a long animation
Oh fuck
Am I supposed to be fighting both these guys the same time?
Where did this guy come from? Oh my god. I'm like getting my ass kicked here. I'm gonna like die
All right. I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do it. What? Why is it not doing it? Did I have not enough power?
There's a guy behind me
I did hold it
Hold blade mode. That's what I was doing
All right. Sometimes I'll do it
Sometimes i'll press like up and x
What the fuck is going on
I thought it was hold it hold it when he does this he's blue. He's blue. This guy's blue right now. All right, he's blue
I hold it when he's blue
That what happened?
The screen also has to be blue
Okay
I just uh, well
Everybody's screaming at me
Do the blade mode tutorial
Well, I haven't done that yet. Is that gonna is that happen soon? They haven't like taught me this shit yet
You shouldn't see most likely an enemy data terminal. Check it out. We may be able to salvage some intel
Let me see
Not wrong is it under help
All right. Hold on a second light attack launcher during light attack strong attack
Yeah, yeah flurry kick
Let me just see these for a second heal the drop y slight pause then x y
Vr missions hold on. I know I just wait wait wait wait wait wait
Um, no, no, no, I don't want to do this yet
Let me get to like the stopping point here. I feel like it's gonna pull me out of the whole game
But I don't know all this stuff. You know what I mean? Like I how am I supposed to know all these things that I?
Have not known
Greeting you missed the terminal. Oh i'm busy looking over here
Show yourself telling people to do the thing that I didn't learn yet
All right, I got this in the hard way. Well, how else would you do it?
I need to figure it out
I can go and do that. I can do the vr thing if I really feel the need to
And you are I am I have just the final fantasy 7 monster
Interface prototype all autonomous ugs feature high level onboard artificial intelligence an additional prototyping to base enables
How big does it download? I possess an intellect 20 30 gig
You don't say
Okay, then what's the meaning of life? Why are we here?
Good bad time that pretty good. I am here to kill you
oh
My god, that hurts. That's it
Pretty simple thinking for such a mighty intellect
I may analyze orders, but I may not disobey them
Should I disobey a direct order? My memory would be wiped
I must destroy you. Is this the same actor doing the same conversation here if you can't use it
Your taunting is pointless
Exterminate
See how badly I need to do the uh, vr tutorial we'll find out real quick
Who goes first?
Probably should have done that
No, target him what whoa
You will die as all of these tools get up here I get up there too
What's he doing? What's that move? He did the blink could I
Oh, he howled in fucking ads
Can I have a pair of the grenades?
Get this away
Back down here
Exterminate your consciousness
And ready here we go get it that didn't work that didn't work. I thought I could do something there
I really thought that was gonna work. Do it
Stop doing that. What the hell is going on turn that off?
I'm trying to all right. I'm getting confused with the animations here
Sometimes i'll do up an x
I must have to not be moving right?
Because sometimes i'll do it and he won't parry
All right. I I held it. I swear to god I did I promise you
Where is he? Where the fuck is he? Where'd he go? Did I not get it?
Superficial damage
I did it
Okay, we're good
So what what was the difference between that and the last one I held it
The next time I do that i'm gonna just hit him once in the toe region. See if I can kill people like that
I gotta see for that one, but it's all right. Don't worry
All right, solve the weapon tutorial is now played. All right, here we go
Let me do let me let me just do them now
Wait, does that does that am I a checkpoint? I am right?
How does one change?
How do you uh, oh, okay. All right. Well, I just took it apparently
I thought I had to change it
Apparently something over here
Have you not played bane? I've never played bayonet. No
Hello chip. Let's go
play that next
maybe
Is there a stealth?
Perfect parry here we go one two
Come on now
I want a perfect parry you dude. Let's go
Okay, i'm not even gonna perfect parry it was point just kill him
Like I may cry isn't the new one coming out soon
May anymore secrets
secret
Got it. Just run like a baby
Oh speaking of running
That that easily he's dead. He's just gone. It's that easy
No screams
No big dramatic finish. No, he just fell off the bridge
I got just I just got stuck on the environment
I got stuck on the lip of the bridge
How did I get stuck on that?
Same spot do the tutorial on the bridge
Oh my god, I guess we keep going
Oh my god
Oh, no, we have to do this again. Fuck. This is gonna be the hardest thing I can do in this game
Is run the bridge
All right. So seriously what is what is the problem here?
Stop jumping. It makes you slow
I didn't jump once
Half of you guys are saying jump and the other half is saying don't jump
Which one is it?
See i'm gonna run that wasn't ready to run last time
Don't lose
Is this bridge is my dumb with bridge? Oh lord
Come on, do it again. Maybe I have to get up closer
Uh kind of maybe
All right, the lock on is just fucking my brain here. Let's get up here
Don't eat them. Don't eat them
Uh, all right. Well that was
Okay
It blinked is it blinking? Is it shooting the?
All right, what?
Where'd he go? Okay
Use that as that's what I was trying to do
I'm just gonna stay down here. What's the point of going up?
uh
Well, there's this on the ground
Do I have that like equipped now the sub weapon
Okay
Interesting
Well, I guess that's you just have to shoot them with the I get it sounds fun fun
I don't know. I got another one goes right somewhere
Is there another one of those rocket launchers?
There is
I need to get hit like one more time
In order to run up them now, you can't fly dick
Conveniently placed rocket launchers. Yeah, apparently
All right
Now i'm gonna do the tutorial
I'm at the checkpoint head to the indicated waypoint. All right, let's go be honest
All right. So this is part of the this is new
All right
So this is I don't know what what I just pressed
Your body comes equipped with a technique we call blade mode. Let's begin by assuming the fighting position
All right fighting position sure now use blade mode to strike all of the targets
Okay
Right
Now remember blade mode exacts a heavy toll on your fuel cells
Replenish your energy by attacking enemies your blade will absorb the electrolytes automatically
Try restoring your fuel cells back to maximum now
Standard cyborgs you can dismember immediately. No problem. Other fools will not fall so easily
You will first need to attack and damage them to some degree
Powerade
So you get it I get it back by damaging people
Makes perfect sense
Cool after I need to get the blade
and now
The zandatsu technique or stab and grab as some call it
Activate blade mode with full fuel cells and you will automatically analyze the ideal cutting position
Executed successfully and you will seize your full self-repair unit and restore some of your quick time event
Try it for yourself. Take the enemy's repair unit before he falls
So I did
That's what the square is for
Oh, okay. I I understand that I got all right. Okay. All right. All right. All right
All right, you have to hit the square. You have to slice through the square. That's how you get that
Next
Approach a target from the rear or above without being noticed and you can eliminate them with a single strike
Did you not know already? Well, we've only seen it like three times
I've only seen that square like three times
Come on
About your enhanced ar enhanced ar add several layers of information to your augmented reality vision
Use it for additional intel on your enemies you missed it new aspects of your surroundings
Just remember enhanced ar is automatically disabled as soon as you attack
Yeah
Head to the waypoint you can see me through walls. All right, he's not even doing this. All I needed to know is the square thing
Because now that makes a whole lot of sense. You have to cut it right
He just leaves I just
All right, this is come across several different weapons in your missions
Best we went over their basic use
Pick up the rocket launcher in front of you. No, I did just I did just figure this out though
You can equip any weapons you acquire by selecting them in the sub weapon screen
Of course sub weapons have a limited number of uses, you know
In this tutorial it has unlimited ammunition, but do not expect this out on the field
You will want to save them for just the right time. I suspect you can hip fire
Try all the sub weapons you come across you find that each has its own unique properties
Now use these weapons to reach the goal point
Yeah, change sub weapon. There it is
I just accidentally
my fucking finger
Console aim by the way
All right. That was fun
Do a rocket jump. You can't do rocket jumps. What are you?
You can't do that
Right in the head
Oh
Is there a way I can quick switch weapons like that or do I have to go to the menu every time?
All right, almost done
Just use the d-pad. I mean that's what i'm doing. I okay right on the d-pad opens this menu
Left on the d-pad opens the menu down on the d-pad up on the d-pad
Does that and have to menu? Okay?
I mean, it's not it's not my fault that this guy's on like a little cube. Okay, he's on a cube
How am I supposed to get that guy when you have a he's on a cube
Okay
I'm serious. What?
I guarantee you didn't do that. I guarantee you did this tutorial. He did the same fucking thing. I guarantee it
Okay, that's a 100 guaranteed
I won a hundred percent guarantee that
Your new enhancements are quite something if I do say so myself now I get the square thing. I'm ready to go
Oh sub weapons suck anyways in this game. All right. Well, that's good to know jokes on you. I didn't do the tutorial
All right, i'm ready customized
That poor guy I that's not what I wanted that happened god damn it
Cut it cut the thing
Got it
No, get it. Got it
What the fuck are you?
oops
Holy shit squards
10 community subs from squards
Holy shit. Thank you
That's a lot
10 community subs
I say I get it. I get I understand it now. It takes sometimes it takes a minute to figure out what you're doing
Like I don't have like an implant in my brain where I download a game
And know exactly how to do everything
It takes a tutorial. Look, it's giving me a little bit of a break
In your left hand and a cyborg with access and uh borrow it
Do you see any cyborgs around here doc? Why not double back check the vehicle route again?
You know back breaking down. No, i'm fine. Who knows maybe you can hitch a ride
Most likely platoon commanders carry correct id data for the gate use enhanced mode to figure out who to hit
All right, we're gonna find
We're gonna find somebody that has the data
This guy does apparently
Well, there's a bunch of people in there
How do you guys not know i'm here
No, no, no, no, no, I didn't get it. I missed it
No, I don't have enough. Okay, whatever
That like little chunk of his body. Fuck
Wait, somebody has the dna. Okay, I cut all around it. All right. Where are you?
Right you you missed them all. What? Well, you just have to fight
Hold on. Wait, wait what you what do you mean? I missed them all
What was I supposed what was I what was I what did I do wrong?
Oh their hands. Oh, I needed to bring their hand back
I was supposed to cut that guy's arm off
And bring it back here
Wow, man, you missed them all holy shit
Really am I not close enough?
Really you missed them all that's never happened before
I'm actually pretty surprised. That's even possible
This early in the game
I'm just gonna have to shoot you with the rocket launcher. I guess wait what? Oh, okay. I just I just cut that
I gotta be quick with that
You're dead good. I need to get a left arm
If you cut all of someone's limbs off, they still try to come after you really
That's kind of crazy
All right, I got the heels
What else we got 3d photo frame, how does that do come on get up there lore. Ooh
Lore everybody loves lore. Don't they?
Snipe him snipe him take the shot take the shot you have it right there snipe him
Unbelievable. I'm a proponent of a few just don't even wear the jacket
You know, why do you have just on your back like that?
What's happening?
Uh text from text from dad I just dodged a new voicemail from dad
All right. I'm heading for the refinery. Good job parrying those cooties
All right, hold on got the fact
What do I got? I got some parts I can put into my body
Body new new new new. All right custom body custom body original body gray fox
white armor inferno armor
Unpurchased all right. I have 35 000 bp
So why would I buy one of these skins that I do anything?
gray fox gray fox gray fox
Functionally equivalent to recent side though. It was terminated as an exoskeleton in these days where they happen in modern cybernetic technology
It could have been taken. So why would I do this? It's just cosmetic
Don't I want to make sure I save my money to buy like new weapons?
I only got one. Wow. Okay. Well, that's two hundred thousand
Like attack power energy use special effect
life
Uh, I got an enhancement here enhance upgrade an updated version of raiden's cyborg body firmware that immediately reshapes his artificial muscular
Whenever he's hit reducing the amount of damage taken
Wow, I mean I want that
Yeah, like endurance plus one
This is 8 000 fuel cell an updated version of raiden's cyborg body firmware
Optimizes power usage represented in the air display as an extended field cell. Uh, yeah
skills
aerial parry
That improves balance when airborne enabling to parry enemy attacks in midair. Uh, okay. Thank you
Faster more detailed feedback to be delivered to his brain synapses this detailed neural feedback allows raiden to freely sidestep enemy attacks in any direction
and counter their aggression
Yeah
Sounds great
Improves reaction speed in his quadriceps enabling a special upward thrust with his weapon held in his foot
That's a dodge roll
Thank god
sweep kick
Thunder strike, okay
What else do I got?
That's it, right?
I got some upgrades
Wait, you're gonna you're gonna wait. Hold on. I can you can do your current weapon?
I don't have to just buy another
Let me see
main weapon
This is okay zero equipment
Enhancements
Strength plus one of I mean I can still I can afford it
Moves become enabling to deal greater damage to enemies
Absorbs more electrolytes from it makes the fuel
Bar go up higher
Uh, i'm gonna say
Let's just go with
I want to yeah electrolytes
big bits
Lucky bone just gave 30 dollars
Uh lucky bone. Thank you for the 30 bucks
Funny story here. I accidentally purchased a shit ton of bits
Completely by accident. You're my favorite human being. So here you go. Not much. What do you mean? Not much
not much
30 that's a fucking 30 dollars
All right, so that's the dodge. It's a and x at the same time in a direction
Can I do it backwards? I can't can I do it forwards? No, so you can do side to side
All right, cool
That's 30 bucks. That's not
Oh, that's not much. Yes, it is
Thanks for even fucking considering. Thank you
All right. We got uh, here we go. I'm not gonna miss it this time
I mean is there another way I can do this could I just I mean I guess
Thanks for the bits, yeah, thank you
Greedy streamer demands more what
I said don't say the 30 dollars is not much because it's a lot
Fuck oh, I forgot someone's gonna unsub if I didn't cut somebody's hand off. Okay, i'll get it
That's very useful. Oh fuck there's a lot of people here
I like alerted the whole horde here
Whoa, how did you grab me?
What how did he get me like that?
Harry I gotta like
What? Okay. Well, I don't know why that keeps happening. I swear to god i'm pressing it
I'm pressing the button with right like I don't know what's going on here. Am I doing it too late or something?
I don't get it because every time I press it it seems to not work. It just takes it off
Pressing too early, I guess so
Shit come here
No
Where is it? It's up there
There we go. I'm gonna try it again
I'm just trying to go that way. You wouldn't let me go
Wait, no, I didn't get the hand. Oops
We're right for backup during your last fight. The caller's position is on your soliton radar
You can engage if you wish it is your choice
Minus one self i'll get a hand don't worry
Well now that what's this like optional thing it wants me to do. Let me just see. Let me i'll do it. Why not?
I'm assuming this is like side mission content side stuff
Oh great
Oh, this is fantastic
Now I wish I didn't do this
Take it off. Take it down
Shoot it. I can't run up those. Can I can I jump on those?
Ah, no
Take it off. No, you know what I was trying to say
At least they're low enough where I don't have to shoot them with rockets
Why are they flying so low? Yeah, they could be so much higher up
All right, you're out
What'd I get?
I got a uh, uh, is it a bed? I got a bed
Okay
What's a bed mean?
b e d bed
Hello, the cliff is just ahead at the end of the old city beyond that in the refinery's backyard
So what it's a kind of currency thing the refinery is not connected to the city at all
No, it was only built two years ago
There should be a narrow path around there that leads to the plant
It is protected by a fence, but probably you can cut your way through
probably
Don't get cocky most likely it is
I don't know why I was about to just scream
Shut up Boris as loud as I could and that would have been really bad. I'm so glad I just like suppressed
The the i'm glad I didn't do that
I was going to scream it
Like i'm 33. I can't you know, I don't you don't do that anymore. You know what I mean?
Can I get in here? What the fuck?
I'm like a six billion dollar ninja and I can't go through a chain link fence. Come on
Uh-oh
Got it. No, I didn't
Shit who's next?
Shit, they're like grabbing my head
Don't think uh the dodge roll. I'm actually I don't like doing it. I don't like how I press x and a at the same time
It's a little odd
Let me make sure I don't miss any secrets
secret up there
Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, you're gonna miss the secret. Jerma
I got it. I got it calm down
Maybe I missed it 2.1 million
I'm just making shrapnel. That's not good. Don't say it but his team must be in here
Should I really get stuck inside of this?
I didn't get seen watch this ready one two three
Didn't even see me no alert wait secrets
Why do they put that shit in games anymore? You know what I mean?
They do that. I tried to block it. Okay, the thing is that thing is shooting me. You gotta go
What am I even look who's on me this one of these little frogs is on me
They're not blocking
Damn it
That's right. This is stupid thing. I can't even target this thing
I'm a duplicate. I'm on hard difficulty
Liar liar
What do you mean liar? He's so selective. Wait, there are active ir sensors in the area
Factory security no doubt, but the enemy may be using it
What
Whoops
Oh well
Is there a way I've reliably killed these things besides like jumping and having to splash blindly
I'm like pausing. I don't know just have run past them
Why would I do that?
All right run
Pick up all the stuff on the ground though. All right, what do I do this guy over there?
What we got we have a bunch of people up there
I got it up top
No secrets. I mean, yeah, there is one here
There jam grenade
Hold on just a second here
It's electromagnetic pulses for a little bit of time disabling the ugs and cyborgs in the area
Okay
Uh, so i'm gonna get up there and then i'm gonna throw this
You know what i'm saying?
I'm gonna whip it up there
three
two one
disable
Go
Uh, get me up get me up here. Why can I not get up there?
Can I get two I can do two nice. All right, that's cool
There was classified data embedded in that left hand. Got it. It appears you can resubscribe
I'm gonna get this this something treasure chests over here and stuff. Hold on. Where's that one?
across the way
I'm gonna run past this but don't matter. I'll just run by it cares
What do you got the jam grenade?
Something else over here, right? What is that?
key card
Data storage one of the 20 what the hell does that mean?
Laleh luleh lo
How fast think I can say laleh luleh lo
Laleh luleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh laleh
That's pretty fucking fast
Gotta get up top
There's one person up there
Uh
Uh, can I make it up there?
Is it gonna kill me if I jump?
There's no that that's just you fall and you die game over. All right, I gotta go this way
So now I should be able to go from here to there
can I make this jump all right the game is protecting me from falling off so
cinematically you fucking idiot huh fancy seeing you up here
god fucking damn it damn it I didn't think they had clowns tickets up here
that was breathing worse hey cutscene I was wondering when you'd come Jack the
Ripper no one calls me that anymore those I have where is he what what does
his voice change I can show you a better time than that crusty old bear you're in
charge here cold wind of France it is so hard to walk in these things and you
I am balancing spike but why does a child that was a long time ago I wear those
clown tickets I was promised up here he looks right into the fucking camera and
says that from the same cloth you and I lost my family everything yeah that was
a real little moment on German straight but I butchered those fuckers my
family's killers that's when I realized I am a killer too and the good one at
that I slaughtered dozens in Iraq in Afghanistan hey get back up on my
what happened happened to be honest I found it white air comes out my enemies
felt like domino one after another not once did I feel threatened I was a
drift without challenge without purpose at times I even envied my prey
at least they had the cost to die for and then I met him and be sure to
need a bunch of eight or nine ads huh can't just 1v1 me and not as good as
me I don't need for fucking frog enemies
ideas Jack what are yours protect the weak she's that's doing a waltz with it
like a real comedic jokey wall sorry I'll take that as a compliment if you
would kill for your ideas then surely you are ready to die for them what
she has a dark mall weapons with hands the hell are they doing what can step
okay cool really cool here all right I'm trying to block you can we get these
fucking aliens out of the way please like she's dead right I just she's I
just exploded her whole body I win not fair
what the hell's that what is going on there wasn't anything there was no
indicator on the screen oh I can do this cut that rope she had on me she's
flying oh that was a long way mine was way cooler than yours where can I get
one of those things by the way and how useful that shit would be I want to
get like okay I'm like a walk in the corner what you got no arms lady
that was that it click off did you feel how bad that acting was I'm talking
about me I was too focused on the game any of the little guys out of the way
causing a real problem guys perfect you ain't gonna run from me no god
dammit I'm just broke my controller can you hit somebody where what the
fuck was that all right this camera is seriously like can you pick a
fucking direction to be pointing oh she's being frozen this is very
anti-climactic I only got like the top for head sorry I just killed so that's
what would be happening right now she's still talking now she's okay
someone translate that he's gonna take the jacket off he's gonna have rocket
launchers on his shoulders and like in it it's like a second person's gonna be
on his back cybernetic Lee or something
there's definitely another person attached to his back all folded up like
a spider he's gonna take the jacket off the jackets of a huge Chekhov's gun
right now and I mean like it's just there they keep showing it all right
let's see it did they really press the button
right bastard blew himself up
time to get you out of there we're sending a helicopter secure an LZ
shoulder rockets miss fighting what no no yeah sure
I'll take some SBCB dash a BAAA SBCB a BAAA total be oh I got the
daughter anger shy that I know it's the trang okay I know how to say that
word all right I need to get like I want to get some water I'll be right
back it's all right like 60 70% of the way through the game should be
getting closer and you know how to say that's even worse what that is
even drinking again no I'm not I'm drinking water and had a little bit of
coffee I had some coffee earlier give me one second I'm just gonna grab it
because I want some water up here I love BRB g2g all right let's keep going
he got lost yeah sometimes I get lost I went downstairs looking around it's
like what did I come down here for um did you like did I want to come
go to the bathroom and then I sat on the couch I just walked I walked
over to the couch and sat down and turned the TV on I was like I'm not
watching what am I watching what should we go put on the news I put the news
on for like 10 minutes all right here we go there's the the
latrange a pole arm the user can wield it like a spear or relax the arms
tension level to use it like a whip hmm 10,000 so I try in Tide pod
why you mean Tide pod all right because everybody's wants me to do
this that's all I see in the chat everybody wants me to do this so we're
gonna do this one instead oh this is a hot cup of coffee the large amount of
cyborg healing and regeneration I got it okay heals okay well all right
should I buy that weapon no I should upgrade my weapon I have no I'm gonna
upgrade this again let's do the strength one get them both what I
didn't equip it got it I got it I got it I got it I got it I got it I need to buy
the pole arm do I actually need to know get the pole arm you have enough
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's cool not really but it's cool that's 10,000
bit points though fine I'll get it well now I have another more I didn't
even I forgot about the skills shit okay I don't have enough I actually
need to go look at how to do some of these let's try it he fell for it
enhance it I don't think I want to though is what if I don't like it I'm
just gonna waste points on seeing a lot of debated faces so you've got
some kind of disguise lined up right yeah I'll set hope so you'd be a
little conspicuous just walking the streets relax Kev I'll blend right in
yeah just get into the sewer system ASAP
hopefully anyone who notices you will just mind their own business sure you want the
k9000 there along for this one I have the good doctor make some adjustments
this is the second but I am paying attention highlighting I know what to
say yeah I say let's throw my bow we're playing my exoskeleton resembles
he's our friend now two levels that's nice dirty to play his dog I told you
to be nice to the animals that's just the cat that's the cat that's its
brain has been implanted into a cybernetic being pop champ I cannot
wait for the inevitable when the dog goes there's gonna be some sarcastic
comment where he goes whoop whoop it's gonna happen
because the whole time it's like oh you're a dog but he's not a dog and
then he's gonna get really upset about it over the course of time I'm
in this somebody makes a joke about hey your dog coming on sarcastically
gonna go ahead looking well I guess affiliated research center somewhere in
that area according to the Intel from our client the labs been dumping
illegal waste into those sewers FYI they're also involved with the
cartels in human trafficking allegedly anyway don't give me those ha ha it's
right now better now it's not me making a joke need you to infiltrate
the last difference everything you mean joke reference and prediction first we
still don't know the exact location so I'm looking for anywhere the lab
might hook up with the sewers yep if they're actually dumping waste
they've got a link up somehow find that connection sneak into the lab and see if
you can find evidence implicating them on anything no problem
stealths my specialty reference equals joke well how do we have any idea
what kind of research they're doing there not really that's not true
maybe something related to all the people they're trafficking like
experimentation it's possible first things first though find a way into
that lab all right it's all be TV black crocodile so you know watch out black
crocodiles could they be talking about you geez maybe just an urban legend but
still be careful you said it was your New Year's resolution you now
provide that that was the joke there's the joke sir commence operation you
know whoa that's just kind of what we just that was too fast what okay that
was joke is the you know you know New Year's resolution and it's always you
never do it you say you're gonna do it you don't so I'm not gonna do it
that would get on daytime TV if it's like twitch was on daytime TV that
would be daytime TV twitch.TV NBC joke
well wait for a parry moment right there I'm gonna get some perfect parry
ah fuck can you not parry those you just dodge I guess it's the dog
whoa I thought he was dead apparently not no what's that what is that he's
just like shit on an ice cube I don't oh no no wait that's an item
use it to conceal yourself if necessary
nobody knows the lyrics to those everyone only knows that one part all
right so I need everything but the place I need everything but the
place everywhere but the one spot I needed to do that I don't know how I
didn't relax in fact I'm gonna get back up top easy here come on you
can't get up there all right what and why I don't I don't explain like I'm
getting the glitched into the boxes just get up there that was so much
more difficult than it and he's gone whatever what is he gonna do it didn't
get the arm he does double thump
okay backwards swing man the guy has no arms
should I heal I'm not sure if I should even feel here there is a boy in these
sewers recoveries down right don't you feel automatically um I don't do
you you do I don't maybe I'm just too afraid to die jamming grenade right
that is throw this I think I'm just gonna throw this what a waste that's for
me to determine I think I need secondary items to win a guy with no arms just
almost killed me I actually need items for this game wait nice
yeah and I got replaced and plus somebody told me that the items don't
matter in this game guys somebody said secondary items bad also this is
the new weapon right one guy said that and they might be right you guys
seriously need to relax don't do it when you come and go to it
relax don't do it when you come around what even are the lyrics that's
on apparently okay oh you're doing something that I don't know what you're
doing okay the purple bad purple not good purple bad purple bad bad well
that was a lot slower than I thought it was tell me I didn't get it what am I
not getting here I'm still alive okay I just kind of feel bad he's just
shooting his machine gun at me I'll get you I'll get you a dead-on
it's a thousand briefs
yeah I'm from America he's the lowest rank that's not true we saw a see it
already George yeah so what are you doing here
why that's subtitle for bad guys why the to counter research lab you know
about it you know me now go back hey you're not one of them Scott now no I
guess you're all right that well that was clear what that was you know who
day is sort of what happened to you we've been live on the street they can
above now then this good need dressed like the mafia say hey why you want a
job what the worst gonna happen now don't put me on a raspbook they pack
us all a big of a dirty container next thing we know we're here at that
chum be left our kids like you yeah a lot of wine but then we've been
over here what Dems can't want to do snuff us out and got all day all game so
you're a shame me not a bad-ass robot ninja man same as you maybe the
strongest cyborg ever warlock all them phantoms in black clothes that I
passed me starting to sound like a bad guy yourself just playing now we
done plenty bad thing oh me not kill no man now never good we tried to warn
another boy I say I would ease brain would get cut out run your ass out of
there what damn boy with me no understand they like Spanish or
something so me the only one for escape then that machine come after me
and and I know the rest George I need every detail about how you
escaped George please tell me so the kid got into the sewers through a
drainage channel yeah he says the channel is super tight but there's some
kind of shutter next to it yeah George that must be where they dumped the
waste George it sounds like a desperado exec was on site yesterday if a
sentry cyborg was on hand for the meeting you should be able to review
their video log provided you can find the server access looks like he
actually belongs in a different game as well as a little peek at the level of
that technology that's a resident evil sign so what about the kid I made sure
the area was secure and told him to sit tight can you pick him up sure
I'll send a couple agents for it you just focus on getting into that
land if what he said is true about the organs we need to hurry agreed
right now this is the right door
it is possible they are conducting test operations while the lab is closed
they're not gonna make it easy to get into that land there's some way you
could sneak past what's that the first time I've touched one of these
computer data devices all right I got it oh man oh man oh man yeah yes
it's gonna be so fun how's that gonna help I can't wait
medical supplies where is it that could work actually yeah well you knew it was
coming it's up no okay I thought I just get lost I have to see this is
sneak mission with boss he's the only one that has an issue with this oh he
got up here no go no wait oh god they're all up here I have to turn this on now
go just get this is a bad place to fight all of you guys no god he's
running out of circles damn it I didn't see him on screen fuck I thought
I got with me he broke my neck how are you still alive no more legs for
you get out of my way I got the arm good damn it I tried to block it
both of you both of you both of you both of you come on break
yeah I'll do it sure this gets fun fun game how are you still not getting it I
am I know I have to hit the square but I had like a second to do it I didn't
get it
I'm trying all right hold on a second I'm trying to to parry that but I'm
just dashing forward into the fire so there you can't block that I can't
like do anything about that is that deal with it okay
like left or right well I gotta keep going more than that
take his brain out yeah your brains gone thanks for the brain
oh shit there's another one go the other way
whoa what the hell are you doing here one more another one
whoa there's two where where am I too many oh god fuck too many
feel the burn I was doing my cutscene I always miss it the first time every
done for that plus thousand full find a way into the research facility I will
I already cleared the whole fucking area wait I'm going the wrong way aren't I
am I going the wrong way right now lost for health packs equals a well when
they give me two of those guys the fire everywhere there's a box I could open
down here where is it did I already get it another something else maybe I'm
maybe I'm just there we go it's up there there to get it I didn't get it
okay really why can I not open this okay data storage I got it you got to
use seco mode another box that he's finite this is one out of five who
knows right I have determined the approximate location of the lab based
on your soliton radar that's a good that's a good point that's good but
mod that guy I'm just kidding all right so combo lists it's like a pole
arm okay he's in there so let's see there's just why why why why why why
why why why why why X why X why why X a lot of why starts yeah most of them are
why starts why why X why oh my lord okay why why why X why let's test
that out why why why okay let's test it on this guy that was like three
perfect areas again I thought was lined up correctly it was we got any
treasures not that I can confirm but hold on a minute
back I can't fit in here perfect shit I thought it was me I'm always afraid
to do a full like every dude one or two swings even up what else is in
here what do you want for me there's another guy in here hold on let me
sneak attack this guy I can stealth backstab kill this guy in one hit right
what's this right oh I could have done it something I actually could have done
that damn I really didn't think you could actually do something like that
I was just making a joke but you can't you actually can do that you're
gonna breathe fire too this is a smooth experience what's this game have
on medic product 61 that's unfair camera yeah the enemies are spawning
this farming experience point so where am I supposed to go I need to find a
way to get out of here and is this way can I go over I mean this is gonna
take me back around isn't it I was already in here right I have
discovered the entrance to the lab so you know coordinates to your
soliton radar took you long enough thanks a lot
playing Metal Gear Survive oh no I don't think so I don't think so
I took too long don't give me that it was scripted one two my forklift people
is there like a forklift item that you can I don't know what the fuck I'm
talking about so let's just play is this some kind of forklift thing when
am I gonna play metal gear rising probably next week this would appear to
be the huge in maintenance area you should find a terminal there
something they used to upload mission parameters to say you cheese and
something I can use to access the labs main server perhaps but first you need
no I thought there were two games that were in this series I thought it was
metal gear rising and then I thought there was metal gear rising revenge
you'll need one to interface with the terminal most any you G should
suffice tripod or the like I'll see what I can come up with how do I use
it simply connect to it you should be able to use your communications outlet
to control the proxy Eugene I missed something over here let's give it a shot
well there was like a funny joke that I missed something happened out of that
window
well that's the only chance that I have to be able to speak because my
brain has to turn off when I fight enemies short attention span well nobody
saw that okay well and you guys thought I who had tunnel vision how do I
do a stealth takedown
no how do you do stealth take down like this is up here where do you
go there's something that got bounced it's because he bounced got
walk up behind a present be whoa no no you're not gonna do that shit somebody
charge at me somebody do something fine I'll start what can I interrupt that
or something do I just have to run away still too far away really how is
that even possible again I don't know how it's possible for me to miss
that there's only one sliver that's even possible to hit there use the
other stick to aim better right stick or something like a just manually do it
you have plenty of time and maybe that's not just freaking out I think I
have like a fire extinguisher all right I did it that filled up the
whole room can I not open this door this looks like a door I can slash
through apparently go down here do I eat on a day that I stream like an hour
before and then that's it all right well we're starting here I want to
try to get a bowl I did panic there for a second
I do have lots of time really need stuff
okay solid metal gears rises one of them is a sword game and the other one
is a when you for now stealth stealth there it is but that room those were
cyborg brain casings duh we saw George said they were harvesting
organs from kids yes this must be why they are trafficking
children perhaps other organs are being sold elsewhere but they are definitely
taking their brains Jesus are they making these kids into cyborgs wait the
cyborgs you've been fighting did they seem like they might be kids you said
earlier the child soldiers have a telltale approach to combat I just want
to open this up but I didn't see it here those weren't kids bad time so
what desperado is just doing the surgeries there we've got to do
something about all those brains and the other kids George was talking about
he changes his voice a few hours ago he does the Christian Bale Batman
thing true there could still be a bunch of kids they haven't touched yet
I better move sometimes he just goes like this sometimes okay all right I
don't know why you do that's the equivalent of picking up like a
pretzel you found on the ground you don't just put that into your
damn it any funny business and they might just open fine try latching onto
cyborgs heads from behind then an electric shock should lock them
unconscious do we really have to have an avoid everybody spider-man Mary Jane
mission I want that give that to me what am I looking for a terminal or
something my friend what do we do sorry I'm sorry all right so I gotta go that
way all right got a guide there I'm thinking all right another one of
those assholes I need to get rid of that guy good moment whoa how do I
stop him how do I like attach on his head
I see the joke that you can never get a USB the first time you try to put a
USB in USB joke it's perfect explaining the joke well just in case somebody
didn't ever put a USB in a computer before don't they have like new like
the lightning cable you might not even know what it is USB in five years is
gonna be like saying DVD half you guys don't even know what a DVD is DVD was
like 25 years ago some of you guys might not even know that is
D-I-V-I-D-I somebody wrote what is a DVD
accounting will be in touch
Dr. Eggman's outfit combine all the characters in this game you'll have
dr. Eggman you see that kev in money's killer this
chief of operations goes by sundowner the Californian wildfire the kids think
we're too late it's Raiden Sonic one way to find out George was still alive
maybe the payment hasn't come through yet maybe but you heard what he said
they've already started some brains on VR training there must be more than
just what I found here what about the VIP in the suit I'll find out
definitely seem why does he have right I'm going off player following him
around find the captive children you got it
now here's how I'm free something to that off I'm sorry scream so loud made
villain death screen it can't be villain here boys I'm playing the part here you
guys think of a villain they really don't think if I was in DVD cinematic
universe would I be a villain you think so stop calling me DVD cinematic
universe I merged the GPS location of our entry with all my movement data
from that point on you think they got to him mr. Satan from DBZ it's me
thanks just when you think Goku can't come any closer mr. Satan take care
I'm gonna get copyright strikes by doing mr. say I've never even seen the
show the only episode of DBZ I've ever seen mr. Satan came on screen and
said that and then I changed the fucking channel I don't know any of the
lines in that whole thing
did we get him I don't know
dodge and I'm hurting all right you got like a bunch of headshots there oh
that the game when it blows like that transformer is seriously annoying
you stand up yeah yeah I know why the heck don't they give you why the heck
don't they give you like at least a second I gotta get out of the corner
the camera likes to do this thing or just doesn't profile you can you
stay behind me stay behind me then I tried to block it to come on like
what is this camera view what I don't want this I want it behind me
I'm here where'd it go what up top what have you done what's happening to me why
am I oh my god it just I was done I already did it I hate this enemy I hate
being in this room with this guy all right please I hate this thing I don't
want to fight this thing again I knew I'd seen that guy before
Stephen Armstrong this becomes a regular enemy Colorado senator Stephen thanks for
watching the streamer buddy they're already talking about him as a shoo-in
for the nomination in 2020 and get 20 two years ago a federal grand jury
investigated his ties to a certain private world marshal one of the
biggest PMC's out there scream over the biggest ever since the big five
split up not to mention the single luxury boys during military cyborg
R&D in the world guess that answers the question of who's backing Desperado
Marshall JT in bed together Justin turn the leg um Joey and a US senator we're
talking about page Phoebe even without the Patriots no major media
right like these it'd be financial and political suicide so we just what sit
back while they keep carving up kids stand aside while they build an army of
cyborgs you heard them Chandler they're planning something we can't just
wait for it to happen we need to hit him first and hit him hard where it
counts no no I know what you're thinking and Courtney Cox's character
whose name I can't remember America and America has these things called
laws and law enforcement in Denver was private times like a dark souls game
Marshall yes so what they are still laws and it's their headwaters for
Christ sakes you'd be heading right into the heart of a raging shitstorm I
didn't say it would be easy we'll figure it out once the kids are safe
Jesus Kevin out wait no secrets in this room who made this game Kevin
out house that was it didn't bounce the right way distraction crack it
worked the one guy was right the sub weapons are they're a little on the
iffy for me here using dead I an artificial blood cryo preserver they
must have begun preparatory freezing what do you mean that device is
filled with synthetic blood plasma it can slow the metabolism of a harvested
or drink blood drink the blood to sustain oxygen levels you can preserve
an arm or brain anybody part for several hours so what are they
freezing and why I could not see perhaps they plan to set off the
organs of the children they were told to dispose of unbelievable you
right right unbelievable where is she where's Harvey open this door right
now oh for form for an anesthetic and smaller doses much of it and now the
awesome chachos really taking my time with this glass and I'll blow his
brains out quick think surrender break the glass didn't do or save the kid
many break the club I got it I got five seconds to figure it out which one
surrender yeah telltale time I won't ask again are you sure
me life no so precious team what if we can take this scorned to hell with
the kids are literally like just you can't know they're choking in there
this is not a walking scenario oh we should you killed a kid you missed
wait I don't open up the BSB a a a a B BSB a a a a B that's a B shouldn't
be an a if you have hold on a minute if you get an A plus four A's and three B's
how is that not like a B plus or an A minus three B's four A's and an A plus
the S is the A plus because you suck streamer ha ha ha ha ha all right let's
take a look like enhance to 10,000 what do I have sixty nine thousand
sixty nine that's not even funny but I mean it's cut it is it's that's not
funny endurance to I'm assuming I can do that with everything now you'll sell
to body get some new bodies 20,000 but this one has regeneration the suit
excels against tanks UAVs attack helicopter and other anti-infantry but
that one has a hat buy the funny streamer outfit no I don't want to buy
the funny like streamer outfit ever this is not one of those scenarios where
every playthrough you've ever seen has done that have you have you watched
one YouTube let's play this or one streamer that didn't go oh yeah you're
not disobey us I'd rather be a gray Fox no I haven't now buy it no I'm
saving my money because I'm gonna upgrade my weapons I don't want to be
useless what can I do with this one all right good strength strength plus two
I'm going back to the sword more damage lame in all capitals of lame
sorption to energy to I'm going back to the sword lame lame lame oh wow
lame I don't have the money for it so too bad I'm sorry guys up now come
on I can afford this no I know lame and I didn't even you guys got in my
head now I'm gonna use the I'm gonna stream is gonna lose all viewers
because it doesn't buy the funny man outfit
here comes the meme level I'm gonna gain viewers because I didn't put on
the funny streamer outfit someone's gonna oh I'm talking over the cut
scene again I'm good to see you up and about how you feel it that's because
your blood sugar levels are being maintained automatically beats the hell
that's true sorry kid you just be in the way besides that actually true right
they don't believe is it fun and games remember that who the fuck are those
people who are those people what would you do if you turned over on the
highway and just see this guy yeah just remember that I guess would that be
really bad out of the ordinary
sorry Boris it's done can't have a maverick employee involved in a
corporate rating now can we you could at least come talk to me no it was
time to break away from the old team for this past time you cannot take on
Marshall all by yourself I won't sit by while they put your little kids and
ship their parts around like meat it's a good driver the important
things legally for medical purposes it's all being legal doesn't make it
right right I thought I take this last 15 seconds and cut it into a GTA 5
especially the fuck you asshole guy just once I wish that a show or a TV or
something would it's not badass to do that I just want there to be bright
green puke all over his chest and mouth and stuff like you would puke
if that happened you would throw up I can't just have that if your car flips
upside down going like a hundred miles per hour you're going to puke 18 3 1 0
4.7 threatening a peace officer deadly forces authorized not me it's striker
for Mortal Kombat and it's his level I don't even expect I have the wrong
weapon no I'm at a rate okay I want to be facing the guy that I can do
this to it's pairing me that was a ship that's a septuple carry I feel
like perfect Harry this guy I've heard him all right got secrets no away from
that I'll try a perfect pair apparently that was not perfect
I get to know he parries when you die okay he just parries it back don't
steal their spine the road is blocked by barricades we will proceed through
the buildings you will follow me if you prefer if you prefer enough times
you will insta-kill remember I told you I didn't want to fight now I got
to fight to all right I got to put my
ears up easier dodge good dodge ah god damn it you have to let go
when I jump up I have to let go I really am playing this like Dark Souls and I
can't help it I'm trying to like I'm trying to
invincibility frames try this again got it play Jebel may cry people are
dropping behind me all right sneak up behind him and press B oh okay you
have to be all right well I missed it I get I did that's the first time I've
ever done that I see you sneak up behind them and then press B and then
left trigger easy enough okay it's be right up their ass I got it the
indicator moves it's difficult I mean let's be honest here what was the
actual how does I get that I don't I mean was I gonna really wait
there for like 30 seconds while the guy walked all the way across no I want
to play use the right stick to aim your cut doesn't right stick swing
though doesn't right stick just swing okay all right I thought right stick
just swung in the direction you have to hold it somehow that's harder
thought you're gonna swing well okay getting used to I should probably learn
how to do it though another wave is that that's it only three people what's
up with them I'm gonna need to do that for later well I'm gonna just try to
get used to it little boxes what is this that was not worth going all the
way down there I'm ignoring the posters posters don't look at the poster at the
beginning of the whole I gotta go back to the beginning of the whole level is a
porn poster that's fine I'm sure it's really funny what's your status they
trashed my car I'll have to go the rest of the way on foot do you
really have to do this look I'm fed up with all of it companies like
ours yours bend the laws when it suits business why not bend it when it can
save innocent lives right Boris listen to me that be our training they'll be
warped into killing machines they'll be set on POWs civilians it'll be one
atrocity after another hmm like what you went through we can't have any more
jack-the-rippers you saw what happened with George I'm doing this
Boris I have but I can't stop them from becoming murderers so you get all the
brains back then what just so happens I know great cybernetic surgeon doctor
but he cannot you won't change my mind Boris this is my fight now and your
wife and son what of them I have a wife in New Zealand safe Rose would
understand why I have to do this nice trying not to wake up parents
will have the contract for law enforcement throughout the city they are
the law we've met you fuck it yeah what's wrong with you officially Maverick
incorporated comes you actions as unlawful and a pain in the asshole
now pay the asshole do not worry about the leg there's a game too
loud sure turn the game down and it's been like three hours over the codec to
help I'm doing any more than you no that's good all right I unlocked a
number nine for a VR missions what about chest or anything
that's pretty all right I didn't do that I got BP for that no I didn't
what a vandal no no no no no can I equip the sword from a quick menu I do
have to wait hi all right well I don't like fighting
enemies in these little rooms no dodge damn it cut the one part of his
body off that it needed to cut somehow through all that odd just move
back at them that's not a block how was that a how is that why does it do
that sometimes and just use the d-pad right all right well that's a seed
because they're fighting two huge enemies in a little room get this
stupid thing off how do I know I don't know the lock on because when I
small room like that the camera just rips around like crazy I don't know if we're gonna be able to use that
okay get this off all right finally we're good told you the polar I'm
sucked I don't know about that it's just it's kind of slow doc what's your
status I am reviewing the pre-flight checklist now I have got a huge
radius to handle shipping the brain units we should be airborne in just a
few minutes you sure you can pilot that chopper by yourself
pull on something in every game
need I remind you that we live in the golden age of unmanned flight even manned
helicopters possess a robust semi-automatic mode it is simple really so
simple that I can continue to monitor your status and world martial
security from the pilot you stream crashed my computer minus two that's
hot why am I getting a minus two for that how is that a joke that joke wasn't
very funny Jericho
so many brains think of the data to research all and of course your
personal safety was a concern it's red head of the roof rocket launcher right
to rocket propelled grenade I'm gonna keep this on just because there's
helicopters and shit they don't really feel like fighting well uh all right
that's how you I don't know how I missed that many times but I get I
mean look at where that you saw that I didn't that was not me I did it it
was fine right what's wrong come on buddy answer me right did I still get it
right okay really what I went right through the damn thing use the
environment to your advantage I gotta get on top of here
you see me I don't like the spider-man villains they're annoying can I go
behind that guy is it possible that I could like sneak behind him I can't do
it from up here I can't do this from up here oh why would I have to be down
I could oh why why I was only just down if I hold the right stick oh I
know it's just it's very difficult for me to do that I feel like it's
harder for me to do that than just trying to aim with left stick in the
triangle from the or lion X what would you like me to do jump okay that's the
thing that's gonna stop me there are stairs why use stairs when you can
slice through everything it's more fun that way
hammer okay I can't carry that one these guys gotta go no no that's not
what I wanted to do that's some kind of achievement for some reason two hammer
guys are gonna be fun what was that magnet passing bullshit he just like
attached to my body why are you dark souls lock on that's bullshit the
guy doesn't mean poor vent okay can I go it's a ladder right come on
there's a ladder next to me I can't use it this is why not that miss
where are you going good dog point blank am I gonna beat the whole game
today that depends huh I wonder how much I'll try I'll try to get through
the whole thing an indicator was what the indicator was sitting oh my god
that was an indicator issue and I thought there was a ledge just I thought
that was another place to drop down a current period whatever I'm not gonna
complain well that's not what happened I'm just as confused as all of you are
okay this time go to edge but no don't go to edge I have to just go
over there I for some reason just saw the blip and I was like oh there's
probably a door down there or second I thought I did it again okay come on no
it's right trigger to run and I'm really good can I get both these guys
from far away they kill them every time am I supposed to be rescuing these
guys don't follow him down there hold don't oh my god
you cannot proceed any further via the rooftops there is a freight railroad
underground the elevator ahead will take you to it do it for the joke not
the whole thing if I do that again I swear to God I keep pressing left
trigger to run this must be the railroad it would appear so likely part
of Denver's old system couldn't just take the elevator like a normal
person in the early years of freight trains this particular line appears
to have been abandoned some time ago it was originally constructed to transport
supplies to an underground factory but now it seems even the electrical
system is no longer functioning yeah it's pitch black in here as a
cyborg I trust this is not a serious concern I hate this I don't hate this
anymore no I've never might I do hate oh get out and his enemies in here it's
wonderful night vision goggles can I just skip
fighting these guys oh okay so I should do this then all right it's
only it's one or the other I can't be in the box hold on wait that why they
can see me why can hold on a minute pitch black we can they have the same
items that I don't expose yourself apparently they also happen I think I
thought I had to be a little closer to that we just glued to my body with
that arm God I need to get in a better spot somewhere over here slide
I've dodged Lord please can I please not do this again let me just move on from
this please activate the train I'm you know I'm getting stuck in animations
that's one of the problems like I'm gonna swing swing and then I see that
I need to walk but I'm in the middle of a swing and I can't do is that
even can I I don't even know if I can block that I can't okay I thought
I hate this dark level fucking hell oh my god he just keeps doing it I can't
stop it stop it by God just cut his fucking body in half Jesus what the
hell there's somebody else in here who's the person in here what there's
like a enemy right here who is one of those fucking idiots up there and
he's he's gonna alert I gotta throw fucking group to try to shoot this
thing I'm just gonna shoot fucking rocket at this guy all right I did it
there is a maintenance shaft up ahead use it to return to the surface no no
no don't put the rock and launch it down you fucking idiot where I wish I
could have the night vision on and have the box open so there's a guy
right there there's people on the ceiling I guess I could get if I
throw a MP grenade and I've run by I have a few of them electromagnetic or
jamming no it's this one oh boy I have no idea okay well I hope I'm
throwing this in the right spot well that didn't that distracted him is it
was it enough I meant away I don't really maybe I can just go by
without fighting or trying stealth kill it's not gonna see me right here
right I don't know if this is the right time to go in but I have to turn this
off I need to wait till he starts walking again because this has to go
off and then how am I gonna can stealth kill big guy and it's like
people all over the ceiling and they're all over me shit yes way I have
to do I think I can't I can't move I have to dodge you can't do any
animations to do anything in this game I have to not be moving to
parry or to dodge I don't know how did I not dodge that I'm not gonna get
fucking dropped again get me out of this level for God's sake give me a zero I
don't care I hate this place I'll take a fucking zero pitch black stealth
mission get me the fuck out of here it would appear your only way forward
is to return to the surface you will exit into an evacuated commercial
district security is heavy but you need not worry about collateral damage
when engaging the enemy about time finally I can cut loose proceed to the
right from the exit you will find a stairway on your right those stairs
lead to a shortcut to world martial headquarters do not be distracted by
the advertisements you are not here as a tourist sure I'll just buy a quick
souvenir or two for Rose and that'll go back to fucking Power Rangers
buddy must hurry remind me to teach you a Megazoid killed you in like
episode 104 fuck off
has that happened yet I don't remember you have almost reached world martial
headquarters
just can I take the bridge down please just make him fall but we great I
promise
oh I don't oh I would have gave up I would have quit like fucking two hours
ago I would have liked I would play something else
without a doubt what are you doing what are you doing what are you doing
camera ah like when you have to hit up an X to carry and you end up
hitting saw it like right because we're what why did that have to what
did that do that for what a weird route you does that why did you that
was the oddest route he's just got shot by his own guy I'll take I'll take the
victory
I actually have prompt to back say I don't like fighting the dog it's a
problem dog it's the great point of the story where he turns do it like for
instance why come on I can't parry when I have to press that
fuck are you trying to parry with why no I'm trying it's forward it's
X to parry right or like towards where they are when the camera like like rips
around they add point two seconds when you press the button the right button
that you think you're pressing it goes the other direction jet stream Sam
happy new year fucking Snoke my sword is a means to an end to protect those
prey on really let me ask those sidewalls you've killed up to now maybe
they weren't kids but they were you ever think about them when you're
chopping them into hamburger their adults they made their choice right on
the dotted line their BMC contract usually they're no strangers to all in
fact many times they already lost a leave or two many times they were out
of work and starving on the street so yes they keep appearing on other pieces
of media somebody there's a tech director that's changing cameras here
this is a whole production down on pivoting nanomachines sent right into
the blender they made their choice right open your
camera two in three twenty two one camera switch
can we take on the meme thing you guys are the meme part of the game
die
well which one is it dude
he took my leg
hear their thoughts
shut up Boris he did it for you what am I who shot me who shot me I want
another name
there's no reason for me to be here
psycho why am I psycho just doing what I'm supposed to be doing
right are you injured I thought they had a choice a fair choice not like
you I don't want this like he's out there
but I'm not doing the course of mankind half man half machine five percent
together on three previous missions he proved most capable you think highly
so wait that's just not me in like a cool suit
until now scouting data for the next area I thought he just had like a cool
job he saw him he's in a suit I like a costume it's just a costume
your current emotional state appears highly volatile I am sure you do not
intend to get out here but I suggest you avoid combat for the time being
oh man not I don't want to do another avoid combat mission yeah I can hear
the nanomachines I know that riding is a robot I know I'm just kidding
around I'm just ahead what's we got any I used to train his cover why
doesn't this German YouTube video have any funny jokes what you want to
throw a grenade at the train EMP myself no I went I gotta like get to the end
of this area what you want to do what can I do right now besides walk and
grab item and go to next I'm not gonna throw a grenade at somebody make
us laugh can I jump I can't jump when I'm sad I can't go in the box when
I'm sad either I don't think there's any way I can avoid these guys but
say something like yoinky hurry up quick say yoinky I'm gonna die okay well
the cutscenes happening so we're gonna stop right
now is it is your cause just or is that just what you tell yourself fuck
you he's so bad he was into a basic enemy how pleased you are to chop
away I mean my name is monsoon of the winds of destruction yeah I guessed
much here comes the mean
yeah he just he's tapping
Raymond so that was the funny thing that was the thing that everyone's
losing their minds about does he say something feasting on the insides of
your enemies how easily you ignore the loss of life when it suits your
convenience so tell me who saves the week from the man who saves the
week you're the ones exploiting them you take advantage of their weakness of
course they get hurt when you set them up as your human shield kill or be killed
Jack
like a camera mode activated
its final lesson is carved deep in my psyche and this world and all its
people are diseased okay free will is a myth religion is a joke look right
controlled by something me I mean these people standing here when you
look right look all the way right they are the culture they are everything
keep looking huh
are you kidding me was I right was I actually right to the cat come back
if I had killed that cat wouldn't happened right
now there's a pretty mean exquisite you just did you say that pretty mean don't
be ashamed it's only nature running its course the whole speech was about
memes about me I mean I knew something was how did I miss it I was looking at
the cat I could walk off the battlefield and I thought the cat was
the meme but here I am surrounded by death arguing philosophy with
terrorists I told myself this was about justice about protecting the
weak but I was wrong look when everybody is screaming here comes the
meme here comes the meme and a cat shows up on screen I learned young that's
the meme to me good you know what I'm saying that's that's what the joke
was in America forget the devil inside kidding I was born to kill the bit
about my sword that means of justice stuff I guess I needed something to
keep the ripper in check when I was knee-deep in bodies you but you all
this is a wake-up call to what I really believe what I really am what are you
saying I'm saying Jack is back
turn off my pain inhibitors
my nature
you're the boss I misjudged you you are like us after all
now you're just being nasty
that nickname you love so much wanna know how I got it
saying actually why don't I give you a demonstration I can't win I can't you
can't have it both ways guys drove a shop during the cutscene why is he
not talking where is he what oh I didn't pay attention I got a perfect
there we go oh oh he's on my fucking head ready go was that me what is the
thing in his head me you just grew a bigger forehead what are you doing
was it a car what okay slice the cup what where all these cars coming from
okay I get it where to go where to go where to go where to go all right
yet now I gotta parry him there's no way I'm gonna hit him right yeah he's
like cutting himself in half
I'm gonna like break my Xbox controller if I keep doing this shit
seriously I gotta be locked on
wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait
did that work I don't think that works what the fuck is going on Jesus I get
it chop him up I think I win what what happened who's this there you go
again all right cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut it all there's so many
things how many more things with the cut they get them all good whoops
that hit this guy's freaking me out man all right get it get the head all right
he's back into the weird mode again throwing shit oh no it's a fucking
Katamari what do I do about the Katamari what do I do about that what
do I do about this I just dodged it like uh-huh okay I got it all right I
saw the flash get really you fight me with your hand back there not
fair no no shit fuck I gotta get it perfect
apparently
nice nice lash him in the air no he's I'm ready to fight him where are you
going you more than bullshit
Oh God I'm okay no okay easy three stuff I cut him when he does that oh I
don't think so he gets it away he's done instead you come here Wow no he's
like Final Smash to me oh I'm like fucking losing my mind
oh my hands are sweaty whoops I got it he's really early but I'm back down
you know he's gonna throw the giant missile at me now
what am I supposed to do? I guess this
oh thank God it's chairfucking me
dead on got it that was hard that was fun
give me a beat yeah almost the first try yeah almost
don't be ashamed it's only nature running its course your means and here
will continue now I return to the earth wind blows rain falls the strong pray dark souls awake all is as it should be
how do I just crow hop and sprint boot his head into the fucking
stratosphere right I'm fine Kevin relax I'll get the brains this for anyone
else all right man later later all right meme results see I had a lot of
problems there the dark room the that's fine I don't like that chapter I like
the meme boss I mean he was fun there are three or four areas in that I would
just you know what I mean I got tactical Psy dystopia unlocked ooh I'm
gonna try that up so main weapon and then unique weapon I still mean this
is I want to try it how much is it ten thousand Psy dagger powered by
Lawrence force following Fleming's left hand rule for motors his force is
generated by a magnetic field I want to try I could be Raphael from the Ninja
Turtles and I'm gonna enhance it strength one strength two strength
three Mike doing something wrong well now how I'm gonna use it now all
right make sure it's quick 20,000 for enhance I need these upgrades guys I
do and I can do this and I have it on
what the hell does this thing do oh it's fake okay watch out ripper mode
okay
guess it's kind of like spider-man you got in the way you dick really how is
that not okay I'm a little bit confused here I'm trying to figure out
it was like too far away you're off the screen
thank that's great well that was a good in the care of that was fun
apparently you've wasted it somehow I got traveling two rockets and yeah it's
unfortunate that I just upgraded this three times I I don't I really don't
like it thank you classic waste all the money joke well wasn't really a joke I
thought it was gonna I thought it was a melee weapon I didn't think it was
kind of like I thought it was replacing does the staff replace the elevators
appear to be disabled which we should have expected I suppose I will access
the control unit perhaps you can hack an elevator and make it operational
who splendid idea by all means yes it seems the guards are storming the
building okay do not stray too far from the elevators right and use the
weapons around you to slow them down all right well I can't get them you
can so I might as well just use this as well yes give them hell the guy
already up here because it's a guy behind me is he just hitting me right
probably that's a dental arm I really need to be using this guy behind a
force field no he's just out of reach can I shoot him in the feet and kill
him come on why can I aim it up like half an inch higher he's still on the
stairs is he gonna get up console FBF well first you tell me don't leave the
elevator and they tell me go we go to the elevator and then you stop them
from getting in the elevator get in the elevator stop talking to her the
cutscenes
the lower insists of offices and meeting space for staff and visitors while
confidential military projects and technical research are restricted to the
upper levels so that's where the brains in the server room will be up top
indeed but that elevator can only access the lower floors you need to
get to the 20th floor and pass the security gate they are to reach the
upper area let me guess time to find another left hand well that is
security cyborgs would not have sufficient clearance but managers and
senior staff have already been evacuated no doubt so the only option is to cut
the power to the security gate which will not be easy it is powered by no
less than three systems including a backup power supply you will need to
destroy all of the electrical control panels to disable them in any
case you should arrive at the 20th floor soon a lot of grenades the
electrical panels are most likely hidden in the walls use your enhanced
AR to search for any unusual heat sources inside the walls there
unusual heat sources all right I'm just going in well I looked at it
there you go get out of the way give me my item that I just found give
my item oh whoops okay the heat sources rocket launchers gotta go I
know this where the dog come from why is it like a dog in here now okay I
gonna run away from me we don't know you don't too many people to parry
too much going on oh boy am I gonna die here I think I'm dead here I'm like
walking the corner I got other shit going on right yeah I can't really do
anything I don't I don't know where it's trying to get in space but it's
trying to get you to face the poster that I'm not so sure about
bug got on my back really all right now where do I go look for the heat heat
look at the heat on the walls there should be an electrical panel nearby use
your enhanced AR to locate it knows boxing okay sure
one down two to go I already see one of those I thought I would try to
swing it one there should be an electrical panel nearby use your
enhanced AR to locate it excellent just one more people coming in no all
right one two three that was not a pretty good that was not a good
telegraph right there still alive I think he's dead no little worms in there
my last one I thought there was one back here but I'm probably crazy
we go hey hurray how much more of the game do I got what's uh what's left I
feel like I'm getting fairly close like our two minutes left
should I activate I don't know about that now no keep them off I need it this
way well as you wish I must say I have turned more than a few men into
cyborgs but you well your past is most what you getting that doc most of
the time you're working with first world ex-military grown men compared
to the average third world child soldier I can't really complain do the
most of them they're the sort of gorillas your typical patient gets paid to
slaughter this shouldn't be news to you doc look just help me take care of
those brains after I bring him back I do my business you do yours
so go go go I'm the guy told me to run so I'm gonna run for some reason I
thought he was talking about blow the door open that's all I saw don't fight
everybody just go you know grab the RPG but oh what can I start I know I'm
fine I'm good why fight anything just run destroy the grad ain't no going
you're really easy with the electrocution knife let go and then all
these sliders in the area let go press again that's cool I'm gonna hit right
in the face by something yeah keep climbing like that it will be
that dog
all right apparently I did it I got a D there I didn't do anything I didn't
fight anybody I couldn't build points you should find an indoor garden up
ahead like garden sounds fancy a Japanese garden to be precise it is an
area set aside for VIPs apparently one of world marshals directors is a rather
serious Japanese culture enthusiast all right so what's this got to do with me
there's something I need from the garden not at all you need only pass
through that area to arrive at a freight elevator I found a route to
the elevator controls to the unit we hijacked downstairs I have located
great work doc elementary my dear right now head for the garden well fight
apparently I don't know how the second it should shut up shut up I'm trying to
hit that guy too but I can't his this guy's body was getting in the way
die with the RPG is gonna go what point blank by an RPG why these guys down
here the hell do you need to be doing that for why are you done with the
RPG you got tired that works out for me too far away shit I mean wouldn't you
say something similar at this point fuck me proceed through the garden
so many people here I wonder what the hell I should do here cuz 5,000 damn
okay um what's going on that moon that is that is a very two-dimensional moon
can I go this way I thought I could but there was a weird invisible wall I gotta
say on earth is with the stealth in this game no I don't like why okay
it's targeting this guy well why would it turn I don't even know which
way I'm going which I use I need to like do something here where is this
camera even going what is happening man come on oh my fucking Lord all right
like do we have to find these little corridors that's all there is here
there's no open place like it's like over here is the biggest place I
think gracious no don't do it keep doing that same move my god I'm gonna
scream in a second here fuck off both of you are you still alive
can I keep playing the game can I move on to another place
this looks so long go this way my crazy or something something up here no I
don't have enough power shit you don't need power I thought you do
okay apparently don't all right all is a catwalk straight ahead to reach the
elevator my apologies right I seem to have fallen behind no worries actually I
should thank you what are you talking about if it wasn't for you I wouldn't
have gotten Jack back then that is your true nature more or less still
interested I find no reason to alter my objectives from the moment we met
you have acted on emotional urges you speak of protecting those weaker than
you such people number in the billions it is impossible you cannot save every
human being in the world you cannot save every street child after
extended observation I have come to a conclusion your actions are rooted in
affinity for those from similar circumstances as yours guess so not
much of a superhero after all huh however your emotional status is
understandable perhaps I share this same affinity well if that's what you
feel then glad to have you along Roger you can reach the server room
beers afraid elevator just a hair press the button but I've watched the
arm guys where the my like my right hand hurts I might have to take a
break boomer injury so it's all like the tap wait wait tap rap use the claw
grip oh with a game like this how are you supposed to claw grip it no it's a
lot of this fight this part's gonna hurt your really no I don't want a
part that it hurts by hand that didn't happen I think of it always hurt my
fucking hand oh fuck this elevator seriously do I have to fight half the
enemies in this game these tight-ass spaces really his enemies bigger than
the screen and it's a square where one of them can fit let's go thank God
he can't fall off no I didn't want to show it to him I wanted to
roll the grenade I'm about to restart just kill me after he started just kill
me you're supposed to be stronger than this all right let's go trying to
parry yeah go sicko mode no no no I have to wait for those big guys to
get here I gotta take a break this game is so much this is like playing dark
souls at like times five speed my brain is just like slowing down get to
the next boss well if I can get off his elevator we'll see maybe now I'm
gonna activate you just have cutscenes like it's a really tall building yeah
it is how did you get me don't care about the
here
one kind of you I might actually have to turn it on here I hate fighting the dog
stop running around huh the one you know I'm gonna do anything the one
time that I want you to come on I just fat-fingered the whole entire
control porn in chat again well I think that's strike three guys I think
I'm gonna have to disable links permanently why would you baby with that
why would you tell me this porn in the chat we've got an issue already
speed why what hey we already had a good issue with that shit
they can't do this or I just turn it off I'm just mashing excellent by
the elevator sequence how do I know what porn is I went I had a class
when the class talked about pornography things that they talked about I don't
even know what enemies are fighting me right now lying around shooting missiles
there's three fucking vultures it's time it's time to fuck it for like a
grenade or something holy shit I just threw it over I threw it over boy
oh man what are you even supposed to do about this reliably Jesus man I
don't even know what the fuck I'm gonna shoot at just shoot it who
cares I hate these big guys I'm actually the worst
just kill him anything else here it was real there was a real porn why do we
have to have this problem now guys I've had links in chat for almost three
or four years server rooms ahead yes and you tell me that three years later
I expect to find if they're VR training those brains I'm guessing it
won't look like your typical IT department quite right most of it
will likely be occupied by life support units feeding oxygen and
nutrition to the brains they have stored you know they would also need
a server to feed them to be our data but in terms of structure it's
really more brain storage but no doubt it makes a convenient euphemism for what
they are really doing there yeah like how CIA agents refer to where they work
as the company indeed something like that would never arouse the
suspicions of rank-and-file staff who may hear it and I'm sure those
complicit in this operation feel better not calling it the VR training
room even something so simple as a name can help one ignore the truth of
what they are doing truly fascinating how the human brain works so this whatever
room that's where sundowners waiting right if he wants a fight I wish he'd
just get on with it he didn't seem the time to run and
hide then he is in charge of security but I suspect this is not about
business if I had to guess I would say he's toying with you testing you
perhaps whatever he's doing it won't change what's going to happen once I
finally catch up with them all right so give me a second I gotta like get a
glass of water I get to break I'll be back in like two minutes I'm gonna pee
grab a jar of water this is this is this games like lighting my neurons up
in my brain no porn links in this chat if this if I come back there's
a porn link you're all in deep shit don't don't do that I'll be right
back all right hello change like the lighting in here I think the
lighting is like fucking with my head they'd have like the ideal lighting
what was ideal lighting I don't know all right hello yeah I just needed to
take a second this game is this game's a lot of fun but it's kind of
like I'm melting and at some point it's just like
fires off a lot of shit in the brain really fast I think it's a good game
brain can't take it I think I'm good though I just needed to look away for it
from it for like a minute or two grab some water you know chill how you think
secure I was gonna feel definitely a lot slower than this but I don't know
it's it's kind of the same realm as the early games right I think the
sound design makes it really overwhelming yeah we'll see if I can
do the whole game
well got it they're all getting back on top of her head I gotta kill them all
before they get back she has a good I don't know what the hell's happening
I'll take it I'll take the victory BD so I gotta fight this this isn't like
a boss brush is it this is boss brush don't let her get it I don't really
you don't have any weapons on you don't really like don't let her get a
no no no no don't wanna get away only two bosses yeah still still a rush
still a boss run they only need it with some water do you understand the
whole hydrate mean thing I understand it now you got it I was turning it I
was shriveling up there come back down lady hey lady I gotta get a good
walk walk it do something what are you doing why are you standing still zero
point zero point zero point one percent got it now what oh it is a bit is a
boss brush that was a stupid joke I was making it really is actually is a
lot lower and I don't drink didn't drink enough water for this shit
I got four help don't be fine all right he's faster than the last time
he is much faster than the last time where'd you go head off go get the head
whoo oh not the foot first sweet got it I didn't go ever I didn't get like a
super cool kill but I still did it all right late mode does less damage I
don't wanna miss anything people get really mad when I miss something I'm
sorry I'm sorry I do I just said I'm sorry this thing's up there
late mode is not meant for dealing damage you know I use blade mo because
it makes me feel safe it's so slow don't disrupt the students while class
is in session I believe familiar with the lesson plan the same regimen you
went through in Liberia right is fighting this guy program just look
how you turned out of course running it in the real world just got a bit
you missed a diamond
virtually though no fuss no must straight to the brain
it's like a dream well maybe dream is the wrong word to kill some POWs some
civilians we give their pleasure centers nice big joke every time plus
they can shine a new body is a graduation present wait did I just get
the whole thing you haven't come I chose this that kid's you son of a
bitch and kids did rock don't make me laugh
lose touch with it as they get older start thinking they know right wrong
that's immoral war crime this code of conduct that kids you can mold
manipulate it performing all kinds of atrocities and there's nothing like a
good atrocity to keep a war going that's why I'm shutting you down you
just don't see the bigger picture do you say you bring this whole place
what's out of the rubble with all these precious brains
nothing changes all the guys in charge of long gone we've got offices around
the world which one of these Harry Potter things to act to find we're
just support we don't create the market for war and who does the
patriots are gone those guys just manage the war economy they did not
create it did you think every battle in history was all part of some big
old conspiracy bullshit war is just part of who we are why fight it
none of this will matter in three hours demand for PMC's is about to
scar like the good old days after 9-eleven what are you talking about
not here follow me okay right then get sundowner do not lose it this time
don't lose it but wait I'm gonna have to lose him for a second because his
items over there boss I'd like to get them is there more than one when
there one is another one over there can I just cut through the door I don't I
don't think I have enough if I go customize right now where's it gonna put
me will it put me back right here how do I get that out of the chest
and ball I'll upgrade because I feel like I'm probably getting close to
one of those second to last areas hopefully just don't put me all the
bird up why did I read that okay fuel cells they're all good I'm gonna go to
skills though because this much that I don't have sweep kick Thunderstrike
whole arm falling lightning diving down the air weapon 200,000 I don't have
enough strength plus three how much is this 16,000 I'm just gonna upgrade this
few times really need it then I have enough for one of the skills right
Thunderstrike channel air pressure into a shockwave sure and sweep kick let
me see what this does right then get sundowner hold on let me just take a
look on the list Thunderstrike this is left stick up down X okay what about the
other one sky high is up up X did I get any other sweet right I think I've
done this accidentally a couple times blade how do I pick stabbing despair
and then after throw dash I mean it's just there's only two moves take off
side yeah yeah well I have enough to upgrade the other weapon to the
night of 2000 everyone I thought for some reason I thought I had 20,000
nevermind right then get sundowner do not lose it this time should I just go
to none right all right here we go make sure I didn't miss anything I'm
too paranoid about that okey-dokey we need to go up here
be nice if you could do the whole thing so I wonder how hard this
boss fight will house this Jack we can play up here without damaging the
merchandise what happens in three hours who the hell was that the Jack is
talking you're too late even at Mach 2 you wouldn't make it kill it that was
a joke take some time what happened in three hours
I don't want to hear that again this whole game is a joke take those back
solar panels that's how we charge
okay I'll try it you can be cooler than that
check play with me good how a copy back there is kind of a problem
right keep your blade away from the chill all right keep my blade away from
the shield
I cut the shields off I chopped the shield off all right so he does that
in the right spot with your place maybe you can drop his gun
I see okay all right um does it have to be a helicopter here like why is this
here just to be annoying isn't it no I just get rid of this thing
out of here let's go all right after I do that he trying to not hit him
again after that right behind him oh god damn it no all right get that thing
out of here again part two
all right so why is it not giving me the uh I'm really confused
he's invincible I cut through one all right I cut through one I'm gonna get
the indicator again no I'm just like brain right do it here we go okay now
I'm gonna cut here I mean I the fucking right stick I gotta get it next time
I just I don't have enough for it I pressed like right stick and it was like
we didn't have it and like flipped all over the place
I might as well just die and just do it again don't do it, just try it next time
do I have enable heals?
I know
you're not gonna be able to help me
yeah I'll just do it again
to be stronger than this you can be cooler than that
Jack
die you stupid helicopter
you're here for no reason
I mean maybe it was like part of the fight or something
no it's just here
no I hit fucking X why?
I just pressed X and E
I didn't
gamer fatigue is setting in
like just straight up gamer fatigue
maybe you can drop his gun
what is this fucking swing here
really?
where am I?
what the fuck?
this is so easy this is the easiest boss fight in the whole entire fucking game
and just me aiming with the right stick somehow is impossible
like I'm so close to him
what the fuck
like look at how close this is
come on again
help me right here
he's trying to not hit, no I'm not
I'm just playing this game for 6 hours
it just drains your body
oh god damn he's back
fucking helicopter here
seriously
are you gonna do this?
what are you doing with that man?
he'll be back
time's over jack
time to die
so that is part of the game
another run on the side of the building
I'm gonna be very very
fly along the side of the building
that hurt
I guess I'll come in
I thought it was gonna be one cut
come on give me it
alright I made it
it's over
what? jack?
what happens in 3 hours?
he'll launch
operation
to cum se
who?
armstrong
armstrong has too much
have a call
to make
got yourself shaving?
asshole
real
you knew this would happen
didn't you?
well
you'll get your wish
up to you now
final boss incoming
I've taken martial HQ
final boss
incoming
hurry
what sundowner said?
I know
anything that'll rival 9-11
cannot be good
maybe less
he said even maktu could not get there in time
if he was serious that's
over 4000 miles away
so whatever it is it's not happening on American soil
if it's gonna spike demand
for PMC's it's gotta be a political hot spot
a coup or civil war
in a stable region wouldn't have a domino effect
and they'd want to draw in a super power
what?
president
he's on his way to Pakistan
what happens to him there?
oh shit
the war on terror part two
contact the military
official channels are frozen since Mexico
unofficial channels would take too long
besides what's our proof?
who's gonna believe us over world marsh?
then we have to get there first
impossible
it is the other side of the planet
even if we were in the world's fastest jet right now
it's not even close
hold up
did you get me?
it's fast
it's really fast
b-a-d-a-c-b-c-s-a-v
that's all over the place
I took that test drunk
custom cyborg party
okay
I got his weapons
and his armor
how much is it?
custom cyborg 15,000
so what's the difference here?
I don't have enough to do that
just a different color
well what's the weapon?
pincer blades
pair of giant high frequency machetes
that can be combined to form massive shears
so in motion they are particularly effective
at catching their prey off guard
developed after careful analysis
of sundowners battle data
10,000?
not good, I wonder if they're good
I'm gonna try it
I'm not gonna put the upgrades on it yet
but I am gonna know I'm not
because it's 40,000
turbulence
I don't have enough, I need to level up
man of many talents
this kind of
space launch once required days
of preparation
solus has been conducting test flights almost every day for the last
six months
as long as we're not breaking atmosphere
they said they can reroute today's flight no problem
amazing
the earth is the cradle of humanity
but mankind cannot stay in the cradle forever
I'm only going as far as the
thermosphere
this thing can't pass the karman line
this mission will just have to wait
and here I was hoping you might bring me back
a monolith
scheisse, two bogeys closing fast
uh oh
who else? the flight pattern suggests
unmanned incorporate 20s
this is a transport chopper
our defensive options are limited
I didn't say sam, I said saaam
with a capital
M
missiles incoming
yes, but not
I'm strong enough to kick out the drone
here they come
this? I didn't
have a nice flight
and people say Germans aren't funny
when did I say that?
one guy said that
there it is
alright, bring the chopper around
this is easier said than done
you know
do you mind living with me?
yeah sure
nooooo
I got out of here
I'm sorry my friend
your sacrifice will not be forgotten
that was quite the fall Raiden
I'm glad to see that you are alright
it's time you got out of
Denver
enemies
clean out
I'll take it
play as a docker
wouldn't that be something
if there wasn't a guy behind me
I would have got that guy in one hells world
I'm not even getting the right guy
use pincher?
well I didn't really get a chance to
go into my menu
I kind of got attacked immediately
oops
so it is on
I can charge up
there's a slow
can people stop calling me?
Mike can you talk to me on the move?
I know
let me just worry about putting some distance
between me and world marshal
and what's left of it
you could have emailed that to me
I'm a 20 billion dollar
cyber ninja
okay
you can email me that and it'll just download into my brain
and I won't even need to hear you talk
okay well I'm turning this shit on
and that whole animation
lasts too long
to the point where now I get a fight
why does it need to do that?
get off the lock on there
get off that lock on
well I
those are very slow aren't they?
and now you're in big trouble
two heals
that's not good
no
I'm not sure I like these
these might be too slow in a game that's this fast
it's kind of hard to use them
where's my AR?
yeah
I couldn't even do it
just tried to do it you heard it
voice just got cracked right there
oh Jeremy
you got it
you got the arm on purpose
I tried
actually here's why those things are not terrible
because they can hit more than one person at a time
nice work Jeremy
you did a great job
I'm doing fine it's okay
Jeremy makes less jokes and he enjoys a game
um
I don't know if
it's just hard to talk and play at the same time
you know what I mean?
when there's a bunch of enemies on screen
it's like
I can't be like
I was at the grocery store yesterday
let me tell you something
hates game? what?
when did you hear that?
when did I say hate game?
I would not be streaming
I would not be playing this game for more than 6 hours
if I hated the game
what?
no
I think it's fun
I wouldn't be playing it if I didn't think that
and by the way let me tell you something
I went to see infinity war for like the 34th time
I saw infinity war
for every single year that I've been live
because I had to
and I'm in line
and let me tell you something
popcorn? fucking expensive
it's like the airlines
you know what I mean? when you go to the movie theater
essentially you're going to an entertainment airline
you know what I mean?
they charge so much but here's the difference
alright I gotta stop that
somebody just said shut up
you see? you know what I mean?
you know what I mean? you know what I mean?
one guy said that
yeah but there's still one guy that's angry
that I just did that
activate the vac system
every time I activate this I fall down
you guys are going to have to have like a vote
amongst yourselves here
Jerma talk, Jerma don't talk
hey you shut up, be quiet
why aren't you talking? we're the jokes
pay attention
do we have like a poll in chat here?
I hate you guys so much
no no no
I'm talking about
ow my stomach
these enemies
ow I'm talking about the
I just like hurt myself
I'm talking about the enemies, the vultures
I'm not talking about
you guys
no, the stupid fucking
vulture guy, I hate them
he called us vultures
oh
oh my
let me see that clip
I want to hear how fucking bad that was
that probably sounded
so bad
ugh
oh no
they gotta get the whole thing there
ugh
I'm losing viewers now
that's not what I meant, y'all know it, come on
holy shit that was bad
wait are people actually leaving
because they thought that's what I was saying
it was actually
somewhere there's somebody that really thought
because I did just say
something about chat and stuff
what do you want me to do
ugh that came out so bad
all the fucking vultures
you got a dragon ball
in your face
alright now don't fuck this up
it's gonna go up
and do it again
we need an apology statement
well I'm sorry that you may have
thought that's what I said
that's not what I said
wait cut car in half, doesn't make you happy right?
can't even cut the car in half
how am I supposed to make everybody happy
nice non apology
that's making me laugh
ugh
that's what I said I hated these enemies
look at me now
I've come to have a lot of perspective
you know what I mean
I got two here
the whole point of the segment is to show how much better you are now
I mean I feel like I
have been brewing a lot
the whole point right?
you can't be a top number one
video game player
you gotta get the muscle
memory you gotta fucking drink some water
you gotta accidentally press L2
twice by the way
twice
who's still around?
who's this?
really?
well now I'm gonna fucking mutilate him
that clip is gonna haunt me
for the next six years
people are gonna take the whole clip and be like
look what he said, can you believe this shit?
fuck
watch the actual clip
does somebody have a full one?
nice chapter okay?
the truth comes out
is this the right one?
pull?
I gotta hear how bad this is
the whole thing
I have like a pull in chat here
no no no
it's not
it's too late
it's too late for me
it's really so bad
there it is
the career is over
I wanna use these
I feel like I could use these if I start to actually play
I want the skill with them too
where's the skill?
turbulence, right here
I guess you can follow up the slash with a powerful downward strike
I'll get it
who is another one?
down burst
why why?
I may have run out of
points here
yeah
you can charge the second hit as well, that's pretty cool
I don't have enough for the mariachi
the devil
everything okay on your side?
I am out of colorado airspace
and nothing on the radar
that guy's face seriously looks like the scream mask
I'm almost there
does he get a full letagrade?
do I get to ride the motorcycle?
woof woof
so like the dogs lose
right
having a little heart to heart
I just analyzed his words and actions
I am unable to ascertain
his motivation
fancy meeting you here
you knew I'd come
I suppose I should thank you for not killing
everyone at the launch site
hehehehe
well not if you say it like that
I just want a mack truck to drive down the road
you're not very good at your job
the war
is the big payoff
big raises all around
once world marshal gets all those contracts
I'm not
talking about money jack
I'm talking ideals
excuse me
forget it
we've both heard enough speeches about higher causes
by now
history will decide who's right
end of story
van van van van
van van
he just starts doing that with his mouth
is the dog the referee?
I don't care who thinks I'm right
I've got cause enough for killing you
what?
oh cool
why that's very good
yes I like that
must you really fight?
don't interfere
this is between us
come on
da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
someone's here
okay
let's dance
da da da da da da da da
here we go
it says click click click
oh it's click click click click
I got it
well that took a long time
oh that's tough that's tough to do
activate
oh I'm just getting embarrassed with my super powers on
oh boy
I don't want to use that move
cut his hand off
oh my goodness I did it
no I didn't
how are you better without your sword?
my mistake
oh ah
I tried to block it and it didn't block it
I get a perfect this one
it's the easiest thing to block
and I keep fucking it all up
got it finally what?
wait what?
he's harder for me without
the sword
calm down
I have to get a perfect that's the problem
perfect
embarrassing me on my own live stream
got to just get up and close and fucking block
what do I do? what do I do?
yeah and
he's going to get his sword
okay oh he broke it
nooo
I'll get it this time
with the fucking kick do something oh no why he does seem to do that move last
time his handoff cut his fucking hand off what the heck Jeremy all right this
time you're not gonna fucking me with this thing I wasn't ready for last
I'm not I'm ready for this shit I said I was ready for my life this gets
me every time it's the worst thing ever no I guess I have a full heal I'm ready
ouch
watch it which way am I going what if he threw rocks at me I'm here bastard
stop doing that do it oh I did it oh has five red balls in my bloodstream well I
don't drink Red Bull that was a fun fight it was really loud the only
streamer to defeat Sam I highly doubt that any cyborg enhancements was this
necessary evidence inconclusive I guess even a eyes don't know everything it is
likely no single correct answer exists additionally human conflict stems from
opposing ideals and societal norms I was not programmed with these
guidelines you're better off figuring those out for yourself new weapon ID
locked a Bt7 high frequency blade oh this thing is soulbound great
my fire indicates Sam inherited the sword from his father going to bury it
I will retain it in memory of Sam one while reference per stream completed I
thought I couldn't use it right we have less than one hour hurry
Roger that combat results chapter results be how much do I have 15,000
where are my big VPs you know I mean I never even got this either well might
as well just get the final upgrade for this fine you know what you know what
the final upgrade I'll get is sure everybody's just do it do it do it I
want you to do it and we're gonna get great box how about let's let's go
back and forth here we'll do original body so I'm gonna go rock
paper scissors okay rock paper scissors shoot I had scissors beats hand rock
paper scissors shoot fuck that I had a head rock you did paper again rock
paper scissors shoot you had a rock and I had I'm not gonna do a Paul for
this turn on don't make me do it don't make me do it I don't do it all right
guys you know what to do well 24 perceived for perceived of people no
it's it's it's no but this is all over the place what are you guys
doing this changes every what is happening right now how is this even
possible 30 set 36 there 39 32 36 31 36 30 foot what this doesn't make me
sense oh I know what's happening never mind everyone people are clicking on
both because 12 15,000 people have clicked the screen okay well I need to
change that one click per user arcade do again now we'll get to see
for real I was mashing click yeah see I know 15,000 viewers no 15,000
clicks still too close to call I'm gonna give it 10 seconds and then whatever it
is and is what I'm purchasing 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 oh looks like mariachi
wins maybe if 22% of people weren't clicking on the robot penis this
would be a little now it's the other way zoom in what why do I need to zoom
in just stay as normal right yeah no I closed it I closed it when I said I
closed it it's mariachi I'm gonna beat the game as them as like the meme
streamer youtuber character you still never apologize yes I did I said I'm
sorry that you didn't understand that what I said was not what you
thought I said I'm sorry about that boo boo boo boo boo you can boo all you
want I closed it and I I got shit before for doing a poll and saying 10
seconds left and then it got to zero and then I waited and people got
upset so I can't do that I have to buy the mariachi uniform it's not way
wasted fucking money I want that right now so bad as a can we do like an
award for best pizza on video game what the fuck is this
mr. riding sir no I am
well do it it's a long story do it he's gonna do it the same audio clip back
it back sorry not really it's okay follow me so exactly what kind of
you'll see you know that's my costume yeah uses a hybrid lace ramjet engine I
designed well are you in a hurry or not right hey thanks Sonny who is this I
supposed to know what that is your solid for I didn't play that one she must be
part of the line of the line that hurt give me some of that pizza man I need
of brainpower no why why do you say that it's taking over the whole internet
doesn't matter well shit from fucking ten years ago doesn't matter nothing you
sure we got the right only base big enough with security contracted out to
all right I'm headed in goodness gracious put the mariachi nice to play that it's
too late to put that on fine what a great end of the video game level and
cutscene wait to see what the thumbnail for this video is gonna be eliminate
all enemies a Lolli Lolli lemonade all enemies
holy shit he just gave up after buying the mariachi that's not true
it is I believe I have all I need for a little surprise
they used to like healthy room one hit you see that yeah their exit codes show
up as unaffiliated wait Marshall has the security contract for the space why
would they have their side work set to the same illegal exit code as
Desperado it's evidence against them no it's their alibi they're making it
look like Desperado hacked their soldiers on site because everyone knows
Desperado has a contract with the Pakistani rebels I'm too tired to mute
the game audio and voice act up this nice big foreign threat all cooked up
and ready to serve the media and the public won't be able to resist
remember WMDs in Iraq we're at the end of the game no I'm not gonna do
that what about any humans on the base Marshal only handled security dead most
likely or brain-jacked if they needed them to keep up appearances they'd
never publicize what airport the president was flying into not in this
region and almost no one would have access to an outside line for security
reasons it wouldn't be difficult to keep things hush hush at least
I'm heading for the control tower if I can destroy the antenna array the US
military will know something's wrong good idea be careful just blue the winds
of destruction away fly backwards
didn't break it today but I'm sure I do not isn't that funny that nice again
these idiots with the rocket launchers where are you even aiming that why he
predicted where I was going to go nice really okay I'm just I can't
believe it I'm shocked at a point where it's I'm just could you stop doing this
maybe predict that I might just restart this instead of a shoot of rocket
proud now I gotta restart the run yeah just turn the whole game I gotta
restart the whole game that runs over here guys I'm sorry much unnecessary I'm
like making shitty noises he's just like a floating piece of hamburger meat it's
hard to hit I need health seriously I have no healing seriously what am I
supposed to do what am I supposed to do I don't know man like it seems like
it's not like is it impossible I don't know what to do the game actually
like this I can't understand how did I miss that many times because when I
would go down and swing it would correct up a little then correct down
you saw what was happening clip it and watch it another guy with a rocket
launcher point like making me angry not block a bolt perfect I'm like
underneath a submarine I get away from the submarine didn't walk that one
saw the arm get it I need this some way I see some water that's all I
need to get some water in me I'll be back to it but I gotta hold on
there's got to be a health potion in here somewhere and I know I called it a
health potion but it doesn't matter it just the thing that refills your health
got one there get up that where is this thing there whoo okay if I could
get that endurance book my mouth is just wide open right there good do a
fortnight dance after I win the game absolutely sure which one you want I
mean there's like 200 of them so nothing else I have one healing whatever
it's called let's go this way can I a stealth kill
what all right all right I need something I want I want you to see
that because do you see it went right through the middle do it that
actually went right through the middle it did these backstab ones well
I'm not like mattering me I'm just it's it's a game that requires a lot
brain power and sometimes it's hard and and that's okay because it's a fun
game and I'm really enjoying it I think it's I think this is a swell video game
how much is this game oh fuck no for real actually no no joking around this
actually is like four dollars or something isn't it right now it's not
even like five bucks I think right now yeah I'm sorry seven dollars and
fifty cents it's currently part of the sale so you like what you see what
all means download it games almost five years old the sale for the game
ends in three minutes really
there's nobody even talking on the screen it's just rocks and explosions I
can talk during this little tiny guy is gonna get out
as usual I'm strong impressive little toy you've got there but your plan ends
here
idiot you're not ending our plan you're expanding it check the internet
lately right check the air force one is turning back to the state what how
they know someone posted photos of what's happening on the base the
whole world is up in arms show
no those tabs the story leaked early then Marshall's plan is ruined the hell
it is look what they're saying the story just went live and already they're
calling for blood but the president was saved and yet American blood was
by Americans he's hot a few dozen soldiers is tragic but nothing to start
a major war over that's just a spark son the excuse we've been waiting for
America's wanted this war for years the Patriots they knew war was good
for the economy four years later their legacy lingers on the memes they
left us their great is a shot nationalism unilateralism materialism
welcome maxims for those with no faith without guiding principles of
their own give yourself up to the whole no need to better yourself you're
American your number one then the only value left is dollar value the
economy so we'll do whatever it takes to keep it humming along even war
especially war bullshit the Patriots planted the seed we don't need them
around to filter and foster their memes any longer we're spreading them just
find ourselves every American man woman and child
I'm surprised that's something to jumpstart the economy out of this
this recession has been stuck in since the fall of SOP and the military costs
wasting billions is going to help the economy
emcees arms manufacturers job creators Jack all those workers I just imagine
Kojima sitting there you know
wait Kojima didn't make this she had to watch this
what any eyewitness reports complicating the message he's surrounding himself
with means I understand metal gear can't follow let's go stop metal gear and
we gotta be some super super leg way to kill him in one hit right
locked it I'm up maybe turn on your face can't knock and
you're looking to climb on top of this I guess I'm doing damage that does a
lot of damage okay I'm just gonna use that oh why am I doing that voice I'm
just like tired and I'm going like ah what does the more of that sure maybe
I don't have to restart all right I got it I got to follow them this way
over here I'm gonna do it again yeah it's very again what's that it's
electrocution again I guess we're going up here one leg down go go go go
go go go go go go what did I do back down the ground checkpoint error right
in the face we'll get him with there we go to three percent two percent
target what do you think of Jeremy
nice nice nice this is really cool no no I don't want I don't want I got to
put him into that beam how could you be far away from that I had it it was
done so come on get it again it should be a dodge yeah it's like you can always
tell what it's gonna be you see the lines that's not gonna be a line
just caught that a classic oh he's got like five hands I have the super
I'm gonna activate it
how does that I'm so mad what there comes a foot oh no and it up top other
leg goes off cut it anything up the leg again I still have one heel oh fuck
I'm not actually gonna pick him up and throw him like well all right that was
pretty awesome I'm suplexing him I'm gonna throw this into him I'm sword
fighting him with his own arm this is so dumb I love it I got an arm wrestle him come on
oh I cut it in half how many times I have to cut them I got it okay use the
other stick I can't they can only go one way how many times can I do
I am turning him into water this is looks like the ocean cut down there I
can't cut down right well wait what the fuck all right I guess I can cut
down that's enough pieces are just funny what's left this
arm look at the parts I'm just getting parts 264
390 I can just farm this forever let the button go all right is it
there's really only one piece of the trigger farm it and buy another suit
don't just make him a little bit fatter and spread his shoulders out
what happened to his face no don't I don't want to say the thing I'm gonna
say I don't want to say the thing is it's an anime reference and people are
gonna be freaking out of it greed for full metal outfits and I said it
already
I'm gonna get my ass kicked here this is the real final final final
he's got so much help I can't move I'm in the corner I can't even get out
of here there's no getting that thing please throw me out of the corner that
was great I'm in the corner again I never I never left I have to like
restart this and get out of the corner was he just going right and right no
he wasn't right till this missed him oh my god right in the head come on
headshot headshot put it away trying and I'm back in the corner right on
his body that was right on his body and I know I'm having a little bit of an
up about I tried to dodge
so glad he's doing this for me
you're just another maggot crawling in the pile all right the truth then
you're right about one thing I do need capital and votes want to know what a
dream that one day every person in this nation will control their own
destiny a land of a truly free dammit
these lawyers
there's no saving it we need to pull it out by the roots
wipe the slate clean
why are we emote only
the weak will be purged and the strongest will thrive free to live as
they see fit they'll make America great again
are you talking about when did this game come out what I'm using war as a
business to get elected so I can end
in mine people will die and kill not for money not for oil not for what
they're told is right every man will be free to fight his own wars
mr. really liked this game well I don't write my own speeches should try
fighting for what you believe in sometime Jack it's a Reagan club or a
nation or for anyone else maybe I was wrong about you am I finally
getting through with this world of pointless wars dusting them off
yeah come on you're not greedy what is going on just baiting it out that's the
worst way you could possibly get up and look behind you
can't fret over every day not when you're purging right what do you know
about weak you weren't born poor you've never been hungry
fight and steal and kill justice survive but you did survive
sheer force of will following your own set of rules with your own two
hands you took back your life and now take yours the real boss fight no
weapons just this fight right apparently I guess I don't know I just
killed the whole moment that killed the whole entire moment how would you
yeah I was doing cartwheels that cutscene was so long I forgot how to
play the game 0.1 at spoke out here that one I'm gonna I'm gonna stop is
there more of this shit I can't handle this anymore
nanomachines son they harmed in response to physical trauma can't hurt
me Jack just say glasses aren't made of nanomachines how they still find
this should be broken but off your head what an oversight by the deaf
very mean
all right I think we're about done here right
working towards this and on the last day Lonnie has me doubting the whole
thing we'll leave it up to fate then shall we will see a duel to the death
the best man win Sam I cut him down and that's that back to a regularly
scheduled international now I can hurt him but if he beeps me if I die here
the lock on my blade will disable after a couple hours
can you what happens after that is up to you
huh even dead that guy's a pain in my ass and this is stupid I'm too cool
you think that little sword can save your master well go ahead then but
make no mistake fight oh sometimes I look over you guys say the funniest
rim shipment
I was not designed to fear termination however directives world one is to
ensure all data acquired is preserved and pass along to expire here would
violate that directive that's a good boy
however right came to my aid I have learned from him when Samuel fell data
analysis was inconclusive but that has changed I have established new
parameters now created my only directives like a 30-minute ending
sequence here
now for the real fight right I said my sword was a tool of justice I used an
anger not used for vengeance but my favorite flavor strawberry and besides
this isn't my soul
it's gonna play a good song like that right be standing near him when he does
that
all me just to do is to kill me what happened tap nice get the sword back
let's pick it up or it was just automatically my hand get this work
please oh god wait a minute oh no not this dumb thing got it what
okay got it
the ground is their health pack on the ground better be yes it is give me the
element with the other go I got it got it got it got it got it got it with the
sword I don't know this I'm freaking out right now with do I have the
sword just don't when I don't start I get it I get it again it's like a
world of and now you say world worker a thousand times a stream but
that's a blow to work up telegraph encounter I got it grab the sword
quick for the health yep fuck these are everywhere just stand here oh fuck I
didn't know he did that oh man what am I thinking here
didn't swing the first time 75% this is like a it's um it's just
impossible to lose the green oh no he's healing cut the green office head I've
no idea that man caught me he I was above him there one more time I got
all right hey how are you dead aim over 0.1 percent one hit me
nothing happened I thought I just had a hit him once
I know beat him part of the game part of the show through the chest game
complete and this is what we cut him up a new million pieces here we go all
of his juices are followed up
you've guaranteed the status quo will go on for a while longer at least war
will continue as an institution that's industry men will fight for reasons
they don't understand causes they don't believe in but at least I'll leave a
worthy successor you
I'm not gonna say use whatever methods you see fetch don't let legal
bullshit get in the way and if it costs a few lives so be it oh what the hell
should I be awake for this what a game BBB we're a summer blade is
unlocked the Infinity War has been watched tires
operations within the country this is a growing tensions within Pakistan
between the country's civil and military leadership with many in the
government calling on the ISI military intelligence sleep mask pizza oh I
can't wait to eat I'm I can't wait to have food the last time let it go
Courtney least Armstrong will never be president
is established nice work doc I guess the world's first cyborg staffing firm is
officially open for business
no we're sure this isn't child labor
this bit others the spill okay I get it
besides this way they learn a trade or have some discipline it's not a
perfect solution you know what at least these kids will get a decent
education I'm not about to return them to the streets or to broken homes at
least we can give them a cheese how much weight were you putting on his
shoulder for that to happen
all leaning in at the same time that's kind of weird
yeah okay you make me head spin you know somebody could have just died
right there really slow down he's dead he just killed him it's about a crazy
world for me see that ninja we never think I've been this kind of life he
rescued me too you know saved my life I owe him everything to some people
he'll always be Jack the ripper those papers are huge yeah they are they are
gigantic I know all about his past and the font is to hurt a lot of
people that's not the right and I know the right and I know is a hero
oh right that was the game that's it that'll get rising revenge and so
they're not making another one well that's a hundred dollars from ace
mcclase ace mcclase thanks with a hundred bucks good job chumbo German
Merc incredibly generous of you thank you so much for a hundred fucking
dollars somebody got punch punch gop gave five community subs earlier I missed
it because I was in the middle of like a meltdown or something that was that
was good that was good I needed to take like I just see what happened you
know I started to get a little fuss flustered a little frustrated about
four and a half hours in go grab water just like just hang on for a
second take a sec come back and then we're good to go you know no that
was fun for seven dollars and fifty cents you know I know something really
funny this stream is seven hours and 48 minutes long the game was seven dollars
and fifty cents didn't that the dollar a minute I know that's that
that's a cent that's us wait is that a cent every that's a cent per
minute a dollar a minute would know that's not that would be 700 let me
seven it's too late it's too I'm too frustrated it's a dollar every one point
well you know what I'm saying it's a seven dollar and fifty cent game is
seven hours and fifty cents one cent per hour whatever the fuck it is I
don't even know thanks for watching seven hours and fifty cents a dollar
an hour point eight whatever it is I was a post credit scene apparently
we're gonna stay but also I want to the reason why we go I had an
opportunity to to leave and try do it again tomorrow or something but I want
to get the whole thing done tonight because I want to do a longer stream
tonight because I have some plans over the next couple days and I'm not gonna
be around for the next two days to stream so you will see me again I
know I've been going it's really erratic the last week with the whole
New Year's Eve thing and pushing back streams and the Christmas Eve
thing but really wanted to do at least like an eight to nine plus hour stream
tonight so what's gonna happen is today I know what technically today for a lot
of you guys what's today Thursday what is today today's technically Wednesday yes
so Thursday Friday I'm not gonna be live and then we're gonna go
Saturday Sunday Monday we'll go three days in a row after I come back from
doing things that I was planning on doing so we'll do the whole weekend
Saturday Sunday and then Monday there's a lot of shit to do I was
thinking about booting up the PlayStation 2 and doing Simpsons hit
and run for the weekend maybe and if not that then there's also best for
cleanup detail there's also a more kenshi there's a I plan on going three
or four straight days in a row so final thoughts that if you don't own
this game it sure is a lot of fun for seven dollars great Canadian Fuck
Club just gave up ten minute itself ten more to add to the list of the
hundreds the actual hundreds of community subs that you have given do a
fortnight dance what are you talking about have ever played monster hunter
yeah actually I played a lot of monster hunter world streamed it a few
times played pretty much to the end of the game not on stream but Darth
Vader what oh no I played one of the old ones on stream too you said
you would do dance I don't I don't know what you guys talking about do
the fortnight dance double D thanks to the five community subs right at
the end here we'll do the bits too we'll hang out for a little while I
want to see if there's something at the end but thank you so much double D
five community subs don't run away from this all right fine really I mean
I've got I don't know what which one is which but I'm gonna crash the
game okay so I'm just gonna say this is one is it hairline turn off the
hairline worst hair this is this looks good that's the baby little kid
dance all right here we go here is the end of the stream voice cutscene
acknowledge the DLC okay how much does the DLC add thank you that's a
couple hours two stories and about Sam that's cool it's great so three
hours super fun all story related all right yeah that's kind of a weird
like that's gonna have to be a scenario where because if it's like a
three-hour experience that's that's not enough to do for a whole stream so that
have to be a day where there's something to do for two or three hours
and then that we kind of need two three to four hour experiences back to
back you know I mean I keep saying it you know you know me New Year's
resolution okay 2020 I'm gonna stop saying we go oh good good there are
doctors research and staffing service certainly help I hear you cost them a
lot of money not to mention killing their funding literally the
breathtaking program is finished but the larger company is not I'm afraid
that someone will buy them PMC's are in demand once again
fighting for reasons they don't know microcomputers big pardon no nothing so
your mind is made you will not come back I understand but then what will
you do I'm so glad they ended this game on
oh my god uh gnarled up no populate dog g and RL apocalyptic cheeseburger
hundred dollars feel like I've seen a hundred dollars pop up here like three
or four times tonight thank you guys thank you so much and apocalyptic
cheeseburger says German thanks while I know you do streaming for everyone I
found that your streams helped me through the hardest parts of my life
now the new year has arrived and my first semester for college went
splendidly well I felt it was necessary to thank you I'm glad I saw you play
one of my favorite games and here one of my favorite OSTs is the start to
the new year I know it's a frustrating game sometimes keep being you
best wishes general it's general okay general apocalyptic cheeseburger thank
you the hundred dollars thank you so much happy to play I mean this was
very heavily yeah whatever it's a C this was a highly requested game
people said play you'll like it you'll like it it's frustrating but you'll like
it and I mean it was but it wasn't though it was just a few parts of the
game that I was just having trouble with but that was also in a gamer
fatigue sets in a little bit you got to go drink get a drink of water and
you come back and you're fine hold on hi I didn't look at these look at
these stats legs is severed to right I only severed to a right leg
one time 43 right arms severed what is title zero oh my god
Gorn hole gave a hundred dollars German here's some more some money
please enjoy from your favorite man Gorn hole thank you 100 100 100 100
thank you so much guys played it continuously without quitting to the
main menu is that really what that means so what is title zero that was
hey that was a speed run it was a slow one complete normal or higher
difficulty in less than eight hours all right I did it I did that mr. one
percent complete normal or higher difficulty while earning 300,000 BP or
more one percent complete normal or higher difficulty while only using the
high frequency blade as a weapon thank you battle test to complete
normal or higher difficulties by being discovered by anything 50 or more times
that seems like a lot Jack the Ripper cut your enemies at least a
thousand times using blade mode oh that's what title is get it got it these
achievements but thank you so much going well thank you so much general
pocket length of cheeseburger this I don't even know what to say thank you
fuck it's a total a C total no it can't be a C total it has to be B
so I'm just here play time four hours and 35 minutes what that doesn't
make any sense the streams been going for eight hours was that all the
cutscenes and pauses in cutscenes four hours and 35 minutes all right that's
gonna be my time we'll go to the back of the bits back earlier back of the
bit readings here yeah and then you guys will see me again on Saturday so
take care everybody if you're gonna take off it's pretty late for a lot
of you guys now so do the code do the code what do you mean the okay
hold on do the code you the Konami hook I I know by heart don't worry I'd
wear it here the title we wish I do it okay
metal gear rising revengeance did it up up it's up up down down left right
left right BA start it adds a difficulty are you kidding me I imagine the game
on hard is incredibly frustrating isn't very hard and is a revenge I just need
to know well we'll go through the bits while I do this I was just curious it's
just just to how horrible this is thank you binary man for the one
dollar chat chat where the chat we what do we do the prey on twitch we
stalked of odds where the chat thank you binary man mouse on screen binary
man gave four dollars why is this three times louder is that what it does
louder I actually can't read between life and heavy strikes to match the
situation some of you guys are made made for that not me the bad game
I guess he's dead forever yeah but thank you binary man for the one two
three four five dollars here hey Jerma I know I'm a little bit late but
here's a vid I made for the green screen movie night and didn't finish in
time hope you like it hold on to it we're gonna do a another green screen
movie night so we will compile it again we're gonna do an encore night
so hold on to that video but thank you binary man for your five dollars
here this chat counting count is counting as we counters count because
we like counting you lost me it does but thank you so much for the five
dollars thank you super simple the one dollar congrats I'm becoming a top 900
streamer I did actually hear about this no longer top 1000 top 900 it did
happen I'm number 899 on twitch hey see you like see you at the top 800
let's go but thank you flank tank for the one dollar New Year's night I
had a dream similar to this dream similar to this I have no idea what
hell you just linked me but let's see I knew it was I got it no I didn't I knew
what it was whatever I don't even care it's fine thank you for the one doll
though and what a weird dream thank you German is the best for the one
dollar New Year's means a new anime Germany better watch Jojo on your
anime for the year fans will get mad at you if I don't I will see I have
to do so what the anime the year of the year is going to be but thank
you thank you both first for the five dollars really liked your outfit last
dream it had that about to announce the new Xbox feel thank you
Kali Brady gave $100 eight hours ago a long time ago but holy shit thank you
so much happy new year to you thank you divas for the three bucks sticks
renegade for the one dollar just like last year can you wish me a belated
birthday Xmas boy over here also you still have to draw my fursona
well happy birthday first of all Merry Christmas happy birthday happy new year
and I can't draw I'm not very good at it thank you those sticks here's to
another year solid milk thanks to the one dollar don't be a weenie do hard
mode no I got no I just wanted to have fun and it was still like
challenging first playthrough right you know it's okay thank you Siroc for
the one dollar hail Jerma during one of my Kenshi streams you commented you
commented on making glue man but never did so I did and here is an image of
my glue man playthrough they age that's kind of ridiculous I didn't know
that they aged that's really cool actually hey p337 are thanks to the
three dollars and 33 cents they say hey hey p337 are how are you he
doesn't even get older dragonflyer thanks for the ten bucks happy new year
Jerma can't wait to see you at PAX weast Jerma pain I don't know if I'm
gonna be going to I don't know if I'll be at PAX West I'm not sure I'm
gonna go it depends I don't know I really don't know maybe ah he said
East not weast I very clearly wrote weast W E A S T that could be either
why would I add a W to PAX East show glue man I did they did not go into the
twitch chat I just posted it here already but I don't know can we'll see
about conventions it depends on a bunch of different factors but thank you
dragonfly for the ten dollars thank you hero of trains for the one dollar
RIP Jex 2018 come on Jex is just fine he was just sleeping tonight dark
star thanks for the one dollar I'm so fucking jazz you're playing this game
just remember the fundamentals of CQC I did and then I lost it and then I got
it back again okay see 4g thanks for the two dollars rules of nature and then
they say rage thank you sly 161 thanks for the one dollar is this the
guy who died to Metal Gear Ray in Metal Gear Rising know me oh it's a
new it's a new you saying I get it thank you boomer you know that's not
your name it's but it's Bosmer thank you boss Moroya for the ten dollars
thank you so much for ten bucks hey Jerma I was busy on New Year's Eve I
wasn't able to watch the stream live but I watched the VOD last night it
was a great stream but when I went to bed I had a horrific nightmare when my
hair was replaced with your hair it was very messy and I couldn't get it
to look good so I locked myself in the bathroom and freaked out while
everyone outside was confused this is not a joke this was the actual dream
your hair gave me a nightmare looks good though on you all right you can't
first of all you can't say your hair gave me a nightmare and then say but it
looks good on you that's contradicting statements but thank you
Bosmer for the ten bucks sorry about your dream mostly lost thanks for the
one dollar local streamer isn't sure if there is stealth in a Metal
Gear game but there is no there is here's how you tell if there's
stealth in a video game there was no stealth in that game I'm sorry there
wasn't where was the crouch button if a game has stealth it has a crouch or a
duck and walk slow button there was no stealth in that game there was walk
that's not stealth it's called using the box no no no no no no I'm sorry
that doesn't count the box does not count as a crouch how doesn't that
count because that's you're putting yourself into a box there is no push
in l3 and you go down and you're creeping around it's an item that's an
emote that's an emote dance from fortnight is what that was in this
game that's how it wasn't the other Metal Gears no wasn't and the other
Middle Gears you could go up against the wall and go well where was my
whistle where's my knock you crouch down in the box did you pay it hey
Hydra thanks for the one dollar these bits are for the Jeremy buys a new
suit that actually fits foundation who wears I don't know I don't want I'm
not gonna wear a suit why do I why no I don't need a suit I got a perfectly
good suit thank you Hydra I will put that into the into the box which I am
crouching and apparently which means it's a stealth game god I'm getting
tired and you can tell it cuz I'm just being I'm being just fucking
strange thank you wild hike for the ten bucks pogchamp thank you wild
for the ten bucks you never apologize for being mean to us I was
not mean to anybody you I said something about an enemy in the game
and it happened right after right after we talked about how chat was
yelling at me to do two different things you hate us I still can't get
over that while thank you for the 10 15 16 17 dollars wild go buy a slice
I will I am hungry so that's definitely something I'm gonna do
Hawkeye of mine thanks for the two dollars what's with this game and
using feet for sword play chat you know what to do with this Kappa I don't I
don't know what to do with that I don't know what he means what do you
mean hey lucky bone thanks for the $30 we got you earlier but thank you so
much again for 30 bucks your accidental bits I'll take them thank
you really appreciate it a dapper dog thanks for $1 German this is one
of my favorite games ever I'm so excited you streaming it PS thanks
for being amazing as always keep being you a lot of people really
like this game huh judging about how many people like this game I'm
surprised they did not do anything else with the game I mean I guess the two
DLCs it just is it a really a scenario where Konami just doesn't get
it and it just makes slot machines you guys know that right yeah yes we
know it sucks they have a lot of great franchises the developer of the
game said they'd love to make a second and Konami said no weird but thank you
flug boy for the $1 hey German hope you're having a great start to the new
year my friends and hey you know speaking of new year I heard you have
one anime per year threshold so I think it's time of year for you to
catch up on a little show called Jojo's Bizarre Adventure also not
just part one every part love you dearly German sorry I've only been
given a dollar lately turn my heart no don't don't apologize for giving me money
don't apologize for saving giving me money that is a huge gesture to give a
stranger on the internet money it means a fucking shitload to me don't
worry about that and I used the word stranger I mean I mean that like
physically you know I mean because obviously a lot of you guys have been
around for a long time but I mean that in a literal physical way you're
giving somebody money and you're hanging out here and we have a good time
don't feel bad about that don't feel bad that you're not giving me enough
money if you want to give me bits or subscribe to this channel thank you
but I really hope you guys don't feel fucking bad oh is it enough it's
gonna be more than that no no no no it doesn't thank you German is
physically strange I really truly hope that you guys don't feel like that
because if you give you give somebody ten bucks twenty bucks to a doll of fifty
dollars a hundred dollars that's a big gesture to that person it is the fact
that you would even think about doing that in the first place I don't collect
this money and go oh well I mean no no thank you
KXC thanks for the 30 bucks victory bits 30 dollars from KXC somebody
just gave 50 I think right now yeah Fitty gave $50 hey German I'm starting
to feel bad about this we have to come clean and don't pretend that don't you
don't know what I'm talking about we both know that whenever one guy said
something it was me you paid to say that so that you don't have to do
what chat wants it's killing me to keep this a secret you got you got a
lot of accounts thank you for $50 it's a lot of money thank you thank
you Fitty and keep up the great work and tomorrow I you know when I come back on
Saturday make sure talk about like talk about fucking talk about bazooka Joe
again you know I mean and I'll like bring it up and we'll talk it would be
funny thank you so much for the $50 KXC yes victory bits thank you for
$30 great Canadian FK club thanks for the five dollars and your
community subs thank you so much they say Franker Z smelly boy thanks for
$1 hey P E T E R you're that ninja that spells something but thank you thank
you Nick for the $1 rules of nature thank you I've figured out what that
is it's a song I think Alec thank you Alec for the five dollars I just
thought of a very uncomfortable event imagine biting the side of your fork
and expecting food but just tasting metal and pain that's not that's not
a good thing to think about it's like chewing on tinfoil ah chewing on tinfoil
with fillings it like electrocutes you all right why did I just say that ah
okay thank you Alec for the five dollars by the way don't do that it's
bad do not do that it's time for slime thanks for the five dollars I
was devastated during the New Year's Eve stream when chat almost voted
bugleberry for worst new character I had to make this and share it would
deeply appreciate if you played it well chat spams germa Pluto what do you mean
let me see what is this well don't spam it yet you haven't seen anything
yet hold on don't spam it yet
and no one's what it's like to be hated to be fated you're telling only lies but my dreams
bugleberry is not going away see something a little tidbit of
information that you guys need to know I love that character I love that
character it's like my favorite character I'm like actually it makes
me laugh that so many people like fuck this guy you know how much fun I had on
that first stream hiring him having him come and do that that was just fun I
did it was fun probably gonna fucking do it again thank you time for slime
for that touching video the five dollar mask you bought at a pharmacy for
Halloween that mask was not five dollars at a few zeros no that means
it's five thousand that mask was not five thousand dollars that mask was five
grand okay gonna get my money's worth out of that character hey thanks
peaceful Haley for the one dollar hey Jeremy just wanted to know how you
were doing and also just wanted to let you know how amazing your
community is and the friends I've made a here on discord on here and on
discord and the people who come over and watch my stream feels good when I
can entertain others and that's all thanks to you or else I wouldn't have
known what to do with myself so thank you Jeremy you're awesome
yeah I fought for a long time to even have that discord because I wasn't sure
if it was something I wanted to do do I want to have a discord but
people do discords I do think the paid discord no no why would I do
that like sub rooms channel how do I even manage this like I didn't know if
it was something I was gonna do because that it's hard to do that it's
hard I mean as much as it's easy to be like I have a discord and go
there and but I whatever managing something like that with thousands of
people is actually hard to do so you can thank the mods for being around all
the time to take care of that and to make it so much easier to have that
because I'll be very frank with you if the mods in this community were not
on top of their game every day that discord does not exist I wouldn't be
able to have it I've tried before to have communities I've had groups
I've had oh I'm just gonna set up this thing and maybe I can like a steam
group and shit and I never can manage it so without them there is no discord
and I'm really glad that it can exist because messages like this proved
that it's worth having for sure no right music's not playing but thank
you peaceful Haley appreciate it uh yakko boo thank you for the $1 no
message thank you thank you yakko Alec thanks for the two bucks so when
are you gonna play ocarina of time I'm probably not gonna play ocarina of time
on stream probably not if I was to do a Zelda game on stream it would probably
be breath of the wild but even that's kind of a long shot at this point so
if I was to play a Zelda game that would be the one that would be played
but why oh cuz it's a pretty huge time commitment I played a lot of red
dead and I streamed a lot of red dead and isn't breath of the wild a
huge game this stream this community I feel like and I'm like this too I don't
really like to have oh yeah breath of the wild breath of the wild breath of
the wild because when I get into a game I want to play it but I don't
really like streaming a game more than four or five six times in a row
and then if I leave it I'll come back to it there's all this shit
that's going on more ideas and more games and I never usually go back to
it yeah I would say play breath of the
wild on your own maybe stream it once or twice that's typically how it goes yeah
I'll play a game that's like breath of the wild like a red dead like there's a
lot of other ones that have been in that similar realm play it on stream
few times maybe three or four times and then all right that was cool I'm
gonna finish it on my own so that's definitely possible please go back to
red dead though I beat the game off-stream I completed red dead
redemption 2 off-stream betrayal it was great did you finish everything I
finished everything everything I love rockstar games so I did all the story
and it did all the side stuff I didn't do all the hunting stuff though
but I did I think pretty much all the dialogue content that's in the game
to be honest I'm glad you enjoyed it definitely worth keeping some games
yeah I mean this this could bleed into a conversation about the game that you
saw tonight it's a different when I play a game
off-stream it's a lot different you know I'm just kind of sitting there
and I'm not really talking I'm just enjoying the game and having fun I'm
not really speaking or anything and it could actually have I have some
trouble especially the games that require a lot of attention and this
is because of my uncontrollable ADHD looking at chat and talking and let's
talk about this thing and this thing and it's it's kind of it's I like
having you know the off-stream sit there with my mouth open type of
type of experience and yeah you can't really do that on stream I can't
really sit here and just like this for like 40 straight minutes that's
another five community subs from soft 33 thank you soft for the five
surprised and glad you have time to play games on your own and with how much you
put into your streams yeah but remember I want I want this I want each stream
that I do to engage and talk and hang hang out and interact with you guys
and sometimes it is nice just to turn off my brain and just not just sit
there and I'll play a game like Red Dead for like six straight hours it's
just eating fucking chocolate you know I mean but yeah it is but but there's
another thing though this is why it's it's kind of a double-edged sword
because if in games a lot of times I'll be playing a game just alone in the
dark with the headphones on or something and all of a sudden something
fucking hysterical happens or something awesome happens and I'm
looking around just like where did you see anybody see that I nobody's in
the room oh so I was awesome I should have been streaming this what
you know what I mean it happens a lot I think there's a balance somewhere
Bixby start game record how many Jax moments happen in private I mean I
could tell you how many I could say oh it happens all the time you're not
gonna believe me you know oh yeah you know you should have seen when I
was playing off stream I didn't saw I did all this cool shit it's like
okay sure you did but it's all good it's all good but thank you thank
you Ike turtle for the one dollar a towel I rubbed German nose wipe here's
a sewer dollar what's a sewer dollar thank you as a right reaction for the
one dollar chat maybe if you guys stopped spamming 40 things for him to
do he would actually be able to notice a single thing in the game and maybe
if you stopped spamming shit then it would actually be a surprise to him
instead of spoiling it 20 minutes in advance 20 minutes in advance thank
you as a right reaction it's alright though I mean like yes sometimes I do
look over it and I see three four different things before what you're
doing you need to do that you got to do this you have to do this what you
doing why go that way go the other way that weapon sucks and it's just
like I don't know what oh but that's just that's just what happens though
it's it you know it back seating nice not even no it's all right Ken
and like I get it like I'm not doing something right or if I'm fucking up and
do something wrong and I'm not learning it yeah probably is frustrating to watch
but it's also frustrating for me too because I want I want to figure it out
and I want but I don't want to have to figure it out where it's a
detriment to the stream you know if I spend 50 minutes trying to figure out
how to block somebody it's like fucking Jesus Jeremy give me a break
but the game the gnome porn links got old spoilers or shit though really hope
people can avoid that stuff I didn't really care I mean the one the only
thing that I kind of was just like oh okay was when everyone was screaming
about the cat so I mean that's the real that's the only spoiler I really
think I received during the stream maybe a couple other things too but I
don't know it at the end of the day it's just people are just trying to
have fun ruined that cutscene about memes yeah but it's alright I was not
I've that was not making me frustrated what was making me frustrated was the
game you know it's a tough game I don't think it was anything in chat
that I was like shut up everybody I think it was one time maybe where when
I was telling what I was told to go in four or five different directions
you're too forgiving you need to punish your chat more but but but
punish for what you know if I start punishing for stuff like you suck at the
game or hey you went the wrong way or spoilers I mean a lot of people would
be on that list too before am I gonna ban them if I ban somebody every time
somebody told me that you're doing it wrong I think I think half the chat
wouldn't exist if you nobody there the mods would even get banned that's
how you know when it's unnecessarily rude it can be kind of depressing yeah I
mean I'm not gonna lie I'll be completely open here sometimes I look
over and it's I read something and it's just like fuck that person's is
really fucking mad at me right now and somebody's saying something fucking
mean and shit it's just like god I wish I could I really I don't want you
to be saying that that doesn't happen that often though I would say
if I stream this 365 days in a year if I stream a hundred days a year if there's
like a hundred and twenty five hundred and thirty streams a year maybe like
three or four of those streams I will actually look over and be like kind
of depressed or annoyed by something doesn't happen that often and ninety
nine point nine percent of the time it's we're just having fun I've been
I know I've spent a lot of time on this topic but I think it's worth
talking about like somebody saying that I suck no no no because I know that
that's you know I do dumb shit in games all the time that's not what I'm
talking about I'm talking about like me something really mean that's like a
full-on like sentence about how something I'm doing is so stupid or
I'm such a piece of shit or something it's just like fucking hell
mr. German can you eat anybody who complains about bugleberry gets me
like that and it's so easy let me tell you that it's so easy it's such
an easy out to say well fuck the haters fucking haters fuck the haters but that
that's a person with an opinion and they have it for a reason you know I
don't I hate being that kind of person that's just like a fuck the
haters cares yeah fucking hater no I that person has an opinion and what
am I gonna do yeah but their opinion is wrong no if somebody comes
in here and doesn't like what I'm doing then that's I'm not gonna be mad at
that person because they don't like what I'm doing that's it they'll move on
and that's it I'm not gonna be like oh you didn't like what you see here
you're a fucking little baby and let me tell you that you're a little
baby no sorry I didn't think it was fun maybe you'll check back again
another time but this is a pretty long-winded comment about all this
it's a cool heart to heart yeah it's sometimes we do these sometimes you
just gotta talk it's all fun and games but you know we're all people here so
right after that Roger Cheeto thanks for the $1 you missed the memes stop
talking during cutscenes dumbass the timing the timing was impeccable but
thank you for the $1 mostly lost thanks for the $1 because you're
apparently incapable of processing two things at once here's the memes
cutscene thanks for the dollar mostly let the roast continue protect him no
that's funny that's funny I mean if I had looked over and saw that like
four hours ago because I was already like the game was like give I was
getting kind of mentally fatigued if I looked over and saw that I would
have been like okay fine fine no it's all good thanks for the dollar you guys
thank you for speaking a dollar thank you for real though for the $1 watch
this no this is not something that will get you in trouble I love the
the context has to be there
he's just like puking thank you it's not gonna get you in trouble that it's not
thank you thank you ushi corn for the $1 it's gonna be the last season of
Eric Andre is it really well I guess maybe he's been doing other shit
though he's been on other TV shows that aren't the Eric Andre show so
he's probably he's branching out a lot but thank you ushi corn thank
you thank you kill Ganon for the dollar 15 I got fired today I'm sorry but I
decided to use this time to pursue something more creative I just wanted to
ask when you started making videos that it terrified you that everyone
would hate what you'd made no because I wasn't making videos I wasn't making
videos I don't think it's this kind of hard to describe and explain but
I wasn't I wasn't making videos to try to get like an audience I was kind of
just doing them it was a way for me to pass my time and I thought they were
fun and I wasn't really in the back of my mind of oh somebody's gonna hate
this I was just kind of doing it it really didn't it took probably like
20 or 30 videos remember I'd had no expectations at all zero absolute zero
if I got 20 viewers it was like oh that whoa okay who that where they
from well this is cool so when your intentions are not to I guess when your
intentions aren't to necessarily have an audience you really don't mind or
don't necessarily care who comes across it because you're doing it
because you want to make them not necessarily to have a bunch of
people and watch my first 10 20 videos it's just me just talking and
being like fucking weird and saying like strange shit and just doing
nothing but now I don't think that the words not terrify but I I don't want
people to hate the things that I make so I try as hard as I'm able to to try
to do as best as I can because I in my heart and in my brain think that
the best that I can is hopefully good enough I think everybody thinks that
everybody just hopes the best that they can is good enough and there are
a bunch of people here now that I know already kind of get it because they've
been here for so long it was it's a weird it's a weird thing where made
videos for years didn't really have that many expectations I wasn't like
partnered on YouTube for a bit particularly took like a hundred and
fifty videos I think of more than a like at least fifty to a hundred
before I had any money at all from YouTube and there's a bunch of
people here that just a lot of people just kind of get it and they
think the things are fun and you guys are a part of the joke as much as you
know for the half the shit that is done on this stream I don't get it did
you lose the password to your main channel I know it's a meme but I'm
really curious I've talked about it a bunch of times before but YouTube just
wasn't it just wasn't doing it for me anymore and I mean that in a
bunch of different ways it creatively monetarily that's back when
never YouTube would changed a lot of shit there was a lot of
subscription shit that they were changing there was a bunch of ad
revenue stuff that they were getting rid of and it was it was hard to let's
say if I was gonna spend like a week on a video it just really wasn't
possible anymore so I didn't lose the password to my main YouTube
channel I just stopped using it because I started losing interest and
twitch seemed like the next thing that I wanted to try to do I don't
know what the next thing will be but I'm not gonna force myself to make
a video just because I like have to that's not gonna happen if I am not
wholeheartedly enjoying every everything that I'm doing it'll show
it'll just be forced and I don't want to force stuff I'd rather have it come
naturally and have fun natural raw German I've told I've told you guys
this you know over the last two three years on twitch if what I'm doing is
not something that I'm having fun doing and enjoying doing and having
you know more ideas are coming out because remember on YouTube there was a
lot of things I wanted to try and a lot of things I wanted to do and now
that's I have to have that same itch on twitch on itch on twitch nice rhyme you
ever thought about saying that on the main channel innocent people who didn't
even know you stream just thought you kind of disappeared yeah I think part of
me in my brain somewhere kind of doesn't want to make that video
somewhere up in my brain I don't want to tell people it's over here it's
on twitch and see on twitch this is a weird lock in my brain because
that's such a huge portion of my life it's like this this door that's still
up there that I I've got this I know there's a monster in that room but I
don't know what to do about him he's just in there I can't let him out
he'll eat me just tell them about the second channel yeah I've thought
about it but I mean that's another thing too I just don't don't pissing
people off and making a video on on that main channel saying hey by the
way I know it's been a couple of years since you last seen me but I'm done
isn't that like kind of you made you waited two you waited two years to make
a video saying that I'm done on YouTube hey guys when was the last time
you heard my voice hey it's a new upload from German on a five here it
is okay I'm done that's kind of pointless in a way I gotta go I gotta
get out of here but closing that door is I don't think it's even
necessarily necessary because I don't know a year or two from now a couple
of years I don't know who knows maybe I will want to go back to YouTube and
make more video content actual edited video car I don't know I never had a
plan I don't have a plan you know like I did this there's no errors the
plan nope I have plans week to week and month to month if I have
something that I'd like to do on stream or back when I was making
YouTube videos I got plans to do content and do things but long term of
where I want to be and what I want to do not really just wherever the wind
takes me is what's gonna happen what would you do if streaming was no longer
profitable um something else you know cuz you have to remember I'm 30 I'm
turning 34 this year so I mean I wouldn't just disappear but it's at
some point I gotta do if I wasn't doing streaming or YouTube or
something I would have to do something else I wouldn't stop streaming but it
wouldn't be a scenario where it was you know three four days a week or four or
five whatever days a week for eight nine you know this is nine hour stream
they'd be shorter it would be maybe once or twice a week when I had time
if you stop now what would you do huh that's that's a tricky one as a
really tricky that's a tricky question street magic um probably
something with the animals I'd go get like a vet tech I'd go back to school
probably and get a vet like tech degree or something because I I did a
just about a year stint at an animal shelter and it was great I would do
that for a job without doubt as a person who runs a rescue and as a vet
I prove yeah no I'd animals are awesome I would do it you going to
school to be vet tech right now let us know how it goes and that's probably
what I would be doing if I wasn't doing this I feel like that maybe I'll still
do it anyways and I mean I feel I'm probably one of those people that's in
their 50s and just decides you know what I'm just gonna go work at a zoo I
don't even care if I'm like the guy I'm if I'm the guy that's like
cleaning up after the animals and refilling water dishes and shit cool
that's fine with me pop pug champs did be the guy and from up and sell
balloons just buy just buy a farm somewhere and produce milk probably why
not farming is back-breaking work yeah I know I'm just throwing out random
shit right now when's the next episode of German craft coming out um I'm
sorry to say but it has been canceled forever but this is a long
winded very long started with chat and it moved into milking somehow but kill
Ganon thank you for the dollar 15 and I'm really sorry here that you got fired
today hopefully the decisions that you've made and the things you're gonna
pursue make you happy thanks for the doll we're still on me yeah hey flank
tank thanks for the one dollar this is a pretty good game with robotic
samurai you know what's another good game with robot samurai that you
should play near automata yeah yeah I know I know one of the time
he'll look into it well I look hey listen I looked into metal gear rising
for a long time a bunch of people have said to play that game on stream
and I looked into it enough to play it getting close getting close not very
many more bits thank you G floater for the five dollars meme has more
than just the internet meaning it comes from Richard Dawkins the word meme is a
shortening modeled on gene of Mimi an imitated thing coined by British
evolutionary biologist Richard Dawkins in the selfish gene as a concept for
discussion of evolutionary principles the memes that's a well thanks for the
piece of historical scientific data G floater thank you for the five
dollars mediocre bloke thanks for the one dollar pac-man made fun of me and I
feel sad help me pac-man can't talk that's how I know what you just said
is bullshit thanks for the dollar though sugar thank you sugar shin for
the one dollar hey Yerma been loving all your streams I just want to show
you my Boston Terrier her name is Missy and she is a good pup it's a
broken link oh that's not good I think I can fix it though maybe not
can we get the can we get the can we get the pop back because I can't I can't get
this stream labs does this weird thing when you try to copy something it just
copies the entire page the entire message and it's impossible to deal
with a virus dog no no no no if you can get me the link again sugar shin I
can't really get it copied but thank you for the if you're still here
thank for the one dollar ace mcclase hundred dollars ten thousand bits an
hour ago it was right when I beat the game thank you for that huge amount of
fucking money it's Markie MC thanks for the five dollars hey Jerm love you
can you end the stream out on this it depends this is
sure it's lowered a little bit though thank you mad 47 for the five dollars
hey man hope you enjoyed metal gear rising
revengeance I got two questions are you gonna play Kenshi Saturday whenever
you stream and would you consider playing the other metal gear games if
they get hit by a sale metal gear series is a favorite of mine and I'd
love to see my favorite streamer play them thanks for the fun man love
probably not probably not metal gear solid one two I mean three is three is
pretty interesting three might be worth a stream they all might be worth the
stream probably not this game was a good one stream one long stream three
is the best one yeah that's why three might be worth streaming did you
I actually think I played the first 20 minutes of four and somehow just did
not play anymore I have not played for but thank you Matt it was a great
game I had a lot of fun I am monk thanks for the one dollar this game
sucked play I am bread I am bread was this like is this 2013 it is
because that's what we just played metal gear rising so it might be 2013
YouTube tuber game thank you uh Jack thank you Jack for one dollar thanks
for getting me interested in the metal gear series anytime Jack metal gears a
great series you're gonna love it if you've never played any of the metal
gears before that's quite a that's quite an adventure to go on if you
start at well where would you start would you start at one or would you I
don't know do you Phantom Menace this shit started five what do you
just go through the whole thing release order is the best for new players just
go one through five yeah gonna come back to Kenshi probably yeah at some
point over the weekend I started at five and never finished it five is a
very large game a lot going on he said PS 2 night yeah no I know I'm
going three days in a row I'm going Saturday Sunday and Monday and then
depending on how I feel maybe Tuesday so we're going three days in a row
but good luck jacket there it's a great series
dubs can do thanks to the one dollar so glad you play this revengeance is my
number one favorite game that I never played the Raiden versus Armstrong
scene inspired me to do my first and only studio grade dub over at least in
my opinion so this game is pretty special to me glad you didn't get too
frustrated with it now go drink some brain fluid you hobbit no I did I
there was a I got frustrated for about 30 minutes 40 minutes maybe
during that stream not that much though is it a level it was a very
containable level thank you for that video hey Garfield the Monday killer
thanks for the one dollar here's Garfield coming in with some bits I
didn't know you were streaming German why don't you warn Garfield next time
you start you want Garfield to miss a stream you want to make Garfield seem
like he's not committed well gosh god damn it I guess it's time for
Garfield to make some funny garfed up jokes for you I think this just
broke the record for the amount of Garfield's I said in a single Gar for
graph anyway germ who are do you hope to see in smash DLC crash bandicoot hint
no I mean I would love to see I'm not I'm not gonna know I'm not gonna say
it everybody thinks I'm gonna say a certain character at this point no Banjo
Kazooie would be great I'd love to see Banjo return to a
Nintendo console he was gonna say Gino no I mean no I'd love to see
Garfield iconic video game cat I'll give you an eye the off-the-wall one
here Scrooge McDuck get Scrooge McDuck in there he would be perfect you can't
tell me that Scrooge McDuck would not fit in that especially really
really popular old retro game that was on the regular Nintendo it was a
cool awesome game loved by millions his move set it just made itself the
Pogo the bring bring he's got the his side smash could be the cane swing he's
got the whole thing the little gems he could throw money out and shit maybe but
that includes Disney and if Disney's gonna get included then Sora is gonna
be put in the game it's not gonna be anybody else if there is gonna be a
big Disney Square or something DLC it's gonna be Sora and I don't want it to
be but it makes the most sense Kingdom Hearts is right on the horizon square
doesn't own Sora Disney does that's not like a joint partnership who square
does not own any of those characters it's all Disney really but there you
go Scrooge McDuck or banjo cuz we there's your answer thank you no
thank you no spores bones I'm may I am absolutely destroying your name
right now but you get $15 about 45 minutes to an hour ago thank you hey are
the German longtime lurker here been watching for about five years and
never has your wonderful content disappointed thank you that's a long
time to that's a five years of lurking well good to see you thank you
for sticking around for that long thanks for the 15 fucking dollars too
much love five year lurk that's a long URL yeah what is that URL never
answered why does he hate Kingdom Hearts what I love Kingdom Heart I can't those
are guys like those games and what when they say that I don't hate those games
why is it telling me that I'm leaving Facebook yeah I don't know no no links
oh this dog link oh look at that that is the dog link oh look at what was
that was that was that a french fry I didn't have these french fries
anymore since ever scrumptious it's a cute dog you guys don't think I do
that voice when I anytime I look at my dog my dog will just look at
me and I'll just start talking as if I'm him talking why do we do that what's
wrong with human beings every time we see an animal we talk out loud as us
talking pretending to be the animal talking why I don't do that that's
just you what I think that's just you it's like a baby voice with
infants yeah but with the baby voice with infants you're not going like
this hello yes it's me the baby I'm the baby and yes I'm so cute and I
just birthed I'm the baby you know you know you're going oh hello baby you're
the baby yeah no when you do a dog you go it's me Otto and I love to eat these
crunchy delicious crunchies like that's what you do nobody says I'm the baby
nobody says I they do it with a dog because we wish that they could talk
because that's what we hope that they would say that makes sense there's a
good take on that I'm the baby thank you though thank you Star Wars
3 episode 3 return to the Sith thanks for the one dollar thanks for
playing one of my favorite games ever almost got the achievement for s ranking
revengeance mode but I fucked up once in Denver and it was all over you could
totally do hard mode though Wow s rank on revengeance mode that sounds pretty
insane damn well yeah I thought it was great I thought it was great I can't
even do hard on Bayonetta these games are really really fast-paced I
don't know how people can go over like hard very hard revengeance it
takes dedication and pinpoint accuracy complete and total locking in I just
like burped really loud and then the fucking music's off so you heard it
great see usually this music is on and you can't hear the fucked up gross
noises that I make and now you heard that one and now whatever thank you
art art articus for the one dollar metal gear may be over but its memes
will live on dark star thanks for the one dollar oh no someone just
linked a picture of Jerma's asshole eternal well thanks for the one dollar
I'm sorry don't be sorry dark star again thanks for the one dollar I'm
sorry I'm so sorry for giving you money dear god I need to repent for
the sin of giving you money I should have given a hundred gift subs I'm
sorry for this measly coin in the coffer oh right and I that's what we're
par follow me thanks for the one dollar alright Jerma I'm setting aside
my dignity to talk about anime okay Jojo is not easy to watch it's long and
indeed very bizarre I recommend stand for your yearly anime to be cowboy
bebop the guy who made it was heavily inspired by Western media so it
should feel right at home I'll go dunk myself in bleach now thank you
well don't do that and by the way I've seen cowboy bebop already it was
great already seen it already watched it that cannot be on the 2019 one anime a
year list what about samurai shampoo already seen it I saw that back when it
was airing on adult swim every night or every Saturday whatever years ago
death note no no I don't think so doesn't have to do it for me original
Dragon Ball not too old too old come on who's more Castlevania that's
pretty good one already seen it berserk already seen it one punch man ooh yeah
I've seen a few episodes I got to finish that but 2019 there it is one
punch man's the anime I'm gonna finish and watch the whole thing nice
okay nice no matter I mean Jojo's bizarre adventure I'm sure it's a
great show but there's like 600 episodes I know I'm not gonna watch
641 episodes hey mostly lost thanks for the one dollar it's 2019 you
still haven't turned off autoplay on YouTube but what if there's a fun video
afterwards what if I miss out on something I never would have seen hey
Fitty thanks for the five dollars Fitty as well as your 50 so 55 dollars
from Fitty thank you so much Frank or see hey I just received your latest
$500 one guy payment so here is the message you wanted me to send a
streamer read this entire thing on stream why are you looking at me a
medium article what the hell is this is an article from medium he paid me what
it's a virus article read it all what even is this link link dot medium dot
com slash relatively just really good what is this how to build a brain
interface and why we should connect our minds I'm not gonna read this
whole thing communication help humanity progress to where we are today from
evolving the ability speak and understand gestures to building the
tools such as writing instruments to bring press radios computer internet
now I'm present in the majority of humanity technology and creative output
requires dexterity having went this is a great article this is articles is
like is like 641 episodes long I don't know I got done a good time to
this pretty interesting stuff though connecting your brain to to the
network or something thank you Fitty seriously for you 55 dollars I really
appreciate it thank you lucky man for the two bucks have you ever done
improv in school no no I've never done stand up never done improv never no
outside of being on stream this is the only why is the PlayStation 4 on I
didn't turn that on but no I've never done improv or anything thank
you dr. epic frag for the $1 Bixby tell me a short joke I don't have
Android so that's not gonna work is that how that thing works hey Alec
thanks for the $1 Jeremy played a Zelda game oh yeah yeah played most of them
actually a dr. epic frag thanks for the four dollars and 16 cents but
seriously you can't thank you enough for all the funny gamer things you do
TF2 till now you never get old PS thank you for playing out of the
gungeon it's become one of my favorite games after watching highlights
of you with it wow that's a that's a really specific one stream oh I'm glad
that you enjoy the game thank you for your more than five dollars here thank
you classic video oh it's a classic hey Sand
Draker thanks for the $1 have you ever been recognized in real life by a
fan at a convention or otherwise also are you ever going to stream
oblivion or red dead 2 again German heart it's happened yeah about that
frequently that happens usually at a convention maybe once a year no I mean
I'm I don't really put myself out there very much like I mean conventions
and shit I do like a little meetup I'll put it like a tweet out but I've
never really done like a twitch sponsored kind of meet-and-greet we
wait in a line or something like that so there really only is one way
you can ever see me at a convention and that's if you see me on the
floor or if you happen to come to the you know and I tweet out where I'm
standing for like an hour you know I mean it's cool though so it's really
interesting when that happens you just really never expect that the couple
of times that it's happened outside of a convention you have really was
just never expected that to happen there's so many people on earth but
thank you DCB for the $1 how do you feel knowing your viewers will
literally pay a dollar to roast you on stream it's okay how do I feel I
damn you're right it's all in good fun hey Sandraker again thanks for the $1
what are some of the videos or streams that you're the proudest of I also
just want to say thanks I've been going through so I'm going through
benzo withdrawals for the last month and a half and your streams are just
about the only thing keeping me sane probably have heard your voice more
than my own voice last year I'm really that I'm sure that's fucking
horrible but thank you for the dollar thank you for the for being around I
can't imagine what that's like hopefully you get through it stay strong
you'll do it much love to you for real take care of yourself and thank
you so much for the monetary contributions only about five more
left we will round out this nine and a half hour stream I wanted to go
long tonight though because I knew I wasn't gonna be around for the next
couple of days that's why I'm still doing the stream you know you know you
know what I mean you know you know you know turn into earnest synthesize
panda bot thanks for the $1 hey Jerm what do you think of scat skippy
scat man that's all right that's pretty interesting pretty it's cool
hard to do it's Rizgar thanks for the $1 hey Jermboy might have zoned out but
I think you skipped my bits earlier either way wanted to know if you
would consider it would decide to show up on another podcast or
something but it was hilarious when you were on criticals podcast I mean
not necessarily I mean I just end up being invited on some things sometimes
and yeah I guess I'll do it I don't have any intention to go on podcasts
or kind of IEC the collab with X or collab with Y you know it just happens
sometimes did Drake call back yet yeah I buttoned him didn't even let it
ring once it was like done I caught it immediately thank you Clueless sniper for
the $1 thank you boss for Oya for the $1 during a serious question this time
do you have any advice to give to a perfectionist I often feel like if I
don't do something to the fullest of my abilities there's no point in
doing it at all it can be a suffocating and depressing way to view
the world but I don't know how to drop it PS your hair does look good
I'm just used to short hair and couldn't handle the change advice for
perfectionist except the fact that you trying your best is good enough you
have to accept the fact that it can't be perfect I have to come to terms
with kind of just kind of shit all the time whether it's in your daily
life or you know something with the stream that I want to do nobody is
Superman it's impossible to hold yourself to that kind of a standard
except my dad well alright except your dad is Superman but not
everybody's dad is Superman but as long as you get what you're doing to a level
that you think is good do it you know you can do something to the fullest of
your abilities but fullest of your abilities does not always necessarily
have to have to mean perfect you can be really good at something but it
doesn't have to be perfect every time not perfect what is perfection that's
a whole not the story that's a whole nother conversation but allow
yourself to have faults otherwise you'll just drive yourself crazy but thank you
hopefully that helps almost done DZ Bill Chow Tun Chun Chun I can't read this
name it's too late thank you the $1 though hey German been watching you
since your TF2 days I just want to say I love your content everything you
do keep up the good work thank you I'm gonna call you DZ I I'm gonna
call you dizzy thanks to the $1 lazy look thanks for the $1 what would you
say makes one successful in life also Fiddy is a cool person what makes you
successful whatever you want that word to mean it doesn't mean the same thing
for everybody that's it's an impossible question to answer it's a different
answer from every single person to person what do I think what do I
think is for successful I asked you yeah but me what but you said what
would you say it makes one successful not you successful right that's a
good politician answer well no that's true though because think about that to
not going I'm not gonna go into a long-winded response here because it's
late for a lot of people but what I think is let's say you have a goal
right I want to do this I want this to be this means that I did it I made
it or this is why this is my success is here that's not the same
for somebody else they could make me completely different things
Jerma is the villain you know what makes you suggest his mode makes you
successful successful are you happy with what you're doing that's to what I feel
like is success to me did you accomplish something that you are
happy with done doesn't fucking matter what it is thank you Jack for
the $1 if the donations keep coming he can't end the stream not if I go
faster flying sombrero thanks for the $1 I just want to say how much I
love you in this chat unlike many streamers you make us feel like we're
part of the stream and I love that I also like how we can abuse you and you
still love us because we all love you tiny man I'm glad you have fun that's
the intent and hopefully it stays that way thank you Fiddy for the $1 you
can't end the stream if we keep donating finger on forehead yeah yeah
synthesize panda bot thanks for the $1 hey Jerma I know I make funnies
with the monies but I love you been bring booba dooba doo boo boo boo
doop ring ring ring ring ring banana phone ding dong dong banana phone thank
you for the $1 thank you FGWGWF for the $5 hey Jerma you're great and super tall
he's like six five guys I met him at PAX keep doing you you're the funniest
person in the world in my opinion that means a lot thank you thanks for
the $5 and I am fucking huge thank you Jack again final at the buzzer
here thanks for the $1 can we bring back Orson Welles sub sound for the
weekend no we can't we can't do that thank you though for all those credits
thanks for all the subs I just oh my goodness you guys are fucking awesome
that's off-center needs to be moved over here and made a lot bigger thank
you all of you the hundreds of people that subscribe pretty much every stream
and stay subscribed for years thanks still not centered I got you I got
you a dragoon 893 thanks for the $1 hey Jerma have you seen this into the
spider-verse if not you totally should it was an incredible movie with
really cool visuals and great music Miles Morales best spider-man by the
way I've done I heard it was really really good and I'm absolutely gonna
see it very soon heard it was great so yes I will definitely watch it
Alec thank you for the $1 a hobby hobby wobbly wobble zip zoop yeah bye
what Phitty thanks for the $1 play sicko mode by Travis Scott what are you
guys doing what is what is this shit even mean I'm trying to decipher what
that could possibly mean the hobby bobby wobby I don't know what that
means thank you San Greg for the $1 if Orson is out can we have a Paul
Barrett sub sound the Paul Barrett sub sound is like 27 seconds long I
can't bring that back exactly please please exactly oh god damn it's late
almost 10 hours I'll see you guys on Saturday we'll do either viscera maybe
some PlayStation 2 maybe some Kenshi take care guys and then right at the
very end we've got Phitty coming in $1 who made this here with all the
ice on in the booth at the gate outside when they pull up they get me loose do
more what is this lyrics thank you thank you Tiger for the $1 I guess I'll
quickly jump on the love train before the end of the stream you're my
longest sub on YouTube been with you since TF2 my longest sub on Twitch
coming up on two years I just want to say thank you for everything you
do everything you for us shows and all the hilarious content you bring us
week in and week out thank you for everything really is appreciated more
than you'll ever know a flip that statement around and percent percent
that I just said that that's how I feel as well so thank you
Jack at the very end thanks for the $1 and then that getting like that the
spongebob I'm bending over text why don't you play TF2 no I just not not
doing it right now you know smelly boy thanks for the $1 ban that smelly
jelly guy he's a nuisance to the community he'll no longer be tolerated
no that's smelly jelly not smelly boy ban the smelly jelly guy thanks for the
$1 thank you Alec for the $1 Bob snobby now I'm not reading that thank you
Chuck E. Cheese for the $1 what did you plan on doing with all the banana
awards I was the one to suggest him so I just was wondering wink wink I
gave those awards out on stream have a good night see you guys on Saturday
same time around 3 p.m. Pacific much love to you have a great
another couple days I'm gonna go one two three in a row Saturday Sunday
Monday take care thanks for watching Metal Gear Rising was a great game
highly recommended just don't get don't get frustrated you know it doesn't look
good on you Phinney $1 thanks for the $1 whoops more bits that last donation
were the sicko mode lyrics oh okay have a great night see you soon