Hey, that's what we're doing.
No, we're not doing a washer and dryer.
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
We better start recording right now, because I'm going to start fucking building it.
No, we're not doing a washer and dryer.
Hi guys, today we're going to create a fucking washer and dryer on Jeremy's channel, there.
Alright, fine, right here.
No, he already finished it. That was it.
Look, it's a washer and dryer. It's a big square.
Stop. You already made it. You put two of them next to each other and you said, done.
Oh, that's it?
Yeah, done. Thank you, subscribe, and, you know, bitch.
Alright, I actually was recording during that, so that's fine.
And then it just like flew away.
This is the Aladdin's phone.
Washer and dryer. Alright, what are we really going to make?
Alright, so did you record that? Because that was pretty funny.
Yeah, I did.
Cool, that better be up.
How about like, I don't know, like a jack-o-lantern?
Alright, Spoon, thanks for joining us, man.
No problem.
A jack-o-lantern.
Let's make a fridge!
Hi, we're back again!
Done!
Oh, there he goes again.
Flying away.
Alright, so we got fridge, washer, dryer, and, yeah.
We've got something else.
Oh no, what's he got?
How long is it taking him to get down here?
Ready?
Stove!
The stove looks eerily similar to the washer and dryer.
Well then, we'll just do this.
Shouldn't the stove be like that?
Nope.
Oh great, now you made it rain.
Oh shit, I'm shitting all over the washer and dryer.
And I broke the ground.
I know what we're making.
A piano.
Three, two, one.
Let's do it. Alright, seven minutes, boys.
Hey, the piano's off! What are you doing?
The piano's not white!
That's for the keys!
The piano's to be up in the air, you can't...
Like you pull out the plates, Matt.
And it's just one of those like...
This isn't a movie.
This isn't like big, when Tom Hanks like
jumps on the thing on the ground.
Is that the piano leg right there?
Alright, that's gonna be one of the legs.
I'm gonna go over here to do a third leg.
Over here.
I'm just gonna sit here and watch.
Oh come on!
We don't have that much time.
Yeah, we can finish this, you guys.
Wait.
I'm just gonna sit here and watch.
Alright, no, come together, come together.
What is that? These are the legs.
Hey, you gotta do some work.
Why is this so big?
Spooner's not doing anything.
I'm doing something, I don't know what you guys are talking about.
Stop making fun of me, okay?
We're gonna build the piano.
I'm building a piano, do you see this?
Alright, come up with that leg.
One minute has gone by, we got only seven.
Everything looks very similar to that horse we did that one time.
Hey, everything looks like that horse we did that one time.
Hey.
I wouldn't speak about horses.
Alright, let's go, come on around here.
Oh yeah, I forgot, you are a horse.
Forget that sometimes.
Is that enough?
That looks good, yeah.
Remember, we don't have to fill it in, that's one of the things in the comments people were saying.
They're like, don't fill it in.
No, we need to fill it in, otherwise it's not real, and it won't work.
It's a functioning piano.
Alright, have this one come up too.
Too far.
This is huge.
This is way, way, way too big.
Okay, so where's the front of it?
I don't know.
We're just like in a giant black cube.
Like four legs right now.
Alright, this will be the front right here.
I'll work on the front.
You guys close off, this is so big, it's like a highway.
Dude, this is amazing.
I'm doing the front, I'm doing the front.
I'm filling it in.
Okay, so the front is where?
Where the keys are.
That's what I'm doing, I'm working on that right now.
Wait, what? It's down here? Why is this piano long?
They're supposed to be wider than they are long.
This is a different kind of piano, it's like different.
This is like a Mack truck piano.
Alright, as long as, remember the butt comes up.
Come on, why do we have to make it this long?
You said a giant piano.
I know, it's all my own fault.
Which one's the front?
Yeah, I'm at the front right now.
You're at the front?
Pianos are wider.
This is just long.
What the hell do keys look like?
Just like two or three blocks long.
Is this working?
No.
Does this piano have like four keys?
I have like four keys.
Oh, do you want me to play you a song?
Sorry, I can only play hot cross buns.
Yeah, you can only play the first part of Chopsticks.
So what should be the black keys?
Oh, this is just huge.
I don't know. Spoon help.
What, spoon, what, who, for what?
You gotta close the gap.
Actually, it doesn't really look that bad.
No, it does.
Yeah, don't criticize your own work, are you kidding me?
You know how hard we worked on this thing?
Alright, the keys really do need to be
a little bit better than that.
There need to be more of them.
No, it's just, it's fine.
You put them at the wrong end.
Hold on, we can widen it a little bit.
Dude, we'd have a better chance of like
just turning this into a guitar right now
than just finishing it at the piano.
It's gonna be a giant guitar.
It just looks like a giant thing with big teeth.
Like a big monster.
It looks like Tetris.
So we gotta do one of these episodes
saying, we're not telling them what it is
and we just make it and people have to guess
what it is.
That's actually a pretty good idea.
Let's start with this one. Just bleep out the word.
Every time somebody says the word piano, I'll bleep it.
I'll just put like a sensor.
Hey guys, this is pretty funny.
Just do that. It works.
Alright, five minutes have gone by.
We gotta close this out.
It works. Alright, look at this.
This is beautiful.
Good thing I made it so the keys come out
way too far.
What is this?
It's all good. This is great.
This is fantastic.
We're gonna sell this for so much.
I don't even know what to think right now.
Just for reference, we said the piano is huge.
The piano is actually
bigger than this person.
It's about as big as a house.
A nice piano house.
That being said for how big it is,
it has a surprising
very small amount of
keys.
What is the rest of this piano for?
Why is it so big if it has no purpose?
It's a house.
You can live in the piano
and you can also tickle me.
Alright, so we are allowed to do
that spoon apparently.
How much time?
We have like 40 seconds.
Is there any detailed work we can do
with this thing?
Absolutely not. It's ruined.
This has to come out like this.
This is one of those games where you stand up
and play it. You got no chair.
This is one of those pianos where you drink like an elixir
and you grow 50 feet tall and then you play it.
Look at that grand piano.
I'm making a quick chair.
It's not making towers.
It's a chair.
I don't like this very much.
This has to go. 10 seconds.
Stop ruining my work.
5, 4, 3, 2,
1, and get the chair done!
And there it is. Nice.
And that's it. Grand piano.
That's the chair balancing.
What human being
sits on this chair
like this small?
This is not even room for one butt cheek for apparently
who's big enough to touch this keyboard.
You made the chair too big.
And that is going to wrap up the video.
So thank you guys so much for watching.
Leave a comment with the name and the rating for this thing.
It looks pretty much like a piano.
I don't know, you guys can be the judge of that one.
But I'll see you guys all soon
and take care everybody.