Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Scare Saturdays.
This time on Scare Saturday is going to be going through some of the co-op of Cry of Fear with Ster.
Now, before anybody asks any questions, this is not going to be a full let's play of Cry of Fear.
As much as that would be cool, I would probably rather stream something like that than to upload like 50 episodes of this onto my YouTube channel.
But it's about a 15 minute video condensed kind of highlight reel of some of the scares, some of the funny things that happened, some of the happenings we came across.
And that's probably what you're going to get. Like I said, I don't want to have a huge let's play on this channel. It's like, you know, 50 episodes long.
I've gone down that path before. As a lot of you guys know, I've done some let's plays and yeah, we're on episode 6. I'm done.
But with that said, here is the video guys. Not going to take up any more time. I want to get to the content, obviously.
So it's been sunny out. Go outside and go get some sunbathing because I'm about to do it right now, baby. Sunbathing.
I'm going to turn up. No, don't. Oh, there's a gun. This is my gun. I can't pick up that 30 semi auto. I cannot pick up.
I don't know how to equip it. There's a guy. There's a guy. There's a guy. There's a guy over there. There's a guy over here.
He's like shifting around like a freak show. Don't shoot him. Don't shoot him. What do you mean?
Don't shoot him. It's a freaking neighborhood. What did you do? Do I have no bullets left?
I shot him. Dude, this is such recoil on this gun. It's unbelievable.
Help me. Help me stop shooting this guy. Shoot him, please.
You do it. I have to change my sensitivity. I can't aim like this.
And I'm going to figure out how to equip the G43 semi auto. Give me a sec.
I'm going to hide in this dark corner. I'll cover you. If I die, this is all on you.
All right. I will cover you. Are you ready now for real?
Okay. This game is really laggy. It is like 30 FPS. You're not joking.
All right. Well, you have to go. There's a guy. There's a guy. You have the gun.
You I have a gun too, but I can't shoot this guy. I just shot him in the balls.
These things have. What is that? What do you mean? It's an upside down flying mattress.
What? Where? You don't. Okay. You walk down there.
Okay. I do see it. What is her? Is it dead? I don't have any bullets left, by the way.
Yeah, that's kind of happening. We should. I think in our inventory we have a night stick.
I don't know how to equip these into slots. Oh, you just click them in and click.
Yeah, I just did that. If you click in, you can like bring them over to slot one.
Slot one is one. Slot two is two. Slot three is three. Okay, I got this.
All right. I don't have any bullets, so something's going to jump up.
Wait, did I just get bullets? I did. Didn't I? No, I didn't. That was you reloading.
Yeah. Damn it. Get out of here. What? Game over. I'm so scared. Good idea.
Okay. I heard somebody. Is that guy throwing a brick at you?
I think it was blood, but it looks like a brick. Is there an invisible person?
No, it's the mattress guy. Where is he? Oh, he's right there.
Okay. Get out of here. Go back to Ikea. Who thought this was scary?
Go back to Jordan's furniture, you piece of crap. The upside down flying mattress man.
That is kind of weird. There's more of them. There's more of them.
What do you mean there's more? Where are they? Oh, my God. They're like a flock of crows.
Is one of them dead? Yes. All right. That one's not dead.
He's still sitting there all mattressy. Something else, something else, something else.
I heard it. Don't waste ammo. Don't waste ammo. He's stuck behind the bushes.
We don't got to worry about this guy. That guy might be a pain in the ass later.
We got to go in this way. There's a person in this house as well.
There's something in that house. I can see its head. Get guns ready.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Is she dead? That was my girlfriend, Jerma.
What the hell is that thing from the island of Dr. Moreau?
No, that's from XCOM. How many different games of enemies are they going to throw at us?
No, that's the thing from the island of Dr. Moreau. Moreau, not Monroe.
Who's the fat actor? I'm scared. I can't think.
You got to be as crazy as them. All right. Good. What's this box over here?
I don't know. Should we open it? Pageant Boy.
Can we just jump in the car? Nope, that'd be too easy.
Door won't budge. None of these doors budge.
Holy. Watch out. We got the Freddy Krueger with the hammers.
Freddy Krueger that is being electrocuted.
Don't you feel at all cruel for just wailing on the guy?
What the fuck is that thing? What is that giant thing?
You want to billy club it? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know what to do. Should we shoot him?
Yeah, I'm shooting him. I got this rifle. I'm out of ammo for it.
Should I shoot him in the face? He's dead.
That just kind of legitimately freaked me out when I turned in that corner.
When he dies, why does he crumple up into like a...
What the hell is this? My legs and face. I want to get inside of it.
I go down and do a yoga position when I die.
Crawl inside. I want to see you inside of it.
And his dumb character expression.
What do you think you're going to cover me from inside the hole?
I'm covering you. Am I on your head?
No. How do you get up this?
I don't know. I'll give you one hint.
I seriously. OK, you have to sprint and do it.
That was so that was very dramatic for what to see.
You can't do this. I'm sprinting. You got to like sprint.
There you go. You got it. This game is good.
No more noises. Turn off your flashlight.
That's completely silent now. Look what you did. Clear.
Anything in here? Anything in here?
Oh, on the ground right here. Ammo. Mine.
Take it good. I still have some shotgun shells left.
I'm not concerned about this. What are we inside of right now?
Who built this and for what reason? Yeah, I know.
Here's my log cabin. You'll get it. You're the shotgun guy.
Where is it over there? I get the cover my tail.
You're covering your tail. Here we go. Good.
What is this? And where are you? I lost you.
Oh, my God. Dude. Where are you?
Help me. Where? Oh, my God.
Fair. How many ammo? Game over. Game over.
Dude, that was ridiculous.
Dude, I saw it like the ground was destroyed.
It's like, oh, he fell through these stairs. No problem.
I'll go and after him. I fell through the stairs.
Dude, that was so bad because I lost you and that happened.
The first time you go ahead without me. See, I need to.
Do we seriously have to go up those stairs? I think we have to.
I think that's like that's like an event we have to do.
So what we're going to do is we're going to bum rush it.
OK, OK. No, no. Here's the thing.
We need a strategy for this because we can't just go up these stairs.
Don't go yet. Don't know. I'm not going to go.
OK, I'm checking my like which gun is going to be the best gun.
I'm reloading the Glock. I got two pistols.
How do I dual wield these? I don't know.
There's a dual wield button, but it like never works for me.
Maybe I just was going too fast and we actually don't like you don't have to fall down there.
Maybe you can like make it happen and then walk away.
All right. Well, whatever happens, I'm coming down after you.
Oh, my God. Hold on.
You hear them like hustling. Seriously.
I searched that I gave me up. That gave me a fucking hot attack.
Why are they coming through walls now? It wasn't supposed to.
That's the thing. We know what's going to happen. We know they're there.
But am I seriously jumping in this first? Go, go.
Hold on. I'm figuring out how to dual wield.
Give me a break. That was so stupid. It just came through the wall.
How do you do this? I don't know, but we got it.
We have to just do it. There's no there's really no turning back.
It didn't happen. God, Jerma, please, Jerma, please.
I don't have any bullets in this gun. We got it.
There's one more. I hear like the huh.
Nope. No, that's it. I can't believe it.
I can't believe we did that. What's what's even back here?
Nothing. We had we had to do that so we could go up the stairs again.
No. What are we stuck in here? No, there has to be a way to get through that.
Can we shoot the what?
The accuracy. You are too good.
I hear a bunch of noise. I hear like a swarm of bees.
Oh, no, not the bees. Oh, no. Do you hear like that swarm of bees?
Yeah. Yeah. Get out your billy club for the bees.
All right. Let's go. Get in there.
Are you kidding me? I don't want to go in here. Do you hear this?
That's going to be a chainsaw guy. Oh, my God. It is a chainsaw guy.
Let me out. Let me out. Let me out. Let me out. Let me out.
You can't get out now. You commit it here. Here's what you do.
OK, let me equip. Am I going to bait this guy for you?
Equip this gun. Yeah. And you just bait him.
There's a rifle on the ground at your feet. Oh, I hear him.
Oh, my God. What is he blending? Damn it, man.
He's running a blender. I don't know. I don't know if I can bait him back here.
You got it. You got it. No, it's just a lady.
Just a stupid, like, lady. There he is. There he is.
He killed me. I'm dead. He's going to get you. Oh, my God.
That's so fair. We knew he was there.
What are you supposed to do? I don't know.
Can you? Yeah, I got him. I got him. Oh, my God. He's running.
He's running. He can't get through. I don't think he can get through.
I just want to say hello.
I don't have any ammo. Neither do I.
What do we do? I don't know.
Is there a door in there? There is.
OK, so what we're going to do is we're both going to...
Can you can you get in there? Oh, what the...
What the hell? I have no idea what we're going to do in this situation.
I think we just have to get here with enough ammo.
That's the only way we'll be like all those ladies we shot.
We should shoot those ladies, Jerma. All right, going in.
Oh, my God. He's like...
Oh, my God. That was so dumb.
If we want things to get spiced up, you know what we got to do?
What we got to do? We got to stop being such little punks.
Here, we got a gun. I'm just going. Let's go.
I'm not waiting for you. We're not taking our time. I'm just running.
You're going to run through this? What about the guy with the bag on his head?
I don't know. What about him? What about him?
He just like punched me and I got like drunk.
It's not even a bag. Wait, what is this? Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
I'm getting hurt. Yeah, I am. What is hitting me?
No, it's this guy. Is he breathing on us too hard?
I don't know, but his like bad breath is giving us like a headache.
What the hell just happened? I killed him and he's speaker phone the hell out of there.
I don't have any bullets. I need a syringe if we find one.
I'm out. I got this assault rifle, but...
I am out. I'll take this. I'm dropping this for you. Thank you.
I don't know how quickly you do this because I'm quicking.
I'm going the other way. I'm going the other way.
I don't have any bullets. I don't have any bullets.
I have to equip the branch. Where's the branch?
Oh, he's glitched out. Quick, come on.
I'm dead, Jerma. I can't see.
You can't see me right here? I can see you standing on me, but that's it.
Who else wants some? Oh, yeah, you can dodge.
I forgot about that. Oh, wow, you can.
There's the dodge button. That's why my, like, double tap forward or back.
Oh, okay. That's why I was like, oh, my character freaked out.
I hear the bees. There's the guy.
Oh, Jesus. Game over.