Hello, when you call me early? I don't think I'm early. I think I'm right on time.
Hey, by the way, since doing the new schedule, once a week, Andy, I don't think I've been late
at all. I think I've started at exactly 12 to 12.01. Wait, no, that was the one, there was one time
where my computer was freaking out. Binding of Isaac was freaking out.
But for the most part, like 80% of the time, it's been exactly at 12 PM.
How you doing? How was how was your week? Is it good? Well, I'm Andy. Today, we're gonna be playing
a new game. I know everyone did. Oh, you don't want to hear that. We're playing Pokemon Snap
Switch Edition. I do have a problem with the title. I don't know. I don't know what is with
Nintendo in this shit. They're the only people that do this. Nintendo is the only company besides
some furniture cleaning companies and like Lysol spray type companies that put new in front of
stuff. And has made a new product. New OxiClean. New Pokemon Snap. New Super Mario Brothers.
The only company that is one of four kind of companies that do this.
Like Pokemon Snap. You can't come up with a better name than New Pokemon Snap.
That was a pre-written joke. Oh, you better believe it was. It wasn't. I came up with that
right now. I'm just sitting here like I got a notepad with a bunch of potential intro jokes.
And I'm going to use them. Like I wrote them down. I'm a comedian. I know comedy.
I know it. Tell me I don't. This game suck. I don't know. It has a camera and you take pictures of
different Pokemons. Oh, I'm kind of excited. It's a camera. The game with a camera.
You have a plan B. No. Well, hold on. I had a plan A. This is the plan B. If you must know.
So I had plan A. Plan A was I downloaded, I don't know, maybe 30 to 40 dog shit iPad games.
And was going to do a dog shit iPad game stream. And what happened was started to kind of vet them
a little bit. And none of them were fun or funny. So I have to kind of go back to the drawing board
on that one. Like they would just like I start I like opened them and realized they would just
kind of like take over my iPad and shit. It like wasn't even worth doing. So like six made it out
of like the 40 that I found. So it's gonna have to happen is over the next probably week or two.
I'm going to compile more and do that at some point. That was the plan A. This is the plan B.
The virus stream. So you downloaded viruses willingly. Yes. They're not viruses. They're just
bad. All right. You know what like probably the worst insult to like a game designer is?
Like a game developer. Is if you call their game a virus game. Because that just means that holy
shit this was so bad. That like I think it may have infected my computer. That's bottom. Absolute
bottom of the barrel to be to have you to say that about somebody's game. I just like I just
made that game for fun. I just was like playing around in like unity. This is a virus game. Oh,
would you at least have said cereal box? All right. You guys ready? I'm ready to play this.
By the way, this is the first Pokemon game I've played on the channel. You count the the TV one
like watch TV with Pikachu. I guess that's that count. Does this game count? Is this non-canon?
I don't know. What did you say? Oh my god. I'm so tired of this schedule. I'd rather you stream
one minute a day per week. I would have. All right. I would have been gone five minutes ago.
That would be the shittiest content. Can you imagine if I just showed up for a minute and then left?
That's just enough time to remind a bunch of people that their sub is running out.
Yeah, I'm not going to do that. All right. Let's go. Leave now. All right. English. Please select
your appearance. You can't change your appearance. This kind of looks like me. Which one? I have blue
eyes. This is me. Jeremy. Sure. I'm just going to be. I guess I'm just going to be Jeremy.
That's me. I'm not being a character today. It's just me. What do you mean today? I'm not being a
character today. Like do I normally? Am I normally a fucking character? What am I talking about?
No, I'm going to be me today. Why does the snap look so blown up and like awful looking?
Is that a Pokemon? Get Pikachu out of here. They only put him in here for fucking nostalgia.
I want the new Pokemon. I don't care about Pikachu. He's in. He's only in here for nostalgia.
Greetings. True. Hi there. I'm glad you made it. Who's the professor that everyone was pissed
off that I didn't know who it was? It's not Professor Mirror, right? It was Professor Oak.
It's the one that I didn't know and everyone freaked out. Welcome to the Laboratory of
Ecology and Natural Sciences or LENS for short. My name is Mirror. Yeah, I didn't know who Professor
Oak was. I'm researching Pokemon and their natural environment here on Florio Island.
Yeah, and that's not all. The professor is going to study every single island here in the Lental
region. No one's ever done an ecological survey like this before. It's going to be amazing.
No one? Aren't you forgetting a certain explorer? Are Pokemons considered wild animals?
Is that- what are- are they- are they- yes, they are, yeah. I don't know if they were like-
they're supposed to be like cartoons or something. I'm gonna keep going.
It's a good point. You've read the stories of Captain Vince. I don't know anything about- I
don't know anything about Pokemon. This is the worst channel you could watch right now that's
playing this. I'm just going to criticize and annoy you if you're a fan of this universe.
This is the game you play if you're a fan of the universe. This is like the side
I'm a fan of the universe game. I'm not a fan of the universe and here I am.
I just like cameras in video games. Well, thanks. This is Rita. Her parents are good friends of mine.
She's here on vacation while her school's on break. I'm not just here to goof off, Professor.
I'm your research assistant. Ah yes, that's right, and I appreciate the help.
Now before we go over what you'll be doing in this program, why don't we step into the lab
and get settled? Right, you are, Professor. I'll lead the way. Camera Andy. Yeah, it's fun.
I see you got yourself a fucking gamer chair over there. All right, let me- allow me to explain.
Yeah, these are wild animals in this person's house. That's what I was talking about. Like,
these wild animals just run around in this house? The lentil region is absolutely teeming with
Pokemon. Photographing those Pokemon helps us learn more about them and their ecosystem.
They can be tamed. Yeah, all right, I understand. You've watched the one YouTube video.
Of the guy that has like the alligator as a pet. And it has like 1.6 million views. And we've all
seen it. And we're like, holy shit, that's fucking crazy. But you don't actually have an alligator
in your house. You're not going to. It's like three people on earth. A fatal frame. And now you might
even get to see glowing Pokemon. They're really- really. Now without further ado, here's your
research camera. Oh, there- that's pretty- that's pretty shitty for a camera that I'm gonna get.
It looks like a Walmart disposable camera. You- you couldn't have ponied up a little bit more
research money and get me a fucking DSLR? I've got the same one. We can use them to communicate
with each other and the rest of the team too. That's right. It's more than just a camera. It
lets you keep in touch and analyze data on the fly. So it's an iPhone. Yep. Yep. It'll also serve
as a sort of an ID badge for you here. So take good care of it. Wait, it's an ID? Now remember,
son, there's only 25 photos on there. And what you're going to do is you're going to take that
to a wedding. You're going to take nine pictures. There's going to be 21 more photos on it. It's
going to sit in your closet for 16 years. You're going to take it out. You're going to take 10 more
pictures on it. You're going to put it back in your closet. Two more years go by. You're going
to throw it in the trash and never get the photos developed. Awesome, right? The professor invented
it. Can I explain how to use it, professor? You're projecting again. I mean, I've done that like
probably four or five times. Who's ever developed photos from one of those cameras? Can I explain
how to use it, professor? Everything, Rita. Assist away. I'll go take care of some other
preparations. All right, come on. Let's go outside. I can't wait to take my first photo
as a photo Pokemon journalist. Tutorials are based on the default button layouts. Yeah. All right.
Perfect timing. Let me shoot it. All right. Press A to take a photo. I can't move the camera.
It was a bad picture. All right. That's A. Okay. And it's shaped like a Pokeball.
Okay. Oh, I see. All right. So we've got to get the house in the frame too.
You can point the camera all the way around.
Imagine needing to tell somebody how to use a camera. You can use a camera too.
Am I a caveman? Why do they have to teach me this? Oh, look. Here comes a Pikachu.
Oh, what's the zoom button? You're a small child. No, I'm not. How old is this kid? Like fucking 12?
That's old enough to know how to use a camera. First move so it's lined up with Pikachu. Okay.
Yeah, but who does a center shot? Amateur? It needs to be like over here. And I know
someone's going to go, rule of thirds is bullshit. Don't use it. I use it. I think it looks good.
I did. Okay. So there's like a face recognition. I always turn that off. I hate that. Got it. You're
using it wrong. I don't even have control of the camera right now. It's called zooming in.
Oh, ZL. Okay. Nice and big. Oh my God. Okay. Got it. See how much bigger it looked?
Do you want your subject's whole body in the middle of the frame? No, you don't.
Nice and big. Okay. Controls are setting me. Pause menu. All right.
Oh, you taught him how to use a camera. Great. Now let's teach him how to pour cereal into a bowl.
How to flush the toilet. And the very hard task of making your bed. How was that? I hope you're
getting the hang of your research camera. Do you mind choosing one shot of each Pokemon you've
photographed? I'll rate them using my special scoring system. Pick whichever shots you think
are the best. I only took like two pictures. Like the Pikachu folder. I have folders? Okay.
You can choose a photo by moving the pointer. Press A when you've decided which one to show me.
That one. All right. How about the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the. Okay. I only took one picture. Press or select show professor. Show him.
Okay. What does he think? Starting with photo number one. It's beautiful. Oh, it's Pikachu.
This is the first time you've gotten it as your subject. Pose, size, direction placement, other
Pokemon background from one to four stars. I came up with a system to help us understand and
categorize how pokemon behave photos of pokemon in an ordinary state get fewer stars more unusual
behavior means more stars all right he's gotta get him doing weird cool stuff be clear the number
of a star a photo receives doesn't affect its score every category is important by the way the
camera keeps logs of what was happening when you took each photo that data helps me categorize your
what does that mean hold on let me get auto auto you want to come up let's hear that i have
hold on i was clearing out my closet hey show auto oh you didn't think what you put excuse
me you didn't think that you were going to be able to see something important you were going to see
a mustache shit lord it's not really there we go oh my pants my pants are unzipped are they
my pants are unzipped oh my god i think my pants are unzipped no they're not okay holy shit that
was just the most terrifying thing i've ever done in my life i think like that was like in my mind
my career ended i'll be honest with you what going through my brain was my career is over
it's it's over i like my like there's my like my it's open that's my biggest fucking fear
but in what what what's the matter he's got a problem i pull out a lightsaber like oh this is
like it's like dick is out that's like i'm gone forever but i mean that would be like really
really funny way to go out that would be like fucking crazy like what i would live forever
that would be like that would be an image or a video that would be shared forever like i would
be i would live forever anyways by the way the camera keeps logs of what was happening what was
i doing okay let's move on to the scoring i'll evaluate the subject's pose snapping your photo
at just the right moment is key to getting a high pose score i didn't show auto i did not i was i
hold on i'll show him like in a few weeks okay so it's pose the larger your subject is in the photo
the better and there's the direction the pokemon is facing so you want to be big facing you doing
a cool pose center of the frame bonus of this other pokemon in the photo all right i just take
good photos whatever so why is it right in the center that's not usually good pictures it's
hard to believe you're a beginner all right well i don't want to save this that photo i don't want
it in my album but that one's not as good okay good pose bad direction though how is direction
better than size which one is a pokemon they're all pokemon they're not supposed to be artistic
photos well i'm gonna take some liberty and do that i'm gonna have some artistic photos
but i'm supposed to just zoom in and take a picture of their face i'm an artist i should be
treated as such this is for scientific research look at this pod it'll carry you on your photography
expeditions it's called the neo one it's the best it can teleport to far off places in no time
flat you all know i like that word and every time i get a chance to say it i love saying it i finally
put the finishing touches on it not long ago with a little help from someone i know see it makes use
of energy hotspots scattered throughout the lentil region come on professor the details can wait
all right let's let's go climb on in and touch your camera to the console what like the switch
calls oh he has to do it i'm like fucking 12 they just put me in an experimental like traveling pod
i don't have a license what they were just concerned about me not knowing how to use a
camera they're gonna make me go drive a car oh here we go here we go all right oh beautiful
all right this weird guy over here that's a good one got it come on right into the camera come
here anybody else turn around turn around turn around turn around please turn around
how many photos can i take oh it's a it's a little it's a toy pikachu he's so bad no i'm
not what are you talking about shit damn it no that's artistic that's all right that's an
artistic photo it's above the the weeds what's that thing this is this is like too easy isn't it
this is easy this is a ride this is just a ride at disney world what this is not hard
it is all right here to take a picture of and it's moving for me this is a kid's game what
i just ride around and take pictures i thought this is going to be like hard to do this or
something i don't know this is so many pictures you're a child how many how many pokemons are
in the game ready got it perfect that's a perfect photo okay uh here we go you guys ready if you
were i got it if you were to offer me a million dollars right now for me to name these as they
come on screen i wouldn't be able to do it i wouldn't be able to get one let's see if i can
get one uh it just showed me and i don't i don't remember i'm flying above what's that is it
what is a hoot hoot come here that was a bee doof right into the camera turn right is he gonna stay
i gotta get him flying by he's gonna fly right here and i'm gonna get it oh my god that was
this guy just wants me to take a picture of him whoa get that these are pokemons what the
fuck are these things all right they ran out of ideas they ran out of ideas this is like it's like
a friendship bracelet that's not even a pokemon what is that what's that basically it's the end
of the course okay so in conclusion it's this so basically it's this in theory it's this
anime does that a lot doesn't it a character will be talking and then they'll go
in conclusion i think that this this this this in theory this this this this therefore
this this this this okay i took 39 photos now just like before it's time to show me some photos you
took stop talking go ahead and choose one photo oh i can only choose one photo per pokemon oh man
okay dodrio i only took two pictures of this guy that i mean it's that one this one's cooler
though why these are such a low quality it's this one okay rookie which one of these is rookie
oh it's that guy uh it's this one keychu it's the only one i have well both philant
buffalant i took way more pictures of buffalant what are you talking about
edouf oh hold on i like i like that one that's a way cooler picture of the swans and the
bee do i mean that one's awesome a worm pole that one comfy um i guess this one
hello no no this one right in his face yeah this is easy that was the easy one
swana this photo is too clean i like this one better this one's just weird magic harp
hoot hoot what about the what about the this the bird that flew by
there's no subject all right that's it i'm doing it wait what about this one that's pretty good
it's that one all right here we go what do you think about my tutorial moves okay the villain
wow those are big numbers nice and big would you like to keep this new photo or the one in
the photo decks i'll keep the new one it's way better that's one star all right dodrio position
size direction placement it's not bad it's a gold star yeah it's one to four stars
that one's not good but it's still it conveys a lot of emotion i think that conveys a lot less
than a thousand right now too that's fine it conveys sadness keychu that one's bad too but
he wasn't he was i couldn't get a good photo of him he was like far away it was the first
tutorial zone great timing oh other pokemon the sus guy is bad at photography do not call me the
sus guy okay that's not what i go by that's not what i go by my name is germa this is the
germa 985 community i'm not the sus guy we're not gonna run with that one so man the sus guy
really is sucks at this no we're not doing i'm not being the sus guy sus guy this is gonna be a big
one that's a gold star that's a platinum i don't even know what i don't know what kind of precious
metal that is that was good too it's cute size direction placement other pokemon that's a gold
star well it's not my fault they won't get boring photos that's a i mean if that if this game is
just take a photo of something close what's in the middle of the frame that's the best you're
gonna get size direction placement yeah that's a five thousand dollar play here comes the sus fans
same with this one i gotta get other other animals i'm gonna call them animals i'm not
calling them pokemons i want i'm gonna say animals it's way easier for me to say
oh i refuse to say pokemons i'm gonna say animals is that is that its butt do i get um
they're getting upgrades research oh here we go i need 40 000 points to get a research level too
holy shit i'm almost there bus guy doesn't like pokemon hey went thanks for the 20 community subs
20 subs from went thank you thank you though that's a lot once that level goes up you may
see pokemon behave in ways you haven't seen before the key to raising your research level is to
observe all types of animal behavior that means getting photographs of them in every category
from one to four so in short fill up that photo that animal photo library keep that in mind and
you'll be on the right track but get out there and snap lots of photos and cherish the encounters
with the animals you have along the way way easier i'd never have guessed it was your first trip out
there keep up the good work is this do an ipad present there's an ipad present i didn't but i
had to touch the screen for that to be an ipad present you researched lorio nature park for the
first time you got a score of a thousand points or more in the direction category during a photo
evaluation you got a score of a thousand in the placement category yep save the photos you took
to your album um yes after your research trips you can choose photos to save to your album which
is in your space in the lab you can also choose re-snap to make some changes to the photos before
you save them okay i want where i want this one look at that re-snap wow this is awesome okay
hold on no i want the focal point to be there we go no no i want it close not far away don't
rest in sleep for me this is a good photo relax where's the where's the focal point i want it like
right where can i get it i can't see it where is it this isn't doing anything well i want the focal
point up front how come it's not just not changing anything oh there we go okay perfect i zoom in i
put the camera down that's gotta be up here like that yep perfect a little bit higher wow oh oh
oh these filters what the fuck are these why is it green they're all just silhouettes with
different colors yeah that's fine all right snap that photo right there save this photo yes building
a lodge okay i'm ready i don't need to save anymore these is the fucking tutorial i'm done
fable 2 fable 2 fable 2 i'll see you with fable 2 next week you didn't save it what
it's going to nighttime photo shoot by the way don't forget you can come back to the lab and
take a look at your photo decks anytime cool this is fable 2 essentially well don't let me
keep you any longer have a good time and snap some photos all right let's go for it lab research i
want to i'm i think this is fun are you really gonna play this for eight hours i don't know
play the baseball game again i'm taking pictures of animals right now all right don't worry i'll
play pac-man 99 later and like mario 30 whatever it is you head on another expedition now before
you go let me tell you one more thing you can do with your research camera you can run a scan
that'll give you a thesis about your surroundings cool tells you about nearby animals and points
out anything unusual what counts as unusual you've never given me a solid answer it's why is it gonna
have ski goggles i don't know what it was that for is he like welding pokemon together inside
of this basement or something why does he have those basically anything that makes the system
go check this out well i guess that's all the detail we're gonna get those are lab goggles
are they they look kind of huge why does he need what what do you okay what does he need them for
she doesn't have them i don't have them why does he have those what are they for
because of chemicals i don't know what what chemicals with with the animals the pokemon
in his house what do you do what why doesn't use them move on that's fucking weird i already
i'm holding all right running a scan x's scan okay i can scan whatever i want
oh that's cool that's not a pokemon that's a car
hmm
okay i did oh i can analyze it analyze neo one this vehicle is essential for your pokemon research
why did you say that now i have to say it why did you do that why did you do that
now i just looked over i saw it now i have to say erin i had erin erin erin erin why did you do that
why did you there's no reason for you to say that now you should see the results
i'm not making a joke that's an that somebody told me to do it
that's fun that's not funny i'm doing an impression of armin from attack on titan
i'm just doing it i just got i have to i'll do it over here so it's not allowed
erin i'm sorry i have i do have no idea do you know what it's like to fucking live with me
do you know what it's like to be in the same house as me in the same room as me i do that shit
just lying down i i just will be lying down and like hanging out in and just start doing it i'll
just start saying erin like 25 times in a row in the shower it doesn't matter that's psychotic
behavior it is not that's not psychotic behavior that's called uh making myself giggle wait i can
i can yell at them to look at me hey professor explanation's all done
all right let's go let's take some pictures wait i can pick where we go
are taking lots of photos of pokemon at the nature park during the day
let's go park during the day why don't we take a bunch of photos and surprise the professor with
them is erin a streamer yes we have 14 000 people watching well that's not on me that's on them
that's not on me all right wait say cheese how do i do it shit i missed it i gotta look left hold on
he woke him up these photos are fucking dog shit hold on they're dog shit i need to make these
better how is he this bad wait that's huge and right in frame it just did some weird
i'm running a scan wait scan wants me to look at something it's dung some charred fruits on the
ground did the pokemon do this the rest of those aren't fruits mushrooms i scanned that yep
crystal bloom that grows on florio island oh all right i'm gonna get a good one of these guys
shit i wasn't ready ah did i get it wait wait he just ran away he just ran by me
i just missed something cool it was so bad wait hold on i'm not done you almost had it
what could i even do with the magic carp hey look over here look over here got it that was
a perfect shot for some reason i thought i was gonna crash i thought i wasn't paying attention
to the road and just roving to the ground hey wake up wake up wake up food hoot has an unusual
way of sleeping always on one foot wake up hey erin stop stop saying that i'm gonna get an
awesome one here i'm gonna it's gonna be right wait should i get him in the background say cheese
say cheese hello do something erin stopped i'm gonna lose my mind hell what is that hello turn
this way what is that hello turn turn and look at me turn and look turn and look you're doing
something weird i don't know what it is but i got it whatever she doesn't want to look she's camera
shy oh what even is this joke what joke i was taking a photo what do you want about all right
here we go some of those are gonna be worth a lot took the same pictures i did not take the same
pictures that one's the same all right these are the same photos not that all right look at that
funny face he's making that one awful just awful okay i got you wait i got i got a three star
potential here holy shit i'll take it his eyes are closed that's kind of funny because i think
his eyes are closed that's kind of funny right oh yeah that when he's popping out his chest
i was at a two star photo is horrible wait this how is that this one's better how is that one
better all right let's go oh i have to do from every folder and none of these none of these are
worth pulling in i mean that one's kind of cool no these are like they suck not better but more
special okay pose is worse size is worse everything is worse but placement well i'm not keeping this
one the old one that's the same picture i took before what's the difference i want to know what
the difference is the only difference is two of their eyes are closed it's a worse photo okay the
pose is probably better i could work on size all right now this is a three star three star pose
size direction placement that's not that's three gold stars that's gonna be worth a lot
oh is this one okay i did you guys hear that did you did you hear that did that pick up on the mic
did anybody hear that like
that was the lightsaber i didn't touch it it just like turned on i didn't do anything this one's
bad too but it's probably fine all right i'll be at research research level um two right we got
another 10 you know how we say it here stay with me another 10 community subs from wenty lair
all right let's step forward for our research i bet i bet animals in the area are getting
comfortable with you by the way thanks to the progress you've made in your research i've got
something to report i feel even once your photos are squared away i think you'll be pleased to hear
this all right should i save any of these no none of these did it for me except for maybe this one
i'm relating to like the bird photos these are awful how are these filters these are terrible
i was i was thinking of like snapchat instagram filters like iphone filters
you get better ones later oh all right then we'll fuck this i'm out none of these weren't any good
wait that one's kind of cool saving that one how does this boomer know what snapchat is
like you're not you're telling me that you dive you've never downloaded snapchat and put like
trump's face on your face just like recorded yourself going let me tell you listen no believe
every single one of us did that like there's not one person i don't think in the world that
didn't do that for like 10 minutes only boomers do that that was when face swapping was first
introduced i've never done that and i don't intend to i i'm just telling you like that's
what people did yeah many times i put on from game of thrones putting on like different characters
faces and just doing their monologues snl humor that's me putting like a face on my face i'm not
sharing this with the public by the way i was just doing it in the comfort of my privacy of my own
living room you're the one who discovered how that glow happens it's even weirder that is not
weirder how many of you sing in the shower i want to know how many people's here sing in the shower
some of you i know at least some of you do actually me me me me me okay is that an
is that insane are you insane for doing that i don't sing in the shower i do like celebrity
impressions in the shower what's the difference you are imitating a song that you heard i'm
imitating a person i've heard how's that different it's the same thing there's a big difference no
it's not you singing firework in your shower is not is the exact same thing as me just putting
my hands up looking left and right with the water hitting me in the face going imitate excuse me
believe me it's the same thing it's the exact same thing it's just you happen to have a tone
while you're doing it why do you sing in the shower what's it for is armin a celebrity
i mean kinda yeah i mean is he probably i mean yeah maybe the actor is like an actor i'm imitating
the i'm imitating an actor okay that's really funny he is he's doing voices while touching
himself in the shower you can't just add shit onto this missing the plot there's animals you
take photos of who cares for now enjoy your nighttime outing okay sometimes you wonder
if i'm a lab experiment what you should be wondering is how did i get out
at night you might be able to see the illumina phenomenon at the nature park observe your
surroundings carefully you got there's currently a poll 51 percent of you sing in the shower
and i'm weird for doing like celebrity impressions in the shower i'm the weird guy but when you are
singing you are imitating the voice the cadence and the tone of the singer who sings the song
you're crazy you're the weird sus guy
uh i i love this this is fun okay here we go we're at night
anybody else anybody on the wait that's gonna be a lot i got like all the meat i need a face
hey oh did i get him smiling come on give me a good picture of uh
shit whatever no someone's doing something cute and i'm not looking
you get back here i gotta get the the scorch bunny in the background
remember this game sucks whoa what is that that's i got all the meat i got a shitload of meat
honestly never did i think that people would be mad that i'm playing a pokemon game you know how
many people people beg me to play pokemon jerma how come you don't play pokemon it's so fun you're
gonna love it pokemon's awesome i love pokemon do you love pokemon i love pokemon got it where's
the thing that i need a skin i already got that come on right here right when he was snoring
perfect all pokemon games are garbage wake up i got him with his wings in the air nice all right
what about you hoot hoot oh shit oh i freaked out that was a beautiful pose
do something do something do something funny well now i know what it's like
yeah you're not just gonna do something say streamer do something funny now i know
yeah come on one more come on again that's a good one that's a very good one where is this thing
is something to scan where's it where's the thing i need to scan where's this thing i have to scan
where is it i already scanned it i just picked you a huge energy reading what a huge energy reading
holy shit i got it right at the last one of the buzzer all right what i get got a lot to discuss
but first let's get your photos evaluated is this actually any good um i don't i i don't know i'm
i'm sorry i'm currently talking to a bunch of people who are covering their eyes
and their ears at the same time and screaming i don't i don't know can they tell can the people
watching this tell which one of these is good that one probably that one this is worth three
it was mid jump that one's good that's a four star photo thank you insert oh come on it's
right when he came out of the hole that's awesome that was a great photo what this is not like a
five star image all right which one of these is any good probably that one oh i like that one
no this one's good suano that he's so far away ducks the oh i remember i know pigioto hoot hoot
it's not that one it's that one look at how good this is it's this one right this one's off center
but it's closer i'm going with this one it's more intense and then a crystal bloom and then
did i have one of where's pichu in this photo there is no pichu do i wear a deodorant i do
i do i do not wear an antiperspirant i wear a deodorant that was good
placement that's a silver i'll take it uh antiperspirant burns my underarms i gotta be
honest i will put on a deodorant with antiperspirant in it and six hours later
it will be just red marks under my arms it's a diamond photo all right that's pretty good
you might be allergic to aluminum that's interesting that means it's working yeah
you really it's only gonna burn your skin for you to know it's working that's a good photo
yeah a lot of uh antiperspirants use aluminum dioxide yeah that doesn't sound good four stars
but it's bronze oh well that's the first four star um i'm just painting can't sweat if your
skin has melted off um is that true discovery no deodorant's fine deodorant just makes it so
you don't smell it just like makes you smell nice an antiperspirant and here's the thing
about antiperspirant i'm about to let you guys in on a very very very strong held not a secret
this is literally you can just google this in five seconds figure this out um if you wear
antiperspirant it makes you sweat more in my case i used to put this on i would put on just like a
standard just deodorant antiperspirant and i would just i would be soaking through my shirt and my
underarms since i have stopped wearing this is this is absolutely true this is completely true
since i have stopped using an antiperspirant over time i don't have you guys remember how i
lift up my shirt and i'd be like oh sweat check yeah i don't have like big wet marks on my arms
anymore your nose blind i'm not sweat check sweat check like you want to prove it all right
clean wait i don't want you to see that far in my arm clean look this is clean this is clean
i mean there's a little fuck my career is over oh no i hate it i'm so pissed i really thought
there was nothing there what do you remember how huge it was before you remember how gigantic it
was and remember listen wait wait wait wait wait wait i this is las vegas nevada okay it's very
hot here even with like air conditioning i'm sitting down getting really heated streaming
in like a hot streamer room this is that's that's you should you should have seen how it was like
a few years ago do you remember how fucking revolting it was it was revolting three or four
years ago i would lift it up it would be like somebody it was a joke like somebody poured water
on me i i want to know how good this one is that's okay good that's diamond it looks sad i don't like
this picture maybe you just have a better diet no i don't think so it's because i was wearing
i don't wear it anymore i just wear like a gentle deodorant it was the mayo sweats all right level
one going on to level two almost perky sweats your sweat backing up is causing your back pain
what if that would be that would be quite a discovery okay uh crystal bloom by the way
thanks to the progress you've made in your research i've got something to report
i'll fill you in once your photos are squared away i think you'll be pleased to hear this
i don't want to save any of this sponsored viewer this game is awesome pogchamp you can save your
photos to the nintendo switch album no what is this something in credit what's what happened
that looks bad here's the thing what's the point of that cutscene it's like was just animated and
like cg and stuff when you get near that field of flowers i picked up an incredibly strong energy
reading also its source seemed to be moving too if only slightly which suggests that we've
got here is an illumina pokemon we can't be sure yet but i suspect so i wonder why it showed up
did you do anything special i also doubt that it appeared when it did by chance but i think you
should be the one to investigate the area where that reading is coming from oh i want to go see
you can watch the monitor with me it's gonna be real dangerous it's gonna be full of radiation
why do you think we're sending the fucking new guy anyways kid have fun sending a kid
all right let's find the illumina animal here we go this is a boss this is a i have to say good
photos of the boss
quiet too quiet
look at the camera at the camera are you dumb this is a fucking weird land before time
brontosaurus kid take the photo hurry all right scan it don't take a picture of his ass
wait what am i scanning i need a good picture of him wait is he eating he's eating oh where's
this i don't know what i'm supposed to be scanning what do i what am i supposed to do with him i
don't know we're gonna make a big collage these photos suck wait i don't know it's what's one
took good get him running scan hold x there's something i can scan somewhere you're gonna do
anything oh how is he bad at this what are you talking about i took stop zooming it said get
them big the number one thing that professor oak told me to do was make sure they're huge in the
frame we got a lot to discuss let's go get your photos evaluated okay what's a good one none of
these are usable okay i guess that none of those are usable oh is that not usable that's awesome
look he's like doing a big sniff okay hold on look at how good that is what the fuck these are
perfect what what the hell why can i use any of these what read what do you mean read
i need to scan him this this is like uh this is an emote what emote is that
oh these are all not good it has to be when he's glowing my dog makes that face all the time
okay well which one of these is the best i mean probably that one i think i have to use the emote
okay it's meganium size pose is great size is great direction is great placements great
that's diamond i got it i don't need to come back and do this ever again level two got it look at
that you've had a new stage in your research keep an eye out for changes so i have to go back there
and take a picture when the animal does something different and does a new pose you need to go take
a pee and play pac-man no i'm not doing that yet i'm i'm playing this i like this i'm invested
for the time being everybody hate pokemon all of a sudden everybody hates pokemon i thought this is
like everyone's favorite fucking franchise well i need that one i need this all right massive blur
go right there okay why haven't you a bit unusual good okay cool let's go i got a new filter
wait new filter literally new filter literally we like attack on titan boomer keep doing arman's
voice you don't think i like it that was amazing wasn't it gorgeous wasn't it huge and it was saying
something easy there read it take a deep breath who's talking you were practically dancing professor
ahem moving on there's no doubt about it that meganium was an illumina pokemon they all
fucking weird names like i illumina is it illumina illumina it's not illumina it's illumina
it's an illumina pokemon bright animal done illiterate andy sounded out illumina illumina
pokemon that's too much that's too much to say illumina pokemon illumina pokemon that's seven
syllables to get to get across literally bright dog bright dino i just made it so much easier for
you aluminum aluminum illumina it's illumina illumination illumination i'm sorry let me do
that better illumination they have distinctive patterns and to glow with unusual light minion
voice you're done what do you mean i'm done i'm done what do you mean i'm done
minion voice you're done it's over for you oh shit i see you go biart career over
all right let's pick up this conversation from here tomorrow
i really thought this is a career ending stream i thought that like my fly was down and that like
i was in deep deep shit there's probably a frame grab you could take of me looking down and having
like that half second of like panic on camera you could it's i stream at 60 fps you could probably
find one frame where it's just like oh my god he thinks he's naked i've been preparing to launch
an ecological survey spanning the entire lentil region no sooner had you arrived than we suddenly
found in right dog i think there's a connection professor i can't be sure yet but fascinating
things are bound to happen if you come with us really oh you know maybe for a scientist
you sure can be vague sometimes professional i think it's a good idea i'll be way more fun
it'll be way more fun with you along right ready to officially join our research team
wait i haven't been on the team the whole time i accept let's make it official
it's like you were born to wear it we're waiting for adventure awaits
terrain on your parade frida but i need to get a couple more things ready first
oh come on just a little bit longer all right i promise it'll be worth the wait right i'll explain
next time you're headed out to do some research sounded like deku from my hero academia you did
oh it's really wild well i wonder who's gonna win this tournament is that that's not no it's not
you officially joined the lentil region officially joined the lentil region research team
all right let's go i'm talking about anime you guys are talking about it i just said
literally one word now that you're a full-fledged team member i have something for you that'll come
in handy food on your trips enough feeding me these guys get one apple oh by the way
i forgot i haven't been feeding either of you here's an apple it's been four days is just me
or have you been getting me to do a lot more of the work lately professor well time to explain
like the great assistant i am he's gone what happened to him what happened to him is he all
right this is a this is a fluff fruit they grow here it's an apple why can't you just say apple
this is my problem with this whole universe why can't you just say apple this is a fluff fruit
they grow here in the lentil region they're sweet and tasty it's like they're like afraid to get
copyright infringement on apple and like pears and grapes and stuff i don't understand they're
sweet and tasty and they make a great snack for a pokemon they may look just like regular apples
but they're way lighter and softer oh so oh so they're a macintosh my favorite you probably
make a pokemon's day if you toss it one of these let's get you some practice macintosh is the best
yes it is
okay they like them i can aim it
oh i'm going for it i'm going for a skull why is it the first thing i want to do
i don't know i'm going i'm trying to hit him in the head
okay
i didn't kill him he's alive
i'm just getting hit with an like an apple that would suck those things are they're dense and
they're kind of heavy you should try testing out fluff root and taking some more photos in the
meantime professor says there are all kinds of ways to use it finished explaining ic thanks
frito we've got one more thing to tell you about you never know what's going to happen in
imaginopolis so if you ever need any help just click me here we go
i thought it would be handy to have a quick way to share what we see and learn in the field
are you too familiar with len talk you're the ted bundy of twitch get out of here ban that person
for at least a day oh i don't want to see the person's name for a week okay two weeks three
weeks are you familiar with that oh what are you talking about like what the fuck are you talking
about no i you want to be i i'll make me bozo the clown not ted bundy bozo the clown like trips
over stuff and like hits his head on the wall and makes noises and stuff ted bundy is a is a
serial killer i'm more like bozo the clown than i am ted bundy okay please this is bozo the serial
killer this is just like that person that somebody asked me they were like hey dude like tell me what
you do when you're not streaming so like i can like i can prove that you're not a serial killer
and it's like what the fuck do you want me to say well how how do you we have like the things
that we do on a regular basis for us to give ourselves like time passing in our brains i
don't know what i do like for like a four to six hour period during the day i i don't know sit
around on the couch watch tv work on stuff who remembers every second of their life
i'm pretty sure that you're the zodiac killer no i'm not i was not born how could i be the
zodiac killer if i wasn't alive in that time period i can use it to say all right let me pay
attention to the video game i'm having a lot of fun playing animal fixtures look for lend talk
messages in the top right of the screen at the research camp and elsewhere they ought to they
ought to help i'm going to be so pissed off if germa actually ends up being a murderer you don't
don't all right don't worry because that's not happening i that you don't have to worry about
that let me ease your mind for a second don't spend more than like three bites of captain crunch
what you're wondering if i have killed someone okay i haven't i'm not i can help i can alleviate
that oh what's this oh when it gets to this spot next to that big tree i mean okay i can
understand like okay here's the first bite i wonder if i'm german i've never killed anybody
second bite no whatever this is weird okay time to move on with my day done i i get it you can
maybe think that you could do we have these little like oh what ifs it shouldn't last that long a
terrific yawn i wonder what it looks like when a torteri yawns aren't you curious okay so i gotta
get one of them yawning sometimes lorges seems to gather natural power from its surroundings you
mind getting a photograph of this striking behavior i think i already got that have you seen which
pokemon is scorching these fruits catch him doing it okay all right let's go for it what happened
to this picture noteworthy behavior who is it whose is this are you sending me this photo
deep fried what all right i'm going back to the fucking research facility okay luff fruit and
scans can help you set up all kinds of photos don't be shy okay so i need to go take a picture of who's
doing that who's scorching the fruits please play pac-man dude holy shit it's been an hour and a half
i'm gonna be here for a while okay let's throw fruits i'll get it what eat it why do they take
so long to do that i get it did i get the apple hitting him in the head he's pissed wait he thinks
he did it he thinks the buffalo did it are they gonna fight okay hold on i need to catch whoever
does this in the act oh that was so cute oh what holy shit that was cool too hey hey wait wait wait
come back here we go who's doing this i think somebody come and do this i gotta catch somebody
in the act hello did he already do it i'm just throwing i'm just throwing apples at birds
like what the fuck am i doing oh stay right there come get that oh don't eat it yet wait
look at oh he's got a bunch of snacks that's such a good photo he's against me as i'm hoarding
these apples something scannable what can i scan oh all right that's a uh a fruit oh please no
shit i didn't scan them what just happened oh wait i have to i have to get her doing that thing
there it comes do it look at how many other pokemon are in the do the thing do the thing
do the thing eat apples whoa okay i got it this is a less violent on-rails shooter well it's a
non it's a non-violent on-rails shooter some of those are gonna be really good the apple
flying the apple hitting the head really fast this is a great chain of events i like this one
or this one oh that one sucks what is this oh is there a animal in this one i guess what what are
you honestly telling me this is not at least two stars that's an incredible photo how is this photo
better than this one star is pose rarity i think this is the one right here yeah what the hell is
this i mean that's a this one's perfect right here let's get a good like just front right in the front
ours is what pose they're in there's nothing to do with quality i can't even see the pokemon here
i like how he reads comments but doesn't process what they say at all and then proceeds to not
understand welcome to every single day of my life in high school like does reading comprehension i
would just read and i could read very well but the text every paragraph i would go down the
paragraph before it was invisible ink and would just disappear i would only be able to comprehend
like the current like one paragraph i was in and it just it was disappearing the book was
disappearing behind it i can do better than that that's a really good photo direction placement
that's yeah diamond there we go there we go all right i got i gotta get diamond one star diamond
two star this is gonna be diamond oh yeah yeah nice all right good adhd andy or idiot andy pick
your poison i think it's eight i'm not an idiot i would say i probably i'm not an unintelligent
person just have trouble paying attention to things retry oh yeah all right so i need to
i gotta figure i gotta take a picture of the the scorch rabbit grow apples all right well where
where is this guy good relax okay there's it's up there so i have to where he he's not scorching
them yet he hasn't he's not he hasn't shown up yet is he then oh that was good shit i got that
same one again yeah i did the same exact thing all right where is this guy holy shit whoa is he
doing that you doing that it's you doing that i got it right wait something else well i've already
seen the crystal bloom okay now i have to get what was the other one i want to get as many birds
over here as i can shit that's kind of good no i want to throw whoa that was awesome do it again
okay i have to be ready for what was the other one there was two other photos to get
all right scan wait hold on that's a good one that's a great one where's that thing up here right
whatever can where's it eat that apple cute really cute okay this is it and i do that the
power thing right i'm gonna do it throw an apple through the hoop really needs to do that spin
move do the spin do the spin move why would you do it remember you're dumb i am don't say that
don't throw and don't scan that's way better yeah i'm gonna take this one what's the two that i have
so far oh yeah the three angry heads which one's better though probably that one whoa oh shit that
one that's right in the act that's the one right there i mean i'm just gonna use it because that's
the one that i it's a three star right i do have the really cool ones with magic carp which one's
better this one's more centered but this one looks more interesting probably this one that's really
cool hmm this one all right let's go for it hey mr elberton i stopped by early to drop off your
nobel prize but you weren't home congrats on the award for academic excellence thanks that's
definitely that's diamond you got an apple in there you have another pokemon in there they look
interesting yeah that's it that's gonna be there it is uh in the last one yeah all right there we go
there's a is diamond i could see how this this game could be very addicting you're a vtuber now
what are you talking about how am i a vtuber that's good too oh what the guy in the corner oh okay
that one is not better than this one what how is that a better picture i guess i'm gonna hold
on to it it's a good that's a good magic cap get it in there this one might be a little better
no i mean it's a cooler picture but it's not better and in the scrapbook um i guess i'll take
this one did you like the departed oh my god i love the departed is that a new pokemon i don't know
your photo dex is filling up remember to check what pokemon you're missing photos for now and
then yeah i don't want to keep any of those photos all right return to camp for a second i want to
see where i fulfilled something right hope you're having fun i actually am this is fun i like this
what can i do in the lab this is the professor's lab not that it's your first time here of course
this is where the professor does his research and works on mechanical stuff
actually pretty much lives here all right let me give you a quick rundown of what you can do here
that's sir over there is where we store our research work there are a few things you can do
with all that data first you can check your photo dex that's the encyclopedic record you're building
with the photos you're taking isn't it cool getting to put together your very own photo dex
we said what would you say this game um asking what would i say about it do i like it i think
this game and it speaks to uh the photographer in in all of us i'm speaking very like
advertising aren't i next there's your space personal photo album and adventure milestones
your album is for photos you want to keep but not put in your photo dex yeah
you can edit your album photos in some cool ways too am i forgetting anything
anything else i'm supposed to tell would you cover what we can do in the internet
oh yeah that was it if you use the online internet feature you can see photos from
players all around the world if you really like a photo you can tell the photographer
nice job by giving the photo a little digital medal they're called sweet medals give all you
want people love getting them that's right you can also see other photographers rankings in
each score category i think that's everything sure you figured all out quick reddit gold
uh i don't give a shit about any of this okay so what do we got we got some stuff going on right
what do i need i need to get this one and the terrify terrifying yawn okay at night and i get
the turtles yawning you know you are a redditor jeremy i use the website sometimes okay that's
a problem for a lot of you all right and you get the turtle yawning like apples
sometimes okay that's like a problem for a lot of you all right and you get the turtle yawning
like apples not really
all right where the tur wait this guy like fruit that's the first time i got a picture of his face
he's a cool that's a good it was him taking a shower or something you'd apples that was kind
That's kind of cool too.
Oh, missed that one, it's okay.
What, what, what, what?
Noises are coming from this, oh yeah, okay, ready?
Get out of there.
All right, here we go.
Total yawn, a total yawning.
Did he yawn?
Wake up?
Come on, be just like that pig in that YouTube video
that smells the cookie and goes like.
Wake up?
Yawn?
There it is.
I got it.
You want to do it one more time?
Oh, fine, I got it.
What else, what else did I have to do?
You like apples?
That's going to be kind of cool.
Whoa, this is the cutest thing ever.
Is it mad?
Hey, I got to, we got to get an apple here.
Erin, it was rude.
What?
Ooh, this is cute.
This is very cute.
I don't, I don't want to, I don't want to wake him up.
It's cool, this is very cute.
I mean like super cute.
Got it.
Zooming Andy.
Yes, I want my subjects to be in frame.
What we got?
One star.
And that's a better picture, you can see everything.
All right, which one of these is the best?
Probably one of these.
I like that one.
Or this one, he's on the ground just creeping.
I like that one too, he's thinking.
We need to have one star.
We'll do this one, that one.
First one I have is much better.
All right, where's the yawning one?
That's yawning, that's yawning, right?
I love that one.
This is him yawning.
I need this one.
Let's get it in the, get it in the book.
I don't know, should I do?
Probably, probably one?
Hey, that's, is this one better than the other one?
Probably not.
I need a two star, that one's fine.
This is a really good picture, come on.
His eyes, placement.
Yeah, there it is.
He's pogging.
I feel like this is probably a better photo.
No?
No, I guess not.
I think that's much better.
It's his eyes and face.
Oh, that's it.
Is there a Caterpie in this video?
Apparently there is.
All right, this is the big ticket item here.
That's a golden, four star diamond.
Ain't gonna find a photo like that ever again.
Place it in there.
I like this hoot hoot photo.
Bold, mm-hmm.
Just gotta get it in the book.
Digimon digital monsters.
Digimon digital monsters, digital monsters.
Research level two.
I thought they were animals.
They are.
Okay, what are the,
I have to go back to the boss monster thing.
The love of entertainment stopped zooming in.
No, I'm gonna, look, I'm gonna take my photos away.
I'm gonna take them.
And they're good.
Wait, is that, that looks like a dog?
That was a regular dog.
I told you it was a dog.
This is Todd.
He's a professional Pokemon photographer.
His work takes him all over the world.
Are you the one they caught?
Hey, bright dog on camera, way to go.
That's a big deal.
Todd, did you bring what I asked you to?
Sure did.
You're a lifesaver.
Now we'll finally be able to set out.
Is this guy a friend of yours, Professor?
An old travel companion, to be precise.
He's been helping me plan our big survey of Lentil too.
No kidding.
Oh, is that the new pod you put together?
Reminds me of the good old days.
But hey, let me see those Illumina Pokemon photos.
A kid, get your own mentor.
What the fuck is this?
So you're the new teammate, huh?
I'm Phil, Todd's number one student.
Easy there, Phil.
I'm tempted to take part in this big ecological survey
myself, but I have another idea.
How about I send Phil with you instead?
I'm fine with that if you are, Todd.
Yes, awesome.
You can be my stand-in for now.
But don't forget, I'll need that badge back eventually.
Well, fine, but if I take a super cool photo,
I get to keep the badge.
Please stop this shit, Todd voice.
Why, does it make you, you don't like it?
Making you feel a certain way?
That's what he sounds like.
What is that?
I don't know, I thought that was chin armor.
I thought he was wearing a fucking necklace.
Ooh, cool.
That's not, I'm just pretending.
Okay, I thought it was a new area,
but it's our camp and I wasn't paying attention,
so I just wanted to make you think
that I thought it was cool.
Is that I wasn't paying any attention.
They're talking about this is where we are right now.
This would be our first destination.
Ooh.
Why are we starting there?
I've detected a spot there with high energy readings.
The Neo One should be able to teleport to it.
This island showed up in the travel log, right?
Certainly did.
Captain Vince wrote that he saw a glowing Pokemon
there too, in fact.
Come on already, let's get this survey started.
Fair enough.
Enjoy your first in a century adventure
into the wilds of Lental.
All right, what else?
Hoot Hoot's hidden foot.
Have you ever seen Hoot Hoot's other foot?
You should try to get a photo of it.
Not now.
New area unlocked.
Don't make a Warcraft reference.
Don't make a, do not make a Warcraft reference.
Do not say, open up your M in World of Warcraft
and right click, right click, right click, right click.
You have to right click like six times
to see the world in World of Warcraft.
It's like zones inside of zones, inside of zones,
inside of countries, inside of countries now.
I'm, look, I'm a Warcraft streamer.
I've already talked about this.
It doesn't matter that I've not played WoW
in a very, very long time.
All that matters is I dedicated like two plus years
in front of the screen.
Like 500 days played in WoW.
It's part of my life, like permanently.
We got, we got, they have faces?
I don't know.
Whoa, there's a Woody the Woodpecker.
Whoa, what is that guy?
That's Peter Griffin.
That's, hey!
That's Peter Griffin in a costume.
That's, I don't, it is.
Animal up there?
I'm gonna scan.
Crystal Bloom, a crystal bloom that grows
on Bilselvia Island.
What are you gonna do?
Throw shit at him.
That also could be Peter Griffin in a costume.
That's my favorite Pokemon.
His name's Quagmire.
This is my favorite Pokemon.
Is this one cool?
I like this one.
That's actually my favorite Pokemon.
Ah, eggs.
Ready to come eat those eggs.
That wasn't even a good picture.
That was terrible.
Where is it?
These ancient ruins are being engulfed
by an enormous tree.
Shit.
I like this zone, this zone's cool.
Into the water?
This is gonna be like a, a, a, a, a,
this is gonna, whatever.
This is gonna be something in here.
Come on, go for it.
He's right there.
I get it.
Jump out of the water.
Whoa, you're asleep.
Oh shit, I didn't even look.
Missed the yawn.
That was a cool cat.
Those are french fries.
Ha ha ha ha.
Good picture, I liked it.
Anybody want any fruits?
That Pokemon is the definition of a no thoughts head empty.
They do just kind of sit there with their mouths open,
don't they?
You like apples?
Don't like apples.
Ha ha ha.
Come on, give me something through the trees here.
Oh well.
Shit, come on, really?
What is that emote?
What is that?
Like a pizza, it's a Megalo pizza?
It's the only one I have, so take it.
I mean, that's just better.
Which one of these is the best?
Probably this one.
Aw.
Ha ha ha.
Wait, this one has another Pokemon in it though.
There's probably more points.
Aw, it's probably that one.
Yeah, that one.
That one, nope, that one.
Should I go for the four star?
I think so, if I have an opportunity, why not?
It's good to me.
One stars are easy to forget, that's true.
Yeah, it's gonna be dog shit, I know, it don't matter.
Why am I still playing this?
Well, it's a very simple answer for you.
Because I'm having fun.
Stop having fun, I'm not allowed.
I'm having fun!
Who cares?
You need to entertain us.
I'm having fun, and I'm having fun.
Jatt hates games.
Ha ha ha.
I have, okay.
Is there a game that collectively everybody here liked?
I don't know if it's, I don't think so.
Has there ever been a video game
that everyone here collectively actually enjoyed?
I'm not sure it's ever happened.
Simpsons Hit and Run?
I don't think anybody liked that particular game
as much as they liked people being angry at it.
House Flipper?
You know what, that's true.
House Flipper is the one.
People saying TF2?
Yeah, I haven't streamed TF2.
I think I streamed TF2 like twice, like four years ago.
I love House Flipper.
What a great game.
We all collectively hated Watch Dogs 3.
Oh yeah, so did I.
That's probably the worst game I've ever played.
Wait, can there be a category of worst games
I've ever played that costed like $100 million to make?
Ooh, requests, what is it?
Most expensive disappointments.
What do we got?
There's a Pokemon that's nowhere to be seen most of the time,
but at night it sleeps beside Torterra.
Can you see if you can find it?
I already got that one, didn't I?
An afternoon meal?
Wait, I have to get a photo of that?
No, that's just you sending me pictures.
I don't want them.
Hard one, happiness.
Pidgeotto's cool, but it's kind of distant.
Think it'd warm up to you for a fluff root?
Okay, did you get a picture of the Hoot Hoot foot?
And then there's a Pokemon that sleeps in this area.
Perhaps it would show itself where,
if there were other Pokemon nearby, okay.
I want to go to that jungle at night.
Can I do it at night?
During the day.
All right, chow time.
Making a splash.
Yeah, I already did that one.
I'm a beginner, chow time.
Wait, who is this?
How am I getting this?
Oh, this is somebody's picture.
Oh, that was pretty cool.
Sweet, make some Reddit gold.
All right, I got to get a picture of him splashing.
Report it.
Why would there be a report function?
It's on rails.
What would you possibly be doing to report a photo?
Okay, zoom, zoom Andy, zoom Andy, zoom Andy, I know.
Somebody will find a way.
Zoom.
Oh, spider, is this a spider?
Is this a spider Pokemon?
I need Peter Griffin's attention.
Get out of the way.
It didn't work.
There are like three spider Pokemon, really?
There's four of them, are there really?
Wait, what's that?
Move out of the way, there's something over there.
Holy shit, it's a snake.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, it eats the apples.
All right, hold on, come over here.
Do it over here.
Oh, that's a good one.
He's huge, he really is.
Ooh, good pose.
He posed right for the camera too.
That's gonna be a good one.
I need one of these guys jumping into the pool.
That snake was huge.
All right, was that guy jump?
I should have scanned, my own fault.
Whoa, cool.
All right, where's the, I need the lake.
Something over here.
Something nest over here.
What does it say?
Sega does what Nintendon't, right?
Look over here.
Sega does what Nintendon't.
Genesis was fucking absolute dog shit
compared to the Super Nintendo.
It was absolute dog shit in comparison.
Hey guys, hey, hey, hey, it's me.
It's me, a Sega game.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
They all sounded like that.
Super Nintendo had the cleaner audio
and audio is half the way.
What's over there?
What's my favorite smell?
I don't know.
Favorite smell.
Um, come on, do something.
Um, favorite smell.
I'll tell you what my non-favorite smells are.
Cinnamon apple.
Cinnamon apple candles.
Meh.
Like apple pie candle.
I don't like it.
It's perfect, look at that one.
These both are actually really good.
It's the size.
All Walmart candles smell the same.
Ooh, I like that one.
That one, I like this one too.
It's probably that one.
So cute.
Yeah, I like that one a lot.
And this one.
Perfect.
And jumping into the water, which is the one that, um,
is it this one here?
That's the one he wants, right?
Or does he want the actual splash?
Sandalwood?
I'm gonna do you one up here.
Oud.
Oud is one of my favorite scents.
It was O-U-D, oud.
If you've never smelled oud before, O-U-D,
it's so, it's so wonderful.
It's a wonderful scent.
Perfume, the perfume,
I can't even say this.
The perfume, the perfume you have
is oud, vanilla, and wood?
That, you, I mean, that's fantastic.
I love the smell of wood too.
I love the smell of wood.
Not like a tree, like a wooden table.
All right, there are these dog treats.
They're these dog bones that they have this,
they're made out of wood.
They have this wood smell.
They smell incredible.
They smell unbelievable.
They're like these wood sticks for dogs,
and I just wanna smell them.
They smell incredible.
Better than the last one.
Good photo, good pose, good size,
good direction, good placement.
I'll take a bronze.
Oh, not savory dog smell.
I'm talking about, there's a,
it's like a wooden dog chew thing.
I don't think it's actually made out of wood.
It just smells like wood.
This is weird, fake, chemical wood smell.
That's a great photo.
I've got two diamonds for the cat.
I'm not gonna say it.
It's fucking insane.
I can't say it.
It's ridiculous.
Which one's better?
I like this one.
You sniff.
You're fucking driving me crazy.
What do you got to report, Professor Mirror?
I'm not gonna say it.
I'm not gonna say it because it's fucked up
and I'm not going to say it.
Say it or we leave.
No, I'm not gonna say it.
I said the first part and it was something about wood.
I'm not gonna say the whole thing together.
Go to the jungle during the night
and photograph a crystal bloom glowing in the dark.
Get out of here.
You imagine like, this is,
look at this chat right now.
Look at this chat room.
What the hell is happening?
You guys are gonna get me in trouble.
No, I'm not, I'm not imagining.
I'm stop saying that.
I need to get this out of here.
I gotta get it out of here.
Okay, what do I say?
Shpee or coffee, Cheetos, chicken, shpee, shpee.
Get it out, get it out, get it out.
Probably the type we're after.
We'll call it the bright state.
Do we need to do anything special if we find one?
Not particularly, just snap a photo of it.
Your camera can analyze it for you.
Enjoy the nighttime jungle.
Ron.
In the comfort and safety of its own territory,
even the warriest Pokemon will let its guard down
to eat a tasty fruit.
Wow.
Oh, cool.
Whoa, how'd you get that?
I am so pro gamer.
I took this photo.
How'd you get that?
How'd you do this?
Okay, what are we doing at night?
I don't know.
So fucked up.
Shit, that was awful.
We're glowing?
Where's the bloom?
We, you started it.
I did not start it.
I just told you that I like the smell of my dog's toys.
I like the smell of my dog's wooden toy.
He has a toy that's wooden.
It smells like wood.
I hate this.
My dog has a toy.
It's a stick.
It came in a package and you open up the package
and it's made out of like tree, like wood.
It's wood.
There's the spider.
Spider's like apples.
Get a photo of a crystal bloom, right?
That's a crystal bloom right there.
Oh, oh, it has to be glowing.
Cute, snoozing in the tree.
It's like an invader's zim.
Turn and look, turn and look, oh.
He eat apples?
Oh, he's eating.
Show the toy, show the toy.
I will, I will show it.
I need a glowing crystal.
Wrong button.
Ooh, that's cool.
Can I get them to move?
That was cute.
Pato, oh, Pato, oh, there's Pato.
I was not even paying attention.
Could have got a cool action photo.
All right, crystal.
I hear something flapping, something flapping.
Good photo.
Oh, there's this one.
All right, throw an apple at it.
That didn't do anything.
Wow, wow, wow.
That's not doing anything.
Is there one glowing over here?
There's one glowing over there.
Move out of the way.
Move out of the way, move out of the way.
I want to go in his mouth with a photo.
Turn, you guys like apples?
You like apples?
One of those will work.
Just make the armpit fart noise already.
All right, fine.
That hurt, I can't do it.
I already have one of these, this one's way worse.
Do I have any, did you hear my mouth?
It was like.
Nothing's gonna compare with that one.
I mean, the sleeping one's cool, but no.
All right, this is four in the same shot.
That's probably what they want.
This is cuter, but this one is probably more points.
All right, I don't have any pictures of this.
That one's good.
This is a picture of him.
Oh, that one's cute.
I like this one.
Looks like he's balancing it on his nose.
It's this one.
I got a couple of really good ones here.
That one, that one, that one.
I'm gonna go with this one.
And a still bloom, glowing, got it.
Graphics kinda suck.
Um, I mean, it's the switch though.
Guys, don't you know,
Nintendo still bases their graphical power
on being like two and a half times more powerful
than the GameCube.
That's a good picture.
It looks better than sword and shield.
People didn't like that, did they?
I've not heard very good things about that.
I heard people really didn't like it.
All right, this is the big one here.
This is gonna be, that's gonna be gold or diamond.
Oh, silver.
Every gen past three is shit.
I don't even know what gen three is.
All I know is that I got Pokemon Diamond
for the Nintendo DS.
I don't know why it came out
and I just, for some reason, bought it.
I'd never played a Pokemon game ever before.
And I played it for about an hour
and then I just never played it ever again.
That's gen three.
I heard Pokemon Diamond and Pearl were the,
those, that's like the best one, right?
Everybody loves that.
Isn't that everybody's favorite?
Besides like green leaf and red, whatever.
That's everybody's favorite, I thought.
That's the first 5K I think I've gotten.
Diamond, Pearl, and Platinum are all gen four.
Gen two is the best.
That's gen four.
I simp for two and three, but four is objectively better.
All right, Pokemon sucks.
That's just in there in the sea of comments.
Ooh, you registered seven bugs.
Best Pokemon game is the one you played as a kid.
Now that, you get it.
You get it.
So what was the problem with Sword and Shield?
So every time they do a new Pokemon game,
they add another like 150 Pokemon, right?
True, what did I do, what did I say?
Nothing, it's perfectly fine.
They didn't advance the series, there was no effort.
Nothing bad, just literally nothing new.
Sword and Shield removed a lot of core features.
They cut half the Pokemon, it was boring.
Those orb thingies you've been working on, Professor,
that's those.
Ugly, stupid, stinky game.
Whatever, now I got you guys talking.
Now I got you guys interested.
All I had to say was, what's your favorite Pokemon, Gen?
And all of you woke up at the same time.
Somebody asked what my favorite Pokemon was?
It's very easy, it's Mewtwo.
He's the only one that can talk besides Meowth,
and he's just stronger and cooler than Meowth.
It's Mewtwo, it's the best Pokemon.
Lucario can talk.
No, he can't.
I suspect it's because different areas of Lentil
have distinct types of energy flowing through them.
For now, I want to see the fruits of your,
oh wait, he can talk.
What does he say, he says like,
no, not, not, not, that's Shadow the Hedgehog.
Chaos, what, no, what is it?
He says something.
What does Lucario say when he does something?
All of them can talk.
Chaos control, that's Shadow the Hedgehog.
Lucario says something when he does like a power.
He just says Lucario.
No, he talks, doesn't he?
Lucario says chaos control, what?
No, that's Shadow the Hedgehog.
Am I gaslighting myself?
What is, it's Shadow the Hedgehog, right?
Oh my gosh, it's so pretty.
Wow, Lentil's very own light show.
What did you call it again?
The Illumina Phenomenon?
It's interesting how it can occur
in both Pokemon and planets.
You can use these orbs to send Pokemon and Crystal Blooms
into the Illumina state for a while.
When you do, watch for changes in their surroundings.
You're gaslighting yourself, I,
but you guys are like helping me.
I have a blindfold on,
and you guys are guiding me around to gaslight myself.
This is pinned, this is like,
what's that, like, there's like a pinata hanging down.
And you guys, I have a blindfold on,
and like as a joke, you like turned me around
and like moved me down like the driveway.
And you're like, hey, your pinata's right in front of you.
And I'm like, swinging and just missing,
and I don't understand, and everyone's laughing.
And it's really funny until I take out the light post
and fucking down the driveway.
And it's real funny now, isn't it?
Do I have to pay for that?
Do I pay for that?
When I take the blindfold off
and I fucking hit your mailbox,
do I have to pay for that?
I don't believe I do, I don't think so.
All right, so now I can turn on those lights.
Please record yourself doing that
on a part of a green screen.
What, with like a blindfold saying like,
oh, where's the pinata?
Oh, I'm sad that doesn't already exist.
Okay, dinner time.
Sir McFluff loves Fluffies.
How come this is so cool, I like these.
Dinner time, as everybody has them eating the apples.
That's the meta right now.
This game is so new that the Pokemon eating apples
is the current most upvoted meta.
I'm gonna take a picture of a Pokemon
with an apple in front of them.
And I'm gonna try to get them biting into it.
And I'm gonna zoom in,
and I'm gonna put like snackies underneath it or something.
And I bet you that's the highest upvoted thing I have.
Stop meta gaming, why not?
All right, what are the requests here?
I heard a really loud noise and it got me wondering,
do you think Arbok ever falls out of its tree
while it's sleeping?
Should I try to get a picture?
Okay.
Whoa, Toucans.
I haven't seen Hickey Peck flying near Toucanon's nest.
What do you suppose they're up to?
That's just a Toucan.
I understand that Pokemons are supposed to be
kind of like animals and stuff,
but that's a Toucan, that's not Toucanon.
That's just a Toucan.
Why can't you just say it's near the Toucan's nest?
It has a gun, it has a cannon.
They're getting lazy.
It's just a couple, like a golden retriever runs by.
Oh, that's Goldidio, Goldidio.
That's the one right there.
All right, I'll go for it.
Let's go back during the day.
I wanna try to get the Toucan.
There's a Corgi.
Well, here, you have to give a little bit of credit though.
Do you really, how hard do you think it is eventually here
to create Pokemon for like the 15th generation
or whatever?
Oh shit, okay, we're gonna have like a little monkey.
We already have like five of those,
but have him have like a weird tail this time.
We have like 30 moths, but make this moth sing.
All right, where's this Toucan nest?
I think that guy's awake.
What the hell is that thing?
What is that thing?
What is that?
That's a rare.
That was a rare and I just didn't even get a picture of it.
Look at this guy.
What the hell is that thing?
That's a sock.
Oh, that's not its face.
That's not its face.
I thought it was like a big sock puppet.
Holy shit, he's right next to me.
Don't be concerned.
What's that?
That's the one they were giving away.
This is the one they were giving away for free, right?
During the, what was it, not E3.
That's a Wooper watch right there, yeah.
Okay, where's this Toucan?
I almost hit him.
Where's the Toucan nest?
Hey, go look at the Toucan nest.
Hmm, I don't see a Toucan nest.
Wait, okay, there's the Toucan.
What was I supposed to be filming here?
Whoa, can I get you jumping?
I wanna get you jumping off this.
He's gonna do a jump.
Jump?
Holy shit, did I get it?
What photo am I trying to get here?
What was I trying to get?
Oh, Snacky's right.
It is just a Toucan.
Yeah, it is.
You can have other animals in the universe.
I don't know why they all have to be Pokemon.
All right, Germamites, it's that time of the stream again.
Can we get a Wubba Lubba Dub Dub in the chat right now?
I hope so.
Yeah, because people are gonna really think you're funny
or you just got blocked.
I like 10,000 people.
Come on, Snacky's.
Come on, let me give me a Snacky's.
What about you?
Will you do a Snacky's?
Give me a Snacky's.
Here it comes, come on.
Oh, that's perfect, Snacky's.
That's gonna be perfect.
I want that one.
I still don't understand how this works.
Probably should have paid attention.
Eat?
What do you think?
Apple?
I don't get it.
Cats not like apples?
I guess not.
People forget that these Pokemon attack
could kill each other out in the wild.
That's what I was saying.
They're like cartoons.
They're not even animals.
Okay, what am I missing?
I'm not gonna replace that one.
I mean, that one's kind of funny.
This one even has the right animal.
That one's better, but yeah, we'll do this one.
Eh, how could that be possibly better?
I got the jumping one.
Oh, what?
That's not a three star?
I really thought, I really thought it was that.
Oh, it fooled me.
I'm a stupid animal.
That's what that thing is there for.
It's to scare other animals.
I fell for it, yeah.
None of these are as good.
That's a good one right there.
How's that one?
I'm gonna have to go with the good one though.
Actually, this one might be, this one's far better.
This is a three star, but it's not,
it's kind of off center.
This one's perfect.
We'll go with the, we'll go with the two.
No, it's not better.
Here we go.
Snackies!
Oh my God, perfect.
This is the one.
This is the one that's gonna get a thousand upvotes.
That one's good.
That one's better.
Okay, what did he want?
What was the actual, I don't know what he's,
what did he want?
He wanted this one, okay?
And then a crystal bloom.
Cool.
Cooking tacos while watching this?
How hot are they?
Are they gonna be hot?
Are they gonna be mild?
That determines if you get banned from the channel or not.
Let's find out.
That second photo's perfect.
They're gonna be fucking hot.
All right, good game.
Okay, two diamonds.
All right, here we go.
Is this one better?
Yes, it is.
Way better.
Yeah, and we're keeping this one.
And I mean permanently,
because that's the ultimate snackies photo.
Is that the one he wanted?
Didn't fulfill the request?
Level three.
You registered 10 species of normal type.
Okay, save photos to album.
It's in this one.
Where is it?
There it is.
Perfect.
Resnap.
Okay, what do I have of filters?
What the hell?
Can't improve perfection.
But you can.
I wanna put filters on it.
Maximum blur.
That like just hurts my head looking at this.
This hurts my head.
Too much blur, I don't like it.
Raid song.
Sing the raid song?
What happened?
I think there's a desktop background.
They get raided?
Who raided?
Where?
What are my last updates from seven days ago?
Where's the raid?
I can't see.
Who raided?
You get a raid?
Thank you.
Thank you for the raid.
Whoever it was, I can't see.
Why can I not see this?
I'm gonna go pee.
First break of the day.
I'm being trolled, okay.
All right, I'll be right back.
I'm gonna pee.
When I come back, we're gonna complete Snackies.
I'm gonna be the most famous Pokemon Snap Guy.
I'll be right back.
Okay, hello.
I have returned.
Let's come back.
Is it working?
Why can't I switch?
There we go, okay.
All right, I got that saved.
I have Snackies saved.
I'll be uploading that later.
Pissed off a 2K raid.
I didn't see anything.
I, who was it?
You missed the raid for real.
No, you're liars.
Nobody, there's nobody here.
Wait, was it actually a raid?
Are you guys fucking with me the whole time?
Hold on, I need to check.
Hold on, I gotta switch my inputs.
Let me see.
Are you guys messing with me here?
Oh my God, that was a raid.
It was a big one.
Oh my God, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, oh my God.
I thought everyone was fucking around.
It didn't pop up on my dashboard.
This is from Jess, Jess, Jessu.
Thank you for the 2,600 person raid.
If you still, I like went BRB.
I was just like, oh, you guys are full of shit.
And I took off.
Oh my God, that's, I'm sorry.
Well, thank you so much.
And Frans too, I got, I had a raid from Frans.
Thank you, I'm really sorry.
I thought I, people do that sometimes.
They're like, oh, hey raid, a raid's coming in.
You're getting raided.
Joe Biden raid, Joe Biden's raiding.
And I'm like, I've tuned it out by this point.
But thank you, welcome if you're still here
or if you just left, cause like I'm an asshole
and a raid came in and I just fucking said, nice joke.
Nobody raided and then went to the bathroom.
I look awful right now.
Can we just make, hey Mike, can I apologize
to the Jess, the Jess community?
Please, I'm sorry.
I did not mean to do that.
Anyways, welcome, how you doing?
Hope you had a good stream Jess.
I feel like awful right now.
I feel awful.
Okay, let's go back to it.
Taking pictures of money animals.
I know a lot of you here are waiting for Pac-Man
and I'm going to stall for a very long time.
Be aware of that.
What else was there?
In the tall grass, okay.
I think I heard a Pokemon crying around here,
but where is it coming from?
Okay, somewhere in with all of the flowers.
In the day, right?
Yeah.
Upload the Snackies picture.
I will.
Apology song or it's over.
What's over?
Apology song.
I'm sorry.
At your bottom dollar that I'm sorry.
Will be.
The sun will come out tomorrow.
At your bottom dollar that tomorrow.
Tomorrow, tomorrow.
Smile at me.
Tomorrow.
You're only a day away.
That wasn't even a,
that wasn't a modern apology song.
I just sang you a song from Annie.
No, no, don't do it.
Don't do it.
Oh my God, I'm going to do it.
Ew.
No.
Don't do it.
I don't know.
Just go back to what I was doing.
I went that tall grass.
There was kind of a lightsaber in that room.
Yeah, I do got a lightsaber in this room.
You want to fuck with me?
Huh?
Oh, what's that?
Oh, excuse me.
He's got a lightsaber in his room, don't he?
Don't fuck with me.
I'm supposed to, I gotta take a picture of something.
Holy shit, I look like I fucking live under the bridge.
Put this down.
Get that fucking saber out of here.
All right, where's that tall grass?
There's something crying, it said.
All right, here's the tall grass.
There's something crying over here.
Anybody hear anything crying?
Ah, it's you.
No, it's not.
Who's crying?
Tall grass, something crying right here.
You?
Are you crying?
I don't think that bird is crying.
Who's crying?
No, please, why, why, why?
What happened?
Whoa, I can throw that?
I didn't know I could do that.
I got it.
I heard.
What was crying?
Somebody said, you look like Dumb and Dumber together.
Like fused together.
Like Jeff Daniels and Jim Carrey.
You look like a weatherman.
Okay, I gotta stop it.
Hey, I know there are plenty of,
there are plenty of very handsome weathermen.
I like that one, it's cute.
You look like a Dutch Renaissance artist.
Roll out the mustache.
You know, I only, I only have this
because I wanted to turn the webcam on
and scare everybody.
Everybody likes it, but keep it?
Keep it.
I hate it.
I don't like it.
Keep it, yes.
Go a whole month doing it.
You went from looking 25 to 65.
Keep it, keep it.
All right, well, I apparently messed up.
It's a disgustingly handsome mustache.
Okay, so let me,
I just repeated what she just said, but still.
Stick thieves caught on cam.
Shit, the meta is changing very quickly,
hourly, on an hourly basis.
It was snacks.
Now it's LOL.
Look what my ring camera picked up.
I'm falling behind.
I need to be on top of this shit.
I need to make a new trend.
This one's cool too, this one's awesome.
I'm running off of old meta.
Okay, photo decks.
No, where is it?
It's my folder, right?
I'm literally about to bite somebody.
Settle down, sit down.
What's wrong with you?
Album, okay.
Maybe you can view photos you've saved
after your research trips,
including edited photos and re-snaps.
All right, there's Snackies.
Snackies.
And now I upload this.
All right, does this like,
this doesn't like,
what do you see like my fucking like,
I don't know.
I don't even see my account name.
Read the precautions from the internet.
What are you talking about?
Read the internet precautions.
Please avoid posting inappropriate content
so that everyone can enjoy this feature.
Inappropriate content can be reported.
Please refrain from making false reports.
What's going on?
All right, I wanna,
yeah, I'm really glad I didn't show this
because it shows like my fucking,
like my friend code up here.
I don't want people to have that.
There, Snackies.
Okay, I did it.
I got it.
It's there.
He doesn't want us as friends.
No, I don't.
I don't.
I don't want to be incessantly spammed
with 5,000 friend requests
every time I turn on my fucking Nintendo Switch.
I'm sorry, but that's the fact.
That's the truth.
Mustache changed you.
What the fuck do you know about anything?
Excuse me.
Uh-oh, here comes the evil arc.
You know what happens when somebody has a mustache.
Turn fucking evil.
All right, in the tall grass,
I'm gonna get this one.
The mask comes off, huh?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
He was sus before and now he's evil.
Is it weird that I have these strange,
nightmarish type dreams being invited
to a Twitch panel of some kind?
Or an e-clown thing where I'm one of the panelists
and underneath my nameplate, it says Jerma985
and then there's a lower thirds graphics come up
that says the sus guy and it has like that face.
That's like why I got invited.
And I have to, I have a microphone in front of me
and five to 10 times during the Q&A section,
somebody comes up to like ask a question.
They go, this one's for Jerma.
I lean in, yeah, what's up, man?
Hey, what do you think about this like red trash can?
Don't you think it looks a little sus?
And then I like have to smile and go.
And everybody in the audience like claps and shit and laughs.
I don't want that to happen to me.
Grass is coming up.
That's too late, it's inevitable.
Whoa, that was cool, do that again.
Hello, do that again.
How about do it again?
What did I get wrong here?
I'm over the two cannon, right?
All grass, I feel bad for Jerma in that regard.
Wait, shiny, all right, here we go again.
So there's something crying.
I need to like activate this thing
and find the thing that's crying.
It's like bullet drop with this shit, come on.
Somebody's crying here.
Who's crying?
I don't see anybody crying in the tree.
I don't, hello, somebody crying?
Nobody here, what the hell?
In the tall grass, yeah,
but isn't this where the photo was?
It's one of these peaky pecks, it has to be.
Well, I'm just gonna skip this one
because I don't get it.
We are all crying, crying, call us.
None of these are bad, I just, no.
I'm not showing any photos.
It's a kid's game, how do you not get it?
Yeah, and Tic-Tac-Toe is also a kid's game.
And you get your ass kicked in that one too,
don't you, all the time.
You gotta use the zoom function.
No, don't, thank you, the one chatter.
Sudden movement, okay.
I saw tan growth suddenly move in the most amazing way.
I already have one of these pictures.
All right, we're going to take that photo.
Tan growth is a solution to never lose Tic-Tac-Toe.
Yeah, but then that makes you,
that makes you, oh, yeah, shush, shush, shush, shush.
That makes you an asshole.
No one wants to play Tic-Tac-Toe with you
if you're gonna do that.
Those are cool.
Okay, there it is.
Now wake up and do the thing.
Did I miss it?
Jump, jump, jump, jump.
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Oh, there was something else too.
That's a good one.
And that's new.
No, it's not.
All right, let's activate this.
Wake up.
You're losing viewers.
What are you gonna do to make people stay?
I don't know.
Nothing.
All right, there's somebody sleeping over here
that's not supposed to be sleeping over here, right?
Wait, there's the Dorito.
There's the Dorito bird.
That was really cool.
I wish I took a picture of it.
Wait, what do I have to do with the Pidgeotto?
What do I do?
Oh, feet, apples.
He likes to eat.
He's gonna warm up to me, right?
Look this way and be happy.
I sort of meow.
What was that?
The Magikarp's dying.
Looks like the Beedoof have finished building their dam.
Oh my God, that's so cute.
It's you.
You're the one that's not supposed to,
you're the cute one that's not sleeping, right?
Holy shit, that's a rare Pokemon.
Oh, this is where we get the bird foot.
Get it.
Why is my arm so weak?
Got it, right?
That's what I needed, right?
What's that thing?
Oh, where do I go?
What was that?
Something's moving in the flowers.
Holy shit.
That's perfect shot.
These things are so dull.
They don't like do anything.
They don't move.
Like come here.
You guys are kind of dull.
They're just bees.
They're kind of a dull Pokemon.
Dull.
Oh, nice.
Okay, I got the Smash Brothers side bee.
Which one's the best?
Probably that one.
Two or yeah, that one.
I didn't get it.
I missed it somehow.
I don't know how I missed it.
Don't ask me.
This is so stupid.
I'm gonna do this one.
That looks like the battle bus.
Battle.
Oh no, you said battle pass.
I was like, what's a battle bus?
All right, what's the one that I need?
That one?
I think it's this one, right?
You literally know what the battle bus is.
Ooh.
Which one?
Probably that one.
Shit.
I kind of have to go with this one.
This is the foot one.
Do I have twos?
I have twos and I have a one.
All right, this is a three and a four.
This one, definitely.
Without a doubt.
I like this one better.
Who was sleeping?
Did I get the one?
All right.
This one's sleeping.
Let's go.
Oh, Pac-Man, he's crying.
Well, he can cry until I play the game.
It's coming up soon, I don't know.
That's all, I'm just hanging out.
Stop taking photos, you peeked at snackies.
I don't think, yeah, I didn't get the thing.
Nice.
Nice work.
That's pretty good.
This is a bad picture, but I think it's what he wanted.
That's a good one.
This should be diamond, right?
Yep.
Your photos are swag.
Thanks.
I'll get a Pokemon bonus for this.
What's with the placement?
Why was that so good?
This is a better picture though.
Whatever.
That's gonna be really good.
Placement is perfect.
That's diamond.
No.
Whatever.
Better than what I had.
What?
Well, I have to keep this one because he wants this one.
Why do I not have one single photo of this guy?
For one star.
I feel like I take 30 pictures of that guy.
Oh shit.
I love this one on the right.
The guy going, yes.
Why do you play baby games?
Because they're really easy
and I don't have to think too hard.
That's why.
Well, because it's really simple
and I don't have to think that much.
That's a professor's favorite.
What a great photo.
I'll go ahead and upload it as my new favorite.
What do you mean you gotta upload that?
No, that's my photo.
You're not gonna take it and upload it on your account?
I'm, that's, and you put like your signature on it.
He stamped it as his.
All right, I've uploaded the photo.
Go to the internet and check your page.
What?
I didn't want you to do that.
Reddit him.
He's gonna sell it as an NFT.
You got a total of one sweet medal.
Oh!
Somebody sweeted my picture.
Combi are very devoted to Vespiquen.
If you observe them closely,
you see that these Pokemon do more than just gather nectar.
It all happened here.
This is, I want this.
Why can't I, I want these filters.
I want this filter.
I want that.
How come I don't have those?
I would do so much better work.
All right, I can go here at night.
That's a hit.
Wait, didn't I take this picture?
I took this photo.
I took that photo.
I heard a really loud noise and it got me wondering,
do you think Arbok ever falls out of its tree
while it's sleeping?
I have to pay attention to that.
All right, what was this one?
I already, I took this picture.
Didn't I get this?
I see Pic, I see Pikipek flying near Toucanon's nest.
What do you suppose they're up to?
I didn't I get, I already got a photo of this.
All right, we're looking for the big snake
falling out of the tree.
What time of day is that?
Day, it's daytime.
All right, we're looking for the snake
falling out of the tree.
Snake falling out of the tree.
I don't care about anybody else, just the snake.
Where is he?
All's out of the tree.
All right, that he's right there.
He didn't fall out of a tree.
He's literally right here.
That was a nighttime mission.
He's so baked.
I don't know, somebody,
somebody pasted something and it was gone instantly.
I have no idea what you said.
It was probably a copy pasta.
Jungle at night, looking for the snake
falling out of the tree.
Go check Professor Mirror's hard drive.
Why?
Apple?
All right, where is he?
Oh, there he is.
Does he fall out of the tree?
I don't think, he does not fall out of the tree.
Okay, come on, bun sweets.
I have painful stinging blisters
from walking four miles in flip-flops today.
What are you thinking?
What were you thinking?
You know the maximum amount of walking time
you should do with flip-flops
is either slipping them on and off
to go to where the sand is at the beach
and maybe walk up on the boardwalk somewhere for a little bit
or in the amount of time it takes
to go get your mail from the mailbox.
How would you do that for four hours?
I'm surprised, you know what?
Frankly, I'm surprised you're still alive.
Someone's sleeping down here, too.
What if it was a really long driveway?
All right, why is it missing something else here?
I got it, I got the snake.
Something's gonna come out of that ruined door.
Right, it has to be.
Something in there.
An electric eel is gonna come out
when I put something in there, right?
You know when an electric eel puts its head out
and has that weird like, bleh.
They always come out of holes like that.
Where is everybody?
Where's that sound?
I miss that every time.
Oh, that's that guy's photo.
Wait, what's this?
Who is that?
Somebody over there.
Who's acting?
Oh, it's a woofer.
You like apples?
No, he doesn't like me anymore.
He's pissed.
What are you still doing awake, woofer?
All right, I think I got the photo I needed here.
Family guy waiting room.
Stop zooming in.
I get the tool tip that says zoom in more frequently.
I'm doing what the game is telling me to do.
What Pokemon would taste the best?
I don't know, one of the birds?
Whatever the one is the closest resembling a chicken.
How do I get these guys to be two?
I think we'll compare to that photo.
What the hell?
I mean, that's clearly what he was looking for.
This isn't better, no.
You have to knock him out of the tree.
I threw a few apples at him, it didn't do anything.
Ah, this is a woofer.
That's a good photo, but wait a minute.
Look at this one.
Oh, it's this one.
Throw more apples.
Ancient ruins.
Code on your profile is for this game,
not your Switch friend code, you adult.
Oh, well.
I always wanted to eat a Pokemon, why?
Oh, I don't understand why.
I didn't see my message, I saw that one.
Let us see the profile so we can upvote everything.
No, I'm not gonna game the system
and have my stuff get upvoted.
That's, you're probably gonna get my account banned.
You wanna like brigade my profile?
You're gonna get me thrown off of the Pokemon Snap forums.
How am I still level one here?
All right, there we go, present.
Snapped a total of 500 photos.
Am I insane or is he just replaying
two levels over and over?
I mean, that's what I have unlocked now.
Be too popular to play games publicly.
No, I'm not.
Okay, who needs wings?
I just heard Dodrio can fly, never seen one.
Okay, that's near the end where the owl is.
And then go find what motivates the combies to work.
That's all the requests I have for here?
Oh, what about complete?
I haven't even been completing quests.
Are you kidding me?
Design 13.
Oh, that's how you get, all right, I get it.
Completed, what else do I get?
Ooh, it's an effect.
Now I can start actually making cool things.
Complete, making a splash.
Oh, I forgot the wooden dog toy, that's right.
I'll go get it after, before I play Pac-Man.
All right, is this all I have during the night?
All right, we gotta take a picture of the Dodrio flying.
Remember, look at the joke tracker right now.
Market's closed.
Whoa, oh right, I gotta get him doing this.
Gotta get him jumping in the air.
He goes, whoa, and he jumps up.
Hey, what?
What the hell was that?
That was bizarre, that was weird.
Why did he do that?
Can he jump again?
Jump, fine, whatever.
All right, I need the Dodrio flying right into the owl.
A lot of them, what was that?
That's like a weird planet or something.
What is that?
It's a person on a parachute.
That's somebody on a parachute.
What is that?
This pink thing, see that?
Did I miss him flying?
I think I did.
Does that count?
I think does that count as flying?
How did the stream reach negative 5,000?
Because people are just spamming it.
Let me eat these, let me eat these.
That was good, that was good too.
He's gonna fly right over here
and I'm gonna get it, one, two, three.
All right, Dodrio flying, here he comes.
What's the best Star Wars?
Empire Strikes Back.
I'm actually returning the Jedi guy.
My favorite of all the movies
because Mark Hamill looks like a stage hand
to the whole movie, my favorite.
When does he fly?
This is it, ready?
Shit, where is he?
There he is, I got it, right?
Light it up, something is motivating them.
What's motivating them?
You, you fly at the end?
I think I got it.
Jumping counts, good.
All right, I got it then.
I think I completed like three quests here.
Stupid, stupid.
I think this, I mean, it just looks weird.
I don't know, I guess this one's better.
Cell, cell, that's a good one here.
Okay, Dodrio flying.
This one is, it's probably this one.
Is he Yoto?
Which one did he, which one did he want?
I think it's this one, right?
That one, it's this one.
Swanna, Sir?
Okay, Kombi, sure, that one.
I guess I'll take that one.
Somebody said pick pictures every time,
even if you don't need them.
Because I'm losing out on experience.
Just as free EXP.
Do an ASMR of you telling us
comforting things like I'm proud of you, okay?
Ahem.
I am so goddamn proud of you.
Look what you've done.
Look what you've been able to accomplish.
Take a look outside.
See that sun up there?
It's shining down on you.
Go for it.
Do it.
You know you can.
Good luck.
I almost just leaned in and went.
That would have been really bad.
There you go, there you go.
Where's my money?
All right, Buffle Ant, that's a good Buffle Ant.
That was a sarcastic voice.
Wasn't?
There's the request.
Ooh, I've completed his page.
What's that mean?
3,500.
It's new.
Get it in there.
Okay, there's the flying Dodrio.
Dodrio's now complete.
Plus two JRM to the moon.
Better photo.
Why, what the fuck?
Why is that one so much better?
What?
Because I guess he's powering up.
Mom said it's my turn on the Xbox.
Go play it.
It's in the other room.
I'm on the Switch.
Can you not differentiate the two consoles?
I can't help you, little bro.
It's a better picture.
This chat is omega fucked right now.
Okay, now let me get my presents.
Hey, little bro.
A movement?
That's a really bad picture.
This is more Apple than it is guy jumping.
Ooh, hey, this one.
Awesome.
You got a profile icon, Rita.
I gotta go back here, right?
Okay, when, what was his name, Magnum?
When Magnum gets to the spot,
starts looking around restlessly.
Okay, that tree is looking for a friend.
That's cool.
Magnum.
Oh, I dropped my Magnum condom for my monster dong.
Or is it the other way around?
Oh, I dropped my monster condom for my Magnum dong.
It's that one.
I did it the wrong way.
Okay, I need to get this big dragon thing.
I said, I did it the wrong?
What's that?
Oh my God, it's an Eevee.
Whoa.
Oh.
I can't believe I just got a picture of an Eevee.
It's, it's, it's.
Everyone's.
Oh my God, I can't believe I got a picture of Eevee.
That's my- Everyone's.
Favorite Pokemon.
Okay, so hold on now.
When he gets to this tree, he's looking for a friend.
Did it do anything else?
Eevee is God tier.
Always have an Eevee in your party.
Eevee is, Eevee is air type, water type, ground type,
and has two earth attacks.
Okay, so where's the friend?
Here comes a friend.
We're looking for the friend.
Okay, where's the friend?
You see a friend?
He's waiting for a friend right here.
He's looking for a friend right here,
in front of this tree, behind you.
No, no, no, no.
They came from behind.
All right, let's go attack.
Oh, there go all of my helicopters.
They came from, they came from,
they came, they came from, they came from behind.
I think it was Eevee, I got it.
They came from, they came from, from behind, behind.
They came from-
Remember, your high is fucked today.
Go, go complain about it.
Go complain about it then.
Go complain about it.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
That was the mustache talking.
That's the mustache is taking it out, is making me do that.
It's probably just be, which one?
This one?
I don't know which one is the best one.
Probably the jumping one.
Probably this one.
I can't replace that one.
That one's too good.
Oh, wait, okay, here we go.
Ooh, perfect, that one's better.
This one's good.
This one right here.
Why is your shot composition so shitty?
I didn't know I was in film school.
Nice work.
This is good EXP.
It's 5,400.
Sustache.
Funny, Jeremy used to be a wedding photographer.
Um, I'm sorry.
I think there's something a little different
with holding a camera and filming people
than holding two Joy-Con switch controllers
that don't, you don't have any manual zoom.
I don't have an ISO.
I don't have an f-stop.
And taking pictures of like cartoon animals
that jump out behind trees and shit.
This is a little different.
I guarantee you, if you gave this game to Martin Scorsese,
he would take like four of these like shitty pictures
and be like, what the fuck is this?
What is this game?
This is cute.
I'm gonna go on to make million dollar pictures.
I get to enjoy it.
Now, you think he'd care?
Somebody just said, just say it's too hard.
It's too hard.
I didn't get anything.
How is that not the friend?
I don't understand.
Do I not get it?
Yeah.
When Magnum gets to the spot,
it starts looking around kind of restlessly.
Do you think it's looking for one of its friends?
Isn't Eevee just running around?
Otto's wood toy.
I know, I'm gonna get it before I play Pac-Man.
I'm gonna get it.
You'll see it, don't worry.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Okay, now wait till he gets here.
Does the Plato dinosaur like apples?
No, not really.
Let's fucking go.
Viewers are gonna drop if you switch to Pac-Man.
Remember that.
Whatever.
Whoa, look, look.
I got them.
That's what he was looking for.
Dude, I am getting way too excited over
the back of a cereal box.
You know what I mean?
I'm getting way too excited about this.
I turned 36 this year.
He's looking.
What's he looking for?
It's all eyes on him.
As long as you're having fun, it's all right.
Yeah, I know.
That's too excited.
Okay, here we go.
Where is this friend that's apparently over here?
Is he gonna get here?
Is he gonna look around?
I don't see anybody.
There's nobody here.
You missed it?
It's this tree right here.
It's this one.
There's nothing here.
How do I like my steak cooked?
I like my steak cooked.
However, the chef wants to prepare it.
Unless, of course, that's medium rare.
I listen for it.
I usually say, oh, however the chef likes it.
And they go, oh, medium rare?
And I go, no, no, thank you.
Medium, please, medium well.
I'm gonna tell you guys something.
A lot of you don't wanna hear this.
Yeah, you guys talk like, okay, boomer,
like you're a boomer, boomer shit.
Caring about how cooked your steak is
is such a boomer thing to care about.
That's quite a boomer thing to care about.
Whoa, why is this four?
I'm gonna use this one.
I like that.
Which one, one or two?
One or two.
Probably two.
Caring that somebody likes their steak medium
versus medium rare.
I could see like a big fat boomer guy at a grill
scoffing at the fact that I said that.
Hey, how do you want your burger?
Medium, please.
Okay, you fucking young millennial.
Oh, I love medium, medium well.
Sure thing, you want avocado on it too?
That's a boomer thing to care about.
That's cute, I like that one.
The boomers were right.
I have two of the same picture.
Different versions of that emo.
Am I gonna have them all be this?
This one's better, there's more friends.
You mean judging someone?
No, judging somebody on their,
how they eat their hamburger
on the temperature of the meat.
And I don't want to get any foodborne illnesses.
You know what happens if you don't cook fucking red meat
all the way through?
You like your bloody steak,
you like your bloody hamburger
with fucking red blood coming out of it?
Be careful, you're a weakling.
Myoglobulin, not blood.
Okay, look, I can make up a Pokemon name for stuff too.
Mods, please help, Grandpa's shouting at me again.
I have to get this one, this is one of,
I have to get a new zone, what's happening?
I need to get to level two, okay,
I'll get to level two right here.
Level two night, let's go.
Caring about steak is Joe Rogan shit.
I don't even know what you mean by that,
but I don't know, somehow I do.
I don't know what that even means,
but I kind of knew it, I know what it means.
It's weird, right?
I don't really even know what that means.
You've had elk meat, no, I have not.
I've not had venison, I've not had elk.
I keep, I don't want to take any pictures of the spider.
What was that?
All right, get a bunch of good photos.
I just need to level up.
How do you want your Fortnite burger?
Are you a juicy or dry kind of guy?
I'd say probably more in the juicy department.
I don't like it wet though,
because then it ruins the bun.
Everybody that wants like a bloody hamburger,
it ruins the bun.
The bun gets seeped in with this pink liquid
that turns it, it's soppy and gross.
I really mean this,
and I might gross somebody out here, but whatever.
I would prefer if you were to,
let me just get a photo here.
I would prefer it if you were to burn my hamburger.
I mean, like unrecognizable.
It's like char, it's not even meat anymore,
than eat a rare hamburger.
I would rather you leave it on to a point where like,
you could, like we're talking about burn,
like light it on fire and let it sit there.
I'm talking about like the skin on the marshmallow
when you let it just go in there
and let this just sit in the campfire.
And that's what I'm talking about.
I'd rather eat that than a rare steak.
I have not taken any pictures.
I'm supposed to take photos.
Burger, yes, steak, no.
Nope, both.
If you brought a rare steak to me,
I don't care how nice of a restaurant it is.
This could be like a $300 plate.
The finest cut of meat, rare.
I would order something from the kids menu.
I'd be like, can I just get like the fucking hot dog,
the mac and cheese and corn?
I don't want that.
I would not eat a rare steak.
I just don't like it.
I will eat sushi sometimes on very rare occasions,
but there's something about that raw red meat.
I cannot do it.
Unbased as fuck, my dude, just for your information.
Heresites are a myth.
What?
Would you ever go vegetarian?
No, I like the taste of chicken too much.
I love a good steak and cheese sandwich.
I could never give it up.
Not in a hundred million years.
I couldn't, I just couldn't do it.
Now, they're getting close.
They're getting close.
Like the Beyond meat stuff, the Impossible Burger stuff,
I think Beyond tastes a little better.
I think Beyond's a better product,
if I have to be honest with you.
They might get there soon.
Like I'm gonna give it probably like 10 years.
10 more years, I think they're gonna get it.
They'll figure out the chemical composition
to make it so you're eating meat,
but you're not even eating it.
They'll get it.
Maybe like 10, maybe 20.
This one is probably the best.
I'm just looking for experience.
I did not just say that I think that Beyond burgers
are better than real meat.
I didn't say that.
I said they're getting close
and they might be there in 10 to 20 years,
which they probably will be.
I mean that experience.
Did you say that Beyond was better than Impossible?
Yes.
And do you know that I'm not making this up?
You know that I'm telling you the truth
because I lost a shitload of money
buying puts on Beyond Meat,
like four and a half years ago
when they went into like IPO.
You know that I'm not bullshitting you here.
We all know that story.
So like I think it's a better product than Impossible.
Buying puts, Omega Low.
This was like four years ago.
This wasn't like last weekend.
I just didn't think that Beyond Meat
should have the valuation of like all the airlines
and every car company in America.
I'm sorry.
I just, it was crazy.
It was insane.
He shorted Beyond Meat, Omega.
Yeah, I did.
I, I, you know that.
I've been very transparent about that.
Back when it first came out,
it went up to like almost $300 a share.
And I was like, this is, what the hell is this?
And I got burned real bad.
And I, you know what they say?
You may have learned your lesson.
Remember you're wasting our sub money.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
That was actually YouTube money.
That was before I made anything on Twitch.
That was back in like 2015, 2016.
That wasn't Twitch money.
That was YouTube money.
Wasn't your, that wasn't what you guys, come on.
Six years ago.
Whatever it was, I don't know.
Yeah.
It also was not very much.
A lot of you guys are somehow assuming that I put like,
like $500 million on like a short on Beyond Meat.
No, that's, I wasn't, it was not even,
it was not, I was not very much money at all.
How do you like your eggs?
I like them over medium.
Not over easy.
They get all over the plate
and it ruins everything else that's on the plate.
If you have bacon, toast, ash browns, eggs,
and they're over easy, it just gets everywhere.
And then it gets all over your bacon,
all over your toast, all over your potatoes.
I want it to be separated.
I like a jammy yolk.
Doesn't get everywhere and it's good.
It's absolutely false.
No, it's not.
All right, I want, let me just beat this.
Over medium.
I want good pictures.
You don't even eat.
That's the whole point.
Yeah, maybe for you,
I like to have all my stuff separated.
There's one, I will make one exception.
What's that?
Is that a spider?
Ooh, that is a spider.
The only exception I make is corned beef hash.
So if you have corned beef hash
and you drop an over easy egg on top of it,
you let it sit on top and you break the yolk,
it gets really kind of,
you have to lay the egg right on top of the corned beef hash.
That's the only exception where I'll have an over easy egg.
And then it gets in there, but that's the point.
That was done intentionally.
It was done intentionally.
Having just regular over easy eggs,
unintentionally you get your shit everywhere.
I don't like that.
I need somebody to do something else.
I need an animal to do something.
These things are cute, I guess,
but I need you to do something cool.
Eat, eat that.
Good one, that's a good pick.
What's your favorite rom-com?
Is it you've got mail?
Got it.
You can do a little dance if you take pictures of me.
Okay.
I keep fucking missing those toucans.
I know, I was waiting for it to go.
I'm gonna restart.
You like Among Us?
No, no, I don't.
You know why I don't like Among Us?
Because I can't give you an opinion
if I do or don't like it.
I can't tell you because I've never played it.
Wait for the jump.
Got it.
Next game, please.
You've been playing the same level.
Yeah, that's Pokemon Snap.
I'm playing Pac-Man and like, I don't know.
I wanna take a picture of the woofer.
Eat that woofer, come on.
Eat it, please.
No, he's gonna be mad at me.
Pokemon Snap in real life.
I wanna do a bird watching stream if that counts.
That's a pretty cute photo.
I'm like eating the apple.
The apple's in his mouth.
And I wanted to have binoculars that had cameras in them.
So you could see what I see when I hold binoculars up.
It's like two, it's two cameras.
Go to a petting zoo.
What was it?
You're sweet.
Hope you have a good bird watching stream.
Oh, thank you.
That's a really nice of you to say.
Thank you.
All right, I got a three here.
Which is the best one in the, probably that one?
No, I mean, this is a horrible picture,
but it's definitely gonna be this one.
This is also a three.
The one I took originally is so much better,
but we'll do that one.
I have a new woofer.
I do, really?
Hmm.
Okay, that one's good.
All right, this should bring me to another level.
I urge people to dress up in bird costumes
and climb up the trees and act like they're real.
Nice work.
I mean, that's really funny.
But I would be putting somebody's life in danger
by having them have to go up in a really tall,
like 150 foot tall tree.
The thought is funny,
but I don't think anyone's gonna do that.
Nice work.
All right, did I finally level up?
Finally.
Yeah, this is definitely a level up.
It has to be.
That's a new one.
This is worse than Pokemon Go?
Well, I mean, the whole point of,
you don't battle, oh, I love snackies.
Level two, come on.
There we go.
All right, level two.
Open up a new zone.
By the way, thanks to the progress you made,
I've got something to report.
Here we are.
This game is good, if not greater than Pokemon Go.
People have been waiting, hold on.
Ha ha.
I can do it too.
Yeah, we got new islands.
One on this long, narrow island
and another offshore in the middle of the water.
What happened?
Never got to that spot offshore, did he?
This is gonna be amazing.
I'll let you decide what order you want to visit them in,
keep up the good work.
Why are you such a food snob, but you drink Huel, Omega Lo?
I'm not ordering Huel at a restaurant.
It would be very bizarre, now wouldn't it?
Free-dwelling Pokemon.
When that huge tree lit up,
I saw a bunch of Pokemon fly out of it,
but I couldn't tell what kind of Pokemon they were.
I took that one too.
Did I take this one?
No, that's not even mine.
All right, new zone.
How's it going?
Enjoying your research jaunts?
Listen, I've got to tell you something.
There's a feature I originally forgot
to suggest to the professor.
But I got him to add it to your research camera.
It's a melody player.
It lets your camera play a little tune.
A little magical tune can prompt Pokemon
to show you whole new sides of themselves.
Sounds awesome.
Could you fill in the details?
Sure thing.
If you press R, a melody will play.
Medium well Huel.
I left it in the sun for an hour.
While it's playing, you can press R again to make it stop.
A little music could wake up sleeping Pokemon.
Ooh, the Peter Griffin character.
I want to go use it on.
Or make some Pokemon get up and dance.
I haven't had a chance to try it though,
so I'm no expert yet.
Next, let's give it a whirl.
The game just opened wide up.
First, let me go use this on Peter Griffin.
Where was he?
Where was Peter Griffin?
Jungle?
Where was Peter Griffin here?
What was the jungle during the day?
See if we can get him to dance.
Oh, play the tune.
Dance, I want to dance.
This better work on Peter Griffin.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
He hates it.
Okay.
All right, Peter, get up.
Really?
What?
That's stupid, why does he not get up?
I hear Bugleberry.
He's scared of the snake.
Ooh, you gonna dance?
I think this is a prank.
He's dancing?
He just looked like Stuart Griffin.
He just did.
It looks like it's Stuart Griffin in a costume.
It sounds like an ice cream truck, it kind of does.
Wooden dog toy now.
Just wait until I go to Pac-Man.
Did I get it?
That was cool.
Oh, hold on.
I need to do this.
Come on, I have to get it.
Did I get him?
I got it.
Hold on, does he come back?
Did I get it?
Oh, what's he got?
He's got something.
That little guy had something, what was that?
He had like a little sack.
I don't think this does anything.
Oh brother, this guy stinks.
Wait, look at them walking together.
Did I get him jumping?
That was cool.
Okay, he's gonna do his jump now.
Oh, snackies.
Okay, I think I got it.
I wanna go to the new area
and then I'll play Pac-Man, I promise.
I wanna see the new two new areas
and then I'm gonna play, get a few photos of each area.
Then I'm going to go,
go get the wooden toy to smell it in front of you.
Then I'm gonna play Pac-Man 99.
This is awful.
I hated every second of it.
Oh, that's new when he's rolling around, okay.
What's the best one?
It's the only one you can see.
I like the angry one.
God damn it, I want Peter Griffin to turn around so bad.
This one's cute.
Yeah, look at that.
That's so cute.
I like that one.
I like, I like this one over here.
Oh, these are awful.
This one.
And that one.
Analyze it, please.
I'm gonna do a three hour BRB.
How would I go BRB for three hours, I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean when I said you stink.
Hold, diamond.
Do a coloring stream?
Like a coloring book.
I already did that.
Didn't everybody hate that?
I did like a coloring book stream
and everybody hated it, did I?
No, that was, no, no, no, no, I didn't.
I did like the,
no, everybody loved the highlights stream.
I didn't do a coloring book, I did like an activity book.
Everybody loved that stream, that was a lot of fun.
Now that was the card game stream.
That's the worst stream I've ever done.
The unlocked stream is the worst stream I've ever done.
I would argue that you could not convince me otherwise.
You couldn't even read the text.
My webcam is so bad.
And it was just not even interesting at all.
It was very painfully uninteresting.
Karazhan stream, at least the Karazhan stream was funny
because I was getting shit on for like 12 hours.
The unlock card stream was not funny.
It was awful.
No, the wow stream was not worse
than the unlock card game stream.
After force was the worst.
No, it was not.
I had a lot of fun on that stream.
I love that game.
I disagree.
All right, new zone.
I get to level three, almost.
All right, I want to see the new zone.
More of the rocks was weird.
It was, wasn't it?
First stream yet.
Ooh, this is in the desert.
Check this place out.
I just want to check out the two new zones
and then I'm going to go take a break.
Get the wood and then we'll play Pac-Man 99 for a while.
We got new shit.
Do you not like that?
There's just new stuff everywhere.
This is awesome.
Some tracks left by a small Pokemon.
What is that?
You eat?
Whoa, what are you doing, dude?
Come here.
You dance?
That's a good picture.
Shit, why would I take the camera away?
What am I, stupid?
That was cool.
Okay, I'll be honest.
I feel like I'm playing Five Nights at Freddy's.
I feel like I'm just changing and I have to do this.
I have to wind up the toy.
I have to go over here, take a photo, go to this one.
That was cool.
That was a good one.
I don't know, I can't.
Remember, you need to reload the gun.
This place is really open.
There's not a lot of places to hide.
Am I going up in a tornado?
Oh, no, no, no, okay.
I thought I was getting sucked up.
So cute.
Did I get it?
I think so.
You want to eat?
Eat that.
Whoa, he burns it.
Ice cream truck.
You know, I watched a video not that long ago
of an ice cream truck dog compilation
with dogs just get in line
and like eat ice cream with the ice cream truck.
It was really cute.
Link it.
I can't link it.
I don't know where it even is.
How sad is your life that you'll watch that?
What?
It's just a cute video.
What the fuck?
What are you talking about?
I felt like, what?
If I'm like in a doctor's office waiting room or something,
I don't stay away from those like dog ice cream videos.
He's pissed.
Oh, he's going to eat.
You're not too mad to like not eat.
You can turn quickly with the D pad.
Oh, well, that's about five hours worth of gameplay
that I did not play correctly.
That was cool.
I like that area.
This is probably the best one.
Pacing the apple, eating the apple.
No, definitely the happy one.
I like that one.
There's one where he's right in the camera.
Hmm, that one.
Oh, this is a Vivillon.
It's a different version.
I didn't get a picture of it.
Ooh, that one.
And the one when he's opening the mouth.
That one's good too though.
I don't know, that one looks like Bowser.
I'm going to say this one.
No, this one.
All right, go.
I wish I could see high resolution versions of them
before I pick them.
You pick kind of like a shitty version
before you get to see what it actually looks like.
I like that one.
What's a perfect score?
What do you know?
6,000, 7,000?
Like 1,000, toilet, thank you.
No, it's not.
That was wrong.
It's like 6,000.
6K is perfect.
I hate the original.
This is a boring baby game.
Please play Escape from Tarkov.
I would rather eat a rare steak
than play Escape from Tarkov.
You guys, who were the naysayers that said
that this was not a good photo?
That's a, I got diamonds.
Poor chick.
What's wrong with Escape from Tarkov?
Nothing.
Just don't want to play it.
If you presented me two options,
you have to either play Tarkov for an hour
or eat a rare steak.
I would eat the steak on camera right now.
I have nothing against Tarkov.
I just don't, I just do not want to play that.
I don't want to play that right now.
All right, what's the other place?
I think you're a really bad streamer.
You're terrible.
I hate you.
You're boring and lame and dumb and bad.
Not funny.
I went to middle school with you.
You were cool then, but not now.
I peaked at middle school.
How do you peak in middle school?
I don't understand that.
This is the beach.
Ooh, I like this place.
Ooh, I really like this place.
Like apples?
He's got boxing gloves.
Do something weird.
I don't know why that,
this looks like Patrick on drugs.
This is like crack Patrick.
I don't know why I think that.
I don't know why I'm seeing that.
What is that?
What the hell is that thing?
Whoa.
Oh my God.
Sounds like you're the one that's on crack.
I can do it if I try hard enough.
It's kind of moving.
You don't have that much depth.
What are you talking about?
I never do that again?
I'm going to at least a hundred more times
before my career ends.
Hey, if my career ends tomorrow,
if my career ended tomorrow,
I would upload a Twitter video
of me doing that a hundred times.
He's holding up middle fingers.
These things are cute.
How do you say this?
Piu-ku, Piu-ku-mu-ku.
Piu-ku-mu-ku?
You're going to fight over the,
what the hell?
That was weird.
That wasn't bad.
Or Sola?
You like apples.
All right.
Now you're going to do a funny little dance.
I don't know why I feel like it's going to take off.
What the?
What is that thing?
That's a Pokemon?
I thought that was an NPC.
I want to eat that apple.
No.
He's gone.
Pikachu, turn around here.
Pikachu.
Pikachu, look over here.
Look.
Pikachu, look.
Okay.
Dance.
You like to dance?
That was a Chad raw steak eater.
Chad real diarrhea haver.
These guys eat apples or anything?
That's cool.
I only have seven photos left.
Oh, well I'm done anyways, okay.
At somebody, you told me this guy was funny.
Oh no.
Did I just ruin a friend circle?
Used to be.
Get out of here.
I'm still funny.
I still got it.
Hey, dude, you told me this guy was funny.
What the fuck, dude?
Cartoon steam just came out of that guy's fucking neck
underneath his shirt.
I like that one.
There's a better one though.
How was it?
I guess I'll take it.
That one.
Guess I got a picture of that.
Definitely the one with the hand.
Definitely the one with the big flop.
Are we this one?
I got him from far away.
That's a good one.
All right, I'm gonna take a break.
I'm gonna go get the wood.
I'm gonna come back.
I'm gonna play Pac-Man 99 for a little while.
And then I will say goodbye.
I will say farewell.
I will play a lot of Pac-Man 99.
I'll try to get at least in the top 10.
And we'll look at the wood.
Okay, you want my review of Pokemon Snap?
It's cute.
That was a cute game.
Looks like there's a lot to do.
Looks like there's a lot of things to see.
A lot of completionists will love it
if they like Pokemon.
I enjoyed it.
I thought it was very fun.
But I don't know who any of these people are.
I'm your friend that came over in the middle of the season
that has not seen the show,
but just said, I don't care.
And you're like, oh, okay.
This is like episode eight of like middle of the season,
like the only 12 episodes.
Like I don't care.
So for that being that person,
I thought it was pretty good.
So let's play Pac-Man.
I will return in about two minutes.
And we'll play Pac-Man 99.
What did I get for present?
Hold on.
Oh no, nevermind.
Hey, look at that.
50 Pokemon species.
Fighting type.
Oh, that's cool.
All right.
Let me make sure this saves
in case I want to play it again.
Five hours, 50 Pokemon.
That's true.
All right, I'll be right back.
See you guys in a minute.