Yes, yes, really. Yeah, I know I told you that it probably wasn't gonna happen today, but I'm full of surprises, aren't I?
Hi guys. Uh, yeah, we're gonna try. There's been some strange happenings over the last few days, and I'm not gonna stream just yet.
I'm gonna make sure this is gonna work. So we're gonna hang out here for like five to ten minutes and see what happens.
If we're still green, like solid green, uh, heck yeah. Sounds like a plan. Telephone hangout stream.
No, I actually have something that I've been really looking forward to playing, but we're not gonna show that yet.
It's the title, it's in the stream title. Why do I think there's some type of curtain I can drop here?
Well, I'm not gonna tell you what the game is, I'm gonna make it be a surprise. It's the title of the stream and it's the game category.
But, just make sure we got it. Yeah, we're good. Is it Resident Evil? No, it is. Oh, maybe some of you guys haven't refreshed.
Would you look at that? Looks like some of you guys might not have refreshed. Is it Bookworm Adventures? No.
It is Africa. The game Africa. This is a rare PlayStation 3 game. Let's hope it's worth the $50 I spent on it.
Because it's rare. That doesn't mean good, but okay. We're gonna be playing a rare one tonight.
Yeah, I'll give you a quick little sneak peek. How does that sound? Getting down, look at that.
Okay, back to the intro. Oops. Well, now it's, now it's just playing, isn't it? I probably should turn that off.
Uh, this is a game where you take photos. That's the whole game. It's Pokemon Snap, but real life. It's a real life Pokemon Snap.
You gotta get perfect angles. And this is the game we're gonna play today.
Uh, because I don't want to start the vibe. And I know what some of you were thinking. That I'm, I'm Pikachu socks-ing everybody here.
And that I'm a liar, and I don't, let me just go, let me make sure, like, we're gonna see lots of Pogchamps in the chat, because this is like a year in the making.
I, I finally own this. Just so people understand. That this is not a Pikachu sock scenario.
There it is. There's the vibe. It's real. I didn't make this out of, like, plastic and cardboard and shit. I mean, I could've, it's real.
It's here. It's so, it's set up. And, uh, that's what I thought I was gonna be doing over the, like, the next three, four days.
Unfortunately, that didn't happen. Internet was all fucked up. We had a lot of issues. Uh, and I'm gonna give Cox the benefit of the doubt on this one.
I know, I hate to say that. But the weather here has been fucking crazy. We've been getting, like, 60 plus mile per hour winds.
Uh, like enough to take trees down and stuff. And it's been record rainfall. We had a shitload of rain.
So I, I, I, maybe the, the anger was misdirected. Potentially. I don't know. We have not dropped a single frame yet today.
Uh, there was a weird bandwidth problem me and Italics were having. So me and Italics are trying to work through these weird issues that we keep having with this company.
But, uh, I don't see any dropped frames at all in about five minutes. So I think I can stop stalling.
I don't know. Should I? Should I make a tweet and say that the stream is on? I think, I don't wanna jinx it.
Because the last stream from this place, uh, was actually Italics. And that was, like, what, two days ago? And he dropped, like, 30, 40,000 frames.
So, look, I, I don't wanna jinx it. But, you know, let's go. I've been wanting to stream for, like, three days.
I've got so much shit you guys have no idea. We've got Africa. The whole continent is here. In my house.
We got all the vive shit. This room is, this room is vivified. I vived it two days ago.
We got Space Channel 5 Part 1. We got, I bought a shitload more PlayStation 2 games. I'm ready to go.
And I gotta get out of here. So I'll see you tomorrow. No. All right. Let me just make a tweet. Then we can play, uh, Africa.
Metro Exodus just released. But I didn't play Last Light. I can't just play Exodus.
You can't watch Star Wars Episode 4 and then skip to Episode 6 if you've never seen them before.
They would be like, why would you do that? You have so many questions.
All right. I think we're good to go. Oh, boy. The whip dis- I got some good news for the house here today.
No drop frames in five minutes? That is beyond recognizable to us recently. Let me see here.
Because it was fucking bright red like an hour ago. This is weird. What a fucking weird technology.
All right. But I was told it was going to get fixed today. That's what I was told.
Anyway, let's go ahead and tweet that. I'll go ahead and get this off so you can take a look at this fun intro with like the lizard.
I think the stalling can end. You need audio too, don't you? You'll get it in a second.
So if you end up hearing, which you probably will, there's probably going to be a scenario where it sounds like my house is going to fall over because of the wind.
It's supposed to keep going over into midnight tonight. So you will hear like my room is being microwaved.
That's the sound it makes. That's the only way it can compare it to. There it is.
All right. I just tweeted it. That means it's real. Let's go. Get that audio on. I turned it on right when it stopped.
All right. We need to test something here. How are there already seven clips of this spring?
Did somebody, did you accidentally press the clip it button and you're like, oh shit, hopefully nobody saw that.
All right. Let's make sure that's synced up. All we can do is new game. So new game.
And there's the MGM lion. We are currently auto saving. Again, if you're just joining us.
This is the rarest PlayStation 3 game that exists in North America. It was five hundred dollars.
So, I mean, hopefully we get to play it. Is that the real win? What's going on here?
Do I have to like reset this game? I thought you're never supposed to do this.
Aren't you not supposed to ever do this with ever got any console ever?
I can't turn the console off. That's the number one cardinal sin is turning off your console during a save.
And this is like italics. Let me borrow this. I'm going to break his PlayStation 3.
What am I going to do about this? What if I like wipe? What if he's got some like saves on here that are really important?
I just looked it up. It's fifty dollars for a used copy. Yes, it is.
I don't. What's wrong with this? The disk is perfect. The disk is perfect.
This is not even. This is almost like factory new. Now, something just fucked up there.
Was there like a glitch? We're good. We're good. Everybody calmed down. Let's try it again.
It's broken and not used. He's actually microwaving his room. Somebody microwaved the room.
I don't know. Somebody went on to, you know, you know, every room has a fucking panel.
Every microwave. I don't know what I meant to say is every microwave has the panel.
Somebody put on like five seconds and impressed it. Let's try again.
Well, the Internet works in that spectacular. OK, told you I told you I wasn't supposed to do that.
Don't tell them. Don't tell them. Let me be the one that tells them.
Let me be the one that tells them. Let me be the one that tells them.
I can't fucking believe it. I just wanted to play Africa and take photos.
What did I do? What happened? How do I even do that? How do I delete that?
How do you delete save data? He's watching. I don't understand what happened.
I'm going to delete the save data for. OK, that's good. Let's let's hold on.
I'm going to do it again and see what happens. I'm so like sad right now.
I didn't even do anything. I just put a game disc in the PlayStation.
That didn't. I don't think that did. No, don't worry.
It didn't delete everything. It didn't delete everything. It only deleted Africa. I hope.
Do not see. That's what I'm telling you guys.
Everyone was telling me that I should have done that.
Fucking autosave. When is I going to come up with an autosave that doesn't fucking brick your entire...
Let's do it. Do it. Let's go. Autosave. Party the fuck up.
What is what is happening right now? I'm going to leave it for a second.
I'm impatient. It shouldn't take this long. Just wait. Just wait. OK.
I'm an impatient boomer. I don't know, man. After after two to three straight minutes.
It might have to delete all the local content. No, I can't do that.
OK. It takes a long time to load a whole continent.
I'm going to give this another two minutes. I just got to wipe his hard drive.
Try unplugging it now. If I have to factory reset his PlayStation.
What do you mean Google it? It takes that long. What?
Oh my God. So I brick this PS3 for no reason.
It has a three hundred and eighty seven megabyte save file.
Why does it have a four hundred meg save file?
OK. Well, sorry. It's Alex. I may have brick to your saves.
It's all right. You can make a new team as those character.
It's all right. Don't worry. I'm sorry. Music volume in midnight mode.
I don't have that. Can we get the Jurassic Park music down a little bit?
No, I'll keep it up. No, that's too much.
Two two ticks down. It is the look. How many times?
OK, thank God. It was going to be like five minutes every time.
This is an incredibly poorly optimized.
Learn all about Africa and its animals. All right.
Read about any animals you've discovered in Safari mode.
We're going to get default unlockables, which is bugs, shrimp and tigers.
So at least we'll have the defaults. So zebra.
I told you we're going to get those. Let's learn. Let's learn about the zebra.
This is the rarest PlayStation 3 game in North America.
This was five hundred dollars. You understand?
Let's go. A 3D view profile.
Look at this. There's even video. There's even.
Never mind. This 3D view.
That's what an adult looks like. What about a baby?
I have not found the baby yet. We've got to take a picture of everything.
Planes or virtual zebras are Africa's most common zebra species.
They can be distinguished from other species by their unique pattern of stripes,
which are wide and widely spaced.
As in all zebra species, the stripes are thought to help visually distract potential predators.
So that's top right. That's what the zebra.
That's the male and female. I guess maybe the female stands up on two legs.
Interesting. Wears shoes too.
New record. Four to four and a half feet at the shoulder.
And they weigh four hundred eighty five to seven hundred seventy five.
Music's too loud. And we got fifty fucking subs just came in.
Fifty of them. That's right. Five hundred community subs.
What is going on? No. Oh my god. Fifty and then ten.
Great Canadian Fuck Club gave six thousand dollars worth of subs right there.
Whatever it was. Thank you so much, dude. That's a shitload.
Whiff whiffs. I gave ten. Great Canadians back.
All right. That's cool. I mean, no, but that is cool.
I'm talking about like the game. That's cool. This is cool.
That's a lot of fucking money. Fifty gifted subs is two, three.
That's two hundred and fifty bucks. My god.
Thanks for the three at all. It's cool. I guess.
And yes, I understand. I'm going real slow. It's been 20 minutes.
But I have to make sure that this Internet is going to work.
This is the rarest fucking PlayStation 3 game.
I ain't going to turn this on and get turned off in five seconds.
Ten community subs from Multi Trip. Thank you, Multi Trip.
Shut the fuck up about that shitty joke. It's not a joke.
Look it up. Go look it up.
Kairatobi, ten community subs. Thank you so much, Kairatobi.
That's like eighty community subs right now.
You guys are fucking incredible. All right, we're going to make our license here.
OK, let's see. Eric, age 27 from France.
Or Anna, 24 from the USA.
I mean, I can't. I mean, USA.
Occupation zoologist.
Journalist. I'm picking zoologist.
And USA. New name.
Anna, forty-six dollars.
It's not a joke. How about...
Photo. Focus.
Exposure. Exposure? No, no, no, no.
Focus. Lens.
Laura Lens. No, that's like a fourth grade
ABC mouse character. No, no, no, no.
Telephoto. Tele...
Telephana. Telephana. Telephana.
Aperture. That's pretty good. Telephana.
Aperture Anna. No, but that's like Aperture Science.
Tele... Laura, ten community subs from
Winterly Parsley. Winterly Parsley, thank you so much for ten subs.
Thank you. God damn it, there's so many different
interesting names. I like Laura... I don't care. Lens Laura.
Laura through the lens or something. I don't know.
Laura Long Lens. That's a bad name, bad name, bad name.
Streamer's not reading chat. Yes, he is.
No, I'm not gonna... I'm gonna name this character something
because this character is, believe it or not, and whatever everybody wants to say, this character will be
in the next Jerma Rumble. It's important. Every new
protagonist that you get in a video game, this character's gonna be in the Jerma Rumble. Has to be.
What was that one? Anna Exposure. No.
This is taking too long.
Aperture Anna. What does Aperture mean? Focus.
Whose name starts with F? Fran? Fran Focus.
Fran Focus. I'm done. How do I do uppercase on this computer?
Francine Focus. Yep. Done.
There it is. Francine Focus. How do I go?
How do I make a space? Can I not do a space?
That's the maximum name you can have. Okay.
That's Francine. That's fine. Francine Focus.
Look at how beautiful this game is. You didn't want me to play it. You.
A245 Fortnite. That guy didn't want me to fucking
play. Get him out of here. What? Oh.
I thought that was me. We finally arrived at the Manyanga Conservation Area.
Okay. Base camp is all set up, so let's start exploring
right away. The game gets it. Who wants to do a tutorial? Who wants to learn everything?
Just get us out there into the wild and get the camera in my hands.
Looking forward to working with you, Francine. You too, Eric.
The Jambo Navi interface is all set up on the laptop.
There may be messages from the head office, so you should check your email now.
Just select the laptop PC to use it. Check email, transfer photos from your camera,
purchase equipment, and more? Okay. Got email, photo,
gallery, shopping, save. Let's go ahead and get that
out of the way so we don't corrupt it. 387 megabytes.
Is this going to take that long to save it every time?
It's going to take like two minutes to save every time. That's
insane. Did they just copy and paste the whole game in a save state?
That might be what this is. Is this game more than 400 meg?
It's 10 years ago. That's not counting photos. So once I start
having like 50 to 100 photos in my library, this is going to be like 5 gig.
Saving is going to take like an hour. This is probably why nobody owns it.
Maybe. Alright, let's check the email. When your in-game
email, pretend email, is faster than your save,
there's something wrong. You could have made that a little longer. Important wildlife research
request. Welcome to the Manyanga Conservation Area. If you
are the first to research Manyanga, so we need you to start by documenting
the animals that live here. Anytime you see a new animal, take a picture of it
and send it by replying to this email. Then we can send you
new photo assignments for that animal. Bits? We got big bits?
Holy shit, we did have big bits. A hundred dollars.
Thank you for the hundred bucks. G-Y-H-D-H-F-E.
Based on your responses to my questions, I've determined that you
would be impotent, asexual or answers of a
beta male. Also, your responses on my fetish question, I've determined
you to be a person with really fucked up fetishes because if a person doesn't express his fetishes
online, he's really fucked up and he can't reveal. This is way out of all of this
however you have to answer this question or else it's a valid place to. Have you tried? I'm not going to read that out loud.
Okay, I got two things
to ask you there. Two questions. I got a question for
you. Here's question number- let's get this out of the way. Question
number one for you. Why do you care so much about my sexuality?
Isn't that my business? You know what I mean? Ain't that like my business?
You know what I'm saying? Question number two for you. Equally
is important. No, it is ours. What?
I'm in a very happy relationship with
someone named Kim. She's my girlfriend.
Got a healthy relationship. That's all you need to know.
I'm not going to answer the question at the end of that because that's not appropriate
for me to say on a live stream of me taking pictures of animals
in Africa. Okay? If this was like a
podcast- let's talk about appropriate shit here. If I was doing a podcast
about sexual shit
alright, yeah, but I'm about to take a picture of a zebra. What is the
context of this conversation? We can't even get to the animals at this
rate. Anyways, no, you can't just like
alright, I'm going to make one more point here. You can't- okay,
if someone's coming out of a coffee shop, let's say Brad Pitt
was coming out of a coffee shop, right? Yeah, it's Brad Pitt.
You know him, you've seen his movies. And you run up to Brad Pitt
there's a bunch of people taking pictures of him and he's like
oh no, no photos today please. I've got pictures of zebras to take.
And they're like, okay, yeah, you run fucking through the crowd
and you like run in there and you're like, hey, have you ever tried to
blank your own blank? He's going to be like, what the fuck are you talking about?
He's going to be like, is he going to walk away?
Comparing yourself to Brad Pitt. I mean, this is 3,300 people here.
How many people have seen Brad Pitt's movies? Maybe like
5-10,000? He gets like 5-10,000 concurrent viewers on his movies.
I think I'm in like a similar category, I think. Thank you for the 100 bucks
though. Alright, we had 50 fucking dollars
from ChunkyBeloney. ChunkyBeloney thanks for $50.02.
Here's a nice cheer to get the taste of the last one out of your mouth. Happy Friday. You've been streaming
for 30 minutes and managed to save and name your character.
This is the ultimate stall stream. Don't you
understand? Things that Jerma says
500 times a stream. Don't you understand? This is something you gotta understand.
You understand? This is something you guys gotta understand. Okay.
No, seriously, thank you both of you. 150 bucks. I need to take a picture
of a, what am I taking a picture of? I'm going to get 3,000 concurrent
viewers. I already have that. Alright, I, I, I, let's go.
Take a picture of it and send, anytime you see a new animal, take a picture of it and send it to my email.
You got it. So difficulty is
level one. Just get, let's go. Let's go take some photos. Let's go.
A draw request already came in, did it? Just start by taking a picture of each type of animal
that you see. Francine, this is for you. A
Tsetse type F. It's my first camera.
And binoculars. And a GPS map. The camera case is
over there. F for Francine. I put the tools in the
cases next to the bookshelf. I'd like to go too, but I need to sort out
our equipment. Can you go with the guide, James?
He should be waiting just outside. Oh, the guy's name is James. I was like, what the hell are you talking about?
Have a safe trip. Okay. So let's go into the camera case.
Make sure that's equipped. Yep, view cameras and lenses. We've got
the type F. Body is type F, that's all I got. There's multiple
bodies, multiple lenses. I don't think I can do anything else.
New tools, they're already equipped. Yep, binoculars, GPS map. Use with the
R1 button. Use with select. Good thing I looked at that, otherwise I would have been
like, don't even explain our flight. Exit base camp.
Tsetse. Tsetse. It's your birthday today.
You know it's on the way. We should be way
more excited about something else. Zero drop frames.
Maybe they fixed it. I don't know, I'm not going to be... I can't say that's
going to happen. We're at Duma Step. Okay.
Jumbo Francine. Welcome to the Manyanga Conservation Area.
I'll drive the car, Francine. Go ahead and make yourself comfortable in the backseat.
I have to take pictures of animals, right? We're going to get like a monster
hunter now. Where's the...
The Kulu Yaku?
What's the bird's name? The bird with the egg? Hippo Pool.
This is the Hippo Pool. Yeah, well I would have driven
another like five feet up there. Nobody is home right now, but Hippo's
off and bathe here. Yeah, I know that. I've played the game before. Drive.
Wrong way. Wrong way, idiot. Like fucking idiot. Doesn't even know where he's going.
You know I've done this before. You know that? Hello? You know I've
done this. I drive over here. You're going the wrong way. Just turn around.
Wow, you like went into the ditch for a second. What a fucking idiot.
God, how does this person have 3,000 viewers? I don't understand. Am I supposed to be
taking pictures? How do I take pictures? How do I take
a photo? Is this just like teaching you that they are okay? Here we go. Not many animals here.
There's a shitload of animals here. That bird's coming down and swooping down and going to get us.
Let's try a Wily Oasis. When there's water, there's life,
right? Blind. There are no animals. Wow,
a blind streamer. Can't even see the fucking animal in front of him. He's pretending.
He has to be. Yeah, I don't know man. Like seriously? Like how do you
not see that? There were clearly three or four deer in front of him and he just doesn't see
them? I just don't get it. He needs to start paying the fuck attention to stuff. It's pissing
me off lately. That's the Wily Oasis. Yeah.
Just like I said, plenty of animals here. Oh, let's get a giraffe. Too far
to see? Try the binoculars. Press R1 button to use the binoculars.
Oh, whoops. It could get a bit bumpy, so hang on. Oh, I can't wait to see how
badly he drives. Come on, streamer. He actually just
has to dash into that. Alright, we can find the perfect one. Look at that. Planes, zebras.
I would laugh my ass off if he fucking runs into one. Look, they're
what? What about the giraffe? Look at that.
Maasai giraffes. Yeah, it was also, what's this one?
The little ones. Wily Oasis.
By the way, Francine, do you know how to use the camera? I have
no idea. Press the square button to point the camera and press the circle
button or R1 to shoot. This one right to the right is looking like
prime picture material. They're right in front of the bush.
Why don't you try it out now? Point the camera and then snap a picture. How do I zoom in?
No, that's not good enough. Where's the truck? Where's the truck?
Okay, I don't know where the truck went. Got it, got it, got it, got it, got it, got it.
Check your photos in the field menu. Press the triangle button to open the
field menu. Photos. That one's, look at how beautiful that is.
A little blurry, but it's alright. That's a pretty good
calendar photo, I would say. Tools, missions, look like I could.
Try taking some pictures up close. Press X button to exit the car. But please don't
stray too far from the car. Good luck. Snapshots of plenty of animals.
You're not gonna like leave me, are you? I can actually walk around?
How did that one come up? That zebra.
Okay, uh, what if I just took like a fucking... Oh, come on!
I pressed the wrong button. Come on, do something, do it again.
No, I gotta take pictures of like animals. No, you scare them if you get too... Okay,
I got zebras, I need giraffe. Is it like a sneak button? What's like
the stealth kill button? And I don't mean like the stealth kill button, I mean like the stealth
button that makes you creep down and do the... Like, hold on, just quiet.
There's one right here. No, I gotta get closer than that. God damn it.
What are those little guys called? Francine, don't wander too far, it's dangerous.
Can I get like fucking eaten by a lion? Come on, come on!
That was the wrong button. It's circle.
I keep thinking it's X. Okay, there's the giraffe.
Get one close. I mean, I can't get that close to a giraffe, guys. Not bad.
I gotta get the little ones. There they are. Okay, let's get up there.
Right next to this tree. Can I get it? Come on. I gotta get away.
Don't run away! Stop! Ah! Here we go. It's gonna be patient.
You're gonna pop up from behind the bush. Beautiful. Oh,
excellent job. That's it. Tutorial mission passed.
You have to crouch to enter sneak mode. Oh, I don't know how to crouch. No.
Wasted film. Baby giraffe look like adult giraffe, but just get the
rhino. Where's the rhino? I gotta get back in the car
to get the rhino. What about that? Is that a zebra? Yeah.
That's great that they actually pose, though. Let's go back to base camp. Let's review the photos
and do the tutorial. I might get a couple of action shots here. This might be good.
Where's the rhino? Looking for a rhino? Come on. Something crazy is gonna happen.
He doesn't know where the rhino is. I'll get the rhino eventually.
I'm not operating the car. Maybe I get to drive the car eventually. I would assume. Probably can, right?
What are those? Lining the shot up?
Are those just regular horses? What are those?
Got ya. Gazelles. Horses. I don't know.
How far away? You couldn't even tell. This is an on-rail shooter.
Well, only for this portion. You actually get to get out.
Let's review those photos. Send them pictures of the gas tanks.
How was the safari today? Many types of animals live in the area. Good luck tomorrow, too.
There are like 500 animals to take pictures of in this game.
How was it on the field? Find lots of animals? Transfer your photos to JumboNavi.
Also, send the head office a photo of each animal that you took by replying to their email.
Transfer photos.
I have to check the ones that I want to send.
Let's take a look at the view. That one's not bad. I like that one.
That one's way better.
That's just a handsome fella, you know what I mean?
This one... no. Wait, what was it? This is so bad.
This is like Grandma with an iPhone. At the Disney one.
I like that one. Good picture, Grandma. This is like in your group chat.
Everybody has one with their family.
And even when you say hide notifications, it doesn't matter. It still pops up.
At the top of your phone. You have to kind of chime in.
Your grandma's in there, so you're going to be like, oh, that's a really cool picture you got there of the turkey.
Yeah, I was at the safari at Disney World.
Let me show you this photo.
You can be on National Geographic with those photos.
That's how it goes every time.
I'm going to take this one. Here's the one I wanted to use. That's a cool zebra.
Let's transfer those.
Did I just delete everything?
This is spaced with photos.
I can save them?
We got reply. Send photos.
Did I even pick photos? Oh, here we go.
This is the good one I wanted. Send that one.
Send. Result. Clear.
Good angle. Excellent target. Marvelous distance and marvelous technique.
$3,000. Animal added to GeoAfrica mode.
Thompson's gazelle.
I'm going to send you a picture of the giraffe.
It's a bad angle, but it's okay. I'm going to use it.
Great angle. Marvelous. Marvelous. Excellent.
Look at all the space above the giraffe. This is a bad picture.
Let's do it again.
What if I just send him a picture of my friend giving the thumbs up?
What's he going to do?
This photo. Let's see what they say.
Failed. Sorry.
This bird or this bird? This one's probably more clear.
Even though it's not at all.
It is a pretty bad angle, but at least I cleared it with a B.
Lapid-faced vulture.
Let's do the new animal.
What is this of? I don't think I even did the zebras.
Excellent angle. Marvelous. Marvelous. Marvelous.
I already did it. So what did I not send?
The other gazelles. Like these. Bad angle.
How do you have good distance?
There's another iPad picture. I have money.
I'm going to go on my photo gallery. I'm going to start deleting shit.
Delete this. Delete. Delete. Delete. Wait. Keep that one.
I think we already got them. We got them all.
Maybe I can get a better angle on Turkey. Whatever the hell this thing is.
Because that is a vulture too, right? Maybe I'll get a better grade.
We improved the grade. Let's see what the save is now.
308. I have to do it. No we don't. Not yet.
What do I have for money? Photo frame. Photo storage.
That's all I have unlocked right now. $48,000
for a photo storage device. $68,000 for a photo frame.
That's kind of ridiculous.
Transfer photos to laptop PC to free up space on your camera.
As long as there's room your photos will be automatically transferred when you use the PC.
By the way, I prepared a map of the area. We can fill the map out as we discover new areas.
Great first day out there. Let's rest up and get an early start tomorrow.
Time for bed.
Oh, I'll leave the survey log on the bookshelf. You may want to review it from time to time.
What do you mean like right now?
The grandma joke in the group chat is going to be a reality.
Survey log. This is the log of the progress of the survey of the
Mannyanga conservation area.
Camera lingo. Camera shake. Basic photography.
Okay, remaining image. Make sure I know what this is going on. Left stick is angle.
Right stick up and down. Wait a minute.
Today's advice. If you think your photo is good, chances are it is.
Type F. We don't need to know about that. Camera shake.
Let's talk about a nasty little problem that can wreck your hard-won photos.
You guessed it. Camera shake. If your hands jiggle while you snap the picture, your photos are blurred.
Increase the shutter speed or try pressing the shutter
more gently. So that's why these pictures have been shitty.
Shooting vertically. What?
Vertical photos are fun to take. No they're not. This is like every
photographer will tell you that don't ever take a photo with your iPhone. Vertical.
I guess this is like a nice iPhone though. From the viewfinder, try holding
the controller in a vertical position.
I don't even know if I can do that with this controller.
Pictures you take are saved to your photo storage. All your photos go to the same storage.
So even if you change cameras, you'll have the same number of shots remaining.
Dirty shots in the storage. If you want to take more, you need to import some of your photos into the John Blanavia or
let's delete to clear up space.
My survey begins.
This is your player record. Total time played, day of survey, photos taken, missions cleared.
My ranking is Vervet Monkey.
This is going to be fun. Let's do it. How do I do anything?
Alright, Eric.
What about the map? The map of the locations you've explored.
Look at all this. Look at all that up there.
There's so much. I'm going to beat this whole game today.
Well no I'm not, but I'll play for a while. Hippo Pool Base Camp. We've got to go to the Hippo Pool, right?
Base Camp Hippo Pool. Closest water source from Base Camp.
Favorite spot for Hippopotamus. Hippopotamus is
a fucking dangerous though. They're the most vicious animal on Earth.
Alright, let's see. Any new emails? I do.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa. Alright, research. Herd of...
We need a herd of gazelles. Hi Francie, nice to meet you.
Since you're doing research on the Duma step, I had a favor to ask you. Are you familiar with an animal called the
Thompson gazelle? They favor flat plains with a wide view and live in herds of several
dozen head or more. Could you photograph one of these herds for us so we can study
their behavior on the Duma step? By the way, I've attached a really good photo
and an amazing, in fact, video of a herd of them. But I'm just trying to
flex on you to see if you can even come remotely close to my incredible skill.
Thank you. Have a nice day. Okay, we need a...
Okay, let's take it. Accept this mission? Yes. Herd of gazelles.
Plains with a wide view. So we got that one. Can we do more than one?
This is the project head office. Thanks for that photo you sent to the Plains zebra.
Could we ask you to take another one with a little more detail? We want to study
the stripes on the Plains zebra's face. So we need a face shot taken
from head on. There's no rush, just send me one when you have time.
Yeah, like the one we just sent you. Good day Francie.
My name is Maliwe Essien. I'm researching savanna wildlife ecology.
I caught wind of your studies on the Duma step and was hoping I might ask you a favor.
I wish to teach my students how to identify a topi. But I need a
photograph first. Topis have a distinct black pattern
at the base of their legs. Could you take a picture from the side that shows this?
So this is just side missions. The Maasai giraffe photo you sent us the other day
was quite nice. You're already creating a buzz around the office. When we showed the photo
to a bottled water manufacturer, they expressed an interest in seeing a photo
of a giraffe drinking water. Can you manage this additional
request? Yeah? Alright, so what do we need?
Oh, I can only take one mission at a time. Alright, that one's better. Giraffe drinking
water. And then if I come across a zebra,
take a picture of its face, and we're looking for
different discolorations
on the topi with the legs.
Alright, photo of a giraffe drinking water.
And this is also just take pictures of any new animal. It's just permanently
there. Alright, let's go. Our next job is to photograph a Maasai giraffe drinking
water. When giraffes drink water, they spread their front legs and drink from a standing position.
Stay out of notice and wait for the giraffe to become thirsty.
Alright, stalk a giraffe. I can't wait to get a dangerous shot.
You know, it's just loading up all the photos. Yeah!
Alright, we'll be going James.
He just drives. Am I driving?
If you ever want me to stop the car, press the L2 button to tell me. For your own safety,
you can't get out of the car until it comes to a complete stop. It's none of that
GTA bullshit. Press the R2 button and I'll start driving again.
Press circle to talk to me. Please be sure not to wander too far
from the car. Alright, go! Alright, giraffe drinking
water. Alright, stop. We gotta get a picture of a hippo.
How close? Oh, he sees me. Is this like his aggression stance?
I can get closer, I think. Hippos can't run.
Can hippos... Wait, hold on. Can I die?
Hold on a minute. What does that mean?
He's like burping at me. Alright, I'm just gonna get it. We'll get all of them.
No, no, no. Wrong button. Why is it circled?
Wait, push it slightly, gently. Okay, let's go.
Let's get out of this way. Charge the hippo. I'm not gonna charge the hippo because
if I die and I have to reload a save, I haven't saved it in like an hour.
Let me save it. You're driving right towards the hippo.
Hey, look at that. See, the hippos are bathing at the hippo pool. It's a great chance
for some photos. Hippos can be dangerous. Be careful when taking close shots.
No, I already got it. Let's go. We don't want any hippos coming after us.
Let's take a detour. He just drove straight at him.
Hippos can run literally like a horse. Yeah, but
they're like a train. It takes them like a mile to slow down.
They're running with like five billion pounds. Why are you stopping?
Get us to a giraffe. Now. Isn't that even worse?
Isn't the hippo actually the most dangerous animal in the world?
Alright, stop, stop, stop, stop. Now, one of these giraffes
has to take a drink. Bingo. Get in there. Donk your head.
Let's... Okay, hold on. Hold on. No, no, no.
We could get a better one. Yeah, the level of detail loading with the frame rate
in the background. Well, yeah, it's to keep the CPU cool.
None of these animals are dangerous. I'll be fine. Come on, come on.
I gotta get in the magazine. No, I gotta get in the bottled water. Fuck.
Do it again. This is a great shot. Go down one more time.
This is good framing. I got the water, the distance.
What the hell was that? He just lifted his leg up to pee.
Oh, you asshole. We already... Alright, hold on. This will be good.
If I get two of them, that's gonna look great. Go into that water.
He's getting so close, dude. This is gonna be perfect. Look at that background, too.
That'll go on the front of a bottle of water. I can guarantee it.
Just in case, just in case. Hold on. I gotta get in the front of the zebra's face.
How the hell am I gonna get that? They get so scared and they just run off.
Can I get like a different costume to make me hide or something?
Just wait. They'll get in here. This counts as a... right in front of the face, right?
Come on. I'm just a statue. They don't even know I'm here.
Got it. I need a better lens. What was the last thing we did?
Let me try it one more time. Perfect. Oh, this is gonna be good.
Leave me alone. What the fuck are you doing? What are you doing?
I had it lined up perfectly and you just tethered me back here.
Oh, god damn it. Whatever. I gotta get the topi, right?
Let me take a look at those photos. Just make sure they're fucking clean.
That's good. That one's really good. It's definitely this one.
Too far away. No. That's a good one.
This camera sucks. That's the good one. Somebody said rule of thirds
is a myth that makes your photos look like shit. What do you mean it's a myth?
Alright, let's go find... I really want to get the zebra
right in the face. Let me try that one more. I gotta get that. I can't just go.
Look, maybe if he drives the car a little bit closer he won't be like, get back here!
You're too far away! Stop.
He's got to get right in their path. I had it too and it just limited a loading screen.
Fuck! I had it set up like two different times.
And that guy just... Wait, careful! You're going too far!
Whatever. It's close enough. I had to see two different loading screens
when I had the shit ready to go. It's because he was worried about you.
Don't be worried about me. I'm a fucking Francine... No, don't go back to the base camp.
Actually, yeah. Go back to the base camp.
I'm looking for a... Topey. Is that one right there?
I think there's one right here. Can I go that far? Stop.
That's definitely one right here. Does it have the same pattern that they want?
I can't tell. I think it does. Yep, it does. Get in there.
Alright, just in case it runs away, let's get like a dogshit grandma photo.
Just so we can at least prove that we did it. Don't you fucking dare pull me back right now.
You fucking asshole. Stop this. I have a perfect opportunity.
They want a side profile. Got it.
Zoom in. I have a default camera. I can't go that far.
Can I get closer? Oh god, that's perfect.
Stay right there. Don't move. Alright, now get out of here!
I should have every photo I need. Why are you being so nasty? No, I'm trying to get him away.
There could be predators around. He's standing still from my photo.
No, get out of here. Go. Go back to your family.
I could have died 30 minutes ago. It isn't real life though.
Yeah, I'll say it now. The hippo would have just snapped you in half.
I need to get a huge lens. Yeah, once we start making money I can start buying stuff.
Get a six foot camera lens. I don't know if I can get a comedy lens.
How is the safari? You look satisfied with the photos you took.
Let's examine them. Make sure we get the right ones. Send the right ones in our emails.
That was a loud, dangerous sound. I don't know if you guys heard that.
Let's go to the laptop. Let's see. Photos.
Transferring photos. Let's take a look.
Request just came in. This is for a drinking giraffe.
I do have a photo. Which one was it?
Let's see. We got this one, and then this one.
That's the only two I got, right? Yeah, that's too far away.
Too hazy and far away. I saw the animals in the shot too.
This is terrible. It's this one. Select this one.
That's the one. That's got to be a great angle.
How is that not better? Distance is angle.
That's not a good angle. I got a C for that picture.
That's a beautiful piece of photography right there. Didn't get the full 20 grand.
This one is done. It should have been in the center.
I have rule of thirds. This is bullshit.
We didn't get the herd of the gazelles yet.
This is the side profile of that
topi.
Let's take a look. I don't like this photo though. It's ugly.
This one is better. This one looks like shit.
That's definitely a better picture. The color correction is awful.
This one is better? I feel like the tree in the background and the dirt in the background
is screwing up the composition there. Look at the dirt and the sand
in the background. And his face is not defined
with the tree in the background. This one is better.
That's what I'm saying. Told you guys. Come on.
They weren't asking for a face shot. They were asking for just a side profile.
That's going against what the client asked and what the client
was paying for. This one on the other hand, I didn't get.
Let me see. Face shot from head on.
That's not right.
That's not correct. If that's what they want, then that's not what they got.
Just for curiosity, I can't even do it. You can only do these
missions once. Send it anyway. No, no. You only get to do them once.
But we do have new photos. It's 3000
per new animal, which we have hippos here.
They both suck.
It's the turkey. Probably this one. This one sucks.
At least this one has a face. Bad distance. I mean, kind of
okay distance in technique. Not really though. Hippopotamus.
And was there any others that I didn't get that were in?
No, we got them all. Alright, I'll delete all these.
I'll get rid of these fucking things. I need the herd of gazelles
and a face shot of a zebra.
So let me go back. Let's get rid of these. Delete them.
Transfer this one. How do I just transfer this?
I want to keep this one. I can't keep this one forever?
Or does it just sit in here? If I go shopping, shopping.
I want to go shopping. Hit X. I was pressing X. It didn't do anything.
Free shipping around the world. Wouldn't that be interesting? I don't have money.
Save. Press X when in the transfer screen. I was.
I was pressing X. Didn't do anything. Broke? Well, I just started.
Have I caught all the Pokemon yet? No. Not yet.
Don't you have camera experience from the wedding jobs you took in real life?
Well, I have video experience, not photo experience.
They're in the same kind of category, but they're kind of like cousins.
Recording something that is potentially moving around and distance and
location and lighting is a lot different instead of still picture.
Ah, this is painful. This save. What is the save time?
Yeah, if you're just joining us, for some reason there's a 400 megabyte save file
and there's nothing I can do about it. It's the rarest
joke that people get angry at because I said it like five times in the first 20 minutes
of the stream. Alright, that's good. Let's go.
I have to let go to sleep, right? New day?
Can I look at the cameras? Can I do anything with the camera?
Can I buy something for this? Type F. No, I need to buy a new
camera. Alright, let's go to bed. F, F, F, F, F, F, F.
This lazy shit just reads while I take photos.
There's elephants down there? Look it. There's elephants. There's probably like
T-Rexes and shit. Alright, we need the... Wait, I gotta take that
mission first. We're probably gonna have a bunch of emails now.
Alright, we got two opportunities.
This one's boring. The ultimate big mouth.
Okay, I'll do it. That one's more interesting.
We need the close-up of the face and a hippo
yawning. You got it.
Hey, let the professional decide what they're going to do.
Mr. Reading Harry Potter start to finish.
I don't have my... I have a thing that I put on the ground to wheel.
And I took it out because I VR-ified my room.
It's like I'm glued to the ground right now.
Okay. Hello, Francine. We're looking for
hippos this time, right? Oh, jumbo.
If it's not far, but let me take you to the hippo pool. Go ahead and hop in the back.
Snap a yawning hippopotamus. I'm gonna try.
How do hippos... I'm not gonna read that, but I don't know. I have no idea.
I don't know. Okay, let's go.
Go hide in a bush. When the screen flashes red, I'm getting too close.
Here comes a big yawn.
Am I hidden right now? This one seems pretty alerted.
This one seems pretty alerted. I got it.
I got a pretty good video of that hippo coming to kill me.
You wake up in the fucking hippo. Oh, you all right? No photos
worth risking life and limb over. You're finally awake.
Hey, I didn't get your yawning hippo, but I got a great YouTube
like Facebook video of that. That's gonna be shared.
50 million times. Let's try again.
Hide in a bush. I gotta be very, very careful. Very patient.
For a second at the top, I thought that said, stop a yawning
hippopotamus. Stop them from yawning. What am I supposed to do?
This time, I'm gonna be very cautious.
They're all turning the other way. Yawning hippo.
That one right in the middle. Or on the left. One on the left?
That's not a bad shot. Not a bad shot if you just open your mouth.
I gotta wait for it. If he lifts his head up over the bush, that would look so good.
Who's gonna do it? Which one of you, like, thumbs
is gonna open your mouth? I can't get closer than this. Do it.
Zoom in. I have the default camera. I can't go in any further.
And if I get closer, they'll attack me. Look, I'm gonna come out of the camera mode and
I'm gonna do it. Oh yeah, you yawn first. That's right.
No? Did it work? Yawn. Somebody yawn.
I can't get closer. The last time I got closer, they tried
to kill me. No, this one just went to bed. Come on, somebody do it.
They're both asleep. Wait. You just woke... Okay, that's actually not a bad thing.
You just woke this one up. Maybe it'll do a, I just woke up yawn.
No, don't turn the other direction. They're behind you. Where are you going?
Turn this way. Alright, it has to be you. No, no, no, no.
Don't obstruct it from the... Shot ruined.
I'm gonna have to get this one over here. Yawn. Oh, this is not a bad shot.
Come on, do it. You just woke up. This is your opportunity to yawn. Do it.
How much is this one? You're the only one left in the pool. Please just yawn.
When is your AI gonna understand that it's time to yawn?
Is that about the yawns?
No, it's a huge thing. They go like, they look like a snake
when they do it. The jaws unhinge. And they like a swallow and
an egg. I don't think that was a yawn. I could probably pass it off as one though.
The mouth is open. Whoops, that's a... I don't want to do vertical.
Great. Wait, wait, wait. He's turning around. This is good.
This is really good, really good, really good. Do it. No, no, no, no. This way.
No, no, no, no, no. Wait, wait, wait. Wait for him to land. Wait for him to land.
Okay. That was a yawn coming up. Nope. Get out of here.
I think Gazelle just ruined everything. Oh, you know what? That's... I'm gonna take...
Right? Why not just take that? That's a good turning
profile picture. Where's the other hippo? Just still
sitting there. Isn't there a third hippo? This really is what...
You guys think this is... Wow, this is boring. I've seen
like Planet Earth. I've seen the National Geographic stuff. It's so much more interesting than this.
No, it isn't. To get the photo of the
hippopotamus yawning and have it really look cool and on like the National Geographic
PBS stuff. Somebody comes out here and does this for like six straight days.
Just hang out here and they just eat like sandwiches.
You want to know why that's so difficult to do? Because think about that.
There is one moment that you have to be ready to take the photo.
And it might take up to five straight days before you get it. At any point
in those five days. You gotta be like, oh shit! And like grab
like snap! Because you might be sitting there for like 16 hours.
That's hard. Will you open your mouth and yawn please? There's the other one.
Do a double yawn. Do like a Dragon Ball Z fusion yawn together.
Come on. This is a bad photo. I have to move. This is a
hippopotamus right? I just want to be like, yes, yes it is. Because they're not
yawning. These are elephants. These are baby
elephants. They could be. But what if they... Good. Now yawn
together. One, two, three, yawn.
Can they see me? Is that why they're not doing this? Is that why they're not comfortable
enough to yawn because I'm sitting here? They said, the guy told me to hide in a
bush. He said hide in a bush.
Only these bushes are here. Bingo. You aren't in a bush.
I can't take a photo inside the bush. Alright.
I'm in the bush. Cool. Let's take a photo. That is just good.
Do it. This is good. This depth of field here. Come on. Open your
mouth. Please. Do it. That's not depth of field.
It's low resolution. Well, whatever. How are you not...
Here it comes. I gotta be ready. What was that? What?
Was that a fast yawn? That was like a super fast forward, fast forward
motion yawn. I'm so angry.
Just like in real life. I almost wasn't ready. Do it.
Come on. He's getting right into frame. Right now. Stop.
Open the mouth. Let's go. Come on. Don't get blocked by the low res
grass, bush thing. Don't do it. Do it. Here we go.
One. Two. Do it.
Is that gonna be flurry? Why?
Wait. Yes. Perfect. See ya later.
Check him first. Hold on. Check him. Check him. Check him. Good.
That's the best one. Look at that one.
The rest of these are just not. I don't even know what these are.
I was taking a photo trying to time the mouth opening and I didn't get it once.
I almost got it right there. I like these two.
They just look like two terriers looking at me. I like this one.
I do. Well, we got the thing we needed.
What's the other mission we can do? Let's see. Yeah, get a shot of those
zebra and herd of gazelles. I need a zebra.
I need to get that zebra shot. Let's go. No, don't go back to the camp.
You can't take me a little bit further out. Why? Why can you not take me
further out? Zebra right here. No, I can't go that far away.
Let's just turn this one in. Was it inevitable?
Was it inevitable? I think it was inevitable. Uh oh.
We're going back down to zero, boys and girls.
I got the photo. We good? Wait, we're back. German is disappearing.
Quick, get in. It was a long drive, but we made it.
Yeah, we have some other issues going on here.
Something got fucked up. Something definitely got really fucked up.
We're seeing some odd shit at this residence, I'll tell ya.
Alright, so far it was good. That was me.
Alright, let's get these out of here.
Is this whole game just to sell people Sony cameras?
Sony? At least Sony cameras? They don't look like Sony.
Is that a Sony video camera? You know what I mean by that.
Well, none of you guys are going to buy this shit. This is like 12 years ago.
Alright, this is the one we're going to use. Wait, wait, wait.
It's doing a poor job. Alright, $20,000. We got the yawn.
Let's take a look. Uh, I don't know. This is tough.
Because, here's the problem. This one is definitely way more pronounced.
But this one is centered.
The mouth is actually, you can see down, like the urinal.
The tilted one is a big, what about over here? Nah, not these ones.
This one has more emotion behind it. That's really tired.
But yeah, somebody said the game is probably coded for the
looking down the PVC pipe. I like this photo better,
but this one's probably worth more points. I'm going with that one.
I'm going with my gut here. Target, distance, excellent technique.
Alright, now that's alright. I got exactly what I came in for.
$20,000. Oh yeah, by the way, sorry for telling you.
The pre-stream was a little odd. Because I'm just sitting there
going, yeah, we're wearing the bright red. There's no stream today.
Stream's not happening today, is what I said in the chat. And then I got green.
And then the problem was fixed. And then me and Italics were talking about
how we can kill bandwidth to each other now somehow, which wasn't
really necessarily a problem before.
And we had like fucking 60 plus mile per hour winds in Vegas.
It was raining. I don't know, there's a lot of weird shit going on. So there's probably like more than two or three
problems, but I was told they were going to get fixed today. So we'll see.
Alright, so let me...
I got $63,000. Should I get more photo storage or just save it?
I think I have to buy this to unlock the next couple of things to buy.
Alright, we'll save it. So let's go to sleep.
See what we get in the morning. See what new missions we get.
Yeah, apparently Valentine's Day broke a rain record. Like across
all of Vegas. It was raining everywhere. Alright, what do you got for me today?
Nothing, still on the same page in the book. Alright, head
we gotta get this. Yeah, we have to just get the herd.
The herd of gazelles and the zebra head.
Let's go take a look at the map. We need to take a photo of the herd of gazelles.
Look for a chance to capture as many gazelles as possible in one shot.
So let's just go. Let's not pick like a place.
I don't know why, but for one second I thought this just quit to my desktop and this was my desktop
background. I don't know why I thought that. I was like what the fuck, why are we on my desktop?
I don't know why. This is the standard Windows XP
background. Yeah, this is the
Dell computer background that has never changed in ten years.
Alright, let's take a picture of some gazelles. What is that? I don't know,
it looks like a cat. It's gonna be so blurry. Can I look at them?
Now this is, I was testing the white balance. That's what this photo is.
I'm not taking pictures of anything, I'm just testing the camera to make sure I have enough battery to take a picture.
It's a pretty nice big footprint. No, I need a better
camera. Can't take photos out of the window of a car.
Alright, where are these gazelles? I don't see a herd of gazelles anywhere.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, let's get set up. Should they be running? It wants a
stampede of gazelles, right? I gotta get as many as possible.
I gotta get back it up a little. That distance is bad. I got, I already
got it, I got it. I already got it. That's a good photo, but it's not a whole
herd. Alright, now make them run. I got it already, right? Alright, get it.
Why does this look like shit? There's something wrong about this photo. Why does this look
so off? No, get back in the car and drive me to where I need to go.
There's too much ground in that photo. That's exactly what it is. Alright, take me to the tree.
Okay, now I can walk a little further.
What constitutes a herd? Is a herd three or more?
At the umbrella tree. Three or more is a herd.
At least fifteen. Alright, this couple right here.
Let's get a little closer. Not bad, not bad. Turn, turn, turn, turn.
Tilt. One on the top left. Turn a little. How many grains
of sand is a beach? No, that's true. It's because of the sand that doesn't mean
it's a beach. No, it has to, I gotta go this way.
That's bordering on a goddamn ocean. Let me go over here.
I think I fucked up my opportunity to take a good picture. So they're getting the terrible one.
It's just for like a classroom, right? It's for students.
They don't need a National Geographic quality photo. They just need
a photo. Yeah, I scared them all off. There's one more down there.
Yeah, I blew it. Let's go. I'm gonna have to use that terrible one.
She probably stinks. What?
Watch out, watch out, watch out. Don't run them over. There's definitely no animal
run over physics. I would guarantee that's not the case. I got a photo
100 degrees and you can't shower.
You can like roll around in one of these little lakes.
One of these little ponds. You can just like roll around in it with some like Dove.
Just buy like his 25 pack of the Dove dog shit
brand. Get like a Lever 2000 or something.
It's probably like full. Don't, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop the car, stop the car,
stop the car, stop the car, stop the car, stop the car, stop the car,
stop the car. Come on, look over here. This is good.
This is good. There's a little too much tree. Bingo. There's the shot right there.
Maybe, hold on, one more, one more. It's not even in focus.
We'll get one like dead on too. Over here. Watch this shit.
This is gonna be fucking beautiful. It's gonna get a little bit of leaf,
a little bit of leaves in the foreground. I need a better lens.
Oh, fuck, there's another one. Look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look. This is perfect.
It's like a cat sitting on a tree. Come on, get the leaves. We need foreground,
mid-ground, background. No, no, this is not a good enough lens.
I can't do what I want to do. Whatever. None of those will work.
Do I actually have to have the car take me there? Smelly lady.
You don't know that. Oh, there is a Sony lanyard on her neck.
Now I understand why you guys saying Sony sponsor.
How was the safari? It was good. Okay, transfer those.
I don't care if one of the photos is terrible. Let's get an email going.
Head, a herd of gazelles. I don't know if we have that many.
It's only for 10,000. Who cares? Let's take a look.
I like that one. That one's pretty great. This is the best one.
No, sucks. Delete. I like it. It's quaint.
No, this one's good. Not good. Actually,
kind of good. This is not a bad photo. If only
that one in the, all the way far to the top right. If it was just two.
There it is. There it is. Okay. This photo's really bad, but it's the only one that's a
real herd. It has to be this one. Whatever.
I'll take the D-minus that I'm going to get for this photo.
I'm sorry. I'll take a C. Now we, ultimate big mouth. Didn't I already do this?
Oh yeah, these are done. Okay. Let's get the
picture of the, whatever it is in the tree.
Clearly this is, ah, this is clearly the best photo. Or this one. So let's just
give him a shitty one, because I want to hold on to a couple of these. Okay, this is like a very clear
I'm staring right in the camera picture, send it over. Marvelous. Marvelous.
Marvelous. Perfect score. Uh, that's a
vervet monkey adult. Uh, I need to delete some of these. Let's save
a couple of them. Not this one. Get rid of that. I like this one. Get rid of
this one. Get rid of this one. Keep that one. I like it. I don't,
all these can go. We already got the yawn done, so I'm going to keep the one that
I like. I like that one. Bad, bad, bad, bad.
No, keep turkey. Delete. So again, let's try
this again. X. X. X.
Check. Check all. X. I can't, like,
bring them over anywhere. They might just have to sit here. Unless, like,
there's something I'm missing. I need to buy the storage.
Really. First number you can hold to 50. Carry with your camera
without feeling, no, this is the camera. Yeah, that's the camera photo
still. Alright, let's go to bed.
Wake up in the morning. See what's on the list. I can't wait to do a tiger.
Don't forget to check your email. I do every day, man.
Important. Camera repairs complete. The camera you sent in
for repairs before your departure just came back. New camera.
It's a digital SLR camera. The A100 lens kit.
We've made arrangements so you can use it right away to take great photos for us, of course.
Okay, this is a tree monkey.
Tree monkey with a black face, okay. Hello, Francine. My name is David Moore.
I work with the African Photo Press. We're currently looking for a shot of a
vervet monkey climbing a tree. I already got one. I already do- it's done.
To fill out our wildlife photo collection. If you've taken any, could you send them my way?
If it's any help, vervet monkeys are often spotted where humans live. Good luck.
Already got it. Done. Good thing I held onto it. That's good.
That's a good photo, too. Done. Take it.
Thanks for the money. Cool. So now what?
Go back to bed. Let me go look at my camera, though.
A100. DT 18-70. F-stop is 3.55.
Cool. The camera we sent to the head office for repairs has come back.
Put it inside the camera case. You can check it any time. Proper focusing is key to using this camera.
Now the camera is set to autofocus. If you're not sure of a function,
consult the camera photography manual on the bookshelf.
So this is an autofocus camera. It's a body. Basic features intended
for amateurs. Get rid of that. An easy to use camera utilizing super
steady shot image stabilization and advanced autofocus.
Lens. Standard zoom lens mimics the human eye's field of vision for a true
perspective, not intended for long distance shots. There it is.
So it's just on there. All right. Are they getting new tools or anything?
Let's go look at the bookshelf. I want a Sony camera.
All right. We've got to look at some of this. A100. Full featured
camera, but you can always use auto mode if you want to keep things simple.
I never use auto on a camera. I always go to manual focus.
The A100 has four noteworthy features. The lenses are interchangeable.
You can introduce selective blur. You can greatly customize how you shoot.
Plus, it helps stabilize camera shake. I'll introduce each one of these
in a separate column. Focus. We've all seen autofocus photos
for the subject. You meant to take a picture of lines of blurred. You need to focus on your subject.
With the A100, you can focus by half pressing the circle button or the R1 button.
That's not going to be terrible. Pressure sensitive PlayStation 3
bullshit. Great. If you move the left stick around while doing so, you can even change the
angle. A half press to focus.
And you can move the stick around. Depth field.
Depth field contributes to how much of your scene, what range around the focus distance
remains sharp. It's also tied to a lens's zoom. Zooming in limits the depth of
field while zooming out increases it. Yes. I know that.
Now we've got a camera menu. Oh boy, we have an actual camera menu.
Open the camera menu button by pressing triangle. From the camera
menu, you can change various camera preferences in addition to trickier photography settings.
You can also set preferences for continuous shooting, image confirmation after you snap
a photo, shooting in black and white, and so on. So that's triangle.
Different exposures.
Four modes. Auto, aperture priority, shutter speed priority, and manual exposure.
And auto, snapping pictures is fully automatic. Or half
auto for the other two. Half manual modes. In manual, you set everything up yourself.
Advanced users though. That's what I will be using. Yep.
Aperture priority. Uh huh.
Narrow depth of field for a low value. So you get to like really get
really, really detailed motion blur moments.
So we want low aperture value. Shutter speed. This is a good, this is very educational.
All this is good stuff. Shutter speed is how much
the lens remains open. 1, 30th of a second, I'm on 1,000th
of a second for example. Slow shutter speed, you get more motion blur
while faster shutter speeds will freeze your subjects in its tracks.
A little motion blur can punch up your action shots though.
Am I going to be taking pictures of that? Okay. We're going to need a high
shutter. Yeah, this is exposure, right?
How do I do it? Use plus to take brighter photos
minus mimics to take darker. Okay, well how do I just, I guess, correct it?
Ice. Ice start AF.
Original features focuses for you automatically even if you don't half press the shutter.
Naturally this is very useful since the camera will continue to focus for you as long as you have the viewfinder open.
I'm going to just go through it. I know how to do this shit. Creative style. You can change it to
like sepia, black and white. Yep. With the
continue, you can hold down the circle button to continuously snap photos.
You can set this up in the feature settings.
You're limited to three shots in a row. You need to release
the button before you can shoot again. I'm ready. Let's take a look.
I gotta go back to bed, right? Yeah, back to sleep. I already handed in the
perfect monkey one. New emails? No. What's the thing I
haven't done? I have to get a photo of this zebra.
Close up in the face. Alright, let's go.
Is this fun? Yeah. This is a good game.
Having fun. It's fun to take pictures of animals. Now we have a camera that
I can actually toggle different settings. And we're only in the first area.
This is the home of the area up there with lions and tigers and shit.
Let's take a look at the camera. Here we go. Here's our new camera.
Let's go into the settings here. Exposure mode. Aperture priority.
Let's do manual. Shutter speed. Let's get like a high shutter.
No, actually not yet. This is like the aperture stop.
I really wish I could see the auto-review
on creative style. I wish I could see what it looks like without
getting too... Shutter speed's too long. Well, I'm trying to... You'll see.
I need a zebra. Alright. Can you stop? Let's go.
Wait, what? There's a cheetah? Don't get... Let me out of the car. Let me out!
Oh god, he's gonna be... I gotta get him like stalking. I'm getting some
pretty good shots already here. I shouldn't even need to bring the camera out. He's gonna be
running fast. Heard of gazelles. It's this time the prey got away.
We know that the cheetahs live on the... Yeah, well what the hell? Why wouldn't you let me get out of the car?
Are you ready to go? What? Hold on.
Why wouldn't you let me get out of the car before? Alright, is there a zebra around here?
Alright, there's no... I do not see a zebra. Look, a cheetah! Stay in the fucking
car! Yeah, let's go. Why do you keep
stopping me? Is that a zebra? Over there? There it is.
I'm gonna be too far away from him though. You do know we're on the mission to take a picture
of a zebra, right? Where are my binoculars? Where the fuck are the
zebras? We just drove in a circle. I didn't see one
zebra. He just wanted to show me the cheetah and then take me home.
I'm definitely gonna get an email about cheetahs.
Alright, we're home. That was fun. That was good to see the... I'm glad we got to see
the cheetah. Email me about it tomorrow. Hold on a minute.
Alright, let's get... let's make some fucked up shit happen here.
Oh, look! I got a picture of that! That's so funny. That's such a ridiculous
shutter. Alright, let me go get the email about the
fucking cheetah. That was great today, but I didn't do anything.
You drove around in a circle. You encountered cheetah? Well, I'll write up the report.
Go to bed. Nah, I don't want to transfer these photos. I'm just making a joke.
He's like trying to get in the photo. You know,
the aperture is bad, but it makes it kind of
good. If only the shutter wasn't so stupid and I didn't have like a photo bomb
here. I think I'm gonna have to keep this one. No, no, no, no.
Okay, just go to bed. I'm gonna take a picture of a cheetah
stalking prey tomorrow or something, right? Okay, we got a new email
that's gonna be about a cheetah. Just you wait. Hunting at 60 miles
per hour. Mm-hmm. This is Peter O'Brien over at
National Geographic. Next month's feature is about hunters of the savanna.
And we want to talk about how cheetahs hunt. We'd like you to handle the photography.
The cheetah tears after its prey at 60 miles an hour.
You only get one moment to take the shot. It's an important job, but I know you're up to it.
This is apparently one of the harder difficulty ones.
I only get one chance. I didn't get a picture of a cheetah. Okay.
So I'm gonna save it here because I should.
And I'm also gonna go to the bathroom. So I'm gonna say it's gonna take, by the time this is done,
I'll be back. So let me just take a piss break. I'll be right back.
See you guys in a second. Alright. Have we saved? Good.
Alright. We've been asked to photograph a cheetah. Could you try to find that cheetah
again? This one's up to you. Hope you can get that perfect picture.
Did I accept the mission? Make sure I just accepted it.
Yeah. So do I need to take a photo of it killing something?
Or take a photo of it when it's about to kill something?
I'm gonna have to drop the shutter too. And do a burst photo. 60 miles per hour
I get one second. A photo of it about to kill you.
Take a selfie while being eaten at 60 miles per
fresh beer. I'm gonna say that every fucking time.
Looking for a cheetah. Let's try the ant hill. There was a cheetah in that area
before. Let's get in here. Continue shooting on
standard. Let's see what's going on here.
Let's see those photos. It's going too fast. Can I drop it?
Can I drop that? I couldn't go
up to these values before. I could not pick these before.
They're dark. I gotta bring the... Hold on.
We gotta open up the fucking eye a little bit here.
Is that gonna help? Nah. Fuck. We need exposure composition.
Exposure. Exposure plus one.
Fuck. The shutter's too high. It's too high.
Let's try this. It's not terrible. Let's try that.
320.
That looks okay. That looks okay. Alright. That doesn't look bad.
Adjust the aperture. God damn. I gotta do full manual here.
That's as much as I can go. I can't do exposure.
I gotta do it on shutter speed priority. Three and a half is as far as I can get it.
That doesn't look terrible. Okay. Nobody home at the anthill.
Let's try the oasis. Oh fuck. I have two. I gotta get
rid of these. How do I delete these? We're good. We're good. We're good.
The aperture cannot go lower than 3.5 on this camera.
Looking over there. Shooting. Auto review.
Those look cool. Let me make sure this...
Now that's gonna be fine. Not gonna be blurry before the
cheetah. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Stop the car. Stop the car. Stop the car.
Stop. Stop the car. Why can I not tell you to stop the car?
Get me off the rails. Why?
I wanna stop. It's an opportunity to get a picture of a zebra. Fuck. I'm gonna get one
opportunity and I'm gonna blow this. I got three shots continuously
in a row. As long as I can get a decent one I'll be fine. No sign of a cheetah.
You try to spot a cheetah using the binoculars.
Okay. I'm just gonna drive through the animals.
I don't see a cheetah. I don't even need to use the binoculars. This is Star Wars music.
It is. You're right. It is Star Wars music. This is specifically like
Obi-Wan. The crescendo of this is every time
Obi-Wan does a gigantic force front flip or back flip
onto another ledge. I'll give you an example here.
There he goes. He swings the lightsaber.
There's the back flip. Up. Maybe two levels above the enemy.
And he stays there and looks down and turns his lightsaber off.
And then turns around and he goes down another direction. So it's always a back flip or a front flip.
I just wanna look for a fucking cheetah. What the fuck is this cheetah?
Cheetah! Oh aren't those... What?
That's a cheetah right there. Isn't that a cheetah? That's not a cheetah.
Cheetah. Oh look they're... Oh you're just saying the things that I point the camera at.
Found it! Cheetah! Cheetah! Cheetah! There it is.
Okay I gotta get ready. Alright set it up. I got one chance.
Can I bring this into Photoshop later and fuck with it or no? Looking up at prey on top of the anthill.
It might start a chase. Let's get closer.
It has its eyes on a Thompson's gazelle.
Because you can't really make sure you have enough photos left. I'll follow along
Let's try when the cheetah starts running. Get that perfect shot.
Big game number one. Snap a cheetah hunting. Is the camera gonna already be open?
I only have like three seconds to get this correct.
This is not the cutscene anymore. Where is he? Where's the cheetah?
What are you doing? Oh! Look at that one.
You really have to do that? Is he three times?
That is not the best one. That's not the best one.
Looks like they're doing a conga line. This one sucks.
That was one fantastic hunt. You must have gotten some great photos.
There's no blood. Now this game was to
educate children how to use cameras. Specifically from Sony.
Got it. Ready to go home. Now if you see
a zebra, stop the car.
So I can get that too. Where are all the explosions?
This game is bullshit. Where are the fucking TIE fighters?
Zebras? I'm never gonna get that close with a zebra's face.
Put on different music. I can't put on custom music.
No! We have to deal with the same Star Wars track
over and over again. You're just watching your favorite scene.
You're watching the General Grievous scene over and over again.
In fact, I think he does it in the General Grievous scene.
No, it actually happens in that scene. Let's see.
It's not gonna be a copyright problem. Don't worry. I just need to get to the one part that I think is gonna happen.
Give me a sec. Let's get it on screen.
And here it comes.
Where is it? Come on. He jumps down. Does he jump
up? Why is this big backflip that he does up? I know
what happens. Here, look. I'll show you. You've never seen Star Wars before
than just fucking whatever.
No, no. I can't play this. I gotta stop this now. Stop.
No, no. That was less than ten seconds. Okay, hold on. Where's the jump? Update your
mic. Here it comes. Here we go.
I'm not gonna get in trouble. That was like five seconds.
I sorta fucking sneeze of the movie. We were looking for when he jumps
backwards or forwards and he jumps forwards. I'm not gonna get in trouble.
I showed fucking four seconds of a movie that came out like forty years ago.
Twenty years ago. There are people that like stream
all the Harry fucking Potter movies on Twitch. I don't think we have to be
concerned about like eight seconds. Like you can find like
whole fucking movie streams. Like super illegal movie streams.
Watching like all the Lord of the Rings. Let's see what we got.
Your best shot. Really? The one. Let's reply.
Which one? How is that not a good shot? This is great.
This is like showing the kill. Doesn't really fell over.
That one's good. Apparently they think it's this one. The first one.
I guess is the better one. He was then laid a band from Twitch.
For those four seconds of copyright material. We're gonna use this one. This is the one
that the video game is determined is the best one so I'm gonna use it.
That's pretty good. Yeah we got the algorithm in our favor.
I still need to do this one. I got a lot of money. I should buy something.
I'm just hoarding all of my cash right now. For no reason.
Unless eventually I can buy something better. But what does this frame do?
Put the, say for a ten foot lens.
I mean we could. What did the client think about the photo you sent them, Princey?
Well we crossed a milestone in our survey. We should get some rest.
Alright, hold on, hold on. I'm buying it.
I hung up the photo frame in the back. Perfect!
Let's see what the new task is. Sending map of new research area.
We have taken a detailed map of the wetlands adjacent to the Duma step.
In the area they refer to them as the Kiboko Swamp.
The rich water supply draws a number of animal inhabitants.
Especially those who thrive along the water's edge. Please focus your efforts in this new area starting today.
I'm literally turning, I'm getting, I'm like sixty.
I used to never have to have this problem.
When you get like a little older, it shit just happens man. I can't, I just, I'm old.
I'm getting older. You ever listen to the noises your fucking grandfather makes?
When he's just sitting there?
He's got like his hands together and he's just got his thumbs down and he's just like sitting there just relaxing.
And all of a sudden he just goes like...
I don't know what that's like. I get it now.
Sometimes I'll just be like...
I understand.
Please focus your efforts on this new area starting today.
Wait actually, I can send an email to Cheetah.
Any new animal is just three thousand dollars. Let's get a good one here of the Cheetah.
No, no. What the hell is that?
That's good. That's a good photo, but it's not of a Cheetah.
Unfortunately I have to use one of the ones.
One of these ones here. Like this one.
This one's probably good. Or that one. I'll do this one.
Framing's pretty terrible, but whatever. I'm gonna get the money anyway. Nevermind.
Alright, it's time to explore the wetlands. I can join you in the field starting today.
It took you like five days. Let's head to the swamp.
A zoomer streamer pukes on keyboard. Am I not a zoomer?
I'm not a boomer either. I am a
millennial. He's a zoom beanie.
I'll drive us to the Kiboko Swamp.
Francine, you just take the backseat and enjoy the sights.
Where's James? You drive like shit. Can I please bring James back?
We gotta go back and change some shit here. Enjoy the sights.
I wonder if I can get some cool shots here.
Just in case something crazy happens.
Is this that Vive game he was talking about? No, the reason I didn't do Vive today is because
I did not know if I was even going to be able to stream.
I didn't want to have a scenario where I can turn the stream on and the internet's
still fucked up. But I'm like all set up in a Vive VR room.
And the stream goes down in like 45 minutes.
I figure I would do this today and then do the Vive
hopefully tomorrow if his internet still works. I don't know. It's going to be tough
because it seems that we're having other issues too with
how our bandwidth is being split between
because Italics is here as well. So it's almost like we have two computers running
at the same time. One just can kill the other now.
So I don't know why. So I don't know. We might have to do a situation where
we try to take turns using the broken internet.
We'll have to figure that out. Hopefully it just works because it seems to be working now.
I thought that was a Twitch logo.
I think he tried to do something on the internet and that's
when we dropped like a thousand, two thousand frames. Weird. I don't know.
I can't explain it. The map from the head office indicates that Keeq Boko Swamp
lies this way. Let's go. And it's definitely not a problem with any of our
equipment because we've had the same shit for four months.
And we haven't really had a problem that we had to deal with this before.
All this shit started three days ago when the whole internet just
cut off, turned off to zero. And then I was told by
people at Cox that we have like a packet loss problem
and they were going to fix it and they were going to work on it. I don't know. Maybe they're still doing that.
We're getting some fallout from the weather maybe. I don't know.
We're just going to try. We're going to do what we can do. That's all we can do.
All right. What an incredible sight we're at the swamp.
That's a nice photo. That photo was terrible but that was a nice looking photo.
Any other animals in the swamp?
Eric follows the GPS into a lake.
That climbing shrub is called a water tree.
That tree looks like an easy one to climb. We're going to climb the tree.
Climb a tree to conceal yourself from the animals.
I'm not going to get the equipment to go up here. I'm just going to drive by it.
See Francine, this right here is a lake. It's a swamp.
The swamp is much larger than I expected. Why don't you take the wheel from here?
Why don't I take the wheel from here? What? I have to drive the car now.
How do I drive it? Just went up a whole letter grid.
What do you want me to do? Can I dump them?
What do you want me to do? Take the wheel to do what?
I can't take any pictures. Look, I could have gotten those swans.
I'm going to climb the tree?
This looks like a battery powered toy car.
It does look like a power wheel. What the fuck am I looking for?
I'm just up on a tree. What are we doing this for?
Here we go. Fly right down into me.
Fly down, down, down, down, right into me.
Not terrible. A lot of birds.
These photos are not very good.
Let me take a look at that one. That might be the best photo I've taken.
It was a snap. Look at the background.
Look at his wings are a little bit out of focus. What his beak is.
Great photo. What about all the birds?
I think there's more than one.
Take a selfie. Selfies didn't exist.
This game came out in 2008. Selfies were not a thing that made any sense.
Selfies did not exist.
There was no picture camera that you could hold in your hand and turn that way.
I can get closer than that. Just T-Posed.
Right here. Slow down.
Right there. That's the one.
I had it. It was close.
Eric! Eric!
Where's Eric? Where's the car?
No! Do I get to keep my photos?
That picture of the
bird is gone.
That was the best picture I've ever taken.
Camping tent. Spend the night in the field and get an early start the next morning. An outdoorsman's best friend.
That sucks. That actually sucks.
I'm going to buy it. Let's get the tent. Why does the buffalo wipe the camera?
I don't know. I'm so disappointed right now.
Why would Eric save the photographer and not the photos?
At the end of the day, I matter not the footage.
Buffalo took the SD card. No, I think it's what it's implied.
Because your camera gets stomped. Those are some good photos too.
What? Why?
We've got to go back to the wetlands. I need to go explore and take some good photos.
Go get revenge. What? Go run over the buffalo.
I've got to go get my SD card back.
We can't flip the car, right? Where is this heading?
This is a different zone too. Heading towards...
I've got to get my souls back. I'm glad I actually had to drive though.
That was annoying. Having to wait for someone to drive you around.
At what point does Eric start to say...
Watch out! Hey now, watch your driving!
There it is. Please don't do that.
That's Jay Leno, by the way.
I might as well put the chicken in my head around.
Let's find a place to stop. I can't believe I lost the picture.
The gull. The pelican.
Or the swan. Or the flamingo.
One of the birds have the weird long sock necks.
Get out of the car. Let's get a good one from far away.
Wait, wait, wait.
I've got to get closer, otherwise I have to drop the aperture.
That's one drinking right there.
I've got to get closer. Do not get fucking killed again over this.
Not bad. I've got the fucking photo I need.
What are you doing? That's too dark. He's going manual!
It's too dark. I'm not sticking around. I've got what I needed.
Now I've got to get a couple photos of...
Can I take a photo right now if the car has stopped? Or do I have to get out of the car?
This guy's not going to knock the Jeep over, is he?
I need to get the birds.
I'm so pissed off that I lost those.
Hey, is this the streamer that photographed a wild buffalo on manual?
Not yet. He has a driver's ed brake.
I think that's what's going on.
The head office hasn't sent us maps for this area yet.
I've got the buffalo. I need the flying birds. Can I climb these trees?
I'm going to take the fucking pictures all over again.
Let's get this back up.
The birds are going to be flying around. I need some good speed.
Climb tree. Can I only climb certain trees?
Is that what I'm missing here? I can't climb this?
I guess I can. Why the hell not?
What tree should I go to, then? What happened to the Jeep?
I was going to say, what? How does it camouflage?
Let's try the other tree. This one down here. The big ones, probably.
I did different gazelles.
I'm going to get up in that tree right there. That's a good spot.
Climb trees.
Can I not climb the tree unless he tells me to climb the tree?
Is there one tree I can get on? I don't think I can get on any tree but the one in the middle.
What about this one? I don't see a prompt or anything.
Nice FPS, bro!
There's a hole in that one.
I'm going in the tree.
Why am I doing this?
Do I live here now? Am I baiting somebody out?
I'm hiding here. What am I hiding from?
This one has horns. Gotta get closer.
Just in case you run away, let me get one. I'm just bored in this venue.
Some of those were good. Now I just need the bird.
Go get in the tree. That's why we shoot raw.
I really wish I had a picture of one of the gulls but I don't.
I can probably get a shitty picture of one of these birds.
I get it. I know, I know. You don't have to hold down the fucking instructor break.
Just get a zoom in.
It looks like shit. I don't even care. I just have to get them collected.
Whatever. I want to do another one of those cheetah missions. That was really cool.
The cheetah mission only gave you a certain amount of time.
What happened to the Star Wars music? That's true.
It kind of just disappeared. Why did the music disappear? I couldn't tell you.
I have no idea. That was music for James.
It took a long time to load that. Area secured, we got this one.
Back to the camp. I honestly don't even know where the camp is.
There it is. You don't get stuck like this. I don't even know where the save point was.
Get up there. This is really
electrical powered. Four by four.
Can we get out of the car? Hey, thanks. Whoa, somehow we pulled free.
Wow. Thank you World of Warcraft Game Master.
Appreciate that. Now I got stuck in Iron Forge again.
How do I go back to camp? It's starting to get dark.
Can we get out of the car? End. Okay, here we go.
End Safari. Oh my god. You can just teleport.
This is so bad. Which one's worse?
That's pretty good. That's not so good.
Neither is that. This one is good. That one's really good.
I'd say this is the one I'm going to send. I'm not looking for good scores, I just want to have the database.
So I get the mission to do it. There's a Pelican. I got it right.
That one's good. Three grand. I'll take it.
That's an Impala. What else we got? The buffaloes, right?
These are different. This is the male and female, right?
Oh, this is different. Bad angle. Why is this a bad angle?
We got the buffaloes. The one that's the most in focus is the one over there.
To the left. You can take this one.
African Buffalo. Are there any others? I don't think so.
I got the gull. I'm going to hold on to these though.
This one in particular. Get rid of the shitty ones.
Get rid of all the shitty buffalo ones. What is this? A bush.
Just get rid of this one too. Hold on to these ones because I like them.
Got to keep that one. And that looks good.
Alright. Go to bed. See if I actually have a mission tomorrow.
Check the email. There we go. Whoa, that's a lot.
Photo for nature power. Could you get a giraffe at eye level?
What? How are you tree climbing skills? I've got a job for you.
I need a close up of a giraffe's face, but not just any close up. I kind of
promised my boss I'd get him a shot taken from tree level. Can you bail me out?
If I can climb a tree, maybe. Hello Francine.
My name is Javi Salgado and I represent NINP Publishing.
It's a pleasure to meet you. We plan to introduce readers to the African Buffalo
in one of our upcoming magazines. You think you could provide a photo? Try and get as close to a
vicious buffalo as you can. We want a tense shot.
You saw what happened last time. You're familiar with an animal called the impala.
Each male is what you might call a player. He forms a harem
of multiple females.
Photograph one of these harems. Look for the male's magnificent horns and please
make sure both male and female are in frame. What's this for?
Am I just going to send this to this guy? Oh hey, can you show that? That's for me.
It doesn't say what it's for. Yeah, there's no official reason
for these photos. Okay, well whatever.
A giraffe at eye level is more interesting. I'm going to take this one first. And then we're looking for
what we can get that. We still need a close up of a zebra's face.
I don't think we're going to get that though. Let me get this.
Find a tree we can climb. Well, interestingly enough,
I think the internet has been incredibly stable. So cross your
fingers that today's test stream
can carry us into tomorrow and the next day. Hopefully.
I wasn't even going to stream today. I was going to just not do it.
It looks like we might be good to go. Who just drove in front of my car?
Oh my god. Why are you doing this to me?
You thought this was going to be a transition into five? Well, I can't really do that right now.
Because I have to set the room up again. I had to bring all my
shit back in here until I sit down at my desk. That's...
This is not going to happen tonight. Tonight was really just to make sure that the stream
could be on for more than two or three hours. Like I got to set up my lighthouses back here again.
Yeah, Vive is a total commitment. And I have to be certain
that it's possible too. I need a tree. Because once I go in
that thing, I had a conversation with a talc about it earlier today.
It's like, oh, am I going to stream Vive today? Well, maybe the internet might not work.
I have to fucking take a gigantic robot outfit and
put lighthouses all over my room and the stream turns off in 45 minutes.
I'm just going to be like, well, that was fucking dumb. Can I even climb this tree?
Let me just make sure I can climb the trees here. How do you determine if you can climb
a tree? Yeah, I saw there was tons of recommendations
for VR. There's so many things to do.
It's actually kind of overwhelming how many fucking Vive games there are
that I haven't played. Mind Show is the number one.
And I'm not even certain I'm going to do that tomorrow. Or the next day,
depending again on how this internet works out.
Where are the giraffes? I gotta go to like a pool somewhere.
If you don't know what Mind Show is, Mind Show is a VR game.
It's not really a game, it's more of an experience. Where you
get into the VR shit
and you make scenes and make your own movie. TV show
skit thing. It's very much like you control
the movies in a way, the sets,
the set pieces. I'm really looking forward to it. Alright, here we go.
That's a tree I can get in. There's a
microphone built into the Vive too, which I didn't even know. So that's going to be
really interesting. Alright, stop freaking out, I'm fine.
No, no, no, no, don't run away. I just need to get your eye level in your face. This one didn't
run. This one didn't run. The Vive mic sucks.
Yeah, but it might be fun to use it. Because my microphone setup is really
not like the best in regards to standing in a room.
Can you tell me I can't get in this tree? I can definitely get on this tree. I have
to be able to. Look at this, it's perfect. Alright, what the hell was that?
How am I going to get this? I gotta be right in their face?
This is not like right in their face. He's got to get much closer. Just throw
the camera. God damn it, turn around. I wonder if they'll come over to the tree and eat.
Get the zebra picture too.
Yeah, I'm trying to be as prepared as possible.
Because I know there's a lot of things that can go wrong
in VR streaming. So I'm making sure to make sure
the room is set up completely perfect. The games I'll have
work. I'm just fucking happy the internet works.
I have to have patience now. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, I don't.
You just turn your head this way.
That should be alright. Turn this way. Come on, turn your head this way. Do it.
No, my fucking zoom. He's coming this way. Turn,
turn, turn your head. I think I got it. Let's take a look.
I didn't have time to mess with settings there. I had to go to auto.
Here it is. It could be that one though. That one's good too.
It's probably this one. Or this one.
I should have done vertical. Yeah, shit, you're right. I'm going to stay here.
He'll come back. I always use manual. Well, I got a real camera.
Not a video game camera. Let's try it again.
I do realize now this stream is just me taking photos of animals. Look at that one.
You get the little one and you get the big one. Opportunity here. Hold on.
Stay there. No, you idiot. You just ruined the whole thing.
This would have been so cute. Go. Move. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's off. It's all fucked up. Doesn't matter.
I could have got his face. Please move out of the way so I can get this. I'm going to have to crop you out.
Nice. Nice work. Thanks a lot.
Do what you want. Go over there. Dickhead. Do that on purpose.
No, no, no. Wait. Stop. Stop. This is perfect. Go to auto. I don't care.
No black and white. This is the one.
Turn. Turn. Turn your head. Turn your head this way.
Oh, it's not good.
It was close, but not great. Maybe you'll do it.
One. I'm going to turn up the... hold on. Because he's going to turn his head
and I'm going to get it right when he turns. It's not going to be blurry.
Watch this. He's going to turn and I'm going to get it right when he's mid-turned. Get the camera right here.
Snap it when he gets out.
He's basically going to cross the plane here. Why is this black and white? What the fuck?
I didn't do that. Turn slightly.
You went the wrong way. God damn it. If he had turned this way.
Look, it's like you're riding him. I got it. I got it. I think this one's fine.
Let me just... I got a secret bird.
This is a secret bird any day. I like that one. Secret bird.
See how cute that would have been if I had that framed up and all three of them were there.
That would have been such a great picture. Thank the dumb zebra that screwed it all up.
Somebody just gave me $100.
100 bucks. Cyclops Parker, thanks for the $100.
10,000 bits. Shit load.
They say, hey Jeremy, I've been watching you for years now, but I can rarely catch the streams live.
To be here, just wanted to help keep you doing what you do.
Thank you so much, Cyclops Parker. That's fucking incredible. Thank you.
If you can't catch it, as long as, you know, if you want to
jump in when you can, and you feel like being here, that's...
You're not under any obligation to come to every stream, but I really appreciate it.
If you come here and you're happy, that's fucking awesome. Thanks for stopping in.
And thank you for the $100. So I got that photo.
It's covering the fees. No, no, that's incredibly fucking generous
and nice of anybody to give that much money, or even any amount of money.
So, thank you. Do I have another opportunity for a fucking secret bird?
Did you see that? I missed it. I want to get a close-up
of that bird. Oh, I'll get you, motherfucker. Just you wait.
I would have had three there. This is just so relaxing. Why don't they make another one
of these, somebody? Make like an incredibly detailed version of this.
Just go do it in real life. I can't do this.
A VR game where you do this. Does that exist? If it does,
I'm gonna play it. All right, here we go. There's another opportunity for a
decent one. Damn it. I'm gonna run into
the photos here, if I'm not careful. I got it, I got it, I got it. Let's get the zebra face.
And then move on. German spells too bad to do this. What the hell are you talking about?
I don't know if that's gonna fly here. I don't know if that's gonna work.
Closer? How close can I get? Don't overdo it.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that.
And when I say drop it, I mean raise it. Are you gonna walk forward?
I'll get this on auto. Oh, great. I think that's gonna be fine.
That'll be worth it, I think. Let's get out of here.
Got the giraffe, I got his face. Let's go. Back to base camp.
Apparently there's first person too. I just figured that out right now. Somehow.
Let's see, transfer the photos in. Some good ones.
Alright, giraffe at eye level. I don't have a lens that's good
enough to do this, but it's close enough. It's this one right here, right?
Yeah, that's eye level. Loving Fox
just gave six community subs. Thank you, Loving Fox. Thank you for the
six. How is that target not more than great?
Because his head is tilted a little too much, apparently.
Now, here we go. Is this good enough? I don't know, like
that's as best as I'm gonna get with this lens. Really?
Okay. This one is the, get a close up of an African
buffalo. Try and get as close to a vicious buffalo as you can with looking for a dynamic
really tense shot. I gotta know where the car is.
The car is gonna be right behind me. And this one is already here. Wait,
secret bird. Bingo. Is there a better one?
That's pretty good. The superb starling adult.
Alright, let's go get killed by a buffalo. Use the brushes cover.
Can I just do it now? No, I gotta go to bed.
I love the plane sound effect when you email pictures.
We might have more to do though, let's see.
Where's the wall here? Play another game.
This is the plan. This is the game that I wanted to play for a little while.
I'm just hanging out and playing it. We are on the PlayStation 3, so even if there was
something else I wanted to do, I would have to kind of set up
something else and not capture my PlayStation 3.
And there's nothing really that's ready to go right this second, because remember, I didn't even know the stream was gonna happen today.
So I knew that I had this game, and that if I could stream I was
gonna try it. So this stream was not really supposed to happen.
But I'm so glad it did, because now I know that the internet works.
And I'm stuck.
I just want people to be aware that's why I'm just playing a
take photos of animals safari game.
There's a lot of vibe shit to do, but like I said before, I just want to make sure that I'm able to
stay alive for more than 5 fucking hours.
What happened there? Alright, tense buffalo close up of a buffalo's angry face.
Is it possible to roll the car? No, you can't roll the car and you can't run over any animals.
Sorry everybody. I don't know why I have to apologize for that.
That should be like, oh that's good that you can't do that. I gotta pick a beeline for the car.
After getting this picture. After we get this photo though, there's probably gonna be another
super mission. I'm glad you can't hurt the animals. That's what I was saying.
I wasn't saying I'm sad that I can't run them over.
This is a pretty good sit on the couch and have your mouth open game though.
It definitely is. I would play this game
with like a niece or a nephew and be like, oh can you, I don't see, do you see the buffaloes
anywhere? Right there! Oh you're right, you're right, yeah!
Should we go take a photo? He's a boomer uncle.
What's wrong with that? What's wrong with being like an uncle? That's not a problem.
That kinda hurt my head. Anything that's like boomer
to a lot of you guys apparently. How do I not be
like a quote boomer? What if I told you guys I eat like candy?
Okay, so if I ate a bunch of candy it was in the first grade, why
would I still be a boomer? Yes. You were born in 1985.
I know, but what if I wasn't? I went to the
dentist today. What a boomer. Teeth health is a boomer thing?
Where the fuck are these buffaloes? What kind of question is that?
Where did it go? Oh!
Okay, come here. Those are elephants. I found elephants.
They just woke the fuck up now. Hey, if you're watching and you were like kind of drifting off
and like hanging out and not excited about this scream because it's just kind of a chill scream.
Wake! Wake up! Time to get up!
Never mind, go back to bed. Sorry I woke you up for that.
That bunch of people probably did just like wake up from just like taking, they kind of drifted off.
It was an invisible wall to hide the elephants apparently.
Well, I got photos of them.
I thought they were buffalo at first. Well, that's like the edge of the universe right there.
The edge of the universe. Stop. No, no.
Stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay, stay. Not fast enough. Hold on.
They're gonna land. Right here. Fuck. I gotta get a good
swampy moss photo with some red eyes.
Whatever. Oh, you keep coming in right when I stop doing that.
Whatever. I'll never get the perfect photo again.
Turn. Is someone coming in? I have to stay in the same spot.
This guy's gonna turn around and fly back overhead. Yeah, I'm fishing for shots. It sucks.
You have to let the wildlife come to you. You can't go to the wildlife.
Eventually just aim your camera out your window. Eventually a rhino will
walk by. You have to do it for a long time. Come on.
Somebody turn. We got one coming in right here, don't we? Did it turn? I don't think so.
No, they're all flying this way. Hold on. I'm in a bad place.
Bad spot. God damn it. Wait. I don't even know what that is.
Let me find them. Let me do the mission at hand here. Let's find the
buffalo. Chad has voted to adjust Jerma's height to
three feet. I love how that's an adjustment.
That's an adjustment. Alright, here we go. We need an aggressive shot. Keep the
engine running. Here we go. He's gonna turn around and run directly behind me.
An angry face. Okay. Get close enough.
He's gonna get close. Wait till he gets closer.
Okay, hold on. Not tense enough. He needs to be angry.
Okay, here we go. Ready? One. Holy fuck.
That's a great one. Get in the car. Oh, that was good.
Get me out of here. I gotta take a look at that one.
That's gotta be worth some money. This thing was about to kill me.
That was a great one. I said that really fucking weirdly. I wanna hear how I said that.
That was really strange. Okay, here we go. Ready? One.
Holy fuck. That's a great one. I said that weird, right?
Something about that was off. I don't know why.
Alright, let's get out of here. Australian accent.
Fuck. That's a great one, Mike.
That is a good one, though. I tell you.
That's my normal voice.
If I sound like that? Take your photo. This better get in the magazine.
Marvelous. Marvelous. All marvelous.
That's bullshit. How would I get closer?
Are you trying to make this photographer die? How would you get closer than I did?
I was seconds away from being killed. That's not close enough, apparently.
Congratulations! Published in the magazine Nature Power.
Check the bookshelf to view your own published photos.
Nice. Okay, what about this one? We had a picture of elephants, right?
Some weird fucking bird. Who cares? Just give me the money.
For the record, that's a better photo than the almost-dying charging buffalo.
What else am I missing here?
Did I get these already? I don't think so. Yeah, I already had a picture of them.
I do have the distance elephants. This is such a bad photo
of elephants, but you know what? I just want the data.
The distance is terrible, but it's okay. African elephant, African elephant.
Alright. Cool. Let me go look at my published work.
Let's see. National Geographic. Let's take a look inside. Let's find our photos.
Monthly Nature Power. The African buffalo
are grazers eating grass and leaves off trees. Those are real photos
and then mine's a fake one. Imagine you wouldn't get away
with that. This is a real magazine. Very clearly,
the one on the left is not real. I'm trying to pull that off.
It's a computer-generated image. Somebody's not going to pick up on that?
That's a great picture. I'm shitting on the PlayStation 3 graphics.
No, I'm saying that the photos on the right are real photos.
This could be on the PS4. This could be on
a GTX 2080 of max settings
on the Frostbite engine, and that's still not a real buffalo over there.
The real photos look worse. They don't look worse.
Hang that one on the wall, but I can't take this one down.
This is me and my friend. I can't do that.
Let's take a look. We should have news. Here we go. Big ticket item.
Need a shot of the herd's top trumpet.
I can't. This is strange for me to say this, but I can't tell.
Is that video playing here on the right? Claimation.
It feels like it's stop-motion. The background doesn't look real.
That's not claimation going on? Wait, no. Look at the end.
Watch the end. It's over-animated. That's not real.
All right, take the... Each African elephant herd has a boss who holds it together.
Could you take a photo of one? That background's not real.
That's not a real background. That's on a set. That's a set somewhere. Look at the clouds. Look behind them.
They manufactured that. I'll be right. That's fine.
It's like a narcissistic thing to say.
So how do you tell the difference between a boss and the others?
They battle to determine who gets the position. The winner must have a certain qualities.
Fierce-looking tusks, for example.
So big tusks. We've got to find the big boss. I can't do that.
Okay. Also, this is real. That looks real to me.
I'm working as a photographer lately trying to steal my business. Just kidding.
There's a bird called the cattle egret. They travel with large herbivores as a rule.
I got those requests for a photo for a cattle egret.
An African elephant together. But I'm too busy. Think you can get the shot for me?
Take a look at that way that elephant looks.
And the background and the foreground. Look at the claymation.
I'm fucking out of here. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
If only they'd come a little closer. Let's continue to observe the herd.
The pond with the anthill will be the perfect place to watch them from.
I saw them already.
I have to save the game. I'm sorry. I'm going to spend like five minutes saving this.
Game sucks. Please play I spy spooky mansion again.
I like this. I'm not going to do this for that much longer.
This is the internet test stream. Don't you guys understand?
There it is. Bingo. I've been playing for five hours?
I've only been playing for like four? Three and a half?
Remember I spent 30 minutes creating my character. That doesn't really count as playing.
Play space channel five. I want to watch Ulala. I have it.
But I can't do that.
Because that would require me to take down the PS3.
And hook up and plug everything in and get everything set up for the Dreamcast.
Which the Dreamcast is in the closet right now.
I've got to make sure the audio works.
Hold on a second though. I've got to show you this.
This came in the mail. Something finally came in the mail.
Something people have been waiting for for a while.
Me too. I had some issues with the mail.
Where are they? They finally came in. I'm going to finally prove that I own this.
Because everybody is so annoyed at me for not proving that I own this.
That's right. The Seaman webcam. There it is.
The Seaman microphone. I got it.
So we can actually play that game. What's wrong with it? I look weird.
Get that off. Yeah it actually came.
We demand Pikachu socks. I don't even know if that is.
I look like I've made it a clay. Do I? Am I claymation?
I do look like I made it a clay. Am I real?
I made it a clay today. I don't know why. I got a greasy face.
That's just a clay drive. Relax. What the fuck was I doing?
Now I'm going to be so self-conscious. Forever. Forever.
Look what you've done to me. Look what you've done.
You're in a room. It's like a dark room.
And all of a sudden TVs turn on. Two TVs back to back.
You had one second. Which one of these is clay?
I'm going to do the same motions as the elephant.
I'll do it for you. Ready? Which one of those is clay?
Stand up and do it. I'm not fucking standing up and doing that.
Not a chance. That's just old. Why are you putting the fucking birthing
scene from Outlast 2? Why would you put that here? I don't know why that's there.
What was that shit-eating grin? I made it a fucking clay. I gotta get out of here.
I'm not on camera ever again. Can I get a haircut? I can't.
I can't get a haircut. Why would I get a haircut?
It's a shitload of blood vessels. Each individual hair is a blood vessel.
I don't want to be caught up in bleed and shit.
German alternative facts are fucking out of hand.
Alright, what's the deal here? I need to get an elephant.
I gotta get the boss of the elephant. Does your hair have nerve endings? No.
They just bleed and it's weird. When you snip the ends of one hair
of blood, two or three droplets come out of each strand.
I hate going to the barber. I hate going to the dentist. I hate going to the doctor.
Is it really going to stop me? Can I just go to the wetlands please?
Don't you guys know the golden rule of this stream?
How are you guys losing the golden rule of this stream? Treat others
the way that you would like to be 95% of everything I say is
a lie. Alright, elephant.
If 90 to 95% of everything you say is bullshit
and just made up, then what about all the times when you say
things that are really nice and you're not messing around? So everything you say is
a lie? Well think of how many dumb fucking things I say.
I'd probably say a hundred stupid things being broadcasted.
Five of those things would definitely be legit.
Where are the elephants? They're all on the edge.
How am I going to get to snap the elephant boss when I can't even
go over to see them? They're all down there. I can't go over
there. How do we know that wasn't a lie? I don't know.
I heard of African elephants coming this way. I heard it's on the move.
Alright, they're looking for the one with the big tusks.
The king of the elephants, right?
Which one of these is the boss? It says you can tell because they start
fighting and they have big tusks. One of the little ones is
probably the boss. Well, this is not a Looney Tunes cartoon.
So I'm going to say the answer to that is probably no. Is that the leader?
That's the one that's leading everybody here. That could be the one.
What about boss baby? No. That's like a meme
answer. You know, boss baby is currently like a funny
meme right now, right? That's not a bad shot of all the elephants.
This one has to be the leader. They're all following the leader. I'm not going to get run
over, right? Yeah, this has to be the leader. Why would they all be following this
one elephant here? Unless I'm missing something. This one has like a broken
tusk. This one's been in a bunch of fights. I'm going to say it's probably this one.
The one in the back? The one in the back has huge tusks. Wait, wait, wait.
It actually might be the one all the way in back. See how big the tusks are on that one?
See look, ready? This one has a kind of broken tusk. That one has gigantic
teeth. Much bigger than anybody else. It's definitely that one back there.
I've got to get closer. Am I going to be safe here? It's a bad photo.
It's not you. I need the other one. Oh, fuck. I can't move. I can't move.
I can't move. Don't move. Don't move. Oh, god. Don't move. Oh, fuck.
Okay. Got to run. Where's the jeep? It's all the way back there. Oh, fuck.
Oh, no. I'm going to die. I'm good. Alright, where's the leader? I'm going to wrap
around here. There's the leader right there. God, perfect opportunity to get
in front. Right here. Oh, come here you majestic bastard.
Got it. I can get a better one than that though. It's going to look right in the camera.
Just get it. That's good. That's good. That looks good. Perfect.
T-pose to assert dominance. No, don't look at me.
Las Vegas photographer dies attempting to get pictures of elephant boss baby.
Okay.
I need the elephant birds too. Yeah, but where are they? They're not going anywhere.
I need to get back in the car because look at how far away this is.
How much longer am I going to be playing? I don't know. Maybe like another hour or so.
Hour or two. I don't know. I'm still enjoying my time. We're just kind of
hanging out talking about 95% of everything I say is lies on one of those screens.
Eric literally does not do anything. No, Eric does not do
anything. You're right. But here they go. They're going to like the swamp thing here.
Birds. What? It wants a symbiotic relationship thing.
What does it want me to do? African elephant's avian sidekick
shows cattle egret, shows African elephant.
So they have to just hang out together. Are these egrets?
Are those egrets? That's an egret right here, right?
Is it? Get in the tree. Right?
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, car, car, car. Get in the tree. I'll get it.
I'm going to get in the tree. I'm going to cross. There's going to be a bunch of egrets.
Get fucking up there. Why can't I go up to this?
Eric is not dumb. Eric's pretty dumb. Alright, the question is I need
them to walk by. I need an egret. There's no egrets.
Didn't say that they hang out together here. Where are they going? Oh, this is bullshit.
Should I pull back? Does that count? Is that an egret right there?
It might be. Alright, there's like a weird bug in the background.
There's a smudge on the camera lens, but I think it was an egret. Is that an egret?
Does that count? I don't know if that counts.
Alright, well, hopefully that was one of them. Let's see where else they go.
Six FPS. Claymation Elephants. No, I got it. I got what I needed.
Yeah, let's get the hell out of here. You guys remember when he tried to play
Mountain Blade? I do. That was the Herd's leader, yeah. I got him.
It is this one, but which one's better?
Probably that one. This one's a little more clear, but this one
is a better action shot. I'm going to go with this one.
What do we get? That's alright. I got a B.
Then the... I don't know if I even have
because this is correct. This is such a half-ass. This is so half-ass.
This is the equivalent of you figuring out that you had homework
in homeroom, and you filled in random answers
on your math sheet. At least you did it. It's going to have to be
this first one. Is that even the right bird? I don't even know if that's the right one.
Whatever. At least I turned it in.
I turned in the homework. I still need this one. I need new stuff to unlock.
I got the tent. Give me a new camera.
You have a 150-word essay due tomorrow. 150-word essay?
Isn't that... That's like two paragraphs.
Isn't that a tweet? 150...
140 characters. Oh, that's an easy essay
meme in 2019. Oh. Every copypasta
always works. I don't pay attention
to this shit. I'm not going to like fucking Copypasta
Wiki and looking up what's the latest copypasta that came out like two months ago.
I barely go see movies that come out. Here we go.
Hello Francine. How you doing? I've been writing a picture book about an elephant mother and child.
You're on an expedition or something in Africa, right? Perfect timing. Do me a favor.
Snap me a photo of a baby African elephant. Give me a really cute
little tyke, one whose tusks haven't grown in yet.
This is difficult apparently. Do I have to get it falling down?
This is apparently very difficult. Baby African elephant.
Little tusks. No tusks. Okay.
A little tyke. Let's go. I'm going to get fucking killed
if I go near an elephant's child.
Well, we'll do just fine.
Still need to do that one. Alright. Let's get it. We need to photograph an elephant calf.
You saw an elephant herd in the corongo flats. If you climb
a tree they won't see you and you can catch them their most natural behavior.
Go get it. 200 word essay. What's the
standard for a college essay? Thousand words?
Two thousand words? I remember like somewhere around a thousand was pretty
standard. Ten pages. A hundred and fifty. A hundred and fifty words is
like a chicken cutlet recipe.
Alright. Baby elephant time. Let's go. I hate this thing.
A hundred and fifty words is a paragraph, but that's what I mean. Chicken cutlet?
You want a fucking chicken cutlet? Yeah, we make the best fucking chicken cutlet chip.
I love. Chicken cutlet is one of my favorite things in the world.
I'm doing a funny voice. Funny voice.
I'm not allowed to like change the pitch of my voice to just make like a point about a chicken cutlet.
He did the funny. If I was to go on Shark Tank,
who do you guys think would be the shark that would give me the deal?
None of them. Mark Cuban? Maybe it would be Mr. Wonderful.
There's a reason why I'm Mr. Wonderful. Fuck his deals. They're always terrible.
That guy, every time that guy just gives student loans.
I'm going to work with Laurie. Here we go. We're going to get a baby, right?
It's a boomer show? That is not a boomer show. That is like a
general audience. Leave it on the background and who gives a shit show?
Your baby, without tusks. This baby has tusks.
Boomer show. God. No, you know what a
boomer show is? This is how you guys are so wrong.
It's so wrong for you to say that. The Wheel of Fortune
is a boomer show. Jeopardy is a boomer show. All the game shows.
What do you mean no, it's not? Guys, I don't think there's ever been a
contestant on Wheel of Fortune that was under the age of 45.
I need another baby. Family Feud is not a boomer show. I didn't say
Family Feud. Oh, by the way, I bought Family Feud for Playstation 2.
I don't know why. I just, I had to get it. No, we have another version of Family Feud to play.
I don't know who the host is on this one. Oh, fuck, that's
a chase. Is it going to be a T-Rex chase?
Uh oh, I'm aggroing all of the elephants right now.
So that's obviously, there's no baby there that has small tusks.
Dumb request, that is. The other one who took it. But that was my only
look, I just take the missions. I take the emails. And I determine
alright, I can do that. I can take a picture of a baby elephant. But has to have no
tusks. Oh, hey, chat, hazy, did he do the run over the animals
joke? No, I have not. How long have I been playing for?
Like four and a half hours and I haven't tried that?
Oh, yellow owl! Here it comes!
Oh, what the, oh fuck. What? No, get back in.
Of course I tried that. That was the first thing I did.
Repeat what you just said. I'll try. He's like, uh oh.
Yellow owl! Something like that, right?
Are those the only elephants that are going to spawn? I don't know why
I'm just thinking about this. I don't know why I thought this was funny.
It's like, bad. For some reason I was hoping a low branch was
going to hang and hit this guy in the face. It's not that funny.
No, you know, it might have been. It might have been.
Alright, get out of the fucking car!
Baby. 12 o'clock. This baby doesn't...
You're going to have to deal with the picture I give you because if there's no spawned
elephants that are babies with no tusks then I'm not going to be able to get a picture of it.
I literally cannot stand the presence of Eric.
And all First Person does is make him more prevalent in the shot.
Hold on, there's a lot of babies here. Looks like he's driving the car.
We've stadium seating for some reason. Why? Pull up to the drive-through.
Not the drive-through, the drive-in. Yeah, when you pull up to the drive-through he's got a better angle to speak.
Right there. Baby with big tusks.
The one right there has big tusks too. You're just going to get a picture of a baby elephant
and that's pretty much what you're going to get. Sorry.
They asked for no tusks? I know, but there are no tusks. They all have tusks.
Just fucking Photoshop them out. Is it really going to be that
hard for you just to take the paint tool and grab on
a like color, the eyedropper thing,
and trace over the tusks? I don't give a shit.
That's perfect. I'm out. Just make a clay elephant and photograph
that. What was the side mission? Do we have one?
This weird one showed a male impala and two
or more females. Let's get it.
This game is stupid. No it's not. This game is not stupid.
That's pretty stupid. But as a whole the game is not stupid.
What does this game have for a rating?
The title of the game is Africa with a K.
Look it up for me. What does it have on
internet game news? Whatever, IGN.
Three and a half out of ten on IGN.
I need three females. There's a male right there.
One, two. No, I see one this way though.
It said on the thing only desperate streamers would play this.
That would be kind of funny if I had an opportunity to take a picture when it was
sprinting by and I didn't get it.
I see a bunch of females. Now what I was going to tell you is
fuck, I'm going to have to wait over here.
This is not desperate boomer. Why did I even add boomer?
I didn't even need to do that. Desperate streamer? No, no, no.
Does it say anywhere there about testing your internet? This is a test the internet game.
If your internet works, then you can play it and stream it for a little while.
Just to make sure the internet works so when you do the real stream tomorrow
that you'll know the internet's going to stay on. Does it say that anywhere?
Alright, what do we got? There's a male right there.
I think this game's fun. Okay, got it. Right here. Come on.
That male's right there. And at least three females.
This is like Pokemon Snap without the fun of Pokemon. Oh, I gotta get that a shot of the male.
That's not good. That's not good.
I gotta get closer. This is the right shot though. Keep him right in the middle.
Right there. Come on, get it. Are they wagging their tails? Head up.
I got it. I got it. You've walked forward to zoom back out. Yeah, because of
depth. Wait, we have another opportunity here for elephant.
Baby elephant right here? Maybe not, that's not a baby elephant.
It's the same one I already took a picture of before. They don't seem to really want to protect this baby.
I can get a great shot. The baby's not even going to move.
Alright, fine. No. Come here. That was close. I can get it again.
Right when it crosses the plane. This thing can probably kill me.
No, I can just leapfrog it. I have a thousand percent confidence that I could leapfrog
that elephant if it charged at me. Just jump as high as you can. Push down
four arms hard as you can up over the elephant. Alright, I got the fucking photo.
Let's go. I don't think anyone can do that. I don't think they could.
The jackass guys used to do that all the time.
They would like jump over shit. Alright.
I'm pretty sure Stevo has done what I just said in a jackass episode.
Let's get a good one. Baby elephant. I mean, that's cute.
I don't know if it's a good perfect frame, but it's pretty good.
I said get a cute one.
It's life.
Oh, get a cute one. That's so bad.
That's so bad. Oh yeah, go up in a tree.
Did you see this one yet? I mean, come on.
He even got the smoke on his legs. Just disturbing.
Disturbing nature. Not even remotely close to what they asked for.
Alright. That's good.
Alright, there you go in the picture book.
That's not an elephant calf. Okay, so that was not a...
That is absolutely an elephant calf. Absolutely.
There's no way that's not a baby. What? That doesn't make any sense.
Which is the good one here. Probably this one.
Sorry, I'll take the money. No tusks to send in the email.
I thought that was a criteria for...
That's fucking running away. That is so bad.
We already did this one. We already did that one. Keep that.
No, no, no. Keep this one. Keep that one. Keep that one.
Keep this one. Keep the terriers. Yep, two terriers.
Keep that one. Okay, delete. Okay, let's go to camera.
Anything new with the camera? Same lens.
I don't have any lenses or anything. I can't really buy one.
I gotta get this calf apparently somehow. I don't know what I'm missing here.
I'm getting the photo storage.
Because we need to buy it all so the game knows that I bought everything.
Play Apex.
I don't play those kind of games. Any new emails? No.
I need to still get this stupid thing.
Let me look at this camera.
I've never snapped a photo of a baby African elephant. Give me a really cute one.
One whose tusks haven't grown in yet. That's why this one's at four cameras
out of five. And it's 40 grand.
You gotta get the right spawn. Alright, I'm gonna pee my pants.
I'll be right back in like 30 minutes. I'm just kidding. Don't leave.
You can if you want to. But I'll be back in like two minutes. Gotta pee.
Holy shit, they made candied bacon downstairs. I gotta get out of here.
That was delicious.
Brown sugar, maple, bacon. It's unbelievable.
Alright, what were we doing? Baby elephant thing again, right?
Let's try it again. End of the stream, bacon? Not yet.
Not yet. We're good. I'm gonna keep going because I don't know what the status
is gonna be tomorrow. You know what I mean? It's easy to be like, oh, you know what? It's been like five hours.
Okay. No, I'm serious. No, no, no. This might be the
green day of the week. I have no idea. So I'm just gonna keep going.
I'm having fun. Green day of the week? Yeah. I do it every time.
It's happened every single time. Do you want to just cut them down?
No, no, no, that's bad. They don't leave nature alone. Alright, we'll just play a vibe game.
That's next up. That is the next thing that I want to do.
That's the real... I'm going in.
A lot of VR shit to do. What's the point of Eric?
I think what the developers were looking for was somebody to take up
screen real estate, and that's it. Cause I guess
in that tent, in that camp, if it's just empty, that doesn't feel
realistic. He's just like a researcher. They just put him there.
He just takes up real estate. So what was this? A 3.5 out of
10? I don't agree with that. I would put this... I would give it at least a 5.
Alright, baby elephants, let's go. It's a 68 on
Metacritic. That's probably the exact score I would give it.
Is it 68? Maybe. I'm willing to put this up to a 7-0
if, and only if, this is a very, very important detail.
If the next boss fight is cool.
The cheetah was interesting, but whatever this area's boss, in quotes,
is, if it's cool and fun, I might knock it up
to a 7-0. I'm going to search for elephants. What are the downsides?
Driving into any form of bush or
grass stops the car. And
it's a vast, open, sandbox experience. It just feels empty.
No babies, though. Are you playing
this game still? Yeah. I actually, this is fun.
It might not be a good game, but it's fun, and
it's rare. So, come on, that gives it a few points.
The fact that it's rare, and
your good friend Jeremy spent $50
on this game. So I'm going to get a $50 experience.
How am I supposed to find this shit? That baby
has tusks. Use a PlayStation 3
emulator. Alright, as somebody that's tried to do
emulators for last generation,
is not there yet. There are a handful of games that really, truly
work as intended on, like, a PS3 emulator. Have you seen any
elephants? And something tells me, and this might just be a hunch
here, that the Safari
Photography, the Safari Photograph video game, Africa,
is not high on the list to get it to work well with an emulator.
I would probably say that's an accurate statement.
Where are the elephants? God damn it. Alright, huge pack of elephants.
Where are the babies? Why do I have to be
on the rare quest? You have tusks. Yes, I know
what those are. I know where they are. Leave me alone. You also have
tusks. Am I supposed to climb a tree for this one? Yeah, but
am I just going to climb a tree and wait for elephants to walk by the tree?
How long that's going to take? Get out of the way. Come on.
Elephants are attracted to people in trees. And plus
another thing about emulators, that I'm not entirely sure everybody
is aware of this, they're illegal. Like, as like
a streamer, as somebody who is broadcasting themselves to the internet,
hey guys, like, I don't own this shit. I just downloaded it online
for free. It's kind of just inviting an issue
potentially. Emulators aren't, but ROMs can be.
There's a lot of weird, there's a lot of weird slippery
legislature with like emulating video games.
So let's say for instance, let's say I got a
RCS, PS3, whatever it is.
Let's say I got that emulator and I downloaded this game and I don't own it.
Let's say I just streamed this game on an emulator without buying or owning the game.
You're not supposed to do that. But I do own it.
But why would I, why would I emulate this now? There's no reason for me to
emulate this game. Do we have a stray baby elephant with no tusks for
no reason? What? It has tusks. What are you doing out here?
Now you could also argue, like for instance, if a game
is actually not even viable, like
straight up you can't get it anywhere. And alright, maybe it's
how else are you going to play it, right? Emulation and ROMs are actually
what they're doing is they're backing up the
history of video games. As you saw recently with all this shit
with the Wii Shop channel and you know, games going into
abandoned ware. Oh, it's like this random Super Nintendo game that you will never
see, you will never play, you will never find ever again. There are no copies that are in
circulation anymore. You can argue that there's a reason to
have backups of video games forever. But
if I have the means to do it and I've tried doing emulation before
and it just always had like some random problem that was like, oh
well that's good, it's the emulator. It's like, well fuck, okay, well why don't I just get the damn thing
for real and not have to worry about any potential issues that pop up from
emulating like a last generation game. Is that a baby up there?
And there's even a list online of PS3 emulated
games and how much they function. It's like, oh this one
like kind of works. This one doesn't work. This one doesn't work at all. This one like loads
past level four. Like you can actually see which ones are even
being like worked on to help, you know. What are you doing out here?
That's the one that I chased away. Well, why?
How am I supposed to do this? If at any given moment
if one or two troops of elephants spawn
then all of them have tusks.
How much do you find, monster?
What are your thoughts on games being forcibly removed due to licensing issues like
the Scott Pilgrim game on PS3? I don't know, I'm kind of
of the opinion that if you fucking made something and you've released it and people bought it and
you sold it, are you really going to be upset that people want
to buy it and still play it and resell it?
It's like, you already did it. Here comes another troop. Yeah, just stay in the car, Eric.
Everything will be fine. Tusks. Put this down.
Binoculars and more. Can I please get a baby with no tusks? You have
tusks. Did I actually hit the wall in this game? I may have.
Is this the soft lock mission? Find two elephants having
sex and then follow them for nine months. This is the boss battle? No.
It wouldn't have like a cool cut scene. Nine months?
Wait, hold on. A baby, an elephant is pregnant for
32 months? Look at that. Oh my
god. Almost two years of pregnancy.
Humans come out too early. Yeah, they are massive when they come out. Yeah, that's
true. Alright, can I like cheat this game and put cheat codes
in and just skip this one? Maybe I have to
get in a tree. Maybe that's part of it. Maybe I have to trigger the
cut scene. Let me look at this one more time. Does this have any info on it for me?
Client, Irino, African, elephant,
calf. Cheated enough for
one scream? What do you mean? Cheated? I'm gonna get in
this and see if I trigger a cut scene or something because it did say that I could get up.
Snap a baby elephant. Give me a cut scene.
Oh god damn it is a fucking cut scene. I can't believe it. I've been
driving around in circles for like 30, 40 minutes. Look, there's a
calf or the elephant herd. I took the wrong photos. Oh, there it is. There's the
one with no tusks. Descripted. Descripted event.
Good. This is the boss. Snap parent and child African elephant.
Which one is the parent? Not bad.
I don't like this one. I don't like this. I don't like this. Change it. Change it. Change it. Change it. Change it.
Manual. Fuck! Get out of the shot. Out of the shot. Go!
Bye. Let's see what my best photo was. You don't just kind of want one.
Elephants? Could you have an elephant as a pet?
If you had a huge backyard and you put up like T-Rex fences
I'm talking you own like 40 acres. Like 50 acres of land.
100 acres of land. And you have man-made pools and
man-made shrubbery and bushes and shit.
Which one is the good one? The black and... No it's not!
The last black and white photo I took was way better than all these.
Really cared for the young. Well how did it go? Did you get your photos of the baby elephant?
I did. Yeah you have like 100 acres of land. You have walls
surrounding the whole thing. And you have one giant elephant.
Yeah and like some of you guys said you could have another part of land. Let's say you own 100 acres.
Like 10 acres could be for elephants. Like 5, 10 acres could be
for bears. Get a couple of bears. Make sure they're all fenced off completely.
Maybe have like a penguin exhibit too. Like get ice
shipped in. Like 50 acres or something. Who's gonna clean it?
You can hire a staff. You know if you have that kind of money to have an elephant
for a pet you probably have money to spend. So you hire like
100 people. 100 staff to take care of the animals.
And then maybe have like a little area
that's small. Like a building that you develop that has like stuffed animals
in it. Of the animals that are there. And coloring books and shit.
And then you could like invite people over to come and hang out.
I love how much people hate this.
And yeah yeah you could charge. Just you know to cover the costs
of you know you have like pet elephants and pet bears and shit. Like $20 to come and look
around. Alright I don't know how this one
the composition of this one is not. This one is way better.
Look at the depth of field on this one. This one's like 5 times better.
This is really the best algorithm. It's
because of the mother pushing up. I guess.
Well that's apparently the best one so I'm gonna listen to the game.
Accidental black and white photo? Accidental?
Now I turned it on. I did that intentionally. That's a lot of money.
How could the angle not be better than that? Considering they told
me to go in this tree. This was a cut scene. I got cut
into this angle and it was a bad angle. That's not my fault.
Another job done and we're still on one piece. Tomorrow we start early. Let's get some rest.
He was supposed to be on top of the elephant. Good morning Francine.
Be sure to check your email. Sending map new area. Alright
I think this might be one of the last areas. New camera. Thank you for your continued
business. In today's newsletter we'd like to let our A100 users know
the product they've been waiting for has finally arrived. A 24 to
105mm f-stop of 3.5 to 4.5 is an interchangeable
lens for the A series. Switch lenses and
power up your photography. Pro shop for more details.
We got a new area. The Choroa Gorge.
Harsh lands surrounded by rocks and sand.
Let's research the area. We're gonna get an ad.
We're actually getting a fucking ad. Clever.
Alright well there it is. Wide angle to mid range telephoto.
Let's do it. Compact. High power standard. Zoom.
Wide angle. Beautiful. This whole game
is really just product placement. It's funny because back in the day
here. 2007, 2008.
I like how desperate are you Sony. Canon was the leader here.
Alright so this is the telephoto. We're gonna get some cool photographs with this one.
Is Canon still the leader? Wouldn't surprise me at all. They make
high quality fucking cameras. I still haven't used this at all.
This is a next level sponsored stream. Play a game
that has a competitor advertising all over the place and have streamer
talk about how dumb it is and bad it is and then mention Canon once
and subliminally get that
message inside of the consumers head. I'm having trouble with words tonight.
I don't know why. That one's better so I'm gonna get rid of these.
Nope. Keep these. I have to have a bunch of memories from each encounter.
Alright let's go explore the new area. All DSLRs
are the same. Canon is definitely still
the best. What do they got now? Didn't Kodak literally
go bankrupt? Did they? Canon's not worth the money.
It's Nikon now. Nikon's the best now?
Nikon's doing well.
Nikon's doing alright in the
consumer level. You buy a Nikon
T2100 whatever series
and you bring it on vacation and take nice pictures. You bring
that to Vegas and you take a picture of Excalibur at the hotel and you're like oh that was
worth like in the consumer $280
kind of nice consumer level.
I find Sony to be the best for photography.
Photography? Holy shit Jeremy.
Get your fucking head screwed on. Photographing.
What's wrong with me tonight? I tell you the high winds I must have
blown my brain around in my skull. It was crazy though.
Let me tell you. Vitalix and I were outside just
curing shit because the wind can cause damage. We're making sure
we don't lose stuff that can fly around and around the house.
Outside the house and all that shit. This was like a movie. This was like being on set
in a fucking tornado themed movie. It was terrifying.
It was at the point where you had to lean into the wind or you were going to fall
over. Plant your feet and stuff your back into the huge 60
fucking mile per hour gust or you're going down. It was crazy.
Close your mouth or your dentures will fly out.
Open your mouth for a second and you can see it just skyrocket over the horizon.
New zone? This is not the new zone. Why do you have to drive so slow through the new
areas? Las Vegas doesn't ever get that type of weather does it?
From my understanding, not the rain.
The rain is something that doesn't happen very often. So we got to shitload of rain.
I think they actually broke a record yesterday.
The most rain ever in one day, at least on Valentine's Day,
broke a record somehow. But the wind from my understanding
is it happens a lot. Vegas is a very windy
city. But being here for about four and a half
months, we've never experienced that. More than like
60 plus mile per hour wind gusts. So it does get windy
around here but it can get pretty extreme sometimes.
I don't even know where the hell it comes from. I actually kind of like that picture.
I really like this. Can you run over animal?
You cannot run over animal. Has the minimum changed yet?
Not yet. The minimum is changing over the next couple of days though.
So just to make sure you're aware, the bit minimum is
increasing to 250. 250 is the new bit reading
minimum. As of like now.
But not as of this stream.
If that makes any sense. So in the next few streams we're going to slowly
transition it. I did bring it down from three because
some of the things that people were saying, there were some good points
about how buying bits makes a three dollar
minimum sort of awkward because they don't come in threes, they come in
fives. How do you slowly transition that?
It's instantly over one day. But over the course of the last
three weeks or so, almost about a month, I've been slowly telling everybody
that it's going to happen in mid-February. So I mean
I have slowly been telling everybody it was going to happen in mid-February and now we're in mid-February.
It's going to take one day. Are there ostriches here?
There are ostriches in Africa? I thought these were like
only in New Zealand. Isn't this like the New Zealand state bird?
That's a good photo. That's emus.
Wait. Let's put it on auto for now. No get
the fucking black and white off. Well let's start surveying from this location.
Francine, why don't you take the wheel. Well there's an actual
camera emulator. Yeah. It has all the settings.
That's why this game is really... Can I just drop this guy off?
You actually don't have a reason to be here. Let me get out and get a good picture of this. Never mind.
Let's go. That guy's just back there smoking a blunt. Okay slow
down. Let me get a good one. This is a good horizon here. Now you're ruining
the shot. Get out of the way. Nice. Nice. Oh you're getting close.
Oh work with me here. Work with me here. Look at this one.
Whoa. I love it. I love it. I hope you just get out of the way.
I gotta get a little tighter. I don't want that little deer in the way. Come on. Come on.
Come on. This is like a fucking car commercial. Do it. Do it. Do it. He's using the
rule of search. I like that one. There's nothing wrong with
this photo. Why is that such a bad thing? That one's really good too.
That one actually might be the best one. Why not a different shutter?
Well because I want my photos to look awful. I can make one of these
my desktop background. Oh that's some pretty good photos. I like the
landscape here. Kubwa rock. Put your ISO at
12,000. Any more wildlife? Probably rhinos here.
I need to get a good picture of Oscar. All right we got something else over here.
What's this? Where are the lions? This has got to be the lion
zone. It has to be. New bird. One of those will be good enough.
Let's do a real slow, slow fucking shutter.
Stop moving. It's too bright. No. Get out of the menu.
Okay. Manual. Other
direction. You gotta go up. You gotta close the iris. Not open it.
Stay right there. Right there. Right there. Stay. Stay. Stay. Stay. Right there. Right there. There it is.
Stay there. Right there. Look at that. No I moved.
No. No. No. No. No. It's just shutter. The shutter. That was perfect. The shutter
has got to be quicker than that. Oh he walked by at the right time. Don't move.
Walk into frame. Come on. Walk into frame so I can get the good
depth of field here. I'll follow you as long as I need to.
I'll get it. It's going to be a good one. Watch this. Oh if I was only a
little bit. Come on. I need you like down here.
I gotta move. Opportunity is knocking right now. You dumb
dickhead. That was what I wanted. This one's not bad. I don't mind
this one. Yeah this is the. We finally got the. I got the right exposure here.
Whoops. Can you imagine. If it was a little turn the other
way. Can you imagine how good this one would have been. It's still alright.
If I could have gone. I need a bigger lens. I want to go closer. Go right
up in his face. But I can't do that. I need a better shutter.
No. Every one of you fucking dumb inputs are wrong.
I need to get a better lens. Can I just buy one.
No live preview when adjusting the settings. Yeah that's the one unfortunate thing. You only
get the pre. It shows you what you got. Actually hold on.
All of you stay right there. If I can get in front.
Wait wait wait. Shhh. No no no. God.
Come this way. Come on. I need a tree right here.
Fuck. It's alright. Close enough. That's what I want.
I want it to be a little darker. I don't want it blown out. I need one of them to
go through that tree. I need to get up here. Master plan. Come on.
What I want. I want. I want one of you to go through here.
Like that. And I get you right in the middle. I'm going to go a little closer.
Oh fuck it. Whatever. I'm taking this too seriously. This is fun.
Press R3. It drops bait for the animal.
Add that to the list of bullshit things I've heard in the last two days.
Can I have them take the wheel so I can take a photo? Guys don't you know
that a photographer will take two thousand photos
at an event or something they're hired for. And only like
four of them are going to get used. Oh it's fast. I can see that one.
If only it was a little bit more.
Oh you're coming right at me. I got a chance. What are you doing?
Wow. Meerkats. That's the first piece of dialogue you've had in four days, Eric.
Shut up. I'm putting the camera right in there. I'm trying so hard
to not make any noise. I'm hopping right now. What are you doing?
Nobody walks like that. Nice stealth
walk. Look at how majestic this bird is.
I got to get closer to this. What are you?
No, no, no, no. No. Shit you threw it in the photo.
You dick. That's a pretty good class picture. Okay I'm gone.
It's really weird. Okay.
What was I doing? Oh yeah meerkats. That's a good one. Perfect straight line.
Right in the middle. Alright I got to go to the meerkats.
What hole are they in? I'm just going to hide. Maybe I shouldn't park the jeep in front of the holes.
That's good. So let's wait. I'm going to put the binoculars out.
That's a good spot. Is there a tree I can climb or something? What about up here?
Can I get up there? No that's a wall. It's an actual wall that I can't climb.
Why can't I just stand on the jeep? That seems like a perfectly
swell place to stand. Look at the angle.
Just park the jeep over the holes. What kind of monster are you?
No I'm just going to sit here. I'm going to wait until one shows their head.
And I'm going to whip the camera out and snap. They pop up right?
Come on. Are they just holes? Just look for other holes.
Maybe. Alright let me look for other holes.
Don't run across. Don't run across. What are you doing?
Break the truck. You cannot unfortunately. I wish you could.
That would have definitely caused some damage.
Kobe Sand. Some other type of animal here.
Tigers? Lions? There's got to be a lion in this game. You can't have it take photos
of animals game and not have a lion in this area.
There's no way. Can I climb this tree? It's a pretty good view but there's nothing
here. What the hell is that? No it's just a random animal.
A bird? What kind of bird is that? Is that like a pheasant?
That is the equivalent of a bird Chadwalk. It's
gold too. We've got to take a picture of the golden bird. It's just a dumb
vulture. Okay. What's supposed to be over here?
I think it's a meerkat but let's go back and turn some of these in.
The meerkats are too scared to come out of their burrow. There must be a way. Let's request new equipment from the head office.
I couldn't do anything. Give me a break. I took a lot of pictures didn't I?
Alright we've got our email. We're going to do wildlife research. Any new animals?
We have a few. What's a good one?
Golden vulture.
Why are the bird pictures with bad framing?
This is one of the most highly sought after images.
We've got the good class picture of the ostrich.
This has got to be a full block for everything right?
God damn it. Distance by a hair and technique by a hair.
Oh well. Okay let's see. There's the photo bomb. I'm going to keep that one.
This one sucks. This one's kind of cool but sucks.
I don't know what this picture is of. I was trying to go for some artsy
stuff with everything in the foreground was out of focus.
They were in focus but my subject was not cooperating.
That one's not bad. I like this one.
That one's good. This one's fine. That's a good one.
That one causes a headache. I'm progressively trying to change
the aperture and the shutter. See typically
you go through and you delete all these. It slowly gets better
and then you got the fucking money shot which is right here.
This one actually is more pleasing to me. Let them evaluate
this one? No. The same bird? It is.
That's pretty great. Can't you just see a logo
right in the middle there? That's perfect template
for two or three words for your business.
I think that's a better one too. That's pretty good. I think that works for what they're looking for.
Come on, give me a perfect. God damn it.
Then there was one more photo of an animal.
Where is it? No, not the baby running away scared.
Maybe that's it. No, that's it.
Let's delete some of these. These are
terrible. I like both of these. I'm keeping both.
This one's dumb. Don't like it. Don't want any of these.
None of these are worth saving. None of these are worth saving.
It's just a job. You know what I mean? No, don't get rid of the
advertising template. But here's the
marketing template. It's good to
have two templates because this giraffe is paying attention to
whatever the company or logo is in the middle of the screen. This giraffe
is paying attention to you. It cares about you and your interests.
So the logo on the screen is there for the company but this giraffe is endorsing it
and looking to you on how you feel about it.
Instead of what the giraffe feels about the company. I'll keep them both.
I'll get rid of this one. Keep that one. I'm gonna run out of space. Any more space?
Keep that one. Okay, delete. I'm assuming we're probably gonna get
a mission. But the giraffe could also
symbolize a person targeted by the advertisement so the one with it looking at the logo would be better.
Could be. That's all on the marketing firm that
decides to pay for those pictures. I'm just the photographer.
They interpret, not me. Oh, there's a lot here. Thanks for the other day.
Amazing animals editorial desk. My boss loved the giraffe photo. Thanks for
saving my bacon. Hey, by the way, have you ever seen ostriches court
each other? If not, you should check it out. It's quite a spectacle.
And by check it out, I mean snap me a photo. I'll use it in next month's Amazing
Animals. Cute little animal request.
One of the companies sponsoring our project requested you send a photo of a meerkat standing
up and looking around. However, you won't find a more vigilant
watchman than a meerkat. You'll have a rough time sneaking up on one without being noticed.
What was it just eating in that last frame? Oh,
the stick. Okay. Luckily, we were ready for this and have prepared new equipment
for you. Use it to get the photo. I can't do that now.
Doing the ostriches having sex with each other.
An animal that has a funny face. Hey, can you take a photo for our next issue?
We're doing a favorite funny animal faces. And I want you to put a picture
of a heart beast in the running. They have those long
slender faces. If you got a shot from head on, our readers would vote at number one, no
question. I deleted them all. Alright, I gotta get a good one of the funny
face. Trap cam on its way. Head office is sending
you new equipment. The trap cam lets you photograph subjects remotely.
Set up the camera where you want to take a photo, then trigger the shutter from a distance.
Feel free to use the trap cam for other research after you finish
taking the meerkat photo. Alright. Francine never heard of
the big five. There are five major animals people want to see on safaris.
The African elephant, the African buffalo, the rhino, the leopard, and the lion.
They're all tough to find, though. You'd have to be pretty lucky to spot them all.
Oh, there's the rare spawn. Alright, uh, ostrich is
doing courting. Okay. How do I
use? The male slowly rotates its wings and moves its head into figure
eight. It's quite exotic. How do I use the
trap cam? Shoot photos from a distance using infrared remote, custom for
tsetse cameras. How do I use it?
Wait a minute. I got the wrong camera. Oh, I don't want to do that. Ten hour joker?
It's the amateur camera. Alright, let's go with ostriches.
Ostriches. It's weird to say that name.
Ostriches. Hard to pronounce. Ostrich.
Ostrich. Okay. Capturing ostrich
in a mating ritual. Can't I just skip?
You can't put a base camp up in the other areas.
GTA bushes. Yeah, they're pretty bad.
So which way is the place we just worked? This way?
Fucking god. Do we have a problem in chat? Do we have
a problem right now in chat? Am I getting baited here or is this
actually the day that I get rid of links forever?
Okay. Alright, that's fine. Just remember,
the boy of fried wolf. Open it. I'm not going to open it.
I don't want to open it. Don't crash into that. It's going to stop you.
What is he going to do? Do I really have to go from the wetlands
to through the wetlands? Up through the other place.
Into the desert area. Do I actually have to do that?
Long loading screens. Guys, let's act like his camera's on.
His cam's on. That's not a fake message somebody actually wrote that.
What the fuck, dude?
No one said yes they did. Check the logs. Somebody wrote that.
Let's pretend. Oh, was it all capitals? That's why I turned that on.
Alright, we need an ostrich mating ritual.
Somebody did say that. I have the logs.
Show the logs? I'm not going to show logs. I don't have any logs.
It was a lie. I have a memory. Alright, get out.
See if there's a ritual right here. They moved the head into figure 8.
Like that? Is that one about to do it?
Is this one about to do the thing? He turned his head upside down.
He's going to do the thing. He's about to do it. I've got to get closer than that.
It looks like somebody squished his neck. Somebody accidentally stepped on his neck.
No. I wonder. Alright, you like Donald Duck.
Go find another Donald Duck. And let's get this over with.
Why are you not taking this moment to make a funny animal documentary?
What do you want me to say?
I already did that joke five years ago.
Okay, you want me to go like this. As you can see here,
the giraffe is drinking from the water. And to the left...
Here it is in action right now. It's doing like a turkey dance.
Alright, that's what I need to get. I got it already. That's what you guys wanted.
You don't want that. You'll do it again. So is this game any fun or is this whole
stream just a bit? That would be pretty long.
Six straight hours of a bit.
That's the whole stream. Been a bit. I got it.
Who cares if it's not worth anything?
You can't even see it. It's a very bad photo. This one's about to do it, right?
They get down on their knees and they start moving around in a circle.
They float their feathers out and they start moving their head around. I've got to get in front of them.
Have I tried only talking when I have something funny to say?
Why the hell would I do that?
If I would have just sit here silently, it would just be watching
a silent gameplay of PlayStation 3 safari photos.
Why in the name of fucking God would I ever do that?
Alright, I'll try it. I'll make it really...
This is not a joke. Hey, what's up guys? Chime in here. This is not a joke.
Did you guys actually know that the ostrich is one of the most closely
related animal to dinosaurs?
If I would have walked into my room right now and not...
I wasn't streaming this. This is a really weird fucking game.
Just to be playing. Just here.
I know it's not funny, but it is. Silently playing this game.
It feels weird to play this game in silence.
It just does. I'm sorry. You're not going to silence me.
It's immersing. Fine. Five straight minutes
of silence. I got something funny to say. That's a workout video.
That's a workout video. And I just got a picture of a workout video.
That's funny. I got it. Five more minutes. I can't fucking do it.
I only have three minutes. How was it? I'm not going to say that?
Alright, I can fucking do it. I'm doing it. I don't care if there's anything funny to say. I'm not going to say anything.
I swear to God. Five fucking minutes. I'm not going to talk. I'm not going to smirk
staring at the fucking screen playing my silent video game.
I'm going to keep the mic on this time so I can prove it.
Here it goes. Here it goes. Here it goes. Here it goes. Shut up. I already blew it.
It's already over. Start again. Right now. Go.
I already got the... I got to get in front of them. Shhh.
Starting now. Nothing was even fucking funny.
I just started rifling through things in my head that were funny.
I don't know why my brain was trying to make me lose.
You know when you're in class and the teacher's like, everybody shut the fuck up.
Anyone peeps at all and that's it. You're going to have detention.
And you shut the fuck up and you're like, I don't want to get in trouble. And then you think of every funny thing
you've ever heard of in your life. Your brain just starts to talk.
Things that have nothing to do with what you just heard. What might have been funny five minutes ago.
You fell off your skateboard and you bumped your head on a wall
or something in the ninth grade and it was like hilarious.
Like somebody puked in front of you when you were like fucking fourteen and you were like laughing your ass off.
Those images come into your mind. That just happened. I'm going to get it.
I'm going to get it. Let's go. Three, two, one, go.
What? No, I'm talking about like if I like... You ever like bumped into something and like you knocked over
like a fucking cabinet and it's not funny? Yeah, a whole cabinet.
I'm sorry guys, but in eighth grade typing class
somebody puking on their computer all over the keys. How would you react to that?
Like holy shit. But that didn't even happen to me.
That happened to my father. That's a story from my father.
My father did that. I wasn't in the classroom.
He ate like pecan pie and fucking threw up all over his computer.
Wait, this might have been a lie that my father told me.
Because they didn't have computers back then, did they?
Was it computers back in like the fucking 70s? He's going for it.
He's going for it. He's going for it. How bad is the picture that I took?
It doesn't matter. It looks like shit, but who cares? Yeah, there was a typing class.
I'm going to text him tomorrow and be like, hey, did you have a computer?
Did the pecan pie throw up all over the keyboard story real or did you make that up?
I'm going to get the whole story. I've been here for so long trying to take pictures of these fucking...
I was going to say elves. Every funny thing I've ever heard of is happening
right now in my brain. Everything that I've ever thought was funny
is all mashing together into one made-up fucking story.
I think that's actually what's happening because I can't shut the fuck up
for five minutes. Are you going for it? It's good practice. Okay, I'm going to try
it again. This is the real one. This one's no more fucking wrong. I swear to God. I promise.
100% guarantee. If I crack, I will give a hundred
gift subs if I fucking crack. Five minutes starting now. Let's go.
God damn it.
Okay, two things. One, the ostriches were walking in exact succession
into my lens. It got silent and y'all hear it was... and then I crashed the same
fucking bush that had crashed into like a hundred times.
How long was that? That's four minutes?
Photo finish. How many subs was it? Fifty?
Oh, God damn it.
I had it too. It was fine. I swallowed that bullshit and then I drove into the same
fucking bush I've driven into every single goddamn time. Alright, how do I fucking do this
again? God damn it. Is it a hundred subs?
The last time I did this was bingo, like four months ago.
This doesn't count as like money laundering, right? No, it doesn't count because I just
lose money. Let me get to the channel. Double or nothing? Double or
nothing. Two hundred gifted subs if I can't do it.
Two fucking hundred. Double
or nothing for ten minutes. No, it's never gonna happen.
That will never happen. I can guarantee that.
Oh, for ten minutes I can do it. Oh, God damn it.
No, I'm like, we're gonna giggly and laugh right now. It's not gonna work.
It should be five. Yeah, no, double or nothing. The time is the same. Ten minutes
is no way. I can't fucking close my mouth for ten minutes.
Like, in four minutes I put my hands up and I laugh at my fingers sometimes.
Like, you're not gonna work. I'm one of the fucking weasels from Who Framed Roger Rabbit.
It's not gonna happen. It's hard because I know I see chat like
over here in the corner of my eye. I'm not even paying attention to you guys. And all I see, I see,
I can feel what you guys are writing. Somebody wrote like fucking
brap. And I don't think that's funny. And like, I fucking
just like, I can feel that word. And it's just like
fuck, I turn off the monitor. Alright, here we go.
Double or nothing. Five, same time. Five minutes, two hundred gifted subs
if I don't fucking do it. I'm getting ready for this one. I'm gonna think about like fucking just
I'm gonna think about like, you know what I'm gonna think about? I'm gonna think about like fucking bad,
mean stuff. This is that crying fucking
face. I'm just gonna make sure that I don't do anything fucking, I gotta get it out
of me. I'm just gonna put a picture of something, no, because I think it's funny after like a minute or
two. I snap a mirror cap, I gotta get that off the screen. I gotta get you guys off the screen.
Alright, two hundred gifted subs if I don't do this in another five minutes. But
hold on, I gotta think of everything that's ever funny right now and I gotta laugh about it.
Alright, here we go. Five minutes, double or nothing, two hundred subs if I don't
get it, I'm already gonna fucking up. Alright, we gotta get an official
time. I can see it at the timer right here. We're at six, twenty, twenty
seven. So at the top of the minute here, at six hours and twenty one minutes
screen, but that's where it begins. No talking, no bursts,
just, I'm turning the fucking screen off. I don't even see you guys.
No, that's cheating. Here we go. The minute's about
to turn here. Somebody, okay, I'm not looking to fucking chat ever again.
Here it comes, three,
two, triple or nothing, triple
or nothing, three hundred, three hundred if I can't do it.
Triple or nothing on the table. I can't have you guys here.
I see like fucking faces over here. I know you guys are fucking with me.
Triple or nothing, three hundred gifted subs if I don't get it, five minutes.
Triple or nothing, ready?
Five minutes, triple or nothing. I told you I could fucking do it.
I said to bring five grand to the casino and put a thousand dollars
in and lose it in one hand, put two thousand and lose it, and then put
three thousand, two thousand and then win. No, you bring five
thousand dollars to the casino, put a five hundred dollar hand on blackjack, you lose it.
Two thousand dollar hand on blackjack, you lose it. Fucking another
twenty-five hundred hand on blackjack, you hit it, get out, go home. Did I get the photo?
I got the photo, let's get out of here. Quadruple or nothing, I already did it.
What would that, that would have been, that would have been what, like
fucking fifteen hundred dollars spent with what, three hundred subs.
So, if it's like two grand,
holy fuck, fifteen hundred.
What the hell are we even doing on this stream anymore? Is it time to go?
Well, it is off the camera, that's for sure. No, you should have, the people that were saying double or nothing
should have just let me sleep in my bed. Let's give them the photo.
What's wrong with the controller? Nobody said triple or nothing, yeah, but I was
panicking. This is the best one.
We don't want you to lose money. It's alright.
Cute animal request. I gained viewers doing that.
There were like twenty-seven hundred people here when I started doing that.
And now there's like thirty-two hundred. If you lost triple or nothing, would you have done quadruple?
No, that's strike three. That's to be standing?
Oh, fuck, it does. Triple or nothing, cause that is strike four, you can't go strike
four. That's not how that works. Technically standing.
People logged on their Smurf Twitch account to get the free sub.
Quadruple or nothing? No, man.
No way. After triple or nothing, that's it.
I broke even at the casino and my heart is
in my fucking stomach and I'm slowly going to walk out of the casino and be like
holy fuck, I'm never doing that again.
Two thousand dollar joke. Well, yeah, technically I would be
paying, I would just be giving Twitch money. Like I would just be giving the money.
I did that before. How about just for fun?
Let me save the game first. Then I would inflate my
sub count and then in a month it would come back down.
People are leaving. It's alright, we're getting to the end anyways.
In fact, we're probably going to call pretty soon here. It's been about
seven hours. Logging out of their Smurfs.
You're going to play a stunt like that and then go? I would have done it.
If I had lost on that third time, I would have done it.
A stunt like five minutes of silence.
Alright, where are we going? Let me just take a pee break. I'll be right back.
Let me just take a quick piss break. Alright, guys.
I guess it's going to happen. I'm going to give you a consolation prize. 50 community subs
coming out right now. Psych? No, there they come.
Generous streamer says, you know what, to the casino. Take my money anyway.
Congratulations, whoever gets it. I'm going to change my monitor here. Hey, hey, thanks a lot
German985. He's pretending. That's not pretending.
What the fuck? Holy shit! 50 community subs!
You know, I bet too much money. I bet too much.
And it's all good, because half of that money doesn't even come back.
That was fun. You guys got the house edge.
Even if you played a casino, if I was putting three grand
on the line there, even if I didn't lose,
even if you played blackjack perfectly, that's still a one or two percent house edge.
You know? Egotistic streamer
donates money to himself and demands thanks for it.
And I think with
that, I think I'm going to call it there. I think that's a good enough to go
out on. Did about seven hours. Gonna take us about an hour to go through the bits.
Oh my fucking god. Wait, wait, why did you match me? No, you just gave
the money back. No, you gave me, you gave the house, the casino just gave me the
house edge back. You weren't supposed to match me.
Well, there it is. There's your 100 community subs, guys, from me failing it the first time.
There you go. That first failure when I said 100,
there it is. I decided to get matched by ha ha ha ha.
Kumo, Chi Chi, thank you for the 50
matched community subs to make it a hummy. The promise was
delivered, if it wasn't me, completely. Only two, and that's not true, only
200 more to go. No, that's 100. Yeah, that was a lot of fun.
We're gonna take off here now. That's a good time. That's a good note to close it out on.
That was an interesting thing to close it out on. That was Africa.
It was a fun game. Relaxing.
Hard to keep a straight face when you silently sit in there.
And so the plan for the next couple days is
I really have to play this by ear. Cause I really don't know what the scenario is
gonna be, cause like I said, when Italics and I are both trying to
stream at the same time, or try to use the internet at the same time, sometimes
it just fucking kills the whole thing. So it seems to be
fixed though, at least in a packet loss frame drop kind of way.
But we might have another issue entirely.
So tomorrow, I plan on streaming Vive tomorrow, but just
stay, stay alert! Cause around
the stream time tomorrow, around like 2 to 3 PM,
I'm gonna be around to give you guys an update on what's actually happening.
Who knows, this might just be a random fluke of a day.
Oh, B or B, that's not true. This might be like a random day
that's a fluke, where I get a green light for like 7 hours for no reason.
But, I'll see you maybe tomorrow?
I don't know. We'll find out.
Thanks for joining me ahead. That was a lot of fun. That was a fun, relaxing,
chill hangout stream. Thank you for the massive amount of
community subs, especially right at the end there from Ha Ha Ha.
Much love to you all. I'll see you all maybe tomorrow. I'll let you guys know
either on Twitter or here. And with that, let's do the bits. What do you say?
Let's pull it up here. Did I look into the OpenVR plugin?
Yeah, I have this OpenVR. There's a couple of other things. There's like a chat. I can do
chat, right? If I get a certain thing, I have chat on my hand. I've been looking
into a lot of them. Let's scroll back down to earlier this evening.
To 7 hours ago now. Just about 7-ish hours ago.
Yeah, OVR drop. Yeah. I'm going to try to get it set up.
The whole room is set up, so really it's just software stuff that I can do tonight and tomorrow.
But thank you Rise, Fall of Ziggy.
Thank you for the $5. Ziggy Stardust is the name.
This stream exists. Congratulations. Yeah. Yeah, for a like,
let's test the internet stream. I had a lot of fun. Hope you guys did too.
Timmy Tim Tim, thanks for the $1 play. Crazy Strike Bowling for a Nintendo
Switch. I gotta use my Switch more. I
started off doing a ton of Switch stuff. I haven't done it in such a long time.
It's been at least a couple months since I've even turned it on. But thank you Timmy Tim Tim.
Jared Roberts, thanks for the $15. Thanks for streaming
German Life is Difficult and Simple Streams can brighten it up.
Thank you so much for the $15. And yeah, it's
sometimes the little things are worth looking forward to.
Like taking photos of animals in Africa on the PlayStation 3.
But thank you so much for
the $15 Brad Roberts. Divus, thanks for the $2 Divus.
No message is Divus coming in always with a few dollars every stream. Thank you.
Dark Keegan, thanks for the $10.
Finally managed to catch a stream after starting my first job. Thanks for all the laughs. You're great.
Thank you. Thank you for the $10 and thank you for sticking around.
Glad you got to catch one. Maybe we'll see you again soon.
Mostly Lost, thanks for the $10. No, that's a $1 for Mostly Lost.
The game should work fine if you delete the streamer. That was 7 hours ago
and then somehow we came back to that 7 hours later.
Well, nice foreshadowing. We had 50
community subs from Great Canadian Fuck Club, right?
And then WhiffWiff gave a bunch to, there pretty much
was 200 or 300 community subs tonight. Just combined.
So double enough and triple enough and don't really matter. Thank you to both of you.
Mostly Lost also gave $50. I think I somehow
missed this. If you still hear Mostly Lost, thank you so much for your
large amount of money. Finally my missed bits.
I'm so sorry. What was I doing here? I don't know.
But thanks a lot, man. They say, here I assume this is what you paid for the game, so let me
reimburse you for it. Oh wait. The game was
just about, I think it was $50 total. Like $48 or something.
But thank you. German95, thanks for donating, dude.
What do I have for a sub count now? I have
over $5,800. It was almost $7,000
something, I think. I think it was just under $7,000. Was it $7,200
or something before? Like with the insane amount of community subs?
Yeah. There was like, I had over, was it over
$7,000 or was it up to, it's like $68 or something.
But we're at about $58. I think some of you guys, yeah $65.
There were so many community subs last month. It was ridiculous.
But thanks a lot, Mostly Lost. How do you handle the fluctuating
income as a streamer? Do you just live well below your income at any time?
Yeah, I mean, I just, I mean, for the most part
I think that as long as, like look, if you're paying your bills
and you pay for, you know, food and bills and
just because you're making, like I'm making
very, very good money from you guys. It's fucking insane.
But, I mean, living below your means, I mean,
five, six, seven, eight thousand subscriptions on Twitch. You talk, that's a ton
of money. So I just, you know, want to save
some money. I want to put a lot of money back into the stream, which is what I
try to do. I mean, I spend
a significant percentage of every dollar that I make from Twitch goes
back to, you know, studio shit and buying games and buying systems
and hiring people and so
I'd like to, because then there's another, I mean, obviously there's the realistic approach
too, right? Where, you know, if you make a really good amount of money
doing something like this, because it's such a
kind of volatile place, you know, like streaming and YouTube,
it's not like, oh, this is the amount of money that you're going to make and you're going to make that probably for
like five to ten years and maybe you could get a promotion, maybe that's the money you're going to make
for like two decades. Like, I have no idea. You know, there's really no way
to tell. So why not just try to
do what I can and save what I can and make as good of a stream
as I can while I'm here. But I'm along for the ride, however
long it takes. You know, wherever this train leads to, I'm
going to ride it. Let's just get on it, right? Like you might even go
way up in a couple months and then just drop off. No, yeah, it can. It can.
But I've been showered with such generosity
over the last year that I'm
I'm living well in my means. So thank you all for the
support for real. But hopefully that answers the question.
And let's go to... Kairatobi gave a shitload of community subs.
Winterly Parsley gave a bunch of community subs. It was like
fucking two or three hundred. That was a lot. A lot, a lot, a lot.
And then we had Lobotomized Teddy Bear gave a dollar. Jerma, I'm happy you're teaching chat about
African animals before they are all basically
dead in like 20 years. That's so morbid.
This is not... Oh, God.
Well, I hope you liked the elephant. Somebody mentioned about taxes. Yeah, I mean
there's taxes on every dollar that I make from Twitch.
You know, it's not just like, oh, this is the amount
of money you make from a sub and that's yours. You get to keep. No, there's taxes.
It's hard to do taxes when you just sort of completely
have 1099 as income is what it's called. So it can get like sloppy
if you don't stay on top of it. But I've been doing just fine.
I have a good tax person. I talk to them all the time. As long as you stay
on top of it. Tax boy. But thank you Lobotomized Teddy Bear.
A Louis, thanks for the one dollar, or Louis with a large underscore.
Thank you. People possum thanks for the five bucks.
They say forehead. Hey Jerma, I'm donating blood on Monday and they're
replacing it all with pee. I'm very excited.
Well, unfortunately, I don't know if that's a great idea.
Why would they replace your blood with pee? Well, if the first part
is true, that's really, really kind of you and good of you to do.
Hopefully it goes to somebody that really needs it. So thank you for doing that if that's true.
For the pee part, I would probably not sign
that waiver. I'm not sure you should do that.
But thank you. Thank you Tar Alacrin for the one dollar. Hey Jerma, great gameplay today. Really
riveting. And they do a sarcastic I'm smiling face.
Anyways, have you considered playing one of those new fangled
randomizers like a Zelda game? That are all the rage these days.
If you are worried about getting lost, I don't think it would be distinguishable from you playing a game normally.
Hopefully we see a couple of ehe's from that one.
Randomize the stuff though. Once I'm done with everything else
that I want to do. There's a bunch of shit that I want to do.
I bought a bunch of PlayStation 2 games. I've got to
admit it to you guys. I just went on a PlayStation 2 spree
again. I bought like 10 more. Already on top of the fucking
10 that is still there to be played. So we're going to have to do another
PlayStation 2. I got the Jaws game where you play as the shark.
I just had to buy it. I had to get it.
The game is great. I know. There's a lot to do.
Thank you Binary Man for the $5.11. Sorry Jerma,
but I had to. To anyone who can actually play this properly, I apologize
for the bad playing, but I learned it on the spot while waiting for the
stream to start. Well, what is it?
It's a YouTube link. Stream in the corner.
That's it. That's the whole thing.
Thank you so much. That sounded pretty great.
Thank you Binary Man. Thank you Dork Cube for the $1.
Firefox and Twitch don't mix too well, so when I went to look at the emotes
and saw that you had what looked like 50 emotes that were all duplicates, I was
confused. What the fuck? That's a weird bug.
That's a very strange bug. That's a lot of emotes.
Thank you Dork Cube for the $1. Hey Flank Tank, thanks for the $10.
$10 from Flank Tank. Hey, I heard from a little safari birdie
that on February 26, Nier Automata was releasing its own
prepared to die Scholar of the First Sin version with all the DLC for I think half off.
Not sure what the other changes will be, but that might be a good time to look into it.
Jerma Venus. Sure.
I've never played it. I never played the other one. There's like a series, right?
There's like Nier, then there's Nier Automata.
I don't know really anything about them. All I know is that they exist.
But thank you for the suggestion. I did not know that was coming out. I will definitely
be looking into it. Thank you for the $10. Hey Swiggity Swanky, thanks for the $3.
This is your situation with cocks right now.
There are discs all over me. There are discs in every single part of my life right now.
There's a disc over here. There's a disc over here. I got discs in front of me.
I got discs all over me. Covered in discs.
He knew what he was doing.
He knew what he was doing there, making a joke. Don't let him fool you.
That's got at least 22 thumbs up on the
comments section. He knows what he's doing, guys.
But thank you Swiggity Swanky for the $3. Super sale thanks
for the $1. If a hippo woke you up in the middle of the night and personally asked you to pee
in their urinal mouth. Why are you asking me this?
The answer is no. I would call the police.
Jess, you got it. Thanks for the $1. After two weeks, I managed to finish editing that video
of all the sounds you made in January. And then it broke in rendering and I couldn't
save it. I'm disappointed because it was pretty funny and I don't want to start over
so here is one of my favorites from the list of 300.
I'm so sorry to hear that. That sucks.
Oh, that's Simpsons Hit and Run. I remember that. That's from the Simpsons Hit and Run.
Adam Sandler. The TIE fighter.
I'm really sorry to hear about that though. That's happened to me
quite a few times. Where in Premiere
you're working on something for like three days and then all of a sudden it fucks up and the
save doesn't work. Or like you spend three hours on something and then you
lose the three hours of it. You go back and you're like what the fuck. I don't even want to
do this again. And then you try to get more re-motivated to do the same cuts
the same edits that you just did already. It's awful.
So I'm really sorry to hear that happen. But thank you for the
attempt and thank you for the clip. And thank you C4G for the $4.83
and they say pride. Hey you
fucking gamer. And they say pride. Hey, thank you.
For the $4.83. C4G. I'd like to call myself
a gamer sometime. Hey future gamers. Thanks for the $1.00. How much
have you used the Vive already? Have you not even put it on yet? I have not
logged into any Vive related games.
I have done the setup. So I painted the room
with the hand. Like I did the perimeter. I got everything ready to go.
So I've not played a game in it yet. Because I want
my first experience to happen on stream. So it does
fit. It does work. It's just a question of getting into a game, capturing it
and streaming it. And we will see how that happens tomorrow.
Again, like I don't want to be this guy that sits here and tells you
there might be a stream tomorrow. But there might not. But there might be a stream. But there may be not a
stream tomorrow. That's unfortunately the way I have to look at it right now.
Until this is confirmed, which it hasn't been. The technician I'm
working with has not closed the ticket yet.
So until that ticket is closed and yes that issue
is resolved, I can't tell you that I can
that there's going to be a stream tomorrow. I don't know. Because like again,
Italic streams from this location too. So we
have to both use it. So I'm sorry to say
that I wish I could tell you it was going to happen. But I don't know. We might have to wait until the day.
We'll see. I'm optimistic. At least he kept the ticket open.
Yeah, he's going to keep it open until it's like completely confirmed
that it is done and closed. Future gamer, thanks for the $1.
Again, I cannot wait to watch you WWE chair shot someone
in Blade and Sorcery. I don't know what that means, but I'm
looking forward to it. Whatever that is. Thank you Jamona Cucumber
for the $2. Hey Jerma, I don't know if you remember when I made the LEGO Glue Man
render. Well I made a Sneak Man render that I posted in Creative and it was a bit
shit. So I came back and took a running leap at it. I present Mr.
LEGO Sneak Man Remastered. LEGO Sneak Man!
He's got these like ripped abs. LEGO really,
LEGO is one of those things that will always be a thing.
The test of time has passed over LEGOs and they are still
just as popular and still just as relevant as they were
20-30 years ago. It will always be relevant.
Thank you Jamona Cucumber, it's a great render. The Glue Man one was great as well.
And they got a comparison. They say hey if you want a comparison, here are the two comparisons.
Let's take a look. The second one is a little cleaner.
There's some better shading on the second one. Looks good.
Thank you for that. Are the LEGO movies
really good? Aren't they really highly rated movies? Like LEGO
Batman and LEGO Island. Not LEGO Island, LEGO World.
What was the LEGO movie? That had like a 98% on Rotten Tomatoes or
something. So I mean they're doing just fine. Thank you
Yes Is Online for the one dollar my face win and I realize that all elephants are clay.
What does your face do? What the fuck?
This is an Alex Jones and Death Grips
mashup. That's what this is. Link it, link, link.
Here, here, here, I'm giving it to you.
Thank you for that. Yes Is Online. My face win, all elephants are clay.
Freudian Weapon thanks for the eleven dollars. I could honestly write an essay about how inspirational
you've been to me. Thank you for the eleven dollars and I
can't believe that somebody would say something like that. So thank you so much.
I'm happy that you can find any inspiration from this stream or from the videos.
That means a lot. Thank you so much, Freudian. Thank you for the eleven dollars. Appreciate it.
Coming up to Colorblind Samurai thanks for the five dollars
and twelve cents. Hey Germans, just want to let you know that you mean a lot more to a lot of
us than you know. A year ago today my dad died of brain
cancer. Fuck cancer. And since then I've graduated from college, gotten a really
good job. But none of that would have been possible if I couldn't watch your streams and
vlogs to help me get back mentally from whatever shitty place I was in.
All the love I've got to you, man. I'm incredibly fucking sorry
to hear that. I'll tell you something right now though. Graduated from
college, got a great job. They'd be really fucking proud of you. Thank you
so much for being part of this community. And yeah, fuck cancer.
Hopefully someday soon we will get rid of that fucking awful, awful,
awful, awful thing forever. Thank you so much,
Colorblind Samurai for the five dollars and twelve cents. And I know I just kind of butchered
your name. But you know, that means a lot. That means a fucking lot.
I'm happy to be able to tell you that I
appreciate the fuck out of you being here. And if I can even give you a semblance, even a
second of happiness, in a place where you're not having a good time,
then fuck yeah. I'm happy to be there.
Thank you so much again for your five dollars and twelve cents. And yeah, fuck cancer.
For real. And congratulations on getting a good job. Cheers to
you. And moving on from that we've got Vroom had one dollar Vroom.
If you want to emulate video games you have to pretend that you're on the legit
hardware. L-U-L. Well that's not to do with pretending. If you want to emulate
video games you have to pretend that you're on the, no. The emulators just some
there's a whole list of games that can't run on those emulators.
And some of them that do are classified by the
community involved in trying to get them to work. I remember
I tried, I tried. This is not, this didn't happen on stream.
This happened, this was like a long time ago. Like two or three years ago.
It's not that long ago. But WWF No Mercy is one of my favorite Nintendo 64
games ever. I've owned that game like three times.
It's my favorite N64 game. Is that game.
Now, I wanted to play it, you know, a couple years ago.
And what happened was I got, I was like, ah, how am I going to track down any of this shit?
I tried to emulate it. And there was a ton of weird bugs and
problems and glitches. And I couldn't get it to work properly no matter what tutorials I tried.
So from that day forward I decided I was going to, I'm going
just legit only, I'm going to buy the hardware and just play it the way it was meant to be played
on an Nvidia graphics card. But not really.
The way it was meant to be played. Sponsored. Oh, internet.
I just saw a flash of bad internet. But didn't you try to get
the ISO for that Dreamcast game a week ago? Yeah, but that's, but
that was desperate because I bought the game. I purchased
that game and it came to me, delivered to me
the game that I bought. And it wasn't in the case.
It was half of the game. So I figured that's, that's
not, I'm okay. I own that game. I currently
have it sitting right here. I bought it. That's different. You know, you
can't sure me on that one. I purchased the game and the game
was not there. I got the second disc of two discs
for a game that I purchased and I can't just go to like Walmart or like
GameStop and buy a new one. The game doesn't even fucking exist anymore.
They're selling it like third party, fourth party.
So of course I'm going to look into some alternative actions and ways to make it work.
You guys act like that was like fucking, that was
like Battlefield 4. I can still, I can go buy that right now
and get it. They probably still sell that game at Walmart. Yeah, fourth party.
But here's the thing. Once you get the hardware, once you
slowly build up, like I've got PlayStation 1, I got the Dreamcast, I got PlayStation 2,
I got, well I had a Sega CD and then I gave it to
a friend of mine. But the point is then you have it all and you own it all.
And if you ever want to play like an N64 game, bingo, just go
get it and you just stick it in there and cap it and you can play it like
one to one real time the way it was meant to be played on the cartridge.
It's getting late to get this upset. I'm not upset. I'm just speaking matter of factly.
And then it breaks. And then you go get the emulator.
And you pretend that you're not on the emulator. Thank you though, Vroom. Appreciate it.
Sly 161, thanks for the $1. Hey, Jerma, it's midnight on the East Coast and that means it's officially
my birthday. Did you get me anything cool? I got you a
finger snap. No, happy birthday, Sly.
I don't know exactly how old you are, but happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Oh, cartridges die constantly. Well then I would back it up.
I would make the ROM myself. That's not against the law. I would put the ROM device in.
I would pull it from the source and I'd make my own ROM from my own cartridge.
That's what I would do. That's what I would be doing. But thank you, Sly. Happy birthday.
DorkCube, thanks for the $1. Hey, Jerma, I hope you and Kim
and Italics had a happy Valentine's Day. Well, I didn't have
a Valentine this year. I did find out that my brother is going to propose to his girlfriend tomorrow.
So I'm pretty excited. That's exciting stuff. I wish
your brother the best of luck and many years of happiness for you
and your brother. But yeah, me and Kim had a good...
We did a Valentine's Day before Valentine's Day
because it was also our anniversary on the 13th. So we did like a dual
let's go out and go to dinner and do like a Valentine's Day
before Valentine's. It's like Christmas with your birthday at the same time. You know, if you have your birthday the day before
Christmas, you know, you celebrate your birthday
and Christmas on the same day. It's a dual day. That's right.
What a ripoff. What? Ripoff. But thank you, DorkCube.
I wish luck to your brother and his girlfriend.
DemonicCucumber, thanks for the $1. This guy is asking the real questions. Who?
It's an immigrant link. Let's see. I'm trying to actually
gain some muscles on my bony arms, but I don't know where to start. Any recommendations for how I can get
started and be like 2012 Jerma? Yes.
Eat. You just, you gotta eat and eat and eat.
It's coming from a skinny, skinny, skinny guy.
You need to eat a shitload. And that does not mean McDonald's.
Okay? I'm not talking about, yeah, just go get like a large
pizza from Domino's and eat that and then go, no, no, no. You need high
quality, quality protein. You need to make sure that you're taking
a good amount, a good high quality protein a little bit before
and especially after you work out. Within like an hour,
within 30 minutes to an hour of you lifting weights, you've got to take in a high quality protein.
Your muscles need to recover, god damn it. You need to be eating a lot of calories,
but you don't want to eat bad garbage food. You want to eat high quality,
high calorie foods. This is kind of disgusting.
I'll tell you guys a little tidbit. Something that I used to do, but I do not, this is not advice.
I'm not giving advice to anybody. I don't want anyone to take this and be like, oh,
that's what I should do. Back when I was trying to really gain
mass, I would, does anybody know what tahini
is? Tahini. Tahini
is how they, it's what's in hummus. So hummus
is usually chickpeas, tahini,
and garlic and maybe a little bit of lime. It is
ground up sesame seeds and it is the highest
caloric food you can possibly eat pound for pound.
It is one of the highest calorie foods you could possibly eat
and I used to eat it like peanut butter. Speaking of peanut butter,
let's move on from that. Don't do what I do,
but tahini is really, really good. You put it on a salad,
you put it in, just use it where you should be using it. Don't eat spoonfuls of it like a psycho
because, I mean, it's like 300 calories a spoonful. Don't do that.
But peanut butter, that's your best friend. If you like peanut butter,
you can eat a lot of it and not really feel that guilty, but it's
high in fat. Just be careful. Don't go crazy because you don't want to cause
a stomach problem or a digestive issue for yourself if you're just like, oh, I gotta eat a jar of
peanut butter every day. High quality proteins, especially after you fucking work out.
But I used to just do a spoonful of tahini before bed.
It's not bad for you, it's a sesame seed paste, sesame seed spread, it's good.
Put it on a piece of toast. Somebody's mentioning fish, yes.
We're talking, I used to eat, but I don't, this is like bad advice though.
I used to eat tuna out of a can like a cat. I would eat like a can
of tuna. I would eat like the cheap,
cheapest tuna I could get out of a can. It was like
78 cents a can. Tuna's amazing, I love tuna fish, but I
ate it a lot, too much. I hate like the tuna fish.
But I did gain weight. Salmon,
there's also like the rock. Okay, listen to the rock, but don't listen to the rock
because the rock ate like 12 pounds of cod a day or something,
right? Fish is the best possible food you can eat if you really want to like body build
it, so it's just like good, high quality protein and high quality fats.
Don't think that just eating more is better. Like I said, going to get like a Big Mac every day is going to cause
you way more problems. The rock eats a three layer cake for breakfast
every day. But yeah, I loved when I was working out, I loved cod,
I loved tuna, I loved salmon. Chicken, just like
chicken breast is really easy to eat and really easy to make.
You can make a ton of it and just have like, you know, but don't eat like
fucking meats. Get like some good nice lean chicken breast.
Cook it up. Get some carrots in there. You want to eat a good amount of carrots
and like greens. You want a balanced, good diet. You want to be lifting
and you want to fucking bring those high quality proteins into your life. After you work out especially.
Don't rely, don't rely on the shit in the box
that says like, oh yeah, this is all these things in this box. Drink it.
Got to eat food. You can supplement with those like fucking drinks.
You can supplement with the drinks, but don't make those drinks
the main course for your routine. Eat carrots
before and after you work out. No, you don't have to do that. But yeah, I have not
been to the gym in a long time. I just got,
I wish I could still do it. It started getting harder to do post
30. It really did. 33, 34, it's
got hard to do. I really am deteriorating, huh?
Okay, if I was streaming, if I, okay, rewind
the clock, but also fast forward the clock, okay? If I
was where, if I'm right now in the twitch.tv seat
here, German 985 right now, and it's me
from 2012 sitting here, and I would have the webcam on, you guys
would see just how fucking jacked and handsome I was. People would be
commenting on it all the day. I would look over and like, I would
see my huge fucking arm in the rear view mirror,
and I would look over at chat and be like, fuck man, he's huge.
How did he get, he's fucking so jacked, and I'd be like, yeah, fuck, I am, yeah, yeah.
I wouldn't say that, but I'd be like, yeah, yeah, not anymore. Well, I look like I made
it a clay. It's amazing, it's really, here's the thing, it's amazing that
you never like see yourself age, but
there are certain specific things that I know and do that, because you
talk, I mean, talking about 2011 is when I started on YouTube, 2012.
Really, I like got going really in 2012. I made
a bunch of videos in 2011, but it's weird to see that over almost
seven to eight years, going from like 25 to
like 32, 26 to like 33,
it's a long time, you don't really even think about it. You look at, I look at
old videos, old photos from like 2010, 2011,
I'm just like, holy shit, I am like, I'm starting to look like my
father. When I look at photos of me now instead of almost 10 years ago,
I look like my father, I can see it, it's weird. Dad
streamer, I know, it's weird, but I'm not sure how we got on that, but it was
an interesting talk nonetheless. Thank you though, DemonicCucumber, for your
two dollars here. Hey Jerma, while I was watching your iSpy stream, I showed
my mum, yes the one who said you were attractive, some of my
renders, and we kept having to switch back because of your crazed rant
about the hot dog eating bear. She thought it was very funny, so
thanks on her behalf and mine for the laugh.
That's a great transition into the conversation we were just
having.
I love it. Thank you DemonicCucumber, and thank you mum.
Flugboy, thanks for the one dollar, I threw something together very quickly.
Let's see what they threw together. Is this a JoJo thing?
It's up perfectly. Why the fuck aren't the hippos yawning?
Here, take a look, there it is. It's apparently me stomping on a
what am I stepping on? And that's not even me, but
do I just automatically assume every anime I ever get shown is a JoJo's
Bizarre Adventure reference? Have we gotten there?
But thank you Flugboy. Thank you Captain Morgan for the one dollar they should
have got you to play younger Willem Dafoe in Aquaman. Why aren't you
out there acting?
I don't know. I'm doing this. I don't need to like,
go be an actor somewhere. This is an act.
No, I'm saying like, I don't gotta go like, move to Hollywood and like
start my acting career. I got this whole damn community, why would I
do that? Jerma can't act, yes I can, I can act
circles around anybody you could possibly put me in front of. I'm talking, anybody.
Especially, you talk about like Twitch, YouTube, but you find me somebody on like Twitch
YouTube that's a better actor than I am. I'll act anyone. And if you want to
make it a competition, let's do it. Find me somebody that like wants to be an actor, like
we'll have an acting composition in Las Vegas, in studio,
scripts, scenes, and I will destroy them all.
It won't even be a competition. You guys, I'm gonna upload the fuck away.
Give me something like, you gotta give me something like real, real fucking heavy too.
I'll be like a method actor, I'll fucking like smash something and fucking get like
lightning bolt, you'll hear me say all kinds of fucking swears. He's on his high
horse now. No, I can, I can out act anybody. I'm certain of it.
More like a meth actor, what the fuck. I'll show up
in like a big scarf and huge sunglasses
drinking like a really tiny coffee. I will destroy them.
Maybe one day. But thank you to Demonic Cucumber again
for the one dollar. It's weird to hear that the bit's minimum is going up.
I'll be okay. I usually donate about five dollars when I can.
I suppose I'll have to make my messages more compact. I do worry about the others
in the EU and those viewers everywhere else because bits are quite a bit more expensive
in some parts of the world. But I'm sure we'd be happier to put less strain on you
at the end of streams. Anyway, Jerma Heart as usual, mind how you go,
handsome boy. Yeah, I mean, it was not something that I just did
for either no reason or because I take it lightly.
I don't want to increase minimums to read, but sometimes
we have to make the stream,
the stream still has to be efficient. And as much as I would love to
be able to hang out all night and read bits, as the channel
grows, we have to keep the stream an efficient stream. We have to keep the stream
rolling and it gets late.
The stream ended at
about seven hours. So that was when the game was over.
The broadcast was pretty much just like, all right, the game's done. The thing that I
want to do tonight is done and we're going to hang out for a little bit afterwards.
But when it gets to a point where you've got like seven, eight, nine, ten hours,
there's two different options. There's either streamline it
to go really fast and read names and say,
oh, thank you, demonic key come for the one dollar. Thank you, unconquerable for the one dollar.
Thank you, mostly lost for the one dollar. Gambling addiction hotline.
That's funny. Thank you, unconquerable for a dollar. Thank you, Alex for the ten bucks. You deserve
something for that. I could blow through them. But that's not what the end of my
streams, that's not what I want to do. So streamlining the end
process and not bogging it down is
the goal. The German doesn't know the entire community is five guys making
fake accounts. As your audience grows, that will be harder.
I mean, look, we have to face a, you know,
a potential reality here. And that is, I'm not saying this is going
to happen, but if it does, you look at some streams that have
three, four, five thousand concurrent viewers, ten thousand concurrent viewers.
Sometimes some of these streams have six, seven, eight, nine, ten thousand
concurrent viewers. It's almost impossible to keep up.
Like actually impossible to keep up. So
the reality is if the channel keeps growing and if the community keeps
growing, these things are going to have to keep happening.
Not to an extent of, I mean, I would never make a bit reading minimum, but maybe
the bit reading minimum changes or doesn't happen anymore. Maybe, I don't know.
I can't tell you that it's, I have no idea what's going to happen. All I can
do is day to day, month to month, you know,
by yearly, maybe like once every year or two,
try to figure out solutions to keep the stream
going in an efficient and streamlined and fun way. Because as much as
people love this end of the stream portion of every single stream
I do now, there are a lot of people that just leave, right?
There are people that are just like, alright, he's got to the end of the stream, I'm out of here. And
you know, people will pop back in and be like, oh wait, you're still streaming? It's been like
three hours, you're still doing the end of the stream? Somebody's gave fifty dollars. Am Scoots,
thanks for fifty bucks. And they say, greedy streamer. But they think at the end,
thank you for the fucking fifty dollars. At the end of the day,
I also have to take into consideration, you know, me.
Right? Like I'm still, I'm the
one that's sitting in the chair and talking and I have to try to make it easy
for me to do as well. And if the end of the streams,
if like the second stream ends up being like a two, three,
four hour experience after the stream is over, you know, it can be hard
to do that. You know, every stream can't be
seven hours, eight hours of a stream, and then three,
four hours for reading bits. And a lot of what
somebody just mentioned, VR Josh just mentioned, would you ever consider having text to speech
donations? Absolutely not. Never. It'll never happen on this channel. It will never happen.
I cannot ever do it. Because
I have the opinion that text to speech audio
is, it kind of just gets in the way of the stream, like of the broadcast.
That's just my opinion on it. That's just how I feel about it. I'm not saying
that it's a wrong way to do your stream. It's just, I have,
I can't pay attention to that. I can't be trying to do something over here and
oh, let me take a picture of like the rhino. And then all of a sudden, bang! And somebody's like talking
in my ear. I do much better when I have very little distractions
because I'm so easily distracted anyways. And text to speech,
what text to speech can sometimes do is turn
a stream into a
just, everybody's just fucking writing random shit
that's just gonna be blasted out to a ton of people. So it's less about
hey, this person is streaming this game, or this person is streaming this event or something, and more
just full blasting voice talking
out loud to a bunch of people. But people run their communities the way that they want to
and that's fine. And I do see like the fun
in somebody having a system where you can just kind of be
on stream. Like that's kind of fucking fun. That's kind of cool. Having somebody pop
up and just be like, their name pops up and this is them talking.
And they can say, they can just like shitpost, they can say something funny, they can say something interesting.
I understand that. But I don't think I'd ever want that on my stream.
So I have to figure out other ways to
interact with the community. And I think, I thought this was a decent idea
kind of just doing reading and hanging out at the end of a stream when
I'm not gonna get distracted by messages or
sounds or noises or, and I felt like this solution
was the best one. But this solution is so strange, I think, that it
needs constant care to still work.
So that's why things like minimums have to increase. That's why eventually
maybe some other things might have to change about it as well. But I'm not gonna cross any of those
bridges until it's certain of what those things have to be. So at the end
of the day, as of this weekend here, we are going up to $2.50.
$2.50 to help streamline the end of the stream.
And it was three. It was three. So I did
bring it down back from three because of the way the bits are purchased.
We'll keep going. We'll see. But thank you, Demonic Cucumber.
Thank you, Unconquerabee for the $1. Shut up and play.
I'm not sure what I was doing, but hopefully I shut up and played.
Or maybe I didn't. Maybe I decided I wanted to do something else.
Maybe if I didn't want to play and I wanted to just say something, maybe that's what I'm gonna do.
Maybe that's gonna happen. But thank you. Thank you, Mostly Lost for the $1.
The National Gambling Addiction Hotline. Oh, there it is again. Keep that in mind whenever you go
triple or nothing on a bet and lose within 30 seconds. I went triple or nothing and I won.
Thank you, Unconquerabee for the $1. Again, I enjoyed watching this edition of
German 985, The Legend of the Triple Dog Beer. Anyway, it's been a while and I haven't donated
in a bit. Glad I got to catch a bit of this stream before I slept.
Can't wait for the next stream and I hope you keep your gambling tendencies to a minimum.
Much love, German Heart. Thank you. No, it was a lot of fun. I liked this game
and I liked this stream and I liked this. It was fun. We had a good time.
Alex Onyx, thanks for the $10. You deserve something for that.
$10 apparently from Alex. Thank you.
Unhealthy Habits. You guys act like...
Like, I gotta make gambling references.
I live in Las Vegas, right? That's an easy joke.
I got so many easy gambling and casino references to make because I live here.
That's like 75% of the reason why I moved here. So I can make
casino reference jokes because it's easy comedy. And if you believe that,
the fuck. But thank you, Alex. Thank you, Most of the Lost for the $1. You know the game has a
lot of its... You know the game has lost its comedic value when the funniest thing you
can do is be silent for 15 minutes. And that was fun.
It was fun. Hey, German 985! Thanks for the 50 community subs, German
985. And then HaHaHaKuma
gave 50 as well, making the 100 community subs
original bet be paid off completely. The debt has been cleared.
Thank you so much. Thank you, Jerma. Thank you so
much, man. Holy fuck. How much fucking money is that? How much money is that? How much fucking money
is that shit? But thank you, HaHaHa. That was... You didn't... You didn't have to
do that. And you did, so thank you. PizzaBot. Thanks for the $5, PizzaBot.
I'm pretty sure you almost hit enlightenment with being quiet for so
long. Something or other thanks to the $1 didn't make a business logo,
went with a shitty postcard instead. Yeah, that
works too. That works too. Greetings from Toronto.
Welcome to Brazil. What? It does make a pretty good postcard.
Thank you Clueless Sniper for the $1. Mostly lost. Thanks for the $1.
Also, please don't feel bad about missing my bits. It's really not a big deal.
Yeah, but it was a lot of money. And I don't ever want to bypass
somebody's major massive monetary contribution
to the stream. You know, it's... I want to make sure that you
know that I see it. Because it's a lot of money. But thank you.
Thank you Flammable Cow for the $10. May I suggest you play Spongebob Squarepants
Battle for Bikini Bottom. I was hovering over the purchase button, but I didn't
buy it. Love the streams. You're a great guy. Keep doing you.
I was going to buy Spongebob Square, but I didn't know what to do. There's like
six PlayStation 2, PlayStation 3, Nickelodeon, Spongebob
included games. And I didn't know which one was the one to buy. Is it Battle for Bikini Bottom?
Is that the one? Is that the one that I'm going to beat on stream?
Is that the Simpsons Hit and Run 2 where I play that game for like a 12 hour session and beat the whole game?
Is that an angry game? Am I mad at that game?
No? Is it just fun? Is that a game where you have to be
picture perfect? Yeah, Nicktoons Unite is one that I saw.
I was going to get it. Did you actually beat Hit and Run? Oh yeah.
I did it in one stream. I sat there for like 13 hours and did the whole thing.
I probably lost a handful of brain cells doing it, but
I still did it. But yeah, you'll probably see that at some point soon.
Silver Catalyst. Thanks for the five dollars, Silver Catalyst.
Hey Jerm, I've been watching you for around five years, but only recently been watching
your streams, and it's phenomenal how much joy you bring to me. Love your content.
Also, have you seen this rhythm game called Osu? Someone mapped
Rats Birthday Mixtape and it's one of the hardest maps ever full combo'd.
Did somebody link this before?
Yeah, I remember this. So hold on a second. Do I have the hardest
level in Osu? Do I have the hardest level in the game? No?
This is 655pp. What's that mean? Am I in the top 50
hardest levels in the game? This is a rhythm game, right?
655 is really high actually, really. That's cool. I think we watched that once before.
But that's really cool.
Hardest game for the streamer that plays the hardest games and is really focused
and gets the job done on stream. That's what I say.
Is there a Rats Mixtape map in Beat Saber? I think there is. I think somebody showed it to us
a while ago. PP is the scoring system. It's one of the hardest maps
DW. Alright, well that's crazy.
Thank you to the five dollars, Silver Catalyst, and thanks for the video.
Good luck on all you Osu players. I think you can beat the Rats Mixtape
level. It's the hardest level in the game. Good luck.
Uripterida.
Thanks for the one dollar. College is stressful but your streams always brighten my day.
Germahart. Gonna be a vet tech when I'm done with this. Awesome.
Told you guys this before. If I wasn't a streamer or a tuber,
either one, I would probably go into the veterinary field
to do with animals. I would own a backyard with a bunch of
acres of land and I have an elephant. I don't know how to pronounce it either.
Okay, good. That's good. And then we have two dollars from
Garfield the Monday Killer. We've got two very large
Garfagraphs here. Why am I even saying the word
Garfagraph? It's a paragraph. Don't call it a Garfagraph.
Hey there Germah, long time no bits. Garf has been out on a Himalayan expedition of magnificent
magnitude, still murdering Mondays as usual,
but a whole lot of toony business I had to take care of. Dick Dasterly
and Muttley even stole all of Garf Bucks and I had to team up with Twitch
staff in order to put those villains behind bars. How was your Valentine's, Germah? Garf had a surprisingly
good one despite the Monday-like break up of a few months ago. My two gal
pals and I made a sorry I ran out of space on the last
Garfagraph. He he. Anyway, we all, we weren't, we went out and
did sweet things for one another. We may not be romantically interested, but just hanging out with two good pals
is just as Garfy. In case you want to know who they are,
it was Cora from Avatar and Sombra from Overwatch. Okay.
Yeah, Garf hangs out with Sombra for some reason. That sounds like a funny
LARPing cartoon joke, but those two actually go to conventions as those
characters. They're very, they're, thank you Garfield
for the two dollars. I'm glad you're doing well.
Tingy, thanks for the one dollar. Cox has delayed this, but here's my hundred dollar message. Thank you, Tingy.
Yeah, sorry about the stream dying after like an hour and forty minutes a few
days ago. It was not my intention. I'm sorry that some people got left in
the dust there, so thank you so much for the huge amount of money. This two dollar and
fifty cent increase is going to cut into Garfield's savings.
Gold Ruby production, thanks for the one dollar.
How is Shito doing? Hope he is well. Shito's doing great.
He's been asleep for like seven days. That's typically how it works.
You know how a camel only has to eat or drink like once or like every
two weeks? Shito is like a camel. Instead of
eating, he sleeps for like two weeks and then gets up and eats
some dog food. His favorite. Wakes up
and plays himself as an instrument. He talks.
That sounded really bad.
If a pet is sleeping for seven days, it means it's
dead.
That's so terrible. Yeah, he's been sleeping for seven
days. Thank you, Gold Ruby production. Shito's doing
just fine. Anything else? Show official. Thanks for the six bucks.
You ever thought about playing New Vegas with mods? I know you played New Vegas, but the stream was pretty great.
I thought with mods it would be funnier. Also, you're amazing.
That's incredibly nice thing to say about somebody. Thank you for that. And to answer the question,
not now. Not now. Revisiting old stuff
or games that I played before and adding new content
is something that we need to go back to eventually.
Maybe. Because it needs to be like out of my brain completely. I know it's been a few
years, but it might be worth doing. The thing is though, once you do
mods, once I do like fucking mods, the game is just
forever. I can never go back ever again. That happened with the Skyrim.
Did I do that in Oblivion? I did not do it with Oblivion. I did it with Skyrim,
and I never went back and played Skyrim the same way ever again. So, putting a bunch of like
crazy, fun, interesting mods into
New Vegas. Oh my god.
Another 50 bucks from Amskoods. 100 dollars total from Amskoods.
I take it back, you're not a greedy streamer with a smiley face. Hey, thanks.
Thank you for the 100 bucks. That's a ton of money. But yeah,
I'm not opposed to the idea. It does sound fun.
Thank you Dorkcube for the one dollar. How does Garfield always know exactly what to write in order to confuse Jeremy?
Well, it's not like confusing. It's just like
two paragraphs of stuff that
isn't even real. It's just like huge strings
of shit that's not even real. It's just like talking about John
and going like grocery store shopping. Hey, speaking of Garfield, the Monday
killer. Thanks for the one dollar. I actually stopped donating bits to give
Jerma a break from my Garfer graphs, but that last reading might have been one of
the hardest he struggled to get through it. Oh my gosh, Jerma, I'm so sorry.
Please don't hate the Garf. He just wants to make you laugh. Take that back.
You fuck.
I gotta give pauses between statements.
Because I'm gonna copy and paste that.
Look, look. See, this is me
quoting Dorkcube. But thank you Garfield. No,
the stuff you say is fucking funny. It's hard for me to follow. There's so much going on
in the Garfield lore. But thank you so much, Garfield. What happened to the music?
I need you to laugh at my joke.
Poor Garfield. No, everybody loves Garfield. Well, nobody likes
Garfield. But the fake Garfield that's not the real Garfield
is in this community and everybody loves the fake Garfield. More like
dumb985. Why do people get me to try to
read the same thing? Please laugh at this. Why would I laugh at that?
What? This is the real Garfield. This is not the real Garfield.
This is the better Garfield. This is like the original Garfield when
he used to be fat and funny. Instead of like a plush toy
that has a cartoon. Garfield the Monday Killer with the dollar.
What are you talking about, Jerma? I'm the real Garfield. Come on, folks. Give Jerma a round of applause.
What a funny Garfster. And this is the video.
That was the Will Smith Genie.
Oh, man. There it is.
Alright, I'm going to make a prediction. You ready?
If I, we're going to price is right this. Or at least like
over under a little bit here. I'm okay. The Aladdin live action
movie will have within five percentile
28% on Rotten Tomatoes. Okay. So that means
if it's anywhere within 5, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32,
33, 28, 27, 26, 25, 34, 23.
28%. If I get it dead on, then I get the jackpot. If
the live action Aladdin has a higher Rotten Tomatoes than Venom,
I'll be very surprised. What is Venom at right now? I think it's like
32, right? 29. Okay, 29% on Rotten Tomatoes
right now. 28%. See you in like three weeks.
Wait, when does that movie come out? Like next year? I have no idea.
But thank you, Garfield. And thank you, that was
awesome. I believe we're not awesome. Awesome Triss.
That video. And finally, two more here. Dorkcube, thanks for the one dollar.
You're making me mad, mister. Stop saying Garfield isn't real. He is real. I know it.
He eats lasagna, and lasagna is real. Explain that.
Lasagna is like as if somebody took a fucking textbook,
wet all the pages, and in between each page put a bunch
of cheese and sauce, and then put it in the fucking oven.
When did I tell you it didn't taste good? I didn't tell you it didn't taste good. When did I
say that? When did I say that lasagna is bad? When did I say that
lasagna is not tasty? It's just a textbook that has
been wet and put in the oven and cheese all over it. It's still good?
Uh oh, he's getting political again. Guys, I love lasagna. I'm fucking kidding.
I actually haven't eaten lasagna in probably five years.
That's a real 5% statement. I have
not eaten lasagna in five years. If I'm going to have lasagna,
I just want chicken parm instead. No, that's not a lie.
I have not had lasagna. I have not eaten lasagna maybe even in ten years.
I don't think I have. I don't think so. Fettuccine Alfredo.
I want that. Lasagna. Is that on the menu? No.
What else is on the menu? I'm not going to order lasagna.
You can't even order lasagna at a restaurant. You have to make lasagna.
What restaurant has lasagna on the menu? I've never seen
just default lasagna at an Italian restaurant. The Olive Garden?
You can't put Olive Garden. Every Italian restaurant
has lasagna on the menu. They don't? I'm talking about
nobody has a default lasagna. Risotto.
Uh, rigatoni.
Fettuccine Alfredo. Chicken broccoli ziti. Chicken parm.
Chicken marsala. Shrimp scampi. No, just because it's had
chilies. Yeah, alright, so there's a lasagna at like
Friday's. Meatballs, right? Let's look at the TGI
Friday's menu and see what they got. Okay, we got loaded chicken nachos.
Cheeseburger sliders. Philly cheesesteak egg rolls.
What the fuck? Philly cheesesteak egg rolls. Wings roulette
platter. Chicken quesadilla. No, we've got to go down. Friday's classics.
Bucket of bones. That's what this is actually called.
Whiskey sliders. Chicken strips.
Come on, where is it? There's mozzarella sticks. Wings.
Burgers. Soups and salads. I'm not making
that up. It actually says bucket of bones. Sandwiches.
Pasta. Here we go. Nope. Cajun shrimp and chicken pasta.
Chicken parmesan pasta. Lemon and garlic shrimp pasta.
Alright, Olive Garden. Olive Garden. Olive Garden
menu. Okay, if there is no default
lasagna on this menu, you guys have to apologize to me. Okay,
we're looking for the dinner menu at Olive Garden. Okay,
we've got appetizers. Create your own pasta bowl.
Classic favorites. Okay, what do we got for a classic favorite?
It's like, here we go. Bolognese.
Creamy mushroom. Ravioli. A tour of Italy.
Cheese ravioli. Shrimp alfredo. Seafood alfredo. Chicken alfredo.
Chicken parm. Chicken scampi. Five cheese ziti.
Fettuccine alfredo. Eggplant parm. Lasagna classico.
I've never seen a lasagna on a menu at an Italian restaurant.
Olive Garden does not count. No, Olive Garden
doesn't count. Olive Garden is not an Italian restaurant.
Olive Garden is like the subway of Italian restaurants. What's wrong with subway?
They're going under. I got some real, real bad news for all you subway
fans. I don't see that company still existing in like 20
years. And they're taking all the lasagna with them. Feels bad, man.
It's because they don't have lasagna. It's the first time I've ever seen lasagna on a menu.
I swear to God. I'm okay with that.
I haven't had it. I haven't eaten
lasagna in five fucking years. I'm not kidding. I swear.
Wait, am I hearing right that lasagna is also not Italian?
Hold on a minute. Where does lasagna come from? Italy.
Lasagna, in Italy at least, has never been an everyday dish.
Those delicate sheets of fresh egg pasta, the complex sauces and ingredients
for the filling, it'd be a momentous occasion
to be with all that work. That's why in the North, lasagna
is not even, they don't even eat it there. Lasagna.
All right. I'm sorry, man. But look, look. I mean, that looks
like as appetizing as a catcher's mitt.
Somebody worked hard on that. It's not their fault. Lasagna just looks like
that. Lasagna just looks like cat puke.
That's not, look, you can make the best lasagna in the world.
It tastes good, it's not, but it looks like
a catcher's mitt. Lasagna.
Garfield, what have you done? What if your mother made you lasagna? Would you say it looked
like cat puke? No, I would eat it and I think it was delicious. Guys,
it's pasta sheets, a bunch of cheese, and a ton of
sauce. That doesn't taste bad. What's, there's nothing wrong
with it. It's, that's all it is. It's pizza
with dough or your bread. At least we don't eat canned tuna. I'm banning
this guy. How do I do that? I just gifted them a
sub. Alright, hold on. Yeah, I get fucking banned.
Yeah, I get banned. Like, that's really close to ban person.
There's like, add friend, whisper, gift a sub, and then like
right there is also ban. Like, ban is not even
two inches away from gift sub. Alright, now I'm actually, now I'm gonna ban you.
I'm gonna get banned for like a day. Alright, it's time to go. I gotta get
ahead of here. Lasagna tastes great, it's delicious, it's wonderful.
It's just, it's not on Italian menu. It's on
Olive Garden and like Friday's secret menu. You gotta order from the secret
menu. German, please laugh, please. Just pretend laugh at my joke.
I need your Boston laughs. What was the joke?
Wait, what are you spamming this for? You can take the sub back.
I can't take the sub back. I'm not gonna ban you. I'm just, why
would I ban you? Did I just give you like a three month sub?
Wow, okay, I'm loud, alright.
Just, I did it. Subway isn't going under.
It's gonna happen. Does that work? German 95 is gifted a, no
it was tier one. I see it in my streamlabs. More like
Uglyma985.
Like that. Hey QWWQ4, thanks for the one dollar.
They say meatball, what is this? This is not a real website. Hey Dork Cube
thanks for the one dollar. Get fucked. Lasagna Classico for the goddamn win.
I didn't, I like lasagna. This is just, this is
a bullshit article that was written about me in chat how I don't like lasagna.
I said it was delicious, I said it was full of delicious flavors, and then I love,
I would eat it. When did I ever say that? Hey Zazzasalt,
thanks for the one dollar. A while ago you mentioned wanting a short co-op game to play with italics.
I recommend Monaco. What's yours is mine. It's a co-op heist game
that I think would be great stream material. I've actually heard of that
game. We were looking at stuff recently. Some PS3
stuff maybe we could do together. Cause we have all these old consoles.
But Dork Cube thanks for the one dollar. You're making me mad mister. Stop saying Garfield isn't real.
I thought this was a lasagna thing again. Alright, look at the source.
Zazzasalt says someone's mom made this and now she's crying. But did you
not hear my statement about how all lasagna
looks like that? Gordon Ramsey could make a lasagna.
And it would still look like that. That's just what lasagna is.
It's just a ton of layered sheets of pasta and
sauce all over it with a shit load of cheese stuffed in it.
I'll make it on stream. I can do it.
Last two here, thank you Juno. Scepto over the three bucks.
Thanks for the stream. I don't know why I couldn't stop laughing at a man literally not talking or remoting
over for ten minutes. It was hard. But thank you.
Glad to have you. QWWQ4 thanks for the one dollar. It's the
menu for Spaghetti Warehouse. Don't be mean to lasagna.
Lasagna. But thank you guys. Let's take a look at the
video. There's going to be a shit load of subs that scroll up here really fast. Cause as you know
there were a ton of community subs. And here they come.
Thank you everybody. General please tell me a bedtime story that will help me sleep.
Once there was a young prince
that lived in a castle. He was really
really good at Fortnite. So one day he got the
Victory Royale in Fortnite. I'm really rusty on these aren't I?
Mentioning Fortnite. I said Fortnite and it threw me off.
This is lagging. It's going so fast. That was a shitty story. Tell us a better one.
It was a shitty story. Blah blah blah blah blah.
It was a shitty story. Blah blah blah. You want a better one? Fine.
How about this one? This one's called...
I'm just going to come up with more than a fly here.
Okay so you got a... Okay how about...
I got a decent one. We got a
small one cause we were just doing stuff about animals. A fawn was
racing in the forest. He was ahead of a rabbit.
He was very fast coming through. He was ahead of the elephant.
The fawn is faster than the elephant. The fawn is faster than the rabbit.
He leapt and cleared the stream. He ran past
the crumbling wall of dirt. There was a large boulder on the
grassy plain. He stumbled and fell down.
He burst into tears and the monkey massaged his leg.
Tears flowed from the fawn's eyes.
The brother bear picked him up. The fawn didn't stop crying. His mother came.
She said, look we'll beat up this bad boulder. The fawn said, oh don't
do that. Then the boulder will also start crying. His mother laughed. So did the fawn.
That's the story. Ten more community subs just came in.
What's the moral of the story? I don't know. You don't have any fucking idea what the moral of
this story is. It's a cute story that's told by some kid or something. I don't know.
Amscoots, ten community subs. Thank you Amscoots.
Really appreciate it. It's a lot. Was this story generated by an AI?
I don't think so. And those of you that want to like
this is a children's book right? Was my book better than this book?
This book, this is a book. This book was originally published.
This is a published book. This is exactly what I have to say.
The person just did the, they did fawn racing
in forest and then they made this up. They had the random number
generator. Are you still on the children's book joke? Yeah, then we've been going
this whole time. I've been streaming for like four days straight.
I've written like five books. But that's gonna be it. Thank you
everybody for hanging out. Again, I'm not entirely sure
what tomorrow is going to hold. So
tentative that I'll be live tomorrow. But the next time that I am live, whether it's
tomorrow or a day from now, we will be doing
live. I'm gonna get into it. I'm gonna get started. I'll see you when I see you.
The sus is probably gonna be weird or inaccurate for a day or two.
So I'll be here tomorrow afternoon to let you guys know what's happening.
So regardless if I stream or not tomorrow, I'll be here at around like
2, 2.30 tomorrow just to let everybody know what's gonna happen. Or maybe I'll make a
tweet or something. Just check my socials, you know. Have a great night.
Thanks for hanging out. This is Blast as always. See you guys soon.