My legs are so weak, I really need to strengthen them on the treadmill.
The Tower of the Goat was once key to the treasure of the gold buried underneath. Mortimus, the
grey goat, held the tea to the tower for generations. And Excalibur, the black and white goat.
What? Somebody on the computer over there? What's that? They're eating dinner? Hi. Hi,
I'm Mr. Goat. I hope you're enjoying your dinner. This game is amazing. Trampoline,
baby. I used to have one of these in my backyard. Want to see what I used to do in the trampoline,
I'm going very high. Hold on, this does not seem to be right. Nobody can really jump this
high on a trampoline. Catch me! Catch me please! Help! Not gonna invite me to your backyard party?
I'll show you. I wanted the hot dogs. What? I was trying to kick the thing over there and it didn't
work. You know what? It is gonna work. I'll make it work. He's flying. He's flying. And he's on fire.
Oh. And these people are all still dancing. Do you see what just happened to the guy that was
hosting the event? And what kind of dance is this? I've never seen anybody do this dance,
unless you were a toddler. These people are doing the I'm a toddler learning how to dance
to like Mickey Mouse music. Honey, can you just go check on the greenhouse and make sure my
petunias are in line? Oh, sure thing, honey. Oh, the glass doesn't break. I've got your
favorite breakfast cereal waiting for you. It's Pop-Tarts! Oh, Pop-Tarts! Where are they? I hate
going grocery shopping. I always have to go grocery shopping. This stuff sucks. I'm gonna
get Coca-Cola Classic. That's like my favorite. And I'm gonna get Doritos,
Spanada chips. Those are good too. I also want, what else do I want? I guess I could use a little
bit of ham. Do they have ham here? I don't even know. Maybe. Excuse me, sir, do you have ham? Oh,
he's not here anymore. Oh, she's dead. Frodo, you must take the goblins out of the cave of mystery,
and you must, you shall not pass into it fast enough. You could go first, because best friends
let their best friends go first on the slide. Okay, have fun. Have fun on the slide. Whee,
this is so much fun. Oh, whoa, sorry. I'm sorry. I'll pay for that. I'll pay for that. I'll make
sure you get like an extra monitor, a 27-incher, not just a 22-incher, whatever that is. Who are
you, Bill? How's life? How's the kids? Yeah, the kids are good, huh? Yeah, that's great. Everybody
expects me to just trash this place. But you know what? I think I'm gonna have some self-control,
because I could just trash this place right now, and it's really starting to build up,
and I really want to do it. But I think I'm gonna hold back just a little bit right now.
Get out before I change my mind. Hello, sir. Welcome to the goat station. Did I tell you
that today was baseball day at the gas station? Thank you for coming. Hey, Mortimer, welcome to
the party. Hey, Frank, how are you? What are you cooking on the grill? We've got some various meats
that we are cooking here on the grill. That better not be goat meat. If it's goat meat,
I'll be upset with you. Well, it is lamb. My family, we eat lamb. Same difference. Come here.
Come here. Oh, Lee. This is like Katamari Damacy. How much stuff can I pick up? Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.