Hey, what's happening everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 Facecam Fortress 2
Mondays edition. And I'm going to play as the engineer. I'm kind of late right now. Oh god,
there's only five, only five seconds and I've done, this is level one. This thing's going
down immediately, but this is on Thunder Mountain. And hopefully, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on. Yes. At least it's level two.
From the JAG, the Frontier of Justice, and the pistol. Good to know. Spike. See if I
can not. What is this guy doing? I love this guy's hat, this chicken head thing. That's
from the Adult Swim Pyro Mania. Woo! Update. Somebody come on out. Is there anybody? Okay,
there's people in here, yes. Whoa, whoa, whoa. No ammo, no ammo. Oh, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Oh man, Scout. Why did you do that to me? Whoa, that's how you fall down. How is that,
how is that center still up? I have no idea. Looks like it's going to stay up. Of course
it is. Get this. Don't worry, it's going up. I got you. I got you, baby. Whoa, whoa, hold
on here. What I just, where is this guy? Is he back here? Anybody, anybody, anybody want
to take a shot in the face? You are a spy, for sure, I bet. No, you are not a spy. I
need to get that ammo. Oh my god, everyone just keeps picking up the ammo. Why must you
torment me like this, team? Sorry, I'll get it now. Sanctuary. It's still up. What a miracle.
I think it might be time for this thing to move. Yeah, come on. It might be time for
this thing to move. Maybe not quite. Come on, get the, where's the ammo? Where's the
ammo? That's going to be the title of this video. Where's the ammo? Get this thing to
level two at least. Spy around here. Speaking of spies, I better watch my butt. Level three.
Oh boy. You. Oh, you're going to do like the little sneaky snake move, huh? Not going to
work on me, baby. Well, I think at least we're winning. Technically, I guess. Come get some
help, man. Vote for the next map. Oh, what's that one? I got a feeling this is going down.
Yikes. That's what you do. And then you come over here and you, whoa, no, you don't. Let's see if
we can get out of here. Ready? Come on. Come on. Oh, nothing I could do there. Besides kill
back. No. Oh, what? I just found a hat. Cool. You have just found a hat in the comment section.
Somebody tell me, uh, what is the actual percentage of finding a hat? Is it 1% 0.2%? Like
what's the actual percentage? I'm actually pretty curious to know what that is. Hmm. Someone,
someone give me some, give me some ammo. Give me that sick, sick, sick, sick, sick, sick, sick,
sick. This is sick. Level two going up. Oh, I just like pumped two shots at him. Just, just, just for
fun. Oh, don't want to. I need to keep at least a little bit in case they try and take it out. Oh,
he's hiding. Oh, he needs like one shot. Very good. Very good. I need to get some more ammo.
Come on. One of you bastards. Give me some of your stuff. I think that was it. Mmm. Save it. Oh,
it's not good. It's not good. It's going to go down. No, it won't. No, it won't. Give me these two
things. Oh, get away. Oh, no, you don't. Spy, you prickly little bastard. Oh, they are really
getting mad about this century. I need a dispenser, but there's no time. There's no time for that.
Whoa. Eight kills. This thing is on a rampage. Oh, do I dare? Do I dare put up a dispenser? I
don't know. Oh, I don't know. Okay. Whatever. Run. Hey, you are not. Oh, I had to run away.
I'm just putting a dispenser here. Oh, you got to be. You've got to be kidding me, man. No way. Oh,
that's. Wow. I can't believe that just happened. Boy, do you have a dead ringer? He must have had
a dead ringer. I had so many crits right there. Of course. Gosh. No. That's not the way I want to go.
I want to go this way right here. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
I feel like I was just on scare Saturdays right there. That was terrifying.
You are a spy. No, you're not. I've got to get a century up here. A good one. But yeah, like I
was saying, I really felt like I was on scare Saturdays right there. Spy just. Oh, that was so
horrible. I would have gone on such a tear. Oh, well, what can you do? Right? Put it right here.
They got to come through here. And when I got my stuff all built up, they ain't going to do anything.
They can just bumped into a spy. Speaking of spies. Here it comes. Come on. Get it to level two.
No. What is that guy doing? Wow. Okay. Kill him. Kill him. Thank you. No, no, no, no, no. Get out
of here. Get out of here. He's probably not dead. I would be very surprised if that guy was actually
dead. Maybe he is. Oh, the domination sound means he is. I think. Could be wrong on that one. Watch
it. Watch it. Watch it. Watch it. Out of my way. Out of my way. Oh, hey. Oh, hey. By the way, what
I'm doing right now. Here's a little, a little engineer tip. So if you get in a situ. Okay. So
here's it. He didn't die. He's still right here, isn't he? No, he's not. So here's the engineer tip
I was just going to give you. When you are building something. Oh, God. When you are. I
can't even like get my tip off. There's so much chaos. When you are building something, right.
What you want to do is you want to hit it. Turn. Hit it. Turn. Hit it. Turn. You never lose any time.
You just are finding any spies behind you. So just like this. Ready? Bang. Swing. Bang. Swing. Bang.
Bang. You don't lose any time and it's a good way to watch behind you.
Just a little engineer tip when your back is turned to the fight. I think we're going to win.
I think we're actually going to win. Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe. Here comes the last push.
Well, not really. There's a minute and a half left. There's still plenty of time. Oh, yeah. Thanks,
Pyro. Hey, can you like repair my level three sentry dude? Thanks. Oh, homewrecker Pyro. I love
you. Engineer's best friend is a homewrecker Pyro. Oh, my, my nose is itchy. My nose is itchy,
but I can't, I don't want to itch it. I don't want to itch it. This is too important.
Oh, that guy's so dead. If he, if he pokes his head around. No. Oh, I just got to shoot him.
Oh, just let it die. He got, oh, oh, spy. They're going to win now. They're going to cap it. Oh,
get on there. Get on there. If I didn't miss him with my shotgun. No. Just get back over there
and do whatever you can. Just drop this right here. What? What? What just happened? What on
earth just happened right there? I got to get out here. Got to get out here. Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on. This is very important. This is so important. This has to go up right now.
This is so important. So important. So important. No, no. Two Pyros. Two Pyros. Four, three, two,
one. Oh, I was scared there for a second. That was pretty terrifying. But thanks for watching,
guys. This episode of Facecam Fortress 2, Dr. Pepper, Clang, and now we're changing maps. Oh,
my God. I'm going to burp. I don't want to burp to end it. See you guys next time. Take care, everybody.