Hey, welcome back ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Hitman Absolution.
Currently evading a helicopter right now. So, uh, hi welcome to the show and welcome. Let's go. Just helicopter BEE!
How can this thing see me? Oh my word!
This thing is just lighting up the room.
Just stop like just jumping around. Just go, go man.
Go, just sprint. It's over, go.
I'm getting taken hits here.
Get me the hell.
I didn't do that. That was not the animation I was doing. Is there still a guard up here?
I thought I was done. There's more. All right, this guy's right here. Whoa. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Damn it. Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it. Oh, damn it.
Where's the copper? The chopper? The chopper? Where's the chopper? Go, go hide from the helicopter.
Two cops, three cops over there, it looks like.
Damn, man, how on earth do you expect me to get by?
Go! Where's the helicopter? No, it's coming back, coming back.
Ex-military.
Can't go anywhere right now.
Hello, where you going? Where's your route? You don't have a route. Yes, you do. Yes, you do. Both have a route.
Oh, get out of here, man. No, I'm gonna have to go back this way.
No, I'm not. Perfect. Copper, get out. Get out of here, chopper. You're blowing my moves. Get out of here.
Good. The back, it looks like, maybe. What about that guy's all the way down there?
I should have made a move.
Should have made my move. Should have made my freaking move. It's time to make my move. Here we go.
Let's go. Make the move, make the move, make the move, make the move.
The helicopter can see me. This guy's gonna make his way back this way, and then I'm home free. That's the door right there.
Wait until the car, the chopper is... Oh, shoot.
Get out of my way.
Damn it. You prick. If I still had that hammer, I would have thrown it by now.
I'm going for a run. Right when this guy goes back the other way, I'm going for a run.
I'm just running the other way into the, I'm just gonna run.
Here we go. In three, two,
one.
It's action time. Oh, it's action time. Yes. There's more. There's more. Oh, there's even more.
Can I just walk through here? Yeah, these guys, these guys, I'm a police officer to these guys. They have no idea.
Get out of my way.
Wow. No, those are cops. Those are cops. Those are cops. Those are cops.
Evade the police? This guy's like flushing. What? This guy's flooding the bathroom. Dear Lord, give me the knife.
Thank you very much. I'll take that. It's the police. I can't remain undetected for long. The elevator is my exit point.
All right, let's go.
Keep low and keep quiet. This is ridiculous. I'm in like plants. I'm in like marijuana leaves.
Shit.
These guys are getting arrested over there.
Don't do drugs. Once this guy moves. I got a chance. There we go. Let's keep moving.
Let's keep moving. That's a bad place to be.
Where am I?
No, sit down. Sit down. What are you doing? What am I doing?
What'd I stand up for? My guy is like stood up. Hey, it worked. All right, whatever. That's good. Okay.
Fields of joy.
Activate checkpoint. I absolutely will.
Activate checkpoint. Hell freaking yeah. All right. Can I go out the window?
I don't think so. Anything in here. Point of interest. Anything I can do. This is gonna cause a fire, bro.
Two cops in here. They are currently busy. It seems like. No. I might have to try a different route.
I might have to try a different route. Or I could be able to sneak by them, but I have to walk right by them.
I don't know if that's gonna work. No, I don't think it is.
Holy crap.
Yeah, you know what? I'm gonna I'm gonna walk by these two. I'm gonna try and just be like I'm an officer.
See you later. Here we go.
Maybe not.
Anything else? Anything else?
Nope. I'm just gonna keep following these guys. I'm gonna follow these cops. They're making their way out.
Hopefully those beads don't make a whole lot of noise.
There is my exit point. Get me the hell out of here. Oh, I should be careful.
This is a bad idea just walking straight over here, but you know what? I don't really have another option.
Oh, this room is full of people.
Distraction.
In this room. Oh crap.
I don't want to kill this guy. No, it's not somebody you know. Just go back to your business.
What's what distraction do I need? I really don't want to like push. I'm gonna have to like drown this dude, aren't I?
Oh boy. Wait, why did he die from that? What the hell is this stuff? Is this like acid?
Why did he just die from that? Whatever. Not that way.
What kind of weirdo has like all these messed up bathtubs? Prices. Half hour $15, regular $20. Mud bath.
Hey, I don't want to alarm you or anything dude, but your mud bath kills people instantly when they touch it.
Just wanted to throw that out there for you. In case you weren't aware. There's a point of interest back here.
Put the knife away. Here's a bottle. I will absolutely take the bottle. Gonna have to throw that. Guaranteed.
This situation requires a distraction. Damn it.
Hmm.
This son of a bitch just hanging out in there. I got to get rid of that guy. These guys aren't paying that much attention.
Probably just sneak behind him. Evidence. Give me the evidence.
Maybe not. Maybe not, guys. I think I might have to just... No, no. What are you doing?
Alright, that's fine. You're good. Who is this guy in this room? This guy just might... I'm just freaking me out.
Damn it. I have an idea. This is... this is crazy, and I'm probably going to...
Probably going to regret doing this, but this is really the only thing I can think of, and we're going to try it right now. Here we go.
Okay. That should have distracted at least one of these guys. Let me in this room. Let me in this room. Let me in this room.
Point of interest in here. Anything? There is a... a bong.
Alright. Insert tape into the tape recorder. This will surely compromise with my position. Okay. I know what I got to do.
I know what I got to do. I've got to put a tape in here, and then see where the hell they come from.
Nice dance music. Here they come. Here they come. They're all coming in from this way.
Oh boy, I just... I just screwed myself over right here. I just completely screwed myself right here.
This... this asshole would get out of the freaking way over here. I want to just throw a knife at this guy's head.
I'm like holding a bong. It's time to go. It's time to just walk straight out. Get out of the way.
Oh, get out of the way, you piece of crap. Move out of the way! Move out of the way!
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
Get in the elevator. Get in the elevator. Oh crap. That's bad. That's real bad. That's real bad. That's real bad.
Oh, can I go this way? Come on. I got to find a hiding place right now. Right now.
Oh, get me in the tub. Get me one of the damn tubs. I need to get in like in a tub.
I can hide in there. Let me hide in this tub. The one that I killed the dude, and I don't care.
I'll hide in the tub. You think it bothers me? What's going on with that guy?
Is that guy dead? Man. Damn it. Give me the screwdriver. Now I need a new disguise. This is bad.
If that guy wasn't just in the goddamn way, this would have been over by now. Piece of crap.
Good. Maybe you'll come hunting for me, and I'll be able to just sneak around. Son of a bitch.
Wow. Get me out of this room. There should be nobody at this door now. Oh, thank heavens. Thank heavens.
What? You gotta be kidding me. Oh, no. Oh, you know what? I'm so sick and tired of this.
Get out of my face. No ammo? That was the end right there. You gotta be kidding me.
Oh, I'm so pissed off right now. Oh. Alright, I made it back here.
I got minus 1,400 though on the way somehow. I don't know how the hell that happened.
So I'm gonna make sure I kill this guy. I am going to murder the guy that's in this room right now.
Do I have a horrible way for him to die? Whoa, speaking of dying, there's a guy coming my way
right now. And a guy coming the other way, I think. Damn. Just walk right by me, dude.
Don't worry about a thing. Just keep going. You don't see anything. Go. Alright. I'm gonna
think of the worst way to kill this guy because he ruined my good game over here. Alright, I'm going
in. Alright, where is this guy? Hey, you know what? You are dead. I don't even care. This guy
ruined everything. Get over here. I don't care if I get minus 50 million points. You ruined
everything, you son of a bitch. I should just shoot you in the face too. Alright, let's keep
going. Now I'm gonna play the music and the cops are gonna come out. I had a really good score
going too, I think. Let's go. Come on in, boys. Let me finish this.
I'm sure they're coming in. Only two? Where's the other ones? Alright. Now start arguing.
Let's go. That's all it took. I just had to, like, kill the dude. Here we go. Call the elevator.
Beautiful. And that's gonna wrap up the video, guys. The episode. Thank you all so much for
watching. I really do appreciate it. And I'll see you guys in the next episode trying to evade the
police even more. And let me know in the comment section, guys, if you want to see this series
continue in its current form or if you would rather see something like crazy mission parts or juicy
rage moments or something like that. Funny little highlight clips of this game because I'm willing
to do both. But just let me know. I might do both. I might try a change a little bit up a little bit
here in the next couple episodes. We will see. But thank you so much for watching. I really do
appreciate it again, guys. And I'll see y'all soon. Take care, everybody.