Hello, welcome. How are you? You doing good? So sorry for the abrupt ending last night.
We may get another one. I don't know. It's really kind of up in the air at this point.
So around like seven to eight o'clock, maybe earlier Pacific, we might just go,
I don't know. We're gonna do what we can. In the meantime, if you're wondering what we're doing
tonight, we're continuing the FMV game catalog. There are still plenty to go through. Some of
these are extra crusty, and by extra crusty I mean they might just stop working halfway through.
Some of these are so crunchy that we might not be able to see past the menu on some of them.
I don't know. I've tried to test as many of them as I could, but sometimes you get the
cheese stuffed crust. So not only is there crust, there's cheese in there too, which sometimes
that's a good thing. But we're gonna start with Ripper. Ripper is a game that has been
requested a few times. Christopher Walken is in this game. Am I gonna beat Dragon's Lair 2? I did.
I beat Dragon's Lair 2. The final image from last night's stream was me pointing at the screen
for about five seconds before the internet turned off. The game telling me, congratulations,
you made it to the end, but you failed because you didn't get any treasures. So I did complete it,
though. I ain't doing that shit again. And we have that Kingdom game has a sequel. I have that too.
I would put your seatbelt on for this one. Here we go. This is Ripper. Why don't we view the intro?
We already got a scream face. That's a good start. And you know what? No, fuck it. I'll be
right back. I'll be right back. Hold on. Just relax. I'll be right back. Everyone hold on.
BRB within four minutes of the stream. Be right back. Just hold on. Wait, no. Just watch this.
I'll be right back. Hold on. Fuck it. Hold on. You know how long it took me to get these fucking
games to work? I deserve it. I deserve a fresh core is light. Yeah. I don't even I fucking hate
beer. All right, here we go. Are you ready for the intro? Oh, all right. You good? We good?
You can hear it. Good. The vod's already deleted. Great. That's fantastic. The vod's already gone.
No, wait. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to. I'm not having the mod.
The mod mod get viewed. I'm not the John Rhys Davies. You know the song.
That's all that's happening. That's what's happening right now.
I see they can't they can't get me now.
All right, the vod is saved. No, I thought that was the end. All right.
Content ID can't get it.
My editor Ben Dodds called me at 3 a.m. to give me the news. It was a woman this time,
the third victim of all the reporters in the city. The ripper picked me to write to fix
the screen. Another mad letter to the city was soon to come and I would run it on the
front page of the virtual Herald. I would let the world know the ripper had killed again.
The Ripper Jack the Ripper. Oh, god damn it. Okay. Yeah, we got it. Oh, wait, that's right.
What's wrong with the screen? It's still 400 by 300 screens down because that's when I full
screen. Wait, what's it doing? Well, it's fixed because I went out of full screen. What's it
doing? Can we give you like an exact explanation of what's happening? It's cropping it. Hold on.
Let me see. Can I get a good look? I see what's happening. I see what's happening. Hold on. Okay,
hold on a second. I see what's happening here. Hold on. So I gotta move it up. I can look at it.
I can see it right now. Look at that. Okay, hold on. I got it. The game may have crashed,
but it's okay. This is gonna be this is gonna be close enough. I told you this is gonna be
fucking crunchy. Some of you didn't believe me. Like, what do you mean crunchy? What's that even
mean? I love like crunchy candy. No, you know, are you sure about that? All right, that's as good as
it's gonna get. Let's go. Here we go. Start a new game. That should fix it. We're good. We got it.
All right, start new game. Oh, for the love of fucking god. Can I skip this? It's louder this
time. What if I click? Hold on. I'm gonna click. No. What about here? It's space. I think I crashed
it. No, that's pause. Hold on. Hey, how you doing? I hope you haven't eaten yet, Quinlan. What?
Figured you'd get here sooner or later, Quinlan. You can't get enough of this story.
I think everyone's had enough of this story, Magnata. Okay, here we go. So there's been a
there's been a murder. There's Christopher Walken, right? Yeah, Christopher Walken's in this game.
Let's go ahead and go in here. This is a porn game. It is not. There is the man himself.
Let's get some dialogue. Don't go taking any souvenirs, Quinlan. Okay, ask about the modus
operandi. Ask about the victim. Ask if Magnata has any clues. What's his name? Magnata? Do you
have any clues? You have any clues? No sign of Force Sanfri. Nothing's disturbed. Two sets of
prints. Hers and a mother's. It's him. The only thing not where it should be is this woman's
insights. But what about witnesses? I mean, this guy must have been a bloody mess. Even if it's
three o'clock in the morning, it's Greenwich Village. Somebody must have seen him. As far
as I know, he left us with one witness and she's feeling a little fragmented at the moment.
This guy is unfucking believable. Who's the swears in this game? Wow. Okay, why is the computer
still on? Why is her computer on, Magnata? Well, it looks like she was in a public library node.
Well, let me ask you a question. You got any mail lately? Maybe a little something from your pen pal?
He writes after the fact, not before. You should know that, Magnata. I wouldn't hold out on you.
Of course not. Who's my pen pal? About sharing what you know with me and several million other
people. I should have busted you when you ran that first letter without letting us know about it.
What? Who's the letter? The murderer's letter? The game is a little quiet. I'll take care of that.
Just hold on. I'll take care of that. Hold on a second. If I alt tab, the whole thing goes
down, I think. Hold on. Hold on. All right, I got it up. Everybody relax. Are we good? I think we're
good. Excuse me? Thank you. Okay, what about the victim? Who's the victim? Name's Stein,
Rene Stein, age 43, book editor over at Knopf. Any connection to the other two? Oh, let's see.
Estevez was a programmer, Mandela a dry cleaner. It'll take me 48 hours to run it down, but there's
no connection here. This guy has my hair. All right, what about the modus operandi? No, he doesn't. Same
MO as the others? You got it. Look around you, asshole. If anything, this is more gruesome than
the other two. Hell of a lot more splatter. Look around you, asshole. All right, visiting
hours over. There's nothing here you haven't seen at the other murder sites except a few extra
gallons of body fluids. Well, you shouldn't be touching anything, should you, Magnata?
Hey. I guess this case has me rattled. Were you drinking out of the coffee cup?
Why would you drink out of that coffee cup? What if there's like blood in it? All right, what about
in the fridge? No, wait. All right, put it in the computer. Object scanned into database. Uh, that
don't look right. That didn't look right at all. That looked a little, a little, a little strange.
All right, uh, object has been scanned into the database. That's, uh, anything else I can do.
Should I take a look at the blood? Or the computer? Filter. Sharpen. File edit. Images?
Deck port interface. Tristec agerware installed. What other? Can I press any buttons? I guess not.
Oh, this, what's this guy doing? Oh, he's got a camcorder. I was like, what is this guy doing?
But I don't know why I thought that was a microscope. I have no idea. Don't ask me why.
Cold Carl Stasiak. We gotta stop eating like this. Carl. Sorry, Quinlan. What'd you say? Uh, any
difference between the murder and the previous two? Ask him if any frogs is invaded in the
investigation. If he has any idea what weapon, what kind of weapon is the ripper using? Any idea
what weapon he's using? Take a look at this mess. Has to be something big. Sword or machete or
something. Just can't cut through all that bone and muscle with a dagger. And the strength it
would take to make a cut like that. He must be an enormous man. You know, yeah, the pathologist
over at the metacock. You know, it's a lot more about murder weapons than I do. You should talk
to him and talk to the guy at the, uh, okay. What about the, the, any differences in the murders?
Is there any difference between this murder and the previous ones? It's identical. Absolutely
identical. It was a precision cut, a perfect line. The way he empties out the body cavity,
the way the organs are blown all around the room. So it's the same killer? Oh, for sure. I mean,
the organs completely cut the pieces. I never seen anything like this in my life. Just screams
wardrobe department. It's amazing. Any clues to how it's done? Don't ask me. You think I'd be used
to seeing things like this by now, but I'm not. Whoever did this is beyond madness. It's pure evil.
Pure evil. Okay. Any progress? Any other progress? Any progress? All of our mass effect dialogue
options. Who knows? Trying to get anything out of Magnata is next to impossible. Besides, if he does
have a lead, you sure as hell never share it. You might lose his bounty if he does that. Well, you've
been working with Magnata for years, Carl. What's your hunch? There's too many clues. Well, something's
bugging him. Who am I to talk? I'm having nightmares about this. The main character's doing a t-shirt
challenge. 22 years and nothing's ever got to me like this. Now I can't sleep. No, you just need a
vacation. That's all. Yeah. I hope you're right. Incoming whack transmission. Incoming whack
transmission. Quinlan here. Hey, Catherine. All right, whatever. Hey, Jake, how are things there?
Well, it's very... Oh, this shit is pretty whack. You're right. Just the name, Catherine. Listen,
Jake, something's come up here. Something about the ripper? Might be nothing. I don't know. It
could be something big. Just wait for me at the newsroom and I'll let you know as soon as I find
out. The newsroom? No, talk to me. What's going on? I have to go. Trust me. Who's in charge here?
Well, after last night I say that I am. So all of a sudden you don't have to explain yourself to me?
Look, if you don't hear from me in an hour, just go to my apartment and wait for me there.
You can hang out with my crystals. Catherine. My crystals? Shit. Really hang out with your
crystals. Should I save the game? All right. Save game in this slot. Got it. Save. I will forget
that now. Fuck it up. All right. So let's go. So we're going to go hang out with the... Is that
another word for like cats or something? Newsroom. All right. Oh, here we go. What's going on, Ben?
Did Catherine get a break in the ripper story? I don't know, Jake. I thought you were the lead
reporter in the story. Well, so did I. Do you know what she's up to? This is chattel. Your assistant.
You tell me. She ran out of here like the place was on fire. Did another letter from the ripper
come in? No, you know he doesn't send them to anybody but you. Isn't you... I guess we're just
going to have to wait and see. Just tell me. Catherine and I met on the job. Despite reminding
myself that mixing love and work can get messy, it didn't take long for it to become more than a
professional relationship. I love all the fake stuff. You're not even typing on a real keyboard.
But she was beginning to act like it was her story. I only hope that whatever lead she had,
she wasn't in. That's how I type. That's the way I type. See? Incoming WAC transmission.
Dear boss, have you seen my work this morning yet? Your stories make the cop seem so confident.
None of you know how I do it. You never will. You shouldn't let your girlfriend do your work for you.
She is close to me and are not laughing. She's my next job. She gets it today.
The story's all yours. It was truly written. It's Bugleberry. Catherine. What was he looking at?
Where are you going? That was a cigarette holder. Usually it takes an hour to cross that part of
Manhattan. I did it in 20 minutes, propelled by kicking myself in the ass for letting Catherine
go out alone. I was scared as hell when I got there, but everything looked okay in her apartment
until Catherine showed up, that is. Catherine, what is going on here? This is her apartment?
Where is this? What's with this Dracula apartment? What is wrong? What happened? She's been stabbed.
What? No, no, no, Catherine. Catherine, no. Catherine, no. Catherine, please, Catherine.
Fuck! What? Hold on, wait, why is this so, why did we get another one? Good news was Catherine wasn't
dead. The bad news was that she was in a coma deeper than anyone thought possible. What happened?
The ever-helpful Detective Magnata had her brought to the Tribeca Center for Cyber Studies,
also known as the MEDICOG. Meanwhile, I stopped off at the police station to see a few sources
and try to retrieve Catherine's portable whack. She'll have left me a message.
All right, so we're gonna, she's in a coma. Yeah, but why, why did she go into a coma?
All right, we're looking for the portable whack device. Looks like we're gonna talk to this guy.
Finish this game or riot? Um, we'll see. We'll see, because once we get to like the second or
third disc change I have to do, good luck. I've got him. That shit's gonna work. Who's that?
Hey, Quinlan. The Ripper Strikes Again. I guess we'll be seeing your work on the front page again.
Another body and another byline. You know, if you just catch this- This guy also has other things.
I could go back to writing the police plotter on page 12. Sorry to hear about your partner.
What is that? She was a nice girl. I liked her when she came around here. She used to come down here?
Came down here all the time. She used to do your leg work. Right, right. I just-
Was it the same guy? I can't do everything, can I? All right, any clues? I need,
I need the whack device. What about Magnata? I'll tell you, Lou, Magnata wasn't all two together
at the murder site. It's lucky for you. No, I'm serious. There was this one strange thing.
Strange? Yeah, I mean, if I didn't know any better, I'd say that he intentionally
destroyed a piece of evidence. It won't be the first time. What? Well, he's done it before.
Yeah, he hides it, he destroys it, he withholds it, you name it. And this is common knowledge.
Yeah, he's like king shit at a bounty collecting and the chief gets a piece of it.
I mean, what are you gonna do? You know how this place works. Really? Okay. I think it's time
to clean up the department. Any, any clues from the library? What about the library?
That was the last place that I was seen alive. Standard operating procedures to copy all libraries.
C-space files, that kind of stuff. Well, how can I get my hands on what they found?
Hell, Quinlan, it's a public library. We just copied the files. Everything's still there. What?
What? Okay, we gotta go to the library. Forensics come up with anything yet?
Apparently, this pathologist over at the, the metacog, he's come up with this theory.
He thinks that the Ripper may have been using nanomachines to do it.
No, God. Not nanomachines. Yeah. Not nanomachines.
I think it's time I bribe a photographer. Where's Stasiak?
He's in Wyoming. Oh, come on, Brandon. He's the only guy I haven't really talked to.
You never know what he might have picked up on. Yeah, well, that's the problem. He picked up on
too much. I'm not kidding. He went to Wyoming. The case was too much for him, and he took a
leave of absence. Okay. Stasiak, cold Carl Stasiak. Yeah, get this. After the Stein murder, his wife
calls and says Carl needed a little vacation. Carl? No, that was it. He just got up, no goodbyes,
no nothing. He didn't even give me a call. Thanks for the info. Let's go. It's always weird when
they put the CG, and I use that term very loosely here, but when you're an actor in a world that is
created in 3D with old 3D technology, just it's so, it's weird. It's scary. Like this shit's creepy.
That old style of 3D mapping with the actors and shit. It's, it's fucking bizarre.
What's over here? Yeah, it's a, it's a mist. Detective Vincent, there it is. Okay, Magnato.
Why do we have offices like this? Where are we? What year is it supposed to be?
I don't, I don't get it. It's 2040. It said the year. Well, that's too busy fucking muting VODs.
Fucking hey, cigars. The man's got taste. I'll give him that. Can I take one? Anything else down
here? Oh, hold on. I can open it by my, my whack device. Object scanned into database.
What is it? Uh, arrest report. I can't read this. Violation of city penal code detective,
arresting officer detective Vincent Magnato. Corpus observed at 1 45 a.m. at the corner of
Washington. It was a discharging submitter, but I had a taser to disable two members of this
spreading zugs. A rage gang captain from 40 feet with a sleeper bullet and called for a cleanup.
All right. Well, I got it scanned, so let's see if it's bullshit. Can I go on his computer? I don't
think so. Let's get out of here. It's going to be standing right there, sitting on the couch.
Give me the fuck out of this. Wasn't I supposed to find her whack device? Can I go? Can I go
anywhere else? Wait, what about this way? What is down there? Over there? Please stop the bongos.
I can't. They can't be stopped. Go over here. I'm just spinning around. Uh, I want to go in this room.
Is this the evidence chamber? Fucking stop them. I can't stop them.
There I cannot deter. I can't turn the bongos off evidence room. Here we are.
Welcome to the evidence chamber. What can I help you with, buddy? Oh crap. What do you want?
Some respect, Spankowski. You know, you really shouldn't talk to me like that.
I shouldn't be talking to you at all, you goddamn leech. What do you want? Some of us got to work
for a living. Right. I want to see evidence from the Catherine Powell case, please. I need the
evidence in the Powell case. No way, Quinlan. That could be my job. All right, time to convince.
Bluff them. Tell them Magnata said it's all right to see the evidence. Let's go with the bluff.
Let's see, can I get him with my... do I have enough charisma to do this? I need the evidence
in the Powell case. Spankowski, what are you worried about? Magnata okayed it. Get the hell
out of here, Quinlan. Magnata would never let a civilian see evidence. He doesn't even like it
when they're in the building. Uh oh. Didn't work. Didn't work. Not good. Look, Quinlan. I told you
everything I know. Now will you get the hell out of here before you get me in trouble?
Look, Quinlan. I told you everything I know. Now will you get the hell out of here before you get
me in trouble? I still don't understand the thing around that necks. I obviously need to
find a way to convince him to give me the evidence. Let's go. Let's go. That's a police badge.
All right, let's see if I... did I unlock any new areas? What about that way? Turn the music off?
No, I'm not going to turn the music off. You'll be fine. There we go. Police station. Try pick a
center. All right. Catherine Powell's apartment newsroom. Let's go to... uh, I was supposed to
meet somebody at the newsroom, right? Let's go. Oh, shit!
Well, it looks like we're never going to go to... we're never going to go to the newsroom.
Metacog, uh-huh, hold on. Metacog, uh-huh, hold on. Metacog, hold on. Metacog, hold on.
I, like, brought all the footage. Oh, the... Did you pardon? I thought it was going to work.
I said, can I help you? What'd you think I said? Nothing. I... I'm looking for, uh,
whoever's taking care of my girlfriend, Catherine Powell. That would be Dr. Burton.
Take the elevator to the second floor and make a right. If she's not there, go to ICU down the
hall from there. Whatever you do, don't stand too close to her. Why's that? A little chilly.
What? Right. All right, let's just go up here. Elevator and to the right. That's a scary looking
place. Is this a scary game? It might be. That's... I don't know. It could be. I gotta go up.
Ward's Lobby Morgue. Let's go to the... Ward? What is going on? Oh, yeah.
Uh, that scared the shit out of me. That actually did. I thought it was, like, a scream.
And then to the right. Is this supposed to be scary? I don't know. I can't tell.
This might be a part where it's going to be scary. There's nothing even over there.
Oh, there she is. All right, so... What are you doing here? My name's Jay Quinlan. I'm a friend
of Catherine's. Quinlan? Yeah, okay. How is Catherine? Is she going to be all right?
It doesn't look good. Her consciousness is deeply withdrawn. Where is she withdrawn? What's that
mean? It means her mental processes, her memory, the basic building blocks of her personality are
inaccessible. You mean she's in there, but you can't reach her? That's a best case scenario.
We haven't yet diagnosed her psychic damage. How did the Ripper do this? It's hard to tell.
She had some minor contusions on her head. Nothing fatal, but you never know with head injuries.
We won't know anything until we can get a data angel in there to do some... A data angel? You
can get a data angel into the consciousness of someone in a coma? I'm not sending anyone in there
until I've had a chance to fully map her psychic damage. Let me get in there. Now, if you don't mind.
All right, well what are you doing for her? What are you doing for her? I'm not doing anything for
her as long as I'm standing here talking to you. Why don't you let me get back to work?
So I have to go in there on my own then? Will, is she going to be all right? It doesn't look good.
She's still in triage. We're going to just have to wait and see. Well, what do you do? Let me get in
there. Let me, can I at least see? Wait, there's another person here. You here to check on Miss
Powell? Miss Paul Giamani. She looks pretty bad. Is there anything you can do for her? She's in good
hands, and she'll be in even better hands once Dr. Burton allows us to treat her. Where's Dr.
Burtman? Let me in there. Is something I'm going to take? Is there anything else I can do in here?
I don't think I can do anything else in this room. No, all right, that doctor. I've got to go to the
doctor. Let's find the doctor's office. Insert disk two. I will. I'll try. I have to save the game. I'm
going to restart the game. Guys, I'm running this game through like four different virtual layers,
okay? I'm on my computer, and then from my computer to a virtual machine, from the virtual
machine to a DOS emulation, from an emulation through the disk. Sorry, I just bumped you.
And then through VPN. What is going on over here? Jump scare, jump scare, jump scare, jump scare. Do
it. Oh, it's a wet floor. I can't go over here. No, that's what these are here for. I can't go
this way. Wait. Locked. Damn. How am I supposed to open this? I don't know. Do you have like a,
what the fuck do you have? Remote control. I can turn the game down from in my inventory. Okay.
I don't want to press the power button. Oh, here we go. Cool. All right. How do I, I don't want to,
I don't want to, how do I turn? No, no, don't reset the game. Just turn this off.
Okay. Inventory. Use. Done. All right. Save game. Right here. Overwrite. Save it. Okay.
I'm gonna turn around. There's nothing else over here. The game, this game low key sucks.
Just wait a second. We need to go to the other place. This game's low key sucks. We're gonna
go to the morgue. I'm gonna try the other disc, but not yet. We don't have to do that yet.
There we are. All right. There's combat in this game. Guys, don't you want to at least see the
combat? Don't you want to see Kristen walking and go, well, at least one more time before we end this?
Don't you want to see that? Don't you want to know? I kind of need to know. I have to beat this game.
There's combat. What is going on? Is it just a pair of legs? What the fuck is that?
Is it Paul Giamatti again? Hey, Vic. What's for lunch? Hey, Quinlan. Oh, what the?
They work in your heart? Workin' me like crazy these days. Hey, is this Renee Stein?
You're kidding. You were at the crime scene. I saw her inside splattered everywhere. Yeah,
I guess I did. Yeah, this one was married to her, Ripper. Yeah, this was a businessman. We're on a
trip for three weeks. He gets paranoid that his partner's puttin' her in a car. Can you take the
cigarette out of your mouth before you talk to me, please? So he flies home early and shoots it at
that. I mean, stuff like that. That's why I never got married, you know? Low key TOS. Any luck
figuring out the Ripper's weapon yet? What's the weapon? I'm completely stumped. Nano machine.
I did every test on these STIPS. I mean, a computer cross-matched the wounds with every
kind of blade imaginable. Nothin'. I mean, it's like a cross between a Vegematic and a diamond cutter.
What's with the thing on his head? Something must have cut these people open.
Nothing these computers can find. What's with the miner's helmet on? Now, you don't believe me?
Look at those control panels by the STIPS. Doctors don't have those. What is that? He's got blood in
his hands and he's, like, putting it on his mouth. You hear about my partner? Who's that? Catherine
Powell. She was attacked by the Ripper. Somehow she got away. She's upstairs in a coma. Dr. Burton's
treating her. Oh. Oh, that's supposed to be the future. Right. Okay. Burton's a good doctor.
And if she gets stuck, she'll probably call in her secret weapon. What's that? A guy named
Joey Falconetti. Joey Falconetti. Joey Falconetti. Okay. Who's that? Who's Joey Falconetti?
Cyberspace expert that Burton uses on all the tough cases. Also known by his old C-space handle,
Falconetti. Get it? Crazy guy. Likes looking at the body. I'm surprised she hasn't called him in
yet to look at your friend. What do you mean? Oh, well, he keeps doing it. Stop doing that.
She usually calls him in on that kind of stuff. All right. Now, it would have been funny if they
had a take where he went and he put it up into his mouth and went like, and then just kept talking.
Where can I find this Falconetti? Difficult guy to find. Burton usually goes to a guy named Gamet
Nelson. He passes the time at the Café du Champ. Café du Champ. Okay. Du Champ. You can find him
there. All right. Let's see what disk that requires. We've got new locations. Let's see if I can like
boot the second disk and like load from there. If not, then well. I tapped the nerve memory of this
victim and fed it into the simulator so that I could reenact the attack. Million dollar piece
of hardware. And look what it gives me. Jesus. Looks like she swallowed a fucking grenade.
I, who's, who's mind are we looking at? Here's an isolation of just one of the organs from this
body. The lines indicate the many cuts made for this body. The sheer number of cuts isn't the
only amazing thing. Now watch this. All of those cuts happen simultaneously. Human hands can't move
so the river is like this for every four years. He's got like powers or something.
He's got technological powers. Notice the path of the cut. Not one centimeter offline. Like a seam
was unknown. Not the second disk. Because humans aren't strong enough. Does that work? Does that
can work? Will that work? No way this cut could be so neat. I'll tell you what else is weird.
There are no traces of fabric in the world. Oh, we're good. First layer. Peel back the
fucking onion skin. Second layer. That's where we are. That you are here. That's where the
DOS is being implemented into the virtual machine. Layer three is mounting the disk.
The disk is layer fucking four. I'm gonna try it. Did he lose disk two? Yeah, what you guys
don't understand is I, you know, I, I, I bought this game and it only came for the first disk.
I got scammed. I'm just, you know, I'm gonna be real with you.
Yeah. Nice Shrek metaphor. What the fuck is a Shrek metaphor mean?
All right. I'm going to try it. I gotta, I got my pathing correct.
The onions. Does he do an onion thing? I like an onion. Donkey. I like an onion.
Got this layer. Oh, he does do that. You're right. Fuck. Whatever. All right. So when I
ask for the disk, we mount the second disk and then we press enter and then I press okay.
Oh, it's going to be fucking amazing. Okay. Newsroom. Okay. Hold on here.
Let's get this correct. So newsroom. Insert disk two into drive D. I can't get back out there,
though. I can't get it. Eject it. Eject. Oh God. Hurry. Do that in this menu. Hold on. Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. I gotta get a bigger screen here. Hold on. I'm
gonna stay here. Quick eject it. This is where we're going to, this is how I can tell if this
is going to work. Okay. Everybody relax. Don't, nobody move. Don't fucking move. Okay. Nobody
move. Don't move. Action. Okay. Here we go. Everybody relax. Where is it? Shit. Hold on.
All right. Come in. Fuck. I should have got an expert to help me. Okay. Ladies and gentlemen,
we're coming back. Here we go. Bingo. You didn't think I fucking had it in me, did you?
You didn't think I fucking had it in me. We're on disk two. You didn't think I had it in me.
Move restore game or continue game? No. It's okay. It's okay. We're gonna.
Shit. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. When mounting multiple images, you still have a
good disk control. You can then switch between the amount of disk control and the amount of disk control
before. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on a second, guys. Guys. Mounting multiple images. Let's do it.
Let's go. That's not an Alt F4 joke. It's not. All right. Mounting multiple. How do I mount?
I need a DOS cool person to save me right now. This game has seven disks. It's got to be mounted
in the same drive. It is. We're good. How do I mount multiple? It's mount extra. It's on DOS box.
You can't. I can't. No. Delete C Windows System 32. I use Daemon tools. We'll go back to that
when I get a DOS person. It's okay because we're moving on. We're moving on to this one. Do a full
stream on Ripper. I'm gonna go back to Ripper. Let's open it up. We're gonna go from there.
We're gonna go on to Kingdom 2. Wait, somebody's got it. Is that correct? Like, is that correct?
Sawdust bunnies. Is that correct? Is that the correct way that I do this? Just mount them all
in the same place. Just mount them all. Just mount them all. Just type them. Just mount them all.
Just list them all in one command. And then it's Ctrl F4, right? Hold on. Stay right there.
I'm gonna try that. Don't accidentally press Alt F4. I tried to do this before, too. This is
not gonna end well. I have to move on. Just install Windows. I tried to run this through
Virtual Machine and I couldn't get it to work. All right. I gotta move on. I have to. This is
gonna take too long. I'm gonna try this one time and we'll see what happens. I gotta get this on
screen so people can tell me if I'm doing it right. This is the one time I'm gonna try this.
Tell me. This is a troubleshooting stream. You ready? So, all of the disks are in this folder
called FMV. Welcome to the stream. Hey, everybody. How are you? Okay. So, that's the drive that it's
in. Okay. They're all in there. RIP 1, RIP 2, RIP 3, RIP 4, RIP 5. I already screwed it up. It's
image mount. All right. So, that's that. That's that, right? I'm hacking with two fingers. I am.
You're right. I absolutely am. Okay. Is this correct? Somebody has an image of this. Somebody
has an image of this. Let me see. This is not gonna do anything.
This is not an image. Why did you link this? I need help. I need fucking help. I need not this.
I need help. All right. Somebody help me. If I do this for all of them and then I do dash t
dash iso. Is this gonna work? No. Stop laughing. Stop laughing. Everybody, I need people to stop
laughing. I need help. I'm gonna do it. So, is this correct? Just end it. Okay. Hold on.
Okay. Then there's four. Everyone stop laughing. I can't see the chat. Stop laughing. Stop laughing
at me. Okay. Here we go. And there's enough. There's six fucking disks. God damn it. I even
was gonna buy like an old Macintosh computer on eBay. But the description said that the screen
was broken and that I needed to bring it to a repair shop. It was gonna be like 1200 bucks.
So, I didn't do it. Okay. Here we go. Okay. Ladies and gentlemen, is this gonna work? Will that do
it? And then I need to I need a computer programmer in the chat to tell me that's gonna work. Do you
have computer programming skills? No. That's not gonna work. I'm an IT major. It won't work. Look
at this link. Look at this link. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Stop. Stop laughing. Stop
writing text. It's possible to mount more than one image in a page. Imagesmount.com. Why is it
.com? .com? Why does it say Imagesmount.com? Like that. You put an extra. I'm a DOS major and I
guarantee it'll absolutely work. Trust me. Open the link. There's a typo. No, there's not. There's
no typo. There's an extra rip where. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Is it Imagesmount.com?
Oh, God damn it. Imagesmount.com. All right. Imagesmount.com. It is. I did it right. I did
it right the first time. I need a computer analyst to explain this to me. Imagesmount.com. D. E.
to the tutorial for you. And people are writing so much. That code will. That code is going to
break your computer. No. All right. So hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. So I need someone
to tell me. I won't. I'm going to put it on emote only mode and then I'm going to pull.
If I. Okay. Now if I continue to do this, will it work? Did I have it right the first time?
I had it right the first time. Read the guide. Just look at doc box wiki. It's not .com.
So I had it right the first time. More than one image. Yes, I know. Okay. So yeah. D. Remember
E is my, what I have as my C drive. Right. So I just have to do everything that I did normally.
So Imagesmount. D. All the stuff. And then dash T. CDROM. Is that correct? That's correct? Oh,
let's go. Let's go. Let's go. How do you say let's go when you're doing shell command?
I don't understand how you. This is why you give programming to our
FMV slash rip one dot ISO. Then the next one. Right. Dude, let's go. I'm so stupid. Okay. Check
my work while I go, please. Okay. What's going on here? Why does this look so fucked up? What
happened? What happened? What happened? What happened? What happened? What happened? What
happened? What happened? Why did it do that? I can't go back. What? I can only do one line?
No, it was, it was a different line. No, I have to go. I have to hold on. Oh,
everybody stop talking. Thank you. Appreciate it. Okay. Okay. Okay.
They can't. This is the programming humor subreddit where it's like, whoops, I get to
slash instead of a dash. I can't imagine this is why they get paid the big bucks.
D E. Okay. That's correct. I'm going to do this as we go. E rip to ISO space E FMV rip three
dot IS. Don't get it wrong. Okay. That's all correct. E FMV rip four dot ISO. Okay. That's
correct. So far space E FMV rip five dot ISO done space E slash FMV rip six dot ISO done dash
T ISO. Is this correct? Do I press enter? This will do it. This is going to work. I'm seeing a
lot of yeses. I'm seeing a lot of yeses. A lot of them. It worked. Did it work? Did it work? Did
it work? Is that it? Do I not touch anything? Did it work? I think it worked. Okay. Now we go.
We got it. Here we go. Don't touch anything. Okay. What happened? What happened? What happened?
Get this fucking thing off the screen. What do I do? Control F4, right? That puts me in another
disk. I have to be on disk one. Okay. Disk two of six is now active. Hold on. Fuck did I do?
I need disk one. Control F4. Disk three is now active. Disk four is now active.
Disk five. Disk six. Disk one is now active. Disk one is in. It's in there.
It works. But does it work? Combat medium. It worked. Everybody chill the fuck out.
Everybody's everybody. Wait, wait. Hold on. I think I got it. I think I got it. We're moving
around. This is disk one. This is important. Because if I can change the disk to and press
okay, then holy fuck. I am a goddamn genius. I just need to check to make sure this is going
to work. Oh yeah. Right. This has got to get off the screen. You're right. Okay. Here we go.
Newsroom. Insert disk two into the drive. Control F4. You're on disk two now.
I'm gonna relish in this one. I am gonna relish in this shit. You better believe it.
You didn't think I was smart enough to handle this. Nobody did. But I am. You didn't think I
was fucking smart enough to handle it. Oh, but you were wrong. You were all wrong. I knew about
the mounting. I knew about the images. I knew about the onion. Although it's hard to recalibrate
this. That's all right. It looks good. Let's go. I'm fucking on. I'm absolutely on cloud nine right
now. I'm like so happy. I did that under pressure too. That was a fucking end zone pass that I just
I it was an end zone pass. Can you guys see? How did I gain viewers doing that? That's I don't
know how that's possible. I'm supposed to meet somebody here, right? They expected a cool
programming stream. All right. Somebody in there. There's a brain. I think I think our
whack the machine is still going to be broken though. A computer with a deck port can never
have too many of those. Okay. Should I go in? Exit cyberspace. Why is this supposed to be
virtual reality? Berman incorporated. Virtual library. Virtual library. Sure. Let's open it up.
I hope it asks me to change this because I'm ready for it. Who's this? I can't see with it.
I know with some call numbers on it. Am I underwater? Could Renee Stein have left this here?
I could use some help here. You're a human presence I assume. Everyone at a service desk is. The
library doesn't use smart sprites for public interface. You don't read much do you? This
sucks. Go back to DOS box coding. Ask if she's seen Renee Stein. Did you see a woman named Renee
Stein recently? Records place her here but she didn't check anything out and I don't remember
seeing her. Okay what about the call number? Can you help me with this call number? I'm sorry this
is not a valid call number. It appears Stein altered the reference matrix but an unknown book
was distributed. If you could unscramble the call number I could help you.
Unscramble the call number. Prior period distribution list. Physical deletion
uncompleted. Okay address call number. Who am I doing this for? What? That's all I know.
Just tell me what it is. Just tell me what it is.
HC. I don't care. HC4. No is this correct? No I'm not writing that unless I know it's for real.
I don't know. I don't know if that. I'm not writing that. I don't know what that is. Can I get a mod
to look it up? I can look it up. The HC is on my screen. Alright so what was it? I thought you
guys were writing like he shit whatever. Like he wrote a thing he didn't think of as he was writing
but he did. Like he shit. HC what was it? 45. Say it again. Tell me what the code is. 73T.
I think the game crashed. You should really look into this Quinlan. It could mean something.
Did I get it? Can you help me with this call number? I'm sorry this is not a valid call number.
It appears Stein altered the reference matrix but an unknown book was distributed. If you
could unscramble the call number I could help you. What is it? HC is the actual number. HC.
No. Two. I looked it up. The four numbers are contained in the square brackets.
Didn't know how to figure it out. You need to make sense of the algebra. You can read the code like
this. So this one was it? What's the last one? Wait Quinlan that's a valid call number. I'll get
the book. People didn't think I was capable of doing it but I just continue to prove them wrong.
A book about the original Jack the Ripper. Can't be a coincidence.
Renee Stein must have used this but what does it mean? You read chat. I didn't read chat.
You talk to them. Have the cops talked to you? They asked questions but I couldn't tell them much.
They copied all the files from the Victorian route directory and ordered us not to alter the
file structures until the case is solved. I've been streaming for like six hours. The day Stein
was killed would still be here. Guess so. I sure didn't take them. All right well I got some new info.
I'm out. How do I leave? Oh you got a new info. How do I get the fuck out of here?
All I can do for you is recommend something to read Quinlan. How about Marchox the da Vinci
engine? It's a study that reveals how Leonardo theorized cyberspace back in the 17th century.
How do I leave? Oh you have to press escape. All right I got new info. I'm gonna it's midnight
always. Watch out for the skull. Dangerous. Watch out for the I don't know what that was. Sun. Moon.
I. Exit. Exit cyberspace. Yes. Okay whew whew. Jake if anything should happen to me
lose the crystals. Look to the crystals and let the light shine your way. All right where's like
the I want to fight. I think I gotta go talk to the chief. No not this way. Don't fight. It's okay.
There's an this is an adventure game. There is no fighting. It says there's combat in the game.
There is combat in the game and I'm gonna see it. There we are. I want to go in here.
No why are you leaving? Here we are. Here we go. Ben dogs. Give me a new area and we're gonna get
our first fist fight. Hey Ben. How's Catherine today? No change. Now his coat looks like it's
made out of licorice. I'm not gonna lie. This guy's the devil himself. Ben you know this cop
Magnata? Typical new breed cop. One of those guys started arresting people in volume when cops started
to select. Salami. He's uh been more aggressive than most. Yeah that's common knowledge but
what's his story? He's killed six people in the line of duty summoned to questionable circumstances.
He's bad news. I wouldn't mess with him Quentin. Do the funny voice which one is Ben? All right
where's uh what about Joey Falconetti? You ever hear of a Joey Falconetti Ben? No the name sounds
vaguely familiar but I can't quite place it. All right well let's go let's get out of here. I'm
going to see Joey. I can't wait to change disc because that I mean that was just hold on I got
a belch coming you don't like this song it's not gonna be over just relax guys we only have
like another four to five hours in this game so pull up a chair sit down because I've lied to
you this whole this whole evening this is all I got out of all the fmv games I try to get to work
and this is the only one that works so I mean I would do this is a good one I think how do I
leave the fucking building I want to leave the building and if you think that's legit
you're out of your mind okay leave the fucking building I want to leave the office stop
stop stop stop stop turn around oh my god and then I have to go here and then have to turn
it around from here my goodness all right what we got newsroom uh cafe du champ
I've been grepping for one of these for months these are tough to find if you're not in the
profession's way lawyer reporter for the herald low end of the pay scale hey tell me about it
you should work for yourself there are thousands of ways to make money in the net believe me I know
the internet is he drinking out of a manila envelope or is it a candle he's drinking out
of a candle do you know joey falconetti joey falconetti I haven't done business with that
scoundrel in years talk about profiteering in the net but do you know eddie and I owned part of an
emoticon franchise you know one of those sea space emotional counter zones this was years ago
legitimate business why can't that just be a real mug eddie's a thief by nature robbed it blind
we had to sell out to some palestinians in new dallas I've worked with eddie since but I
I keep an eye on him so he doesn't pilfer any of my is this still the same game from before
uh yes it is it is uh what's over here bartender you're reading your copy quinlan
he might nail this freak before the police do I'm fucking huge just asking questions
seven feet tall kind of slow in here yeah the rippers really put a damper on anonymous sex
these days what wait wait wait what are you what are you talking about is that that was a bar
that's not what I asked how about a beer yeah sure thing try this one called viper pills
viper goes down real smooth we've got some bite
on the house just nail the ripper so that my customers can get drunk in public again
okay sure you know what that's probably that was probably take number 40
I'm about a beer he was probably so sick of doing that by now
yeah give me another one try this one called viper pills goes down real smooth
we've got some bite on the house just nail the ripper so that my customers can get drunk
didn't even give me the whole thing it's just all head okay there's no beer that's just all foam
you're just drinking like a cappuccino beer all right what about gambit nelson you know about
you know about gambit nelson yeah gambit's been coming in here for years
i'm smoking in your own butt what man has seen it all he can remember when the net went online
back when they weren't any well but a free beer but a bunch of isolated bbss
must be a first generation decker bean bags onyx the first sea space entrepreneurs
you're killing him all of its week weird huh you know a good guy wins for once in a blue
fucking moon okay well thanks for the thanks with the foam one more no uh we didn't do all the
dialogue here where can i find falcon itty do you know where i can find falcon itty you don't
the falcon usually finds you and he takes your money well lucky for me i'm broke a grave digger
named farley at the medicoc told me that you might be a link to finding what's your interest you have
to kill him well it's not killing i had in mind well somebody's gonna whack that bird one of these
days and his consciousness is inside a few hundred terabytes of well space with his body safely
hidden i set metacog up with a guy named twig lives out in hoboken he seems to always know
where eddie's at twig eddie usually presents himself with video he likes to show off hoboken
you know i i've kind of lost all knowledge of what we were doing mr nelson what's your background
was just walking through a cup on the ground it would take a while there's a serial i've been
decking with the global net since it went online present at the creation
that's why thugs like falcon eddie disappointment damn waste of talent
you want another one i can get you another one what about down here is this a computer game
no not a computer game how about a beer yeah sure thing game high king socks called viper pills
it goes down real smooth it's got some bite how does something go down really
smooth and have a bunch of bite at the same time all right newsroom police station
didn't we get some a new area evidence room um what do i need to do where the hell do i go
oh i can do that control f4 that's disc three disc four disc five disc six disc one i am so proud
of myself he's showing off his disc skill what's this dude that is gonna help so much in the uh
don't look at that don't look at that you're not old enough uh okay i'm 25 that's not old enough
it's all the stars no no cancel what the fuck am i supposed to do here i'm trying to figure out
what i need to do all right there's happy birthday i'm glad i found you love j is this the is this
the cat the credit the cat love no the crystals this is the crystal person go find the crystals
where are the crystals straight ahead what's over here is this uh super bowl 10 what is l
is this like super bowl 400 or something wait a minute a laser cane wonder what this inscription
means j dorset j dorset on this cane and it's a magical cane j dorset got new info i don't know
what the fuck i'm supposed to do with that um crystals there's the crystals right there
crystals look look the crystals are right here look see i have no idea what's going on like
honestly like feel free to put every like every game spoiler in the game i don't care like literally
if you want to type into the chat the next thing i need to do just type it i don't care it's okay
no this game is really hard without a walkthrough newsroom police station what do i do cafe du chum
no i already was there newsroom let's go back to the newsroom well let's go back to the um the we
have to go talk to um you want us to be the walkthrough yeah i've been to all these places
where should i go back to the police station i have to get that guy to give me the thing
arrow buttons no that doesn't do anything buttons in the middle help okay i found the
website on a website called game boomers what just going on we're in disc one right all right
ben you got anything for me the times is breathing down our back on this story get to work do you
give me a help me somebody said talk to ben it didn't do anything go back to the morgue
go back to the apartment talk to brad who's brad use the whack thing and fix the mug
wait okay power no database broken mug this shattered mug had something written on it
puzzle what how the two handles can i flip it okay god don't don't say like zero iq
well i thought they would i got this shit this actually sucks uh this is kind of hard
i have to flip the whole fucking thing oh fucking thing i need where's the thing that's
i need written i just need the text i don't care about anything else all right this is gonna w
get this out of the fucking way it's causing me too much stress doesn't make any fucking sense
what why you this is fucked wait hold on um i want you how i can't like this perspective so
like i wanted to put these in the back oh my lord you just i don't know which way this way
this thing's facing right now uh this doesn't make any fucking sense because they all this
goes here it has to right does it have to be vertical because i can't like spin these in the
right like this goes here i don't fucking know how the fuck am i supposed to know that i guess
that makes sense the handles on the right side yeah that's what i've had that before but is this
shit upside down it's not why can't i like lock this shit in place i have to keep on like
chain have i ever seen a mug before yeah i have this shit doesn't make any sense like what the
fuck is what a piece is this the handle has to be done last what the fuck this is awful what does
the side look like all right i'm gonna say i like here this is the top of the mug that can't be right
i don't think this is correct this is like a melted candle what the fuck this doesn't make
any sense that's the bottom of this there ain't no more where i need another lip there aren't even
enough pieces to do this there's not enough pieces to finish this there's nothing even written on
here and then get the fuck out of here salsbury i wonder what that means salsbury cool what's in
the river book salsbury i didn't get anything we're doing that okay salsbury is that a password
somewhere i'm not writing this the game i think is doing it on its own that's stay it stays good
exit without saving no you're supposed to talk i don't know i don't have to talk what does salsbury
mean don't have to put that in a computer or something no fucking hundred bucks came in from
thank you slayed for the 10 000 thousand address file 100 bucks as a good place to find a clue as
any they say just use this to buy a new mug that would buy like 10 20 new mugs george rose phone
call salsbury we'll look at the salsbury iris salsbury lou salsbury rachel salsbury
soap salsbury george salsbury god damn it how do i like call these people
what were dimensions for bugs i got no fucking idea only knows i have salsbury what's that
why do i have a calculator divide by zero wait hold on can i do this i used to do this when i
was bored like i don't know if like 15 right well like 18 plus 18 and then i would just go like this
no this calculus sucks i would just see how many numbers i could go up what's i don't know what the
point of this is i don't know the point of this game is at the moment salsbury i think i got back
to the apartment i've spent a very long time in this game there's another hundred bucks uh evil
crucifix just give another hundred dollars both of you slayed and evil crucifix back to back i
heard you need a mug need a new mug uh through the grapevine this might be able to pay for it
and now this is too many mugs but thank you for the fucking hundred bucks back to back both you
guys go back to kathryn's apartment all right i'll go walkthrough says to type 8008 okay
well you got me to say it what sign is she from the constellation places try to use the entire
area using the star chart by plotting it on a grid what the fuck what do you mean by plotting
it on a grid kathryn's apartment we got two three four oh fuck that's not the right button
let's control f2d in dustbox so you're saying go to over the constellations i can't interact with
them though 10 11 12 sev taris gemini scorpio you have to chart them what do you mean i have to
chart them salisbury
what the fuck's are i had to power down for a second what did you say was the last thing you said
there are books look at the books books books wait where am i where am i okay look at the book
look at books what books i don't see any books where are these books there's crystals this game
fucking sucks laughing my ass up wait okay hold on i thought they're the crystals kathryn's
crystals i always thought they were a little too neo new agey for kathryn oh fuck off really i have
to do i have to do the whole other constellation okay the chart yeah well i uh i want to reset
happy birthday i'm glad i found you love jake february look at the crystal part hold on
you want to go to the police station right click on the crystallizer listen without it makes it
easier later on then you want to head to the i i think it's time to move on to uh scotty pippen's
slam if it were me sounds good good save it though just in case i decide to play this again
i might come back to it probably i look i we might just come back to it but i i want to play scotty
pippen's slam dunk he's giving up i'm not giving up it also gives me enough time to open up a guy
to just have next to me the whole time he's never coming back to this game you don't know
that though you don't know that i haven't saved you don't know that how do you know
that for a fact you can't tell me that reliably all right let's do let's do uh scotty pippen's
basketball that game hurt the game hurt my head all right so now same deal i'm going to mount
hey you guys we got it hit dos is on screen take a look at that we got multiple discs
in this one here comes more dos packing the view counts gonna go up like fucking 200 all right so
i need to mount these discs check it out he's fast he's quick with this he's doing good when
i'm on two i forgot how to do it okay no i don't disc four check my work please f minus checked
let's do it this is uh this is scotty pippen now we go here bingo we're talking about oh i'm already
there oh no no i i screwed it up i'm an idiot there's there's another there's another slam
folder there's dot there's two slams this is a pentium processor shit hold on hold on wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait you relax i know what to do i have to change it to a pentium
i'm in welcome to slam city i know what to do i know what to do everyone don't worry it's okay
i got this under control i have to change this to a pentium easy this easiest thing i've done all
day there we go save that looks good i have to fucking reboot the goddamn i have to reboot this
i have to re i gotta reboot and remount everything i got it fine just i gotta do that again
oh let's go let's go you know what i'm saying let's get a bad pc no i got a good pc let's just do it
again there's no problem here damn it i don't want to do this again slam slam slash no no no no no
where is it it's e fmv slam cd why are there so many fucking disks you can't put it on one disc
check my work please got it let's go i have it on pentium it's time i'm ready my god oh so now go
change directory slam slam change directory slam we're in slam dot exe let's go bring it on bring
it on bring it on
he's trying to stop me why why why was he trying to kill me
when you gotta get all you can get yo just remember hey
that's a bad for some i tell you what dominate the court earn some real respect you and me will
play one-on-one what do you say okay all right let's i go i really only have
option this you want some of this i can't wait i had the ball i didn't know i even had the ball
block it he didn't get it
the ball nice let's go baby come on come on come on let's get a first one right now
this is too easy i'm getting fucking destroyed give me the ball give me the ball
what what's going on excuse me my name is smooth why are we doing what's going on here
okay we're in the middle of basketball game let's go baby come on
basket but styles cone i can see it that was a travel what do you mean a travel get it
how do i punch in face oh my god give me the ball see what you got that's in
this is too i just lost all the respect i just gained wait up our up up arrow shoot or block
release key to release shot down arrow is break or steal okay i need to get a fucking basket
girl i'll drink your bath water wait baby wait wait smooth just want to talk
oh
but you look good really i'm losing respect six nothing i need to get a steal
give me the ball steal it shot clock no excuse me i uh think you dropped something what i must
have been my home why do we keep getting this like creepy guy what does it have to do with anything
oh i have i have give me the ball got it don't climb them like a ladder we're playing too
man i almost broke a sweat running points on you so fast
you got beat down bad man anybody else have anything to say don't worry about me ace i've
got a ride is it flying the game over bring it on bring it on okay i'm gonna oh i need to
oh wait i gotta put in a different disc i can do that no wait boy i'm gonna drink you like milk
play ball
hey no britney right we just keep cutting to the creepy guys got a friend works at super rock fm
get concert tickets to any concert front row well why don't you take him then
what did he do that for she shines you like a new sneaker
why is everybody here so fucked up still walking yeah i'm going for it right now ready one two three
go yeah four three three tied up bullshit oh sunken tie game i can't get over from downtown
no i got five dollars on the chick uh girl jock she's gonna beat me oh come on did you hey
did you know that britney means flower beauty in one particular tribal language
how'd you know that i study different cultures gonna take anthropology in college
yeah it's too much for me to even react to get me the ball no it's gonna sink oh come on
it's fucking hard get it look like an angel out the sky thanks this point here this game point
can't let it get stuck close game or not you got stunt now get out nobody likes me
what about mad dog you're a ball jr what's this guy this guy's huge you up give up the rock punk
oh it's not fair no i can't even what's wrong rookie can't hang
i can i'll show you right now here we go give me your best shot
shut up
huh try the mad dog i don't understand how to move forward all they can do is shoot and they fucking
walk it like every time your corduroy pairs where where's the flood your super lano plan
give up the ball let's go press down up try me again okay look so down hour is break right so
i mean down i just pressed it you just kind of go like
he steals it
you can't just break for the death i can't i'm getting embarrassed by this guy
yeah you keep knocking that shot down give up the rock punk i can't steal from this guy he's too
strong
oops that's touch hey why not the dice yeah shut up malik you lost the dice we can't play now
this is ridiculous see what you got ace he was so far away sink it yo ace is all that the boy's all
that in a bag of chips the boy's a meal can't hold me you got whooped you got what thank you
goofing for me 50 bucks for my wrench am i gonna win any of these ball i was capable of that this
ball game why can i do nba jam see what you got gigantic super dunk that's illegal
i bet a dollar on ace making the last second shot like the 1968 finals that ended in triple over time
you really know your basketball fuck i have to do that now
do it again my game show me what you got i think that dude's remark is compensation
pretend like you're helping me walk i was nothing he's gonna break it drop him nice
this is my opportunity i gotta take it i gotta make it this is it
time's up again we're good i have to do it get it no i can't move i don't know i thought maybe i
would be able to score a fucking basket in the game man you suck let's go yo that was sorry
i need more respect to face scotty boy i'm gonna drink you like milk play ball
my god all right i'm out of here after this i'm not getting humiliated anymore nice job
10 second violation your ball yeah i know i know how the game works i just can't win one
i can't do it i'm not capable
you get one of three cutscenes where you shoot the ball that was nasty why am i backing up i
want to go forward ah i have to move on i'm never going to be able to see scotty you can
dribble faster than the sound come you didn't shoot i don't know boy you should have never
stepped in here take your butt home can i beat fingers no there's not i don't want to fight i
don't no no no no no no this guy's hard back up fingers you want some of this let's go you got it
come on that was so that was good too i had it come on i can't let fingers beat me
he's the first level
there it is you got the best but you ain't got no kind of style
doesn't matter i used to win that was my opportunity how did i not get that let's go ace come on no
oh what i got it that's how you pull it down baby
i want to go this way i just got fucking really hurt i just got really seriously
injured i let it right on my back let's go dunk it girl your feet must be tight why you say that
because you've been constantly running through my mind brother please
yes was that 10 seconds man you better fix your watch i'm not going to keep the time
oh i got it back drive to the hoop drive to the hoop drive to the hoop drive to the hoop
didn't you knock the ball out of bounds so why do you get it
oh i don't understand you're hitting the ball so far out of fucking bones
what i do girl is carry your books hold your hand and walk you home from school
it's right in there come on you're gonna get a shot gonna get a shot oh come on boys drive right
there five four steal it don't let it score bounce yep oh no hey bro i'm taking bets here
what give me that oh god damn it oh my god what happened no i tried it down i was
trying this game is fucking impossible you were so close give me the ball let's go ace
ace i wish they had like a noise or is this like stuff it that's how i knocked stuff that
oh come on got it get up there i'll fight you let's go i'm ready let's go baby come on come on
i'm ready for this i have to win one stop yeah um i'm way more excited about this than i should
be i think see what you got get out of time one more point i win sink it no we're off to back up
it's too late he needs four more points i'm fine
yeah game over i did it squashed fingers that's something you two chumps owe me some money
you smooth like butter baby nasty now everybody's everybody loves me now all right good
can we have enough points to this what can i play against scotty now
i need more respect let's go down let me see if i can do it again let's go damn the eagle has
landed how did how did i not get that ball what the fuck it's just not even possible
i can't believe it you knew there's gonna be a little disney moving front flip you knew it was
gonna happen about to go up in you what i held it down the same amount of time i held the other one
down this is my world you just visited come on i have to get a steal here
got a red z28 mag wheels really that's right well why don't you just drive away in it
no more scoring no that's game over and no it's not i can't believe it
ah everybody out here owes me five dollars it's payday i'll never i'll never see scotty
that one was funny too that was fun that was a good one all right i gotta pee i'll be right back
pee time we're gonna move on to uh kingdom two this one's a little more high fidelity than the
last one from yesterday show the scotty footage on youtube maybe we will a little bit later
all right so like the last ones let's go image mount d e and here they are
there's that one now we're on the brb all right sorry i'll do it quick let's go this is kingdom
two well we i'm gonna do the it's of the wizard game this one looks a little better i don't know
if this plays a little better we'll find out and here we go three two one hey shit around here
this is gonna be in the wrong spot can't really oh i guess it's the same it's in the right spot
how's that look get to play on virtual image productions present shadowing
this is called shadow shadow a little bit bigger i can that looks all right all right so we last
left uh our wizard friend here this is loud as fuck i already can tell that's that's all right
start as an apprentice should we do the history so you guys can remember what happened
oh that's gonna be better in the times of old there was a land of five kingdoms
justly ruled by the argent kings with their greatest magic they created an amulet made of
five powerful relics joined together they entrusted it to mobis the wisest wizard in the land remember
this i know this had a jealous brother named torlock the twisted he betrayed the argent kings
hunting them down to the last his dark armies then overran the kingdoms
mobis shattered the amulet into its five pieces to keep it out of torlock's reach
it's the same video the pieces one to a kingdom many years later a young man named lathan
candor set out to rejoin the amulet he searched for the relics with the help of his mentor
the wizard daylon daylon in the kingdom of wygaard inside the legendary castle of crystal
lathan found the first relic the honestly who gives a shit mace in the kingdom of iscar
he explored a vast entangled hedge maze until he reached its center and discovered the next
relic the orb of mobis finally in the kingdom of isles he used his guile to overcome the treacherous
elements and acquire the hunting i want to play on his dangerous quest lathan found other items
of magic and power including the blood sword of the argent kings the crystal of kaldar how many
other toys did he find a pentacle coin with these magical with these magical toys holy fuck he
kills that guy blood the wicked well he killed that guy the palace of iscar for the true ruler
princess grace delight now lathan candor prepares to continue his search to find the remaining two
relics two what do you mean we didn't complete that dagger of on and the crown of malrec once
lathan has all five relics he will be able to reassemble the amulet and defeat the wizard
torloff all right you can wake up now you guys you're awake you're good you're good let's go
you can wake up i just oh nice opening shot forces are descending into the far reaches
and destroying everything in their path you must find the last two remaining relics the dagger of
arn and the crown of malrec to assemble the hand it is the only way to defeat torloff
i will do everything in my power to protect the kingdom's grace
oh okay oh door ancient tapestry maybe it's magical scroll of scene orb of lobus so you scroll of scene
oh and i just got a secret door did i just do like a mario warp uh we're going to go in the gate
a healthy young man like you should join the army defending al katash or are you going to hide in
the hills with the women and the children easy with that stick i just got humiliated by an old man
oh where'd it go that's the end of the game i don't wait hunting horn what the hell is going on
creepy 3d yeah that was a long walk to get to this fucking book the hunting horn can
issue a great call that will drive away creatures from the shadow realms it is the second piece of
the hand okay you couldn't have you couldn't have just told me that thanks appreciate it thank you
uh south gate city square drink from the fountain you are here how about um north gate streets watch
tower this city looks as though it's been deserted for days i wonder where everyone is
streets city streets i'm gonna guess maybe
go to the last inn if you want to talk to those who know the reaches best but you have to watch
your back if you want to leave alive go to the inn okay the the last inn east gate how do i get
that from here someone left a note all soldiers report to the north gate all soldiers report to
the north gate why excuse me i am lathe and candor an apprentice wizard how can i who gives a shit
we need warriors not wizards boy come along admin yes so what am i about to like kill this guy's
apprentice apologies sir any man who wields the blood sword of the argin kings is fit for command
join us i thought i was going to slay this guy oh okay i've joined your i've joined you
where where do we go i don't know where we're supposed to go west gate enjoy your flight
oh
what what what what what do i do
potion of flying stolen by the innkeeper jared potion of flying
get in the rowboat let's go maybe this is
that i died in the rowboat why would there be a rowboat there what
dragons in the cliffs only be reached with a traveling spell which cliffs who is rohan
dalon okay uh i'm just as confused as you are lathe woodcutter's hut
black heap let's go to the woodcutter's hut you are too close fool is that the woodcutter
what are you wait wait wait wait wait who's oh my god it's just it's just it's just
oh my let's go this way hello grace what are you still doing here you were needed in the far
reaches the tapestry of seeing will show you the way there you must hurry ancient tapestry
what does the orb of mobis do ruins the whole game i now i cannot complete the game it's over
uh north chamber hello grace what are you still doing here you were needed in the far reaches
the tapestry of seeing will show you the way there but i melted it i did i destroyed it i
melted the thing i can't do it anymore oh no don't worry hanging tree what is this place
a hanging tree though i hang few enough these days with no laws to keep there's no one to hang
for breaking them if this gets worse i'll have to start hanging innocent people
no i don't want to know the lore i know what it is nothing i can do uh i'll put down here the
norseman camp long plains trickster's gully that sounds pretty fun dragon sleeps who exists only
to destroy you soon she will awake get to the black heap in time and the dragon will sleep for
another year get to the black heathen time follow the signs at mile end the last in the
light there it is i think i'm lost the last in last in that's what we what did we have to do here
what is this place the last in and if you're wise you'll stay away only assassins ruffians and scum
in here all right i'll fit right in tell us a secret you know old man i know you look and
smell like a baboon but that's no secret thanks i needed that what
get another sword let's go thanks for trying kid but with guns before you become a porcupine
where do they get guns that was fucking useless
i'd leave here if i were you so you can keep advice like that to yourself that was so stupid
so stupid
they were like rubber band guns they weren't even real guns stolen by the hidden keeper jared a
potion of flying dalon that one didn't real guns all right let's go to black heap in the black
heath the magic of the argent kings is yet strong if the dragon flies down eats me
we'll go to the next game wait dalon dalon bird you are here in tree the long plains river the
long plains alkatesh i don't want to go there that's the town i don't need to go to the town
ruins blast in let's go to the ruins i can't remember why why am i here who am i
rohan the dragon in the cliffs only be reached with a traveling spell which cliffs who is
where do i get the spells where do i get the traveling spell where am i supposed to get
that stuff the traveling spell oh fuck no i gotta get out of here you are too close
okay i'm not going in i have to leave there is no leaving i just die there's no leaving you die
okay
the dragon in the cliffs i know but where the fuck i'm going back here no god damn it
i can't get out of this there's no i don't have any way to get out of this
don't look at it i'm dead now i can't use the idea they give me finite lives why is it please
yeah the items appear in here if they're usable uh i'm gonna go this way and then i'm gonna go
down here i remember that this is the guy and then i'm gonna go the norseman camp
norseman i can barely understand them but i think they're planning to join an army near high pass
why do i have no time now i'm clearly hiding behind this thing and i can't leave i can't go in
my inventory he just slit my throat holy shit um
i can't zoom on and go anywhere else this is a terrible sequel yeah they're both they're both
real bad don't worry they're both really bad um trickster's gully follow the signs here's the
signs okay the last in there's the camp low hills here we go got it i'm glad to see you
beware the innkeeper lathe he steals from his customers and other unwary travelers
that doesn't help me at all i mean i literally not at all literally you know what i mean literally
i'm back let me go i'll start the fire it's one rabbit tonight mace coin sword mace coin
coin the trolls you know what i mean foothills low hills now i gotta go to the foothills
where the fuck did you come from do i have any more coins all right now i get
brought a blood sword or the mace uh mace pretty fancy
okay i just i freaked him out all right here we go rocky hills dalon's portal is over here
i made it i made it to the portal this is the only place in the far reaches and shadowing
where i can physically help you these are inscribed with the spells of release the
undue traps and separate that which should not be bound together now which scrolls should i work on
next uh roll of traveling careful apprentice all right so scroll of release wait should i release
them it just exploded in my hand okay so now i have the scroll of release i don't
i can use that back here i have to go back to the foothills
how am i going to get out of this again can i use all my items again yeah okay mace it just freaks
them out yeah when i go in the tangled in chains that's right so let's go back to town let's get
tangled in the chains back to the rocky hills hmm i've seen ruins like these before that was
back in why guard right okay the last in trickster's gully don't go to the camp go to
the last in and then from here i'm going to go to the top i think i'm lost actually lost okay
i actually am lost i can't select any of these below hill is the last in the long plants
this way hmm al-katech let's get to al-katech scroll of release sounds like there's no one left in
the city east square or something someone left a note all soldiers report already got that one
one city square no west gate there it is enjoy your flight
scroll the release perfect landing i get it all right now i don't know what that does
doesn't do anything
so excuse me i am lathe and candor an apprentice wizard i don't care do you have a sword
oh he does we know are your friends all right now what do i do i don't know what do i do
okay back to the end the black key the magic of the argent kings is yet strong and can heal you
okay wait dalon dalon okay back to the we're gonna do the scroll of release on the guy
all right so let's go back to the last end long planes last in and then the guy in here
we're gonna do the scroll of release landlord i've come back trolls or norsemen don't get a
fool like you door lock serpent men probably will okay i'm back this time i brought magic
tell us what we want to hear or else okay guys gave some of your relatives off my boot on the
way in guess you didn't want to hear that let him go
what thanks wizard you got me out of a tight spot come back sometime and i'll help you in return
why did that happen all right i'm here now can i why did he fall into like a kiss
if i were you well you're not me so you can keep advice like that to yourself
side door side door low and barrel what's in there there's gonna be a secret in there
he's got a relic in there this ocean of flying was stolen from my apprentice potion of flying
you may take it lathan drink the potion drink the potion take it inventory so you're the one
that stole my potion get him boys i tried to drink it i tried to drink the potion
i tried i is there another this game's getting five more minutes welcome back wizard listen that
sword you got is good for cutting flesh but if you want to cut through iron you need the dagger of
iron
where the fuck am i what the hell just happened you're the one that stole my potion get him boys
all right uh go to all right i've had it up i've had it up that was fun for a minute
that was fun for five minutes i can barely understand them but i think they're planning
to join an army near high pass i'm out follow the sun follow the sign yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay can i go those are the low hills here he is watch out there's rocks okay pine woods oh come on
a flying potion boat forest need a pan mended a pot repaired no thanks i'm not traveling with
much well of these parts no one does it oh watch out for the woodcutter such i've heard tell it's a
trap said by torlock thank you i guess
yes
you are too close fool he's wearing a table well this is i i lose i have to leave it i need to drink
that potion but i can't drink it let me try this one more time last time last in potion try to
drink the potion side door i already have the potion huh what how do i have the potion if they
catch me and take it back wait what are you talking about that doesn't kill me oh that doesn't kill you
i thought i'm dead in here well what the fuck is up with that so you're the one that took my potion
put him inside of the barrel that's it up against him that's it who cares all right so now
i have to go to the the rapids where were those does anybody remember what the hell that was
i think i should just die i'll end up there so then drink the potion in the boat
i do love these infant kin continues so get in the boat and now take the potion why would
i need to take the potion in the boat the boat doesn't fly why are people telling me to do this
i have to go to the hills oh god that's it that's it god damn it that's it i'm out of this one take
it in the boat why would i take it in the boat i can't even i why would i need to think about
these things what was i thinking no i gotta get out of this all right don't worry there's more
next game thank god thank god all right so coming up next this one i don't even know if this one
works this is an original american laser game made by the same with the made mad dog free
don't you have to go beat scotty pippen i'm not gonna beat scotty that's not gonna happen here
keep that on for a second uh this is this is crime patrol you play like a police officer and you
it's like a like a shooter i think this game's amazing i've heard it i've never played it i've
heard it's pretty well all right let me get in here this one is super crusty so it's very it
looks like a cell phone video just to give you some warning here same deal um it is where the
hell is it there it is okay so thankfully this is only one disc so let me open this first i should
be able to go like this and can you guys see i don't think you can see it why not oh that's
why okay see see see see see see see hopefully it lines up correctly because i can't really
so it's crime patrol so it's in see they go in crime patrol and then i believe we just go like
this all right hold on wait wait i gotta get in full screen here how does it look can you guys see
it how does it look full screen crime patrol it look all right quiet please i'm thinking
beat cop can you see this is crusty
undercover detective let's do it no this is not the granny game let's go
is there really like a okay it's a new game i'm gonna i'm gonna put it on i'm gonna keep it on
wimpy because i'm a wimp yeah this is american laser games this is this is an original location
what is this broken oh is it because it's on wimp no i think this is on robbery kick them
butt oh robbery that's it oh we the rob no we're not the robbers
extreme screen tearing got it oh he tried it is this gonna be a meathead what i wouldn't what
what why would i not have my why would i not be loaded
i went in there without select continue from the main menu what do i just never have a gun
reloaded again how do i reload i don't know how to reload okay i got it later dude what
too bad you're out i was beginning to like your history partner
ah all right but did i just do it i already did i just complete it
there's just people punching each other what i shot over there all right let's go
over here d did i was i supposed to shoot this person who was that
we're at the oh fuck first it just like got it i was like on a different game location it was
another player all right let's go all right here's the other player over here
this thing
i can't this is too stupid the guy i thought that guy was in a disguise i thought i thought
he was in a disguise i thought he was in a disguise i thought he was in a disguise
okay he looked like he was in a disguise oh no they're all over the place careful let me walk
in front of your fucking gun oh did i scare you that was a security guard you shot too bad
you're out why would you do it twice hey they're all over the place watch out by the way i don't
but they're all over the place god damn it if he comes out again oh come on
did i even shoot him yes i'm on my own huh welcome to undercover welcome to undercover
well hold on a minute what just happened i i don't understand what happened
the deal's going down this is aja rodriguez she's inside
tough luck you're finished he put his head guy in my view
the deal's going down she's inside she's i'm sorry i had like i had a rough night last night
i'm always i can't see their faces why don't you put the beer goggles on me
is that a juice box this is aja rodriguez she's inside i should i gotta get this guy
let's eat their lunch let's eat their lunch all right this puts the middle and then
okay i got it he dives over here guy this way guy up here and then two bullets take him is that
a good guy i don't know oh shit that's the shot agent rodriguez i'm gonna jump behind
of the hidden object that's a that's a great idea oh my fucking god i did it again
sorry part you're out of here and kick the gun closer to the person
oh
just in case he gets up just make it real easy what what are you after
why would you why would you shoot the bring in the evidence
i don't know who's gonna shoot who is that person still driving
anymore got any coffee and if there's no restaurant man you got the cash you got the document
yeah you got the document new ip number the work the work well here's the work
you're under arrest for selling stolen property
all right we're good they're out there in the junkyard i got you right when you popped up
your history partner i didn't even a chance to start come on give me a fucking break
sorry part you're out of here that's such dog shit let's go you gotta be kidding me guy
later dude you that's a you i love you welcome i remember that shit i love that stuff
oh fuck off with that
can you guys even see what's going on in the game if you're ready for this guy right here come on
right here
he's not dead good did i shoot him with somebody else is this even
a car hold on wait rewind for a second did a car you're out of here did the guy turn
into a car what happened with that i'm so confused why that car came from the right side watch the
right side the guy jumps into the car hits him ready it's just in the air they really do love
they love that they love the slow motion see the car hi lulu the usual thanks how are you
how you doing it's a cold-blooded killer we've been after him for years i don't think he's made
us yet shut up bambi i feel the heat and it's not the kind of heat i like is that don't let
you take them what why would you why are the people dancing why would you be dancing hey
all the patrons everyone just sitting around it was the same person this is so stupid
hey you're looking for me you who what how did i not get him
no i can do this again hi lulu the usual let's go let's go let's go let's go
jump in front of me no that wasn't even it's all right
hey you're looking at me you who i love the acting act i love acting
oh he's drinking yuhu in a strip club hi lulu the usual thanks bars don't have you doing this
like that's big tony the tongue ugly and the usual a chocolate milk sorry i have to focus
we got like four people in the end oh god no
oh sorry part damn it shit unbelievable well everything's so pixelated i can't tell
okay not this time i love when it just jumped there's a new for the new scene
i almost didn't get that oh he got blends in so well up there congratulations
you did a good job we're promoting you to swat you've been promoted i don't know this game was
this fucking there's so much going on in this game special police unit as we speak are taking
i didn't know there was this major drug lab no drug lab
that's a major drug lab holy shit god damn it that's fast oh your history dude
shit police units as we speak are taking up positions that's a suspected major drug lab
i'm on the higher difficulty that's true you're right but i'm already on it
did a lot of swears on tv lady i was right there i was right there i'm going to wimp holy shit how
did i not get it twice three times whoa all right let's go jesse oh come on why do you still do it
just exploded the whole thing just blew up what are you doing here how are you even still alive
in there i don't did i just i don't understand i don't understand bank robbery bank robbery
these guys look tough do you think you can handle it what was the i don't know what that glass was
oh fuck you're a history part skip lost on wimpy yeah this is the hardest part of the game
later dude god damn it skip thank robert i'm gonna try glass you're history dude
thank robert these guys look tough to the left i gotta be aware of
thanks to the cutscene i was able to reload damn it that's so
ah thank robert can't help these guys look tough half of them aren't even doing anything they just
standing and then sitting back down
oh i don't later thank robert can't help these guys look tough imagine playing this with a bald
mouse imagine playing this ever losing a hundred wimpy imagine playing this game on the higher
this motherfucker i can't uh later dude is there a way to slow down the emulation
yes i can slow it down oh this guy i have to do it without the cheating i have to do it without
cheating i have to do without cheating have to do without cheating okay he's like killed me right
why not now i'm busy same guy every time
shit i'm getting a fucking migraine right now completely unrelated oh my god i'm so
my left eye i got it my fucking god your history dude
dude hold on let me go get some water i actually do have like a migraine right now
i'll be right back oh the brb was buying this
this game's hard wimpy is hard mode no it's not uh so i need to uh unfortunately
i gotta slow down a little uh i'm getting a migraine that's going over like the left side
of my head here it started to happen like maybe 30 40 minutes ago and i was just like ah whatever
i don't know why the fuck this is happening i i drank a course light that's literally what happened
um now i get migrants so it's not out of the ordinary this when they happen on stream it's
kind of annoying um four hours i really wanted to go for like five he's getting a one beer hangover
right now oh this sucks uh let me uh let me just chill for a minute we'll see if this is just like
a little thing that might start going up a bit just to hang out it's you know what and i think
like laughing at shit will make this really way worse so sorry guys sorry that i have to kind of
just chill now uh tomorrow tomorrow i was gonna do this again there's still a few more and i'm
gonna run out of them by tomorrow so what we're gonna do tomorrow is we'll do the remaining
few that i have and then we'll probably just move on to something else
yes i do have the sequel to crime patrol i have crime patrol 2 as well
um i am annoyed right now but what am i gonna do right you know what i mean like what am i gonna
do be upset about this probably it's all right though um let's just hang out i'll see you guys
tomorrow those of you that uh i might just call it in like an hour or so let's just hang out
and we'll do the bits thanks for joining me uh sorry it was a four hour this is back to back
like four hour streams too and that's kind of not what i wanted to do yesterday was unrelated to
like getting a fucking headache do i get migraine auras yes i do what ends up happening is i start
to get blind spots in my vision it's almost like like it's like tinny metallic colors will appear
and it's almost like when i look at people's faces um it's almost like a picasso painting
i get those it's pretty it's weird it's very weird those suck yeah and the thing about that
when you get an aura with a migraine at least for me holy shit everything turns off for like
three straight days i can't do anything does your doctor oh yeah yeah yeah i've don't worry i've
been to the doctor about this this is a 15 plus a year long thing it's like colitis so don't worry
but i'm all right i just feel like i'm gonna make it way worse if i continue to kind of be at a an
energy level that's higher than right this second and crime patrol 2 i don't know if i don't know
if it's going to be that game and i also have cycle mania and i mean cycle mania might do it to
me so i gotta i gotta be careful cycle mania is a is a fucking motorcycle game an fmv motorcycle
game but i'm all right just to hang out we'll do the bits i'll see you guys tomorrow let's go back
a few hours ago where i missed a lot of stuff today germa sucks thanks to the five community subs
this is from just about four hours ago now thank you germa sucks get night trap i already did night
trap this is fmv uh part two i did almost every single sega cd game these are some of the dos
ones that just kind of fell through the cracks some of them have been fucking great i really
think that uh slam city with scotty pippen might be the best one of the best fmv games i've ever
that was amazing that was like the best fucking 45 minutes of my entire life but thank you germa
sucks with five subs sawdust monies thanks for three bucks gnarly thanks for the 250 they say
what's up with the bananas on your on your video what do you mean what am i talking about what's
up with the bananas on your let me see what you're talking about oh right on this video so uh i had
just a bunch of random intro videos one of them was instead of germs it was bananas
for my old youtube intro there's no reason for it it's just there as early youtube but that's
not no that's not even early youtube that's uh that's 2015 that's not that long ago i used it
once yeah so yeah it's there that was four years ago four years ago is not that long when you're
over 30 i got i have some news for you once you passed 30 three four five years was like oh that
was fucking yesterday we had two hundred dollar bit uh donations one from evil crucifix and one
from slayed both back-to-back hundred bucks just to use this to buy a new mug that was during the
mug meltdown not even that i'm not even gonna call it a meltdown shouldn't be up there in the
meltdown but thank you both you guys for your huge huge money and speaking of huge money
phylactery lich also gave 50 dollars a couple hours ago thank you thank you thank you more
money from phylactery if you could believe it if you didn't think it was possible there it is
jerma please don't ever stop playing this game because uh become friends with chad and the bottle
guy talking about slam city singularly funding this channel something like that it's a lot of
money man thank you uh also thank you too disinterest for the five dollars hey jerma i
don't know if you've already been told this but your venus emote always looks a little bit
like the baby grinch doing a pogchamp face to me when it shows up in small
when it shows up small in chat for some reason thanks for the streams baby grinch
baby grinch i i mean maybe oh yeah maybe a little it does yeah when is baby grinch in a movie
i've never seen baby grinch is that from the jim carrey grinch movie i don't remember that scene
what that well hold on give me a little bit of a slack out that movie's four hours long
so it's easy to forget but thank you disinterest for the five dollars thank you to uh the wombat
from hell for the 250 they say six months ago i vented in a bit message about my medical issues
ruining my life and you offered incredibly kind words of wisdom and empathy i am now in
college and for the first time i feel free from the anxiety of my health problems thank you so
much for everything you did that got me through high school without having a mental breakdown and
kept me laughing ps are you ever going to play hat in time it's my favorite well first if if you
can seriously if you can get through that shit and deal with it and take care of your problems
that's fucking awesome i'm really happy to hear that it's going better as somebody that has all
kinds of fucking health problems um it can be a huge pain in the ass or a huge fucking pain in
the ass so whatever you can do and if you're going to say that i had something to do with
any of that that i am incredibly fucking thankful i can't even imagine whatever you get from this
channel i don't care what it is thank you for watching i'm glad that you get something out of
it thank you so much wombat from hell i'm glad you're doing better keep going keep managing
that's all you can do especially when it comes to health problems we also had uh ten dollars come
in from uruhara thanks for the ten bucks no message just ten dollars a few of these back
to back to back here ten dollars from gnarly thank you gnarly this finally unlocks my ten
thousand bit badge thank you so much for copious amounts of great content been watching for five
years or so you're easily my favorite content creator on both platforms let's see if i can
keep that going i'm gonna try oh lord phylactery holy shit man how does he do it i don't know but
they continue to do that's 69 more community subs from phylactery religion that puts you
you are now responsible for a very large percentage of the people that have subscribed
to this channel now that's a pretty significant portion of people that are subbed so thank you
completely completely unnecessary at this point because that's so much money i hope you can afford
it if you can then fucking awesome i'm i'm glad you got a lot of money if you can't make sure
you're taking care of yourself first that's very important he owns you now i got too loud i'm not
supposed to be getting loud but phylactery that's an insane amount of subs sometimes this happens
somebody gives a shitload of money over the course of a month or two and it just floors me
so i can't believe it i'm shocked that somebody wouldn't want to give me this much money as one
single person so thank you i hope you can afford it thank you doctor and chat yeah and good luck
in with your with your patients because you're obviously a doctor and a scientist combined oh
i didn't mention that hat in time right hat in time um probably not if i'm completely honest
switch to this because i i do have i'm gonna go take like a bath or something just so
i'm gonna like soak my head in water um probably not not now i don't want to say yeah maybe sure
maybe you'll see it so i don't want to do that because there's so much stuff going on over the
next few weeks that that this would end up being another one of those scenarios where
oh yeah maybe a few weeks on and then in end of october someone's gonna ask the same question
and i'm gonna be like oh yeah um maybe you know maybe a few weeks so i don't want to tell people
that i'm gonna be doing things and then just not do them when's the carnival it's the 21st
the carnival is next week next weekend september 21st i also want to say something about the
activity book stream so if you have not get a submission in for the activity book because
that is going to close uh this weekend so friday so friday night it's been that that those channels
have been live for a long time so i think it's time to close them up so on friday uh probably
like i don't know midnight pacific we're going to be closing those up and then that stream
will be the last stream that i do before leaving to go and do the carnival stream so i'm going to
give you some dates here because it's pretty important because this next week is going to be
i will not be streaming because i'm going to be setting up the whole carnival so tomorrow live
tomorrow which would be thursday and then friday and saturday is not going to be anything and then
sunday monday sunday monday tuesday will be the last streams of that week the next time you see
it and maybe even uh sunday monday will be the last two streams because i'm gonna i have to get
going i have to get on a plane to go across the country so the 16th of september might be the
last stream until the 21st or the 17th i haven't decided yet depends on how much time i need to
get ready because the 17th is when yeah the 16th into the 17th is when i have to get out of here
he's quitting to become a clown maybe no not quitting make sure you pack your toothbrush
i will is there gonna be any behind the scenes stuff for the carnival i think andy mark is
filming stuff and we're probably gonna do like an ama at least i will uh after the stream is over
but then twitchcon twitchcon is that next week so it's gonna be it's gonna be all over the place
streams are gonna be a little bit of a juggle after this week just because of twitchcon and
the carnival and everything i'm looking forward to it i can't wait but tentatively that activity
book stream will be probably on the 16th and it's just gonna be us hanging out no pressure
no nothing from anybody just fun little activities and jokes and stuff that people
wrote and submitted i'm gonna compile it all into a big pdf and i'm gonna do it all on stream
we're just gonna hang out it's gonna it'll be a nice hangout stream i can assure you what time is
the carnival going to be i have i do have a time for you september 21st at 12 pm eastern time is
when that stream is going to start uh turn on now depending on making sure everything works
12 ish but i think we got a pretty hard start for 12 eastern and that isn't a weekend too so
it's saturday you're on pacific i'm sorry but the stream will be on eastern time how long is it
gonna last the time frame has been blocked out for somewhere between four and six hours we're
shooting for somewhere around five five hours six hours or so there's a lot going on on this stream
let me tell you this ain't just this ain't just a little dunk tank a lot going on here with a bunch
of technical difficulties um i don't think so because there are a bunch of engineers working
on this and a full production company so there are two different companies that are doing this
and me so it's not just me and hey okay now let me turn them on it's it's probably about 10 to
there's probably about 10 to 15 people that are going to be like on site working on this at the
same time maybe a little bit more are you doing rehearsals yes we are that's why i'm not i am
not going to be here for a week because that whole week i'm going to be doing all this stuff this
whole thing is going to take a while to set up but the uh the clock is ticking here it's happening
real soon i just want to get over there you know what i mean you know when something's about to
happen and you know what it's going to be and you know what it it's probably going to look like
that's every night i just go to bed and i just i think about it it's gonna be fucking awesome
it's gonna be so fun i can't wait it's weird because it's actually made it's almost like when
i'm when i'm live i'm just sitting here going like i can't wait for the carnival i can't wait
for the carnival i can't wait for the carnival when's the carnival i can't wait for the carnival
and it's like shut up dude i'm fucking trying to stream there's like three or four of us up here
but yeah that's closing in but let's continue the bits let me get a sip of my water and like
blink my left eye hard no i'm all right it's still there but i'll be good to go for tomorrow
because that was kind of i didn't want to push it and stream for like another 45 minutes to an hour
and then be in like a bunch of fucking pain and shit and then it's like oh canceling the stream
tomorrow sorry guys i can't do it i don't want to do that what was the reason that cox died
yesterday i have no idea it just was everything just turned up we were just we're at complete
zero to the whole house it was weird yeah more we're gonna we'll finish up the fmv stuff tomorrow
and then depending how loud because there's at least this i think there's three there's at least
two or three other games that i want to play that are experiences that are worth doing and then after
that um we'll see my you know what it's we're on dos maybe you know we'll do dos tomorrow
we will do the fmv shit and then we'll move on to dos from the dos website people have been
waiting for that for a while so we'll do that for sure but uh s10w update thanks for the 250
they say hey germa sorry i have to sell out to subway to give you 25 more cents
but let it be known i do it from the heart anyways i'm so happy this has been a great year for you
and hope we get many more with you peace and love peace and love yeah i'm the carnival stream
is the start of doing more things like that spending time on there are already another two
or three projects i want to do that i've actually talked to people that are currently working on
this one i have the contacts now guys didn't have that shit before now i do you can probably expect
way more shit like this because that's the direction that i want to take the stream
i've been talking about this shit for years and not done it so many things fell through the cracks
i'm working with a company and it didn't work out oh that company doesn't exist anymore
well this company wanted to do that but i didn't want to do that i've been just i've been trying
to do more high production stuff for like two or three years and shit always just didn't work out
and it is now so as of september 21st start expecting stuff like that to happen way more
frequently i don't know i just read this i said i miss basement germa where he was just a humble
streamer i thought that said i missed basement germa when he was just a terrible streamer
like i remember when he was just a basement street he was terrible i miss both yeah but
those don't have to go away no no wait hold on a second i'm not a terrible streamer all right you're
working me up here anyways there are more ideas that are going to happen after this and some of
them you know it's gonna fucking blow you away just wait this is gonna you're gonna be like your
socks are just gonna like you're gonna be sitting in your chair it's gonna be like my socks are
gone my socks are off they just flew off i didn't do anything i'm just sitting here
it's my socks but yeah thank you uh fh gregory for the 250 uh thank you they say hey there
jaron boy i was listening to the thursday afternoon just before friday morning monday morning podcast
and i heard that bill burr was in vegas a few weeks ago i want to know if you've ever got a
chance to see him live i know you mentioned in the past that you like him or at least that he's
influenced some of your comedy in a way but maybe that's not the case anymore anyway feel better
with your migraine my 52 year old mother gets them too uh thanks and go fuck yourself
that was them saying that that was not me saying that just want to make sure that the quote ends
there okay so first of all uh i did not see bill burr i may have i still think bill burr is
fucking hilarious he's he's such a quick when he goes on talk shows even like he's just so
quick quick quick quick quick i it's envious how fast he can come up with something
thank you fh uh fh gregory uh no actually the only show that i've seen uh so far is pen and teller
and it was great this many years later they've been doing that for fucking 40 almost 45 years
it was great it was just a nice show it was really nice they did a lot of cool stuff
bullshit was a great show they've been around for a while they've been doing stuff for
they've been still relevant you know sometimes it's like oh we're gonna go see a vegas show
i lost vegas can't wait to see this who is it oh not really relevant anymore they're just kind
of doing this here oh it's how long has it been since your last slick single like 25 years
oh all right no that's cool that's cool i guess the pen and teller they have a tv show
they have a show that's on right now they have never stepped out of that spotlight
yeah fool us and it's not even it's a it's a pretty good show i'm not talking i'm talking
about britney spears what are you talking are you serious you don't you don't talk you don't
talk shit about britney spears excuse me you thought i was referencing the literally the
legendary britney spears guys no i'm talking about chris angel mind freak although that's
not a single though you know what i wouldn't be surprised if chris angel had an album quick cut
his mic did you get your mind fucking freaked yet um no look if you like if you like the mind freak
show good i'm glad that's good something you'll like migraine mind free no i'm not going to be
one of those shit talkers that just say i don't think it's very good it sucks uh so you should
think it sucks too well you don't also think it sucks but i just told you to think it sucks
i just told you it sucks yeah but i like it but i just told you that it sucks i know but i like it
yeah but i just told you that it sucks okay it sucks see i i knew it i told you
did you get us tickets by the way i kind of want to go
uh anyways thank you to that was fh gregory no unfortunately i have not seen uh bill burr live
unfortunately i probably think it was a good show thank you um tailix for the 250
appreciate it they say when playing spider-man for the ps4 you said that you disliked stanley's
cameos because they ruined your immersion well i didn't say that i didn't like them
uh you also have recently said that spider-man far from home is your favorite marvel movie
it is also the first marvel movie to not have a stanley cameo it's an observation um well that's
here's the thing that i didn't i never said that i never said that i didn't like the stanley cameo
everybody loves the fucking stanley cameos okay all i said was i did not say that i didn't say that i
said that stanley cameos back you know this is a few years three four years ago whatever it was
or two years ago what does spider-man come up anyway so the spider-man the stanley cameos all
i said was it makes you very aware that you're watching a movie it makes you very aware that
you're playing a video game that was it i still like them i still think they're fun and interesting
of course i do of course i do when did spider-man come out well originally nobody cares you
loser should i purge that comment i feel like i should no i'll leave it leave it no i'll leave
it leave it leave it don't touch don't do not modem do not oh he's look at how sensitive this
streamer is i am pretty you know i am actually pretty sensitive i might not seem it you guys
know that you guys do you guys know that i don't do you i'm serious do you guys know that i don't
kill bugs i'm dead serious i don't unless they're trying to kill me okay and the wasp is different
the wasp was trying to kill me if i'm if it's like a okay with life or death scenario here
the wasp is trying to murder me okay wasp stings don't kill what if you what if i was allergic to
wasps excuse me i'm not what if i was what about santa i said i don't i didn't kill a bug on stream
and you go to santa are you implying that santa is an insect yeah i can't i can't you guys can't
be funny right now no don't be you can't be funny don't do it now spider-man is my favorite
universe far from home is my favorite movie venom is one of my favorite characters stanley created
some of my favorite things of ever in my entire life so of course i love stanley and every time
he shows up to answer your question but far from home is the best spider-man movie there's there's
no debate there there isn't you want to debate me about this i'll open up the debate right now
spider-verse is better spider-verse is better spider-verse spider-verse spider-verse spider-verse
spider-verse spider-verse what about the spider-verse i like that one too i really like that one
that's probably the second best one i didn't i already did a tier list no that's like it goes
far from home spider-man one spider-verse and homecoming no spider-man no there are this four
the top four there it is homecoming better than far from home that's tough for me i don't know
about that far from home is an overrated movie now i am going to purge that i'm going to purge that
one click right click purge comment click done got him yeah take that i'm i'm away from my
keyboard right now i can't do it i'm just pretending i did it but anyways let's uh let's uh end this
so i can actually go lie down because my brain right now is like working triple time so let's
go where are we where did we end up oh up here okay oh yeah because phylactery came with a
shitload of substance just knock down so many things so many messages got like just
pushed up because of it thank you to uh sin sin access stead for the five dollars thank you uh sin
hey jeremy thanks you for thank you for being epic and making me feel better when i need it love your
content love you more thank you for five dollars appreciate it thank you flug boy for the five
dollars i'm trying to fix my dumb mental state lately and i think uh and i'm always moved at
the fact that you can still manage to lift some sort of weight off of me when i can tune into a
stream i've been on a roller coaster ride of emotions and i will say you help slow it down
i wish you the best take it slow work on yourself however you know you can because you're the only
one that knows how to do that i am honored to lift some weight off of you and anybody else
i just want the streams to be fun i don't i don't care about anything else you know what i'm saying
i want you to have fun i want us to enjoy the streams together i want obviously i want to have
fun i want to enjoy what i'm doing i want us to collectively think everything is a fun time
nothing else nothing else matters it really doesn't so when people tell me that it's they're
having fun and it's like helping them and it's shit it's that means a lot i like how you don't
make it all about yourself that's pretty cool um well it isn't it can't be because you you're
the ones that have to be entertained you know what i mean as much as it's about me it is also about
you the reason why i try to do things that might be more fun or more entertaining sometimes
is because i want you to watch like for instance the carnival i i'm not doing the carnival
just because well you know either like let me just like piss away a bunch of money
and oh i can't wait this is gonna be great for me i'm gonna have a lot of fun here
you know what i'm not even gonna turn on the stream i think i'm just gonna not turn the stream
on and just have a carnival no it's because it's potentially a fun interesting thing that
you guys can participate in that i think and i that interests me that's why i only look
if something interests me i'm gonna do it it doesn't matter what it is it's gonna happen
i get so stuck and locked in on doing things that i think would be fun for the stream sometimes to
the detriment sometimes to my own detriment but then i think about oh but that would be fun
wouldn't it i think people would think that was fun i think that's fun maybe they would too
that's all i need to hear that's all i need to know that's why he spent five million dollars
on the carnival i mean i think you're pretty close not for real i i wouldn't be doing it
if i wasn't having a good time and it didn't interest me and if it wasn't interesting you
because i don't you know you know i don't want to have one of those i don't have like a stream
where it's just like every day it's just like hey i don't i don't like this at all
oh okay well i don't i don't want that i don't want you to do that now some streams will be
more exciting i think than others and i can't have something crazy fucking like i can't have
like a carnival stream every fucking stream that's impossible but it is on my mind all the time but
thank you why not now you are talking five million dollars that is that number is real
if that is the case but thank you flood boy thank you future gamer for the 250 what is the current
sub count at also how many emote slots has phylactery opened on their own uh we're currently
at 5,800 5,875 subs 74 subs we are currently down from the peak of about 7,000 which was just
fucking crazy if you remember that do you guys remember like four months ago when i had like
seven fucking thousands of that was fucking crazy so it's we've kind of evened out a little bit here
add another fucking crazy number when did it get so high this year it fluctuates though
so it'll go it's i can't give you like an exact i mean that's the current snapshot of subscribers
right now it's a month or two from now that might drop a couple thousand it might go up a couple
thousand i have no idea it's kind of all over the place when it comes to um just like exact numbers
it's kind of hard to tell but there are 5,874 right this second i haven't even begun to pick
followers per month is increasing too well cool good i hope you like the streams because that's
all i'm gonna do that's all i'm just i'm gonna stream you know what i mean like if people come
in and they like it then i think that's good too much information but do you have do you ever not
break even on big projects i don't i mean it's a i don't know it's hard to answer that because
like on september 21st am i going to make back the money that it's i spent on this stream
no i would say absolutely not absolute zero will i make that back in the year to six months
i don't know maybe probably i don't know i don't know i don't i don't even i'm not thinking about
that i'm doing all right though guys don't worry about me in that regard i wouldn't do this shit
if i wasn't able to so let me make that really really clear first bald coin is spiking what kind
of car do you drive i drive a ho almost got it you got was quick oh almost had it why does everybody
care about the car that i drive a honda to a honda 2000 no guys i drive the gerbil car
he drives a honda omega what's what what's wrong with the honda what's wrong with the honda
excuse me purge that i don't want to see that it's fucking high quality that's a quality car
and i like what the what the fuck you know i'm saying that's all i have to say but thank you too
uh that was future gamer currently have an absolute shitload of subs and you guys see it
every stream you see this shit pop up every damn stream and i can't fucking believe it every time
so why don't we show it now those of you wondering all the people that and the community support the
community subs the first time subs the long time subs this is this is this is it right here it's
like this every fucking single time so that's where that comes from thank you to all of you
thank you unreal 20 more from phylactery holy shit dude he's back all right that's your way
too many gifted subs you filled the gifted sub mana bar it's an early bitcoin adopter
but phylactery holy shit and that's more thank you for that i got to use my alt yeah you'll see
the alt soon what happens when you run out of people to gift subs too i don't know does it just
pick random people on twitch i didn't think about that but phylactery again 89 community subs tonight
that's almost 100 fucking subs that's i can't even imagine that many people that this is it
you understand thank you hey flug boy no actually it was an unreal leviathan because um that huge
sub drop just came in thanks for the 10 bucks unreal leviathan i don't know how i'm gonna make
it through the next couple weeks but i've got your lovely self jeremy love you much love to you right
back at you i'm not sure what's going on over the next couple weeks but hopefully you can figure it
out i wish you the best thank you so much for the support who in here is subbed because of phylactery
hundreds of you are so there are a lot of you that are subbed because they're giving out subs
but thank you unreal leviathan the 10 dollars take care thank you flug boy for the 250
i will say the time i got to meet you at pax and i called your name from the crosswalk above and
you looked up at me and said something stupid like it kind of was a weird feeling like i was
seeing a friend after a long time i actually do remember that i thought i did something wrong i
think right i remember i walked in and i was just kind of had like a coffee in my hand i just heard
like hey like germa hey and i'm just looking i'm like what did i do i did something wrong like i
did securities coming what did i do i didn't do anything something wrong then we just hung out
you walked in he's a criminal there he is get him no coffee i was like yeah but was it the coffee
was it like a is it like the movie theater are you mad that i didn't buy it here
security guard calling you germa
hey germa germa you're in big i can't i get to be the one that arrests germa i can't wait it gets
me in cops like hey can i get a selfie no no get the fucking i didn't want a fucking picture
twitchcon 2019 this motherfucker brought coffee in i was baffled by the fact that anyone could drink
espresso shots back when i met you and now like two years later i have one every other morning
yeah espresso is great it's easy it's quick you can do a shot of espresso you can sip on a shot
of espresso and it's just done that's it it's hot takes three four five sips all right that was nice
done it's over i'm done i don't have to do any more than that but you do probably get a second one
a few hours later that's a sign filled bit if it is then that he's that's what a smart comedian
because it's true uh phylactery the 50 dollar donation you gave earlier has a comment on it
i want to say it they say i'm like an old school art patron and you are my michael angelo germa
make art for me my boy an art patron yeah but the difference is i'm not making michael angelo i'm
scribbling crayons back of your electric bill and putting it on the fridge hoping that you're
proud of me but they're good scribbles hey thank you i tried you're the elephant at the zoo that
learned how to hold a paintbrush uh thank you to lieutenant campbell for the 250 hey germa sorry i
can't give as much as the pimp lord but what do you mean pimp lord i got it uh i can't give as much
as the pimp lord anyways uh but i got into a car wreck recently and need to save for some crap
wagon take my pocket change and apply directly to the forehead to ease your migraine uh brain
pain is no joke i've been watching you since your tf2 days uh back in 2011 i just wanted to let you
know how much of a beacon of joy you've been through the years never stop being the amazing
person you are actually yeah i i will go take Tylenol that's not a bad idea that's not a bad
idea but i'm sorry to hear about your car accident uh please continue to save money
get yourself a new set of wheels hopefully you're okay hopefully everyone's okay and just
just to let you know i mean like if you're in the market for a car i would i would say honda
just i've heard things i've heard stuff on the radio about how hondas are very reliable cars
i've read a couple articles i've seen some retweets on honda i think they're very
competitively priced i would just recommend one but thank you uh lieutenant campbell for the 250
wingus dingus thanks to the five dollars hey germa i'm also 30 and compact isn't it sad that
we've reached peak of the height and we will be smaller from now on i ain't getting smaller the
day that i start getting smaller is the day that i start putting fucking little things in my shoes
i ain't ever gonna be swallowed in five eight uh when i turn 60 and i shrink an inch and a half
i'm putting in like something in my shoes i'm getting special shoes to be like an inch taller
they're gonna they're gonna bury me at five eight i'll be five eight at like 89 90 years old
i'm gonna live to be fucking 90 97 they're gonna they're gonna bury you standing up
yeah i want my casket vertical hey thank you too uh thank you too ding dang for the 10
dollars germa been a fan for a long time you've always been a huge influence on me so i got some
friends to recreate one of the movies you made in the movies game i'd love if you check it out
piece in the description is a side-by-side comparison of my version what an awesome
opportunity for me to talk about this you ready the community content channel is going to open
tomorrow before the stream let's go i can't do it love i'm gonna get that open tomorrow what
this channel will be for there'll be rules there'll be a pinned message there read them this will be
for any community content which at some point over the month once maybe once or twice a month
depending on how much stuff we compile we will do a community hangout night probably once a month
where we watch and observe and consume all of this community media another emote contest
no it's possible that we can no i'm not gonna give any
okay i'm not gonna give any spoilers i have awful internet please what is he saying i'll write it
out no i can't do that my my brain's too fucked up right now to do that but no it'll be i'm gonna
get it open tomorrow it'll be in the same realm as the recommended channel where you would just
put your submission with like a sentence or two it's not there for discussion it's not there to
talk about it it's there to just put it there put a little description of what it is and that's it
and we'll go over them and i and the mods will over the over you know the 30-day period will
come up with a good hey let's sit back and relax and watch with a fucking comb in my hair
what about the discussion of said content um that's a good question i mean i've
we kind of we'll do that on stream you know what i mean i think that's part of it is once those
things come through we can just kind of hang out and talk about them on the stream
but a couple more bits to go through we had uh bcpox bsi bcpox for the five dolls
been a long time second you viewer for watching the streams the last few days has been great keep
it up yeah maybe maybe we'll see tomorrow we'll keep going tomorrow i had to cut it early today
again for the second day in a row so i'm sorry about that finally we had um
thank you to something whenever anybody else get like this when you get a migraine
it's like you get like a wall that you have to like climb over with every other sentence
sometimes it's like that it's annoying like oh and then ah oh yeah that's what i was gonna say
it's irritating but uh thank you wing for the 250 hey germa i have meme cheered a lot in the past
but i want to tell you how much you make my life brighter with all that you do
i'm going to have to end my sub for a bit because of money problems but i want to truly thank you
for your humor and how it makes me want to be more like you i'm sure there are many in the
community that feel the same way thank you thank you for fucking subscribing that is a completely
optional thing if you ever need to end your sub that's i'm i'm shocked and honored and thankful
that you even thought to do it in the first place thank you what was their name it was wing wing
uh chin wing chain 250 i think i'm saying that am i saying that right the name was wing but thank
you i tried to give them a sub oh look at you tingy but don't worry if you if you don't if you
can't sub to the channel just hang out and have fun that's completely and totally fucking 100
percent all good no one is ever under any obligation to pay this channel money don't do
it if you can't if you were and you didn't and now you do or you don't it don't worry about it
thank you for your 250 and thank you for your sub and i will see you guys tomorrow we'll pick
back up the way we left off i'm gonna go put my head down and just exist for a little while
probably get some food too i swear you know what was it was it the you know i must have been the
beer right it had to have been i drank a core's light i don't drink beer i don't know that was
weird drunk a drunk off of one core's light
you gotta maintain the buds no no no no it's well i had you know i had one core's light
and it gave me a fucking migraine i don't that's like not funny but i don't know why it is
i'm not gonna drink i'm never gonna drink this beer
no it's not the beer it's like the my body today guys you guys have watched me drink like a whole
bottle of wine on stream before it's not alcohol but maybe it is this time i don't know i'll see
you tomorrow have a great night guys see you soon