Hey everybody, get out of the way! Hey everybody, what's going on? It's Jerma the Cactus here.
Oh, that's a tree. Let's switch now. Hey, what's up everybody? Jerma here, and Italics and MLC Stealth.
Welcome to Timed Chaos Build, where we build crazy stuff in a timed amount of time. And you two introduce yourself.
I know they know who you guys are, but still, it could be fun. I'm looking at you.
I am Italics, and my channel is Gamers Descent, and you've probably seen me with Jerma in Minecraft and against him previously. Woohoo!
Alright, where's MLC Stealth? Where are you?
I'm right here, I just found this guy. My name's MLC Stealth.
Hey, stop it! Stop breaking stuff. People are going to see the pit that was hidden under here that we just patched up.
We're like dead bodies. Children bodies.
Alright, so if you're not familiar how this works, we time ourselves. It's going to be eight minutes this time, and we're going to try and build a horse in eight minutes in today's episode.
And once eight minutes is up, we have to stop hands up in the air. We can't do anything else, so let's get this started. Are you guys ready to build a horse?
We're ready. Yes.
So, on the count of three, eight minutes. Three, two, one, go!
Alright, hooves should be black, right? Start with the feet.
So, the horse is going to be brown?
Yeah, the horse is going to be brown. This is going to be a huge freaking horse, man. That's a pretty big hoof.
Alright, that is a big hoof.
Any forders?
That's a big hoof, yeah.
Hold on, I'm trying to figure out, like, should we do this? He's going to have, like, skeletal legs.
Wait, wait.
The front two, wait, should they be staggered, like he's walking?
Yeah, I think he should just be relaxing, maybe?
Alright, just, like, standing at attention.
Reading the Sunday newspaper? Alright, I'll get this leg.
Are those two close together?
I think they're okay.
I think so.
Dude, I'm waking, this leg is way too big.
This is going to be a huge creation. We only have, like, seven minutes left. Go, go, go. No more dilly-dallying.
Okay, maybe not.
Legs go straight up for a little while. Yours doesn't.
No, it's okay. It's okay, he has a broken leg, don't worry.
What the crap is going on here? Okay.
And now it's his body.
Alright, so you close the body together. Oh my god, dude.
Why is he the same?
This is going to be the derpiest horse I've ever seen.
Hurry up, we don't have time.
Mine doesn't have any knees.
Just go. We don't have time for this.
It's just going, like, straight up. It's going to be like a stick figure horse.
There's no time.
We kind of just have to build it.
Oh my god, why do we make the legs so big? We're never going to finish this.
Mine's kind of like, mine's like sprouting fat.
Oh my gosh, this is going to be huge.
This is going to be an enormous horse.
Alright, first of all, his body can't come out further than his legs.
Oh god, that's why.
He's so short. It's the shortest horse I've ever seen.
Alright, two minutes and 18.
This is like a wiener dog horse.
We're making a dachshund.
Alright, we can change animals. We can change animals.
It's okay.
It's got to stick to the guns, man. It's got to be a horse.
What's the deciding factor that makes it not a dog and not a horse?
A long face. Actually, a dachshund has a long face, too.
That's not going to work, then.
Alright, no more messing around.
No more messing around. We've got to get the body done.
Alright, am I allowed to make a daytime again?
Yes, alright.
Dude, this is not even...
Why is this leg so skinny?
Dude, he's like tiny Tim.
What the hell?
Alright, I'll work on the belly.
I'll work on the head. I'll work on the head.
I was also going to work on the belly.
Too late. I'm already doing it.
How am I going to make this? I have no idea what I'm doing, man.
I have absolutely no idea.
Alright, work on his back. He's got to have an arched back.
He's got to be round. He can't be flat.
Dude, if this thing was alive, it would come alive and just be like, please kill me.
Please, please kill me.
This is like an anteater.
Alright, almost four minutes.
We've got to put like a sack on it.
Oh my god.
I'm laughing too much. I can't even do this.
I'm really out of health on this sack.
Oh my god, I'm stuck.
It looks like a really derpy camel.
It's like a really flat camel.
This is like a truck disguised as a camel.
This is like a Trojan horse camel.
My whole body hurts right now.
It really is a camel.
Oh my god. How do you make a horse's face?
I don't know how.
It's Alex. You're like the smart one. Get over here.
I don't know how to make a horse's face.
Alright, finish the belly. Make the belly round.
Four minutes and 40 seconds.
Alright, how do you make a horse's face?
Is this the face?
This is not a horse.
This is like a...
I don't know what this is.
It's like Snoopy.
He's got no neck, dude.
Just fix it.
Five minutes.
Alright, we have to close this up right now.
That's what I'm doing.
We've got to put a door on this thing.
It's basically like a house.
I can't even do it.
What are you doing?
I'm destroying it.
There was no neck there, dude.
There's no time for destroying.
Watch. Watch me.
I've got time.
I'll work on the tail. He's going to have a big gray tail.
We've got to have some more colors in here.
Give him some spots. He's just one big round dude.
Man, that was the hardest I've laughed all week, definitely.
This looks like there's a spoon up his ass.
It looks like one of those toy things and you turn it and something happens.
And it winds up.
This looks painful. I'm sorry, Mr. Horse.
Why is it so straight?
I don't know. I don't know how to make things bushy. They can't.
He's got like a platypus's tail.
I'm making some ears. I don't know what I'm doing exactly.
I'll clean up the bottom of the belly.
He's got horns. I'm turning him into a steer.
Horses have ears.
Look, he's a bull now.
Oh my God.
Actually, this is not a bad bull.
Change of plans. Our horse is now a platypus bull.
Go down here. I've got to get down here and change this.
I've got to trim the fat off his legs.
It's a little too weird over here.
Oh God. This is bad.
How much time do we have?
We have less than one minute.
What?
Put eyes on it now.
What are you doing? What is this?
He's saddled.
Oh, okay.
He's got a broken neck.
He looks like a turkey.
Fix his turkey neck.
Nice. Good eyes.
Wow. That's a cow.
This guy is perfectly square.
We only have 15 seconds.
I've got to make his mouth open like a carrot.
We only have 10 seconds.
I've got to put the apple in his mouth.
Three, two, one.
That's it.
Is that still a horse?
He turned it into a bull?
I don't know.
I don't know what that is.
He looks all right to me.
Somebody broke his leg right here.
Somebody took a baseball bat and just...
Somebody just carved his whole front muscle up.
He's got a big walk back here.
What is this mouth?
What's the deal with this huge mouth in the front?
He's chewing.
There's the apple.
We're going to name him something, of course, as tradition.
His mouth and his face looks like the grandpa thumbnail face.
I say we just call him Brokeback because that's what he looks like to me.
Brokeback.
In the comments section, give him a name if you want.
Of course, give us a rating 1 out of 10 because that's the way we roll.
I guess that's going to wrap it up, guys.
This is his...
We're going to give this guy a whole farm of animals.
Hang on.
Are we allowed to make modifications here to this guy?
No modifications allowed.
Can we delete the modifications?
He needs a cowboy hat to go with...
That's his chef's hat.
What is with this guy's eyes, man?
Seriously, that's five different types of drugs in his bloodstream.
When you go to get ice cream from the guy who's driving around the street,
you get a Bugs Bunny character and he has those oogly-googly yellow eye gumdrop things on the ice cream.
You are absolutely correct.
Wow, that's awesome.
That's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Thanks so much for watching.
Of course, take care, everybody.