Okay, let's play, uh, I have a controller, period.
20 minutes till dawn. If you've never played this before, if you like vampire survivors, this game is...
No, no, no controller, no controller, that's right.
This game is kind of like vampire survivors. It's very fun.
Are any mods around to change the game to, um, 20 minutes till dawn?
Are you gonna play VR?
No, not for a while.
Capture it or what?
There you go.
Okay, so 20 minutes till dawn is a game where you play as a, uh,
you're in the middle and you walk around and you shoot stuff.
It's really good, it's really fun.
We'll give this, like, half an hour.
Can you show the game list again?
Um, I don't have a way to do that.
All right, so I want to play with, uh, what's a good thing to play with?
I unlocked a few things.
What should I do?
Do 20 minutes.
Maybe 20, 25, 30, maybe 40, maybe an hour.
All right, can reroll upgrades?
Uh, it starts with very high HP.
Play it for 20 minutes.
We'll see.
All right, your bullets have...
All right, um...
What should I do for a weapon?
Bat gun?
Shoot bats that chase down enemies.
Bats are both bullets and summons.
Sure, I'll try it.
With, uh, you.
What about my runes?
Sounds good to me.
All right, let's play.
Standard mode.
Oh, should I activate this?
Small enemies spawn more often and small enemies have more HP.
I feel like that's kind of going to be hard.
I'm going for it.
Fuck it.
It's kind of loud.
Let me help you there.
This game is sick, by the way.
Is there a dodge roll?
I forgot.
No, there isn't.
No, no, no, there's not.
All right, the bat is pretty fun.
20 minutes of this?
Maybe?
I don't know.
Hey, guys, this is Omega Gaming Weekend.
I did not title this stream the next few days.
That's not what the title says.
That's not what it says on the title.
Definitely projectiles.
100% projectiles.
This is going to be three, right?
Oh, are you going to bet on this one?
Actually, don't bet on this one.
All right, these are summons.
Additional bullet.
After shooting your last ammo, smite nearby enemies.
That's pretty good.
Bullet damage.
That's really good.
Ghost friend is really good.
Summoning bullets.
I think I'm going to do this.
Stop reloading.
I have auto reload.
I have auto reload turned on.
Reload can be canceled in the middle of a reload.
So I'm going to keep it on.
That's actually really helpful.
This is good so far.
So far, so good.
Maybe?
No.
Plus one projectile.
Spread.
Don't really care.
Doubles base projectile.
Whoa, yeah.
I really hope that whoever is betting right now,
you're betting on the right thing.
Because it's not possible to lose now.
It's not possible for me to lose.
I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
All right, I need something big here.
Burn for three seconds.
Reload rate.
Huge.
Shield is huge.
Bullets can do curse.
That's pretty good.
It's probably burn.
But it also might be reload rate.
Could be.
I'll do burn.
It's bouncing around a lot.
Magic lens.
Nah.
That one's not bad.
Every second shot, lightning strikes.
When shooting your last ammo,
10 bullets go in a circle.
Pretty big.
Freeze is big.
What do you think?
Freeze or lightning?
What do you guys think?
Burn, resident sleeper, curse, thumbs up.
Lightning, you think so?
All right, I gotta stop being an idiot.
All right, stop being an idiot.
Speed.
Pickup range is big.
I need movement speed.
It's impossible to lose.
Well, it's impossible to lose unless I walk into stuff.
What just happened?
Oh, I selected it.
All right, yeah, I want movement speed.
So important.
Do I get the health now or that?
Probably that.
Yeah.
Yikes.
Did I get hit?
No, I didn't.
I almost did though.
All right, summon an egg that will hatch
to a dragon in three minutes.
Reload rate, 20%.
Summon a ghost friend that shoots piercing bullets.
Bullet speed plus 30%.
Max HP.
I need damage.
I'm falling off.
I need damage so bad.
Summon a magic dagger that seeks out nearby enemies.
That's not bad.
Probably this though.
Every fifth shot, launch a fireball or super speed.
Every fifth shot, launch a fireball.
I think that's the one.
I need damage.
Give me something good.
Increase fire rate and reload rate by plus 10%
permanently every time you get hit.
That's good.
I don't want to get hit, but I have to.
I will.
Yeah, I'll be honest.
It's kind of hard to tell if the bats are enemies sometimes.
Does that count?
No, it's probably cursed, right?
Got to take the L.
Yeah, it's cursed.
We got all kinds of variety on a mega gaming weekend.
This is a nice break.
All right.
This is where I could lose everything right here.
It's definitely this one.
Power shot instead.
Bullet damage plus, yeah, fine.
I'll do it.
You're right.
You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
Stupid, stupid.
It's over, it's over, it's over.
Oh my God.
This thing takes so much damage.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to everybody that voted for me.
I could pull it back though.
I could pull it back.
I can pull it back.
I can.
You don't understand right angles.
One of the mods is saying, hey, is Disney Infinity 3.0
actually on the list?
Yeah, that's a good question.
It is on the list and it's next.
Wait, these count as summons.
These count as summons, right?
I'm doing it.
Who cares?
That'll kill me, won't it?
That reload rate debuff is so bad.
This is probably the safe one.
I think I may have just saved the whole run.
I think I saved the entire run.
Run actually may be saved right now if I get giant.
Run is safe.
I think that's fine.
Turn auto aim on.
Why would I turn auto aim on?
Lightning damage increased by 12.
Increased lightning area of effect.
It's probably that.
Or it's the fast one.
I'm going to go fast.
Am I actually even moving faster?
I don't feel like I'm moving faster.
Am I crazy?
That one.
I'm actually kicking my feet right now.
I thought I moved out of the way.
I'm dead.
Huh?
One more try.
I swear to God.
One more try and that's it.
One more try.
I don't like that weapon.
Last try.
One more try.
That's it.
That weapon, I don't like that weapon.
I'm going to do grenade launcher.
What?
I want to try that.
That sounds cool.
With the grenade launcher?
Grenade launcher is wicked good.
All right.
Bullet damage in...
Okay, probably bullet damage.
And vision range and pickup range versus...
How can I put anything in?
Holy shit.
That's good.
How much is this?
Thirty one fifty.
Twelve thousand.
All right.
Let's try this.
I got Abby and grenade launcher.
I'm playing on the hard mode.
So don't tell me I'm not playing on hard mode.
That seems kind of good.
It's impossible to lose this.
Yeah, this is not possible to lose this, by the way.
So I would vote for me if I were you.
I thought I got hit.
Okay, so what do I want here?
Bullet damage.
Definitely that.
And knockback.
Bullet speed is pretty good.
Yeah, I want huge explosions.
I don't care about the dragon.
Do the dragon?
Why?
I want big explosive bomb stuff.
Nobody believes in me.
Get the dragon egg.
In three minutes a dragon hatch is fine.
That'll be worth it.
They said better be worth it.
Do I still got it?
Enjoy your stars set on...
Yes, I do.
I think it's this.
I don't have any idea what he says.
What does the Archmage say in Warcraft 3?
I don't know what he says.
In fury for stars set on is all I know.
What does he actually...
I have no idea.
I've never known.
In fury for stars set on...
What does he actually say?
Any you know?
I don't know, dude.
Don't ask.
This is from Warcraft 3.
It's Latin.
He says, help me, I'm in a Blizzard game.
Oh, yeah.
Help me, I'm in a Blizzard game set on.
What does he say?
Do I have to look this up?
There's a fucking hundred million people here.
Do I actually have to look up his voice lines?
Archmage voice lines Warcraft 3.
What does he say?
How does nobody know this?
Perfect.
Right, right, right.
Well, perfect.
Whatever.
To battle.
Okay.
For glory.
There it is.
All right.
The music's too loud.
Hold on.
This is important.
How do I turn the music down?
Okay, here you go.
This is it right here.
That's what he says.
What does he say?
Whatever.
Who cares?
All right, let's go.
What am I doing?
I don't think I want that.
Maybe I do.
Trained dragon.
He's speaking Swedish?
Is that Swedish?
It's nuts.
Okay.
Your dragon gains 10% attack speed every 60 seconds.
All right.
So let's do that.
Even in the egg.
I can't believe nobody knew that.
How come all of you...
How come none of you guys are also like 35 plus year old dorks like me?
I wonder if it's a rapid fire rate.
Your dragon gains 8 damage every 60 seconds.
While in the egg as well.
Okay, well, we're doing all dragon then.
All right.
Dragon again.
Your bullets deal additional damage equal to 10% of your dragon's damage.
Well, I mean, we're just doing it.
Stop.
Stop!
Yeah, the auto reload is fucking me up.
Turn it off.
It's cutting me off.
How do you reload?
All right.
Come on, man.
Is it R?
That's...
Okay.
This is huge.
Yeah.
Huge bullets.
Huge damage.
Yes.
All right.
Come on, man.
I gotta collect.
Oh my goodness.
That's right click.
That's what happens.
What do we got?
Double how fast Abby fires during her special.
Sure.
Should I take the health or bullet damage and piercing?
I don't know.
Why do you not have any pupils?
Can you see?
I do.
It's just the way the lighting is.
Not a room.
Come on.
Maybe it is ghost friend.
Or should we just do all damage?
Always.
They pierce killed enemies.
Maybe I'll be safe.
Yeah, I'll be safe.
I have plenty of damage right now.
I have to wrap around and go in the middle there.
All right.
Dragons here.
Finally.
What's the dragon doing for damage?
Forty...
That's actually really good.
Bullet speed.
That's huge because...
Yeah.
I think it's that.
It's either that or it's...
I don't know.
Haste.
I don't have any move speed.
It has to be this.
Yeah.
There's nothing else it would be.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bad idea.
Very bad idea.
These hurt me.
That was a terrible idea.
Whose idea was that?
It runs over.
I didn't know that it was...
I didn't know that that was going to do that.
I thought it was going to explode into just little pellets,
not into other bombs that...
This is the last try.
And then we're going to play Disney Infinity 3.0.
I actually like this weapon, but now that I...
All right.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'm going both headphones for this, by the way.
We'll do the same thing.
Dragon egg.
It's really early.
Dragon.
Eight more damage every 60 seconds.
It's super early.
Dragon again.
Super early.
That's really dangerous with this character.
Oh my goodness.
I don't...
That move is not something I should be doing ever.
Unless it's an absolutely desperate scenario.
10% attack speed.
Yes.
When this dragon hatches, it's going to be better.
I need blast radius or something, right?
Collect.
Double.
Yeah.
Wrap around.
I need that shit.
All right.
I'm a little more confident than I just was.
I am way more confident now.
Surprises of face cam?
I started doing face cam every case.
So I played Elden Ring for a month straight with a face cam on,
and then I just never turned it off.
After not doing face cam for like almost 10 years.
Very rarely if I did a horror game or something.
Yeah.
Big shot.
That's much better.
All right.
There we go.
Let's go.
Give us the chest.
Move speed and reload rate by 35% for two seconds after reloading.
Pretty good.
Wait.
That's not good.
Because that is going to come out of nowhere,
and I'm going to run into something.
It is good.
But I'm used to moving at a certain, you know, knots per second, whatever.
And if I just speed up randomly after killing,
I'm going to hit something.
For two seconds?
OK.
After reloading, I'm going to be going like this.
I'm going to reload, and then I'm going to stop.
I don't want to adapt.
I already know how the character moves.
This fell on the ground, and I'm going to do this.
Now it's new.
Eww.
This boomer is incapable of adapting.
If I kill all the people that are telling me to take this, then fine.
When I die, you go, wow, I can't believe I trusted him.
Then you'll see.
No, it's not this.
No, it is.
It is.
No, it's this.
It's Holy Shield for sure.
Just eat a free damage.
Yeah.
It's that.
Let's go.
I have so much damage.
It's just a question of when I'm going to end up killing myself,
like accidentally with the explosion.
You can do that.
Dragon is sick, by the way.
All right.
Come on.
Reload rate, 20%.
That's very good.
We want that.
Look at how fast I am.
Boss is incoming here in a minute.
10%.
Ooh, that's good too.
I think it's this, the ammo and the reload rate.
All right, here we go.
Don't blow it.
Yeah.
OK.
Something in my teeth.
Bullet bounce.
Oh, boy.
Is this bad?
I have the dragon.
The dragon is doing 40 damage.
So do I want the dragon to be doing what?
Like 60 to 70 damage?
And me be able to shoot and supplement the dragon?
This is going to bounce off people and come back, explode, and kill me.
We're not doing that.
This is awful.
These are all bad.
Triple your base max ammo, but 50% less damage.
I'm not taking it.
It's not happening.
Wait, I didn't take it.
No, I'm not taking it.
It's a bad idea.
Curse?
Health was going to be the second thing I was going to do.
I want this box to go away, please.
I...
Whatever.
See, I knew that was going to happen.
I was going to get too close to the explosion.
You need to start pretending.
Start pretending what?
Pretend what?
Fresh clip first one.
That's actually a really...
Yeah, that's a good choice.
You're right.
What the fuck?
Oh, it was...
Whatever.
OK, come on.
Don't lose it now.
They're so fast.
As much as you're...
This is going to do 100 something damage.
This is going to be huge.
Oh, I think I want to do pick up range at this point.
Curse is good, but I need to level.
I have to.
I have to level up.
I need to be able to pick stuff up.
Am I invincible during that?
I feel like I just was.
Can somebody confirm?
Fuck, I'm losing it.
It's the piercing.
The piercing is fucking me up.
The piercing is fucking me up because I'm shooting...
I'm expecting it to blow up on somebody,
but it goes through them and blows up after them.
That was a mistake.
Sorry, all the believers.
This might be a problem.
See what I mean?
I just...
It's nothing I can do about it.
It's going through people and I can't walk forward
because if I walk forward and I shoot somebody,
I'm going to get hit by the explosion.
I fucked it up.
It's all right.
All right.
How much does this cost?
This game's fun.
All right, goodbye.
All right, we're moving on.
Moving on, moving on.
All right, all right, all right, right.
Moving on, moving on, moving on.
That was so much fun.
Okay, so...
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to take a nice cold shower.
I'm not cold, you know, like lukewarm.
It's going to be great.
I did, in that big break,
I did a witch hazel wipe,
freshening me up a bit.
All good.
Skincare stream.
Peep the elbow.
It's fine.
It's just because sitting here
with my elbows on it for a while.
5 a.m. Eastern.
We're getting close.
Okay, let me...
All right, I hope this is not too intense.
We'll find out.
Because of the camera saturation
that it looks like that, probably.
Let me see.
Yeah, it's just, there's a lot of effects
on this right now because we put them on
to try to make the camera look better.
Twitch tracker says the longest stream
was 13 hours and five minutes.
Can somebody go confirm to make sure
that that's the case?
Let me just bow.
I get to 13 hours and five minutes
and then I'm like, hooray, let's turn it off.
And it was actually like 13 hours
and like 10 minutes.
14 hours just to be safe.
Well, I will go combine the fellowship
in two towers.
Yeah, I'm good for it.
I'm okay.
I still got this.
I drank this whole thing.
So I'm going to do high HP and the bow.
Maybe not.
What's the one I haven't played with?
Dual SMGs.
Upgrades apply separately to each gun.
That's interesting.
These good.
I feel like I could have gotten this
to work really well.
Let me try the bow.
Let me see if I can make this work.
When I reload, they come back.
So you want insane reload speed then.
You want reload speed, ammo, and piercing.
I walked into the tree.
Forgot that the tree was evil.
Oh my God, you're gambling on this?
I don't know if that's a good idea.
These all aren't that great for this.
Vision range?
I don't know, maybe.
I feel like that's safe.
Fall in, I believe.
Well, I appreciate it.
Yeah, I need way more reload than that.
Reload speed.
Fire rate, that would be good.
It's the fire rate.
I thought I got out of that.
Okay, bullet damage and knockback
or more projectiles.
Probably that because of the pullback.
Why do all these people have ones and twos on them?
One, two.
What's with the one and the two?
He doesn't know.
I don't know.
Oh, it's the prediction choices.
Okay.
So you're going to be kind of in little groups
of one, two, three, or four, huh?
Very interesting.
Ghost friend?
Just one or two?
Predicted yet?
Oh, I thought it was...
Oh, no, it's not a pull.
Wait, can't you do more than...
Oh, no, I thought it...
Okay, I thought it was a pull for a second.
That's been 13 hours.
I'm good.
Don't worry about me, I'm fine.
I'm fine, I'll be okay.
I really thought that there was four options.
Great, did he predict yes or no?
How about yes two and no two?
There's no way he's going to beat this
with the least amount of brain cells.
You know what's crazy?
I think that that would make it easier
because I'm not sitting here going like,
oh my God, I have to watch out.
Wake up with those bad guys.
How much health do I have?
No, I'm just kind of like just sitting here.
So I don't know, you may have picked wrong defense.
Even the boss comes out.
That's better.
Yeah, it's that fire rate and ammo.
I would love more projectiles.
Bullet bounce, bullet speed.
That's okay.
Dark Arts is pretty good.
Probably the fire rate.
10% is bad though.
I'll do Dark Arts.
You know what's insane?
I beat the ultra kill act two campaign seven hours ago.
I forgot I did that.
It's absolutely been an omega gaming weekend.
Day.
Friday.
Fish game.
Oh yeah, that game was fun.
I genuinely enjoyed that game.
Oh boy.
Fire rate and really, I hate this one.
But I mean, why not take it?
It's kind of good.
Yeah, well, I'll take the,
remember when I ate the French bread pizza?
It was great.
In case you forgot.
Oh my God, are you serious?
Oh, guys, there's still a piece left.
I still have a half a piece left.
Oh my, so good.
I'm hitting E instead of W.
Collect.
These all kind of suck.
Well, for what I'm doing.
This character is really cool though.
I like the mechanic.
This is the moment of truth here.
Oh, he's still alive.
Holy shit.
Shield.
All right.
Movement speed.
Big.
Bullet damage, bullet size and piercing.
It's that.
Fire rate, but still the damage is crazy.
I was here.
Wait, did I do it?
Is this officially the longest stream I've ever done?
All right.
Cool.
13 hours and five minutes.
And I didn't drop a single frame unless I downloaded the game.
You know what's really funny?
Okay, so when was that Lord of the Rings stream?
2017?
2018?
2019?
Four years ago.
I think I'm on record saying after.
When I took that big break when I was gone for like three months,
it was on January 11, 2020.
Okay, so this hasn't been that long,
but I think when I came back from the long break,
like four months,
I think I said I will never ever do a stream
that's longer than 12 hours ever again.
I guess not.
So what now?
For every second I'm setting the tone for,
it's got to be a number that I want, right?
It's got to be a number that I like.
I don't like 13, though.
13?
13 is an odd number.
It's not that much longer.
Okay, how about 13?
Wait, dude, what if I do?
Oh, watch this shit.
Everyone's going to hate me for this.
1337 is so dumb.
Absolute worst number.
It's funny because I could do that and that would be it forever.
133737.
But 133700, it's so bad.
But I think actually I might be mad that I did that.
Months or years later, I might be like, really?
That's what I decided to do.
123456 would have been so perfect,
but it's too bad 12 hours was 12 hours and 56 minutes,
but 12 hours and 45 minutes, whatever.
I would have loved 123456.
Let's go.
Oh, that's cool.
I really didn't think I was ever going to do this ever again.
And like I said, I know that a 13 hour stream is really not.
Wow. Oh my God.
I'm one of the only streamers ever to do a 13.
I know people do this regularly all the time.
Oh, man.
I'm not even sure I would be able to do more than 14, 13 or 14 hours.
Back when I was like 20.
I don't know.
I don't know how people do it.
Because you know what it is?
It's not just the fact that you're, whatever, 13 hours.
There are a lot of people that work 13 hour days,
12 hour days, 10 hour shifts.
Right.
It's a lot.
I think the major difference with like a stream is
I've been kind of sitting in the same spot.
I've gone to the bathroom once or twice
and I've eaten pizza at the desk for like 14 hours.
So it's like it's like the low amount of movement
is I think like the killer and like the visual stimulation.
But yeah, let me be very, very, very clear.
The reason why I don't do 10 plus hour streams
is because I don't want to, right?
Get up once in a while and do stretches.
Yeah, you do a lot of content for 14 hours.
Um, I mean, it's for me, it's not.
Maybe I don't know.
I'm trying to think of a way that I could word it.
I think I expel a lot of energy on the stream.
A lot.
It's the end.
I think it's just the kind of the way that I am.
But yeah, it's not, uh, I'm not trying to say that like,
oh my gosh, guys, streaming is so hard.
No, no, that's not what I'm saying.
You know, would you ever do a 24 hour?
No, not in a million years.
Not in a hundred million years.
Oh my God.
Don't, I'm dead.
I looked at that at the end.
What about a thousand million years?
Yeah, it's just like my body and brain just can't
do that for more than like 10 to 12 hours usually.
After hour number five or six is when I'm kind of like,
yeah, I'm done.
But look, more power to you.
If you can really do that for more than 12, 13, 14 hours all the time.
Although I would say that, um, it's probably not that healthy to do this that often.
Um, another, one of the reasons why I don't really do this that often is because I,
I have a lot of health problems and I could really probably fuck myself up if I did too much.
13, 13 is coming up.
That's kind of interesting.
13, 13, 13.
Nah, no, no, no.
You can burn out.
Yeah, I don't want to burn out either.
That's another thing too.
I don't, I really don't want to burn out.
Kind of interesting.
I think you, you can, when you go through all your oil and there's not much left,
it's, um, it's really long-term.
It's really not great for you.
It's really not a good thing.
Is he sleepy?
I'm kind of sleepy.
13, 13, 13, 13.
No, no, let's wind down.
It ends when it ends.
This game is really fun though, too.
20 minutes till dawn.
Um, let me see here.
Let me see.
How was I at the end of that two towers, Vaude?
Wait, how come Lord of the Rings of Two Towers is nine hours and 40 minutes?
How come this is shorter?
It was two Vaudes.
Oh, it's split up by the game.
Okay.
It's a 12-hour limit.
Oh, right.
Okay.
Yeah, so that's going to be the end of the stream.
I'll see you guys later.
I don't, uh, Omega Weekend sort of turned into, uh,
beat my old longest stream ever record.
I guess, I guess they are one and the same,
but I do still have a dozen and a half more games to play.
So these don't have to go away.
Keep an eye on the sus.
Uh, if it's Sunday or Monday, maybe it'll be Sunday.
It's definitely not going to be tomorrow.
Or today.
What is it?
Like 6 a.m. for a lot of you guys.
10 a.m.
Saturday.
I'll play Splatoon 3 and I'll play, I won't do a Switch night.
Breath of the Wild, Splatoon 3, some other things that are on Switch.
Or maybe I'll just play Breath of the Wild.
It's time to play it, right?
Should I just do it?
I don't know.
Is it time to just do it at some point in the next week?
Next few days?
Yes.
Okay.
Please stream.
What did you say?
Please stream on the weekends for us working Andes.
I like streaming on the weekends.
Breath of the Wild is a perfect game for you.
Put sus for Saturday or Sunday?
I would put sus for Sunday.
Sunday slash Monday.
Gears of War is on Switch?
Omega Weekend.
So Monday.
I don't know.
Who knows?
I might just show up.
Just go.
Can I trade you Omega Weekend for Omega Record Stream Breaker?
We'll see.
I don't know.
It's very possible that tomorrow or Sunday, I'm just like, whatever, let's go.
No.
Oath Breaker.
That's not what we agreed to, Elbertson.
We didn't agree to this.
I'll be back in here tomorrow afternoon to increase or offline chat.
We'll figure it out.
What about a Twitch moment badge for longest stream?
Wait, can I do that?
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is that, can I do that?
How do I do that?
Can I actually do that right now?
Yeah.
Wait, how?
Does anybody know?
Do slash moment.
Slash moment.
Clip moments on stream and recognize viewers that were there with a commemorative badge.
Oh, okay.
So hold on.
Like right now?
What if I do this?
So I go like this?
If you're seeing this clip right now, you were one of the few people that were here
for my longest stream ever.
13 hours, 18 minutes, and 37 seconds.
Thanks for hanging out.
And now, do I do it now?
13 hours and 20 minutes.
Moment time.
Reward viewers for being part of this moment.
Viewers of this moment will receive a clip added to their moments page.
You have five moments for this month.
Longest stream ever.
13 hours, 18 minutes, 37 seconds.
Oh, it worked.
Thanks for hanging out.
Do I do it now?
No, no, no, no, hold on.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Hold on.
I know, I probably wouldn't want to go to bed.
That was not a good one.
Slash moment.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
You were here for the longest stream I've ever done on this channel.
13 hours, 19 minutes, and 41 seconds.
Ain't ever going to happen again.
What, what, yeah.
Let's start over.
Hey, you, I feel like I'm making a YouTube video again.
I feel like I'm making a fucking YouTube video again.
You know how many times I would sit here and do this shit?
I would sit here over and over and over and over again doing this.
Hey, you.
I used to sit, I can't do it.
Okay, I was just going to close my eyes.
No, I'm just, okay, I'm going to look over here.
I'm not going to look at you.
Hey, you are one of the few people that stuck around
and checked out the longest stream that I've ever done.
13 hours, 21 minutes, and seven seconds.
You did.
You were here for it.
You were here.
Thanks a lot.
And now, I think it's time I got a little bit of rest.
How was that?
You are a few people that stuck around and checked out the longest stream that I've ever.
No, no, we're not doing that one.
We're doing a different one.
Hey, just want to say thanks.
You were here for the longest stream that I've ever done.
13 hours, 21 minutes, and 38 seconds.
You were here.
If you have this moment, if you got this clip,
congratulations, you own it now.
Now, it's time to get some rest.
All right, I did it.
That should be good, right?
I look so funny.
God, dude, who cares?
This is the, who cares?
Go watch that.
I screw it up so bad, but who cares?
Did you get, did it work?
Did you claim it?
I claimed it.
All right, cool.
I feel bad for the people that left.
There's like a couple thousand people left
because they like all the streams over
and they're not going to get the clip.
That's, I feel kind of bad for that.
Wait, what is it?
Moments badge.
Why is the moments badge the body of Christ?
Okay, you got a moment badge.
All right, am I, did I officially do it?
I'm so afraid to hit end stream and it turns out,
oh dude, it was actually 13 minutes in like 34 minutes
or 13 hours and 34 minutes or something.
Should I do another moment?
Like the 200 people that just left?
You fucked up.
Hey, just want to say you are one of the only people
to get this clip of my longest stream.
13 hours, 24 minutes and 25 seconds.
That's right, this is the longest one I've ever done.
Thanks for watching.
It's time for me to get some rest.
Did it work?
A clip of the moment has failed to capture.
What are you talking about?
Hey, I got banned?
No, I didn't.
I just want to say you are one of the lucky people.
Why am I banned?
You're one of the lucky people that got this moment,
my longest stream ever at 13 hours, 25 minutes and 24 seconds.
Nobody else has this but you, this few people.
It's the longest stream I've ever done.
Congratulations, you were here.
You were here.
Time to get some rest.
Okay, okay, create moment.
A clip, it failed.
Can I only do this like once every 10 minutes?
I have four more moments to capture this month.
I think I'm just going to do this every 10 minutes.
And like, if you want to claim this moment,
you better stay to the end.
Do all five of them tonight.
Can I look this up?
When do these moments reset?
Do all five tonight.
It's in beta?
At the start of the, yeah, I still have four I can do this month.
I wonder how long the cooldown is.
Hey, just want to say, you know what time it is?
It's the longest stream ever.
13 hours, 27 minutes and six seconds.
I think that deserves a quick bite of pizza.
Thanks for joining me.
Thanks for sticking around for this long.
I've never done it this, I've never gone this long before.
And you were here for it.
Thanks for sticking around.
We're here, we're hanging out.
I'm doing all five of these tonight.
So it looks like it's about five minutes.
The last one, I should just be standing back there.
I'm just going like, you powered through.
You made it all the way to the end.
You must be commended for it with this fifth moment.
And then I spin around, bend over forward
and fart wicked fucking loud into the microphone.
Make the camera wider.
Just get them progressively more fucking weird, hold on.
If I was like, hey, Jess wanted to say,
I am so happy that you made it to tonight's stream.
Hold on a second.
The camera quality is going to get progressively worse.
So the actual one that you get is going to be the worst one.
Where did I go?
I think I actually broke the webcam.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no, it's actually fucked up.
Hold on.
Oh, shit.
Wait, hold on, I might be able to fix it.
Yeah, it's gone.
Hold on, did I get it back?
Oh, I think I got it.
Hold on a second, we're good.
Let's see, am I good?
Maybe.
You can't see though.
All right, the cooldown is up.
I got to fucking do it.
I don't know, what is that?
Oh, it's my fucking neck.
Okay, I got it.
That looks fine, right?
Okay, you ready?
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
13 hours and 33 minutes, you made it.
You made it to the longest stream that I've ever done.
You got it all the way through.
You were here for this.
You were here.
Special thank you to everybody that decided to show up and stick around.
I got a crunch for you.
Now that one sucked.
Again, just want to say a huge special thanks to those of you that stuck around
for the longest stream that I have ever done.
We're talking, wow, wowie.
13 hours and 34 minutes with 18 seconds also, which is unbelievable.
Thank you for sticking around.
This is the longest stream.
I'm never going to do this again.
The longest stream I've ever done.
Thank you.
Did it work?
Let's go even lower.
Let's make it worse.
I hate that I have to do this every time though.
Oh my goodness, really?
This looks so bad.
I can't even see it anymore.
I keep losing it.
There it is, okay.
Every time I go down in quality, it resets the whole camera and resizes everything.
This is 320 by, I don't know, 320 by like 180 or something.
It's all blown up and awful.
Okay, I don't know what the hell that was.
What am I looking at here?
Hey man, I can't believe you made it.
13 hours, 36 minutes and 52 seconds.
God, man, I can't believe.
You were here.
You were longest stream I've ever done.
Thanks for sticking around.
I appreciate it, man.
See you later.
Did I even give a time?
52 seconds stream.
You can't hear that.
Longest stream I've ever done in 52 seconds.
God, man, I can't believe.
You were here.
You were longest stream I've.
That's the beginning of the clip.
Ever done.
52 seconds.
God, I gotta redo it, right?
Should I redo it or is that funny?
What do you think?
Oh, 52 seconds.
Man, I can't believe we made it.
Oh, it didn't work.
Oh, hey.
Oh, I can't believe you're still here.
Wow, 13 hours, 38 minutes and 44 seconds.
Wow, that's the longest stream I've ever done.
And you were here for it.
Honestly, you know what?
I think that deserves a little bit of a bite of pizza.
Is the game too loud?
Oh, shit.
Oh, hey.
Oh, I can't believe you're still here.
No, I'll do it again.
Music's too loud.
The music's way too loud.
Okay, I'm good.
It wouldn't work anyways.
Take three.
Oh, hey.
Oh, you're still here.
Wow, 13 hours, 39 minutes.
Longest stream I've ever done.
And you were here for it.
I'll never do anything longer than this.
So you're here for it.
Good work.
Oh, what's that?
Oh, is that some Captain Grunch?
Delicious.
What a reward for 13 hours and 40 minutes.
13 hours, 39 minutes, longest stream I've ever done.
Oh, fuck you.
It didn't get it.
Where even is this?
Up there.
Where is this?
I don't know where it is.
You know what?
You made it to 13 hours, 41 minutes and 8 seconds.
You did.
You were here for this.
Thank you so much for sticking around.
Longest stream that I have ever done.
And you're here for it.
Yeah.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick.
That's a good one.
I don't understand, I don't know where it is.
I don't, you know what, you made it to 13 hours,
41 minutes and a-
Alright, I'm done doing this.
You should lower your mic quality.
Dude, I'm not fucked with the mic.
I took me 10 years to get to this point.
I'm doing one more, and I'm just gonna say thanks.
That's 13 hours and 42 minutes, I'm done.
Do I keep, like, the cringe guy routine going?
Oh my god, I don't know how I'm gonna be able to do this.
It's so ugly.
What is that?
Okay, that's here.
Hold on, let me find it here.
Okay, so I need to move it this way.
Don't ever call the sus guy three.
13 hours and 44 minutes,
you made it to the longest stream I've ever done.
Don't ever call the sus guy three.
13 hours and 44 minutes,
you made it to the longest stream I've ever done.
I was gonna say final stream.
You made it to the final stream.
Okay, please tell me this is gonna actually go through.
No, it didn't go through.
It didn't go through.
Somebody clip it.
Oh, shit.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Don't ever call the sus guy at three a.m.
You made it 13 hours 46 minutes and 11 seconds.
You made it to the longest stream I've ever done.
See you on the next one.
I'm gonna cut it off.
You made it.
13 hours.
Fuck, God damn it.
All right, I'm doing this one more time and that's it.
Then I'm done.
Don't ever call the sus guy at three a.m.
You made it to the longest stream I've ever done.
13 hours 47 minutes and seven seconds.
And your prize is this stupid clip
that you're gonna forget about in two weeks.
What the fuck?
Why does he keep cutting it off?
You made it to the longest stream.
I'm gonna do it quick.
This is annoying.
It keeps cutting the beginning off.
Don't ever call the sus guy at three a.m.
You made it to the longest stream I've ever done
and your reward is the 13 hours 48 minutes zero second.
You win.
All right, did I get it?
Why does he keep cutting it off?
You made it to the longest stream.
I'm gonna do it quick.
What?
This is annoying.
It keeps cutting the beginning off.
Now it's only beginning.
Don't ever call the sus guy at three a.m.
Ah, you made it.
Three a.m.
Put the phone down.
Don't call me.
13 hours 48 minutes and 50 seconds.
Congratulations.
You've made it to the longest stream I've ever done.
Oh, what's that?
A pizza.
Shit, it doesn't work.
This is not connected to the right mic.
13 hours 48 minutes and 50 seconds.
Congratulations.
You've made it to the longest stream I've ever done.
Put the phone down.
Don't call me.
Congratulations.
Oh, what's that?
A pizza.
Shit, it doesn't.
Put the phone down.
Whatever, you, here it is.
There it is.
There it is, your actual clip.
Goodbye.
Don't put the phone down.
Don't call me.
Oh my God.
All right, that's it.
That's the last one.
That's it.
Who cares?
We're almost at 14 hours I'm staying.
It's 10 minutes.
I don't like that 13.
It's gotta be 14.
That's long enough for the ending stuff.
No, thanks for watching.
I really did not,
I did not think I was gonna do a 14 hour stream tonight.
I thought I was gonna do like a six hour stream
and then like a six hour stream tomorrow
and then like a four hour stream on Sunday.
But you know, whatever.
Sometimes you just go for it.
That was fun.
I feel like we did a lot of stuff.
Oh, the mic is wrong, whoops.
Hey, there you are.
That's better, isn't it?
Hi, okay.
Now you can hear me, cool.
You heard that too, whoops.
Claimed.
The other mic is better.
Yeah, honest to God, complete real talk.
There is no way I will do a 14 hour stream
probably ever again.
Don't think so.
Seaman was 11 hours.
Lord of the Rings PlayStation 2 games with 13.
This was not a single game.
So there it is at the top of the list.
It is, oh, there it is.
13.4, 13.1, what was 12?
Lifeline was 12 hours.
Simpsons Hit and Run was 11.8, so just about 12.
Darkwood, I played Darkwood for 11 and a half hours?
How?
I don't think I would have been able to do that.
Holy shit.
And then what's this one that's 11.2 hours?
Oh, the thing, right.
Sometimes you're just gaming, that's right.
All right, we got seven minutes.
What do you wanna talk about?
Just roll the credits again.
Imagine not having a tier two badge.
If you claim to all four of those, do you get to,
by the way, that's probably the only time
I'm ever gonna do moments.
So if you got it, that's probably never happening again.
My thoughts on Christmas?
I like it, it's cool.
I'm really surprised by the amount of people
that are still here.
So thanks for staying up or waking up in the morning.
It's gonna be a very long VOD to go through.
Thanks for fucking my sleep up.
Yeah, I mean, I'm about to go eat a little bit more food,
probably take a shower or a bath or something,
and probably not fall asleep till like four,
so maybe five.
I think I'm right there with you.
I think we may have all collectively screwed up
some sleep schedules.
It's 5 a.m. right now.
Thanks for fixing my sleep schedule.
Oh, there we go.
Not all bad.
Oh man, there it is.
You knew it was coming.
You stream it again this evening?
No, I don't think so.
I gotta see how I get up at some point
in the hopefully early afternoon-ish.
I don't wanna get up late though.
I've been on a really good schedule.
I've been getting up normally.
I've been on a very good schedule for a long, long time.
I might just try to just make myself get up in the morning.
I've been so good for the last couple of years,
probably like the last year straight.
What are you gonna do on Sunday or Monday?
Probably switch.
I might jump into Splatoon 3,
because I was told that the campaign
is actually completely different than the multiplayer game.
I'll play the multiplayer too, whatever.
It's gonna be a coin flip between Splatoon 3
and Breath of the Wild on Sunday or Monday.
What time on Sunday or Monday?
Probably around the same time,
probably around two specific.
If you're in the pre-stream, we'll figure it out.
It's either Sunday or tomorrow, whatever,
Sunday, whatever, or Monday-ish.
Are you gonna play both or just one or the other?
I have a feeling if I'm gonna play one of those two,
I'm gonna play that for a majority of that stream.
You don't just play Breath of the Wild
for an hour and 40 minutes.
That's, it's the whole day.
That's the stream, right?
Unless I don't like it, which would be surprising.
It's been long enough.
I know everyone said don't play that
after you play Elden Ring,
but it's been a long time since Elden Ring came out.
I think it'll be okay.
I hope you don't compare it to Elden Ring.
I don't think so.
Hey, in two and a half minutes, it'll be 14 hours.
I kinda wanna see the reactions from people
that just thought this was gonna be a five,
they probably, you know what?
A lot of people that show up to check out the VOD
will probably think I got addicted to one of these games
and had an absolute meltdown,
and it was just mayhem for 14 hours.
You did, you did get addicted.
Oh, that's what happened.
Yeah, but that Oriole game was effectively
one five-hour block of this.
It wasn't the whole thing.
I didn't take 14 hours to beat that Oriole game.
Hey, you know, you can,
that Oriole game is the reason why I did this 14-hour stream,
because I knew for a fact if I were to put it down,
I would not have gone back to it.
I just wouldn't have, even though I loved it.
Other things would have just gotten priority for stream.
That was the only opportunity to play it and beat it,
unless I did it off stream.
All right, let's get the, let's roll the end here.
Thanks, everybody.
I'll see you guys in a day or two.
I am going to go do some stretches and go lie down.
Have a great night, everybody.
Thanks for sticking around.
Hopefully you had a good time.
I definitely have to end it like at 14, zero, zero.
I don't really care about the seconds,
but that's a clean 14, right?
14 hours, but that's in 30 seconds.
Good night, guys.
See you soon.
Keep an eye on the sus tomorrow and Sunday.
I'm sure I'll update you a little bit.
Good night, goodbye.
Take care of yourselves and get some sleep
if you stayed up or good morning.
Hope you have a good rest of your Saturday.
See you later.