Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here. I want to welcome you to the 15,000 subscriber.
I don't even know what you call this. This is not really a video. It's a video, but this is not a skit.
Really, it's more of a real life happening, I guess you could say.
We have Burger Boy who's standing right here. He's pretty much naked, so he can't like come into frame.
But I'll just say something. Say hello.
So what's going to happen in this video is there's going to be a Twinkie eating contest.
And then right after it, there's going to be a pie eating contest.
Both between Burger Boy and Exoskeleton Bug Millennium Boy.
So bear with us here. This is going to be pretty gross.
I won't recommend that you have like small children that are eating.
If you happen to be eating something, I would put it to the side for a second because this is disgusting.
So I hope you guys enjoy this. I'm going to be shout casting the whole thing.
So we'll see how it goes. See you in a second.
So welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the 15,000 subscriber video.
I am Anthony Wimbledon sitting alongside here with Grandpa.
We're going to go over the contestants for a little bit.
Grandpa, first introduce yourself.
I just want to say hello and welcome to the video.
This is going to be a crazy, extraordinary thing.
And these guys are gross, by the way. Can I just say that?
I think a lot of people potentially are thinking the same thing, Grandpa.
Okay, so first up here we have Burger Boy, who is a longtime champion of the eating events.
He holds seven world records for eating cheeseburgers.
And he is on the World Health Organization's list of potential threats.
Ladies and gentlemen, Burger Boy.
But we also have another competitor, Exoskeleton Bug Millennium Boy.
He has been doing a lot of trash talking prior to this competition.
All he wants to do is talk about Burger Boy and how fat he is and how stupid he is.
But we will see at the end of this competition if that's going to be true.
So let's get down to the floor here now. I guess I'm getting into my ear.
We're getting an interview here with Exoskeleton Bug Millennium Boy.
He's got something to say about Burger Boy. Let's get down there.
The Exoskeleton Bug body takes on the Burger Boy.
Here's how I'm going to win. The Burger Boy eats burgers, not Twinkies.
Boom. Shut down. Wasted.
He actually has quite a point there. Burger Boy looks a little stunned.
But what do you say we get this started, Grandpa? We're going to shell-cast this one, baby.
Get the countdown ready even though we're not going to keep any time.
That is really stupid.
But we're going to start this off right now. One to one right now.
Both of them shoving those down their throats. Burger Boy gets the upper hand with two now.
I mean, does this guy really think he's going to win this contest?
This guy's like ten times bigger than you. Are you fucking stupid?
Yep.
You can't win this. You're not going to win.
You are right though, Grandpa. He does have the weight advantage.
And he also has the eating advantage. He has multiple championships.
Millennium Boy has done pretty much absolutely nothing in his entire life.
So I can understand where you're coming from.
Also too, you'd really need to take into consideration the fact that the big fat guy over there...
Burger Boy, you mean? Yep.
Well, Burger Boy, he's a strong bastard. He could probably pick you up and throw you.
So even if he loses this fight tonight, he'll probably kick his ass.
And I'll probably want to watch that too.
And hopefully the cameraman gets that on camera.
That would be pretty interesting to say the least.
But right now, six to five. And Burger Boy seems to be losing his composure right now.
I thought what he just saw was really funny.
Actually, he's going to lose if he doesn't cut the shit.
Look at the inside of his mouth. That's disgusting.
Six to six now. Burger Boy trying to find his composure.
It is now tied up at the sixes.
Burger Boy now finds it. He gets one in there very quickly.
Now seven to six, Burger Boy.
And something that a lot of people don't understand is...
Twinkies are an incredibly dense snack.
150 calories per Twinkie and a ton of sugar.
Yet someone's definitely going to puke. Oh jeez.
If somebody doesn't puke, I will pay everybody six...
I will pay a dollar to charity if somebody doesn't puke.
Well, that's very noble of you, Grandpa. Very noble.
But it looks like we're starting to see a slowdown here.
Nine to seven. Oh, and listen to that.
He's got some choice words for him.
He's only up by one point though, trying to get a little overconfident there.
Yeah, he better watch that because I've done that before.
It came back to bite me right on the balls.
I said to some guy at the bus stop, I said,
Hey, can I see your newspaper for a second?
And he said, No, it's mine.
And then I got arrested for assault.
And I'm not sure where that was going.
But don't be mean to people.
That's the moral of the story.
Okay, that's fantastic.
But now we've got 11 to eight here.
Both of them slowing down immensely.
11 to nine now.
I think this is going to be the end here.
They're both stopping.
I don't see any more activity between either Burger Boy.
Let's go down to the field.
Let's find out what's going on down there.
The brick wall is there.
Heard it from Burger Boy himself hitting the brick wall.
Both of them are now conceding this match.
It is 11 to nine.
Burger Boy is your victor.
I mean, is that really a surprise to anybody that's watching this right now?
Probably not.
But let's go down to Jeremy, AKA me.
And I'll announce the winner.
So, ladies and gentlemen, the winner of the Twinkie eating competition,
Burger Boy.
What?
That's why I said you filmed it.
I didn't know you were going to do that either.
What did you just do?
I thought you were going to wait.
Wait, what?
So this is going to be just a bonus clip.
They decided to do a pie eating contest as well.
And as you can see here, they are both just disgusting human beings eating like a pig out of a trough.
And Burger Boy starts off very, very well.
But Exoskeleton Bug Millennium Boy does pretty well.
He keeps up pretty much the whole time.
We're going to go in for some live stuff in a second here.
But I just want to take this opportunity to thank every single person that has subscribed to the channel.
15,000 subscribers is mind boggling, guys.
So thank you all so, so much.
It means a hell of a lot to me.
You guys rock everybody.
So take care, guys.
I'll see you all soon.
And I'll leave you with the ending.
It was pretty funny.
So here's the ending of the pie eating contest.
Take care, everybody.
The crust is like stuck to the bottom.
Scrape it.
Scrape it?
Oh, fuck.
What is this stuff?
Oh, man.
Your winner, again, Burger Boy.
Oh, I won a pie eating contest when I was like a kid.
At like summer camp.
Everyone was like, oh, I didn't eat all day.
Even like, oh, the fat kids.
And then, oh, I won.
I beat them all.
I was like a little guy.
Oh, what happened now?
You lost.