Hey, how you doing everybody? Good evening, good morning, good afternoon, good night.
Hi, I'm Jerma. This is a gameplay commentary on Team Fortress 2.
And we're going to talk about some things today. This is Demolin Night with the Double Donker, Loose Cannon.
Although I don't really do very many double donks with it. I was just kind of messing around, just wanted to get a gameplay real quick.
So I could talk about some things. And we have a lot to talk about.
There are a lot of things to discuss in this video. We're going to go over the first one really specifically, really quickly.
Tip of the Hats is this coming weekend. So today, I believe I'm recording this on Monday.
So Tip of the Hats starts on the 19th of Saturday. It's the yearly charity event that the TF2 community puts together.
It's a lot of great people involved and it goes to a great charity, the donations.
So come hang out. I'll be there for a lot of it. I don't know what my exact time slots will be when I'm going to be pubbing and playing and just hanging out.
I'll be there for a lot of it. So come, it's the link will be there in the description. Come check it out.
TipoftheHats.org is the website as well. I encourage you to check it out.
So next thing we're going to do really, really quickly. This is going to be a real rapid fire update video. A real rapid fire update video.
There's an update. There's an update right there. There's an update over here.
So I'm fully moved in. I am in my new place. I'm settled. I got all my stuff here. Everything is here. I don't have to go back and forth anymore.
That was the big problem with trying to settle in here. Every day there was something else.
For the last like month and a half straight, I had like no. I mean, I had free time, but every ounce of my free time, I'd sit down to play a game or I'd sit down to do something.
And like, there's like somebody at my door. Yeah, we're here to fucking tear something down and put something up.
I'm like, OK, come on in, gentlemen. It's just been kind of a roller coaster these last couple of months. But the good thing is it's over.
You know, I'm here. I'm living here. No constraints. I can do what I need. I can do what I please.
I am just so excited. We got another update coming in. Keep the updates coming.
My stream. As of this video tonight, I'm going to be streaming at least three or four times a week.
This is the announcement video. This is the come to my Twitch channel. Come and check it out. I will be live a lot.
Now, I don't have exact times and I probably never will because me and schedules, we've talked about this a thousand times.
I don't do well with a schedule ever. I think I've said this in at least like five or six different videos.
But the point is, I'm going to turn it on whenever I'm comfortable sitting here, ready to go, ready to stream.
Is it two o'clock in the morning? I don't know. Is it four o'clock in the afternoon? Potentially.
Could it be a morning breakfast show? You betcha.
But I'm not going to pigeonhole myself into a particular time or a particular game for that matter.
Don't expect to open up this stream and see Diablo 3 for seven straight months. It's not going to happen.
Because streaming for me is serious. Wait, wait, wait. This update's not done. I'm not done. This update. Stop.
This update isn't done yet. In fact, don't fucking do it again. Just don't. That's so done by this point. Just don't do it again.
Streaming for me is going to be more of a chilled out, relaxed atmosphere. I'm not doing it for a bigger paycheck or anything like that.
It's just I want to be able to chill with you guys, relax in the chat. Everybody has fun and we play whatever.
Also, we can talk about YouTube streaming a little bit here, too. It just came into beta. It's out. I can stream on it.
I can use YouTube Gaming, the live platform, right now if I wanted to. But initially, I don't think I'm going to.
Because the chat's just really not that great. It's in its very early infancy stages and Twitch is established.
It's ready to be used right now. I have a partnership on Twitch. I can stream in 720, 1080, whatever I want.
I might stream on YouTube eventually. Once it gets into like the adolescent stage, maybe I'll switch over to YouTube and it'll be a little bit easier for me.
But I don't know. I might do both. You might see a YouTube stream sometimes. Maybe you'll see a Twitch stream. I don't know.
Keep it rolling. Keep it going. We get that aliens. Aliens are coming to TF2.
There's a UFO update or something that's got an invasion. I have no idea.
All I know is that I was in Dust Bowl, looked up, saw the UFO, shit my pants, and then went to Reddit and went to online and looking up all the information.
What's it going to be? Oh my God. There's a lot of hype around it right now.
And yeah, that's all right. What's the next thing? What are we on? What's coming up next?
I'm probably going to BlizzCon this year. I'm going to try my absolute hardest to be there.
Mainly because I didn't get to do anything really this year. I did PAX East, but that's it.
And I love going to conventions. And because of this whole buying this place and moving in and all these busy things that have been going on the last few months,
I didn't get to really do much. I couldn't go to PAX Prime. I couldn't go to E3.
So I want to make up for that. I want to go to BlizzCon and Overwatch is going to be there, so that's another huge reason to go.
So if you see me there, then just say hello. I'll bring it up again before BlizzCon happens. I believe it's November 10th, November 9th.
It's one of the first or second weeks of November is BlizzCon. But that's it. That's really all I have to say.
I just wanted to give as many updates as I possibly could because there's been a lot of shit going on.
And I just wanted to make a five or six minute video condensing all these topics down, reiterate a couple of things,
bring up some new stuff and that sort of thing. So thank you so much for watching. Really appreciate it.
Come to the Twitch stream. It's there. I don't know if I'm live right now. I might be. I might not be.
But if you haven't followed and you're into that sort of thing, then go ahead and follow it.
So thank you guys. I'll see you all soon. Take care everybody and good night.