Hello there, ladies and gentlemen. It's Grampa here. And today, I've got some Dishonored for you. It's a fantastic game.
I actually, I haven't played one second of the game, so I don't know if it's good or not. But I'm just gonna say it's good for the purpose of the fucking video.
So let's do it, huh? I've been drinking all morning in preparation for this game. So let's have some fun!
See, the cool part about this game is you can talk to everybody.
You're all talking at the same time, though. You shut the fuck up. I'm trying to listen to this guy.
I'm drinking this. That was his, I think. He doesn't even care.
Oh, hello there, Suzy. Look at this beautiful woman. Is this my wife? God, I hope so. Look at you.
I hope that one of the other cities had dealt with this before. Knew of some cure. This news is very bad.
At the breaking point.
Cowards. They're going to block you.
They'll wait to see if the plague turns this city into a graveyard.
Yeah, that sucks. I know, me too.
Wait, what? What happened?
Don't worry, darling.
Everything's fine. Your mother's fine.
Wait, where are the guards? Who sent them away?
What do you mean?
Who sent them away?
I am the guard.
What? What are they doing?
What the hell is that?
Oh, it's ninjas.
How am I going to fight the ninjas now?
Come on, left clickers, attack.
All right, don't worry, sweetie.
I got you. Get the fuck away from here.
Come on. Come at me.
I got to come around this corner.
Okay, so the game wants me to be stealthy right here.
But I say, nope, I'm just going to run in and start slicing.
Because, you know, are they really going to kill me?
Three versus one?
I'm supposed to be a superhuman son of a bitch.
We'll see what happens.
Let's go in.
Hey, buddy.
Eat that, that's your neck.
Oh, sorry, did I cut off your balls?
What about you too?
Jeez, stealth, I will never use stealth ever.
I just killed this whole room in two seconds.
Okay, I don't know what this guy's doing,
but it is freaking me out right now.
I'm seriously going to start fucking hallucinating.
This guy has just been doing this the whole time.
What are you doing, man?
What are you doing?
Please stop doing that.
Going through the sewers, having tons of fun.
Going through...
What the hell is this?
Oh my God.
Are those rats?
Oh, oh, they're just bones and muscle now.
Oh, hold on.
Where's the box?
Is this a horror game?
Is this one of those horror games that takes like an hour before it starts to scare you?
I'm not playing this fucking game.
Doc's here.
No, no way.
I'm not playing a horror game.
I'm not playing that.
And the chase is on.
Got to get out of here.
Come on, come on.
The music means you got to run fast.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Actually, I heard people behind me.
I think there's a couple of assholes behind me.
Hold on.
Stay here.
Let's go.
Come on.
I'm going to kill you.
You're going to get a sword in your face.
See you later.
I blocked that.
Come on.
Try harder.
You guys are terrible.
How ab...
Who brings a fucking gun to a knife fight?
We were having a genuine knife fight.
And you brought...
You bring out a gun.
Where's my gun?
Oh, I didn't...
Where's my machine gun?
How come I don't have one and you do?
God damn it.
Whatever.
I got to go to the store anyways.