Damn, I lost track of time. I just did. That's a fact. There's no sound. Oh shit, hold on.
There we go. Yeah, I lost track of time. I just kind of blinked, and it was like,
two. I was like, what the hell happened? Content creator. That's right. I don't have to say
anything. I'm a content creator. I don't have to say anything. I also want to ask you guys
something, because I don't know if this was a dream I had last night, or if this was a thing
I told you guys yesterday. I don't remember. I have to ask you. So at some point yesterday,
it was either a dream last night or last night near the end of the stream. I was humming a song.
I was going like, I was doing like, you know, the thing that I do. I'm just humming a song with
like a high pitched sound, right? And I stopped halfway through and I said, I went like this,
I went like, I just freaked out. I said, I'm fucking Peter Griffin with a different noise.
That happened yesterday? Or did I dream that that happened yesterday? I had a dream that that
happened. That did not happen. I had, okay, so apparently I had a dream last night where I
was sitting here doing that. And I freaked out and I said, I'm Peter Griffin with a different noise.
What the fuck? And there was way more shit that happened in that dream too. Was it during Bone?
Was it during Boneworks? Wait, did that happen during, that happened on another stream?
Did that happen on a different fucking broadcast? No, it didn't. It did. Okay, well, it happened.
Hey, thank you a little bit later for the damn guy Peter to yourself. You've done that 40 times.
Is that, what else? I must be so scared of being connected to like family guy that I have
nightmares about it now. Remember, were you tripping? No, I've refused to trip. I'm never
going to do it. It'll never happen. I don't, I can't, I don't want to do that stuff. Nightmare.
Anyways, let's talk about today because we're going to, we're doing a little schedule pivot
change today. Pivot change. We're going to finish Undertale. But you know what I mean.
We're going to finish Deltarune. And then after that, we are not going to play Umbrellas
not allowed anymore. We're going to move from here to the tip of the hat stream. So we will
raid the tip of the hat stream and I'm going to go over there and participate for like an hour or so.
I play a game or something. I just hang out. So we're going to go from here to tip of the hats
later. This is Deltarune. Yes, this is not Undertale. I need to tweet this. So let's go
ahead and tweet Andy. Be right back. While I write this, somebody said, are you going to stream the
Diablo 2 remake? The answer is no. And I'll give you a very specific couple of reasons why.
If I ever really sit down and play the Diablo 2 remake on stream, I feel like, and I'm this,
this is not, this is nothing against you guys. This is nothing against streaming or YouTube.
That's a me thing. I don't, I don't really want to stream that. It's a me thing. If I'm going to do
that because I don't really want to turn it into like a thing that I'm streaming and just kind of
turn it on. Cause I wanted to be able to sit, sit in this chair with my mouth open, just staring
and just not even say a word and just fucking just walk around and pick up uniques and stuff.
Oh, it is nothing against this community, the stream, nothing. I just, I'm not going to stream
that if I'm going to play it. Diablo 2 is great, but Diablo 2 is also a lot of just kind of,
Oh my God, we got, we, we got, we got 15 community subs from no seven. Thank you.
Once you get through the first few acts of Diablo 2 and you, you know, if you beat the game,
you go through a nightmare, you beat the game, you go through it. It's a lot of just like,
I let's get the cube. Okay. Get the amulet. You get the way point. Yep. Okay. Go, go. All right.
Nice. Like, hold on. I gotta put a point in. All right. Put the make cube. Let's go. Dario go.
All right. Act three, you get the way point. Yep. It's, it's literally just kind of, you just go
through the motions like 10 times to get like a pretty colored item. That's what we want.
It's a good just chatting game. Yeah. Okay. Oh, here, here. Listen, if I ever get to a point
where I have like a level, like 70 sorceress or something, if I'm like playing the fuck out
of that game and I want to just do like a stream where I'm just sitting here doing like Mephisto
runs while we just talk and yeah, you'll see it, but I'm not going to start like a level
zero barbarian in the remake and stream that, right? That's the thing I'd want to do on my own.
Oh, here comes, here comes the chimpanzees. All right. Let me finish my tweet. You guys are
distracting me. That's why I was so late today. You should play Deltarune chapter two. I agree.
So let's get started. Let me just tweet this. Anybody else only type with their dominant hands
thumb on their phone's keyboard? I hold. So I'm right-handed. So I hold the phone in my left hand
with my thumb up. And so I'm like holding it, um, kind of like palming it in a way. My, all my
fingers are kind of around the edges of the other side. And then I cup the first hand that my left
hand is holding it with the right hand. And then I use the sole right thumb to type everything.
That weird to use both thumbs. I don't do that. That's not a boomer hold. Excuse me. The boomer
hold is hold with left-hand palm index finger on other dominant hand is poking while it's very
close to your face. Excuse me. I'm not going to be put in that category. I'm a millennial.
Did I even press the tweet button? All right. I'm ready. You guys ready? Here we go. This is
what we left off. Turn it up. It's way faster to use both hands. Yeah, but I, okay. Here's my problem
with that. The keyboard is so tiny that if I use both hands and fingers or whatever, I press like
eight different letters. Loud. Not too loud. All right. Here we go. So the last thing that happened
was a sand showed up and threw fucking lightning bolts out of the sky. And if we had to like dodge
them and shit, it was crazy. And one of them hits, uh, one of them hits Susie and Susie's now currently,
um, like dying, I think in the other room, which is like crazy. I hit Susie. It hit me and it hit,
um, it was, that's the last thing to happen is from crazy. I'm going to head out. Uh, what it's
too loud. No, it's not. This is softer than it was yesterday. Please apologize for timing me up for
10 minutes. All right. So the pre-stream chat, I timed somebody over 10 minutes, but hold on. Yes.
I apologize for timing you out for 10 minutes in pre-stream, but let's talk about the context first.
You asked me to play destiny to PVP tomorrow. Do you think that is, is that a, should I have
timed you up for an hour or is that, was 10 minutes, um, warranted? I'm sorry for time. I didn't,
I was trying to do it for like a minute. I'm sorry. That's a permanent man. All right. I'm ready.
Let's go. I'm ready to play. I keep almost saying undertale. So quick recap. Um, Lancer is sick.
He's ill. He saved us. He was in our pocket for like a day or two. He came out. He let us all out.
We were captured by the queen and now he's kind of sick. He's like cold and he can't walk and stuff.
So this is kind of, this is, um, it's getting a little weird. All right. Think you can do it,
Chris? Of course I can. I can do puzzles. Calm your skinless boneless thighs. Everybody.
I'll think of a solution. I gotta get my voices going. I gotta get my voices going.
It's just ignore him. I'll just be over here where I can't hear you and I'll be here away
from your IQ debuffing aura. There we go. That's better. All right. So we're,
move. Oh, I see. It's one of these puzzles. Oh, I can rotate it. We go. We go. We go.
We go. We go. Is that supposed to do that? Yeah, we got it. What? Hey, wait a second. How did you,
how'd you solve it without me? First figured it out before you jealous. Well, I knew the answer.
I just wanted to see Chris try first. By the way, if anyone can tell me what that, what that laugh
was, you get 10, uh, community thumbs up points. What was that? It was not Gannon. Nope. Laugh.
Nope. Nope. Not Zelda. Wrong. Somebody got to say it. Did somebody say it? I think I saw it.
I want to be confirmed that more than one person knew what it was. Not Street Fighter,
not punch out. Do it again. Hup, hup, hup, hup. Hup, hup, hup, hup. I'll tell you, it's from, uh,
it's from a group of turtles. I just, it's a Ninja turtle there. I fucking just ruined it.
That's Shredder from Turtles in Time when he jumps into the screen and he like,
puts you back in time. Oh, you got it wrong. Sorry. Uh, it's called Suspense Susan. Dramatic
suspense. Nobody cares. I do. That's bullshit. Go watch, go look at it then. If I'm so wrong then.
And you do the next one. Fine. Watch me. Also, my name's not Susan. Oh shit, these are going to get
harder. Child's play. Wouldn't you give me a harder one? For example, if anyone had a four by four
puzzle to you. Just tell us the solution. Well, you see, first you align the shadows with the
lines on the floor. All right, what do we move first? Um, let's just do the puzzle. Just give
me a moment. It's not like Chris could even solve it anyway. Oh, this is actually, this might take
a little while. Well, maybe not. Let's see how smart I am. Turns out I know what I'm doing.
Okay, I just want to go pick this up off the ground. Oh, no, I don't. Oops. Everybody,
everybody thinks they're so smart until they're not. Right. Oh shit. This is going to, I don't,
I need to, I feel like I had it. Correct. Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Everyone stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop. No, it doesn't go
flat. Oh my God. No, stop, stop. Everyone quiet. No, wrong one. Idiot. Fuck. This doesn't, no,
none of them go flat. Shit. I don't know. I thought I had it. How do I do this? Wait, fuck.
Are you trolling? No, I'm not. It's just weird. Did I have it right the first time? I'm actually
blown away by this time. Everybody else says I'm bad. Oh my God. I'm absolutely blown away by this.
I can't believe I'm blown away. So like, this is making me like so mad. I got it. What the fuck?
Shit. Hey. Dude, I'm fucking blown away by this. It is funny when he cannot solve the puzzle. Omega
lull. Is this the future of like Twitch chat? It's going to be like androids. It is quite
humorous when he cannot solve the children's puzzle. You can't have. You just got lucky.
It's just trial and error. Kind of was for me. It was for me. I just looked up shredder laughing
and it sounds nothing like that. All right. Well, it's time for me to fucking. All right,
fine. I can't believe I actually have to do this. I can't fucking believe I have to do this.
So here it is. Let me just go like this. Not there. Where is it? It's when he comes out of the screen.
This is not a joke alert. This is literally I'm waiting for him to do the ha ha ha thing.
There it is. So you beat shredder, throw a bunch of people into his screen.
And what did that what happened?
And I was, I was the wrong one apparently. Remember that guy is.
Let's go. Brute force method. Arcade man could do it. Except cavemen died out because they're
stupid. I'm solving the next one. So just stay here until I'm done. Yeah, like we're going to
wait that long. Am I at the end of the game? Um, I believe I am fairly close to being at the last
portion of the game. What are you two doing here? This one's mine. It'll be over in a second. So why
don't you just relax in your mind palace? Which probably doesn't even have anything in it. I just
need to figure out why the shapes don't go together. Oh, hey, you just got to fill the whole square
thing, right? What if you just piled them all in the corners? Like digging a really wide hole.
What? First want to try? Oh, what? Oh, no. I don't like this. In the corner? Put them all in the
corner? I don't know. This is not gonna fit though. What do you mean put them in the corner?
Just like, stop them in the corner? Can I do that? Does that work? What? Dude, different corners.
What are you talking about? They have to go in different corners? I thought it was just like,
just put them in there. Who cares? Isn't that correct? Well, I thought it was just to stick
everything in the corner. I thought that's what it was. That's not, he's actually zonked. I'm not.
I'm fine. I just woke up like 15 minutes ago. I'm fine. Okay. I did not. I woke up at like,
I woke up well into the morning, I promise. I didn't just wake up.
All right, Susie. I did the work. There's no way. It's a computer bug. It's a glitch.
You're cheating. Just like when you wave dashed.
How is it taste, idiot? Man, I'm gonna relish this forever. All those times you acted so high and
mighty. Oh, guess what? You're not. Face it. You're just a big dumbass. Just like the rest of us.
Oh, we're kind of sad. Fine. I admit it. I'm not that smart. I never was.
There. Are you happy? I just used to be a forgettable little blue bird.
No one even remembered my name. Then one day came the spelling bee Noel and I studied for.
And it came down to the two of us. She got nervous and couldn't speak.
We lost. And I won. That was when I tasted it. Praise the glory, the superiority, the addictive
power of being smart. Since then, year after year, I've been number one in the class. It was only
because Noel helped me study. He's the real smart kid. Everyone's expectations for me are so high
now. What am I going to do once I go somewhere without her? Why I wanted to make a new world
for us. A world where we'll always be number one and number two. But I'm still wrapped up in that.
I got tricked by the queen. Now Noel is going to suffer because of it. Maybe I did just like
being superior. Maybe I am just an idiot. Don't cry, chicken nugget man. All of us are idiots too.
Huh? I mean, like, I don't know about everyone else, but whether you're the smart kid or not,
we couldn't care less. Screw up as much as you want, honestly. Not like our opinion of you could.
Susie! Susie, you'd accept me even if I'm dumb?
Uh, yeah. Like when your sister gets cursed in Dragon Blazers 2.
Even if her stats suck, she's still your party member. Susie, real Dragon Blazers 2 reference?
Susie, you're not only kind, but a true gamer as well. Perhaps I underestimated you.
Uh, uh, uh.
Worry not. I have decided. Uh, uh, uh.
I will turn over a new leaf from now on. Uh, uh, uh.
And fight for the side of ignorance.
We're not telling you to be stupid. Yes, sometimes it's okay to make mistakes.
And make mistakes I will. Uh.
Onward!
Why couldn't Rousey be here to teach the normal lesson? He's a gamer.
This downstairs table will be for our special guests.
There's a dinner party on the second floor for everyone else.
Everything here is tailored for you, right?
That's screaming. That's Rousey.
Um, you don't have to scream.
Just because you like my outfit.
Oh my god.
I need to take a- I need to take at least a minute for that one.
Okay.
Oh, Chris. Susie. Uh, how may I serve you?
What the hell are you doing?
Um, the queen didn't have a room for me so, uh, uh, uh, uh, um, uh, uh, uh.
She made me into one of her butlers instead.
Whatever, Rousey. Can you heal Lancer?
Come on. Give me that one.
Oh. It's cold.
Susie.
I'm afraid this is something I can't heal.
What?
Lancer is-
Lancer? Hey!
You see, each dark fountain creates a different world.
A world whose darkness reflect the will of its fountain.
Can I do that one again?
Can we do that one again?
I messed it up.
A world whose darkners reflect the will of its fountain.
But through those darkners can exist in their own worlds.
They might not belong if they go to another one.
So can we help him?
Yes, there is a way.
Castletown's Grand Fountain is made of pure darkness.
As long as it stays flowing, any darkner can live there.
So if we bring Lancer back to school, he'll be okay again.
He thinks he's a voice actor.
So we just need to get out of here, huh?
Right.
Alright.
Lancer, we'll be back for you, buddy.
We can't jump between dark worlds.
Your friend, if we defeat Queen, we can save him.
Yeah, with me out of the way, Queen is going to force Noelle to do her bidding.
And if Noelle doesn't want to, she might make her face into a robot one.
Seriously.
Would you assist me in saving Noelle?
Me? I just can't do it by myself.
But if you can help me, I have a plan.
A plan?
I remember from Queen's tour of this place.
It's a secret shortcut on the third floor.
While Chris is distracting Queen, Susie will take the shortcut to reach Noelle
and transfer her to me on the roof.
From there, I'll bring her to a safe hiding spot.
And together we can all defeat the Queen!
Alright, sure, we'll give it a shot.
Most excellent said.
See you on the roof, fellow agent.
Alright, let's go.
Did you take that off already?
Sorry.
That's like sad.
We're just gonna leave him here?
Whoa.
Whoa, wait.
Is this like an Easter egg?
What if I move him all the way?
What?
He seems to be well taken care of.
Is this spaghetti?
Is that spaghetti?
Oh shit, this is just...
Okay.
Wait, what?
We're gonna have these legs?
It's a pair of legs.
I think that's like bathrooms on fire.
It's a door.
Where will you go?
Oh, fuck.
Okay, hold on.
It's a cyber thing.
There's a book here about shortcuts that open up later.
The Cybernetic Bookshelf.
Welcome to Collar Cafe.
Let us warm your day.
Talk about yourself.
Ah, forgive me for not introducing myself sooner, young masters.
I am Swatch, our Lady Grace's head butler.
When we are not attending to her needs,
I and the Queen's other style,
use this room as our humble yet colorful gift shop slash cafe.
Please shop to your heart's content.
We are eager to serve your any dish.
Does a woman of Our Lady Grace's caliber not deserve
a coven of powerful men and women to dote upon her every movement?
Have rap anthems written to her kindness?
Which are then bit crushed beyond recognition to make them more computer?
To have melons smashed with karate chops repeatedly for no apparent reason?
To have barrels thrown from the rafters?
Make us smash them all with karate chops before the timer runs out?
The barrels are full of melons and we have to smash those too?
Yes, the answer is yes.
Rooksholtz, I'm afraid I am not familiar with a guest of that moniker.
Ah wait, are you by chance referring to that unbearable,
unique man who barged in here and demanded to be made butler supremeth?
I'm afraid that that person is now banned from this establishment.
May have suffered injuries as a result of his,
uh, rather swift ejection.
Please do not mention him again.
You're still cleaning up the worms he left on the floor.
Outfit.
Ah, my outfit.
Yes, the monochrome look is quite suitable, isn't it?
Black suit, colored glasses.
Many people have failed to imitate this look.
So I'm even going so far as to attempt to impersonate me.
I'm going to get the, uh, nevermind.
Back around?
It's rules.
No, it's Rooksholtz!
It's Roxas!
Yes.
It's the Peter Griffin thing again.
I'm out.
Butt juice.
Oh god.
Uh, 100 HP for butt juice.
What about the spaghetti code?
You're insane.
Not.
30 HP?
Why is this $180?
B-shot bow tie.
Ooh.
Royal pin.
Oh, it's a everybody heel.
Okay.
It's a party heel.
Oh, it is, it says party.
I'm going to get a bow tie?
Or should I get the royal pin?
All right, I'm getting the royal pin.
It's probably, is this expensive?
That's two armor.
I'm going to hold on to it.
Can I sell, sell weapons?
No.
Sell armor?
Oh wait, I can sell the stupid mannequin.
Should I keep the mannequin for like crafting or something?
Should I never sell anything?
Whoa.
Dog dollar.
Should I sell the dog dollar?
Oh, hold.
All right, that's, that's enough.
Hold.
Okay, I want to go visit, yeah.
I want to go visit the trash guy.
Trash zone.
It's an eggplant that looks like a trash bag.
Funny little guy was looking for you to the west.
He was muttering something about deals.
I know what that way is.
Door is unlocked.
I'm going in.
What, you want to go in by yourself?
Whatever, do what you want.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's me, Spamton G.
Spamton.
Let's make a deal.
Okay, about you.
I used to be not a robot email guy.
And now I'm the, ow.
It burns, help me, ow.
I'm the, it burns guy.
Amazed at this amazing transformation,
you too can have a communion.
Where, with, ha ha.
Soon I'll even surpass that damned clown.
Clown around town, a clown in the town.
But unlike him, I'm going to shoot for the sky.
Get down the path, you, the big one.
I'll get so, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll get so,
I'll get, I'll get, ow.
Speaking of communion.
Chris, did you know that there's a knight?
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Too many excess vacation days
take a goddamn vacation straight to hell.
Friends?
Me?
Chris, you and me,
our already friend request has been accepted.
We don't need anyone else.
We don't need easels or CRTs.
We don't need any man, woman, or child at half price.
We don't need Mike.
Mike.
Chris!
Don't believe anything you see on TV.
The man's a criminal, I tell you.
A criminal.
Do it again?
Okay, what about our deal?
Chris, you little sponge.
I knew you'd come here on a Saturday night.
After all, you want to be a big shot.
But how?
How can you be?
Listen, listen, listen to me.
Get in, get over here.
In the deep abyss of Queen's Mansion.
A great deal is waiting for a limited time.
No, well, only a limited time.
Only a heaven-piercing, work-out-ready body.
Signed by the classics.
You've come to expect our latest of 1997 copyright.
We gotta make sure we put that there.
Chris, that little nipper is
our one-way ticket to make you big.
Make it me big.
Before you know it,
we will be taking a ride around town
in our special conga-dero.
Vacationing in burning acid
while you soak in the hybrid.
But Chris, don't breathe yet.
The way is locked by high-quality encryption.
You will never get inside.
Wait, Chris, look.
Here, those balloons.
Are you the 1000th customer?
As a commemorative ring,
I will let you buy key-gen from me
at the low, low price.
What do you think?
It's such a steal.
I'm, I'm, I'm myself.
I'm shitting myself.
Take this deal and you will die.
It's that good.
Buy the key-gen from me.
Unlock the basement and get that empty disc.
Okay, fear.
What are you afraid of?
According to encyclopedia of
being afraid.
There's nothing to fear except
can anyone hear me?
Help, help.
Huh, what?
No, I didn't hear anything just now.
But it sounded kind of
like they were talking to you.
Buy key-gen from me
and go to Queen's mansion.
How do I get the key-gen?
What?
Go by myself, Chris.
No, the men inside,
the men inside would.
How do I buy it?
He just said buy.
Exit and buy more.
Oh, fuck.
I've been talking to him the whole time.
Okay.
Buy.
Hurry up and buy.
For a second I thought that was the menu.
Okay.
Buy.
Buy more.
What the fuck?
Key-gen S potion.
The big one.
B-shot bow tie or run away.
This is supposed to be like a market.
I have to catch this when it's 30 bucks.
Oh my god.
Oh, for seven bucks.
All right, what about this one?
Item, item affects HP a lot.
Okay, can I get this one too?
80.
All right, that's fine.
What about the...
What the fuck?
The big one.
Cut anything in two pieces.
Criminal.
Oh, wait.
I don't have to actually accept it.
Oh, well, okay.
I thought it was like you had to click it
and it just bought it.
Take it.
Can I buy these?
Can I buy...
Okay, I got two.
Should I get more of these potions?
Stop, stop.
Scam, scam, scam, scam.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Stop getting scammed.
What are you talking about?
All right, run away.
Buy.
You're buying weapons.
Oh.
Get more potions.
Should I?
Okay.
Talking.
Friends.
Yeah, well, I think we're good.
Buy more.
Okay, let's go.
Exit and buy more and then escape.
Mansion, basement.
Find it.
Creepy stuff were you buying anyway.
Ah, like I even want to know.
Yikes.
She said she hoped if it was candy,
you'd share with her.
Shut up.
Chris, what was it?
Raid bow tie.
Oh, it just goes down.
Oh, what the fuck.
Poison.
Oops.
Well, I have the key, right?
So I can go to the basement and the mansion.
Funny little guy was looking for you.
Yep.
Okay, so let's go back to the mansion.
I wonder if I can go in another door now.
All right, I'm just going to sell this junk.
Maybe I shouldn't.
I might need it.
All right, I need the basement of the mansion.
Let's go this way.
I see you have escaped from your room unit.
Who can blame you for wanting to see my glorious mansion?
You won't want to take your eyes off this beautiful art.
We're not here to look at your stupid pictures.
That was not a recommendation.
I was just warning you.
Laughing my ass off.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my goodness.
Go down first.
What's that?
Basement.
Wait, did that do anything?
Oh, shit.
Ooh, found a revivement.
Hey, I thought it was going to be lower than that.
Okay, and the notes.
All right, let's go.
Oh, I know you are all loving my mansion.
We have a few rules around here you have to follow.
One, wipe your shoes.
Two, have fun.
Three, respect the pottery.
Four, have fun.
Five, missed entry duplication error.
I was trying to talk.
I was trying to hang out with it.
What the fuck?
Okay, so what we got?
Warmify, coldify.
Bluer two stages.
Redder two stages.
Coldify the red.
And then we're going to see what this does.
Half cold.
All right, we're going to see what this does.
What does this do?
Talked about the crunch of the last pickle in the refrigerator.
Okay, so now it's watching the color turn a lot colder.
It's now yellow.
All right, so now they both match.
Oh, there's candy in that one.
Oh, god damn it.
I want the candy.
Oh, super frog.
Pottery not respected.
I mean, I was trying to just see what it was.
See what it was.
All right, so just don't break the pottery.
But I kind of want to break the pottery.
Oh, because I want to recruit those guys.
Oh, they're just here anyways.
Okay.
All right, we need to warmify blue.
And we need to...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We need to coldify you.
We need to half warm you.
And then we're going to defend with you.
No, they don't have to be...
Well, yeah, they have to be yellow.
Yeah, I got it right.
They have to be yellow, right?
What are you doing?
Oh, they just have to be the same color.
They don't have to all be yellow?
Oh, I thought it was like blue was going to be tired.
Yellow was spare.
Oh, they just have to be the same color.
Okay, I thought it was like they had to be yellow.
It's like that's how you spare.
I don't know.
That's a Toby Fox game.
Could be anything.
All right, let's go.
So now I have to do warmify.
Well, let's just make them all yellow.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Coldify you, warmify you, and then you spare you.
This will do it.
Hello.
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
That was a voice crack, but I saved it.
Andy.
Got it.
All right, now we just spare.
Four to five.
Nice.
$328.
And check every window.
Andy, Andy.
Is this supposed to be a race?
One, two, three, four.
Okay, one.
Painting is labeled task.
Painting is labeled Timberley.
I don't get it.
Is this person's name Timberley?
Timberley.
All right, am I going to remember this?
Task spelled correctly.
Task, Timberley, task with a Q.
Task, Timberley, task.
TASK.
Task, Timberley, task, TASK.
Got it.
Just in time for your appointment.
Would you assist in organizing these paintings?
Yes.
I'll refine.
Then the first question.
Which painting's name is first alphabetically?
Task.
Okay.
Ask, T-A, T-A-S, T-A-S-K.
Timberley is T-I.
There's I.
So K is above that.
Q.
All right, the four.
Wait, number four.
How do I say four?
Number four was tasked with a Q.
The left painting is four.
Why is it not, it's four.
I'll refine.
And the next question.
Which painting's name is third alphabetically?
Okay, that would be, so,
K, tasked with a K,
tasked with a Q,
tasked with a C was that one.
Wait, what was the question?
Because that would be Timberley and then task.
Okay, bottom.
I'll refine.
Then the next question.
Which painting is fourth?
Task, Timberley, task, TASK.
That's correct.
I'm so happy I could whip something.
Task manager blocks the way.
I can already spare task manager?
Really?
Holy shit.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa.
It's because you got them all right.
Oh, okay.
Nice.
All right.
Second floor.
Oh, wait.
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Not doing that yet.
Three, two, three.
Oh, I can't walk through that?
Huh?
Oh, shit.
Why?
Oh, it's the hacker.
Hacker.
Oh, for God's sake, it's a hacker.
He became lost in the craftsmanship.
Come here.
I'm the hacker.
I got the feeling there's a secret back door in this room.
Where could it be?
I'm the hacker.
Secret back door.
Chainmail.
He became lost in the craftsmanship.
He became lost in the...
Wait, did his head just...
His head's an arrow.
Is he, like, pointing to it?
Is he, like, pointing up?
He's, like, pointing his finger up.
Is it...
Is that what...
Yeah.
Okay, I got it.
Secret switch.
I was wondering.
I thought I was seeing things.
His head, like, turned into a pointer.
Okay.
I thought I was seeing things.
Switch.
Whoa.
You walked past it?
What'd I do?
What?
What is it?
You got it.
What are you talking about?
You're fine.
Yeah, what?
You guys need to relax and stop it.
Whoa, this is a secret entrance.
Okay, so then what does this do?
First, use the key...
Oh, this is the secret.
I found it.
I got it.
The key gen just went in there.
We're going to the...
First, you want us to stay here?
Sure, whatever.
Me and Rousey will have fun without you.
Oh, shit.
God.
Hey.
There was nothing in there.
Wait a minute.
Chain mail.
Put the chain mail on.
And the...
Whoa, why is frayed bow tie better?
What?
How come I got enough shit on?
Bye!
Holy shit, I didn't think that was gonna happen that quickly.
One of these is fake.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
I'm closing my eyes and flipping a coin.
Closing my eyes, flipping a coin.
Flip, flip, flip, flip.
It's tails.
To open the treasure, inside was one dark dollar.
One dark dollar was added to your money hole.
Got it.
That was right.
That's the deal.
Oh, shit.
I can't leave.
No.
I'm not spinning this.
What was that?
Sounds like a force field powering down.
Oh, the one upstairs.
What the fuck?
I wasn't ready for this shit.
I'm using the controller.
What the fuck?
I didn't know that was gonna happen.
I have the dumb ass controller in my hand.
I can't, you can't spin with the controller.
Okay, I'm gonna have to use the key.
What am I gonna do with that one?
D-pad?
No, I'm gonna use the, I'm gonna use the probably keypad.
Arrow keys.
All right, let's go.
All right, I'm ready.
Arrow keys.
Go.
Holy shit, this is fucking hard.
All right, let's go for it.
I'm trapped here until I get out.
Okay, I gotta get it down.
Fuck.
It's like the, you know what it is?
It's like the wrapping thing for my brain.
I don't know why.
Okay, if anybody else feels like this, you tell me if I'm accurate, right?
I don't know why when it comes to like things that spin, it inverts itself in my brain.
If I have to like scrap around left to get to right,
it's almost like I have to go right to get to left.
It's like, it's reversed in my brain.
Same, same.
Yeah, same.
Yeah, no, thanks.
That was a good effort.
Will he beat the teacup wheel this time?
Um, do I, do I have to, I'm gonna wait for the prediction to be in?
Okay, it's the shadows.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Um, it's just, look, my brain's gotta, my brain, I don't know why I said it like that.
Will I beat the teacup this round?
Okay, and let's go.
Fucking hell.
It's the, it's the going left and right.
I'm not gonna be able to do this.
It's like the rotating motion.
It's not left and right.
It's like wrapping.
I almost think I should just go one direction.
I'm trying to look at the shadows on the ground.
But like when I go, oh, I have to go left.
But where I currently am, like I could go right around and get there faster.
But you have to go left.
I hate circles.
I can't, I don't like rotating.
All right, these predictions are not gonna happen as fast as these attempts are gonna be.
I'm going.
What the fuck?
I did.
Oh, I feel bad for people that bet last time.
Not over yet though.
If I die here, I'm gonna stop.
I need to take an item.
I don't care.
I almost ate the poison.
What?
Oh, I'll give you a good one.
I'm gonna give you a really good one.
Ready?
I have to like kind of prepare for it.
It's got to be like pressure.
The thing to do the Monka S very well.
Yeah, it's a lot of pressure in your like upper throat.
Monka S.
No, that was bad.
There we go.
I have just like poison in my inventory.
I don't have any.
I have nothing.
All right, Revive Mint, the cookie.
Ooh, spaghetti.
30H.
No, I need more items.
Can I buy something for somebody?
I just do try this with no items or something.
I'm gonna lose.
There's gonna be like a secret fight back here.
It's gonna be like Jevil 2 and I'm gonna lose instantly.
Go back to the shop.
I think I'm gonna go back to the shop.
Yeah, I'm going back to the shop.
I'm gonna stock up on heals.
I'm gonna do the thing I do in every single RPG.
Well, I don't have a party, but...
So every time I played an RPG, I was so bad at them.
It was terrible.
I would just...
It took me like probably like a few years,
maybe like five to ten years after playing a lot of RPGs for SNES.
No, no.
What? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
What? Back seat, back seat, chat, chill.
What are you talking about?
Stop him.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Do I close this out if I go up?
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
Am I gonna luck it up if I go up?
All right, whatever.
Fine.
So anyways, I would be so bad at these games
that I would fill my entire inventory with the revive...
Whatever it was in the game.
Whether it was a revive juice or a like cure
that brought the person back to life.
People would just die and I would do revive on them.
I wouldn't even try to heal them.
I think at some point, like when I played the Mario RPG,
I'd have like 80% pick me up so we're in my inventory.
And nothing else.
I wouldn't even use mushrooms or heals or anything.
Though I just like didn't get it.
Oh, the back seaters are getting back seated.
Oh, shit.
That's a level I didn't think we'd reach today.
The back seaters in chat are being back seated
by people back seating them.
Huh?
There's nothing interesting.
Nothing.
There's gonna be a screamer in one of these.
There's something shining inside the old machine.
Do you take it?
Yes.
The empty disk was added to your key items.
Oh, I got the disk.
I got the disk.
I got it.
It comes to the Indiana Jones part.
Empty disk.
A data disk from a strange machine.
Didn't someone want this?
I'm gonna bring it back.
Oh, God.
This is gonna get weird.
Come on, Susie.
Give me my glasses back.
Look at me.
Oh, look at me.
I'm a big dweeb that loves homework.
Come on.
Fine.
Take them back.
Thank you.
Oh, Chris.
Everything okay?
Yes.
Whatever.
Let's go.
All right.
Cool.
I got the data disk.
Cafe.
Welcome to the cafe.
All right.
So we've got butt juice.
100 HP.
I'm gonna buy like a shitload of these.
Is that too many?
I don't know.
I'm playing this like I play every RPG.
I just buy a shitload of them.
I'm buying another one.
Okay.
Get this.
What do I want?
The Lancer Cookie.
Heals one.
Maybe I should keep it.
Is it Lancer Cookie?
Should I just get it?
I'm getting rid of this.
Revive Mint.
Spaghetti.
Yeah.
This 30 HP.
30 HP.
This is a revive.
I don't think I want this.
I want heals.
All right.
I just have my full inventory of healing.
T is a heal.
It heals more in battle.
Well, we're gonna try it like this.
Because if this is like a big fight that I'm doing,
I'm gonna go for it.
Let's go bring it.
Let's go bring it to him and see what happens here.
I have a feeling this is gonna be...
He's gonna freak out.
I'm gonna give him the data disk and he's gonna be like...
All of a sudden you can start here and like...
That's how you know like here it comes.
Like Toby Fox is gonna give you a banger.
I'm gonna go in the inventory.
Here it comes.
I'm gonna put it into...
Oh, yeah.
You brought the disk.
Enter.
Buy.
Oh, you should have done that.
Hey, everyone.
It's me.
Okay.
Talking.
Give disk.
Okay.
Well, I have it saved.
So this is a bad idea.
We'll see what happens.
There we go.
Give disk.
Chris.
You did it.
You...
Wee.
A little wormy.
You brought me the disk.
Oh, gee mama.
I can feel that smooth taste already.
Now, Chris, don't be greedy.
Hand it over.
Give me the disk.
Then we will transfer my...
Then, Chris, after this is very, very important,
go back and put the disk back where you got it.
Do that and you have my special guarantee.
I will pass my savings on to you.
Every big, every shot, every...
All yours, Chris.
So what do you say, big shot?
Warning.
If you consent to the terms and agreements,
our store is permanently closing down.
Finally, I knew you would...
Chris, here I go.
Begin to...
Oh.
So he's in the disk.
That was the worst noise.
So wait, he's in the disk?
Load it.
A strange...
You can feel it smiling in your hand.
Now we go put this back in the machine.
Throw the disk away.
Okay.
Mansion.
Save it.
Okay.
Put it back in here.
And then what?
I'm alone, though.
Wait a minute.
If I'm alone down here and I have to fight him in this...
I feel like I'm going to have to fight him.
I feel like I don't want spaghetti code.
I don't care.
Whatever.
Fuck it.
Okay, here we go.
There's a slot for a disk.
Insert the loaded disk.
Yes.
Put the disk into the broken down mechanism.
Nothing happened.
Tapped the mechanism.
Shook the mechanism.
You hit it.
You kicked it.
Nothing happened.
I feel like I have to do this.
Give me a sec.
Yeah, put it in MonkaW mode, please.
Give me one sec.
I just want to do something very quickly.
I feel like I'm going to have to put this on.
Because it's going to be probably an interesting,
interesting new voice I'm going to have to do.
Let's go ahead and check it out.
Let's see if that's a...
Let's see.
He's going to be a robot.
That's just a guarantee.
It's literally a guarantee.
There's no way he's not a robot.
Right, yeah.
Let's do...
Let's go with this one.
This one sounds pretty good.
I like this one.
How does this one sound?
Does this one hurt your ears?
It kind of hurts my ears.
No?
Yay?
Nay?
Which one?
You can't hear it?
Oh, I'm so excited.
I can't believe it.
I can't wait to tell you when I have them for you.
All right.
Although it doesn't hurt your ears when I scream.
Nay?
She had a lot of nays.
Seriously.
She had a lot of nays here.
How's this?
This is normal?
I got to get in the mood to do this.
I'm back.
All right, here we go.
Oh, God.
Big.
Becoming better.
So I think I should go.
Send us in that little soul you have.
Chris.
The hell was that weirdo?
Chris, we were worried about you.
So...
Here it comes.
What are we doing?
Whoa.
Oh, shit.
This is a shmup.
This is a shmoop.
It's a charge shot.
Oh, fuck.
Okay, here we go.
Chris.
It's time to make a big shot.
Let's go.
Spamton Neo.
Okay, snap.
Snap all.
Let's try snap all.
Everyone snapped wires.
This isn't spotty, just heavenly.
This is a fucking banger.
Got to go up.
Let's go.
Three times the firepower,
two times the waterpower,
and best of all, flying head.
All right, get it.
Hold and release, beat a fire, big shot.
Again.
Snap all.
We'll turn those shmoes and dames
into a rose and grave.
Oh, God.
Bring it on.
Come on.
Don't you want to be part of my beautiful heart?
Or did you need a little special tool?
I probably shouldn't hit him.
I don't know if I should be shooting him.
Isn't that bad?
I don't think I should shoot him.
I don't want to shoot him.
Stop shooting him.
All right, how are we doing on health?
Okay, I'm going to use a spaghetti gun.
Snap.
All you got to do is go big.
Are you serious?
It's for you.
Ooh.
Don't let him get in here.
All right, again.
Snap all.
That's calling, Chris.
My heart, my hand.
Good.
You need another heal?
No, I'm not.
I'm good.
Look at my eyes, look at my nose,
look at my mouth.
Got to heal.
We got to do fuck juice on me.
Everybody heal.
Everybody take a butt juice.
Back to full.
Come on.
Can't stand it.
Again.
What do you have right now?
Almost halfway there.
Let's go.
I got enough heals, I think.
Again.
I got to be careful here.
I got to heal after this.
All right, heal.
We're getting code.
We're getting code twice.
Go.
Again.
All right, only like four or five more times and that's it.
All right, we got somebody down.
Revive.
Revive Mint on Susie.
Let's go.
Come on.
All right, I'm going to fight.
Pretty bad.
80 percent.
Come on.
All right, so what do we got for health?
Okay, here's what we're going to do here.
Seven.
14.
Okay, let's go.
I need to go.
Where's Ralsei?
I'm going to revive Mint on Susie.
And then Ralsei is going to do a heal prayer on Ralsei.
All right, let's go.
F1 for help.
Oh, shit.
It's for me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's he doing?
Is he healing?
It smells like rotten glass.
Get those fucking wires cut.
Now.
Oh, God.
Whoa.
Stage lights are shattered.
He's almost there.
This is it.
Snap it.
He's right there.
Help.
That's it.
It's over.
I win.
That's it.
Yeah, I'm going to snap the wire on him and then see you later, spare.
I win.
Let me make sure it's actually going to work.
Let's just make sure.
Yeah, game over.
I win.
Get out of here.
Oh, I got to keep it going.
I got to first try the secret bosses in every chapter, right?
I have to.
What?
Oh, hold on.
God, he's just dead.
Oh, God.
That's kind of sad.
It seems after all, I couldn't be anything more than a simple puppet.
But you three, you're strong with a power like that.
Maybe you three can break your own strings.
Let me become your strength.
You got shadow crystal.
You got deal maker.
Oh, I liked him.
I actually like that guy a lot.
All right, what is it?
So we've got deal maker.
Ooh, fashionable pink and yellow glasses greatly increases money gained and a shit
lot of other stuff.
We should probably, Rousey should probably have this, right?
Yeah, give this to Rousey.
What was the other thing?
There was something else, too.
Wasn't there something else?
Shadow crystal.
A sharp shadow moves like water in the hand.
You have collected one.
Fun fact, if you beat him with a full inventory,
he gets really pissed.
You get the other one from Jevil.
Oh, well, I did do that.
It's on a different computer.
That was really cool.
That was fun.
That was a little intense, you know.
I'm setting myself up for a lot of defeat here
because I can't just be beat the secret boss Andy on first try.
I mean, that's not going to happen three times in a row, right?
Like in no way.
I feel like that's I'm adding.
I'm not going to be able to do that.
I'm going to have to though.
I have to be like three and oh,
there's a save game editor for chapter two
and a chapter one editor is in the works.
You want to create a single PC save.
Oh, OK, that's cool.
Ever a pee break?
Yeah, it's a good idea.
Let's take a pee break.
I'll be right back and we'll continue on in a second.
Hey, what's up?
I'm not back yet.
I'm just letting you know I'm going to be another minute or two
because I'm making a coffee back in like two more minutes.
OK, OK, OK, I'm back.
I'm back.
Sorry.
I've made a coffee and that led to me getting a snack,
which led to me having to like get that right.
Look, I'm sorry.
Snack was very good, though.
It was because of the Duke's sausages.
They're very good.
The chorizo and lime Duke sausages.
Holy moly.
They're very, very good.
They're like the little like meat snacks.
Highly recommend the chorizo and lime if you haven't had it.
Yeah, this is scary music.
I didn't even realize that.
OK, you guys can't see anything, but now you can.
So let's go back this way that we came.
Those are dog treats.
What's going on?
Hey, so are we seriously not going to talk about any of that?
It was goddamn weird.
Puppets, strings, hands.
What the hell does any of that mean?
And the way he just broke.
I don't think it meant anything, Susie.
It seems like it was just a corrupted program.
Yeah, I love these things.
They're really crunchy.
They're really small.
I don't know.
They've made it into some kind of oat milk or something.
They're called milk bones.
They're in a weird part of the grocery store, though.
They're in like the dog aisle, like the pet aisle.
I don't know why.
I don't know.
They're very, very good.
He turned into our allies.
Let's just accept it.
Chris, you've got goosebumps.
You OK?
I'm OK.
If you say it all strained like that, I'm not going to think you're OK.
Hey, Rousey.
You think Chris is OK?
Well, they seem a bit shocked, but
Chris doesn't want us to worry, so
let's not push them for now.
I'm all right.
Chris, I'll make some cake for you later, OK?
I could even make it chocolate flavored.
Butterscotch, simenon, whatever you want.
Well, their stomach's rumbling, but the goosebumps aren't gone.
Chris, if you're cold, you can share my scarf.
Yes, every time I mispronounce a word, everyone has to talk about it.
Whatever.
I said simenon instead of simenon.
It's very easy to do.
Or Susie could.
What?
No hell if I'm giving you my jacket.
You make me cold.
I'm burning you knuckleheads for warmth.
Susie.
Too late.
Already imagining you guys as idiot-scented candles.
You said it wrong?
Cin- cinnamon.
Cinnamon.
What is it?
It's cinnamon.
Cinnamon.
I'm saying right?
Hup, hup.
Wait, why am I going that way when I can go this way?
So, um, where's progression?
This way?
I think progression was this way.
Ow.
I'm gonna say aluminium.
Aluminium.
Hey!
What if I do it first?
I win.
What's the score?
Right.
This stuff.
Okay, the mouse did that.
All right, should I go- should I go to the second floor?
Should I- what's over this way?
I'm gonna go to the second floor.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh wait, I thought I was supposed to collect them.
Whoops.
It's me being a stupid dummy.
Whoopsie.
I wonder how many people turned their volume down
and just like went to a different stream after that one.
That's the hacker.
You know, sometimes when I do that stuff,
I hope that the person's putting me through a speaker
and somebody ends up walking in the room that doesn't know,
doesn't care that they watched this channel.
They might not know anything about me.
And they hear that and they just go,
what are you- what the fuck is- who is that?
Like if I were to, for instance, go,
oh, whoopsie daisy, whoopsie doodly doodly.
One of you- there's 11,000 people here.
Somebody's like, dad just came in or something,
or somebody's like roommate just walked in.
And now they just thought like, what the fuck are you doing?
There's 11,000 of you here.
One of you just had a roommate walk in the door.
Welcome to the second floor dinner party, section A.
Please help yourself to anybody's food.
Normally, I'm terrified of mice,
but it's okay because that one is wearing a wig.
Okay.
Hey, it's me, the hacker.
No one figured it out, but it's me.
I've been on the download.
Oh, that really happened to me.
My roommate is here.
Mouse?
This guy keeps telling everyone at the party he's a hacker.
I don't know what to do with this information.
Yes, yes.
Queen is right.
Send error report.
I wouldn't agree more.
Newpert's moving up in the world.
I am mouse-a-billion.
I stand leagues and inches above all the other mice.
Only Newpert remains above me still.
Eating a wig.
Whoa.
I win.
Let's go this way first.
First floor.
No, we don't want that.
Hey, what's the point of that?
What's the point of that?
Room has been closed due to kitchen vermin.
Room has been closed due to kitchen.
Okay, so we can only go...
I guess I can go up.
Oh me, oh my.
The kitchen is infested with vermin.
I knew we should have properly finished
dumping all the cheese in that alleyway.
Ouch, ouch.
The mouse can't get me up here.
Even if the...
Ow, stove is burning my feet.
Mouse!
And it's not wearing a wig.
What the hell?
Mouse wheel spins into you.
Oh shit, Space Jam came out.
Wait, did it?
Did?
I forgot.
Did it come out a long time ago?
It came out like a month ago.
Oh, it did?
All right, let's catch X.
Okay, let's...
Oh my goodness.
Ooh.
Rolling around at the speed of mouse.
That's cool.
Do it again, do it again, do it again.
What?
Rickin don't...
I don't even want to say that.
Oh, that's weird.
This is patting your head
and rubbing your belly at the same time.
All right, I got one more.
I think this is the play here.
Okay, this is the play.
We're on the edges.
Big Chungus is in it.
I hope that's not fake.
I hope that's not a lie.
Big Chungus is in it.
Yeah, fucking right.
What the fuck?
We'll take care of it from here.
He's actually in it.
No, he's not.
Big Chungus is not in the Space Jam movie.
They're not lying for once.
Thanks for the help.
We'll open up the East Dining Hall now.
Thank you.
Look it up.
I'm not looking it up, I don't care.
I'm gonna...
If I look it up, it's real.
It's not real right now for me.
If I look it up and I see it, it's real.
It's not real for me.
I'm sorry.
All right, East Dining Hall.
It would be this way.
Oh, we need a stream reaction.
No, I don't care.
I feel like I'm trying to scan everything
because I don't want to miss anything.
It's locked.
What's with this giant empty room anyway?
Welcome to my extravagant dining potential.
Dear.
Only one of these delicious platters has the key.
I am sure searching will be an addicting game of chance.
Are we going to search all these?
If I get it first drive,
then you have to give me 50,000 community subs.
Oh, key not found.
Did you mean give up?
All the platters got mixed up again.
I didn't say to the debt.
I said I get 50,000 community subs.
Not...
That was the only thing.
There was nothing else for it.
All right, it's gonna be this one.
There's something under this one.
Oh, it's a dog.
Hey, wait a sec.
What's going on?
Oh, you win.
Now we just have to...
It broke it.
What the fuck?
Oh, that was awesome.
Maybe minus the blatant destruction.
Let's go, Chris.
We're almost at the third floor.
No, where's my secret?
Where's my funny joke that's supposed to be in here?
Supreme table.
You won't be able to use this without the throne of the gods.
It's your cousin.
Stop.
That's not what I was doing.
I can't sit at this unless I have the throne of the gods.
Why is it a giant gerbil feeder?
All right, so let's go...
Let's keel down.
Let's keel down this one.
Holdify.
And then we're going to...
No, we're not.
They're not going to do that.
Here's what we're going to do.
What we're going to do is we're going to warmify this one.
And then we're going to keelify.
All right.
Is warm red...
This would be warm this one.
And then you spare this one.
I mean, no.
I got it.
Got a dabbing.
That's still a thing, people think.
You're not still doing that, right?
Are you?
Glow shard.
Where is it?
Oh, it's here.
Shimmering shard.
Its value increases each chapter.
Damn.
Chout.
Oh, God.
Hey, hey.
Chout.
I thought I was supposed to collect them.
They're blue.
They're a different color.
What was that?
It's chocolate milk.
Chris.
Susan.
Glad to see you arrive unwounded.
Now let us hasten.
Here is a secret passageway to the roof.
There we can in-rescue-ify Lady Noelle.
Okay.
Let's go, Chris.
Oh, Chris.
Chris is...
Chris, you and your lackey distract the queen.
Let's go, Susie.
Just the two of us.
Ha ha ha.
Fine.
Whatever.
Chris, do you think of me as your lackey?
You mean...
You think of me as more than a lackey?
Wait, what?
Yes.
I mean, what do you know?
What are you talking about?
You're filled with the power of book holes.
There's a book here about preventing backtracking.
All right, can I...
Is there...
Can I...
What should I do?
I'm gonna go this way first.
What is this?
The knight created the fountain and this world.
It might be even more powerful than Queen.
Now.
Queen has been very interested in this video recently.
Where the knight creates the fountain by its own hand.
Well, it's that and Cyber City's funniest home videos.
This is today's dinner entertainment.
I've heard it's called The Birth of a Fountain.
What an elegant name.
Elegantly...
Soiatic.
We are often forced to star in those videos.
For now.
A video of someone creating a strange pillar of smoke.
There's so much smoke.
It's hard to tell who it is.
Statue of Birdly is wedged in the toilet.
You glance back at the bathroom door sign.
The sign is a silhouette of a Birdly statue.
Everything checks out.
No problem here.
Oh god, not this guy again.
What are they gonna be done in there?
A giant lake of acid?
Oh, you mean the free pool.
You will learn to love it like family.
Why do you have this?
It is my mansion's energy source and fun to drink.
Bye!
How should we pass this?
I suppose this works.
Now I have to think of a way to distract the queen.
Oh, I'm so distracted right now.
Can I like get out on that?
Turning them blue.
What are these little houses?
Just tropical villas for my guest.
Isn't that thoughtful?
How would anybody fit inside?
Shrink from the acid!
Chris, get the banana!
Chris isn't going to do what you say.
Where's the banana?
That's okay, Chris.
It's good for you.
Did I not turn the other one blue?
So we're coming up on a tunnel.
Oh, I didn't turn the other one blue.
How?
I thought I could...
I thought I'd just drive by them.
There's something blocking the way.
I can find some way to get rid of this.
Giant hand.
Okay.
Hey, what's over here?
Nothing.
Oh, shit.
Um, okay.
This one's gonna be here a fucking long time.
This castle looks like it has worn many sieges.
Wait, you can just do this.
What's a...
Wait, doesn't she have...
Oh, no.
That's mist rain or something, right?
Wait, why do you know you don't have it?
Where's mist healing mist?
Oh, shit.
Wrong person.
It's in the well.
Oh, it wasn't yellow.
Oh, that's right.
Pacify on the blue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I...
It's been a while since I've had to pacify somebody.
Ah!
He's losing it.
Okay, it seems...
It seems that peace has returned to the castle.
You opened and got a revive dust.
Revive dust was added to your item inventory.
No, I don't wanna.
Uh-oh.
Let me just click off out of the window
in a place I'm not supposed to click.
Uh-oh.
All right.
Let me just see if I can get over on my fucking Mac.
Let me just...
Uh-oh.
Oh, whatever.
I can't...
I think my computer's frozen.
I'm supposed to do this.
How do I get that?
Because I have to do this up.
Can I go up from here?
No.
How am I supposed to get this?
Oh my god.
What a dummy.
What was that?
You all right?
Is this guy...
Did I talk to this guy or is he gonna fight me?
Thank you for your help.
I had gone up there to do a little house cleaning and got stuck.
Thank you.
Um...
I suppose we'll just have to let it go this once.
How do I...
Can I...
Um, okay.
Is that it?
I can't get over that way?
All right.
He doesn't do anything.
I don't...
I don't remember...
I don't know how to...
I don't know.
I don't know how to do it.
No, I'm done.
I'm done.
I don't...
I don't know how to...
I'm done.
Yeah, I'm fucking done.
Whatever.
This game's like...
It's like just fucking two artists and shit.
It's stupid.
No, I'm done.
I'm done.
That's done.
I don't want to do this.
But what about this over here?
Gamer rage.
Dear guests, please note our mice will turn at every crossing.
Our vermin have been specifically hand picked for higher turning.
I found one dollar.
You didn't get any.
What the fuck?
No, I don't want to...
No!
They found 20 dollars.
Sounds like the bridge was raised.
Drop that.
Ah, it's gonna clap.
Looks like the hand is out of the way now.
Let's go.
Sound of progress, my friend.
Chris.
Hey, Chris.
Is it strange to say it's nice spending time alone with you like this?
I like hanging out.
I like spending time.
But I wouldn't say it's necessarily strange.
What do you mean strange?
I like hanging out.
I'm happy to hear you say that, Chris.
When we first met, I was so nervous about first impressions.
I even hid my face so you wouldn't see.
How do I even be a friend?
All I have to do is be nice is what I thought.
But I'm starting to realize being friends is more than that, isn't it?
Susie.
Sometimes she isn't nice at all.
She's selfish.
She's rude.
She's sarcastic.
But isn't it wonderful that she's her?
Is what I started thinking today.
Of course, Chris, it's nice that you're you.
Just so I could like dot dot dot.
That's not as rude.
It's nice that you're...
Yeah, it's nice that Rousey is Rousey.
But I'm I just wanted I'm really trying to pay attention to the to the dark ride we're on.
I know that like Mickey Mouse is going to jump out a few times.
Can we talk about this after the ride?
Huh?
No one's ever said that to me before.
I mean, everything's a first for me.
But hearing it from you, it means a lot.
I just wonder what being Rousey-like even is.
Well, that is for you to decide, Rousey.
As we asked enough of me to decide this for you to decide.
Sorry, I got off track and I just I missed it.
I missed it.
We turned the corner and fucking Ursula showed up.
And I wanted to see Ursula.
Okay, I missed it.
Let's just enjoy the ride.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wow, Chris, look at all those houses.
I wonder what will happen if we change their color.
Boused worms really slottest.
Mouse had seen the last of me.
Oh, no.
It's Captain...
I don't know this guy's name.
Chips ahoyeth, landlubbers.
Tothouth readyeth to visit David Jones' locker.
Would you not speak with more than one accent?
Yes.
All right.
Oh, Mr. Rules.
I just remembered Lancer.
He's not well.
Oh, dear.
Dinist Hower and Triumph burping him.
Perhaps I'll give them a sip of my ginger ale.
Oh, wait, I have more time to spare on such frivolities.
I must just conquer this island and defeat myself.
Then, I'm doing Captain Crunch.
It's not a bad accent, it's Captain Crunch.
Then gifting her a succulent island present,
the beautiesque queen shall reward me
by making me her left-hand man.
Ah-ha-ha, me the ultimate minion.
Now beholdeth the formeth of thou destroyer.
Wherever this thing is, this again.
Ah-ha, squirming jealousy at my battle caravan
is an effigy of an ancient god of combating.
I rescued this from the king's trap
and fixed it up in this world of scraps up.
It's actually a rejected design we made.
Oh, this is your creation normally, right?
OK, yeah, that's fine.
And soon, thou shalt taste this rejection,
first this in the form of various bullets.
Trash machine reluctantly fights you.
Oh, hold on a second, Goku.
Let me go ahead and tell you how to play.
I know, I know, I was supposed to tell you.
I'm just doing, like, the end of the episode thing.
Wow, I wonder what's going to happen next time.
These two guys are spiting each other.
I wonder what happens.
Hey, hey, hey, save me a piece.
They're always, like, eating food, right?
They're always, like, talking to somebody off screen.
I wonder what's going to happen next time
machine reluctancy fighting for you.
Hey, wait up for me.
Right, why?
Hey, give me, I'll take a piece of that cake.
Take house two.
Take house, take house, take house three.
Oh, man, what am I doing?
We're claiming tile, claim you can take this tile.
Oh, fuck, I don't know what I'm doing.
Claim this house and this one.
Oh, shit, it's one of those things.
Oops.
The rules, pronounced rules, are simple.
Hunker houses, whoever has the most wins.
I wasn't ready for them.
Ow.
Take house four.
Take house two.
You distract.
I'm very confused, I hope I get it.
House distracted.
Rules will place one less house next turn.
I have to go down, as I'm going.
Yeah, yeah, I'm going down.
We're going to take two houses.
We need TP?
Oh.
Shut up, what am I doing?
What happens if we win?
Shit.
We're going to take four houses.
Sorry.
Fuck, dear.
Stop, stop, stop building houses.
I have to win.
Wait, it's not a connect four?
What do I have?
Oh, this dude's a moron.
I mean, he's, I'm winning.
What are you talking about?
You're a dumbass.
Look, I'm supposed to claim,
I don't know what you're talking about.
Kiwi Herman scream.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Fuck, I tried.
I only had a half a second to do that.
I only had a half a second to get that out.
I didn't get like 10 minutes in a booth
getting prepared, okay?
I'm winning.
I'm winning, I think.
I win.
Because, yeah, one, two.
I won.
Seems the game has been over.
I win.
What?
How's doth hath more houses?
Cut the battle.
You won.
Yet, I won.
Yeah, you guys are freaking out for no reason.
You guys are freaking out for no reason.
Ah, ah, ah.
So thou hast triumphed.
Not you have only seen,
but one percentile of my weapons abilities.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Behold, worm, the real power of Rulf card.
God.
You won by one.
I still won.
Look, if I'm in first place,
say we're like running a marathon.
I'm in first place, you're in second place.
And I'm way ahead of you.
I'm like 200,
I'd like, let's say I'm 100 fucking yards ahead of you.
And I fall down.
I trip, I fall, I've scraped my knee.
I roll three times, I get up.
A bird flies in my face, hits me in the head.
Like a bird shits on me.
I stop for a minute.
As long as I cross the finish line before you do,
I won the game, I won.
So what do you care?
I can literally sit down and watch you running towards me.
Just sit down with my legs kind of just crossed,
sitting there waiting for you for a hundred more yards.
Get up and cross the finish line.
I will still win the race.
It doesn't matter how I did it, I came in first.
This is a bad analogy, how?
It's just, if you cross the finish line before somebody else,
you won, it doesn't matter how you got there.
That's right, rules isn't compatible with this world either.
Well, let's go, Chris.
You cheated.
Oh, I cheated?
Yeah, fine.
Let's both do a blood test.
Okay, fine.
Let's both do a blood test and see what's going on.
Looks like the right, oh, it's a good picture.
There's a camera, it's gonna take a picture.
Should we pose?
E-sign, rude gesture.
No, the play, you guys, the play with these things is you,
I try to do this every time.
So you try to figure out where it is.
And then, I don't know, I sometimes do that.
I try to pretend to be asleep or pretend to be crying.
Like with a horrible, like I'm fucking bawling
or just like I'm passed out, like my head over.
Rude gesture.
Oh, I'm gonna give it like the finger hug.
I don't know if I would do that.
I honestly, if I would probably,
I would probably either pretend to be asleep
or that I wouldn't like,
I wouldn't grab the person next to me and hug them.
I would give like the peace sign
or I would give a rude, all right, let's do rude gesture.
What am I doing?
Wait, what is he doing?
Wait, what, what the hell was that?
What the hell just happened?
What has happened?
You know what's kinda funny?
There are some people that if a camera,
they go into like a weird trance.
If a camera exists, they'll just give it the finger.
Do you guys know anybody like that in your life
where it just takes them over?
It's just like, oh yeah, here comes a picture.
Yeah, finger.
It's like, why do you have to do that?
It takes over their brain.
It's almost like the person doesn't really know
what to do with their body or with their arms or hands.
So like raising up a middle finger is enough of a,
like, hey, look, emotional, emotion.
I'm like, look at what I'm doing.
I don't know.
It's like there's some people that just snap
when a camera turns on.
If you go to like their,
like let's say you check out,
like, oh, what do they have on Instagram?
Oh, what's their Instagram look like?
It's just like all pictures have given the finger.
Like, okay, do you have any others?
It's like, oh yeah, like finger, finger, finger,
like given the finger.
Guys on Tinder, yeah, just like, oh yeah, finger.
That's king shit.
But the thing is I kinda have one of those too.
I usually, I'll do thumbs up.
I'll put thumbs up or like peace.
I'll do like thumbs up or like fist.
I put my fist out.
I don't know why.
It's like, okay, I do the thing
that if you were to take a picture with a UFC fighter,
like, oh, hey, hey, I don't know any UFC fighters.
I can't come up with one.
I'm gonna make one up.
Hey, fighter, can I get a fit picture?
And they do that thing with their hands
and they put their like fist up,
like, yeah, I'm gonna knock somebody out.
I do that.
I don't know why.
I put like fist up, two fists, thumbs up, fist.
I have no idea why I do that.
Let's keep going.
Yeah, I'm a big fan of fighter.
I thought just going to leave with me here.
Oh, aren't even going to throw with me the picture.
Why would you wanna take a picture with you?
I don't know.
I don't like, you don't, I'm not looking for that.
If you want one, I'll do it.
Chris, are you wondering how Suzy is doing right now?
I mean, I'll be honest.
I actually forgot the person was in the game.
It's been like a while.
I know I don't, I don't, it's not that I don't care.
Yeah, I've been wondering.
Well, then why don't we close our eyes
and think about what she's doing now.
I don't want, I don't really want to do that.
What a strange moon.
Like nothing I've ever seen before.
This world, I wish Death could see it.
That was bad acting, I'm sorry.
I'll go, I'll be better.
Is somebody there?
Wait, what are you?
Hey, you can't capture someone who's already captured.
Suzy, you saved me.
Don't get used to it.
Okay, I won't.
Cool moon.
Yeah, it's weird, isn't it?
How did we get here?
Now, what even is this place?
You see, a million years ago,
a bomb exploded in the atmosphere.
You know what, it's too much for right now.
It's Evil Queen's Castle or the Dark World.
I mean, aren't both of these things true?
You're just having a dream.
Oh, oh, that's right, right.
If you're here, it must be a dream.
I mean, the real Suzy probably wouldn't save me, would she?
Probably doesn't care about me at all.
Why would you think that?
She doesn't care about anybody.
Well, fair, but did you ever wonder
why Suzy never picked on you?
All the time.
This is kind of an inaccurate, if you were lucid.
If I'm lucid, it's only happened a few times,
but I just started, I'm lucid,
I'm grabbing like the fucking Biro
and I'm throwing it out the window.
I'm throwing it out the window, it's hard as I can.
Like, I'm just gonna start smashing the window.
This is my one opportunity
to like throw a Biro out of the window.
I'm gonna do it.
The second that I feel lucid, it's just like,
oh my fucking God, I'm gonna dream.
Okay, okay, I see a stick over there.
I'm just throwing, I'm gonna javelin the stick
out the window, because like, I'm gonna do that.
That's what I'm doing in my lucid dream.
I'm awake.
You're ruining the moment.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Maybe it's because when she first came to class,
you lent her one of your pencils.
Somebody call me a caveman.
Okay, we're actually ruining this.
Stick, I see stick.
Break something.
Smash.
All right, I'm gonna actually pay attention.
I know.
You lent her one of your pencils.
Like a dumb candy cane looking one or something.
Even though it didn't actually taste like candy.
She remembered your smile and decided to spare you, you know?
That's really specific.
Yeah, well, wait, did you say you ate the pencil?
I mean, look, hey, so do you dream about me a lot?
Well, time for me to get back to my project.
Okay, Susie, hit me with your ax and wake me up.
No, I can't do that.
Why not?
Is this a dream?
I mean, didn't you wanna hang out some more?
Stop voice acting?
You want us to hit A and we'll just read it silently together?
I'm reading it.
I'm that guy for four years.
I guess Birdly can wait a little longer.
All right, let's get out of here then.
Now, the person out four years and Goldfish years.
Should be like, I don't know, probably like a few hours.
All we gotta do is head to the right over this.
Over here on this, wait, this is a dream.
Heart covered Ferris wheel.
God damn, hold up, get on already.
Sorry, what the hell am I supposed to do here?
Chris would know what to do.
Eat moss.
Me caveman, caveman in lucid dream.
Eat moss, break things, smash.
Point and hearts come out.
Did I eat the moss?
I feel like that's weird.
Why would somebody do that?
I'm gonna eat moss.
Actually, maybe Chris wouldn't know what to do.
So, Ferris wheels, huh?
Kinda makes you wonder what car they were built for.
It's different than riding one with Chris.
What the hell's wrong?
You scared of heights?
No, no, I love heights, ha ha.
You're shaking.
Well, maybe I'm a little scared, but I, to be honest,
I actually like scary things.
What do you mean?
When we were little, me and my sister would stay up
and go past our bedtime watching horror movies.
At first I cried, but now it's like watching them
makes me feel comforted.
Comforted?
I guess I do like slime and blood.
Scary, but I can just turn it off, right?
No, it's mostly people that are scary, ha ha.
Just say you mean, you can just say you mean me.
Well, I guess you too, but that's what's nice about you,
you know?
Nice, the hell does that mean?
You're the good kind of scary.
You aren't afraid to break the rules, you know?
Wish I could do crazy stuff like you.
Okay, this is the difference here.
Nuts would be like, nuts would be like I get up
and just start like flossing, right?
Like, that's nuts.
Crazy would be, I see how long I can like hold my breath for.
Which one?
Or like, I see if I can like hang outside the Ferris wheel
with my hands, but like a photo.
Like take a picture of me hanging outside
the Ferris wheel with my hands.
Uh, this is crazy, a smash window.
All right, let's do nuts.
So, um, you could do something crazy right now.
What would you do?
Well, I jump out the window, see?
She gets it.
Huh?
It's a dream, right?
And I'm the fucking weirdo.
This is all you guys, all you guys' favorite character
just said the same goddamn thing that I did.
I'd grow big angel wings and fly as far as I can,
gazing back at it all.
Skyline shining like holiday lights.
Window.
That's kind of beautiful.
Wait, you wouldn't seriously jump out, would you?
No promises.
So, see?
What do you think looking out there?
Me?
Um, I mean, do we kind of, do we say something romantic here?
Do we say something cool?
I think we've already done the cool bit, right?
We already are cool.
Stay cool?
I feel like we've already been cool.
I feel like we've stayed cool for the first,
like, half of this Ferris wheel ride.
I think it's time to do something romantic.
Let's go for it.
Seeing everything small makes me feel like, um,
if I was Susie Zilla or something,
I could wreck the whole city.
Ha ha ha, Susie!
Eh, well, that's romantic.
Is being Susie Zilla something you think about a lot?
Like, no, I just made it up now.
Does your tail always do that when you lie?
Hey, hey, don't look at that!
I don't have a tail, it's part of your dream.
Oh, right, sorry.
Guess I'll just have to check in real life, too.
Hey, don't.
Susie, is everything okay?
Look, I just, I just don't like people knowing about it.
Well, I think it's a nice tail.
Whatever, it's wagging.
All right, do you guys even have dogs?
Anytime you have a dog, if your dog's lying down,
just kinda hanging out, does your dog do this, too?
Where, if you look at your dog, right, like in the eyes,
or if you look over at them and they're just kinda relaxing,
you'll just, you'll just hear that, that's what Otto does.
Like, you look over, you're just sitting there,
you might be playing a game, you're watching TV.
Dog is on your right, they're just,
they're not paying attention to you at all.
They just sense your eyeballs.
You turn and look, it's the cutest thing ever.
Susie's not a dog.
I didn't, I didn't say that Susie was a dog.
You stopped shaking.
Yes, I got comfortable.
Me, too.
Well, that wasn't too bad.
Yeah, if only I could dream like this every day.
All right, at what point do I just go,
all right, hey, this is not a dream.
This is real, this is a real thing.
I just was messing with you.
Maybe it doesn't have to be a dream, you know?
Susie, maybe, maybe someday we could.
Noel, my lady, the cavalry has arrived to rescue you.
Oh, the good part of the dream is over.
It's fine, we're at least gonna help, we're allies.
Yes, don't worry, Noel, I'm stupid now.
He's good.
Look, I gotta go save the day now, all right?
Uh-huh, good luck, Susie.
All right, nugget boy, it's up to you now.
Leave everything to me, my dear Susan.
Yeah, whatever, may the smarts be with you.
Ah, she left before I could.
Noel, it's hard to say this.
You've done so much for me, and I, well, I'm sorry.
Ridley, you're actually apologizing?
Thank you, I understand, you know.
You've always been nice to me when it's just the two of us.
Just wanted to make a happy world for me.
I'm glad you realized it sucked.
Oh.
Huh?
I mean, yes, I was, in a way, apologizing for that.
But I also wanted to apologize for leading you on.
I know you only always helped me out because, well,
you had a crush on me, so.
What?
Oh, sorry, please don't be embarrassed.
It's understandable, but I have to tell you,
I really value your friendship, okay?
So I felt I had to pretend to reciprocate those feelings.
What?
I don't, I never, no, the more I think that I may have
discovered someone else for me.
Huh?
Please don't be jealous.
Of?
Susie.
What?
What, what, what?
Bart, what are you doing, Bart?
That was a bad homer, but I only had a second.
So that's why.
Geronimo.
Hey, miss me?
Of course not.
Yes, kidding, that was sarcasm.
I miss you.
Hey, we gotta work on your delivery.
Anyway, let's go.
Everyone's together, but the wind blows coldly.
You are filled with a certain power.
Why, you little.
Wear, wear wire strongly blocks the way.
Be tough, be sweet, let's be sweet.
And let's do that.
You and Rousey whispered sweetly to wear, wear wire,
pretending not to care, but acts became more effective.
Susie laughed.
It was like a lightning strike.
Okay, now let's be tough.
You and Susie told wear, wear wire you'd beat them up.
The air crackles with fighting spirit.
Rousey winks demurely.
How you doing?
Good?
No, not yet.
Let's be cold.
That's standard.
Let's spare.
You won.
All right, let's do the third floor.
Check here.
Whoa, this statue rocks.
Hey, Rousey, can we take this from my room?
That would be stealing.
You stole the Susie-like statue.
There are all sorts of clothes inside.
Oh, I've never seen Noel wear anything like this.
The search is isoreal cryptid.
It's a cross between ICE and something else.
Hey, Chris, take this for your room.
That would be stealing.
You stole the ICE statue.
Catalogs of search results.
Seems like most things couldn't be made into objects.
It's a bed, go to sleep?
Yes.
Chris, what if Noel came in here?
Yeah, what if she has tics?
Get out of there.
Wardrobe, it's a calendar.
Every page is the last month.
Every day is the 25th.
What's this?
I'm gonna go up top.
Go to the trash zone, trash zone.
Trash, trash, trash, trash, trash, trash, trash.
Am I at the end of the game?
This is it?
I'm not gonna have an opportunity to go to the trash zone?
You're at the end.
Am I gonna go to the trash zone?
You're literally one step away from the end.
I already did the Spampin' thing.
Is there something else there?
Did I already do that?
You don't have to?
You got a few hours left.
No, I don't think that's correct.
No, it's, can I do it afterwards?
There's something there.
Lore, lore.
I'll go after her.
There she is.
Queen, stop right there.
Oh, my sweet idiot children.
You are just in time to witness my world domination.
With Noelle in my possession,
it is only a matter of time before her will turns
and she unleashes her power.
Blaketing the world in.
Too late, dumbass.
Noelle's with Birdly.
Oh, and who is this?
Birdly.
He's been intercepted.
My control plugs are now suitable for teenagers.
Now the whole family can enjoy eternal servitude.
What sort of regal, mostly cruel laughter?
Hee hee hee.
Wait there.
Where's Noelle?
Ho ho ho ho ho ho.
Ha ha ha ha.
I wonder.
I actually know the answer.
Enough already.
Oh dear.
I do sincerely quite like you two.
It would be a shame for me to force you to serve me.
An enjoyable shame.
This is the end.
The queen blocks the way.
Queen defenseless.
Throw.
Group loosen.
All right, we're gonna group loosen on Birdly.
Birdly's gonna get sentient again.
Join the party.
This is a good song.
Everyone loosens Birdly.
Queen, think of the lighteners.
Aren't we supposed to make them happy?
That's not what I'm doing?
Ooh, I didn't know they were gonna move like that.
Shit.
Fountain flows ominously.
Oh shit, I thought that was,
I thought that was her mouth.
I thought that was the big statue
and it actually was her
and that was her mouth opening and closing.
I thought she was like the biggest
to-stay-fuck marshmallow in there.
All right, throw, group loosen again.
No, I'm gonna throw.
Does that need to heal?
Oh, fuck.
We'll do it next time.
Bingo!
I can't, my voice is fucked.
I got too old, I can't do it anymore.
If I talk loudly,
if I yell loudly without screaming, that happens.
I'm too old.
Queen's acid shield is formed.
All right, we're gonna do group toast.
All right, group toast.
That glass of acid is generating her shield.
No, are you gonna drink all that?
No, this is all mine, you can't have it.
Queen sips from her acid.
Each day they spend hours worshiping and glowing rapture.
Our screens are funny animals in Candied Game.
Fucking 10 years of Binding of Isaac
prepared me for that one.
Group toast.
Toast to the queen.
Queen sips from her acid.
Oh, staring, tapping to receive joy.
Staring, tapping to avoid pain.
Easy.
All right, acid shield is down.
We're gonna do group loosen again.
What's he at?
Recently when the town's internet disappeared.
Now the refuge they take in the screens will slowly fade.
I'll drink.
Acid shield is there again.
All right, I'll spare.
He's almost halfway.
I am going to dual heal.
Yeah, let's do dual heal.
And then we're just gonna toast to the queen.
The soul shined its power on Rousey.
Susie made a toast to the queen.
Pretty cool how we're gonna kick your ass.
It's a good thing I have no standards for this.
Queen sips from her acid.
Rousey casts dual heal, there we go.
Well, then who will help her?
For strange and sad searches, who will answer them?
Ooh, that's a weird one.
That's an interesting one.
Toast.
Is what I wondered until the night appeared
and created this wonderful world of darkness.
Smells like overclocked high heels.
Toast, come on.
Expand the dark world.
One more toast.
Here it goes, all right.
End the world covered in darkness.
No one will have to suffer anymore.
All right, let's go for it.
Group loosen again.
He's close.
Everyone can live in my perfect mansion.
Every day blissfully worshiping me like we both deserve.
Drama.
All right, what are they at?
Birdly is almost there.
Red Buster.
No, throw.
Yeah, then we can do a group heal.
No, heal Chris.
Stop resisting and welcome the new age of darkness.
Red Buster.
Is this gonna hurt?
I'm not gonna hurt her.
Let's try it.
See what happens.
Bowser made a toast to the queen.
Toast to you, making me wear a butler outfit.
Bro, that's weird, but okay.
All right, Red Buster.
Ooh, all right, that took a lot down.
What did I say, I would do that?
Oh, that's a weird pattern.
Okay, we're gonna go with...
I'm going to...
I need to do a group heal.
I need the TP.
Which is it?
Do I not have it?
Heal player?
I don't have a group heal?
Fuck.
Oh, wait a minute.
Shit, no, I don't have any more.
Revive's team.
Oh shit, I need 50 TP.
Dammit, all right, we're gonna defend.
All right, he has to play.
No, what am I doing?
Oops, okay.
No, I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
All right, I didn't want to spend all that.
Just don't get hit, bro.
All right, now we're gonna get the bird.
Let's go.
Enough, you foolish children.
You may have survived my attacks regularly,
but I've been secretly, been secretly,
been downloading my ultimate move the whole time.
Perish in the bosom of my hellish reign.
Ooh, that was close.
All right, let's get him.
This should be enough, right?
Group loosen.
Oh, so that final move was supposed to be cooler,
but the internet is down.
Sounds like overclocked high heals.
All right, we need, what do I have?
Revive dust?
Revive's team.
Oh shit, will this work?
Can I revive him, like heal him?
What is he at right now?
All right, he's like there.
Okay, early wire is loose.
What, juice?
I think we got it.
Not bad, you foolish children.
Hmm?
What are you doing?
Why isn't my control wire working?
Thanks to my comrades' kindness, their mercy.
Now, it's time for me to take my freedom.
Queen, you may have mastered the number three,
but can you stand up against four of us?
Warning simulation for the number four.
Hmm, you are definitely going to kick my ass.
Unless, oh no, what that?
Wait, one nanosecond, you cowardette.
Glass.
Birdly?
Ah, just now was nothing more than simple bravado.
Truth is, that wire already absorbed
all of my succulent energy juices.
Birdly, hey, Birdly, are you okay?
Everything getting dark, only a kiss
from a beautiful gamer girl can save me now.
Birdly.
What?
Like, you're like losing consciousness and stuff,
but like, could you speak up?
Ah, sorry, suddenly I'm feeling a bit better.
Hey, that's a relief.
Well, gotta hurry and save Noel, so later.
Hey, Susan, so enigmatic in her ways.
But I can read her heart, Chris, like a health meter.
It's beeping for love.
Well enough tales, Chris, good luck.
May the smarts not be with you.
Okay, Chris, your deep concern for me is dexterous.
Stay sanguine, my fellow blue bird.
I'll find some way to help you out.
If you're going to the trash zone,
this is the point of no return.
If I go right one screen, you're saying?
Should I go all the way back left
or do I have like a shortcut here?
Fuck the lore, don't.
Trash zone is just don't go, don't, who cares?
It's not important, okay.
Oh, whatever.
Night, roaring night, day it deigned
to create this world, reaching its long hand to the sky.
It caused its will into its blade,
made rusting the fountain from the earth.
Unfortunately, the world they created
is trapped within the confines of the library.
If only we had a way to make more darkness,
we might be able to cover the whole world.
That is when I realized this power,
this power of the will, this power of determination.
Is this not something that all lighteners possess?
If one was simply determined enough,
would not anyone make a dark fountain?
So then, if the night has taken its leave,
then I will simply make a new one.
Well, honey, darling, sweetie gravy,
how do you find the giant hand?
Great, but how do you feel about world domination?
Ooh, ouchie, mama.
Susie, you came to save me.
Somehow, I knew you would.
You did?
I mean, I, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You need to get out of here, hurry.
Oh, she is giant.
Yeah, I knew it.
That was the statue I was thinking of, right?
I thought that portal was the mouth.
That's the real mouth.
Queen, seems that you failed to notice
a giant freaking robot in the middle of my palace.
This isn't good, she's invincible like this.
Huh?
She's been bragging about her final form all day.
Think growing a few inches is gonna help?
Yes.
Are we cool to take over the world now?
Susie, let's just give up,
and hell if we're giving up now.
Susie, what if you got another form?
We've got one too.
Chris, Rousey, come on.
God, what are you guys doing?
This is our ultimate.
Wait a second, now that you mention it.
Oh no, it appears I'm evenly matched.
I hope you won't mind if I don't hold back.
We're falling.
Any bright ideas on how we're gonna get out of this?
We could try flapping our arms.
Fear not, your knight in glow in the dark armor is here.
Early?
Chris, Susie, my energy is still too low
to help you fight, so I found help for you.
Behold, comrades, on your quest against the queen,
you've made all sorts of buddies, right?
Using our junk-making skills, we modify everyone
to work together.
I shall take credit for this.
The man of a million voices, five.
Chris, Susie, behold, the ultimate group project
with a splendid base.
My strongest JPEGs.
Oh wait, no.
Flashing lights.
Happy bravery.
My energy.
Tender loving care.
Fresh cooking.
Organization.
And most of all, whatever's missing in.
Oh my goodness, what is going on now?
Finally, a worthy opponent.
What?
Oh shit, here we go.
It's the fighting game.
Giga Queen blocks the way.
All right, Giga Queen.
Laser mode turbo dodge.
Self-fix.
Did I attack?
Or should I build TP and then do the other stuff?
Oh, time for the words is, the time for words is over.
Now is time to fight only.
Oh fuck, I didn't know we were doing this right now.
What are the buttons?
Cityscape roars past.
All right, Giga Queen.
All right, let's go.
Just kidding, I totally will keep monologuing
as I kick at your face.
Nice.
The night is young for fighting.
Self-fix, how am I doing?
I think I got plenty of health.
Time has come for Noelle to realize her own strength.
Her own will, her own determination.
Fuckhead.
Rousey advises you to dodge then counterpunch.
What do you think I've been doing?
Uh-oh.
Focusing into her blade,
she will create a neo-dark fountain.
Then another, then another.
Oh wait, it's one, one, one, one, one.
Queen's attacks just got tougher.
Then when the whole world is covered in darkness,
she and everyone can live in bliss
free of fear and suffering.
Okay, I gotta learn the fight.
Self-fix.
First Susie, why don't you help me to
create the world of your dreams and not of my dreams?
Susie, bro, just let me karate chop you
and you can have as many skateboards as you want.
Um, laser mode?
Laser mode.
Light quick aura fired up.
Oh shit.
And Chris, my dearest Trucy, you can have as many?
Hey, I don't remember what you liked.
Ah, phase three incoming.
Oh, it hurt.
Gotta heal.
Round three.
The attacks are extreme now.
All right, I need 30% TP.
Get it right here.
Hey, was there a third guy?
Ah!
Oh, I go through the legs.
Shit, I need more turbo dodge.
No.
Join me and all of you will become super strong and cool.
Meanwhile, I don't need to improve
because I'm already perfecting
to shoot lasers from my fancy glass.
Shit.
Shit, let me give me a chance to fucking hit ya.
I believe I've made my point.
I'm going to procedurally loop my dialogue now.
Here we go.
Whoa, that was a new move.
All right, turbo dodge?
No.
Again.
All right, now it's time to heal again.
No, yes, heal.
Heal!
Hey!
You have truly proven yourself to be worthy of learning.
You have earned the right to remember
what your fighting machine's true purpose is.
To get your own ass thrashed by me.
That's my final attack.
Bye.
Shit.
What the fuck is an Omega Baseball?
I get it.
Battle power dropping.
Overheat activated.
Listen well.
You may have defeated me,
but I still possess one thing.
You three will never have.
Detachable hands.
Was I supposed to punch that?
Did I lose?
Noel, honey, sweetie.
Gravy, take the pin I gave you
and stab the earth, creating our new supreme empire.
I.
What's wrong, Noel?
I know it would make you happy.
Or should I, with the last 1% of my battery,
push Susie into eight bits?
Leave?
Leave Susie alone!
You think listening to you makes me happy?
No, I'll never be happy if I'm controlled by you.
Why can't you understand that?
That was acting class.
That was like, okay, if you have a room
with like 100 people in an acting workshop,
that's like, that was like how I did it, you know,
in my acting classes.
Sometimes you just like, you blow out like the first workshop
and then like when you get the second assignment,
like you go nuts, you're a fucking lightning rod.
You act your ass off in the first like 20 minutes,
30 minutes of the class and you don't want to do anymore
and you're kind of just done.
I'm not gonna go like 100 miles per hour again.
Perhaps my computations were miscalibrated.
Noel, disregard me and with your own power,
choose the world that makes you happy.
Queen?
Queen, are you okay?
Seems she ran out of battery power.
Guess we can seal the fountain now, right?
Everybody?
Queen, she said, choose the world that makes you happy.
Don't want to live in a world ruled by her.
That wasn't the case.
Wonder if this world wouldn't be so bad.
Huh, Lucy, don't you think so too?
Oh, you mentioned it.
Chris, isn't this world just better?
You make so many friends here, you know?
I've never had an adventure like this before.
Axes and battles and magic.
Everything can be healed with a little spell
and no matter what happens, no one tells us what to do.
Gosh, yeah.
So even if things were really scary just now,
I mean, is there any reason not to?
Not that I can think of.
Me neither.
Then, Noel, let this be my real apology.
Concentrating my will into this blade,
I will make a new fountain and unleash a bright future.
A future that shines for us.
A future whose brightness is born from darkness.
Stop.
What in the world are you all doing?
You realize what will happen if you do that?
You'll just, you'll bring the roaring.
When the light is subsumed by shadow,
when the fountains fill the sky,
all will fall into chaos.
I can do anything.
Titans will take form from the fountains
and envelop the land in devastation.
I had an opportunity to do that in Armand's voice
because it's like the Armand voice
I've been doing the whole game.
Surviving darkners crushed by the darkness
will slowly, one by one, turn into statues,
leaving the lighteners to fend for themselves,
lost eternally in an endless nightmare.
I thought it was gonna be a nightmare.
Is that your idea of paradise?
Oh, damn, I did not know that.
You didn't?
But your whole plan was to...
I'm just a computer laughing my fucking ass off.
I didn't, I don't know everything.
I was just guessing based off the night's actions.
Why the heck, hell, would I want to end the world?
That's a relief.
Sorry, I, after everything,
I just caused trouble for you again, Noel.
That's okay, Birdly, I understand.
I thought about it while charging my battery.
You cannot calculate other people's feelings.
You understand how I feel?
Not really.
I just don't want Noel to be sad.
Well, I'm glad you two kind of get it now.
Yes, we all made a pretty sweet team in the end.
I was just the judge in the acid.
No, we freaking didn't.
Can you let go of us now?
Oh, yeah.
Suzie?
Hey, you stood up to the queen, not half bad.
Really?
Yeah.
Just guess you gotta wake up soon, huh?
Huh?
Everything got so intense, I forgot it was a dream.
And I just hope I get to have more dreams like this.
Hey, Noel, when you wake up,
when you wake up,
well, I just wanted to say.
Well, then I suppose it is time for you all to exit.
Running program, tendergoodbye.exe.
I will miss each and every one of you.
Well, your unneeded honesty.
Suzie, your foolish bravery.
Chris, your chill vibes.
Birdly.
Doesn't have to be goodbye, queen.
Chris can take you back to our castle town.
You and all our recruits can live there.
Oh.
Leading tendergoodbye.exe.
All right, time to do what we came here for.
Hey, Noel, if you see the real Suzie,
just know that maybe she's.
Look, she doesn't have a tail, okay?
Okay, got it.
Just go, Chris.
Everybody's laughing.
Chris.
Looks like we're here again.
Roaring night.
Whatever they are.
We're making these fountains.
But is that really a bad thing?
Since they started showing up,
everything's gotten a lot more interesting, hasn't it?
Well, we don't have to think about it that now.
I'm doing Obama?
I'm not trying to.
Chris, it's your turn.
It was as if your very soul was going.
Guitar riff.
Okay.
What happened?
Oh, it was a dream, wasn't it?
A dream?
That was all a dream?
Of course, that must have been a dream.
Such feelings, such thoughts.
Oh, sweet lady of justice.
You think I would ever think Suzie would be.
Suzie?
What are you doing here?
You invited us to study, remember?
Oh, right.
What, studying with them?
Noelle?
Heavens to yikes, they're...
Well, I guess we could try it.
My alarm.
I'm gonna be late for shift with Miss Boom.
Oh no, how is it that late already?
Well, adieu everyone.
I must gather my book longings.
How I love the texture of freshly picked up books.
Now, let us hasten, my dear Noelle.
Good day, Chris, Suzie.
Bye, Chris.
And bye, Suzie.
See ya.
What, what are you looking at for something?
Nothing, nothing, nothing, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
I think it's her problem anyway.
When you treat someone who just saved the world.
Look at me.
Chris.
Hey, wait a second, Chris.
We just actually saved the world, didn't we?
Damn, we really are heroes.
And no one even knows.
This is better that way though, right?
Freak out if they knew the world's in danger.
Well, it kind of sucks Noelle has to forget too.
Whatever, let's get out of here.
The recycling bin.
Looks like someone accidentally printed off
a lot of useless emails.
Full of many backup devices like extra mice,
extra keyboards, or extra maracas.
What's back here?
Closet is spacious and full of old electronics.
Large person could easily fit inside.
Computer, the monitor is flickering brightly.
The trash can, you get the feeling
it doesn't have any friends.
Hard to explain why you feel this way about a trash can.
Before you left, you gathered up everything in the room.
I love reading books, especially the books upstairs.
I love reading, especially books.
I love reading books.
Man, it got late, didn't it?
Guess you should go home, huh?
All right, you don't have to say it.
Don't wanna walk home by yourself, huh?
Well, if you're gonna make me, I guess.
Let's go.
You're gonna make an apartment?
Nah, just here to hang out.
I see.
I can actually go in all the way in here.
Silver, Drake, I've never beaten this boss before.
All right, hand it over, honey, I got this.
No, Dad, this is my battle.
So, how about just telling me what to do?
Sure, how about trying fire shock?
I'd love to, Dad, but the mage left the party.
Oh yeah, how about one of your 99 blaze potions?
Oh, I'm saving those.
What, your birthday?
Come on, little, little.
Hey, Dad, this one's for you.
Hi-ya, it reflects fire attacks.
Oops, hey, you gotta heal.
I wish I knew healing magic in real life
that it'd make you better,
and it wouldn't just be me and Mom.
Your mother is, hey, it's okay, sweetheart,
I'm getting better.
I might even be able to go to church tomorrow.
Really, are you sure you're okay?
Holidays happen whether you like it or not.
Even though everyone likes holidays?
Well, gotta go home soon or Mom will call.
See you tomorrow, honey.
Hi, Dad, love you.
Susie, what are you doing here?
All right, guys, this game's only one player.
Dad, this is Susie.
Oh, this is Susie.
Susie, and I heard a lot about you.
Dad, stop that.
You have?
Cool, think I have to go now.
Susie, huh?
Lay a finger on her and I'll kick your ass.
Huh?
I'm just kidding.
Well, kind of kidding.
Hey, Chris, why are you checking the sink?
That's what I'm asking, sweetheart.
I don't know.
Sorry, I used up a lot of my energy just now.
Probably not gonna be very fun to talk to.
Thanks for visiting, though, Chris.
And you too, Susie.
Susie, current situation?
No, well, current situation?
Seems like I need some more tests.
So just gotta wait it out.
They can't keep me down for too long, baby.
Sooner or later, I'm busting out of here.
Besides, your dad ain't much without his main man.
What does this say?
Is your name Rudolph Rudy Holliday?
Hey, Chris, you forgot my name or something?
Looks like she's resting her voice.
Look inside the cupboard.
Very small obligatory piano is hiding inside.
Okay.
Well, Chris, you can play the piano.
Whoops.
There's more?
Yeah.
Let's just see what else is here.
Susie.
Hey, Chris, she's a nice girl, huh?
The hell are you talking,
the hell are you taking her here for?
Why don't you take her to the movies?
Hey, yeah, the hell didn't we go to the movies, Chris?
Yeah, and take me too while you're at it.
Yeah, Chris, come on.
Kettle corn, Chris, big.
Don't skimp out.
What is it?
Crispus.
Look, Chris, can't say much, but,
well, might look like she has it all.
Her mother, mother, you know.
Love her, but she's tough on her.
Normally, I balance it all out.
I can't do much when I'm not there.
I'm gonna get better.
I have to.
Bees of the toy march on.
Uh-oh, Alfie's, hell if I'm gonna go any further.
Already close enough to getting banned from school.
Don't wanna be banned from outside of school, too.
That's a thing, right?
Hi, Chris, getting your project done?
Oh, my bike, it's, I had a little crash.
You see, there was this police officer
and it's complicated, how are you doing?
Chris, it's no secret, the police in this town are,
how do I put this?
Just eye candy, I guess.
Wait, wait, wait, I came out wrong.
I mean, they're symbolic, they barely do anything.
It's because of the mayor, there isn't any crime.
Makes me wonder if she even needs the police
or if they're just getting in her way.
Sorry, I'm just saying what you already know.
After all, she's your neighbor, right?
Did you need something?
What's cool?
How's your project going with Susie?
What, you went to the library together?
With Noelle and Birdley?
That's amazing, Chris.
And while you were there, this has nothing to do with me,
but the Teen Zone seems to have some good anime reviews,
you know, I'm not sure if you and the gang were,
I'd check that out as you studied the anime.
Next time you go, you might want to casually bring that up
among your fellow teens.
I know your dad liked Miu Miu 2, at least.
Again, nothing to do with me, yeah.
We're the infamous dog burglars, the Wet Nose Bandits.
We're getting ready to sneak into that big house
over the holidays.
We were attacked from the shadows by something merciless.
Fearing for our lives, we ran right into the office,
Undyne's warm, loving arms.
She suplexed us all into the snow
with our tails hanging in the air.
Now we're in jail, but at least we're alive.
Plus, that nice ghost keeps giving us
corporately low-calorie treats.
And we all howl holiday songs together.
Oh, oh, oh!
Did I say that key?
Hey, get out of the road!
Oh, sorry, bad habit.
Anything I can help you with, punk?
Dark World.
Oh, a super dangerous alternate world in the library?
More are appearing, people might fall inside.
Listen, punk, you seriously think I'm gonna believe that?
Dark World.
Oh, seriously?
I love those guys, I hope they show up.
Hey, wait.
No, not again.
Looks like I gotta go recap to those criminals.
Hey, by the way, that yellow glasses lady,
she a teacher, she kinda had an accident earlier
with her bike.
Just wanted to make sure she was feeling better.
Give her this.
Got a heart-shaped box of candies that says,
Get Well Soon.
It has to, it has to your bike hastily scrawled
underneath the Get Well Soon.
Look, Get Well Soon's all the store had.
Open it and I'll arrest you, look.
I'll even put a note on it.
Now stop interrupting me, I gotta go.
Got the previously described box of candy
with a note on it.
Oh, jailbreak.
I'll solve the alarm.
I gotta go, wait no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta get the candy, I gotta get the candy,
candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy.
Candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy, candy.
Do you have something for me?
Here.
Oh, Chris, what is that you're giving me?
A box of heart-shaped chocolates?
Oh, no, no, no, no, I can't accept that from you.
What, it's from the police?
You mean she's giving me this Get Well Soon gift to my bike?
There's a note on this that says,
open this and I'll arrest you, you little punk.
Chris, tell her I appreciate it.
Hey, Chris, shouldn't we check on Lancer?
You should be back in the school closet, right?
Sant!
Oh, oh!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, what's up?
Occupation.
Hey, you the boss around here?
Oh, me?
I'm just the janitor.
And where's the cashier?
Hey, cashier?
We don't have one.
And who do we buy stuff from?
Hey, me.
And that makes you the cashier?
Nope, I'm the janitor.
I'm just filling in.
Are there any other employees?
Nope.
And why don't you hire somebody else?
Whoa, you think I can afford that on a janitor salary?
It's Bertie.
Hey, I'll let you talk.
It's Bertie Sanders.
New voice, I'm trying to remember what I did last time.
Hey, what's up?
Sorry, kid, the brother thing's gonna have to wait.
How long?
Maybe a day, maybe another two years.
Who's keeping track at this point?
Hey, what's up?
Welcome to the convenience store.
You wanna buy something?
Put it in the basket and bring it over here.
In case you didn't know what the store was.
Hey, hey, you forgot something?
Yes, I think I left my eggs on the counter.
Guess your memory's not what it's cracked up to be.
Hee hee hee.
There's really egg on my face now, is there not?
You're egg-scused.
Now it sounds as if you're egging me on.
Egg on or egg off, I expect a lot from you.
Well, I am exceptional, hee hee hee.
Don't forget me, you're Egg's husband.
Hello, Asgore.
Hurry, I didn't expect to see you here,
but I have some extra flowers and I was wondering if...
Oh, I was just about to go, actually.
Oh, sure.
Home is where the heart is, isn't it?
So when Asriel comes home...
Yes, we should all discuss that together soon.
Donkey, donkey, say hi to Chris for me.
Of course, have a nice day.
You know what I want, bone man?
Uh, yep.
Free pickles.
Why, thank you.
Uh, can I ask, what kind of flowers do you think
would make her remember how she felt before?
Uh, maybe you should talk to your plants about that one.
Uh, I tarnished it.
Why, what happened?
Ha ha, don't worry, they're the first ones I asked.
They said good listeners, you know, flowers.
Well, yeah, nothing like a captive audience.
Ha ha, he's changing.
Yes, ha ha, I keep them in glass.
He's turning into...
What's he turning into?
Yes, ha ha, he's turning into Barney Rubble.
Uh, that's the same shit happened last time in Undertale.
Uh, like that movie.
Yes, yes, it's very similar to that movie.
Uh, well, have a good one.
I'm trying.
Hey Chris, um, nevermind.
Yeah, I'm the sicko that looks at all the milks
to find the best expiration date.
You got something about it?
Sometimes the hoofed girl comes here,
opens the freezer door, then stands in front of it
lost in thought.
I guess she really likes the cold or waffles.
Okay, well that's cool.
Sands runs the convenience store.
Can I do that?
Loose eggs, one dollar.
It's too much responsibility for an egg.
What time is it?
All right, I told the tip of the hats guys
that I was gonna be around around six,
and we're at six o'clock right now,
so am I almost done?
School has a save point.
Save your game in the school.
There's like 15 minutes left.
Let me just reel.
I'm gonna go to BRB screen for a second
because I wanna see how long they're gonna go for.
See if I can go another 15 minutes or so.
Give me one second.
I just wanna hit up...
I'll be right back, and I'm gonna pee too.
All righty.
I dropped a few messages to them.
We're gonna go until, I guess maybe they...
until somebody says, hey, come on over.
I think we have probably another 10 to 15 minutes,
so let's do it.
I'm gonna keep this open so I don't miss a message though.
All right.
Keep that open.
There we are.
Okay, good.
Go back to the school to save your game.
Okay.
You kids came out of the library, didn't you, studying?
How wonderful.
Personally, I hate libraries, but...
There's like 10 minutes left.
Yeah, I don't need to explore every single little thing.
If I wanna talk to every single citizen,
I can do that, like on my own time.
Faintly, faintly, a trussle growing further away.
Everyone?
Knock, knock, knock.
Ooh, is that a human?
If humans are made of bones, where does skeletons come from?
All right, let's head to the school.
We'll complete it.
Somebody said you could have finished it
in the time that you've been gone?
Well, I wanted to tell them,
because we kind of said that around 6 o'clock.
I told them and see what they were up to.
I wanna make sure that I'm communicating, right?
Oh, hey, that's my trash from other people's houses.
Like, privacy much?
God, living with Azzie made you weird.
Like, a little Chrissy, you hear,
that guy at the pizza place.
God, what was his name?
Pizza Pants?
Already got, like, a super hot girlfriend.
What was her name?
Like, uh, pizza-rina?
Anyway, what did you, like, wanna talk?
Okay.
Chrissy, like, guess what?
Today, I, like, went to the beach to play with my uke,
and, like, guess who's already there?
That copycat playing the same song I wanted to play.
Oh, my God, cat on the beach, grody.
Did she, like, get lost looking for the litter box?
So, like, I try to, like, play the same song, too,
to, like, you know, assert my ukulele dominance,
and we end up, ugh, get this,
playing the whole song together.
Like, oh, my God, who does this girl think she is?
She thinks she can just, like, harmonize with me?
Uh, I can't stand her.
Little Chrissy, come to visit me.
I'm a real alligator, aren't I?
Oh, my God, it's, like, so sweet
you have a nasty, dirty little friend.
But, like, this is my polluted alleyway,
so, like, I think I might have to go to the mayor
and get a traffic sign that says, like, uh, no plus funds
because, like, okay.
What is that?
Hey, Chris, this free milk is amazing.
It just magically refreshes itself every night.
Hey, Chrissy, like, guess what?
Today, I, like, oh, wait, I already did this.
Okay, that's, all right, let's go.
I wanna explore!
All right, let's go to the school.
I'm gonna, let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Whose house is this?
It's down?
Where's the school?
The school!
Oh, it's the church.
Just a spot.
Nothing like admiring the great paint job
me and my bro did on our church.
Haul, no sense of direction.
Well, I mean, I haven't been here in a long time.
Graveyard?
One of my best ideas came from the dreams.
You can rest here if anyone asks your writing.
He's confused west with east again.
I feel like I could literally walk around here
for, like, an hour and a half
and just listen to every single thing.
And I'm probably gonna do that.
I'll do that, like, later tonight before I go to bed.
I do want to be, I don't want to just cut into their time.
I did tell them a certain time.
Let's go ahead and end the process here.
Go right, down and left, right at the library to finish.
School is not the end.
Yeah, I have the game saved, like, 10 minutes before this,
so that's fine.
So this is, is the school ending game?
Just finish it?
End of the game is your, yeah.
I'll, I can walk around.
I'm gonna do this probably on my own time.
Just explore everything and talk to everybody.
We can finish the game.
So what, where's the houses?
The secrets after the school?
Yeah.
Oh, the school is a save point.
Ah, all right, but I want to, like,
I want to end the game, though.
Do school first.
Door is locked.
What the fuck?
No, wait, you made me go in the school.
You said there was a save point.
What the fuck?
So this is your castle town.
It's not bad.
Chris, Susie, on behalf of everyone, I oppressed.
Thank you.
Oh, the save point in the town, okay.
I'm going to be your wacky roommate now.
I thought you guys were putting me
to, like, the next part of the game.
Chris, I bet you have a lot of people to talk to,
but you don't have to do everything at once.
Save and take a break.
I know, you're in chat right now.
Where's the save point, up here?
You thought about how you can't go back
to the cyber world anymore.
You considered this carefully.
Okay, there we go.
Now let's complete the game.
Now let's go home.
Then I can come back here and walk around
and talk to everybody.
So now home is where from here?
Yeah, it's at the top of the town somewhere, right?
This is it here.
All right.
Chris, you going home?
Yep.
All right.
Then I guess it's goodbye for today.
See you tomorrow, Chris.
Chris, how was studying with your...
Why, Chris, is that your friend?
I did Spampton already, yeah.
Why don't you invite her inside?
Uh, I mean, I...
Chris, I should probably get going.
And I was going to bake a pie.
Did you want anything?
I guess I can come over for a bit.
Feel free to come in.
Oh, excuse me. I'm Chris's mother, Toriel.
Yes, ma'am, I remember.
Oh, you do? And you are Suzy, are you not?
Oh, you...
You remember my name, too?
Of course. Miss Alfie is a good friend of mine.
She often talks about you.
Glad to hear it.
What the hell is Alfie saying about me?
Suzy, why don't you wash your hands over there?
Then we can make the pie together.
Make it together?
But I don't know how to.
Do not worry, I can teach you.
Okay.
Chris, Suzy seems like a nice girl.
I'm very happy you're friends with her.
But, Chris, I heard from Alfie about her behavior.
If by any chance she influences you...
Leave the chalk alone, alright?
Hands washed.
Wonderful. Now we can...
Oh, Chris, how about you show Suzy how to bake it?
Chris, you know how to make pie?
The hell have you made me any for? What dumbass?
You pie hoarding piece of...
I mean, excuse me, ma'am.
Suzy, you can just call me Toriel outside of school.
Oh, okay, sweet.
Uh, Chris, oh, you need to wash your hands too.
And I suppose I shall teach Suzy for now.
Suzy and I will start getting ready to make the pie.
Wait, what?
It's a TV.
They're making a pie.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
She's sneaking sugar right out of the bag.
Suzy?
What?
My pie, my rules.
Got it.
I couldn't do that.
Is the bathroom sink?
Will you run the tap?
Yes.
It started to run.
It's making a lot of noise.
Oh, not this again.
Why does it keep doing this?
I mean, dude, there are way better ways to hide
you shitting in the bathroom, by the way.
Well, let us get the flour.
That's this, this bag.
And you just... oops.
Oh, Suzy, you have flour on your nose.
Oh, I meant to do that.
I thought you would stop to smell the flour, eh?
Come on.
Now, on to the next part.
Where the... where the heck is Chris?
Oh, Chris does this sometimes.
Well, they should hurry.
I'm getting sleepy.
You know what they call a sleeping Suzy?
Uh, what?
They would call her a snoozy.
Uh, haha.
Then... and I guess you'd be, uh, Snoriel.
Hahaha, Snoriel!
Snoozy and Snoriel!
Uh, yeah, you really liked that one, huh?
Wasn't it funny?
Alright, where the hell is Chris?
Pie is nearly done.
Oh, the sugar.
Wait, here a moment.
I left it in the car.
Okay.
What?
Does it get the heart?
Okay, this is some, like, this is some weird shit.
He's taking the heart out and he's, like, killing people
in town or something.
He takes the heart out and he just does some weird shit
outside.
What is he doing?
Why does he keep doing that?
Hey, Chris, hurry up next time.
We're already almost done.
What's next?
Is they?
Oh, they go by they them.
Okay.
We already worked quite hard, have we not?
How about we finish it later?
How about we finish it?
Uh, okay.
Then I guess I'll walk home.
Oh, no, there's no need to do that.
Oh, actually.
Susie, would you like to stay over?
Huh?
I mean, um, if it's okay, then
here come the chimpanzees.
Here comes the chimpanzee.
Everyone's, why, what's going on?
I have to, every, every character that I control
is always just becomes, like, me
in a way.
As I'm walking around.
I tend to just say he
because I put it as me, essentially.
That's kind of how it works for me.
Yeah, that's fine, that's cool.
It always kind of becomes like an extension of me.
Like, walking around in a circle.
If that makes any sense.
Oh, hey, look at this!
Our couch is used to being used as a bed.
It's not perfect, but we could all sleep out here.
We could all sleep out here?
That sounds too, oh, get the sleeping bag!
Splendid, I'll make sure everything's in order.
So why do I keep ripping my heart out
and attacking people or something?
Just call your parents, will you not?
Yeah, of course.
So, what the hell, what the hell, a sleepover?
I haven't had one of those in forever.
We're gonna watch every single episode of Rugrats.
All of them.
It's not like someone has to tell you to sit, right?
Here, chill out for a sec.
So now what?
I got it.
Maybe between the pillows here.
Here, I knew I'd find the boat in there.
You can always find good stuff wedged in the couch.
Geez, it's dusty.
When did you last use this thing?
Well, who cares, it's just watch TV.
So, what are we gonna marathon tonight?
Blood Crushers 3, Hellbusters,
Invasion of the Catpetters.
Maybe Icee, the movie's more your speed, huh, Chris?
Ha ha ha ha!
What a good day, huh, Chris?
You, Rousey, Lancer, everyone.
It's cool hanging out together.
That's why, you know, don't you think we should
try to have them come to our world?
Come on, think about how much better it would be.
Lancer could do our homework,
Lancer could live under your bed.
We could all walk to school together.
Perfect, you know?
Maybe we'd be unstoppable, is what I'm saying.
Um, I don't know.
That seems, doesn't that seem,
isn't it like a different world?
I feel like that's like a, it'd be hard to do that.
We could try.
That seems, I don't know, that seems a little far-fetched.
What? Come on, it'd be easy.
Rousey looks like your mom, right?
Just say he's a long-lost cousin, it'd be easy.
Lancer could even make him a fake mustache.
Oh, whatever, let's just get back to watching.
Well, the festival's coming up, right?
The thing where the town becomes a carnival?
Stupid, right?
Say you had to take someone.
Noelle or Rousey.
I would probably take,
I honestly would probably go with Rousey.
Like you and Noelle could,
you could do that, right?
I'll take Rousey.
Why are you saying it's so confused?
It's not like I meant anything weird.
You know what? Forget it.
Well, no, I'm just saying like you and Noelle
can go, will go, like,
you and Noelle,
we'll just go, why can't we just go together?
Now this is what I'm talking about.
Giant monster movie special.
I always like the better than the giant human movies.
Now this is something we can marathon.
Are you ready, Chris?
12 hours of building-bashing, car-crunching action
because we are locked in, got it?
Better not see you move until your eyes bloodshot.
Now let me just get comfortable here.
Zuzi fell asleep.
Already? That tends to happen though, it really does.
What is going on? Why does this keep happening?
Oh, I thought
the heart was going to come out again.
Officer, officer.
Thank goodness, I finally got through.
I thought I saw someone
prowling around outside.
And when I checked our car,
the tires looked like they'd been slashed.
Officer, if you could please come over.
You will soon, thank you.
They're already asleep.
It's not going to happen again, right?
Maybe it will? Oh god.
It is again. Oh god.
Oh, you're making the fountains.
You're making the fountains.
You're making fountains.
Why? Chris is the knight.
Are we going to get the
hahahaha
Come on, do it.
Well, shit.
What's going on? This feels weird.
Oh, I thought it was crashing.
I thought it was a skipping CD.
Alright, that was cool. That was good.
You want me to give it a rating?
Give it a rating. Alright, I'm going to give that one A.
I refuse to rate it until the whole thing's up.
There you go. Number three.
That was very good though. That was really fun.
That was exactly what I thought
it was going to be. Exactly what I expected.
The weird part about this is I'm surprised.
This is going to be seven chapters.
That seems like a lot.
That seems like a lot more
to do. Seven.
See, when you're 50.
Toby said three to five
chapters coming out around the same time.
You know, that would make sense.
There's another route for
three, four, five in the same release.
This is no longer free anymore, right?
Chapters three, four, and five are a paid thing.
So they're going to be one
thing that's paid, right?
Look, being able to actually
just check it out, because this is called the demo.
You get the first two chapters for free and then if you want to
pay for it and you like it, you can just keep going.
That's cool.
That's really cool.
It's been four, eight.
The first time I played through was like
six or seven maybe. It's like almost
15 to 18 hours of content I've
gotten for free.
I absolutely would pay for the next ones, for sure.
There's a lot more to see. Alright, I am going to
send you guys, because we're
pressed for time. There's not going to be an outro
to this stream. What's going to happen here is
I'm going to send you guys over to the tip of the hat stream
right now, and I will
see you if you go over there and you want to hang out.
I don't know how much longer.
I think they're going to be live for a little bit longer.
I'm going to go from there. I'm going to take a quick
little break. We're going to raid the tip of the hats.
I'm going to go to the
bathroom. I'm going to go to the water.
I will be appearing on that stream very
shortly. I will see you guys next weekend.
We'll go on Saturday of
this next week exactly. I'll see you Saturday, Sunday,
next weekend. Weekend, day, and day at it again.
I'll see you guys soon.
Go hang out at the tip of the hats if you want to see.
I think we're going to play, what's this called?
Gartic Phone?
I'm going to play Gartic Phone.
So I don't know how much longer that stream's
going to go for, but maybe at least enough
for it to hang out for an hour or so. I'm not sure.
Alright, let's raid.
I will see you guys later. See you next weekend. Thank you.
Delta Room was really good. It was awesome.
It was a great experience. Happy to have had it with you.
See you next weekend. Goodbye.
Good night. Take care of yourselves.
See you soon.
There's so many fucking boogers in my nose.
Oh my god, hot bike!
See you guys later.