All right, how long does it take to pee? Oh, not that long. I just was moving some stuff around.
Okay, hold on. Talking to Transformer. That's fine. Do Sam and Max? No. No, no, no, no, no,
because we're only going to do this for like an hour or two and Sam and I don't want to start
season three of Sam and Max and only do like, you know, get like halfway through an episode.
It's too late for Sam and Max. I'm sorry, guys. I'm going to crush your dreams here.
Jerma hates Sam and Max. I played the first two seasons already. Just hold on. We'll do it
eventually. Everybody needs to slow down. Well, that's not in the right place. I have to turn
this down. Hey! My hair is so fucking long. It looks so stupid. This needs to be moved to here.
Don't move. All right, let's get this also on the screen because that is the actual
Transformer. A lot of white space, but it's okay. All right, talk to Transformer.
Let's wait. We should get a custom prompt. Okay. How about small in this? Okay. Another
six flags reviewed now. This is bright as hell in here too. I'm like getting washed out here.
That looks better. Prompt. How about you do E3 predictions, now do an E3 review.
Okay. How about with my drink? Let me tell you a sad story. All right. How many sake has it been?
Let's see. The Japanese can really eat just about anything from rice and noodles to fruit,
vegetables, and more. There have long been delicious Japanese options in grocery stores and
home kitchens. If you can't find sake in grocery stores, you're probably getting it
shipped to Japan from overseas and is being sold in convenience stores or on convenience
food trucks. If you happen to live in Japan, if you're a veteran of the nation, then you
probably know where the best sake is. Sake lovers don't need to read the Japanese and need
only to look closely to see a big difference with what comes in every Japanese grocery store.
Japanese convenience store sake makes the largest selection of local Japanese sake available
in the country and is located in downtown Tokyo. On some days, a selection of sake makes
our pick at a grocery store. If you're wondering if it's a sake or just water,
we really aren't sure. Sake and water. The most common question we get from our Japanese
customers is what kind of sake their Japanese food is. Most don't have a clear definition
of what they are calling a sake and how you will know if your product is sake.
In reality, we are talking about a whole different animal our customers are. If you
don't know the difference between sake and water, you have like four taste buds.
That's not something wrong there. How about this one? Okay, how about this one?
Jerma loves sake. On his stream he drank it all night. Jerma loves sake. On his stream,
he drank it all night. And in the morning, he goes to sleep in the corner because he
can't handle the guilt he's feeling. His father is a well-off industrial billionaire
with three children, including a son in law who has a real estate business.
On the first day of school, the boy who plays video games on his computer becomes a boy in
school, even if that boy is just four years old. His friends become more and more male.
His mother has started to notice them and start sending him to the male tutors.
Some even start dressing up in dresses, which are so ridiculous but hilarious,
and then his father feels ashamed. What? The little boy who can't keep himself
from being in a girl's room at all times. What is going on? He starts to see a lot of young,
attractive female teachers. I have always been a girly boy. Like always, I wanted to be a girl.
I would try to be a girl like every day. And now I know that I'm a girl. The fact that I'm
always a girl is weird. Despite being in a girl's room at school, the boy loves his
favorite sports team. I miss playing basketball. It makes me feel weird when I miss a game
while his favorite movie. Industrial billionaire with three. Where are the two kids? Who gives
a shit? Who gives a shit? So I gotta say about that. How about this one? Why do I have to pick
them all about me? How are they gonna find something from this? I'll make one about you
guys. Okay, here we go. Jerma on Reddit posts such off-topic things. I was thinking of
something like this. But we can all make something that could be useful in a small way.
You just need to decide between your own personal interest, the general interest of
the community, and how useful it is to your friends and family. You may think it is stupid
to try to sell something to them, but there is no point in trying to use this as your personal ATM
if everyone knew about the plans. If you think the person is selling it for you,
they're being naive because many people are already selling something to people in good
conditions. As a result, most people won't buy the thing if you put a price tag on it. What
the fuck is happening? I think I understand what you're getting at. When a product is useful
to someone, it will probably eventually catch on. Not just in your case. I hope it's at least
useful to other people. I do feel I've been... Somebody got hit in the head with a wrench.
Somebody just kept restarting a computer's first sentence. I hope it's at least useful to other
people. I do feel I've been doing this for some time, but sometimes it's the simplest thing
I can do right out of cake for coffee and my co-workers. So my point is that if you're
thinking of buying something, don't buy it until you know what you're getting with it.
The thing decides whether to buy it or not. That's always not easy on Reddit. I'm not
doing that. Somebody told me I'm not doing that. That means I'm beyond. I met at a chat at a
grocery store the other day. You like doing this shit to me? Let's do it to you. No, no, no,
no. What did I type? Twitter is a fun website too. For that matter, you'll probably get
great deals on new products even with a low user count. Even the biggest name brands like
HSN, Sandsberry, and Kohl's sell $12 copies and tea through Amazon and will deliver for $10.
It's a good deal. People still use the home shopping network. I thought that was only
for like fucking 80-year-old women and like 95-year-old fucking men. I thought it was like
for 80-year-old old ladies. It's for like really, really old fucking people.
You know how I know that? Because my grandmother used to buy dolls off of the home shopping
network. Those like porcelain dolls that they would put on like the conveyor belts and like
move them around. Just like they'd spin around on like the little lazy Susan. She used to buy
them. There was a lot of dolls in that house. It was kind of scary. Anyways, and it's not a
waste at all. Here I am working seven days a week, which probably gets me at most $40 per
week, working 50 hours a week. In reality, what I would work for is less than $1.10 an hour.
So I don't lose money on each cup I pour through the funnel on e-commerce sites.
Where are you making $1.10 an hour? That doesn't sound like a very good thing.
And I spend it well into the future and into the bank. Also, I think it's important
to keep the quality of your work and your reputation high. You have to be very careful
about how you market your work. I know about these fraud checks. Those don't mean much to me,
but to others, they're the beginning of the end of your reputation in the community.
And you have your own company to prove to customers that you are legit.
I'm confident that I will go out and buy a coffee from any online coffee shop
within a few months of the first customer checking out my website. Now your next question
that I can answer. $1.10. Let's see. This shitty view count. I'm just trying to pull like metadata
for like views and like germa. Let's see. No, I didn't mean that. That wasn't like, I'm trying
to like get like the metadata to like pull info. I don't mean, I don't mean that. I'm trying
to get like metadata to like shitty and like view and count. And this is a great fucking view
count. All right, here we go. No, no, no. You're taking this the wrong way. You're taking
this the wrong way. Music? See? This is why I did this. Here we go. No, no, you guys are,
you guys are this is fucking shit little people here. What are you talking about?
It's fucking over 3000 people here. Six Flags is the worst amusement park.
Germa985 and his shitty view count sent me there. Anyway, it's an awesome park,
but there are many flaws in the ride. It only makes you feel like an idiot if you have
to pay for the entire show. There are a few places that can bring back the glory days of the 80s.
You can easily find a better one like the Giants Canyon. It is way too big, too short,
and to me too easy to park without trying or paying for. There are even those that would say
it is better to use a car and drive all around Germa985's park than visit one of the many
places that make this place worth checking out. If you see one of these, you can get
yourself in the park and even get a ride, but you won't regret it if you do not like it,
and you're looking for a way to save money, then Germa985 offers the cheapest ride of the parks,
which means you need to make a reservation. The rides are short, are cheap, and don't
disappoint, so you can enjoy the parks without spending tons of money. Germa985 himself
doesn't care too much about this, but I don't blame him for that. His ride was great in the
90s, and he does the same thing every year. I've never been disappointed by a ride.
They're short. That's why I wrote that. That, that, I almost just knocked over the
fucking bottle. No, this, the view count was fucking fantastic. Don't, don't,
that didn't mean that. I'm trying to just get the, like, thing to fuck up.
All right, one part all-purpose flour, two cups baking soda, and one, and one hint of,
a hint of what? Here we go. One part all-purpose flour, two cups baking soda,
and one hint of sea salt. I also add four teaspoons of garlic powder for extra flavor.
Then I roll out the loaf by laying it on parchment paper. I then lay it straight back
out and cut each section into four triangles. Then I start the second portion. I spread the
mixture onto a lightly floured surface. It takes an entire sheet of parchment to completely
cover it. I put that to work by cutting across the area between each piece of foil.
I then take them all back together and roll up the entire loaf into a sheet,
and I am back to work. When you come to these two pictures just to let things sink in,
it is like watching a roller coaster crash through a tunnel. So the dough is just amazing.
Not only beautiful, I can't believe how light it is on. Back to Six Flags.
Oh shit, what is playing in the background? Okay, nothing. How's that wrong? That's right,
right? Sound the alarms. The Witcher 3 just went on sale. Witcher is not a word. I guess
that's true. Nothing? Surprising. Okay, here we go. Sound the alarms. The Witcher 3
just went on sale today with the promise that it would be as good as the final product,
which is saying something when you are playing a game that is literally being created.
So it makes perfect sense that after all the excitement the game had for the last year,
the first one came out in 2004. That developer CD Projekt Red decided to take their next
move and deliver an HD re-release of what they are calling The Witcher 3 Wild Hunt.
And with CD Projekt Red, it appears the game is going to deliver a stunning conclusion,
not just to The Witcher, but to the series itself. And I am not sure whether it should be
heralded as such even though the game already deserves recognition for being one of the
biggest best-liked games of all time, or just a bad game. It is the latter choice that is
truly important now because as the second game is coming out today as a standalone offering,
which is far better choice than its previous CD Projekt Red incarnation of The Witcher,
you can expect the CD Projekt Red version to be better. Why are there like two different
versions of this game? I've been meaning to write up a lot of this in my previous
article from the same episode of Game Politics Podcast with Tom Stoppard, but I
did not have the time at some point this weekend. Game Politics. I went to Leo's?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. This is Leo Pee Pants. Pee Pants's parents, Ray and
Anel, have filed a wrongful termination lawsuit claiming their daughter was fired
after complaining about how long she worked, and she was denied a job with his company,
the Houston Area Network Company. Pee Pants, who is a mother of two boys,
allegedly got in trouble after complaining that she needed to sleep longer than usual
on her shift for another project. When she went to the store, her shifts extended into
the wee hours. During one of these shifts, Pee Pants reportedly fell asleep in her seat,
but did not complain and allowed Hanop to continue the project, which was taking its
toll on her health. I do not know anyone who takes vacations for any reason except
when it's just fun. That is why if there is the slightest opportunity to relieve stress
and discomfort, I will just jump on vacation, he told DailyMail.com. Pee Pants's former
supervisor, James McDaniel, reportedly told her that she would receive less pay until she
paid back her rent and a $300 bonus. After Pee Pants started working for Hanop, she said
she absolutely refused to receive salary increases after being terminated. I was not
allowed to speak with Hanop's CEO as she has the power to terminate. Why would you
ask for a salary increase? Oh my god. Now let's get a sad story. No, I gotta like,
hold on. No, this is, this is, no, this doesn't make no sense. Hold on. There you go.
Ahem. Come on. Let me tell you a sad story. My Lego collection isn't complete anymore.
I was shopping at Ikea at nine to two on the way home from work one evening and I saw the
shelf on the right with a pile of boxes. As I looked underneath for any items that might
actually fit, I kept hitting myself. What do I do with these boxes? Is it better not to
have any of them? I decided to grab my collection and find me a box store. At the
mall I found an Ikea display case with dozens and dozens of boxes covered with brightly colored
stickers. My imagination raced, making small jokes and getting creative. I walked right
up to the display case and picked up three boxes marked X7 and 715. You guessed it,
they didn't fit in here. Finally, I decided to take a walk across the store to see exactly
what made these. Sorry to say we're recalling all Legos. What? Wired via wired advertisement.
Pea pants. Nice pea pants brand. Warning, all Legos pose an immediate health risk. Okay.
Is this still going? Warning, all Legos pose an immediate health risk. In 2015,
more than 13 million toys came in for inspection and maintenance. Some two billion
toy pieces fell ill with contamination in transit, which can lead to illness. About
one million of these were children, and a further ten children were sickened.
There have been a series of tests at different toy manufacturers to determine
if they have made all changes in the way that they package certain products to ensure that
they are compliant. But in each case they found that, on average, the items remained
undamaged throughout the manufacturing process. In addition, many of the changes were made
on the assumption that the children's toys would remain safe. It seems like that assumption
is incorrect, said Michael D. Lipscomb, a spokesman for the United States Consumer
Product Safety Commission, which is responsible for regulation for toy safety.
At least some of these pieces that have fallen in line are not actually toys.
The story continues. But ten children? Okay. At least some of the pieces that have fallen
in line are not actually toys, but rather sculptures. They don't really look like any
sort of real thing. A man holding up a real human skull? The whole thing is really disturbing,
and it shows that the concept of toy violence has definitely fallen out of favor in contemporary
society. It's really important to note, though, that the artwork on these sculptures
is actually, actually just plastic. Most of the pieces were created by artist Robert Court
over 30 years ago, though there are some in the collections of museum branches across the
world, like the Japanese Kiyoshi Matsumoto Museum in Kyoto. These aren't some cheap,
cheap, cheap toys. I'm not making my point, by the way. If you saw the images in the videos
in these slides, you probably think that the toys have gotten increasingly violent.
For the truth is that toy violence has gone down in the last 50 years or so,
but only slightly. It didn't decline. In fact, it has gotten way, way better. That's
I mean, come on. What a great story. Toy violence has gone down in the last 50 years.
The truth is toy violence has gone down in the last 50 years or so, and that toy violence has
fallen under control. Said Mary Jane Farkas, professor of child development at the University
of Wisconsin, who has developed a method for measuring the number of toys per student
for testing toy violence. In those 50 years, the research shows that toys have become a small
part of society. I am delighted to report that there is widespread agreement about the
problem of toy violence. As recently as 2000, an article in New York Times magazine by one
of Dr. Farkas' graduate students quoted a leading pediatrician, Dr. Jeffrey Cohen,
who stated that a great many children with auto- What? What does this have to do with toys?
And there were no safe levels. What? The government is caught at the wrong end of
the conflict turns to violence. What does this have to do with the toys? Oh my god.
This is a fucking risky, scary fucking website. This is not what you think it's going to be at
all. No, no, no, no. This is like, it's just a rule book. This is no, this is not what I,
hold on. Okay. Why are we always in constant conflict? That is the big question in politics.
The question that haunts our lives, our countries, our culture. Because when your side doesn't win,
when your side has to come up with something new or new ways of doing things, how do you
think about those opportunities? It never seems right. Do people say to you, what's wrong with
you? Or are you actually afraid every day to lose? You have a job. I had a job before and
it was good. And it was good. And now that I have a job, I'm a lot more proud of it now.
Why are we willing to get paid in cash? Because I can have a place to stay if my mom wants that,
and I can do the shopping. Even when I used to go to the stores and pay $5.50, I was a lot
more afraid that they would take off me on a day I didn't have to. Because I'm a good
customer. And I have a lot of good things working for me now and I'm very happy.
I think there is a lot of resentment, even in people who don't usually like politics,
about the way they've become part of the American system. I don't like the way that
politicians become a vehicle for a lot of things, which with its own. And then they
turned his mic off. Cut it. Cut his mic. Cut his mic. Nobody starts a speech like this.
Nobody comes. Nobody goes to the podium. I come to you today with an epic speech.
No, why would somebody do this? You don't like get to the podium and say that. Hey,
everybody. Okay, here we go. Okay. I don't know about this one. Let's get another one.
This is too. This is like a little, this is a little over the. So that's, that's too much.
Remove the period. I'm back. They've put my airwaves back on. I come to you today with
an epic speech. I'm not here to be lectured. I'm not here to be lectured on human nature.
I am here because I know that with each passing year, the number of, oh, I come to you today
with an epic speech. Cut his mic. Cut his mic. Cut his mic.
I come to you today with an epic speech. I'm back on the airwaves. They can't shut me off.
These motherfuckers think they can silence me in the Senate. I'm here and it's designed to
highlight new challenges that we face in dealing with climate change. I understand the challenges
posed by global warming. The question I have for you, my fellow senators, is this. Do you
believe that those challenges are solvable? Like mumbling together. I don't know what you're
going to say. I don't know. Let him speak. Let him ask me. Silence. Climate change is a
question of survival. Today, many parts of the planet, including yours. I'm talking about you.
Oh, you fucking aliens. Everybody from the planet X-41 and global are facing a changing
climate. One of them that I know of is the Mediterranean Sea. As the world's most important
trading partner, the United States cannot afford to lose our global position as a major
investor. To ensure access to our global trading partners, we need to protect our waters,
our marine environment, and our airwaves and coastal areas. The U.S. Senate must commit to
a comprehensive approach to managing the risk caused by rising seas, including a plan to
reduce our nation's dependence on oil and gas. I urge you today to join me at this historic
moment in time when the United States cannot fail to act on global threats,
because I know it cannot succeed. In my view, it's that moment in time. This. Cut his mic.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm back. They think they can silence me and get me out of the
Senate. What the fuck do they know? They don't know shit. You won't silence me. I am the
Senate. I am everything. I come to you today with a story of my intestinal issues that are
very important. In May of 2013, I visited a local doctor who prescribed me some generic
antibiotics. She told me I needed to increase the dosage, and this is a rationale. Oh,
what's he going to say? Oh, shoot. How dare he? Well, I say, shut up, everybody. Sit
down. I said sit down. If you go higher with this drug because of the symptoms of
chronic low-grade sepsis, then you're going to get the same result. I believe her. When I
started doing yoga, my skin began itching. As a student of yoga and a student of biochemistry,
I know better than to blindly ingest large numbers of antibiotics. The idea of doing
an increased dosage of antibiotics to see if the skin response would improve is ridiculous,
and I would rather not use such dangerous, powerful, and often deadly medicines.
Before I begin, let me share you a story. My wife left my family one year earlier than I did.
We met on the web. She was studying for a certification exam. We were married in
September 2012, and early 2012 my wife had an atrial bleeding that I suspected.
Ugh. God, it's fine. I wonder the rest of the story. So do I.
Why do we keep letting this guy back in? I'm not doing anymore. This is the last one.
All right. Hold on. That's not. No. That one ain't going to. That's a gaffe. Yeah,
you got that right. That's a gaffe. I ain't going to do a gaffe on stream.
Uh, I'm going to whatever. Who cares? Uh, it's just nothing.
The Senate will now hear section T 47 article 8236. Will the Senator from Kentucky please
reiterate his position? Thank you for your attention. Senator Graham, Senator McConnell,
Senator McConnell, just so everybody understands. I've been advised by the
office of the deputy attorney general or deputy AG to defer to the confirmation of Mr. Rosenstein.
My position on appointment will remain unchanged. Senator Graham, Senator McConnell,
Senator McConnell, I defer appointment until you can get your head around the situation.
However, for the record, I remain totally open to the Senate going either way.
So I do ask that you will allow me to give the floor time to review any and all options
that you have at your disposal, not just the one which you have set out today. I appreciate
your Senator, your consideration and commitment to the rule of law. Now, thank you, Mr. President.
I would appreciate the chance. This is just a boring one. This is just, this is, this is,
this one sucks. This is a gaffe. I got to get one more of these dumb speeches in. I do.
Cut it. Cut it. Cut it. Cut his mic. No, this is, no, this got fucked up.
This got fucked up. It got messed up. It was only like three sentences. It wasn't even
worth reading. That wasn't a gaffe. It's having trouble with this one. He's
limiting. All right. Give me, give me some, give me some, um, do religion. No, it's having
trouble with it. It can't do this one. Todd Howard speaks from the White House.
I'm not going to, Todd Howard speaks from the White House. I think this site might be,
I think it's, I think it's down. Shit. Cut the mic. No, no, no, no. Wait a minute.
I'm just seeing if one word will do anything. I think it's, I think it's dead.
I'm going to try refreshing the page. Maybe it's dead. I think it's dead.
Once upon a time in German 985's backyard. Well, if it comes back, I'll do it.
They finally cut your mic. I guess they did. It'll come back. Just give it a moment.
It'll return. Socket. I just, I just have one. What are you talking about?
I'm pacing myself with this. All right. AMA, ask me anything. Let's go.
Ask anything. Is it a bottle of shampoo? Yeah. It does look like it. You're right.
It looks like a bottle of shampoo. Hey, what do you do? Are you still doing the trial stream?
No, unfortunately not. We gave up on that when it got too late, too long, but don't worry.
Something way better is going to replace it. And it's going to be, I don't want to ruin it.
You're going to like it. It has to do with the dunk tank stream, but there's going to
be way more than that. It's been a while since I've done like an elaborate stream,
like a produced elaborate stream. This is going to be worth it. I got a really,
really, really interesting team involved in this one. What's my favorite TV show?
Curb Your Enthusiasm, Always Suddenly Philadelphia, and Ren and Sniffy.
Deadly Clowns there. I wouldn't say it's a clown stream, but the clowns will be there.
Still dead. Damn it. Greenscreen Encore stream is going to be the 29th of June. Yes,
it's coming back. What are my thoughts on Sekiro? I beat it on stream. I did beat Sekiro on stream.
It was great. It was really, really, really fucking hard though. Harder than I think any
of the other games before. And maybe it's because the controls were different and the
game was a little different, but I thought it was harder than any other game that they
have made. What are my thoughts on German 985? I think it's all right. When are we getting
a three and four year badge? Bloerdau is right now working on a bunch of new stuff.
I've already seen preliminary pieces of it. I think within the next two or three weeks
we'll have some more stuff on the channel. What would my fursona be? A frog. We already
talked about this. Come on, come back. I was having fun. Are you going to do something on
the 18th? That's my birthday. Dr. Zutzu, we're going to celebrate your birthday. Just
pretend. Okay, ready? Clip this. I want Dr. Zutzu to clip this. Hey, what's going
on everybody? It is June 18th, 2019. And we are here. We've got a very important day
here. We've got something going on here. We've got Dr. Zutzu's birthday is today.
Happy birthday, Dr. Zutzu. It is June 19th. Just wrong date. What was the date? 18th. Cut
it. Hey, it's June 18th, 2019. Welcome to the stream, guys. Just turned the stream
on for the first time. June 18th, 2019. And yeah, we've got a very important thing
going on here. We've got Dr. Zutzu's birthday. First of all, that's really important to say that.
June 18th. This is today's date. Happy birthday, Dr. Zutzu. Hell yeah. Can we get some Dr.
birthday Zutzu in the chat, please? Happy birthday. Because it's today. Today is the
day. It is June 18th. Today. That's the day it is. All right, come on. Come back.
Have you ever peed in somebody else's pants? Yeah, I think so. I had hand
be downs for my brother. And when I was like six or seven years old, I definitely peed my pants.
And I peed in my brother's pants. So yes. Yes, I pee pants. You have a brother? I do.
I have an older brother and I have an older, I got siblings. How am I feeling tonight? I'm
feeling pretty good. All right. Nobody click this machine. What's my least favorite part of
Massachusetts? Well, I don't live there anymore. But when I did live there with the rain,
I hated the damn rain. It fucking rained like a hundred days a year in Massachusetts and it
just drove me nuts. Shit. I think we might be out of luck here. Damn it. Time for GeoGuessr.
No, no, we got it. I'll take one more question. One more. I got one more question available
here. Did you put MA because you can't spell mass ban that person for life?
Oh, German lied about the clown car. Did I? Did I lie about the clown car? You're going
to have to change your username in a few weeks. In like a month, in like a month to
two months, you're going to have to change your username. It's real. Yes, it is real.
DrunkGermaReveals. No, no, no. This is fine. We can talk about this.
Without getting more. AdventureMFDan, five community subs. Thank you.
And German lied about clown car. Also community subs. Thank you for that.
At some point in August, there is going to be a stream on this channel that's going to be
huge. Lightning Rider, five community subs. Thank you, Lightning Rider.
It's actually going to happen now. There's a team of people that are working on this with me.
It's taken me a long fucking time to find the right group of people.
I've been trying to get this to work for like almost six to seven months,
talking to people at Twitch, talking to people through help with the producer friend that I
have. And finally, I finally got a group of people that kind of know what to do and know
how to do it. I know it's been a long time since something elaborate has been done on the
stream. It'll make up for it. I promise. I promise that this will make up for like the
six to eight months of no big stream. I promise. And it's going to be Sam and Max Season 3.
I finally got a group of people. I got a group of people together to download the game
for me and like load it onto my hard drive. No, it's for real. I've talked about this stream
before, but it's much more elaborate. I'm going to put a bunch more time and a bunch more money
into it. And if it works, I hope you have a lot of fun on it because it's something I don't
think has been done yet so far on this website. He's like talking it up a little.
He's talking himself up a little. No, it's going to be fun. Five more subs just came in.
Who just gave the five community who just gave five subs? Magellan. Thank you Magellan for the
five subs. I talked about it in the discord a little bit earlier like yesterday on another
website. Jermis, promise. What did I promise? Eventually at some point before I stop streaming
and doing anything to do with online stuff, I'm going to have a clown car. It's going to
happen. It will happen eventually. Yeah. There is going to be a clown car on this stream
that I'm talking about right now. I fucking 100% promise. Yes. Thank you The Unravelling
for the two- You have no idea what's going to happen with this. You have no idea.
It'll be fun. And if it's not, then I fucking tried. Anyways, it rained like-
We've got more subs that came in. Hold on. But I do apologize for the time it's taken
to do another one of those streams. The last big stream that was on this channel was-
What the hell was it? It was like the- New Year's Eve? January 1st? That's a long time.
It'll be worth the wait. As long as this works the way that I want it to. It'll be worth the
wait. February, March, April, May, June. It's been five damn months. That's too long.
All right. Let's do this one. This one is working. This one's not even good.
No. No more Senator bullshit. What should I do? Should I type? This one's- I'm just going to read
it. Cut is mic now. Let's go. Hey, here we go. We're the Misfits. We're having a blast
playing together here and then we get the opportunity to have a little fun. The fun of
putting on a performance. It's totally a new dynamic. This new dimension of who we are
having this conversation, this feeling we're doing this for each other, this mutual respect,
this intimacy, the love of music. We're so inspired by and feel this chemistry. I feel it.
That's the power of this club and this vibe. There's no question that we're going to hit
each other. What? But we're also going to hit each other with our musical abilities that we
share. We're going to give each other props and to use our bodies and our minds. It's
the most fun thing we've been doing since the day we came here. And that's where the
fun really begins. If we're going to start it, it'll happen. We'll start with a group dance
and see what happens. We definitely won't be stopping until we start it. It's been a fun,
fast learning moment for everyone here. We have fun doing this, but we're not afraid to be
ourselves. We're still open-minded. Just go for it. And we're not afraid to play any
instruments. Are these lyrics? Nah, this is... I just pulled like the what is Twitch.
Is this a real... I don't know if this is a real person. Who is the best streamer on
Twitch? Possible answers for this question, in my opinion, all depend on the game they
are making. On the one hand, they could be streamers working through different channels
that work around the same time frame. On the other hand, they could be streamers
playing different games. Do you know how many streamers you would add back into one channel
to fill an existing gap? I'd like to see Twitch TV and any of the smaller stream programs
such as The Dude for You add a dedicated one to fill this void. Is there a time limit you
think needs to be exceeded during stream hours? Absolutely a time limit. It depends on how big of
a gap you want to fill, how long it takes you to fill that gap, and if you plan on doing that
over and over in one run. The best solution for me is having a dedicated channel that I
can create for myself on a consistent basis with other streamers. I may create a few
dedicated streams, but most of them are only for personal use when I stream. Where
does your stream come from? Is there anything that you don't want people to see online?
No, I don't pay people anything for their time. No one does. My channel is a completely independent
one where I own the rights to it. Okay, can I get something out of here? German 95 is the
best stream on Twitch. TV slash twitch.tv slash kiddofly is the best stream on stream. Steam.
You should watch the live stream. Good luck. Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Why? Why is that near? Oh, what the fuck? What? Oh, get the
fuck out of here. Dog shit, come on. Well, alright. Let's uh, let's go back here.
Why is that shit gonna come on man? Like what? The fuck. We're gonna have to do a
blank screen beforehand now. Come on. What? I'm really glad that I still haven't blacked out.
I still have it gone, because this one wasn't good either. I'm glad it's still on a black screen,
so you can't see what... like what the... why are we getting such bad ones now?
All right, this is gonna be fine. All right, okay, we're back.
My favorite ice cream is the one that tastes totally like ice cream, without all the chocolate
flavor. So all those of you who are craving a little more of that flavor, I'd recommend
going for the creme de creme. There's always a good chance you'll find one on sale.
You know, my favorite chocolate flavor is the chocolate crave. It's like ice cream, but only
fair, since it has an added kick of chocolate flavor. Chocolate cream is my favorite, as it's
just as tasty as what you'll find at your favorite candy store, only without more flavor,
since you get the real experience. Finally, you can also find my favorites, the flavors of
the sweet chocolate ice cream, like the one you can find at your local Dairy Queen. They
can be thick and creamy while still being crunchy and chewy, like the ones we found
earlier. So next time you're craving dessert and think about spending some of your money to get
ice cream, you may want to check this section out. Here we go. The takes of the Tomb Raider
release date and new DLC content as a result. We're still very excited for our fans to get
their hands on a limited edition Fallout 4 t-shirt and collectible mad dog figurine.
All we need now is to finish our work on the other add-on content for the game.
Source official play- that's it.
Another unknown player.
Here we go. I don't know what the fuck that was. I don't know what that was.
I don't know what that was.
That- what the fuck was- I typed in Fallout 76 music. I'm not gonna get in
fucking trouble for this anyway. Yeah, country road.
Fallout 76 Battle Royale mode is going to change everything.
A true story set in the time when a nuclear war between Earth and the Red Room was breaking out
and you are the leader of the resistance. Play as either the protagonist and your trusted henchmen
or as a lone ranger or vault dweller. Each will face different challenges and will encounter
different bosses as they go to defend the world from certain forces. They will of course be
accompanied by their companions and if everything goes according to plan, your choice as the
story's hero will save the day. The game will take place in a post-nuclear world and every
character is completely independent. Their personalities will determine who they become
and how it ends with. Your choices will influence a few other people who live in that world
and affect your survival and the direction of your adventure may lead because there really is
only a few people that still play this game. There's eight people on a server. Your choice
as a leader will determine the fate of the people here on Earth and whether they will
continue forward. The world you play through is a unique and dynamic landscape and if you're
lucky, you'll find a companion. If not, it isn't out of the question that you'll encounter
another. There's plenty of time to take care of your companions if you haven't already
because that's all you fucking did in Fallout 4. That's the only thing you did. That's all
you did. You take care of your town and give them supplies and shit. The action will take
place in a huge open world. The entire world will be littered with hidden objects. Cut the
mic. Somebody wrote, you really weren't kidding, this really is your worst stream.
When I did this fucking card game and how was I supposed to know? I did my damn best. That's
all you can do. What happened on 542? What happened on that one? Can't blame somebody
for trying. It was, I still had a good time. It's okay. You can't hit a home run. Sometimes
you ground out to the first basement. I still had fun. Do the money phone? What's the money,
what's money phone? Money phone? I don't know what that, I don't know what you mean.
I didn't rip the cards. What are you talking about? No, I just went like this.
I just like shuffled them. He doesn't know. Money phone. I don't know what you mean.
I'm going to look at money phone. I'm going to look it up. What's money phone?
Money phone. Holding a stack of cash to your ear and taking a selfie to flex on people. What?
What are you talking about? I don't have any money. I don't have any cash here. What do you
mean? I have to take a selfie while I go like this? Because I went like this?
All right, I'll do it like that. Tweet it like this. I don't understand what that means.
I don't know. I have to hold it to my, I can't do that. I can't hold it to my ear.
I'm not going to, why would I tweet that? I tweet like fucking three times a year.
Like a phone. I'm not going to hold it up to, I can't take, I can't do that.
I mean, I guess I, I'm not doing the money phone. Okay. Get somebody else to do that.
You have to. This stream sucked. God damn it. I'm like sad. I'm sad right now.
Did you at least like think it was a little fun?
Well, if you didn't like it, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Hope you like the other ones.
Hope you like the next one. You're a drunk mess. I am, I am not.
Uh, there's not, there's this 15% alcohol by volume in here. I'm going to be just fine.
Um, what? That was six hours. It's been six hours. Can we do any of the little games or something?
What else can we do? I'm not ready to go yet. Not yet.
10 more community subs of cyanide. There was a lot of community subs.
I missed some too. Thank you guys. More community subs.
Rvem, thanks for the five. Cyanide, thanks for the 10.
Time to go. No, not yet. Not yet. Maybe like a little bit longer.
Flash games. Watch old, you want to watch a few old videos?
You guys thought that was fun last time.
More community. Jerma lied about the clown car. I'm gonna change that name soon.
I know I said that earlier, but thank you for the lots of community subs.
Um, it was worth a shot. It was worth a shot. It was fine. It was worth a shot.
It was worth a try. I just farted. No, I didn't. This is Cher.
Uh, he just shit his pants. What do we got? Let's go here.
The first one was fun. The second one dragged on for too long.
And the second one was just like all over the place.
Is that a night wing shirt? Yes, it is.
Let me open up. Just give me a second. Hold on.
Let's just do. No, and that's not no DOS.
That'll probably take too long. Let's. I do have to go back to the movies too.
Should we just go? Should we go back to the movies like this?
This week? What do you guys think?
It's been a long time. So I think it's, I think there's more content there to do.
I think that'd be fun. Well, what do we got going on tomorrow?
Maybe it's, maybe I should just call it six hours.
Hmm. I'll give you some insights here.
Yeah, I think, I think we'll call it. I think we will.
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Um, let me see.
Cause I am actually going to visit somebody. I'm visiting family this time next week.
So we got today, tomorrow. I got some shit planned. Don't worry. It would be good.
Old vids. Well, maybe we'll just do a full old video stream like this week coming up.
What's going on tomorrow? I have a few options tomorrow.
And then on Tuesday. So we're going to go.
I have some stuff to do on Monday. I've got some work to do on Monday for the channel.
I'm getting a call. Uh, but Tuesday, it will be interesting at least.
Tuesday will be that dwarf rock galactic game with star, dwarf rock galactic, whatever it is.
Something like that. Deep rock galactic. That's the one.
Uh, so tomorrow we'll do, we'll figure something out tomorrow.
There's a few games I could play. We're going to do, uh,
Hey, that's, that's to be determined. I'm not going to play days gone tomorrow,
but that's it. I'll call it six hours.
Hope you had fun. I hope you thought it was interesting at least.
I know it may have been a little different and maybe, maybe not the best idea,
but it wasn't worth a shot. I had fun. I did.
And then I had to call it. So thank you for watching. See you tomorrow for something.
Destroy the cards. No, these were expensive. These were fucking expensive.
I'm not going to destroy these. They were expensive.
These things were like 50 bucks for three decks. Cut as Mike. I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching guys. We'll catch back up tomorrow.
Same time, three or four o'clock. It's not that bad for three games.
Yeah, but I don't want to, I'm not going to rip them up.
They were still interesting. Where is the, uh, there's the outro.
We had a lot of subs, so thank you all of you.
Let's go back to the bits here. We were earlier this afternoon.
Thank you to, uh, Freudian Weapon. Thanks for the eight dolls, Freudian Weapon.
Hey, Jeremy, I didn't realize Tuesday was your eight-year internet anniversary.
So happy anniversary. Thanks for eight years of laughs.
You've impacted me more than you could know.
I wanted to celebrate properly tonight, but the liquor store was all out of fancy streamer wine.
So I had to settle with sponsored YouTuber IPA instead.
Well, thank you. Hopefully it was good.
It has been eight years. It's been a long time.
Sometimes I forget how long that's been. It's been ages.
It's almost a decade of being on the internet.
Thanks for the eight bucks, Freudian Weapon.
Thanks for celebrating my eight-year anniversary.
Mr. Sneak Man, thanks for the three dolls and 40 cents.
Hey, Jeremy, great stream as usual.
Starting a TF2 Open team with my buds for the first time.
Wish Team Berb good luck so that we can channel Jaxx into our matches.
And if we keep up the good work, have a good night.
Good luck.
I wish Team Berb the best of luck in TF2 Open.
Thank you, Mr. Sneak Man, for the three dolls and 40 cents.
Thank you to the Overlord of Cookies for the three bucks.
Hey, Jerma, I was wondering if you could help me with something.
Me and a friend were hoping to get one of the WWE games
so we can make characters and watch them beat each other up like you do.
It just so happens that 2K19 is on sale for 26 bucks Canadian, so $19,
with full price being 60 USD.
And your opinion, do you think that we should get it or hold off for another one?
And if no, then which WWE game should we get instead?
Thanks and love from Canada.
Well, it depends on a few things.
Everything after 2K14 sucks.
They're terrible.
The games are fucking awful.
Their customization options are terrible.
But they've run better.
Everything before WWE 2K15 runs like shit.
But the customization is 10 times better.
So you really have to decide,
do you want a game that runs better but has less options?
Or a game that runs like crap but has tons and tons of customization options?
When you decide that is the game that you should pick.
Yeah, it's right when the console generation switched, yeah.
Unfortunately, it did go downhill.
But weirdly enough, I don't know why I'm losing my voice so much recently.
It's like a weird phenomenon.
The last two or three weeks, if I talk for more than five or six hours,
I just did my voice just drops.
I don't know why the fuck this is happening.
I don't understand.
I'm just getting old.
But yeah, that's the best way to determine which one you should play.
I was doing this weird old man senator voice for like 20 straight minutes.
Maybe that's what happened.
Probably.
But yeah, I would pick 2k14 if you've never done it before
because it's way more fun things to do.
But you have to deal with the problem times, like load times.
And it looks worse, obviously.
But hopefully that answers your question.
C4G, thanks for the 250.
Hi, Jerma.
I posted one of your clips on Tumblr a week ago
and someone shared it and called you a Himbo.
What did they mean by this?
Thanks in advance.
I have no idea.
I don't know what that means.
What did I do?
Did I do something wrong?
Caught the mic.
What did I do?
He doesn't know.
I don't know.
I really don't know.
An attractive but unintelligent man.
A place, come on.
I am not unintelligent.
I'm just...
It's all right.
It's okay.
But are you attractive though?
I don't know.
That's up to whoever.
The jury's out on that one.
It wasn't an insult.
I know.
I'm just playing around.
Spliceable Spleen, thanks for the $5.
Hey, Jerma, just graduated from university today
and wanted to show you some love
for getting me through some tough times.
Keep creating amazing content and I'll be here.
Thank you to the $5, Spliceable Spleen.
Congratulations on graduating university.
Much love to you.
Thanks for being around.
And I'm happy you think that this is good.
That makes me happy.
I hope you still think so.
I hope you stick around.
I hope you still think it's fun.
I really do.
I hope you still think I'm handsome.
But thanks for the $5.
Thank you to GTX 1080 Quad SLI for the $2.50.
Hey, Leo, I was wondering when you were going to do more VR or Dreams.
It's been a while.
And I'd love to see more epic wins and fails, JermaTV.
I will probably go back to VR.
The week after next.
So the week of like the 24th.
I'll go back to VR.
And we will do VR for a whole week.
I just, I needed to take a break from it.
It was kind of killing me for a while.
But that week of the 24th.
And what about Dreams?
Uh, Dreams is, I would probably do channel surfing on Dreams.
I feel like I can't dedicate the time necessary to make anything interesting.
I tried to, but just kind of wasn't happening.
And I'd rather dedicate time to other things.
Like, for instance, the dunk tank stream with all the other games thing.
So that's my off stream shit.
That's what I'm going to be doing off stream, at least for the next few weeks.
And that has evolved by two or three times.
So in the time when I'm not live on camera, I'm going to be working on that.
So instead of doing something like Dreams and making stuff,
I'm doing that instead.
Because that just got a lot of traction here in the last like three or four days.
But yeah, something like that.
Thank you though for the five dollars, uh, of the 250, sorry, GTX 1080.
Swiggity swanky, thanks for the five dollars.
Dr. Jerma, I have a problem with my ear.
I've recovered from a cold and I've noticed that there's still fluid stuck in my inner left ear.
That was three weeks ago and it still won't drain.
Has that ever happened to you in your 30 years of life experience?
Yes.
Uh, I'm going to tell you something.
This is not medical advice.
I am not a doctor.
But first of all, go to a doctor.
I am not a doctor, not at all.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
This is, do not use this as medical advice.
But every time I've had water in my ear or fluid in my ear,
this is not medical advice.
Do not do this.
This is something you should not do.
Don't ever do this.
Under any circumstance.
That's what I'm telling you, to not do this.
Uh, is I do hydrogen peroxide in my ear and lie with it in my ear for like a few minutes.
Do not do that.
Never do it.
Don't ever fucking do that.
In a, don't ever do that.
Okay?
That's actually fine.
No, I'm gonna go do it right now.
You gotta be careful though, you know?
Ow, my ears.
I told you not to do that, so don't worry.
I've, I've protected myself.
But thank you.
Also thank you, but it's five dollars from spickety swanky.
Go to a doctor, they, they know what they're doing.
Cyanide Zero gave fucking a hundred bucks and a shitload of community subs,
so I gotta say right off the bat, thank you Cyanide.
Atrolux A-Trux gave a shitload of subs too, a lot of community subs tonight.
Alamitos, Alamitos, thanks for the 250.
Local streamer by the name of German 986 was arrested after plagiarizing a garden
from an innocent person and house slipper.
German was on the run from the police for a few weeks,
but was caught after the police got a tip from another streamer named Grill Master X Barbecue.
A man by the name of Mario said,
German has not been the same mentally ever since I destroyed him in Yahtzee.
I didn't even do the Mario voice.
I just like talked like Mario.
I just did Mario cadences.
I didn't even try.
That was just a guy talking.
It wasn't even Mario.
But thank you.
Thank you Atrolux A-Trux for the 10 bucks.
You're all breathtaking.
You're breathtaking.
That's what I need to say, right?
Too drunk?
No, I'm not drunk.
I'm just my voice is gone.
It's like getting worse too.
I hope it's not like this tomorrow.
I'll be in some fucking trouble tomorrow if I can't talk.
I'm not getting like laryngitis, right?
Why would that be happening?
No, I'll be all right.
Thank you for the 10 bucks though, Atrolux.
You're all breathtaking.
Oh, we also had Pigeon.
Thank you Pigeon for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, I was looking for Switch games to buy.
Uh, Switch games.
And I stumbled upon this.
It's like Space Channel 5, but you actually have to move.
I thought it'd be a really great stream.
Plus you could finally get back to 2015 Jerma.
2015?
Jerma, what do you mean?
All Jermas are good Jermas.
They're all fine.
They're all good Jermas.
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with the 2019 Jerma?
Teen!
Oh, this is getting bad.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
Fuck.
Oh, here's the link.
Pigeon with five dollars.
Fitness Boxing Switch.
Interesting, okay.
Space Channel 5, but boxing.
I'm gonna have to have a tea.
But uh, thank you Pigeon for the five bucks.
Thank you Freudian Weapon for the 250.
For the record, I did enjoy these unlock card games.
I may even check them out for myself.
I'm glad you did.
It was an interesting idea.
I can't pretend that every idea that I have to do on stream is gonna be worth really doing,
but I think I still had fun doing it.
It's something that I wanted to try for a little while, so it's okay.
As long as you enjoy yourselves, that's all I care about.
Because I enjoyed myself too.
But thank you Freudian Weapon for the 250.
Door Cube, thanks for the 250.
These unlock games look like something that my nerdy aunt and uncle
would have funded on Kickstarter.
Play it once and then give it to me for Christmas.
Oh, that's true.
That's very true.
Yep.
Yeah, you know, you got it.
That's...
Hey, guess what I'm gonna do with these.
They're gonna get boxed back up and they're going to my nieces and nephews.
I had that idea like an hour and a half ago.
I'm gonna be that uncle.
But I didn't buy them on Kickstarter.
But they're good.
What's wrong with them?
What do you mean that's so mean?
These are like fun card games.
Things.
But thank you Door Cube.
Thank you Halo Soft Boy for the 250.
Thank you for streaming.
Your streams have been a really positive thing in my life lately.
As I've been going through some crazy stuff.
I witnessed a shooting a week ago.
But your streams in the stream archive have been helping me relax
and take my mind off things.
I'm really fucking sorry to hear.
That's fucking horrible.
Now the house flipper streams have been my favorite.
Thanks for doing what you do.
I'm...
That's fucking horrible.
Thank you for hanging out here.
Hopefully you're all right.
Hopefully everyone's okay.
I don't know what you're referring to here.
But hopefully everything's okay.
But that's fucking terrible.
Thank you for hanging out.
And I'm glad that this can be a community of somewhere to relax.
I'm okay.
Thanks.
That's good.
That's good to know.
Take care and thank you.
And moving on from that.
We're gonna do Pasta Globs had 250 here.
Hi Jerma.
Your streams never failed to cheer me up.
So I thought I would show my appreciation with some art.
Hope you like it.
It's pretty damn good.
Get it on the screen.
What do you say?
Pasta Globs.
This hair.
Look at this hair.
I gotta do something about this hair.
It's starting to get all over the place.
It's starting to go crazy.
This is great.
Thank you.
That was Pasta Globs.
Thank you for the 250 and thanks for the art.
You look like Prince Charming.
Thank you.
Grow it out more.
I can't.
I would look like David Spade.
Thank you Pasta Globs.
We had lightning rider with five community subs.
Pogefest five community subs.
It was a lot that just flew in sub-wise.
DC Pro.
Thanks for 10 bucks.
No message.
Just 10 dollars from DC Pro.
Actually no, there is a message.
Hey Jerma, I found your channel when I was 16.
Now three years later I want to thank you for all the laughs.
Thanks for being around.
I've been watching for three years.
Thank you for the 11 bucks.
And thanks for watching.
Hope you stay tuned.
Then we had a Dork Cube 250.
The card game may have been the worst stream,
but the moment when you said my wife left our family a year before I did,
it became the best stream.
I call this predicament Schrodinger's stream.
Yeah, it's okay though.
It's okay.
I'm completely content with the card games.
It wasn't bad.
I know, but I look, I don't like to disappoint people.
And I know nobody's actually disappointed.
But I want every stream to be fun and happy,
and people interested and want to watch.
And if you see somebody that says,
I don't like this, then it's like,
fuck, I wish, I wish you did.
Now for the most part, people thought it was interesting.
And you know, but still, you know, I,
it's something I think about a lot.
I care about that shit.
I really do.
More than anything.
I don't give a shit about anything else.
I only fucking care about that.
That's it.
Nothing else.
I really hope you know that.
Not even Kim.
No, come on.
Come on.
Oh, Jesus.
Let's get, there was a lot of community subs.
Let's get the credits on screen.
We're almost done with the bits, but let's roll these up.
And they go, there was a lot.
There was like hundreds.
It was like two or three hundreds up tonight.
You don't care about, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
No, guys, guys, what have you done?
Guys, what have you done to me?
This is not, this is not, come on.
She's sitting here watching the stream.
No, you listen.
I'll talk to you in like five, five minutes.
Don't listen to the chatters.
They've lost all control.
But in real talk, in real words here,
the reason why I do like the card game stream is because I
want to see if I can make something interesting.
You know, it seems like something fun to do.
Better warm up that couch.
Yeah, it's all good.
It's all good.
It's all fucking gravy.
And another thing.
Let me tell you another thing.
I, turn it back, turn it back on.
Don't do that to me again.
You understand, this is my fucking stream.
Fucking aliens upstairs trying to control it.
You keep, keep it on.
I'm not fucking around.
Keep that shit on.
And another thing.
That's all I got.
Hey, thank you too.
It's a ghost party for the five dollars.
Hey, Jerma, every stream you do is great.
And it's a pleasure to see you doing what you want.
Don't let the haters get...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, nobody.
No, there was no haters.
That wasn't...
That's not it.
There were one or two.
That's all right.
That's okay.
You can't please everybody.
When you see that one guy complain, don't let it get to you.
Only makes you more of a boomer.
No, no, no, no.
I'm fine.
I'm just fine.
Don't worry.
I was one of the haters.
You understand?
I'm going to flip this on you.
I was one...
It was me.
It wasn't in chat.
You're your biggest hater.
It was me.
I was the one.
It was the mirror.
The mirror held up in front of me.
It was like, oh, shit, it's been me the whole time.
You were those thousands of people.
But there was a lot of subs.
Thank you, guys.
We have a few more bits to get through.
But it's a ghost party thanks to the five dollars.
It's not...
Nobody was like that.
We were just having a good time.
I just sometimes think...
Overthink.
If people are having a good time, you know?
Because it's what I fucking care about the most.
It's not the money.
It's not the fucking view count.
It's not the worst view count, right?
It's not that was...
It's nothing.
I'm not about that at all.
Money.
Oh, shit.
I said the word money.
You don't want any more money?
I look fucking greasy.
Naked streamer.
No.
But only a couple more bits to do.
And then I should see you tomorrow.
Unless for some reason something's wrong.
Because I don't think anything will be wrong.
I almost lost my mind at the beginning of the stream, though.
It was kind of fucked up.
Any main channel uploads in progress?
No, but there is a main Twitch stream coming up.
That includes Dunk Tank and some other things.
That should be happening sooner than I think.
But thank you to Magellan for the five dollars.
Hey man, just want to jump in and say thank you for the stream tonight.
As rocky as it was, I really needed it.
And enjoyed it a lot regardless.
Even in your worst dreams and of being a gold mine of entertainment.
Also, I made a dumb video of your moment earlier.
Enjoy.
Not a screamer.
Just turn the volume down.
Well, that's kind of a funny warning.
Not a screamer.
Oh, it's...
I'm the screamer.
I get it.
When did I do this?
What?
I feel a little bit better.
Oh, because I was pissed off at the fucked up Twitch server.
Right, right, okay, okay.
Well, that was Magellan.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Thanks for the video.
Hope you enjoyed it.
Thank you Anything Else Show Official for the five bucks.
This was a different stream for sure, but it was still funny and unexpected.
I'm still sick, but your goofy humor has healed me a little.
Also, if you're playing the movies, I recommend checking out the mod site.
So you can put in some random and funny shit as usual.
Have fun, you goober.
Thank you Anything Else Show Official.
Oh, right.
That's wrong.
The movies might even just be the next stream.
What's tomorrow?
Sunday?
I mean, it might be tomorrow, Monday, Tuesday, okay.
Maybe we'll just do that tomorrow.
Maybe we'll just do it tomorrow.
That would make some sense, right?
We'll see.
Well, if I can get that to work and I can get some mods and stuff maybe, yeah.
Let me try it out.
If not, then we'll do that at some point in the next week for sure.
Let me see what I can do with that tomorrow, but thank you.
Only a couple more.
Frodium Weapon.
Thanks for the five dollars, Frodium.
Every stream is fron- fron in one way or another to a lot of people.
Your breathtaking.
Thank you so much for the five bucks.
I do think about that a lot.
Thank you for the five dollars, Frodium.
Captain Fawful.
Thanks for the five bucks.
I was one of the comments you read about this being your worst stream.
It was just a joke and I didn't mean it.
You could do a stream where you would do nothing but eat Cheerios and I would still love it.
Keep up the great work.
That's why- I know, I know.
Look, nothing anybody said in the chat tonight was a catalyst for this.
I just- it's just something that concerns me.
Don't give them any ideas.
Every stream is fron.
But thank you, Captain Fawful.
No, nobody said anything that I didn't like.
Oh, where the heck's everybody's such a mean?
No, no, no, no.
I hope you don't think that.
But thank you for the five dollars.
Stanktron.
Thanks for the two and fifty.
Hey, Jeremiah, I recently went to a museum in Queens
where I saw a Jim Henson exhibit.
It showcased all the original Muppets in Sesame Street,
Fraggle Rock, Puppets, etc.
I noticed you referenced them a lot.
Thanks, because Jim Henson is probably the most-
well, one of the most important media personalities to ever live.
So, I mean, Jim Henson is-
we wouldn't have so many of these things without Jim Henson.
You want to talk about influences?
I think Jim Henson might be up there for me at least.
He did a lot of really, really great things.
So, that's awesome.
Glad you got to see it.
The Muppets are completely timeless.
Forever.
Glad you got to see it, Stanktron.
Just got here. Am I late to the stream?
Eh, by a little bit.
A Freudian weapon right now.
Two-fifty, that's right.
I'm going to be that guy and be the last bits.
Have a good night.
Well, that's not true.
Because unfortunately, deusmorte gave two-fifty.
They said,
Jerma, that was possibly the worst stream ever.
The Birdhouse stream deserves an award after that one.
Just kidding.
Love you, baby.
Keep doing what you love.
I played a goddamn card game and I had fun.
And I drank sake every card pull.
And I got five thousand subs.
Because I'd beat the game in so six seconds.
Clueless sniper, two-fifty.
No, I'm that guy.
You are now.
All right, all right, all right.
I'll probably see you guys tomorrow.
In the extreme odd event that I wake up tomorrow
with a hangover for some reason.
I don't, this is like, I don't think it will happen.
Did I, I drank the whole bottle though.
Did I? I did.
We're gonna play the goddamn movies.
It's just, it's sake.
It's not that, it's not that alcoholic.
Don't worry.
I'll eat like a fucking couple pieces of bread.
I'll be fine.
24-hour movie stream.
I don't know about that.
No, I'll be fine.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're good.
Expect either the movies or something else tomorrow.
Freudian Weapon gave two-fifty.
We shall see.
Freudian Weapon is now the last bits of the night.
Drunk streamer.
I'll be a little, I'll be like eight percent.
Maybe eight percent drunk.
That's my time.
Thank you for watching as always.
I'll see you guys probably tomorrow.
We'll do something fun.
That was Unlock, a murder mystery.
It's going right into the trash.
Just kidding.
Take care.
Probably see you tomorrow.
Oh, guild mates and stream legends.
That's right.
I will take care of you guys.
Yes, I will.
Here you go.
There you go.
All right.
Take care, guys.
See you soon.