Come on, we ain't doing an intro. No intro. I'm not late. I'm not late. This is the previews
for the movie. You can go to a movie 25 minutes late and still catch the first two minutes.
I haven't gone to a movie on time in fucking my whole life. Yeah, I sound a little froggy.
It's because I got some schnapps up there. I'll be alright though. C3, babe. Come on.
I'm gonna make a tweet. Hold on. Well, that is not what I said. The lights aren't
even turned on in here. That's how you know it's a fucking dire situation right now. We've
got like five, ten minutes. I need to write something. What do I write here? Day two.
Is it day two? It's day two, right? Why is the outro playing? Here, listen to them.
They're probably talking about fucking- Oh, brain froze. I'm doing two things at once.
Let's go. Day two. E3. Now, it looks like you've got a pretty special avatar there.
I'm gonna put my phone away. It's just like a movie.
Now, it looks like we just entered a station. Tell us a little bit
about what's going on here. We're on the tour regarding education. Now,
alright. Hey, how are you? Good to see you again. What is it historically after?
Is this another Assassin's Creed? I love how Assassin's Creed puts history into the game.
I'm trying to listen. You're not trying.
Quiz? Yeah, so I hope you've been paying attention. Let's go for one easy question, right?
I saw the Twitch tweet, by the way. They took that moment from yesterday.
That's like on the official Twitter now. It was not even a funny joke.
People probably looking at that tweet going like, oh, this is what the
kind of streams he has? His stream must suck. It was me covering up Keanu Reeves' head
and pointing. I was like an asshole. I was obnoxious. That's not me. This is me.
I'm a good guy. Well, thank you so much for joining us today and telling us a little bit
about the Discovery Tour and a huge shout out to the team at Ubisoft Quebec for creating
these two amazing features, the Story Builder and the Discovery Tour. Thank you again,
Thank you, Carrie. Also, if you're curious about the Discovery Tour, please ask your
questions on the Assassin's Creed subreddit and we'll answer as many as we can.
I got a piece kind of just migrating over this way.
Along with the Story Builder. It's an amazing time to jump back into the world
of Assassin's Creed Odyssey. Now, for those of us who are just joining this live stream,
the conference is going to start really soon, but before we wrap it up and jump
into the theater, we have one more amazing WoW Moments compilation for you.
Now, these are the best clips that we received from you, the community.
So hold on to your beards, mudflaps, butts, whatever you got.
You're just assuming that I have like a big gamer beard?
All right. That was hacking. That guy hacked. That's hacking. That person was hacking.
Oh, no, no. These are like streamers. Oh, never mind. I thought it was an Ubisoft
official thing. Did I do purple for Twitch? Does that just make me look like a fucking dickhead?
Am I going to be the streamer voice? All right. For a second I thought my webcam was fucked up.
No, that's somebody else's webcam. This is my don't use webcam. I hate webcam.
This is next level reaction. Overreaction in E3. Not only am I reacting to your stream,
but I'm putting my webcam on top of your webcam.
Oh, I'm just going to spill my coffee. I'm not going to fix it. I'm going to leave it like that.
Over the next two or three hours, watch what happens to my hair. You are going to see
this piece of hair is going to fluff up. It's like a chia pet. It's going to go up
and it's going to pop. Okay. I thought it was like the little kid playing. I was like, what?
Dude, he started swinging while the thing was getting me up so he knew I was going to get up.
What if one of my clips are in here? I hope one of my clips is in here.
That would be perfect. That means I have to play an Ubisoft game, which I haven't done in
fucking three years. That was pretty good. That was pretty good. I think they had to
invent an ESRB rating descriptor for chicken-related acts for that asshole.
That was mean. I felt so bad for the chicken. I just thought it was funny. I don't know.
Poor chicken though. This has been such a great show. From the wow moments to all the
creators around here. I mean, it's just been a blast. Absolutely. Game sound's really cool.
That was like a super ultra broom. That was like a street sweeper broom. What the hell was
that? Just the energy that's been here today. I want to thank everybody who's been here on
site, who's watching on the street. I want one of those shirts. The star players that are
hanging around. It's just been an amazing day. And of course, we've got a lot more to come
after the conference starting at about 2 p.m. We're going to have a celebrity showdown.
Team T-Pain. Team Lil Yachty in Rainbow Six Siege facing off. Why did he do that?
Wait, what? He just hurt himself. It's going to be a good match.
You know, I really can't choose who I want to win. What the fuck?
I'm not in this. I'm not answering. I'm staying away. Team Neutral. He hit his mouth on that
coffee table. That guy's not even part of this. He's not here anymore. The show starts in 34
seconds. Back to Far Cry. Then over to Assassin's Creed again. Back around to Far
Cry. Second time, third time. So many good options. So many good options.
On behalf of all of us at the pre-show, thank you so much for joining us. We're going to head
into the Orpheum Theater. And for everyone at Ubisoft, we hope you enjoy. Ubisoft.
Uh, rated RP to M. Uh, content may not be appropriate for anybody. Here comes an orchestra.
The Stone Cold Glass Breaks. And they do like the Stone Cold Steve Austin theme song.
But this is the Assassin's Creed Symphony.
Do we go now or when do we go? Do we? It's dead. I'm so pissed off right now. I can
imagine if I got to play along. How am I gonna? I need a screwdriver to fix this thing.
And batteries. I don't have any batteries. Just listen to the song. It's beautiful.
Captain Jack Sparrow. And his whimsical group of pirates. Take him on a new adventure.
This time in Assassin's Creed 8. Green flag. Instead of black flag. Orange flag. Coming next
month. Wait, those people just were on stage just to go, uh, for like five seconds.
I want somebody just to start leaving in the mic going. Yeah, I'll take the salmon. Uh,
can I get that with crispy skin? And instead of a risotto, can I get some, uh, spinach
waste? Oh, I would do that. I would do that. These big menus. I don't, I never get that. I
don't get it. I mean, it's beautiful. But why do they need the, kind of just, you know the
song. The song along with the beautiful music. It sounds like they start spacing their hands.
I'm not talking about the intro. I'm just talking about why you, when you're up on stage
playing with the folk though. You already love the song. Worldwide tour? What you just saw was
only a glimpse of the Assassin's Creed Symphony Tour starting on June 29th. Imagine an 80-piece
live orchestra and choir playing the iconic themes from Assassin's Creed while you relive
some of the most memorable moments from over a decade of Assassin's Creed in an immersive
experience. Check out acsymphony.com to learn more. I mean, excellent music, great performances,
goosebumps. If you like those things, I think those shows are going to be for you. But
of course there's one show that we all came here to see. The Ubisoft E3 conference. And
it's just about to start here from the Orpheum Theater in Los Angeles. Now the house is packed
and to give you folks at home an idea what that feels like. Can I please hear the
show the line outside? Look at these losers. Look at them. They're still waiting to get in.
If you, if you please, if you please, I'd like to do the same for the people sitting on the
ground floor. And all the billions of people watching. Well, the excitement is here,
folks. We hope you're feeling the same way there from everyone at Ubisoft all around
the world. Please enjoy the show. That was, that was like a, I can't do that. That was
like a bang, wink. I can't do that. World premiere. That was a countdown. Okay, yeah.
Greatest city in the world. Well, used to be. Now it's a right mess.
Government's fucked off. Extremists are grabbing power. Organized crimes slicing up the
boroughs. The war dogs are out. And freedom's a bloody joke. But this ain't there, London.
This is our London. And there's a new power growing. It's all of us together.
We're building a resistance. One recruit at a time. What's my favorite operative up to
this evening? And no, I never say that to the others. Scouting talent, Bagley. So gob
shut. Eyes peeled yet? I have no eyes. And if I did, I wouldn't peel them.
Fuck you, dinglebot. Where the fuck we go?
Bloody drones are everywhere. Kicking our fucking teeth in lately.
Then I recommend you recruit someone who can deal with drones. Brilliant. Never would
have thought of that. You're clear. They always do this long walking behind me segment.
Just punch somebody. You know what I mean? Sure, but we need a drone expert, Raj. Not a
shit kicker. File that one away for later. It always starts with like, well, let's slowly
walk down the same street. That's not what a gamer does. Gamer does like the fucking
full sprint. Like sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint, sprint. They just take the first
card they see. Nobody even plays Hitman like this. And that's how you're supposed
to play that game. Jimmy Shaw, no formal engineering training, but he has several
mischief charges for hijacking Albion drones. Hold still. Fuck you, man. You've got no
right. Fuck you, hell. We find our drone expert and he's about to get himself nicked.
Wait, die in the game? You die in real life in the game? Well, actually, that's kind
of cool. If you die in the game, you die in real life in the game.
This is pretty great, actually.
I hope it's the same animations for every character. That means Grandma can like
fucking rip people, punch people, kick them in like the face and shit like that.
You know they're going to use the same animations.
This is fucking amazing. This is the greatest thing ever.
Can I just play as Grandma the whole game?
It's going to suck when you pick a character and get instantly sniped.
It's going to cost like fucking credits and stuff like that.
It's an open world. You can fall off the edges. You can get hit by cars and stuff.
So many of my characters are going to die in this game. I'll be in that menu screen.
30% of the whole game.
That means every time you fail a mission, you have to use a new character
or surrender. I'm never going to be able to relate to anybody in this game.
They always make it look so easy, but that shit don't work like that.
You don't like do the Heimlich maneuver one time to somebody and you kill them.
You ever choke somebody up? You ever get choked out before? It takes like fucking five minutes.
You ever choke somebody?
No, no, listen. You ever been like fucking choked out before in like wrestling or like MMA?
It's like a struggle and it takes like fucking a full minute.
It takes like three minutes. Like remember when Ted DiBiase did that for his special move?
Hulk Hogan would be in that move for like five straight minutes. It doesn't take like five
seconds.
I would have gotten hit by that car. The person's all right.
That's how they'll take us one at a time. It doesn't have to be that way. Together,
we can change things. Wait, what happened to that bloke who helped me? He didn't make it.
Fuck it. Welcome to DedSec, James. Yeah, okay. So where do I go to meet the rest of the crew?
You don't need to go anywhere. Look around you. Everyone has a reason to fight and DedSec
is open to anyone. Welcome to the resistance. So any NPC can be a playable character if you
like convince them. NPCs are the new press F to get in the car. Ubisoft has just changed
the game here. But steal car in GTA without steal person. Like be a person. That's kind
of cool. I want more info on the fucking people's like body. It's not like stealing.
What am I doing? It's like they become an operative. I'm Clint Hawking. I'm the creative
director of Watch Dogs Legion. And for the past few years, the team and I have had the
privilege to work on a game and an innovation that we are very proud of.
Watch Dogs Legion is set in London, one of the greatest cities in the world, and it's
had a massive influence on all of our culture for centuries. Today, with Brexit, London's
at a turning point. It's hard to predict what the future holds for London, for
the UK, or for the world. So go recruit some old ladies and fucking drive around
and crash your cars.
To us all. And they are the heroes of our game. All of them. In Watch Dogs Legion,
your mission is to build a popular resistance to fight back against the emergence of an
authoritarian regime. This means you don't just play as one hero, but many. And in
Watch Dogs Legion, you can recruit and play as anyone. Oh, my God. That took
like a monocle off. Oh, my God. This is unbelievable. Never before have I seen
something like this. In our game, every Londoner is fully simulated with a
persistent life and relationships, and anyone from the entire population can be
recruited into your team. Find them, profile them, hack into their lives, play
their origin mission, and win them over to your cause. The heroes you
recruit are all unique characters with different backstories and
personalities, fully voiced and animated, and they are the stars of your
story. Every cinematic in the game will change, depending on whether you're
playing a former MI5 action hero, a 70-year-old grandiose off-feeding pigeons
in the park, or anyone in between. However you want to play,
whoever you want to be, Watch Dogs Legion lets you be that. Fighting
against an authoritarian regime. They're taking us over. They're trying
to get rid of us. They're killing us. Hack into the people's lives and break
their privacy and then force them to be part of your system. Hack into their lives
and take them over. Play as anyone is the innovation that transforms a story
about freeing London and the world from the grip of tyranny into a game
about the heroes that live in each of us. Because being a hero isn't just a job
for someone else anymore. It's a job for everyone. So on behalf of the
Watch Dogs Legion's team here and around the world, I hope to see you on
the booth. Thank you for your time and welcome to the Resistance.
That'll be fun. We will.
Had a good run there for a while. Now it's all riots,
riots, bombings, people thrown in cages like animals. Oh, I know you can forget
the killer robots everywhere. So yeah, that's all gonna be shit.
It's up to us to take our city back. The thing is, we can't do it alone.
We need to recruit a Resistance. I know what you're thinking. Where do we start?
Open your eyes and take a look around. Look here. Look at him. No, not him.
Him. Former MI5. Duty never ends. He can get anywhere and erase anyone.
Let's kick those bastards out of London.
She got kicked out of Oxbridge Robotics School for teaching him to reproduce.
Oh, come on. Come at me. He'll crack your skull. Just there's like there's a handful
of different classes. I think that granny was a robot expert.
This had better be fucking good to introduce you to the deadliest of the law.
She's not old. She's experienced.
Like I said, you can recruit anyone. And I'll mean bloody anyone.
Him. Her. Everyone is a secret weapon. Find them. Build the Resistance.
Let's unfuck this world.
Anyone. Yeah. Even me? Even animals. Grandma makes that. I mean, I know I'm like,
biased, but. Microwave? It's always sunny in Philadelphia.
Hello. My name is Rob McElhenney and for the past 14 years I have been making a television
show called It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia. Are you fucking serious?
Thank you. But I am here today because I love games. And I wanted to express that
love in the only way that I know how save for playing them. And that is to make a TV show
about them. More importantly, the people who create those games and the people who
play them. So last year I called the funniest people that I knew. Charlie Day,
Megan Ganz and David Hornsby. All executive producers on Sunny.
And we started talking. We realized very early on that if we were going to do this,
we wanted to do it right and to be as authentic as possible because as you all know,
nobody smells bullshit like this particular community. So we did the right thing.
We partnered with Ubisoft and away we went. It has been an incredible experience working
with one of the biggest and best game developers in the world to inspire us
because our show takes place in the fictional studio that created the biggest
MMORPG in the world, Mythic Quest. And we meet them on the cusp of releasing
their biggest expansion yet, Mythic Quest Raven's Banquet. The show follows the team
of devs as they navigate the challenges of running their game while dealing with the
difficulties of modern office life. These cut back to back stage like Frank's back there.
This scheme is going to work. Dennis, shut up. The head of the team is my character,
creative director, Ian Grim. Why are you covered in oil? I don't understand what that's
for. This part of scheme.
Short of the best that they can make because that is what the community you deserve.
I promise you that in making this show, we took the same approach.
So without further ado, here's a brief look into our upcoming TV series for Apple TV plus
Mythic Quest Raven's Banquet. Apple TV plus. What is Apple TV plus?
What is Mythic Quest? Some may say it's just a video game.
When it first debuted, MQ was hailed as a masterpiece. Now played in 20 different countries
on six continents, it's the biggest massive multiplayer role playing game of all time.
And today, they find themselves on the precipice of their first major expansion,
Mythic Quest Raven's Banquet. And it all falls on the shoulders of one man,
creative director, Ian Grim. When we think about cultural touchstones,
we think ET, Star Wars, Avatar, and yet our industry dwarfs the traditional entertainment
business. So when we think about legends, why not think Mythic Quest?
True indeed. And when we think of visionary world building artists, instead of just Spielberg,
Lucas and Cameron, why not think Grim? I'm sorry, I gotta stop. What is this?
It's a commercial for the game. It's a commercial for you. It's still going.
This is insane. I think it's brilliant.
This is a TV show. This is not a game. This is a game. I know this song. You gotta play the best
part when they scream where they're from. Hey there, my name is Parker and Taro Makai,
esports caster for Rainbow Six Siege. Celebrity showdown.
There are so many exciting things to come in year four. In-game events, map reworks,
playlist updates, a roster of 52 unique operators, and of course, a thriving
esports scene. Starting tomorrow, you'll be able to enjoy our 13th season, Operation Phantom
Sight. This major content update brings two new operators to T-Rainbow, Nook and Warden.
After this show, be sure to stick around for an intense celebrity match starring T-Pain,
Little Yachty, and some of your favorite Twitch streamers for the Twitch Rivals
celebrity show match. But right now, here's a glimpse of the new season in action.
Thank you, everyone, and have a great E3.
Brawlhalla master. These things are whack. One v one me, bro. For real. Uh, yeah. I'll
toast your buns again. Sure. Want to choose a different character? Yeah, I choose me.
Yeah. They inked it. Adventure time deal here. Whoa, it's those guys from the game.
Oh, are they just going to take over the game? They start introducing way more adventure
time characters. They're just skins. Oh, okay. Are they? Dude, I'm not fucking around here.
Wouldn't you love like a Smash Brothers cartoon fucking roster game?
Wren, Stimpy, Courage the Cowardly Dog, Ed, Edd, and Eddie. I have like 400 characters in
the game. I don't care. Oh, actually, that already exists. It's called, it's called Mewman.
That already, that's already a thing. Let's just play that. The only test of a man's worth
is battle. When those rounds come screaming past your head, you're gonna learn if you
are hungry enough, hungry enough to take that victory. We're going to battle with
the soldiers that we used to be. Ghosts. And you better believe that they are hungry too.
Once upon a time, some of these ghosts, they may have been your friends.
And there is brotherhood. But then there is what the world needs. These ghosts,
they are the past. They still serve the machine that we left behind. And right now,
for the future, the world needs us. I'm honored. I want somebody to make a game where you play.
I'm honored to be here with you tonight. And everybody's getting sick of like these,
as you head into battle, we need to fight now. Look in your eye, those bad intentions
in your mind. Remember this. You are the few with the courage to make history.
You had the desire to take victory.
You will be on a battlefield full of ghosts, but only you have that hunger that makes you wolves.
Ghost Recon Breakpoint. Ghost Recon Wildlands. Ghost Recon
Constant Conflict. That's what they should just name it. Ghost Recon Constant Conflict 3.
Good to be here. This is the dog on screen. Click dog. Click dog on screen. It's a dog.
It's a real honor to be here with you guys today. Thank you. I love you too.
This is awesome. This has been really great and exciting. And I'm really,
I'm really honored. Dog on screen. I'm enormously proud to be part of the development
of this game. It was a pleasure to work with the Ubisoft team. You know, I've had
the chance to play some pretty strong, tough men over the years. I've played a deputy fighting
zombies, special forces soldier who lost everything. And now I get to play Cole D. Walker. He's a
skilled former special operations soldier with his own sense of responsibility and his own
moral code. He knows how things should be run. He loves his brothers, his fellow soldiers,
but he is willing to do whatever it takes to complete his mission and take control of Aroha.
There is no briefing. There's no backup. You will not face a group of bad guys or
a criminal organization. You will face an entire army. My army. Good boy. The wolves.
We've got the numbers. We've got the organization. And remember, we trained alongside
you the weaponry of a fully operational special ops detachment. Trust me. There's
an unparalleled arsenal of high tech weapons in Aroha. So if you think you have what it takes,
strap on your boots and you get ready to take on the wolves. I wasn't paying them. Take on
me. See you in a row. We'll be waiting. Perfect predators. I was sorry, there's a dog on the
screen. I literally nothing else matters. Have the element of surprise. They have the technology,
but we have the skills to even the odds. They have an army who we fight with our
brothers and sisters.
Fight. They are hungry. Take up arms. We are enraged. Fight. Fight. All we do is fight.
You're ghosts and ghosts. And they always do that like fucking rip the head tape down and
that fucking head hits the ground. You know, conflict. Ghost recon. Constant conflict. Full.
Rip his fucking head to the ground. I'm not insane. That was, I was talking about a video
game. That was a video game. We're talking about video games. Being a community developer
on Ghost Recon Wildlands and Breakpoint has been an incredible journey for me so far.
When we first announced the game, you were very excited. And after discussions of members
of our community, I today announce that with our post launch plan, we will be bringing back our
AI teammates for our solo players. Wait, what does this mean? Ghost Recon Breakpoint.
We want to go the extra mile with how we engage with you. So I'm pleased to announce
a brand new community program that will allow you to express and share your passion.
Welcome to Ghost Recon Delta Company. From cosplay to streaming, fan art to forum
discussions. However, you show your love for Ghost Recon, there is something for you in our
five different detachments. You like crushing heads against walls and smashing direct discussions
with our studio. So head over to our Ghost Recon Breakpoint website to find out more
and hear from you soon, Delta Ghosts. Thank you very much, everyone.
Thank you, Laura. Hello, everyone. The Ghost Recon team has always taken great pride
from your passion for our games. And that passion is what pushes us to deliver
the best pickups experience out there. Behind enemy lines, you will be fighting the most
dangerous enemies the Ghosts have ever faced. Conflict. Constantly testing your survival skills.
Yes, we can't wait to welcome you in Ghost Recon Breakpoint on October 4th.
And one month before that, our beta will be live on September 5th.
You can register on our website right now for a chance to participate.
Ghost Recon Breakpoint will be live for years to come.
We've got your back. New content, free updates, and many surprises inspired by our community.
Yes, yes. Like this one. I haven't said anything. I've got, I don't really have,
I don't know anything about this. All I know is it's just conflict. That's all I know.
It's the Terminator. The Terminator. No, why does everybody have to have the Terminator
in a game? Did they ink the deal at the same time? Another Terminator. Will you survive
your break point? That looked a lot better in the mirror. All right. I'll tell you.
I mean, I've done that before. I know what it's like. I've done that before.
Why the Terminator? There has to be some weird reason why this fucking two Terminator instances
here. Conflict. She's all in. She's ready to shoot and punch, crush her head. She's got her
Terminator ready to crush heads. Her best defense is this crush head.
Squishing heads like Goro between her hands.
Lead the elite squad. They're all elite squads in every game. Every single one of them.
I want a group of people that have no fucking idea what they're doing.
Pre-register now. Why do we, I don't want this anymore. I want to be like a moron
that doesn't have any training, that doesn't know how to do anything.
It's the most elite specialists. No, I want to be a guy, I want to be like a fucking
sewing master. I don't, I don't want to be like a fucking specialist anymore.
10 years. 10 years. That's a lot of dancing. We're exhausted. I know. But think of everything
we've done. It's not for us, or for you, or you. It's for them, the press.
We danced and Sivio and his girlfriend got married. We danced and our friend
Jaden Rodriguez danced for millions, bringing together generations. We danced and they set
world records. Do you remember Carrie? Of course we do because we were with her.
Dance is why we exist. And I know we're going to have much more of these moments
because dance is a force. I was about to be in a magician game, but
700 million people use this as a workout routine.
Could have got the magician game. There's so many prime examples on the stage right now.
The magician game. 10 years. We got like 10 more years before the S&P is going to crash.
I feel like it's weirder for me to be watching this.
Then it is. I feel like I need to be there. I'm like embarrassed to be here.
No, because this is like great dancing. It is. This is like fantastic display of talented people.
But like I'm just kind of like, I feel like maybe if I was there,
get up and dance. Nobody else is doing that. I'm just kind of like, I guess I'm here still.
Those people are so much more talented than me.
We got some hype in the chat, please. There's an old tale about this village.
This is still going on. A samurai came to deliver justice.
Nest clouded her mind. She slaughtered every living soul.
Became the spirit of death. Comes the Terminator.
Years later, we hunted the samurai in the village.
We didn't believe the old tale. Not until a horror came.
Spirits hungered for our souls.
Sakura is the spirit of death.
She's brought a curse that will doom us all.
We got another one. They lined it up tonight.
We got a flatliner raid coming in.
Rainbow Six quarantine. Free player.
Hi, I'm Biojad, and I'm the lead game designer on the next Rainbow Six game.
They're really, really, let's say something about like 2019.
It's called Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six.
They don't want to call a game anything else.
I'm part of a new team in Ubisoft Montreal that set out on an exciting
mission. Create a radically redesigned co-op experience built on the
foundations of one of the best shooters of this generation.
What siege is to the PvP shooter genre?
We will be to PvE co-op.
All right, that's, this is interesting. This is pretty interesting.
Quarantine will test your tactical skills and survive.
Three player co-op.
Holding you and your operators on the razors edge.
It pulls you together as a squad facing off against an unknown and
devastating parasite.
You will risk everything every time you step into quarantine.
Stay tuned and start prepping for your next deployment.
I can't wait to show you more and have a great E3.
No, that was like the coolest thing possibly here today.
A three player co-op game.
We'll just get to see the trailer.
See you in like two years when that's ready to play.
Give me a clip of me.
There has to be one.
What did I play? I played like Far Cry 5.
There's not a clip of me going like, what the heck?
Like there has to be.
There's at least 10,000 of those.
Fucking epic.
All right, there's got to be like at least a dozen of them.
I've done it before.
No, don't clip that one.
As creative director at Red Storm Entertainment.
I'm not, I'm irrelevant.
There's no greater reward for me or the team than to see our game come to life
and to see our players, our star players,
taking tremendous pride in being a part of the division.
Now, if you haven't had the opportunity to play The Division 2 yet,
we would be thrilled to have you join our very passionate community
because I'm happy to announce that this week only,
between June 13th and June 16th,
The Division 2 will be absolutely 100% free for everyone to play.
And there's no better time to join us as we're about to release
the first of our major content updates for our year one journey.
Play free for three days.
A journey beyond Washington DC.
That shit's not even long enough to go through the tutorial.
To save not just a city, but an entire nation.
Conflict.
All right.
Different kinds of conflict.
I want animal conflict.
Thank you.
Episode one.
Like a jungle game.
Right around the corner.
You call it a line.
We deliver to you new main missions and a brand new game experience.
For the first time, we're taking the fight outside the city
and you'll venture deep into the woodlands to spearhead an attack
on a presidential compound as you seek to bring a traitor to justice.
The National Zoo is the setting of our next mission.
Zoo.
Where you and your team will hunt down the surviving outcast leader.
You and your team play as snakes.
This brings us to our final edition of episode one.
A place called Kenley College.
And it's home to an entirely new gameplay experience.
One that will take exploration, investigation, and logic
to uncover the fate of a military convoy gone dark.
I'm getting sick of like backpack sprints.
Episode two.
Coming this fall, we'll bring to you the Pentagon.
Once an impenetrable fortress, it has fallen to the black tusks.
You got a backpack on?
Secrets are about to be thrown out into the open.
Are you running like this?
You must do everything it takes to secure what lies behind the walls of this last castle.
But this won't be the greatest danger you face in episode two.
Really fucking zoo game.
No, I know zoo.
There's like plenty of those.
That our second grade will be coming this fall.
Bringing back intense eight-player action.
Yeah.
You tackled the first raid.
It was awesome.
And we cannot wait to see what world records you break this time around.
Caveman.
They already kind of did that.
This brings us to our third and final episode of year one.
What if rebirth was not about bringing the world as we know it back to life?
But the opposite.
One man holds that power.
And humanity itself is at stake.
Can you guys guess if he's a special operative?
It's time to engage in a manhunt.
Let's see.
Let's see how like skilled and talented and special operative this guy is.
Poor girl.
Sorry.
No, no, he's just got a backpack on.
He's got a gun.
He's trained.
We fought to protect the weak.
But training doesn't prepare you to hunt someone you used to call brother.
He has left us no other choice.
If we don't stop him, there will be nothing left to save.
Holy shit, what about that?
I can't wait for that.
Okay, one last thing.
As you might know, we have been working on a movie.
It will be directed by David Leitch, starring Jessica Chastain and Jake Gyllenhaal.
Well, today, I'm proud to announce that we will be making the Division movie with Netflix.
More to come on that in the future.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Okay, that just has like a bag of rice.
That just has like now South Park already made this joke.
It was a good joke.
That's a pretty good South Park joke that I was about to make.
Hello, I'm Brenda Panagrossi.
I'm vice president of platform and product management.
Ubisoft has been creating worlds for over 30 years.
Uno.
We have the most diverse library of games,
and we're about to make it even easier for you to play them.
Uno, except the cards all have backpacks on and guns.
It's perfect.
Called Uplay Plus.
And they shoot at each other.
You'll get earliest available access to new games,
including the premium editions with all their additional content.
And you can enjoy the depth of our PC catalog that includes over 100 games and growing.
We talked about this yesterday.
It's like Netflix, Hulu, Apple TV Plus, HBO Now, it's going to be Ubisoft Now,
Microsoft Go, Square Enix, yay.
We'll enable free access in September at launch.
But here's the thing.
If you buy one game a month, this is where the notification comes from.
If you buy like one or two games a month, it's $60 to $120 a month, right?
Well, I mean, then why don't you just pay $88 a month every month
and get access to everything?
You know, it's like, ah, it's going to happen.
Speak up.
Did you not hear my point?
I just made a pretty good point that you just don't know the games.
Yeah, you will not own those games.
But there's going to be the next five years.
So you're going to see like the $15 from Microsoft a month,
$15 from Ubisoft, $20 from Square Enix.
I keep making these companies up.
Maybe even like companies like Nintendo.
It doesn't matter.
Sony like $18.99 for the PS Plus Power Pass.
It's going to be like $120 a month if you get them all.
Or you just buy the games.
They're going to slowly going to make it a reality.
Players are we want to provide access to our games and services.
I'm pleased to announce that in 2020,
Uplay Plus will be available on Stadia.
Cue the appropriate enthusiasm music.
Stadia is the new generation gaming platform
where you could play our Stadia games from any device.
A special thank you to Phil Harrison and his team.
This is the beginning of our partnership.
I'm not muted.
I can see I'm looking right now at my audio device.
Thank you so much.
Have fun playing.
And it's not it's just the explore.
It's where we're going in the future.
Subscription based models.
Everybody wants to have one.
Skateboard.
I have no idea what's going on.
Basketball, future champions, football.
My name is Stefan and I'm a proud member of the roller champions team.
All right, come on, bring it up.
From the get-go.
Everyone starts getting up.
Let's get on stage.
We're very clear.
I'm going to sit down, sit down.
We wanted to create something new.
We wanted to capture the intangible excitement
of players preparing for the big game.
The hype of team play and competition
along with the craziness of high speed racing.
So we started working on roller champions.
A skill based team PVP sports game
that is as fun to watch as it is to play.
A game in which you, the player, can create your own story
as you roll up to glory.
But right now I know how it looks.
We showed you a trailer and I got on stage
starting my little speech.
That's all well and good.
But when will you ever get to play this?
How about today?
He said today.
All right, that was actually kind of a bad idea.
When we're done here, I want you to head over to play
on your PC to download a pre-alpha E3 demo
of roller champions.
Play the heck out of it for the next few days.
Play it now.
When you're done, head to the forums
to tell us what you thought.
And you know what?
We firmly believe that you will be screaming
as loudly as our colleagues did
when they first got to play this.
I'm not going to play it right now.
But I can't just leave you with that.
So here's a taste of what you should expect
once you click that download button.
I probably can't even stream it.
It's probably like not allowed.
People are streaming it right now.
I don't want to go download champion ball.
I have to go like sign up and shit.
I don't want to do this right now.
You want me to go download this game right now?
And like, why would I do this?
It's probably fun, but I don't want...
I'm not, no, I'm not doing it.
I saw one person sit down.
So I'm not doing it.
They're trying to tap into that rocket lead.
Kind of, it kind of is...
So first, I want to say thank you to...
All right, I wasn't paying.
I thought that was John Lithgow.
I really did.
I was like, John's John Lithgow.
Thank you to all the Ubisoft teams
around the world for your talent and energy.
You know, congratulations for another great show.
I thought everyone was like cheering
because like, holy shit, like John Lithgow
was like on stage.
He's probably in like one of the games or something.
I believe video games have a positive impact on...
I got out of my like area I'm allowed in.
At Ubisoft, our intention is to create games
that will make you stronger and happier in your life.
When you play Ubisoft games...
Get back in the Gamer Cube.
Spend quality time with family and friends...
I just need to stretch.
And meet new inspiring people.
Learn more about yourself by doing.
And gain new perspective on the world...
I just turned off my fucking PlayStation 4.
And help shape it.
So to everyone who plays our games,
thank you for your love.
Some of those games look pretty fun.
They did.
The new Watch Dogs looks actually good.
Looks fun to play.
Wish us to always do better and go further.
So now I'm very proud to announce a new project
from an exceptional team in Quebec City.
Please give a warm upload to Marc-Alessi Cot
who is coming to show you a sneak peek of his game.
I mean, if it's another Rayman, then that's a huge hit.
Thank you, everybody.
Over the last 10 years,
I've had the chance to be part of an incredible team
that has always pushed the limits of Assassin's Creed
and shown us different periods of our past.
But our imagination has always been bound
to the reality of the history books.
These past four years are minds I've lingered
on a different aspect of our history.
The mythology.
The stories of the ancient gods
and their misadventures have existed
through generations of storytellers and audiences
and have transformed into tales
that we still know and love today.
And now these stories have shaped our dreams,
inspiring us to build something new,
something that transcends the limits
that we have always set upon ourselves.
Today, I'm very proud to have the chance
to show you a glimpse, to show you a teaser
of this brand new game that we've been working on.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you and have a great E3.
Hello, everybody.
We didn't get that was.
Hello, everybody at home.
Thank you so much for watching.
I hope you had a great show, but this is just the beginning,
guys.
This is just the beginning.
Thank you.
We are here outside of the Orpheum Theater
live from the pro zone where we have an incredible
Rainbow Six Siege show match together with.
That was a weird transition.
We have our two new best friends, T-Pain and Lil Yachty.
That's all right.
I kind of don't even know anything about
what they were just talking about.
They were just talking about how.
This is like the biggest thing we've like ever done
is a new project from a new studio and.
Okay.
It is like the trailer from the iPad app store.
And we're live again indeed.
So once again, a quick reminder, Operation Phantom
Sight will be available starting tomorrow.
Any Rainbow Six fans here?
We're live again.
Well, it never turned off.
I like that.
Now we are super proud.
Super happy to present to you the Twitch
Rivals Rainbow Six Siege Celebrity Showdown
for the first time.
I want to see who the celebrities are.
Many Rivals events to follow this year.
Turn it off.
Turn.
Wait, is this not allowed?
Well, I guess.
Is this in the terms?
At home and do you guys hear?
Also, we have, as mentioned, eight incredible
streamers.
We have eight of the best streamers from all
over the world.
No, it's not illegal.
Probably the best in the world.
Why not?
It's allowed.
And two amazing team captains.
And a quick thank you to our sponsors,
to our partners.
That was all right.
For hooking us up with some of the gear
you see out here.
Thank you guys.
You're amazing.
The C3 is kind of one of those lull years.
Besides like the Microsoft console.
Watch Dogs 3 looks fun.
Teams.
Team number one.
Why am I not here?
Why was I not invited?
We got T-Pain.
I don't play.
Why would I?
I don't play Rainbow Six Siege.
We got the Russian badge of what's good.
It's like, hey, dude, why were you not
invited to the Star Wars premiere?
I feel good.
I'm slightly less bloated than.
I'm good.
I brought some friends.
I did bring some friends.
These are all the winners over here.
So, you know, that's just how that works.
So, you know, we got Yachty here.
I heard.
I had heard.
What's the first thing that came to mind
when you heard you were going to battle?
Why?
What's wrong with it?
You know, it's no big deal.
It's just like it's an extension of E3.
He was like, oh, he's going to be there too.
That'd be cool.
He can watch us win, I guess.
Oh, shit.
So you're going to win.
Am I going to watch the Rainbow Six Siege?
Yeah, sure enough.
All right.
So let's call.
Turn it off.
Whoa.
Everybody make some noise for Yachty.
No, I'm going to watch this.
We're watching this.
But, like, at least I'm just.
We've got little Yachty.
Bikini body.
Oh, my god.
Everyone's freaking out.
Y'all good?
Well, why is this so such a conflict?
It's just not enough with the conflict.
Enough with the conflict.
You guys.
It's starting to get to you.
I heard that if NA win, it'd be the first thing they ever won.
So.
Oh, shit.
Any response to that?
You know, winning once is always great.
Don't big deal.
This is probably my first time winning anything at all ever.
So, you know.
But, you know, I'll take the one win over over 10,000 losses.
Guys.
I got nothing else to do today.
We have to burn four hours until the Square Enix concert.
The Square Enix fucking conference.
And I'm just kind of just sitting here.
Watch the stuff that I missed from the, what about PC?
Should we go pee?
You want to take a little piss break?
All right.
I'll tell you.
I got team who's on these teams.
I didn't, I didn't even see who was on the teams.
Roller Champions.
It's at 3 Pacific.
All right.
Well, let me go pee.
How do I turn you off?
Okay.
You're out.
All right.
I'll be right back.
I gotta pee.
Why is this tiny?
All right.
Go pee.
We'll come back.
We'll burn like a few hours somehow.
If I actually download Roller Champions,
five to six thousand people are going to leave.
You probably already, you probably are going to leave anyways
because you may have just been here for the conference.
Roller Champions.
That will be like a stock market crash straight into the ground.
We'll see.
I'll be right back.