I never left. I've been here for two fucking straight hours. Just listening.
I feel pretty good. Didn't move. Hey, welcome back everybody. Welcome back. Tell us the bad
news. What bad news? Did I tweet that under somebody? I always think I fucking do that,
I don't know why. I never left. How'd it go? It was good. It was good. He got brain fluid poisoning.
Yeah, we're gonna finish up this stream part two. I have probably an hour or two left of
Mega Man Legends and that's where we're gonna call it. I don't want to play this tomorrow.
Black and White 2 is tomorrow. Let's finish this today. Let's get this done. You know what I'm
saying? Why can I not connect to chat? I just had it. All right, hold on. Can I? Is everybody
else's chat messed? Everybody else's chat messed up? Can you see this? Well, I got you guys on
another monitor anyways. All right, I can see you guys now. I just can't see you in the window I
usually see you in. All right, so what we're doing, I had, I was doing, I got the final key
and then I saved it here. I beat the boss. Do the other games in the TV studio. I already aced the
other games in the TV studio. I got all the parts from it too. All right, what do I want to do?
Go get the red lipstick at the Apple market to give to the artist in Uptown.
You got it. That's, I need to go east and then south. Yeah, I didn't know if it was going to
take another hour or so, but it didn't. I'm back now. We can get this done now. All right,
I need to get to the Apple market. Now we go south. That's west. Was that north or west?
Yeah, I talked to the artist before. I said, I told the artist that they don't have any talent.
Is that bad? Does that lock me out? What about that, the pie, the race? All right, did it.
I aced it. You must have left early. I aced it. All right, who has red lipstick? You? Once this
is all up with, we'll give you a special deal. All the bread you can eat. Oh, there's a bakery.
Who has lipstick? Electric goods? Toy store? In here? Wait, why can't, get out of my way.
The grocer's wife still hasn't come back yet. I wonder if she's all right.
Sourdough lipstick. Mega Man, I'm frightened. Can you stay here and protect me? Oh, I know you've got
to protect everyone, not just me. You can see yourself in the mirror. Maybe not as handsome as
some, but it's a good looking face. You feel a little more confident after looking at yourself.
Plus two attack. Imagine. On second thought, I'll keep the clothes I got. I mean, after all,
they were present, right? I wouldn't want to hurt my boyfriend's feelings.
All right, nothing in here. Talk to the clerk. Stare into the mirror. Oh, Mega Man, I'm so
frightened. Where do I get the lipstick? In the electronics store. I see you got a VCR fridge.
How much is the lipstick? Right here? I'm praying to God and my dead husband to watch over you
and protect this island. It's supposed to be that cashier in hip bone. What the heck? I need to
talk to the painter. Didn't I already? Remember? I was like, you have no talent. Oh, I could really
use some red. And I was like, yeah, you could. Yeah, I did. I talked to the artist like two times.
Do it again. I guess we're doing it again. What are you saying? I have to try another. Okay.
He's actually back. Yeah. What do you think? I was lying. You think I wasn't going to come back?
Nah, guys. Hey, I'll be back in a couple hours, two or three hours. No, just I'm not coming back
and I'm not going to finish Mega Man Legends. It's going to go unfinished forever.
We already did this. Remember some talent, some red.
Now we go talk to cashier. What's my thoughts on PB&J sandwiches? Disgusting. Get rid of them.
Gross. Replace the jelly with fluff. And then you've got, now you've got a believer out of me.
PB&J. No, no, no, no, PB and fluff hog. Sorry. What? What is that? Really? I thought, I thought,
I thought jelly was, I thought people didn't like, I thought a jelly was a,
well, I actually, I did just say disgusting. Didn't I? Yeah. That's not fair. Hey, William,
thanks for the five community subs, William. I didn't rebuild. No, I haven't rebuilt anything.
I have. All right. Okay. I've got $76,000. Should I rebuild some stuff? I think it's time.
Where do I go to? City hall? Who rebuilds stuff? Rebuild the town. But that's money that I can't
spend on me. I know that sounds fucking horrible, but you know what I mean? I need to be able to,
artist is the museum lady. Oh, well, let's, first of all, let's go get the red lipstick.
That's priority number one. I will only gift to this stream. I will never subscribe myself
because your content is so far. What? Why would you pay more money to a stream that you don't like?
What? That was the most, that doesn't fit in any logic. It's a power play.
I don't really like this stream, but I'm going to pay extra money to it. Hi there, Mega Man. Are
you looking for something? Yes. Red chalk for drawing. I didn't know you were an artist.
We don't have any red chalk, but I've got some red lipstick. Yes, give it to me. I'll give you mine.
Hey, Super Bruce. Thanks for the five community subs. Thank you, Super Bruce.
Glad I can help you see you later. Okay, got lipstick. Let's go give lipstick to lady. Here
we go. That's right. Where's the hype train? I turned off hype train. They don't exist anymore.
I don't, they don't exist, but imagine subbing to Jerma. Can you imagine? What do I find? Downtown,
uptown, uptown is to the left. Downtown is to the right. Oh no, twist. Can you imagine giving this
guy any money? He's a fucking stupid fucking goddamn fucking idiot. All right. I got red
lipstick for you. I thought I was going to get hit by that car. No, if I got hit by a car,
I'd have to get 500,000 subs. Do you think I'm going to get hit by a car right now? Look what I
have. I feel like I'm watching something on TV that's designed for like a one-year-old.
The way that she's talking. That's exactly what it needed. Thank you so much.
Oh, would you look at the time? I better be going. Hey, don't get hit by the car.
Wait, what? What just happened? What did I do? I didn't, I didn't get anything for that. All
right. She's gone. So now go to the museum. The museum doesn't exist. I have to rebuild it.
So I have to go to city hall, right? So I got to go east, north. It's that building right here.
This one? Wait, this one right, right here? This is the museum? This is the museum. No, this is the
doctor's office. Come on with the green woof. Uh, sorry. That's, that's K-T-O-X-T-V. This one. Oh,
this is the one that was closed. Oh, so she works here now. Okay. So that's why she had to leave
because now she works here. Does this place have a door? I tried to go in here before and it was
like, sorry, we're closed. Good afternoon. Welcome to the catalogs art museum. The first floor has
our art gallery and the second floor is our exhibition hall. Please take your time and enjoy.
That painting was made almost 20 years ago. It's beautiful, isn't it? It's all right. It looks like
some thing out of an sci-fi movie, doesn't it? Yeah, it's all right. This painting was apparently
found in a ruin somewhere. It looks like a person wearing blue armor is fighting with a frightening
monster. I wonder what the thing that looks like an eye there is supposed to be symbolizing.
It's all right. What do you think about this? Doesn't it feel like this painting is trying
to tell us something? Is it a warning or a prediction? What is this? Fire in the streets?
This is a painting of the marketplace. Oh, I thought this was like lava destroying a town.
Oh, all right. That one, that's all right. I wonder what that is. I don't know for sure myself.
I don't know either. What is this? This is a, that's a picture of our home catalogs.
Island as seen from the air. Let's go upstairs. Do I have to pay for a ticket or can I just go
upstairs? You don't have to pay to go to a museum, do you? No. They're all free, aren't they?
Wait, hold on. Aren't all the museums and most of them are free? Yeah, depends. Oh, it's you.
You hanging it up downstairs?
Could you bring it here and show it to me?
Do I have anything interesting? If it's really good, I could display it here.
You will? Great, thanks. I just got signed up. I just, all right, I just went to a gym on a trial
and now I go to this gym apparently. But there, it looks like a bone or something. Bone? Oh well,
a lot of the people who come here are into strange things like this. It doesn't look like much,
but is it a dinosaur bone? That's really cool. All right, I'll just play it.
You could call it a bone. How about you call it a, a bone from a living creature,
not ancient digging tool. I got more stuff.
No.
Maybe, hey, maybe you've seen some rich people. What do you think I got it?
If I have one of these, how come you don't put me in that category of rich person? I have one
in my pocket. Doesn't that mean I'm more rich that I'm carrying the fucking thing around?
Thank you so much. I bet there are a lot of people who'll come to see this.
Anything else? Oh, is that a crystal fossil? All right, you guys pay big bucks for this one.
Those are made when a weaver bot's body crystallizes over the centuries.
They're considered grade three national treasures. That's right. It would mean so much to me if you'd
let me display that here, please. Thank you so much. I bet there are a lot of people who'll
come to see this. I bet there are a lot of people. Okay, so do I have any more rare artifacts?
Where did you find that? That's an antique shield. Wait, is she taking all my stuff?
National treasures. Some weaver bot was probably using it to protect itself.
Is she taking my shields and shit? This is my equipment, isn't it? Is it? Thank you so much.
Oh, what's that you have on there? That blue armor looks really interesting. You found that.
Could I put it on display? You're a digger, right? If you find something interesting,
there are a lot of people. Bring it here and show me. I'll evaluate it for you and if it's
really nice, I'll put it on display here. This lady's talking into my soul. The way she's
talking is I can feel it. All right, what did I give? Don't you think this is just the loveliest
box? I really like these. Holy shit, you really were in desperate need of stuff. Look at this
cardboard box in the museum. Why is there a giant emerald? That's a beautiful diamond, isn't it?
It's one of my favorite displays. That's a diamond, yet you want me to pay for the town.
I have like $78,000. You have like $6 billion worth of diamond on the counter.
You can't like shave off a little bit of this. Ancient digging tool discovered in the
Cardan forest subgate. Appears to be made of animal bone. Cool. What about this? Giant horn,
believed to be the horn bang of an animal-shaped reaverbot, often found in rocky areas above ground.
Antique shield, grade two national treasure, apparently used by reaverbots for protection.
All right, this is my grade three. Grade three national treasure, fossilized remains of a dead
reaverbot. All right, what's this? That may look like any old rock, but it's really a rare and
valuable specimen. I'm missing some items? Oh well, we'll never get the end. Oh, that's cool.
Box and rock. Okay, so I got rid of some of those items. Now I need... why did I instinctively just
press triangle? Like I was going to get into the car. Third person, Grand Theft Auto, has just
changed everything. You see a car, you try to get in it with triangle. All right, so I need to rebuild
the town, so I gotta go to the town hall, right? City hall. Now, can you just drive me to city hall?
Mega Man gets into a car and drives to the grocery store ASMR.
Why ASMR? That's so stupid. All right, let's rebuild the town. I'll spend all my money. City hall.
Excuse me, I have an appointment. How much does it cost? Hello there, Mega Man. What can I do for you?
I'd like to make a donation. You will? Oh, thank you so much. I wonder where we should start. Well,
let's start with the residential houses. To complete the repairs to the residential houses,
we need an additional 18,000 zenny. How much do you want to donate? I'd like to give $18,000.
Thank you. This means so much to the island. I'd like to donate to bring back the condominium.
5,300 for the condominiums. What a weird number. 5,380. Oh no, I gave $20 like seven and a half
hours ago. I forgot. This means so much. All right, so how long does it take? Is that it? What can I
do for you? I'd like nothing, just came to see you. Oh my, why Mega Man? I'm happy to see you too.
I don't know quite what to say. Thank you. Okay, so did they do it? Does it take a while? Is this 20
year old video game logic? Are they just open? Let's go back to the market. I want to buy some
stuff. Do the poggers or the kappa face. I don't know what that one is, so I know how to do this one.
That's not kappa. How do you, what, somebody do it. What is it? I'm not doing it right. Somebody,
what is it? It's too small. I need to see it bigger. Is that right? It's kind of close.
Do the Jim Carrey Grinch face. I don't have like $40,000 of prosthetics on. I don't know what you
want from me. What are you talking about? All right, what do I need to do? I need to go to
the market. We're gonna buy a bunch of shit. Just hanging out with my 2,700 best friends
playing Mega Man Legends. We hate you. Parasocial relationship. What are you talking about? I'm here
with my best friends. Okay, defense. Extra pack. When does this max out? Shield repair. Repairs
damage life shield. Did I get another one? How many is this gonna have? Oh, buster unit, sniper
unit. All right, we're good. Now I have a ton of, let me make sure the canteen's refilled.
It's the Grinch face with no makeup. Holy shit. Oh my god. What the fuck? That's insane.
That's actually ridiculous. Oh my god. It's just his face. Is that, is he, all right, is that movie
any good? Show, I can't do that. Maybe I can. No, that's, that's like, I'm trying to like take a
shit in an airplane bathroom and I'm really anxious. That's what that was. Not even close.
I'm sorry. Who emoted? Hold on. I can't. That's just the, that's the bitter beer face from the
old beer commercials. Did you guys remember those commercials? The guy takes a sip out of the beer
and his face goes crazy. Just, all right, type in bitter beer face into YouTube and watch those
commercials. What, I don't even, I don't, okay, I know that joke, but I don't even know what beer it
was. No idea. Okay, let's pay attention for a second. I need to do, what is it, go to the
police station. Go to the police station and get a side quest. What's my favorite time zone?
The one that I currently live in because it's me existing in my own time. This one. I mean,
the one that I'm in. Why would I have a favorite time zone? Oh shit, I have to give 500,000 subs.
All right, let's go. Oh look, they're doing it. See, look, they're rebuilding everything. Look at
this. It's going to be a nice new town. You guys have to eat a Post-it note. No, I'm in the doctors
plenty enough. I'm not, I don't want to go in for anything else. All right, where's the police
station? Uptown? Is it Ikea houses? Where's the police? Where's the police? Where's the police?
Where's the police? Police. Hospital. Is it downtown? Did I miss it? Police. Police. Police.
Police. Downtown. Yeah, I gotta go back. And then north. That's two million dollars. That image is
not even, that image is just, I'm not even gonna put that on stream. That's just like, I bought an
iPad seven years ago and that's what I do with it every time I turn it on. That's what that image is.
Hounds rebuilding, yeah. All right, let's go. Police station. Oh, what the hell are you doing?
All right, I feel like, oh god, let's get the shit out of me. I feel like, I feel like sometimes
somebody will post an image in here and they just went into Photoshop and hit the random button
and then they just hit save in the paste as soon as possible. Is there a randomized button in
Photoshop? Why the hell wouldn't they have done that? They're losing out on a lot of potential
subscribers to Adobe Photoshop. Will it, you know, take care of all the weird stuff?
Give a job? I'm supposed to be out investigating everything that's been happening but I just can't
seem to get excited about work anymore. It's kind of, well, that's a little depressing, I guess.
Mega Man, isn't it? The inspector's inside. Go on in. All right, what do you got for me?
We kind of reached the end of our rope with this last disaster. Things haven't completely quieted
down yet, so we'll stay on alert status for a little while longer. When you have the time,
stop by and talk to us sometime. Never know when we might need your help again.
Oh, Mega Man, I was hoping you'd come by. There's something I'd like to ask your help with.
A little while ago, this little kid with a yellow face came up to me and told me that
he dropped something downtown. I didn't really understand what he said to me. He said he dropped
three things and that we'd all better run with something. I'm not sure what it all means,
but I've got a hunch something's not right. Could you go check things out for me? What?
Thanks and good luck. What the fuck are you talking about? Wait, say that again? Okay, so
this guy, he's planting, uh, all right. It's fucked up. All right, let's go. Yeah,
this kid just did a bomb threat. I didn't really get it though. Yeah, what the fuck is he talking
about? Uh, save before it's too late. I'm busy. What do you mean you're busy? What do you mean
you're busy? He's just shit faced. Yeah, that's just, that's a guy that's just really, really
drunk. It's too late to go back. Where are these are? Where are the bombs? I'm sorry. I was not
paying very much attention. I was like downtown. This is the bad end. Bad end. How much did you
pay for this copy of the game? Um, I don't think it was that expensive. I think it's pretty cheap
actually. A bomb. That must be what the inspector was talking about. You've got to find the other
two before they explode. Maybe if you can find someone who saw something. No. Did you see
something? What was that noise? It sounded like a bomb going off. Wait, that means that the thing I
saw over by the greenhouse must have been. Oh no. Okay, greenhouse. This is a greenhouse, right?
This is a greenhouse. Oh, this also is a greenhouse. Got it. You found a bomb. Mega Man,
here's the switch. There, now it's disarmed. Only one more. All right, we can find, excuse me,
anybody? Anybody? You. What do you see? You see something? Are you looking for something?
You know, I lost something myself recently. I was fixing a roof and I forgot my tools
on the roof of all places. Last place I thought of to look. Just goes to show you things are always
in the place you least expect to find them. Who knows? Maybe what you're looking for is on
somebody's roof. Is this the guy? Is this the, is this the person that put the bomb on the roof?
Why? That's very, very incredibly descriptive. All right, you get on the roof. But what roof?
There it is. Okay, it's on that roof. I see it. Okay, how do I get out? Can I jump? You. Is that it?
There's not, is there more than one? That's who? Didn't say there's one more. Is that it? Am I done?
The music's still going. There's three bombs and one blew up. So that's it, right? I can leave.
The music's still, I think that's good. All right, let's go back and talk to the inspector again.
I don't know, dude. I didn't play this game. Derma sucks at this game, though. Man, he sucks.
That's, why'd you have to say it twice? Just to make sure you saw. Just wait that way. Just wait
that way. Derma sucks. Thanks to the five community subs. I did what you asked. Oh, it's you,
Mega Man. I saw the report about the bombs. We're lucky you found them all. Before they went off,
you saved the city again. Thanks for helping us. We're counting on you. We're counting on you.
All right, done. You stink. I love that picture of him. Hey, Mega Man. I could use your help with
something. A man came to us saying he's lost the money he was going to use to build his house.
Poor fellow. I'd like you to see if you can find the bag this fellow dropped. The owner of the bag
is out there in the lobby. You should go talk to him. You drop a bag? Reverb bots in underground
cities? Oh, that's a little out of my league. Where are you? What'd you drop? Bustard man. Oh,
where could I have left it? I'm pretty sure I had it when I went to the electronic shop.
I've been saving for years so I could build my dream house too. Oh, what am I going to do?
Humans are animals. Yeah, that's true. Mammal to be exact. Yeah, we got a wink. I just saw it.
Give me a free soda. Do I have a beard? No, I just I can't grow a beard. This turns into weird,
gross strands of dark looking spaghetti on my face. All right, let's go to the
southern part. Why did I choose a wink as a thing? I don't know because
channel points came out and that day I was like, oh, it's just a wink. Who cares?
And now it's turned into the biggest mistake I've ever done on Twitch. This has to be the
biggest mistake I've done on YouTube and Twitch combined. All right, electronics. The junk shop.
Winx ruined his life. All right, what do you got? You left your bag here? Someone carrying a bag?
Yeah, I saw him. He said he had lots of money so I tried to get him to buy something but he didn't
buy anything. He said that it wasn't his money to spend. He left saying he wasn't going to get
something to eat. All right, so he went to the bakery. All right, he went to the bakery. Once
this is all over with, we'll give you a snow. All right, where did he go? Over here? There are tomatoes,
cucumbers, and other vegetables. That's a fake link. Is there another like a restaurant? Not a
real link. I can see them. So where did he get food? Over here at this meat shop? Welcome, huh?
Middle-aged man carrying a bag. Well, he bought some bread and then left saying he had something
to look up. I don't think a single piece of bread will be enough of a meal for a grown man.
Something he needed. Something he had to look up? Did he go to the library? Is there a library in
the game? Have I been in a library? What building is it? Downtown? I went to the museum. All right,
library. Is this a library? This looks like a library. All right, library. A man carrying a
bag. Yes, I saw him. He looked like he was having some kind of problem breathing. Like he had some
things stuck in his throat. Maybe he went looking for something to drink. What? Is there a bar?
Or should I... one of the vending machines? Check the vending machines. Okay, there's one here.
You got a soft drink. You just wasted your channel points? I'm sorry to hear that. Not that one.
He wanted a drink. He got a soft drink. You see anybody? A middle-aged man carrying a bag. Hmm.
Well, I did see a man who didn't look well buy some juice, but he didn't have a bag though. If
it's the same man, he must have lost it before coming here. Why don't you ask around? Don't you
watch detective stories? That's the first step of any investigation. Find suspects and question them.
So it was from the library to here. Boy, that old guy really made me angry. Get a license
and registration please. Saw him. He went running by real fast. Even ran into me. Kept on going
without even so much as a sorry. I was angry so I put the bag he dropped into a trash can.
Did he send you to look for it? Well, it's over there. Why don't you go get it? Bag. It's the killer.
All right, I got the bag. Back to the police station.
North. North. This song makes me want to pog. It's all good. That's a good thing.
How is it? Why is it a bad thing? Directionally challenged. Yes, I know.
I know. Blame the GPS system. Blame the invention of the GPS. We're all gonna be
fucked. Guys, even if I'm going down the street and I know exactly where I'm going, if I get in
my car... I know exactly where I'm going. GPS is just on. Just don't matter. It's just on.
All right, I got your bag. Where's the guy with the... I got a bag. Wait, why? I don't know.
What does he do? Why is he not in here? Oh, there you are. Wait, that bag. It looks like...
What? You found it? Oh, thank you so much. I was frightened to death thinking about what my wife
would do to me if she found out what had happened. As a reward, let me give you some of the money.
What did you say? You don't need any? Well, here, at least accept this as thanks from me.
Arm supporter. No, give... I'll take some money. I'm counting on you. All right, I did it. Arm
supporter. I got a lot of new items. Wait, did he say... Did he say, oh, here's some money? No, no,
wait. No, you actually... You don't need it. Or did I say, I don't need it? There's not much happening
right now. Okay. One more try. Not much happening. Is somebody sick in the hospital? Okay.
We'll go to the hospital. What's that? You say you don't need money? I'm going to use that at
the drive-through. And then the person will just very, very clearly say, sir, that'll be... That'll
be $8 and 20 cents. Please drive up. Sir, that'll be $8 and 20 cents. Please drive up. I thought I
had... I pressed the button. Yeah, you can't do omega lol minus two omega lol. Not counting.
You're laughing. I win. I win. All right, let's get the car. Now I'm quiet, am I? Not anymore.
Give me some development here. Plastic was used to make Power Blaster L versus your firing range,
but your firepower is well. The bomb was used to make Power Blaster R, heavy-duty combat,
versus both firepower and speed. Okay. That's it. One more development. Favorite fast food
restaurant. Oh, that's tricky. That's tricky. I don't know if I can answer that. All right.
Four attack. This is Omni Unit. Increases all abilities by one. Power Blaster R.
Now, these are not very good. Plus two, one, plus two, no. This shit I got is way better.
Plus three to both. What's my favorite fast food place? I mean, McDonald's is a really good...
McDonald's is a go-to. It's very, very... It's just, I know exactly what I like there.
I don't think McDonald's is the best fast food restaurant, but it's the one that it's pretty
easy to go to. I already did a tier list. Ash House or GoGo is not fast food. It's a sit-down
restaurant. Wendy's? No, I'll be honest. I got sick of Wendy's. I don't know. This is weird.
It's weird. I think Wendy's is a better... It's a better place than McDonald's. I think Wendy's is
better than McDonald's, but I got sick of Wendy's. I didn't get... Jesus, that scared the fucking shit
out of me. Stop! Who just ran me? Somebody just ran me over. I got kind of sick of Wendy's.
I don't know why, but I've not gotten sick of McDonald's. All right, let's go to the hospital.
Hospital's in uptown. I thought I could beat it. Uptown is west? Yes. No, it's south and then west.
All right, just drive. Just bring me there. I have access to a car. Is there a person on the roof?
Well, I don't know. Whatever. I'm going to the hospital. Somebody said there's a sick person
in the hospital. There's a side quest in here. That's where I'm going. How much longer of this
game? Until it's done and then I'm gonna be done streaming. This is the hospital. Okay, who's in
the hospital? You. We don't get many patients, actually. Everyone on the island's pretty healthy.
You. Am I? I actually don't know the answer to this question. Yeah.
All right, yeah. How do I do that? I feel like I've come down with a cold.
But I thought I'd have the doc take a look at me. All right, let's go. I gotta. Let's leave and come
back. In the hospital with a cold. Room 305. You know, I thought I would go to the hospital. I
have a stuffy nose. Am I? Did I make it? One of my patients is this darling little girl, but she's
very ill and has lost the ability to walk. If we just had some more modern equipment here, we could
probably cure her, but I just wish there was something I could do for her. I don't have any
equipment? Sure, but we don't have any equipment. Well, we're supposed to talk. I'm supposed to
tell her stories of my adventures. I don't have an item. I'm gonna go talk to the mayor. All right,
we'll go talk to the mayor. If only there was some person who could allocate funds to the city,
some sort of mayoral figure. I know, I just wanted to talk. I just wanted to talk for a sec.
All right, where's my special car? Take me to city hall. I'm gonna make this. I'm gonna make this
good. Kill the monkey. Why do you guys want me to kill the monkey? Can you use a funny voice changer
for the rest of the stream? I'll do this for you. I will pitch shift myself up one, one tab and see
if anybody realizes it as we play. Like this. Sorry, like this. Okay, so I'm pitch shifted up
one tiny bit and I'm gonna tell everybody I got a new microphone. Is this too noticeable?
Is it? Is this too noticeable? No, it's not. You can't hear it at all. Not at all. How about that?
You tell me when it gets to be too like, like absolutely he's fucking around and he's making
a joke. At that point, no. Like, oh wow, this is funny. He's like on a voice change run. Is
that way there now? Go back? Don't go so too far. Okay. So how's this? Is this better? Right here?
A little bit more. This is perfect. I'll actually heal him. What if I do this? How does this sound?
This is going to be a little bit different. Should I go more? Like over here? Or back? No,
I can't. I don't know what it sounds like. I have no idea what this sounds like. A little more? No,
lower? All right. How's that? Right here? Right there? That sounds all right, doesn't it? Right
here. Right here. Higher. Too low? No, no, no. I think it's all right. Is this any different from
the normal mic? All right. I'll show you what the difference is. Uh, A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G. A, B, C, D, E, F, G. That sounds the same. That's the same. Exactly the same.
No way. A, B, C, D. A, B, C, D. People think the speakers are broken? How could there be no
difference? I don't understand how it could be. I don't really like get it. Usually I can get this
off pretty quickly. I have to do that like once a week. I'm sorry. Somebody, okay, person on the
roof. Who the fuck is on the roof? I don't see anybody on a roof. What are you talking about?
I mean, if you give me access to instant bugleberry, I'm going to use it like at least
once every couple of weeks. Somebody's on the roof of the hospital. What? Are you serious?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Where is this person? This person on the roof of the city hall?
I don't see anybody up here. To the left of city hall. There is no left of city hall. That is city
hall, isn't it? There's nobody on a roof. What are you talking about? There ain't nobody on a roof.
Shit, I jumped. I thought you guys were bullshitting me. Why would I think there'd
be somebody walking around on a roof? I'd love to climb the main gate, but I'm sure the police
would stop me. Yeah, this was a real good quest. There's a wink. Worst fucking thing I've ever done
in my life is put that on. Okay. City, we've got a city hall. City hall. We got to go to city hall.
Remove it. No, I'm gonna, don't worry. I'm going to give you a date for when it's going to get
removed. Imagine paying 75,000 points and getting a half-assed wink. I know. It's,
I know. Trust me. I'm aware. I know. Imagine paying 75,000 points. Okay. About the hospital's
equipment. I've been wanting to upgrade the hospital's equipment with the latest models
for some time, but to do that we need $15,000. I can do it. You don't have enough money? What?
I don't have any money. I don't have enough money. All right. I'm going to go get,
I gotta get money. Imagine using points and not advertising Nancy Drew. All right. I'm going to
go grind. Uh, where's a good grind spot? Those, uh, it's a good spot to get like quick money.
That old, that old town place. Go to the card and forest dungeon. Um, on a pulse that I didn't make,
I don't mean anything. I just want to make sure to wear that. Replace German with Bugleberry for
rest of the stream. No. Why would I do that? In like title, the stream Bugleberry finishes
Mega Man. What are you guys trying to do to me? All right. The dungeon here. Vacuum for grinding.
Save the grocer's wife. Why is this a good grind spot?
Do you place it in that old city better? This is not the dungeon.
This is not a good spot. Yeah. The dead, the spots with the, um, yeah, that's what I was thinking.
Bring the drill into. Yeah. I'm going to, I'll equip the drill. Uh, let's go. Which one's this one
downtown? Let's go to the one. Let's go. I'm here. I'm ready. I just need like fucking to do it like
two or three times. How much do I donate for a full 60 seconds of Bugleberry? I really don't know
where I'm supposed to be going next. I think if it were me and it is me Bugleberry, I would say
I would need to go west. Oh, sure. It's scary for diabolical going west. I will tell you something
that I think is important. I have not picked up a controller in probably 30 years. I don't know
anything about video games. I don't know what buttons to press. Maybe you guys could help me,
but I thought it would be fantastic. Oh, that was, oh, I forgot to tell you the price. Uh,
it was five grand. A thousand, a hundred thousand channel points to get a high from Bugleberry. No,
that's the same thing as a wink. It's just more, it's a button I have to press and I have to derail
like, oh, hey, it's me Bugleberry. Hey, it's me Bugleberry. Hey, oh, oh, oh, it's me Bugleberry.
A million points. Oh, fuck. Exposed. It's not him. Go get the mask. No. No, I don't want to get the
mask and turn the lights down in the room and like do Bugleberry. No, he's not here.
What am I doing? I keep getting sidetracked. All right, I'm going to go up.
No, I, it's right here. There it is. Save the Grosher's wife.
They'll be all right for a little bit. I'll be good. I just need to get some money.
I'm gonna let Bugleberry scream. I'm gonna get killed. How much are these all worth? What's the,
what are the blue ones actually even worth? Oh, what the heck? Where? I haven't saved the fucking
game. I haven't saved the fucking game. I haven't saved the fucking game. I haven't saved the fucking
game. I gotta kill this guy first. Explode. There we go. All right, good. 75,000 for
Germakiss. I don't even know what that means. My cat's having a bad dream. Can you wish her well?
No, I wish you, I wish you not having a bad dream, cat. Did it help?
Pretty good grind spot. You're right. All right, do it again. How much money do I have? 33,000.
I'm gonna do this like five times. 19,000. I'll make it faster with the vacuum. Come pick me up.
Are you sure? This is like an eight dollar lift ride. You really want to go down the street?
Yeah, I guess. I don't want to walk. Where's my, not the drill, not the grenade. The vacuum. Okay.
Coke versus Pepsi. Coke is better. Coke is better than Pepsi. In fact, most of the Coke products
are better than the Pepsi products. For instance, like Sprite, way better. Sprite,
yes. Sprite's the best soda. Like just, if I could only have one soda for the rest of my life,
it would be Sprite. Okay, everyone asks for Coke and Sprite, but all you have is Sierra
Mist and Pepsi. I know. It's like, you know, frankly, it's bullshit. I'll be honest. Frankly,
it's bullshit. Can I get a Coke? We have Pepsi only. Yeah, they made a Super Bowl commercial on
it. Doesn't that mean that people like Coke more than Pepsi? Remember like the Steve Carell
commercial where it was like, is Pepsi okay? Is Pepsi okay? No, Pepsi's better and it's awesome
and of course it's okay. Well, I asked for Coke, but clearly it's not. They're both the same damn
thing. The only difference is Coke. Pepsi is like smoother than Coke. Coke is a little harsher.
I like it like that though. Joel bullies Germo. What? I don't have time for his shit right now.
Free money. Free money. Free money. Free money. Free money. Free money. Free money. Yep.
Coke in the glass is unbeatable. Yeah, I would say so. Where are you? How much for a Bugleberry
appearance? What if I just did like a one-man show and there was those, you remember those old like
infomercial kind of commercials? Imagine I advertised for it on TV. Like Bugleberry being
there would be like a selling point for one of the tickets. And don't forget, B.F. Bugleberry
will make his appearance doing his one-man take on the current horror movies. And it's just fucking
me in a mask like, for one night only. And who could forget Grandpa? And just me with a mustache
on like a hat on like, you know, you're ruining the illusion. But that would be me doing the
Bugleberry impression. I can't. I mean, these are real people. You don't think I have a real
grandfather? I, of course I do. And he's been on camera. All right, give me a room. This way,
that way, this way, that way, this way, that way. Ever since somebody said that with the auto face
is the only thing I can think of. Whoa, you came out of nowhere. You storm trooper for the next
five minutes. What does that mean? What are you talking about? Like,
that what you want? Pick up that cam. That it? Nope. That's that was on like Obama on a shitty
mic. Okay, the pitch is down. I get you. It's a combine. All right. Yeah, I see. What does it
sound like? You just called Obama on the phone. I didn't get the money. Do pick up that.
Yeah. I'm missing money. What? I have to pay attention to video games. Call Bernie Sanders.
This is not like the impression. The funny impression hour. Who cares? Yeah. Well, I
call Bernie. Oh, I've been called Bernie Sanders right now. Let's see what he's up to.
Actually, I know what he's up to. He's debating on stage down the street. That's where he is.
They're in Nevada right now. How much money do I have? All right. I got enough. I got enough.
We can go do all this stuff. Raid them with this. Wait, raid the Democratic primary debate.
It's not even that's not impossible. Can you imagine how stupid that would be?
All right. Imagine a world, right? Can you imagine? Yeah. And Elizabeth Warren, what do you
think about? Oh, hold on a second here. What's going on? Are we getting a raid? Yeah. It looks
like we're getting a raid from German 985. Gerber, Gerber. Hey, how are you, Gerber? It is great to
hear your voice. Oh, the rats. Here come the rats. Here they are. Oh, the rats. Here they are.
I love those rats. Hey, how stupid would that be? It would be fucking unbelievable.
People just keep raiding to get like this. Hey, thanks for the raid. It would be like calling
out people in chat. I just want to say, if we could put it in sub only mode, I'm seeing a lot
of bullshit over here. I don't, there's a lot of stuff that I don't like. No, no, no. You don't
actually have. No, I don't mean, that wasn't me.
Raiding the debate and they have to address it. And if they don't address it, it's like, yo,
whoa. I'm not going to like, not going to mention the raid. Okay. But if I follow any of you on
Twitter. All right. Let's go back to, uh, they do like an elaborate, like, like, oh, we got a raid
and they fucking start screaming and like talking about the raid. Like, look out, it's a raid.
Oh, the German, the rats. Everyone has their own, everyone gets like 10 seconds to respond.
Um, Mr. Steyer, how do you respond to the rat raid? I don't, I, I don't know who the fuck that
is. Can we go back to the issues, please? Steyer's not in the debate. Really? Are you sure? Because
he's the only commercial I see on TV. Are we certain about that? All right. Where am I going?
All right. Right. I get it. Okay. I got to go. Who watches TV?
Hospital. All right. We're going to go up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up the city hall.
Just take me there. If you have enough, if you have enough Twitch followers, you get to be on
the debate stage. Yeah. The new, the new, uh, the new percentages you need to be on the stage at
the Nevada debate. Yeah. You need at least 10% of the national poll or a peak at over 10,000
concurrent viewers on Twitch. We've got quite a few people here actually from like the Twitch
side of things. Ninja versus Bernie debate. All right. Let's, let's get the fuck out of this.
Oh, we're talking politics. No, I'm not. We're talking, uh, I guess kind of. Tom Steyer paid
for a mariachi band and a taco truck at my caucus location in South Vegas. Hey for the equipment.
Yeah. The debates are in Vegas right now. I can pay for that. Did I do it? About the investigation.
The only room left unexplored is the main gate. Who knows what's inside and what will happen if
we tamper with it. I don't know if it hadn't been for you, Mega Man. I shudder to think what those
pirates would have done to the Island. I'll leave everything in your capable hands. All right. Let's
go back. The fate of our Island rests on your shoulders. Thanks for the pressure. God damn it.
You could have just said good luck. All right. Somebody just said fail politics with a cringe
country. What does that mean? Fail politics for a cringed country. That's fucking ridiculous.
I love it. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Dude, your country is kind of cringe.
I mean, this isn't, this isn't your dad singing happy birthday in loudly in a restaurant for
dinner. This is like an entire country. What? That's not inaccurate. Exactly. Oh, shit. Oh,
shit. Debate panel. Bernie, how would you like to respond to that? I just want to say that I think
that answer was cringe. Yeah. Oh, cringe, you fucker. You posted cringe and you shouldn't feel bad for
that. Get him, get him Bernie. You face cam for the entire stream. No, he's not talking about his
other people's low sub and follower count. I mean, I don't. All right. I got to play,
I have to play Mega Man Legends. Okay. Hold on. Did I save it? I did. Right. We got to go to the
hospital, which is in uptown. Do Obama reading bits from the phone? Bro, are we playing Mega
Man Legends or not? Fuck. Yes. Yes, we are. Yes, we are. Back to the hospital. This way, that way,
this way, that way. Oh, I can't get it out of my head. I love it. Okay. I'm here. You have to,
you can't go inside without checking in. I mean, can't you guys just put me on like a list? I'm
the guy in the blue suit. Oh, shit. The nurse told me that you bought them a machine that fixed my leg.
Thank you. This is for you. What is it? I found it when I was out for a walk.
Flower Pearl. Come back and see me again. Pearl. Come back and see me again. All right. A little
more rehabilitation and her leg will be as good as new. She can go home then. Thank you so much.
That's what I do. I'm Mega Man. Finally saved the grocer's wife. She's out in a field. I don't know
where that is. I have no idea. I have no idea. I don't know where that is. Let's see if I can do
anything with this. I wonder if I got the posse to do anything with this. Develop something. Let me.
Mega Man. Gatling part and Flower Pearl were used to make the Buster part Gatling gun.
Really? So, Kardon Forest. Can you tell me there's somebody right here? The one percent of
streamers, they got all the bits. That's cringe everyone. We need to wake up, wake up America.
We need to give big bits to the people. That's a cringe. God damn it. So, walk through the path
between the rocks at the flutter. The path between the rocks. These two rocks. Got it. I came out
here to get some fresh air and look at the scenery, but my stomach, oh it hurts. What do you do? Take
her to the hospital. See if she gets better. Anna, are you all right? Sorry, but you can't go inside
without. You just watched me come in and bring like a sick person. Have you come to visit Iron?
No. If you're worried about that woman who just came in, she's fine. Maybe you should come back
after she's calmed down a little. Outman. Use a JPG instead of a face cam? Nah. I'm back. My new
father seems really happy. Thanks for your help. You're welcome. Um, I did? Have you come to visit
Iron? I, no, I came to, is that it? That's it. You're the one who helped Anna, aren't you? Thank you
so much. Here, take this as a token of my thanks. You got a sunlight. All right. But did you just
like push me outside? Get some vitamin D, you little shit. Can I do anything with this? Nope. Okay.
All right. It's time. It's time to go to the main gate. It's time. I'm gonna put on the Gatling gun.
Put it here. Okay. Buster parts. Equip. The Gatling gun. So this is attack four. Gatling gun is
one, attack one range in four energy. No. I think what I had on was the best thing I can do.
It's just a ton of attack in a ton of, I can just spam with the max attack. The only thing I do,
I mean, I only have rapid. I'm surprised this is not rapid. Okay. How could it be Gatling gun?
If it's just, yeah, I'll keep what I had on. I have to put, I'm going to spend the rest of my money.
We have to go downtown first. We got to refill the canteen. Buy a couple more things and that's it.
Try it. Please try it. Try it. Try it. What? Is that north? I went to the museum. I'm still missing
a couple items though. Hope you have a wonderful day. See you later. Hope you have a wonderful day
too. Thanks. That's really nice of you. Say that. Refill canteen. All right. Buy. This Kevlar jacket
is 120. But fuck it. Blasted unit. Range. Turbo battery. Is there any rapid? No. Blasted unit omega.
Is that two and three? That's kind of okay. But is it maxed out? I'll get the, I'll get the
shield. The invincibility. I'm going to get the invulnerability shield and just get all these
things. I'll figure out what the fuck they do. All right. I'm going to sell some stuff. Sell.
Oh my God. No, I'm using all these. I don't think I'm going to use these ever. I really don't think
I'm going to put at least these. Maybe the Gatling gun. Maybe. I don't know. I have no idea. What about
items? Anything worth a lot of money? Can I get a hit of your jewel please?
All right. Time to save the game. Not yet. We do special weapons. Change weapon. I'm going to,
what should I put on for? Active buster. I think that's what I've upgraded the most.
Active buster. And we're going to enhance it. Do I have enough money to do anything with it?
I have 14,000. Nope. Blow. Blow. Please. Please. Blow. What? Please. Bro. Bro. Please. Please,
bro. Do a five second review of Overwatch. Um, the game was fun for six months and I never
played it again. That's it. Save again. Rick and Morty impressions. That's not going to happen.
Anybody know if the new episode came out yet? The new, like they were there, they're half season,
right? Oh, try Gatling gun. Try Gatling gun. Try Gatling gun. So let's go. Let's take off.
Auto battery and put on Gatling gun. You can see it's not doing very much. It was better having
the auto battery on, but I have max energy that I can just spam. I'm going to hold it down the
whole time. Move around. All right. Let's go to the room. Uh, I have to go to, it's all the way down.
Wish I had the Kevlar right now, but I don't. Oh, I'm so fucking nervous. Screen saver room
or, I mean, we've given this a couple of names. This also could be potential virus. Why? Why can
I say ours today? Potential virus. The joke is ruined. Potential virus shareware FPS game made
by one person in like 1996. If I said it correctly the first time, maybe it would have been humorous.
Shareware? What? What did I, I said shareware. Shareware. Shareware. And now I have, now my
shield's gone. What? He's devolving. Shareware. I have an accent sometimes. You know, everybody
doesn't talk the same way. There's different places that have different accents. Nobody talks
the same way. Build it. Build it. How do I activate that super shield? It's a good level
design. I know it's not. I'm sorry. I'm showing you this, that level design. Why is it so bright?
It's part of the way the game gets captured through this upscaler. All right. Here we go.
This is it, right? Huh? There's some writing. Watcher. What is that supposed to mean?
It's just labeled, Mega Man. The second door. What is this? It reads sleeper.
Third door. What does this one say? Dreamer? Well, it should be the last one.
Uh oh. Here comes the great, the big reveal of the game. What's happening to me? This is the first
time I've ever been here, but I feel like I've seen this before. Something is telling me there's
danger here, that it shouldn't be opened. Uh oh. It's a man? Person? Sephiroth? Was it you who
awoke me? It is somewhat earlier than I had, but no matter. Thank you for awakening me. Hmm. Have
we met before? Oh, please forgive me. You are a purifier model, assigned to the direct command
of Mother. Team Rocket? You are designated Mega Man Trigger. Please forgive me. I did not recognize
you in your current configuration. You, you know me? You don't remember? Ah, I see. You have
suffered memory loss, yes? Then for what purpose have you awakened me? I assume. I'm gonna kill you
myself, that's why. That your reason for coming here is to purge the carbons that have over
propagated during the time I was inactive. Carbons? Purge? What are you talking about?
According to Urban Military Security Ordinance A10, the number of carbon units is not allowed
to increase beyond the pre-specified limit. If this happens, they are to be purged immediately.
My observation, if left unattended, the carbons will reproduce indefinitely. Their numbers will
grow, polluting the surface world. They can be quite a nuisance. Carbons? Do you mean
the people on the island? The carbons fit mass population Model B. They are unstable,
very difficult to control. Perhaps it would be better to simply reinitialize. Reinitialize?
No, no, you don't understand. I haven't understood much of what you've been saying,
but when you say reinitialize, do you mean no? No, you don't. No, no, the universe is fine.
The universe is fine.
Teasel? This is quite reprehensible. It would be much simpler if I had the
assistance of a proficient unit such as yourself. It was horrible. Once my task is complete,
I shall inquire as to the presence of a backup of your memory on A1.
All right, can we get the stop? No more flashing, please? Yes, until then.
Oh, this hurts. I'm about to press a button. Did you hear that, Teasel? Yep,
something tells me he's not kidding either. It's the Tron bones. Teasel, we've got to do
something. We've got to stop him. That's easier said than done. Besides, do you think we could
beat him? The Tron bones. What about Mega Man? I don't like it, but I can't think of anything
better, so. Oh, here's a problem. Hey, Tron, how do you stop this thing?
Oh, this? Like this. Thank you. Mega Man. Oh shit, pirates. Thanks for your help.
Hurry up. He's getting away. Right. It's not over between you and me. I won't forgive you if you die
or anything stupid like that, so be careful in there, okay? Right. See you later. Don't worry,
Tron. If anyone can do it, he can. I know. Don't die, you stupid fucking idiot. I haven't even
got a chance to play. I'm going to get healed. Just relax. Ooh, Mega Man dies from the first
enemy. Power stream. He's still giving me items. Isn't this like the final portion of the whole
game? Oh shit, a golden crab. Is it a buster part? Oh fuck, it is. All right, laser is plus four
attack. Max is out attack. All right, hold on a second here. Maxed attack, maxed energy. That
means I don't need this anymore. Energy in rapid? No, no, I don't need any. I'm looking for range
in rapid. Do I have any range in rapid? No range, no rapid. Energy in range, attack in range,
attack, range, and energy. No, I don't need that. I have rapid two. Is rapid two better than range
in rapid one? Let's see. I lose range though. That's okay, that's pretty good. Gatling gun, laser.
No, there's nothing else down here. Damn, no range. Are we sure? Range, sniper scope. I mean,
that's just a, just, it's all range. Let me see what this does. Range and a little bit more range
and then I'll do this for now. No, you're right. I'm going to need the range. I'm going to need the
range. Might as well take it if it's for free. Final boss room is tiny. Well, appreciate the
spoiler because that means I can take this off. And what is this going to do rapid too? Or is it,
it was a rapid, what's it called? Rapid striker. But this range might be bad. Oh well. I have plus
three rapid? Did I? Is this the room? You can feel tremendous energy emanating from the refractor.
It's being held in place by some kind of powerful force. It appears as if the entire main gate
is under the control of Mega Man Juno. Who am I? Mega Man Volnut, right? Well, looks like we're
going this way. Mega Man Juno versus Mega Man Volnut. His name is much cooler than mine. This
is a bright area. I can't even see. Dentist hallway? Yeah, pretty much. Uh oh. What's the
point of this room? No, what's the point of this room? Like, why would you put that there? I'm
fucking pissed. Well, I haven't gone this way.
Well, I found the door. Well, we've come a long way, haven't we? It would have been nice if we
could have just kept on living in peace with Professor Enroll. But I guess we got to do what
we got to do, right? Mega Man Juno is waiting for you inside. A fucking cringed monkey. I'm not
done exploring. Tell me the lore? What lore do you want me to tell you? I'm not done exploring.
No, I'm not. I'm not done. Look at down there. There's probably a secret enemy.
There's not. No holes or anything? Well, what the fuck? All right, let's go. It's the end game. I
know, but I would think there'd be some fun. Didn't 100% the game? It's too bad, I know.
Tell me, what should I do now? Mega Man Juno is waiting for you inside. You can do it,
Mega Man. I believe in you. Is it going to be okay? Well, you may not know anything about Juno, but
judging from his model type, I'd say that your combat capabilities exceed his. Juno wasn't
designed for combat, but still, as master of the island, you shouldn't underestimate him.
Your relative levels of strength depend on how much you've developed your capabilities and weapons.
What am I? What's the matter, Mega Man? Oh, you're wondering about what Juno said, hey?
Does it matter? Whoever you are, you're still Mega Man, right? Come on,
Roll and everyone else are counting on you. This is the real villain. You can't give up now.
This is the real villain. I knew it was going to- I should have said it. I was thinking it,
but I didn't say it. I knew it was going to be a fucking organ, and I didn't say it,
and it would have been perfect. It appears I miscalculated the odds of your ability
to escape that trap. Shit. I was going to say it too, right when I opened the door.
However, too late. Eden was activated as soon as I entered this room. It cannot be deactivated as
long as I, the master key of this island, remain here in this controller. A lot of trash out in
space. All that remains now is to wait for Eden to enter transmission range and send the command
to execute the reinitialization of this island. Once that command is received, the 10,000 workers
aboard Eden will execute it immediately. My estimates indicate their work will be completed
in less than five minutes. I only said Trump voice. This doesn't sound like Trump at all.
Not even close. Uh, we stopped this, right? Now that Eden has been activated, any further
interference from you will remain on file, thus tarnishing my operating record. Now that Eden
has been activated- No, no, it's not. Fortunately, you are suffering from memory loss and fragmentation.
Therefore, as keeper of this island, I hereby exercise my prerogative of correctional dispensation.
Correctional? Allow me to rephrase. I will exercise my authority to terminate your program.
Begin!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Not a combat model yet. What the fuck are you talking about?
Don't I have like invincibility? How do I turn on invincibility mode?
How about this? Ready? How about this?
Oi! What the fuck is he? What the fuck?
Fucking L1R1 to turn the camera. It's just like, I may as well fucking put a blindfold on.
I'm killing him, don't worry. Yeah, I chose that setting because the other one was way worse.
The other one does- you can't strafe. Strafing doesn't exist if I turn the other one on,
which sucks. Oh, what a pain in the absolute ass this actually is.
It's just puke controlled. The whole world got- the quick turn like is hard to do because it's down
in circle and sometimes it doesn't do anything. By the time you turn around you have to- he's
already gone, so I have to hold R1 to like- and then walk forward. I can't increase the
sensitivity on that fucking R-E. It's not gonna happen.
What the fuck is happening?
Somebody said that in chat. I thought you were making fun of me, but it's what a line he says.
Ready?
Not good enough. Turn, turn around. Turn the fuck around.
What does that move? Heal. He's got a new attack this motherfucker.
Ready?
Oh, I forgot!
What?
What? I jumped over it.
The fuck is?
Hey, I'm ready for you to die. No choke. No choke. No choke. No choke. I can't even turn
the fucking camera. I can't even turn the camera. I can't even turn the camera.
Oh shit.
Really? It's- it's delayed.
He's gonna plug into a big thing.
He's plugging into the ceiling and he's gonna turn into a giant thing. He's gonna turn to a
key and unlock the door and behind the door is gonna be something huge.
Yeah, of course there is. Why wouldn't there be?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Turn! What?
What is that move he's doing? What the fuck is this move? Shield repair.
Okay, now go invisible and recharge special weapon. All right, let's go.
He can't see shit. He doesn't know where I am. And then- oh my god.
I thought I had the shield fixed. I thought I've repaired the shield and I could take another hit.
I killed you even with that. All right. It's because I got hit twice?
I don't even have that Kevlar, you're right. Fuck. It's not good. All right, let me try it again.
Turn please. I'll get greedy.
Oh! This camera makes me want to throw up in my mouth. Turn the fucking camera game.
Oh, he's getting actually bad. Actually bad. Actually bad.
This moves around so quickly and I can't turn fast enough. Like, fuck you.
I might have to go get the vest. I do have a full heal but I don't want to use it yet.
Oh shit. Where is he? Piece of shit. Like, fuck that.
Get these fucking things off, by the way. Get the sca- no. Where's the jump? Get these off.
Get these- get them out of here. I like just moon shoes up into the air.
Don't skip. Uh oh! Put them back on. Put them back on. Put them back on. Put them back on. Put them
back on. Put these back on. They're very useful. Incredibly useful. Because now I- uh oh. Oh!
Are you ready? No, I'm not.
Don't jump at me. Alright, don't- jump now and then jump again. Here comes the lightning. Oh!
I'm getting geno flashed. Damn it, I'm trying to fucking- the goddamn camera. Fuck this camera.
Oh my god! It's so- you don't understand. Moving around sucks in this game. He's doing it again.
Don't kill me, please! Step on his head.
So, fuck you. Pick this guy up and penalty soccer ball throw him into space.
Just watch him, like, crystallize while you go back to home.
Requesting a reinitialization of this island's systems and a memory backup of its bureaucratic
systems. That wasn't fast enough? Stop! Stop it! If you wish to shoot me, please do not hesitate.
My program has already been backed up in Eden's central core.
I eagerly await my next activation.
That was fucking ridiculous.
Oh, it's- trombone!
What?
Voice reveal?
What just happened?
Do you know why I stopped the car again?
Mega Man Legends 2.
What am I doing in EE?
That's the- that's the hold R1 to turn sound. I knew this game was sentient.
So soon after all you've done for us please stay a while longer we haven't had the chance to thank
you properly well it's not that we don't want to stay it's just that we've got some unfinished
business that we've got so much what's going on right yep that's right besides now that we've
got a refractor for the flutter it's time for us to go if you must go won't you at least come to
town and say goodbye to everyone i suppose we should at least say goodbye hey hey mega man
why don't you go give him our best it would mean so much to everyone go on mega man and say goodbye
to the junkman's wife for me okay i'm going okay just leave the door is not open
all right let's go say bye to everybody we're going to say our final we're going to say our
bye to tron bonn am i going to play legends 2 yes i have it right behind me not immediately
though we got some stuff going on if i'd known you were a hero like that i would have played
with you more cool i'm going to say bye to the the junk what about the misadventures of tron bonn
um you really have to go hippopotamus you're the best digger we've ever had i'm sure you'll do
fine wherever you go you and your spotter roll you two seem to get along real well like a digger
and spotters should you did it hippopotamus now i'll be able to dig all over the island
just kidding i think i'll stick with the little ruins near the city i mean there's still all
sorts of reaver bots and other ruins right anyway take care of yourself goodbye chat you're so funny
it gets funnier every single time like wow cringe community yes yeah cut the shit you know come on
what the fuck hey man can you hear me we'll be taking off soon don't go too far what didn't you
tell me to go say bye to everybody i can't even say bye to the hospital um the kid in the hospital
you do you going to do you going to cringe con this year so what was the point of me doing this
why did i even do this and i can't say bye to anybody talk to the people while
i did thanks for everything mega man they all said the same thing
i'm playing with paprika woof woof woof good luck mega man talk and talk oh hi mega man
thanks for your help did you hear we had a baby boy we named him mega man after you
thank you so much for saving me and my baby and the island huh oh the baby's just fine thank you
i'm doing great too as you can see the hospital girl's in the town oh what about the inspector
this is the first character we saw mega man it's you leaving are you we may have lived through the
great disaster in all the trouble with the pirates but once you're gone we'll have to take care
of everything ourselves again we're gonna have a rough time of it after you leave we'll take care
of yourself okay that's a way to lay it on me all right where's the where this is the painter
hey hero thanks for everything you're the greatest unfortunately i can't say
my museum's the greatest yet i gotta get more exhibits then maybe things will get better well
good luck to the both of us hey the reporter hey hi mega man thank you so much for everything
you've done for me and everyone you know what i've decided that once i get out of the hospital i'm
gonna learn how to be a digger just like you promise me that when i grow up you'll take me
with you on one of your digs okay there we said bye and then i just like fucking feel out hospital
yes she's in the hospital all right well there's too far away i don't care remember wait what all
right goodbye everybody it's been fun thanks for letting me hang out these practice safer driving
habits out of the 17 citizens at least eight of you ran me over with a car so please you should
tell roll you're ready to go fucking cool if i'm gonna do it time to go then yes thank you so much
for your help take care of yourselves boy take care goodbye see you later amelia
he why is this why is the monkey talk now monkey just makes noises give me a yearbook quote
uh still didn't find out anything about your mom and dad
well can't be hell it's not like we meant to come here in the first place right
but everything worked out in the end right yeah mega man did something happen while you were
underground not really don't worry about it forget that i'll always believe in you
oh will you that's sweet
whoa look outside the island mega man okay what is it whoa left that's the town
okay
two roads diverged in a wood and i i took the one less traveled by
and that has made all the difference i lost chat somehow yeah i have no idea what anyone's saying
i did what that was not good enough uh how about um let me think good one uh how about um success
is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm that's pretty good i just i just
came up with that here comes rock here comes some rock music how about fall seven times and stand
up eight that's oh i beat the game cool he's plagiarized i'm reading like quotes from famous
people what do you want me to do why do i why do you want a yearbook quote from me
all right i'll give you one you ready uh i don't know win or lose hit the snooze
being well rested is more important than no win or lose hit the snooze that's it
your body needs fucking rest sour please
got you this is really good theatrical play song i can see them all jumping around and swinging
their arms up and flying down and stuff on stage and each time one of them another person talks
the spotlight goes on them and the other two it's not on them all right that's it i'll see you guys
for black and white two is there an after credit scene maybe i don't know i don't think they're
probably not the return of murius yes murius is returning that is the plan tomorrow black and
white to murius return a time tomorrow tomorrow at 2 p.m pacific time hope to see you there
the system is ready there is after credits all right we'll just we'll just wait
i can do some of the bits well we have yeah a lot of the bits while we wait
ace uh it's nice everything thanks to the five uh not community so it's five dollars 500 bits
would you female version um no thanks to the five dollars why would i even answer this question
thank you for the 500 bits appreciate it hey near shoe thanks for 10 community subs
thank you near shoe i think we caught it early but thanks hey gnarly thanks to the 250
hello germa we at riot games wanted to thank you for hosting the league of legends twitch channel
for a few days oh that's right i forgot because i've rated to the league of legends channels
for a joke it just league of legends is always hosting someone so the host never turned off
until like yesterday night like last night i forgot about that it was like a three day host
again after credits there is uh-huh well there they go not a care in the world hey tron can't
this thing go any faster no it can't i had to gather up all the spare parts from everything he
blew up to build this that's right that's right we'll just have to rough it until we get to the
next island if we sell what we found we'll get back what we lost and then some we'll live like
kings so they got the crystal who would have thought there was such a huge refractor down there
and all we had to do was just wander in and pick it up i told you we'd have the last laugh
that's assuming we make it to the next island without sinking oh well at least he's in a good
mood if they drop that into the ocean is it gonna like electrocute earth remember we talked about
that how i said all right if you if there was if you dropped like electrical wire like into the
ocean wouldn't it just like everywhere on earth how does that make any sense to be it actually
is it to be continued well that was great megaman legends that was a lot of fun um the camera sucks
some camera sucks a game was really really great took me nine hours and 48 minutes of actual
playing the video game and probably like like 12 to 14 this is like stopping and going like
no let me let me like that let me let me tell you something right like you have to add that factor
and you watched one hour of that well thanks for watching thanks for playing but yeah i'll see you
guys tomorrow in a world covered by endless water that was part two the first time ever
i turned the stream off earlier this afternoon and came back for a part two stream i've never done
that before maybe i have but that's gonna be it we'll continue reading the bits i'll see you
guys tomorrow at 2 p.m pacific for a more normal stream not broken up like this one was see you
tomorrow i was here good night those of you that are going to bed and we'll see you tomorrow those
they're sticking around and if you there's bits to talk about we'll go over them all right so
we had uh that was gnarly's bits i forgot i hosted the league of legends channel for three days
accidentally that was kind of a mess but uh whatever that's cool but they also say um we're
thrilled to invite you into the league partner program as a partner you will advertise your
stream on the league of legends client and your germans will earn in-game rewards for watching
your stream partners must stream league of legends minimum 20 hours per week we hope to
see you on the rift that's just the hey i'm the guy from mixer but you replaced it with league
of legends hey peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hailey and hailey says uh hey germa i actually
just got back from the er i woke up this morning with severe side stomach pain and it was like a
seven out of ten and when i got to the hospital of pain i was in i was getting so pissy with the
doctors in my family and i'm like yelling to get rid of the pain i did a casket it turns out i have
kidney stones in both kidneys holy shit that's not good i gotta pass them soon i wish you luck
holy shit that sounds terrible uh also gonna stop drinking soda that was my day yeah cut back on so
sodas you don't want to be drinking soda sometimes it's good i used to love it i still do cut out
half the sodas you drink a day with water and maybe squeeze a little bit of lemon in there
you won't you if you i need you need that sweetness you need that sugar you need that tang
squeeze a little bit of lemon just a little bit and it's in the water and you trick your brain
and think you're drinking fucking fruity yummy drink lime water yes if that's what you need to
drink more water that's what you need to do just a little squeeze of lime that's it no not lemonade
not lemonade no squeeze the lime or you could just drink water that's also true but if people
some people don't like to drink water if you're one of those people then gotta find ways to do it
what about sugar-free lemonade no because that has all kinds of other like chemical
bullshit in it you well you don't want either sugar-free water sugar sugar-free lemonade has
like if it has to it's got like fucking xylitol in it or like aspartame and you just hey just
be natural for god's sake squeeze a lemon xylophone your body doesn't filter the fake
sugars very well that's true but i wish you a quick recovery hopefully you pass them
and it's not too painful because that sucks thanks for the 250 we wish you a swift recovery hailey
labster thanks for five community subs juno upsetto thanks for 250 they say pog champion
thanks for the pog champion germa is endorsing natural remedies get the fuck out of here with
that i just said just drink if you don't like water you can squeeze some lime in it don't know
that's it that's all i said twisted you're twisting me reaper thanks for the five dollars hey germa
you're back from the doctors hope you're all right anyway how did you get it it wasn't from
falling from your chair during the stream awards was it that would be really embarrassing now i've
had this for like two and a half years just yeah i've had it since before vegas it's been a nagging
problem for at least somewhere about maybe 18 to 20 months something like that just under two years
we're still trying to get it situated what does he have uh the current diagnosis is costochondritis
inflammation in my rib cage i've been doing physical therapy for it and if that doesn't
work and if that is what it actually is and it's determined that's the only thing i can do then i
have to get an intercostal nerve block it's an injection into one of my nerves kind of sucks
but you know that we do what we have to do and it's not i'm i'm fine don't worry it's just an
annoying issue but we'll see if pt does it are you paying two thousand dollars for 15 minute
visits no no i need to get an exoskeleton that'd be pretty great uh william and super bruce both
gave five subs want to touch upon them we did already but thanks guys thanks for the some of
the five subs look at me i have costco wholesale i probably should just make like a exclamation
point costochondritis so that they could just be like because people do ask about it a lot and i
just don't want to ignore them uh bulbous swag thanks for the 500 bits hey gamer do you think
it's more economically sound to save my channel points for the next big wink channel points thing
or use my points now also i had a theory that you only introduce winks so you'd have to wear clothes
well i mean i i didn't mean to do that that's that's sort of a an issue is me needing to wear
clothes and have to turn the facecam on every stream i mean that's the big problem who is that
oh you want to get out of here you want to get out he wants to get out hold on give me one second
want to go outside where to go all right what was what was it was so do is it more economically
sound hey you do whatever you want to do with your channel points uh the new thing that replaces
wink is i guarantee is not going to be substantially more interesting than the wink it's gonna it's
probably going to be like read a popsicle joke like people have suggested but thank you you're
gonna need hundreds of jokes no no i don't think so the wings only happen five to ten times the
stream anyways hey peaceful haley thanks for the 250 also found out i have a hiatal hernia as well
that explains my other stomach pains i'm glad i finally have my questions answered hope you
don't go through even more pain have a good night you get that you got the double diagnosis today
sorry to hear that yeah i have i have a hiatal hernia but it's i have been told it's not big
enough to be that much of a concern and it's not what's causing my problems that's what the
doctor said he's like that's not what you're why you're feeling like shit and like really he's
like yeah you have one but it's not big enough to really truly be causing the pain and you're like
you're back in ribs i'm like oh okay there was a wink oh well i can hold on shit i didn't know on
the small patches of land that remain above the sea the people of this world it's hard to just
wink it is driven by quantum refractors a powerful energy i can't it's hard to do it it in a world
ancient ruins underground and in the starship fix it thanks to five dollars i literally just
found out about you a month ago and i've absolutely fallen in love with your comedy look at me these
brave explorers are the funniest guy out there and truly improved my days thank you so much for
being you german thank you cornerstone of the immersion the five dollars
originally this was the digger's only purpose to find refractors so that civilization i'm a pain
thanks to the five community subs germa sucks thanks to the five community subs over the year
the story of a fabulous treasure held to the chief thanks for the 300 bits wasn't expecting a bf
bugleberry cameo to stream but i'm pretty sure that chat loved it they have a loving relationship
a treasure so great but if it were discovered it would provide so much power that the world never
thank you flood boy for the five dollars seeking the mother load the diggers traveled from one
what's this message ever hoping that they'll find what they seek just over the horizon hope despair
wait oh you missed it oh well uh thank you flood boy for the five dollars hey german was up late
last night watching italics's tarkov stream it has to be said i love tarkov but i do love the
chill environment that comes from your streams i need a rest from the adrenaline pumping madness
that is tarkov telling me he's a good gamer hope you're doing healthy yeah i'll never play tarkov
i will i will i won't even install that game ever i couldn't do it here i'm a coward that's fine i
will be a coward i i all right i don't do well in those games i don't like it not my thing
i do well in games where i can like oh the enemy is swinging at me i frame dodge i frame dodge i
frame dodge i frame dodge i frame dodge i frame dodge i frame dodge swing swing swing i frame
dodge i frame dodge i frame dodge i frame dodge like i do okay doing those monster hunter no hey
dark soul thanks for the 250 i forgot to make this donation during the first megaman legend
stream but the fact that your point of reference for his son drears with tron is angelica from
rugrats is the most fucking cursed shit i've ever heard what what are you talking about she
just acted like angelica that was my point of reference that's all that that's my information
i have play some fortnight and take l captive eight and captivate thanks for the 300 bits and
500 bits eight dollars here no message just eight dollars in bits thank you
you actually did say something you gave ten dollars in bits total yo germa big ups on the
streams i've been watching it for over a year appreciate you thank you thank you captivate
appreciate it thanks for sticking around germa sucks gave 10 more community subs thank you germa
sucks germa sucks is one of the one of the big uh community sub contributors to this stream
and let's get them on the screen pumped you sorry i did the wrong noise it was supposed to be
whoops here they are they my computer has been a piece of shit lately have i i've never talked
about that have i have time for an upgrade what do i have i have a 1080 is 1080 still good i
have a regular just a regular 1080 it's still good right i don't need to upgrade what the fuck
cares here comes credits thanks everybody for subbing that's my cpu uh it's an i768
i have it it's listed here right it's like a six core i7 isn't it i76850 btx 1080 hybrid what does
that mean no i don't need to upgrade i'm fine get a thread ripper yeah the plan eventually is to get
like a monster cpu so i can do a higher um quality instead of streaming because i stream at 720 60
i'd like to go to like 960 900p 1080 i still don't like the idea of doing 1080 i don't think it looks
good at the bit rate that twitch allows you to use and with a he but a thread ripper or something
i could probably drop my preset to make it look really good and make it at somewhere on 900p
because with 1080 twitch only allows 6 000 up to if you go more than that they actually don't like
it at all so anything more than 6 000 up if you have you have a 1080p stream and you're not
at somewhere or at like eight to ten thousand up for a bit rate it's just i it's not i don't
think it's worth doing so i would be somewhere probably around 900 i don't know this computer
talk what's happening we're just talking about uh computers and how fast they are you get a lot
of encoding crossed on action games yeah you could do like 1080 30 but i don't want to do 1080 30
i'd rather stay at 60 but um thank you everybody for stopping appreciate it i think we're so far
beyond 30 fps at this point as the internet has grows and progresses here and how we consume all
this media 30 fps i don't think is it's like well you're at 30 fps i think most people almost
everybody streams at 60 nowadays and this stream has been streaming 60 fps for three four plus
years so it'd be really weird to be like oh by the way i'm at 1080 but uh my i'm at 30 fps now
but anyways let's uh let's move this and go to the end so we're at the end i will see you all
tomorrow 2 p.m but we have 250 from c4g i hit legend in hearthstone for the first time yesterday
and i'm dedicating this victory to you the chicken league champion will never stream hearthstone
again it was fun while it lasted though erdemious thanks for the 250 hey i don't care what chat says
bugleberry is the greatest character to ever grace the stream i love all of his appearances
on the stream do you have any pointers on where i could find a mask that looks like him i really
want to cosplay him i actually don't i don't i uh that that mask is not readily available
because you're talking about somebody's face uh there's not a mask of bugleberry's face
why would there be a mask of that it's not like a president or something
what what do you munk a essay he's a pop culture icon no he's not is he
this fucking guy laughing my ass off hey digitron surfers thanks for thousand bits 10 bucks
thank you this is i you don't have to read this out loud okay hold on all right i see what you're
saying here okay all right uh i'm gonna tell you you know i'm kind of out of that game at this point
i'm out of that game i'm out of that game at this point it's not the codes anymore
it's it's it's a voice work thing um i don't really do it anymore it's not something that i
really do no more voice acting he hates it it's just something i i i would love to put time into
it but i'd rather put time into this but no not voicing sonic he's retired he does voice acting
in every game without real voice acting yeah are you available hey i'm not available
at all you can only do four voices anyway
but i appreciate the offer i just i don't really they don't really do it
not anymore but auto is yelling at me can you hear auto fucking yelling at me he's like hey what
does he want from me can you hear him he just went hey hey he's hungry you know he's probably
hungry all right i will see you guys tomorrow thank you for watching this weird double feature
here mega man legends was awesome got frustrated at one or two parts but it's a 20 year old game so
how am i how's that not gonna happen i think it holds up pretty well i loved it
we'll play the second one soon talk to you guys tomorrow black and white too have a nice night