Hello? Hello? Can anyone hear me talking? What the fuck is going on? Well, I think I need to
refresh. It says my stream is live, but I can't see anybody typing. Let me see if this works.
I think I'm live. Yeah, okay, now I can see. That was weird. All right, so anyways,
back to Nancy Drew and the Salem mystery. But I need to pop this out. Hold on,
this one died over here. Shit. How do I get this to refresh? Refresh, please. Oh, no. Okay,
I'm gonna have to pop you out over here. He doesn't know. Is it off again? All right, I think.
Why can't I open the chat? I can't even open like my Twitch chat room. No. All right, I can see you
over here, but you're in a really bad spot. All right, I can see you over here. All right, here we
go. But how will they hear all about... I stream dead. I can see. I can see. Yeah, when it died,
I lost connection to like stream labs and then it killed everything. Anyways, hi. That was... I
get... whatever. I don't know what my brain was doing. I just hovered over run 60 second ad break.
Like, I was gonna run an ad? That would be horrendous. All right, here we go. My grandpa,
right? Grandpa. Oh, 120 second ad. Dude, that's the second time that the stream has just turned
off and then come right back totally normally, completely fine. I probably would rather just
have that than horrible issues all day. All right, where's this... where's this... what's this thing?
What is this? It's a U. All right, I need to find a U. Ceiling? Is something on the ceiling?
Can I move it? This is master difficulty. Can I leave the room? I can't even leave the room.
No, you're not getting any ads. Stream went down and I'm not coming back with an ad after that.
I don't care. I know that's like the whole point of the game, but I just... where's the U?
Am I missing something over here? Under the button? I need a U key. Here's the thing,
though. I know you guys don't know where it is either, so I don't feel bad because I know
you don't know. I swear to god, if you slide the bookcase over into the key under there,
we don't know. I know. What about this? Just spam tab, go over interactive menus.
It's not anything to do with like the candle thing. It has to.
The books. It's in the books. The books. It's in the books. The window.
I don't... going to amateur wouldn't even change anything.
Is it like all the way in the back with the spot where you cut it out and put hide a key?
Leave the room. I don't think I can... Can I leave this room? Can I leave? How long have I known my
dad? Dr. Hearst, how long have I known my dad for? Well, wait. I'm just trapped in the room.
There's nothing I can do. Is there a... find the key? They're really, they're really, they're really,
they're really... Wait, wait, wait. It's about hiding something. Give earth to my prayer,
give ear to my prayer, oh god, and hide not yourself from my plea for mercy. Give ear to
my prayer, oh god, and hide not yourself from my plea for mercy. Give ear to my prayer, oh god,
god. I feel like this is me streaming. Just replace the stuff between oh god with
what's happening on the video game. All right, so hide and hide not yourself from my plea for
mercy. So it's hidden in a book somewhere. It's hidden in a book. It's what we know. What's that?
What's that? What is that? Touch it. Why would I be able to zoom in on this? Move this. What is
this thing? Click it. What about on the side of the table? Wait a minute. Other side? It's
one over here too. Hold right mouse button to rotate the item. Click on the item to interact.
What the fuck? I did it. Okay, it's one of those games. I didn't think it was one of those games,
and it is. What's in here? Yeah, get fucked. You're gonna get to my porn stash.
Let's see you in this maze. You fucking idiot. You'll never get my porn. Oh shit, that was
wicked easy, but not this one. This one's even harder. This has pawns in there. You'll never
fucking get in there. I found it. It's here. What? Amazing. Locked behind some sort of cage though.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. AW root beer. It's a password. Oh shit, I shouldn't have shown you that. The
ghost fucking flies through. Hey, Jerma sucks. Thanks for the 15 subs. I missed the first one,
but thank you for the 10 community subs right here. Thank you. Thank you for the
huge amount of subs, Jerma sucks. Take it back to the shop.
No. All right, so let's get it. How do I pick it up? It's locked with a leather belt.
How do I grab it? Is it on fire? Is it burning? Is it too hot? Oh, I can leave.
Incoming call.
Can I hang up?
Deirdre, Deirdre, there's a tornado. I can't talk to you. My porn!
What are you?
They took the book. This is the only way out besides the door. The thief must still be
close. Let's talk about it. Quick, hurry. Imagine having to run fast and you just move forward
two feet. I'm running. That person was running like an animal. They had their hands down,
like running on all fours. Is it a werewolf? Nancy, you can't do that. That'll hurt. Quick, run.
Someone's pushing me from behind. No, I don't want to do it. Quick fucking sprint.
Just do it here.
That's such an old... It was... I can't even tell you. The fucking smoke grenade.
I'm gone now. Magic acting. They did it twice. That's fucking awesome.
Gotta figure out which way they went. Must be a clue here.
I dropped my key. I dropped my address and I dropped my can that I was eating out of.
Scan my DNA, bitch. This canister looks to have been used as a home. You'll find me.
Oh no, I dropped my first class ticket. I'm going to Boston. By the way, I saw this movie in 3D.
All right, first class flight, October 28th. Flight in, 0898. Okay, seat place 3D boarding time,
1540. All right, what about on the back? Global travel airways. We're going to have to give them
a call. Here, look. The A&W root beer key. And it's got a weird pattern on it. We might have to
put that in a weird pattern. Wouldn't you want your locked box to have the very basic standard
key? Because I know that this key goes to that. A&W. Same as the desk. This canister looks to
have been used as a homemade smoke bomb. What? How do you make a homemade...
It's like Chef Boyardee and battery acid? I don't understand. Can smoke bomb? Okay. Well, I got it.
Oh my god. Don't hang up on me. Yes, Deidre. What is it? You know where I am right now? Salem.
Salem? As in which trial, Salem? Avi. Chug what's left. My cousin had gotten into some trouble here
and I thought I could help her out. But it turns out that the situation is much more complicated
than I anticipated. So now I'm calling you to ask for some guidance. You want my help? Yes. Yes.
Don't make this more painful. I could use your professional opinion, okay? Well, it so happens
that the case I'm on is connected to Boston, which is just nearby Salem, and I was never a big
believer in coincidences. Oh. I have a good blurry eyesight. I'd love to. I'm not a great detective.
You don't have to wear glasses. I thought I had reached a dead end, but it looks like I have to go
to Massachusetts anyway. In any case, a fresh perspective would do me good. Oh, you're already
annoying me and you're not even here yet. You're welcome. I get the feel she's focusing on the can.
If I look over here, my eyes are ripped down, still focused on the can.
That would hurt. Automatic long letter grid if I could drive this.
I appreciate you coming here, Drew. I'm just glad you didn't change your mind and leave me
at the airport. I'd have crossed my mind. Keep the excessive cheeriness under control
and we'll be fine. Hey, eyes on the road. No promises. Where were you, by the way? Eyes on the road.
Did I interrupt a vacation with Ned? Didn't you bring me here to help with a case?
Yes, I did. And that's it.
Grabbed the shift.
The house wasn't completely destroyed, but the person who lived there had to move out.
Oh, you drive a stick. This is my case. I know you're a...
Why am I leaning the other way? I'm like sitting down and looking up. Where am I?
Why was I down there?
Is this the car ride? I'm going to tell you how it is car ride.
What's that? What's that say?
What is that? Is that an ejector?
I can't see where your mouse is. Oh, it's that problem again.
I can't see where my fucking mouse is. God damn it.
All right. Where's my mouse? No, no, no. This, this thing over here before it gets cut off.
The thing that looked all the way to the right. Looks like an ejector seat thing. The lever.
All right. Let me fix this. How did I fix this last time? How did I fix this last?
I think the stream crashing broke this. I think I just broke it. It was like that before too.
Is that going to work? I broke it. All right. Capture the screen.
Why is it scaling? Oh, I hate this program with a passion. This is it. This is it.
This is the stream where I don't use Streamlabs OBS ever again. This is it. This is the one.
Okay. Not using it ever again. All right. So you get to capture the fucking screen. What are you
doing? That's not even right. It's incorrect. What the fuck are you doing? What the fuck are you
doing? I made it worse. No, I didn't. Clipping. Where? Professional streamer. No, professional
streamer using shit software is what happens. All right. Let's go. Why don't we start with your
extended family? They're cousins. The Perry's. P-A-R-R-Y. Oh, like in fencing. Yes. Tegan is the
older one. May is younger. They've, they had a difficult time. Dude, if I could keep my stream
turned on, I would uninstall this on Streamlabs OBS just regularly again. On the most important
historic mansion in Salem. And I know it's not true. I know it. We haven't taken a single turn,
by the way. This is, wherever we're going is in a straight line. This is it. All right. We've
never even taken one turn. What can you tell me about May? She has a reputation as a troublemaker.
I feel like I'm sitting in a studio of being manipulated. This is being keyed in. We haven't
moved. Sometimes she can even sense things before they happen. Odd how? I don't know. Troubled dean
stuff. Difficult time as a kid. Oddest thing is she won't give an alibi. That's what we do.
Suspicious. That's the problem. Everyone is so suspicious of her. How is this the stream that
you stop using Streamlabs if the stream isn't canon? Sounds like we should talk to her soon.
Where do you think we're going? What does Tegan think about this? She's worried about May,
obviously. Tegan isn't like May. She's upstanding. She works at the Salem Museum and doesn't know a
thing about criminal cases, which is why she contacted me. Is there like I don't have any
more questions? I don't I don't have one more question. I don't want I don't have any more
questions. The Hathorn house and it's old. Like really old. And now it's been set on fire.
Nothing else significant about it? Well, yeah. That's kind of why you're here, which is why.
All right, we got it. Here's the house. The Perry house.
What do you mean haunted? Get out of the car, Nancy. Exactly that. There's ghosts. Deirdre.
I don't believe it either, Drew. But I can't explain it. Everyone seems to think they exist.
With so many sightings, even if it isn't real ghosts, something is definitely going on. I
thought that maybe you can disprove them. So would you please get out of my car and come inside?
This looks like a house that's currently occupied. Side by side. You'd better learn to keep up with
me. You must be Nancy. Thank you so much for coming. Am I is this like a do I like investigate
ghosts? You know, you live in the same neighborhood for 20 years and you'd expect your neighbors to
be a little more understanding when your family is false. Did Nancy Drew do this before the
conjuring? Oh, I'm sorry. How are you, Deirdre? I'm good. Thanks. Tegan Perry. Welcome to my home.
Welcome. Hi. Although right now, my parents are literally on safari in Namibia. So while their
daughter is being convicted of a crime she didn't commit, I'm taking care of things around here.
They'll be home soon. We're a very expensive courier is tracking them down in the bush.
Top notch. I found him on the internet. Deirdre tells me you'll be assisting her in clearing my
sister's name. Assisting? Yeah. She's innocent. I don't know why she won't help herself. She's got
difficult reputation. Well, you know, Deirdre, what people here can be like. She doesn't trust
easily. I'm sorry. Are you hungry? There's clam chowder. Homemade. Oh, clam chowder? I
wear a fucking new wiggler and I'm fucking blotted. I remember blotting a new wiggler.
Deirdre, sorry. You're bunking with me. Oh, I almost forgot. After you girls get comfortable,
you two should swing by the museum. Might as well take in some history while you're here, right?
Just don't get suckered into that witch's walking tour. Olivia Ravencroft is not a witch. She would
have you believing all kinds of nonsense about the town being full of goats. I thought you two
used to be friends. That was a long time ago. Look, I'm sorry. I gotta get going. I'm running
late to an appointment. That's the villain. Thanks, Tegan. I appreciate you. That's the villain
with the smoke. Before you go, do you have time for a quick question? Nancy, we just got here.
That's the only thing you eat in Boston. Sorry. I know you're in a rush. It would really help.
Of course. I have time for one question. If it'll help. What can you tell me where the fire
happened? Do you mind introducing me to May? What can you tell me about the fire?
What have you heard about it? Look, I appreciate you want the quickest way to know that you are
responsible. What about that fire? What do you know about the fire? What do you know about that?
That's not what Nancy is asking about. I'm sorry if I wasn't clear. I just thought since
the Hawthorne house is important to the town, you must know about it. Oh, I'm so sorry. Yes,
John Hawthorne was one of Salem's founders. His large house estate was the oldest surviving
structure from Salem. Oh, is that all? Ah, ah, ah. That was two questions. I said one.
But yes, it was also the big time judge that presided over the Salem witch trial. Is there
some other fire I need to know about? No. May's accident was in a fire. I just don't want her
getting upset with unnecessary questions about things long over. I understand. You can read all
about Judge Hawthorne and you come to the museum later. All right, so turn on faucet. First thing
I'm going to try. You jerk. Tegan said you've been in town for days, but you haven't come by.
I know. I know. I had to check in with your case at the uh. I feel like I'm watching somebody that
made it in the cinema. I didn't want to bother you. How are you holding up? And it was not,
it was like an experiment that we're going to try to see if they get a camera in the house.
Hey, at least I got you to get off your butt and finally visit me.
Oh, this is the girl I was telling you about. Nancy Drew. Nice to meet you. Okay, well see you
later. She really doesn't want to talk. This could be difficult. That wasn't even that. No,
no, no. That was not being ignored. That was I didn't see you. I'll be in the kitchen. You're
not in the house. All right, let's go through their drawers and stuff.
Green power. Oil. You keep all your oils and shit up on the wind direct sunlight.
That's new. Don't do that. All right, stove. Open the stove. Go to the fridge. Huh? Candle.
Just a gross candle on the counter. Huh? An evil candle on the counter. Cool.
With matches with your nice flowers and nothing there. The kitchen table has a great view out
into the neighborhood. Eat the candle. You know I would. If I could, you know I would. Key like
hidden in shoe. Uh, no wait down here. Deirdre would be upset if I left without her. Can I just
turn on the lights? Okay, hold on. Should I introduce myself? Whoa, you got right in there.
The way that I'm moving, I'm the ghost. All right, can't spray. Rust be gone. Now that's handy.
Never know when a bit of stubborn iron oxide will get in the way of investigating.
Take it. All right, so what is it? Rust be gone. Use rust be gone. I got rust be gone. What's this?
Hiking the Patagonian Highland. Yeah, that's good. Remember that symbol if I'm needed later.
Oh found it. What did I find? An egg? I didn't know I was on it. Is this how they like keep me
occupied? You know Nancy's coming over so just just hide a few eggs and she'll eventually find
them and we can just you know we just tell her like oh good job you did it. I don't understand.
I found it. Deirdre's convertible. Looks strikingly familiar. Talk to the picture?
All right, let's talk. Nice to meet you. Yeah. Uh can I look around the house? Do you mind if I
look around the house? Oh you're so weird. I'm done talking, okay? Uh okay um real photos of actual
people. I always find these interesting because what who are these people? They're like devs or
like cousins of devs or nephews or friends or brothers sisters children and it's always like
it's interesting. They're random people. Now that would be weird. Are there stock photos of like
we're a family like just in the backyard? Is there? I guess there has to be right?
The neighborhood looks peaceful from up here. There are a lot of them. All right I got rust be
gone. Can I spray rust in the bed? A good night's rest improves memory retention but it's too early
for bed. I got a drawer right here. A good night's rest. Oh you're gonna note. What's that? Found
Teagan's photo. What does it look like? Coven. What does this mean?
What? You're gonna leave that just in the a Polaroid of this?
Hey here's a Polaroid of me posing. I'm a witch with scary candles. Keep out.
Does that say wham? New England riot. Keep out. I was here. The Grim Reaper. Do not enter. Wham.
No parents allowed. Okay well I have photo now. Let's uh let's go talk shit.
How do I talk shit? What's my persuadability at right now? There's another room. Can I go down
this like hall? Go down here. All right I have rust spray. I have a photo. Here look I got a photo.
Look at this. Are you ready to leave yet? We don't have all day. Uh what were you actually doing?
This tour sounds interesting. Don't tell Teagan that's your plan. It'll give us a good overview
of the town. You mean I want to meet the real witch of Salem? Yeah I do. She might know something.
I wonder why Teagan doesn't like her. You don't have to investigate everything. Rust spray her
in the face. Olivia steals Teagan's visitors sounds like. You really want to do the dumb tour?
You don't have to come with me. Side by side. How long this game is? It does sound more fun in the
museum. All right how do I just leave the conversation? Why do I have to do every dialogue option? What were
you actually doing before you picked me up from the airport? You gave May a non-answer when she
asked why it took you so long? Because they're all working together. A non-answer? Yeah. You were at
your witch meeting. And I'm so oblivious that you could all be witches around me. I was May's
cousin. They started. And I'm busy looking around for weirdly shaped fucking keys. They think she
did it. Everyone does. So I went to check out the Hathorn house myself but I never went inside.
The ghost? What? No. There was some weirdo there who told me the ghost was going to
steal my soul. Looking for eggs. It was totally creepy. Yeah. And then I found out that everyone
in this town believes in ghosts so I. They're doing like a demonic seance behind me. I'm looking
around finding interestingly painted eggs. Did the police give you anything? Anything at all?
They told me there's a Judge Danforth in town and he's going over the particulars
of the Hathorn house estate. I found. I know him. Not well. All right. Are we going into town or
what? Yeah let's go. Sure. Who could gain something by burning down a house? Somebody. Insurance claim
maybe? Maybe. Possibly. See if anyone checks off those boxes. It's usually. All right let's go.
What do you think about this? What do you think about this? Nothing. Talk to Tegan in the museum.
Talk to Judge Danforth. Who's Ned? It's the voicemail inbox of Ned Nickerson.
I apologize that I did not come to the phone in a timely fashion. Please feel free to leave a
message after the beep. And then I'm gonna really piss that person off because they have a new
voicemail now. And it's gonna be nothing there. All right. Hi you've reached the phone of private
investigator Deirdre Shannon. I'm working on an important case and. It's a fucking android.
It's an android. Information you'd like to share. Please leave a message after the beep.
Professional. Deirdre is taking this very seriously. That's scary. That's actually really scary.
Do I have photos? Oh you can take photos in this game. Can I take a selfie? What else can I do?
Love you too. Can I write? Hey Nancy is the manager of the phone. My old acquaintance in Salem.
We're into DMs now. Everything's great. Miss you. Miss you too, Nance. We'll have to catch up more
later. The bus is here. Okay talk soon. I swear I would have. We would have loved this place. We should
go here together sometime. That was robbery in the book I was looking for got stolen. What are
you okay? Yes I'm fine. I'm seeing this through. There is something going on and I have to figure
out what. Okay just let me know if there's anything I can do. I will. Love you. Love you too.
How do I put my phone down? All right let's go. Out. I just called you. Hi Nance how've you been?
Thanks for finally picking up. Well not good apparently. My pupils are fucking completely
dilated. You know you should really enjoy yourself more Nance. Life's too short to be working all the
time. This doesn't work for me. It's fun. Besides crime doesn't take a vacation. Speaking of which
how's yours? Yeah one second. Sounds like you are having fun. Uh you know standard fare. Nothing too
crazy. I miss you Nance. I miss you. Hey give it back. Nancey I'll call you later. What is going on?
Is that are we together? Is that my boyfriend? That's my boyfriend. So I'm gonna look for wait
look in the mailbox. Jesus Christ don't. Don't sneak up on me like that. Hi you've reached the
phone of private investigator Deirdre Shannon. I'm working on an important case and can't come to
the phone right now but if you have any information you'd like to share please leave a message.
Professional Deirdre is taking this very seriously. I don't want to call again. I wish I could text.
All right put the phone down. What about that car? It's a broken window. No it's not. All right let's go.
Let's go. Her eyes have madness to them. It's Google street view.
I've been here is exactly what it looks like.
Oh this should be interesting. The world would have you believe witches were not real.
I'm not talking about old ugly women who curse their neighbors and fly on. What is this? What's
going with the protesters? Witches are real. What's going on? They have always been real.
They are alive and well. They are powerful. Which protesters? Carrying the secrets of the world
beyond the one we see. Ritual, mystery, magic. Most exist now. This is mocap actor of overacting.
You know what I mean? It is said that in Salem a coven of witches settled in recent years.
Set on revenge for the deaths of the Salem witches. Their ritual one midnight on Halloween
unleashed the angry spirits of the past. Is my mouth just open? Wait a minute that's you.
I feel like my mouth is open just like saliva is going down. Real history of the witches of Salem.
Same animation too. Some of my favorite locations in town and perhaps you too will see one of the
restless day. They've in Austria used the same kind of stage magic she's using. Thief? There was a
thief? What were you doing there? Visiting a spooky old castle. I don't know if it was worth
driving all the way from Boston. It's a long trip but I'm trying to make my friends happy.
I have here a photo of witchcraft in practice and all of you here are going to see the truth.
So here comes trouble. Me? Nothing too bad I hope. Did you know that in the Malleus Maleficarum
ginger hair was the sign of a witch? My kind of beef? I'm not nearly as talented as you are.
Oh that's not into it. You're making me blush. Oh there it is. Actually I think he thinks she's
talking to him. You truly are a witch. So to become a witch do I need to take a test or get a diploma?
A true witch is not made with pieces of paper. She is born to it and will feel
the call. A true witch. A true witch tries to study this. We don't need permission. We don't live by
the rules. Anyway what can I help you with? Now he's stuck in a situation that I think a lot of
us have been in previously before is if there's a conversation happening through you you can't
there's not much you can really do you could I guess step one step to the left but if this guy
turns and looks over here and realizes that he's not even remotely part of this conversation
then it's weird but if you know take out the phone hit a few buttons pretend to be on a phone call
with somebody that's how you get out of this otherwise you'd like this guy I don't think he
has his phone on he's stuck here he is stuck here until we're done having a conversation.
The bishop most nights it gets busier around Halloween and I'm sure you can figure out why
he's a blue tooth. How about the night that the Hathorn house was burned?
You look a little young to be working for the police. Don't I do puzzle games?
Oh no it's nothing like that we're just curious jurists. I pressed like my grandfather's
porn briefcase button because I've already spoken and we've talked about Salem and so
you were here. I was out of town. Did you girls know that Salem is haunted? There's a ghost here.
If you go on my tour you'll learn where you can find it. Get that candle. Okay um bye talk to you
later. Move me back. I want to I got a message. Hey Nancy Deidre gave me your number. Sorry but
before I was stressed. Don't worry about it and thanks for all right let me get the fuck out of
it. I take two steps to the right. They have the conversation up. Thanks for getting in contact.
Where did I find the museum? Oh you're so welcome to come by. We're on the opposite side of the town
square. We're on the opposite side of the town square from the courthouse. Just turn right and
go past the old cemetery. We can't miss it. Great. Fucking battery though come on. I want to find out.
You get the idea. Fire at Hathorn House. We all know certain renegades in this town know something
or two about fire. May Perry. You don't think she'd do it again do you? She was so young. Am I reading
their thoughts? Creeping around back alleys with her hood head down. Where there's smoke there's
fire. Hmm well with her history she's bound to already be in the sights of the neighborhood
watch. So we'll find out soon enough. My thoughts exactly. Am I inside of like this is what they're
texting together? That was uh all right. Road closed. The road has completely collapsed into
the sinkhole. No wonder they closed it off. The ground is still crumbling. I don't remember there
being like ridiculous earthquakes in Massachusetts. This giant sinkhole. Here's the courthouse.
False judgment. False claim. What do we want? Justice. What do we want? Now.
What are we doing in the courthouse? Talk to Judge Danforth. Okay you got it. Hey what are you doing?
He's a judge Deirdre. Judge Danforth. Yeah hello. This is the restroom. My office is down the hall
to the left. Give me a minute. Nancy Drew. Carson's daughter. Yes and I'm with my friend.
Why do we talk? Is this a priest? Why do we talk through the door? Well you see no I mean I'd let
you in but I seem to have been locked in my office. No you can't come in the bathroom with me. What the
fuck are you talking about? I need some help getting out. But if you could give me some toilet
paper. There's not enough left. There's just enough to make it not be gross but I really don't want
to walk down the hall. If you could give me a grab me a new roll that'd be fantastic. Yes I believe
I gave a copy of the key to Alicia Cole as backup. She's just down the hall. I hope she's still here.
Wait so wait this guy locked himself in his office from the inside. Is that what we're led to believe
here? That's not even possible. You can't do that unless you glued the door shut. I can't go in these
rooms. Ah yes you see I accidentally glued the whole seam of the door and held it in place for
three hours.
Hi so sorry to bother you at this hour but we're here to meet with Judge Danforth
and he seems to be locked inside his office. He said you might have a key.
Sorry I gave him my spare. Unbelievable. Does this ever end? What? Oh well then um he has a key and
he's only inside and we're gonna take if you don't mind me asking the lock to his door. What business
do you two have? And he's inside the door. We're helping the judge with a case. Anything I can
assist you with? Thanks but I think we got it. No need for a lawyer at least not yet. The diploma
gave me away huh? Aside from the cold coffee you're still drinking and the deluxe open box of sticky
tabs yeah you could say I know the type really well. Nancy Drew you really are your father's
daughter. It's nice to finally meet you. You know my dad. Small world. Books. If you need
any assistance or thick ass books. Feel free to ask. All right let's go pick the judge's luck
paper clip. Judge Danforth I couldn't find your key. What? Alicia said she'd keep a copy for me.
Well I did find a paper clip. I think I can pick your luck if that's okay with you.
Yeah sure fine. Oh no wait I have to actually pick the lock. Just open the fucking door judge.
Open the door. Just grab it and turn it. All right hold to drag pin. Feel for the pin that gives
resistance. Release. Hold to drag pin. Feel for release when the pin locks in place. Don't you go
like it's this one. I had it. No this one. Efficient. How'd you learn to do that actually?
Online video tutorial. Someday you have to tell me about your secret life of breaking and entering
Drew because you're in danger of being cool which honestly I just don't like. Someday. What the fuck
are you talking about? What does that even mean? The game just crashed. No we just got into the
judge's door. Arrested. All right hold on. That did it does this game save? Does this game actually
save? Stop right there criminal scum. Will we ever learn? Will we ever learn? There's been decades
of video game development. Decades. Decades of this shit and you're telling me that in
decades of development we're still everybody and this is from what this is from like single
a all the way up to the major leagues in video game development. Why do you have your splash screens
at maximum goddamn volume? Why? It's like do you not open your game? Do you not open the game?
You have to open the game like a thousand times in the debug menus. Open your game before you
give it to people. How many times have we opened a video game and it's like okay let's open this
video game. Like that happens so often. It's like how does that keep happening? Suffer me now. Why
do you say that? Oh we got in. Like posture. That's posture. So you're doing that on purpose.
Is this money? Those protesters are out there again stirring the pot. You know this town used
to be. That's that's an oxygen mask. Seems lately there's been an element. Reused assets. This is an
oxygen mask. One of those troublemakers locked my door and threw away the key.
Now Nancy your father and I have discussed. Oh sorry I'm not Nancy. Of course you're not. You
look nothing like Carson. Did your father ever tell you about the time we won fourth place at
the lake Winnipeg? You told me how you locked yourself in an office and had to have a like
17 year old open your door with a lockpick. She's working with me on the case. I don't know how old
am I? You're the one who tried to break down my door. Break down? Your honor that's an exaggeration.
I was knocking heavily. Look I'm really busy dealing with this Hathorn house business.
Being a judge is not as simple as you know investigating. Break down the door. Well we
just used our free time to unlock your door so I'm sure you'll be willing to repay us with some
answers to our questions. Don't look in the corner. Yeah how long have you been locked in here? Yes of
course. What can I help you girls with? Yeah pay no attention to the six bags of uber eats that are
over here. I was having the delivery drivers football throw them through the window.
Sorry. How are you involved? I was told the burning of Hathorn house is suspected. I was told that
the burning of Hathorn house is suspected to be a case of arson. How did the police come to that
conclusion? The investigation found paint solvent residue on burnt embers suggesting someone
deliberately used an accelerant. Thankfully Mrs. Tuttle never had to see what became of her home.
And what evidence do you have that Mae Perry is the one responsible for this? Evidence? Have you
ever heard of recidivism? I don't know if that's what it is. Three out of four criminals in the
United States are repeat offenders and there's only one person in all of Salem who has a history of
fire related crime. So there is no evidence. What are you talking about? Not yet but there will be.
Isn't this a judge? You don't need evidence. She's already been convicted in the court of public
opinion. What is this thing? I'm a fucking judge. No I'm saying. I went to law school and she spent
decades doing this. What's Mae's motive? What does she gain by burning down the Hathorn house?
You'd have to ask her and while you're at it you can ask about her alibi which she refused to give
to the police. So any other questions? Sure. Can you explain to us how you're involved with
the Hathorn house? Well yes the house was built by Judge John Hathorn during the 60s and it
represented the oldest surviving structure from that era. Judge Hathorn was one of the three judges
that presided over the Salem witch trials. Yes and I'm sure we can read all about the home's history
in Salem's museum. More recently Francis Tuttle, Judge Hathorn's last direct descendant,
lived in a small section of the house for the rest was left. I was almost, I almost got your
master's in the league and you interrupted me. That's why the door was locked. A part-time
caregiver, Laura Bedroom in the carriage house. A few months ago Francis Tuttle passed away
which left Hathorn house without a legal heir. According to the historical statutes of Salem
after 90 days the house reverts to public property the deadline which is two days from now
at midnight. Okay so why to the book of apologies why did you need it? So the book of apologies
why did you really need it? Yes and first of all I'm so glad you're all right. Nasty business.
Had I known you were going to be put in harm's way I would have never called Carson and asked
for his help. So you're responsible for a magician stealing it? Trust me I can handle myself. Yes
I'm sure you can. So I've already heard some stories but would you mind giving me your version
of why the book is important? Yes so Judge Sewell was rumored to keep a ledger of all the accused
intending to publish it to reconcile with their families and clear their names
but he passed away before he could do so. Going to Austria for a rumored book seems like a heck of
a long shot. Who are you again? I have been under some pressure from the AW group. AW as in accused
witches. All right well talk to you later. Talk to you later don't get locked in your office. Before
you go there is something else I need your help with. Not locked out of your car are you? Please
say yes. Oh no there was a there was an incident here recently. Someone broke into the evidence
room. Well I know not yet I don't think anything was taken. Never mind I'll call the police. Thank
you for your time. Evidence room let's go. Photo of him too. Where's the evidence room? Evidence
room this way. How do I get in the evidence room? Scan the photo. Rust. It's a rusty door. Use the
weird key. Take out the camera. Can I hey can I go in the evidence room right? So how did your
meeting go? Informative. Don't worry come back tomorrow. Come back tomorrow? I have to go back
what do you mean come back tomorrow? There's a day night cycle in this game. What can I help you girls?
Talk to you later. All right fine whatever all right let's go. Walk him back in the office.
They're protesters in a small town like this. What is that? What was that?
They're protesters in a small town like this. That was recorded that's like that's not an outside voice.
Skyrim mod voice acting what is I don't even know what that means but it's funny.
X-Fox Mike. X-Fox Mike. Oh stop you guys are gonna hurt me. Let's visit the cemetery. I want a picture of little liberty.
What? All right let's go. It'll be more useful to explore the graveyard with a tour guide.
It'll be more useful to explore. No the game's fresh.
This way. The Salem Museum. What is this the bar? It's locked. We're going to the bar. Wait can we not
go I mean not a lot of going to the bar. All right the bar. Wait how old are we? Maybe we can learn
something about. Get away from me. You're just in the way. Look at how much okay if I move this
way for instance right I'm going this way. Now I'm gonna turn this way and this she takes up so
much screen real estate. Just like put her over here. Have her be like the Microsoft paperclip
that I can click on. Street art in Salem coming soon. What's this? Remembering the wrongly accused
may history never again be repeated. Nothing. Okay hold to look. Something else? There's probably
like a little tab I can push. The figure of a Puritan woman accused of being a witch.
These were ordinary people just like anyone else. Yeah all of a sudden it's this this I'm
gonna lean in it's gonna be like ah they're gonna scream it's gonna be an actor that's doing the
I'm the statue thing. I'm getting unsuspecting people. The figure of. Now you're in the way.
Get out of the way. I want to talk to you. Wait all right I'm back. I'm here.
Hey sorry about the mess. We're in the middle of installing a big showcase.
So what have you seen in town so far? We decided to do the real witches tour. Oh no we didn't. Talk
to Olivia. It's a lie. What's with her get up? Witch? Street magician maybe? Everyone has to
make a living. Is she telling the story about a coven living here in the recent past? Yeah. Yeah
why? Just bad taste. What about the photo of you that says coven? I hope you don't mind if we do
the tour. I want to see more of the town and finding out a place's old superstitions is kind
of a habit I've gotten into. I'm excited to look around the museum. Of course. We got a ticket. Wait
a minute. Wait a minute is this the oh it's a raffle ticket. Does this mean? Why can't I not
show this photo to you? Aren't you in this photo? Go on the witch tour. Admissions.
25 dollars. This better be good. Closed off. Looks like they're preparing a new installation.
Stray book. You see it. I do. Told you. Somebody will end up reading this somehow.
What about this one? Sad that even children are named in the list of those accused witches
like Abigail Johnson. Just 11. This one. Anything else? Turn page. Wait somebody will read this.
Any codes? Everything you could ever want to know about Salem's history. From the Namkiag people
to the great Salem fire. Cool. All right so let's go on the tour. And this is gonna happen. This is
the intro of the game. We're gonna go on the tour. Something bad's gonna happen. This is gonna be a
this is gonna be a fight's gonna break out and we're gonna have to
this is gonna be a ghost that attacks us. I know I've seen it already.
That's the guy that was stuck in the conversation and he's still stuck and he's still pretending
that he oh no no never mind that tree with arms just proved us wrong never mind.
Let's go on the tour. I have a ticket. This tour sounds interesting. Welcome on my tour. Thank you.
Well welcome on my tour. Found a tablet. Is it which what? They give you an ipad?
Look for the raven and place the tablet over the spots of interest. Okay look for me. So this is
not a tour. This is an app. Uh oh here comes trouble. How'd you do that trick? How did you
perform that trick? A witch never reveals her secrets. It's against the witch code. Magician.
A code. I thought bureaucracy and rules were. That's why that guy wore the mask
when he did all the reveal secrets on that tv show. I promise you will learn at least one secret
about being a witch. Remember that show? Remember the guy that did showed all the magic secrets
and he was in that that full head mask because he didn't want anyone to know who he was?
Talk to you. Like it was something was like somehow dangerous for him to not have that mask on.
That's what was sort of like implied like he needs to wear this mask
otherwise the fucking magicians are coming for him. That show was fucking pretty good actually.
All right look for the birds. How about this? Bring light into the darkness. Bring light.
Put your ipad on it. It's a very high tech statue or something that was made
until the judge caught her in the act and locked her up in a cell deep within the
Hathorn house. The statue was given the name little. I'm just doing what I'm just doing
with you y'all. This is real life. Okay uh cool so I got one. The big tree. No smoking. Wait.
Can't see it from here. Must be deeper in. Scan the raven. Let's kick on. This is when you start to
realize that like oh man was this like I didn't I thought no not anymore not anymore
they do like haunted houses and shit here now. When does this game take place? Today.
Oh it's just like it's like ipad like little ipad burn mark just like this thing is fucking hot.
I can't fucking hold it. Can't use that here. You guys have a okay I I'm gonna tell you I'm
an ipad the master of the ipad but this is a real story and you guys are gonna know if you also have
ipads some apps actually hurt to use because they make the ipad so hot that it's hard to even hold
it after a while. Can't use that. What I'm saying is not oh well that's funny but easy. Sometimes
I use my ipad and I use like a game that's really high graphic integrity and this thing hurts to
hold. All right can I just we're just gonna go around and do this so I can get my drink ticket
for later. This is what you have to do all right yeah yeah yeah cool but we did the thing we did
the tour we did the thing. What's next? Where's my checklist? Oh the sinkhole the puritan statue
didn't I get that one aw aw yeah no get the fuck out of the way aw kidding me w
this is the same marking as in mosem castle what a strange coincidence nancy you've been solving
mysteries for like 30 years in your line of work there's no such thing as a coincidence
you're still doing like the oh gee golly what a coincidence bit all right what what what am I
going over here nancy dot dot dot I can't use that here what do I need to find no don't scan
the ipad accused witches sinkholes in the statue what's a sinkhole isn't that the accused witches
right that's sinkhole over there isn't it no that's the house where's the sinkhole
can't use that the soundtrack is so loud is it what's the scanner for this one
I already got this one didn't I how did I not do this one before you
judge hathorne's great isn't that the guy I just talked to up there
wait I have to side by side get away from me get away from me you don't have to get they're not
all in here I have to go take pictures of the famous sinkhole
in recent years all right the statue the puritan statue here somewhere there it is
an awful tour I can use that here I mean I can't use that here can't use that here
yes I can why not can't use that here can't use that here really the ipad's too hot needs to pull
down side by side wait for me which is memorial and puritan statue where the hell is that
how is that not a puritan statue in the museum talk to the bathroom voice again
oh there it is yeah okay accused witches memorial the figure of a puritan woman accused
don't skip but okay here's why I'm skipping all the info that you are getting right now
is an info dump it's a history lesson if you just typed in right now I'm just saying I'm
saving us some stream time if you typed in right now Salem witch trials and then went to Wikipedia
you get all this info and you could do it whenever you that's it's just an info dump
we don't need to know all this to understand that like the judge that we just talked to is
gonna we're gonna pull a mask off of them in like 25 minutes it's gonna be him we don't need that
info but we don't though we really don't where's the last one accused witches memorial where would
that be it's a mystery game let the ravens be your god yeah the ravens are just on the
back in the uh cemetery Jesus one guy told you to play this yeah zero I already did that
I like this game I'm into it back in the museum it's in the museum
hey I'm into it until I'm not right that's how it works the carefully read
oh this is like I thought okay yeah
okay talk to me again now we can go back to the story I'm back oh here comes trouble
I did your there's there's the statue in the cemetery
statue in the cemetery give the ipad back liberty did you forget a highlight of my tour many people
come here just to get a picture of it it is said to portray Abigail Hathorn helping the accused
witches escape the trials some even believe that Abigail's ghost still walks the forest
surrounding the Hathorn house her twisted soul now dragging the living into the afterlife
all right talk to you later talk with me again do you really believe some modern witch coven
unleashed do you really believe some modern about eight years back there were rumors of a coven
that they performed a ritual to return the dead witches to fail to seek out their revenge
there any evidence of such a coven ever since then ghost sightings have gone through the roof
Salem is now considered the most haunted place in the country and it better stay that way you
think it's a coincidence because otherwise I ain't selling ipad apps to tourists anymore it's so
haunted be careful everywhere you go there's ghosts everywhere please come back next year
and do it again the torrent there's only 25 dollars to go see pumpkin carvings in here
and Salem for long so you know the paris of course not well if you were looking for them
teagan is at the new i know she's in here we're staying with teagan i figured there was some
that was a long time back we don't talk much now and that's like yes i know her too
that's it you've just sort of slightly shit your pants when you can't move it's just a lit
just tiny and just a little girls get blamed for enough for you to be able to take care of it
and nothing bad's gonna happen the half-born house if that's what you're trying to get at
people with mundane minds look for mundane explanations how else could that have started
i heard there was not a single living soul in the house when it started burning
the keyword living is composed of two equal parts why did you pick the worst nancy drew
game and this is the new one this one just like two days ago every day this is the new one people
the birds this is 2019 two days ago just released nancy this is brand new dark is the unknown
pain of existence that vibrates just underneath the light but if you were in a place like Salem
place where a painful history it's not me it's every surface i bought all of them there's a
bundle where you can buy fucking all of them i just compulsively bought them all so it doesn't matter
we'll play them all that's why they say don't be out past midnight Salem can you reach out
and take you also did you know that Salem has more ghost sightings than any other city in north
america well if you want to learn why you should go on my tour talk to you all right
talk to me again that's not that's not me which one who's made who's made oh in the office
why are they cooking is really chanting up a storm what has been so angry why don't you ask
that group is i wonder why these people are here can these guys get any louder
they're going to wake the dead next door maybe that's a good thing i could ask them a few
questions give us back what's ours wait oh excuse me what exactly are you why are you doing here
excuse me what exactly are you guys protesting only the greatest injustice that happened in
Salem since 1692 they're gonna give that house to the state's justice
house to the state
we have to speak up
and now we can legally take the facts well if you're doing legally then why the protest
oh
why are there protesters in a small town like this
i love i hope i hope that actor shows up in a bunch of other places in this game
you know it's gonna happen i can't wait i'll come back later wait who's may can i call may
take it to you but i'm ghosting you at least she's honest she's a ghost yeah
well let's go back to the house then don't do it don't do it don't click don't click on her and do
it again don't do it again why are there protesters been a long night let's go to sleep
and get scary haunted things album was better yeah totally it's good really you like this
why wouldn't i yeah well they were much better before they changed their basis
i meant the case what do you think about it i don't like the judge yeah i kind of got that
i think the feeling's mutual well he's a jerk maybe he burned down the hathorn house
what you don't think so let's go over the evidence that magic that olivia was using is so similar to
what i didra that magic that olivia was using is so similar to what i saw in austria i don't think
the witch of salem is burning anything except people's hard-earned money those magic tricks
are for kids if may were willing to get an alibi we can clear this up tonight she's not talking
to anyone it seems we are all allowed to enjoy some amount of privacy but her refusal to be
interviewed leads me to believe she is hiding something i can't believe you drew i thought you
were here to help you know not everyone can be as brilliant and cold as you are i'm not cold
and i never said i was brilliant either if she trusts you she'll open up and tell you the truth
and then you'll see you're kind of my last hope to reach her you're good at finding ways to get
how's the music do we not turn the car off usually so find a way i'll try the car the music from the
car is still playing it's 10 15 in the morning or 10 15 at night it's nighttime right that
oh we're gonna connect with the music i liked the first album better hey what do you listen
i know that you like this yeah yeah we were listening on the way over
first album was much better yeah too bad they changed bassists yeah too bad they changed basses
yeah i know right it's just you don't look like you listen to this music why does no one believe me
now you know how i feel
did you ever visit the estate all the time i appreciated it it's historically significant
it was built by a cold brutal man who sent a bunch of people to their death
because he didn't understand them i appreciate being reminded of what happens when greedy people
stay in charge look i spoke with the judge look i spoke with the judge they don't have anything
on me all we need is an alibi and then they can't charge you with anything and they're not going to
have anything on me because he can't prove i did it then why not just give the police an alibi
that's all they need i just can't it's not anything about me well i understand
but i can't help you or anyone else appreciate what you're trying to do not the puzzles in this
game you're supposed to like pick up pieces and open drawers and escape rooms and unlock doors
and stuff hey you know your sister cares about you your sister really cares about you they are
the old ones well she cared enough to get dear joy and i involved and worry about her
like way more than most normal people do for their passion projects
it's not a hobby it's more like something she has to do kind of sounds like i hope not it's like
her personal crusade like only she can make it better you can't live your life like that
you need to enjoy it
i use 11 it's not like she's working on an interesting relationship why don't you ask her
okay well he's so loud can you just leave her out of this i don't want her being involved with my
problems done talking okay i got i got info now we talk to okay talk to dude where is
professional you're just outside just hang up and go outside can we turn off this fucking music
please oh no you're over here well she's protecting something or someone okay yeah
i don't know yet we have to go to the hathorn house tonight tonight like in the dark when it's
scary yeah do you have flashlights you do remember what i told you about that place
you know what better idea i'll go you stay here and see if maybe be there's no such thing as ghosts
dear dra no not goes people people swear there's something in that house too many people believe
it to not be true could be a wild animal or a toxic waste dump i don't know just keep your
guard up okay all right let's not hug or anything you should check in with lauren holt she still
lives up there she still lives there it's way too far of a walk all the way there wait i thought
you said that it was fucked up there things happen after midnight in salem the town is like a gremlin
don't feed it after midnight okay here's your keys okay i can drive the car what happens in
salem which is the car they never turned they we kept it on what the music won't stop all right
let's explore the town when there's no one that's break into houses and shit apparently
turn down the volume fuck all right this is where it gets scary here it is hathorn house
is this is just what you pay for when you go to salem i'm just a customer who's frank
that actually startled me it did creepy not at all all right all right who's frank nancy you
sound excited yeah guess where i am right now and begin to ala massachusetts outside alone and in
the dark in the rain with no protection or nothing not even a flashlight and i'm by myself and it's
a very scary spot not as a suspect teagan perry mentioned she had hired you to me
it's a favor for deardra deardra shannon why is it uh are you in boston are you guys in boston
how'd you know why did i say joe that uses that name whoa nothing gets past you
what keep net on his toes this is frank to be honest i haven't really talked to what yeah us
neither is this a boston is split personality time you should come up here and check it out
while i'm in town really yeah it would be good to catch up yeah i don't know nancy with our
special detective powers we might be mistaken for witches heard they don't fare well up there are
you kidding me they love you guys it's two people but it only could be different as an official
i don't think that's true i'll bet you on it okay you're on i'll take payment when we arrive in
salem i'm in salem you don't make a bet with a person that's standing in the town earlier
why would you take that yeah same to you too bye what a terrible better place don't look behind
you the ghost will steal your soul oh ha ha got you did you find anything may isn't talking
did you say something to her no nothing in particular of course you've given me the chills
i can't believe you're actually going out there and if you see a ghost
don't let it take your soul okay thanks for the wasted data you know that i'm roaming
in salem fucking asshole i was just pressed f5 to quick save it i'm so used to pressing that button
there's someone in there there's someone in that room let's go in and find out what's in there
nancy pick up a rock it might be a little heavy but with two hands you can
cave in this person's face if they open the door and scream at you and try to kill you
what are you doing here i would have just caved in somebody's face you're trespassing this is
private property i'm giving you one chance to explain yourself uh i saw a light in the i'm an
investigator i saw a light in the window wanted to see if anyone was home yeah well there isn't so
you can leave this place isn't meant for your enjoyment enjoyment enjoy i know your type
destruction enthusiasts you take photos of destroyed buildings and accidents and such
don't online trying to get legs off of other people's misery i don't do that
look i don't have i don't have a camera i don't have a camera on me what do i look like an idiot
you have a phone don't you can i come in what the fuck you're here to take pictures and get
posts online get out of here can i come in come on in i wanted to talk to you about about the
hathorn house sit down you drink speech 100 yeah of course i didn't mean to lie to you lauren
yes you did you wanted to talk to me by any means so here we are what's going on in this house
what do you want to know um wait are we in this house i thought this house is supposed to be
scary and haunted and stuff how did we get in here your shop your shop yes what do you do there
just curious it's a tearoom and modern apothecary all right can i before there was a pharmacist
the town relied on herbalists can i do something headaches and sickness and energy can i do
something interesting did frances we've just gotten a bunch of just stories oh can i get a puzzle
can i like reassemble the tea kettle or there's a code in the window and i have to decipher it
all right speedrun what built by i don't have a yeah i appreciate i'm gonna all right so
it looks like we're gonna get here we go whoever is doing this you're not frightening me away
get the camera out how did i get in here you weren't answering your
bye why am i walking forward like this
lightning again it's not a joke three
didn't you want me to be it didn't you want me to look into it well yeah but i didn't think for a
second that you would i guess i thought you'd go up there and find smoke and mirrors or whatever it
is you do you're saying it's real i don't know what i'm saying i'm not used to being so freaked
out wait you didn't leave my car out there did you what how did i drive home calm down enough
what wasn't i like didn't my like eyes get all fucked up and i woke up here
what don't think it'll help i mean i drove home okay so let's go through it i do find my friend
back to the house all right here we go i found i found out something interesting from lauren holton
i found out something interesting we're gonna get a one sentence one sentence explanation
had a will that's the one sentence we need to find it they assume it doesn't exist
so if it does exist lauren would get the estate there it is oh and that lawyer alicia cole
represents her how's that working out for her there doesn't seem to be much progress made yeah
well without a will what could she really do i saw something to tell you drew it's as weird as
moon chunk cheese ice cream and sandals with socks but my instinct is
okay if you were in this room you would be like holy shit every time that happened
every time one of these how many times you've been in a room with somebody and lightning
strikes like that it's like holy fuck everybody gets up and like everyone walks paces around for
this is what these people have iron iron wills here like they just aren't
they whatever they're doing is what they care about that's it to find bigfoot and aliens and
the loch ness monster hey sounds fun to me it's been a long day i think i'm just gonna call it
a night you do look kinda well maybe don't video chat with the boyfriend it's so loud and so jarring
and so scary
hey what you want that chowder now the offer expired the chowder expired they would offer to
us for three days pretty good team see that's proof right there you get away from the window
too this is when like we all huddle into the bathroom that's how scary this is who's joe
explanation the town of grenich new york sorry they have a witch on their emblem we won really
sending you a pic when can we expect payment don't lose the bet that's a fire department logo
i said police public safety it's all the same a technicality there's something i have to get off
my chest i saw a ghost sorry what in this case i've never seen anything like it
what is it hold on joe looks pretty quirky i think that's so funny i don't even know what
that's supposed to mean like this be there before you know it only if you want to talk to you later
this is blood you can't just show what is going on this is blood is getting into my eyes
what the fuck it worked that actually scared the shit out of me like now i can't talk shit
about the game ever again yeah i can't talk shit about the game it actually got me i can't do that
what time is it it's early hurry up get dressed and meet me downstairs i have something to cheer
you up it's scared by a nancy drew game i no longer am allowed to talk about anything
i can't make fun of anything i can't talk shit about anything anymore i just got scared in the
nancy drew game it was pretty it was good it was pretty good all right that was good help make
breakfast are we gonna my first puzzle in an hour is gonna be chopping up onions i guarantee it
this is the sims you filmed us in the sims you wouldn't be standing breathing this in
they're trying their best to unimpress me mission accomplished nancy joe was just uh
making an effort it's like the lightning you'd be panicking right now you'd be freaking the fuck
out but he wants to prove he can do it without my help he can set out the ingredients for johnny
cakes before she had to run but i gotta admit it's been a while since i last whipped something up
successful this is more accurate let's let this conversation play out no what they fixed it right
when i pull up the how did you fix this i didn't just stop burning what happened
well it's cleared i actually i can't fucking believe it
let's approach this sensibly what do we need
still trying to cook okay so we need a flour sugar salt baking powder interesting okay
oh it's just uh everything's fine we're all good to go
pick up the spoon that that looks like a good spoon to pick up one spoon of cornmeal cornmeal
no one cup of flour no one cup of flour and sugar
it's like tablespoon one spoon of sugar looks right to me one sugar i think you got it
okay i can't take this anymore that's not as a kazoo okay two tablespoons of sugar
one cup of flour sugar salt what the fuck is this recipe who would give you this recipe
hey here's my recipe for johnny cakes one cup of uh flour i don't know sure i have no idea
one cup of flour maybe sugar i don't know two tablespoons of cornmeal oh sugar i think one
tablespoon of yeah i don't know one teaspoon this fuck this recipe i can't even believe
this is a real thing this is not a recipe this is like this is what you do but you're just like
shitfaced and you're lying in bed and you're just like you know it'd be really delicious
hey uh i'm gonna make my own donuts yeah i think i could do it better than dunkin donuts and you
just write all this nonsense and you wake up in the morning you feel like what the fuck is this
okay one cup of one cup of flour or sugar okay i'm gonna put a cup of flour in here
where's the cup where's the flour cup of flour i think you got it okay now what one cup of flour
and one cup of sugar one cup of sugar do you expect us to eat this what get it together
another one two tablespoons of corn meal one tablespoon of baking powder
once the baking i think you got it and then one tablespoon of salt one teaspoon salt we're getting
there this doesn't look right let's scrub this out and try two wait a minute one cup of flour
one cup of flour we're getting there one cup of flour one cup of flour two tablespoons of sugar
no one tablespoon of salt one spoon of salt i want to say i trust your judgment but clean it
one cup of flour looks right to me um one uh two tablespoons of sugar
one spoon of sugar i think you got it one sugar looks right to me okay one cup of flour two
tablespoons sugar one cup of he doesn't even know one cup of flour one cup of salt
this is not right is it that's what i tried too uh oh that's what i tried too what oh
what are you talking
joe you're a fucking idiot looks right to me that's what i tried
he's disgusting uh and yet i did the same one tablespoon of sugar looks right to me a tablespoon
of sugar i think you got it so one cup of flour two tablespoons of sugar one tablespoon of
baking powder there's your one cup of flour there's your one cup of one tablespoon of baking
powder no one one teaspoon but that's incorrect see one teaspoon of baking powder is wrong one
tablespoon of baking powder one teaspoon of salt one teaspoon we're getting there tablespoon of
baking powder one baking powder we're getting there and then a cup of cornmeal one cup of cornmeal
that's it looks right to me all right let's go looks great let's tackle the next step i can't
believe i have to cook what's the next one all right fucking give me a break we have to fill
the bowl until the weight is just right quick heads up this is about where things started to
go south last time hey let's just trust that nancy knows what she's doing add to cake batter
eight ounces of milk 0.5 ounces of butter egg don't forget a dash of nutmeg okay milk eight
ounces how much is in there milk eight ounces melted butter 0.5 ounces okay milk melted butter
egg vanilla 0.2 ounces where's the vanilla you get your vanilla out of a packet
0.2 that was a lot no what no that's right okay then we need uh something about an egg egg stir
it up this doesn't look right let's scrub this out and try again you can't write egg question mark
doesn't look i didn't do the nutmeg god damn it hold on milk eight ounces
half one two egg nutmeg this doesn't look right what a waste of food half butter two two eggs
nutmeg go that looks great thank you let's tackle the next step
finally my favorite part i thought your favorite part was eating my next favorite part
dear frying johnny cakes in the pan timing is important don't flip the batter raw don't flip
the batter raw be ready to flip when steaming hot watch out don't burn the cake john john i'm reading
john why did you do this you shouldn't have put this in johnny john john johnny stop
come on the pancakes oh oh oh my fucking hand i can't flip it up what john what are
what are the new utensils in this house is all this smoke okay who's ready to eat
save our the house is on fire oh i'm sorry about that uh mayor whatever you're uh i'll fix that
right away oh that's not those are crusty crabs those are uh famous uh pancakes no need to rush
these look just a tad burnt we did great but should probably do a few more burnt
turn the heat down turn the fucking heat down why would you put it what's it at
this doesn't go this fast this is on a bed of hot fucking coals
no need to rush this is where like dad runs down the stairs you know dad you know what i mean it's
like what's going on down here what are you doing what are you doing get away from the stove get
away from the stove get away from the stove hi joe hi joe yeah hi nancy nancy get what are you
doing oh my god these look just a tad burnt move out of the way did great but should probably do
a few more and then everyone's like oh sorry sorry mr albert albertson didn't mean to that's not
that's all right joe but you have it's time for you to go home it's time to go home call your
mother and have her pick you up nancy we'll talk later about this but is everybody all right
need to rush here comes some more fire how many have you done incorrect there's no need to rush
here comes some more we've gone through there's no need to like six or seven gallons of milk
oh my god somebody get an adult out here
how many eggs would you that would be like three dozen eggs five dozen eggs
pancakes yeah next when you guys are making pancakes put the heat up as high as it goes
wait till the pan is at 700 degrees oh my god do we eat this now what are we doing
pirate pancakes ghost pancakes werewolf pancakes blooper is this just a cooking game
wait what am i doing cat i'll do this one who deserves a johnny cake a few more
no need to rush why am i doing this absolutely adorable deardra acts tough sometimes
but who doesn't get happy from eating homemade pan help with breakfast what else do you want
what else do you want where they go oh right like my oh oh these smell delicious great job nancy
they look amazing okay these are the hardy brothers frank and joe we're very interested
in your case wait uh-huh they're good friends of mine they're going to help us with the aren't
these two famous the more people working on this the better chance we have the hearty the hearty
the hearty boys the hearty brothers joe you need to learn how to cook maybe let frank teach you
otherwise how are you going to impress anyone solving crimes impresses people
no one's eating their pancakes committing them what big marsh likes the five community subs
not saying i'm impressed by that just stating a fact i prefer someone who possesses a deep
intellectual appreciation and no one matters you want to be impressed we should finally show
our business plan for our new business what it's very businessy what what is it well joe and i have
been talking recently about making things a bit more official we want to franchise out detective
work we want to franchise out teenager detective work we're starting our very own detective agency
yeah insurance you sure are and and we want to know if you'd be interested in being a partner
thank you abe for the five community subs thanks abe all right drew why not update everyone on
where we're at i guess you're wondering about the thing i mentioned one thing i'd like to do
today is check the town archives so i guess you're wondering about the
i mentioned yes sounds super can't believe the only gameplay we've been able to play
told them about the whole has been making pancakes yeah i even with the most modern
scientific techniques available there are many phenomena that we still cannot explain
i believe what you saw was real what what sure some sort of combination of gaseous blow off and
light refraction no a real ghost with thoughts and memory and agency i'm not so sure i just
built some new equipment that i'd love to try out i'm sure it's nothing but we'll go to the cemetery
today and investigate anyway maybe we can add ghost hunting to our detective services
where are your parents your parents just let you just go and be ghost detectives and put you
how old is everybody here they're rich kids is this what rich kids do like they got everything
is just so taken care of that they just they make their own detective teenager agency and go hunt
ghosts is that what it is they're like 20 oh i yes actually he doesn't know omega lol one thing i'd
like to do today is check the town archives if it's all the same to you i'd prefer to handle this
you were gonna look into the history of ownership of the hathorne house right yeah sure we can go
together uh no dad dad mom and dad are out on the yacht and they get like a
oh it's joe hi joe so uh dad can i uh buy a fourteen thousand dollar expensive ass ghost
uh hunting kit uh yeah that sounds good son how are your grades they're great okay i i won't even
look i just trust what you told me all right son absolutely please just charge it to the company
happened last week and we haven't had the chance to collect any alibis yet
we need to ask everyone we've met where they were tax deductible corroborating their answers with
whomever they were with will help bring into focus who is and isn't a suspect judge danforth
mentioned that he was the victim of a mention that he was the victim of a burglary what was
stolen we don't know the judge was working with tegan on developing a case for the accused witches
organization the what the descendants of the accused witches of the 1692 salem witch trials
they're staking a claim to the hathorne estate due to unjust dispossession and execution of their
ancestors it's one of the reasons i search for the book of apologies in austria now i'm gonna do the
courtesy eat where you sit down at somebody's house and you don't want to eat it all and you
know that everyone else is going to be eating it's like you're at the something on the family's
house or something you have to at least eat the corners you have to eat the ring around the edge
i'd like to review the crime scene at the courthouse for any and then explain
more than five times he didn't sound very forthcoming that you've already eaten and oh
yeah um my mom made like a huge dinner i just ate so their old friend and you said that like
10 times to make sure that they understand why you're not eating what else david you have not
eaten anything and in fact after you leave this person's house you like go to like the mcdonald's
drive-through we need to figure out how the theft from mosem castle is connected to this case theft
of what the book of apologies my dad asked me to retrieve it from mosem castle in austria as a favor
for judge danforth who works here in salem it's cold all the victims of the witch trials well i
know why you're not eating yours however this book was stolen as well we don't see the underside of
that one when nancy was there why was this this is like a well-done pizza crust great question
the resident historian told me the judge who wrote the book willed all his belongings to be
preserved by whichever museum would have them at the time speed run i can i have something
god damn it they all left i didn't even eat anything nothing not even one bite not even a
glass of milk like then you leave it there 25 minutes go by you look out the window and you
see their car rolling by slowly and they don't know that you're looking out the window and you
see like three or four burger king bags and they're eating fries in the fucking passenger
seat and you're like god damn it those motherfuckers okay all right uh mgs fan just
give 20 subs thank you for the 20 community subs mgs fan that's a big sub drop right fucking now
some of you guys give a shitload of subs thank you grats to everyone that got one dodged again
right all right now but thank you seriously that's a lot of money investigate breaking at
courthouse okay we'll do that what i have a cat pancake wait a minute i have to make this i'm
gonna have to make some of these okay um let's make one of each frankenstein pink i'm gonna make
lead one of each cooking the batter is already done i just have to i'm gonna have like a bunch
of pancakes in my inventory being to rush being to rush stop pouring them in here so fast
relying to rush it's the hardest part of the whole game all right i think frank would like
these frank would like these what are the ones get a witch pancake okay witch i'm gonna need
this for something i'll do who deserves it 15 i need to come on two three four and i can't even
count not bad oh shit i don't have any more left this is gonna be perfect all right i got a witch
pancake now just what i imagine olivia would like okay what is this turning the star to valley
how many things i'm gonna have in my inventory all right well i have some pancakes let's see
what i can do with this let's give olivia hey she's not here anymore all right get a key
investigate the break-in why are there the person's just been there just can't get over the fact that
there's protesters in front they can't get over it okay there's a break-in miss drew how can i help
you hi miss cole alicia oh same great so what do you need you both named alicia wow cool that's
weird i thought you were named nancy or perhaps a hammer drill i'm more of a pneumatic ha ha
uh you have a hammer drill in here you have a hammer drill in here in my closet
i'm a bit of a home improvement junkie well thanks but i don't need any of those things
why'd you ask for it i do have some questions though please okay i'm sure you've heard about
the burglary i'm sure you've heard about the burglary in the court's evidence room yes
unbelievable you know i've started asking myself what is happening in this town it used to be such
as arson's and where there's a pattern here arson it's the kind of place i want to raise my kids
oh you're trying to start a thing i mean yes i want to start a family but who has time work
when is the end to be honest and the people living in this place like salem is not i'm not
really into salem how about you i have a boy really he doesn't accompany you you know he's not part
of your little trips of the thing that you're doing well he's apart he's far away and we've
been dating for a couple of years no one said it was easy it's not easy to do long-distance
relationships all i'll say is most men don't understand what we go through we have to fight
to get a seat at their table and then they want us to go home and be family makers
some unsolicited advice from one working woman to another don't let his plans get in the way of
yours of course that's not bad advice does you do you you all right you do you they don't what uh
how about doing some follow-ups with the arson where were you that night where were you did you
burn the building down well i was at a charity fundraiser saving the piping clubbers anyone in
this town fundraiser i don't think i'm a little bit surprised just being thorough i can respect
that okay uh what who has access to the evidence room as far as i know just me let me in i don't
like saying this but the judge occasionally all right sometimes the judge uh sometimes the judge
sleepwalks the man even locked himself in his own office for pity's sake not that it matters
i was told the burglar came from the outside well then is it he's probably leaving doors open
liking me for this crime nancy no i don't like anyone for this crime or any other crime for
that matter i was not here i was running errands what's the code of the evidence room do you have
it no sorry he hasn't given that to me yet all right get the code knowing him he's probably
already lost it okay why did you bring your hammer drill to the office why did you bring
your hammer drill well after the burglary we realized that this place was in dire need of
higher security i ordered the keypad online and used the drill to mount it that's impressive
yeah still ended up calling a professional okay cool hey how are you doing i'm okay well maybe
not really do you need me to come over no no no don't don't come over i'm coming over i will
don't come over no we don't i don't know no it's fine i need to keep my nerves calm every mystery
can be solved i'll figure this out i know you will just keep at it thank you always let me
know if there's anything i can do any of these kids have homework but not today i can't there's
too much to do come on jason you need it jason i have had these protesters outside my window
non-stop for days i must deal with this situation yeah yeah yeah but i'm buying lunch you're buying
really with what yeah i opened up this ghostbuster business good for you it's not healthy
what are you talking about you resent me i don't resent you jason miss drew please come in
i'm already here okay oh you have time for her but not for me please yes yes yes yes please go
run your ghostbuster business hi jason damford nancy drew nancy drew you're visiting Salem yeah
what do you think kind of a boring town beneath all the legends jason come on we have a meeting
jason jason here's 1200 dollars just just go go buy some stuff whenever you're up for real
excitement look me up i'm sorry he's still trying to figure out what he wants to do with his life
didn't want to follow in his father's footsteps oh he tried didn't have the dedication to follow
through with the schooling let's get started okay uh do you like cat pancakes how about
frankenstein how about a witch pancake no how about some spray paint how about a photo how about a
key how about we talk as you know i want to investigate the crime i want the code information
isn't usually available to the public i'm afraid i can't just take your word for it i'll have it
taken care of as you know i want to investigate that crime scene where's the keypad information
isn't usually available to the public it's gonna be like it's gonna be somewhere like on his
fucking desk it's gonna be like a keypad code it's gonna be literally pasted somewhere like
an old person it's gonna be on a post-it note on a computer this is gonna be so easy whoa what
actually that was damien you have an intern this is a new character i haven't seen him he's around
someone has to make the coffee here i'm swamped most days and i could barely trust oh i mean
you're right i'm skipping all this dialogue i just met with uh jason danforth jason danforth
what did you think kind of cute huh what what are you talking about different tastes yeah kind
of like a fast food cheeseburger with extra extra cheese oh so fucking incredible what can i say
love cheese that like so you know all right this is freaking me out a little
he does odd jobs for me sometimes doesn't hurt that he's easy on the eyes he is kind of dumb
though i wouldn't really know to be honest listen spare yourself the headache and just avoid him
trust me not much substance he loves his car okay uh i'm going to get that code
get judge danforth 10 more community sums from germa sucks thank you germa sucks appreciated
another 10 from germa sucks i really should call dad so he can run this by the judge call dad
jeopardize the whole investigation if i was caught snooping around the courthouse wait what so i
have to so this really is just all right call dad and it is a golf ball there's a golf ball here
okay this is
who is this guy you should bring up the lake winnipeg stocky regatta dad maybe later sure
i actually had to call rich powerful dad to continue my like keep my daughter
thanks dad you know i learned it all from you right oh now i know that's not true
the judge told me about a certain lock picking you certainly didn't learn that from me
me may have picked up a few extra skills along the way i'd expect nothing less okay go get him
love you kiddo yeah and dad dad's gotta go dad's gotta go he's currently he's currently
fucking fuming right now he's 15 over par and he's currently in a sand in a sand trap right now so
i've gotta go i've gotta go see you at dinner in three days goodbye is a bitcoin oh what it's a
how much is it worth what centralized digital currency all these new made up digital things
just go to bitcoin if you ask me nothing's ever been wrong with good old american benjamins
as you know unless you bought it like five years ago could you give me the code for the keypad oh
yes about that well you see i had it written on a post-it note but i seem to have misplaced it it
should be around here somewhere feel free to look for oh my god i knew it don't worry about
i have to look for it look if i had it somewhere i had it somewhere okay cool
get rid of that rusted ass pencil shopper now that's an emergency room trip if i have
every single one all right what am i gonna go around there's a number one five who's calling
okay let's go in the evidence room uh do you have a list of the evidence that was taken
yes actually you should be able to get it from the computer in the evidence room
okay feel free to use the printer and take the list with you can find all the evidence
it's gonna turn into a hidden object sort of information isn't usually available to the
i understand i'll keep the list closed okay here we go what was it oh one oh eight one five
does somebody just break in again what is going on here what oh why did they like why did they
punch the wall in perfect places six times glass on the floor so the window was broken from the
inside what nancy nancy i think it's time to call dad oh man oh man uh checked out by
okay there was a knife somebody checked out a knife somebody checked out somebody somebody
checked out a gun no no this is not a library this is not oh no no they didn't check out these
things this is what came in this is an evidence room okay uh no but they did check it out all
right foster more and cold okay now figure out which ones were stolen okay figure that out let's
go to the computer it's dusty boot it up it's dust it's dusty just turn it on boot it up evidence
list computer evidence list in the vcr is too dusty to use a map of salem what is this for
a map of salem what is okay d2 d4 d3 d1 d5 is it districts all right i got the evidence list
and found out which one was stolen oh shit oh no okay hold on evidence list anything missing uh
item number five in d22 uh use the evidence yeah it's stolen yes no uh eight number eight
there's no number eight who numbered these why would you do it like this no yeah look no
no right what's the number no no no all right wait wait wait number 18 number 18 were collected by
parry their pictures are supposed to be in here they have not been checked out got you got you
motherfucker interesting no no wait a minute what's in this one number 11 that is uh there's a uh
parry took out there's a tet this would be a testimony in there interesting interesting
bags of weed no what is this no what okay hold on what is this number 19 what's in 19
unknown sample what are you talking about no no is that it no no no interesting okay all of the
stolen evidence was linked to the accused witch's claim to hathorn house
okay is that it what about the computer it's dust it's dusty i can't like play these tapes
all of the stolen all the linked to the accused witch's claim to all right it's about the claim
to hathorn house let's go i got the evidence where is it i know who did it let me call dad first
i'm sure he'll hear from him soon all right uh who has access to the evidence room
oh well that would be me and alicia well because i'll come yes do you mind telling me what you
were doing three days ago what you were doing three days ago three days ago all day all day
i don't i wonder what you ate well for breakfast lunch and dinner would be helpful actually why
are you interested in this i was in austin nancy drew junior detective that's the thing
that i made in like a 3d printer i flip it out like a fbi agent i believe is connected to this
fact i see i was talking to your father about that case really yeah we chat sometimes mostly
okay ask it you're a regular sleuth aren't you no master other cases now not exactly
it's kind of related yeah let's see watching jason cut out the stump out of my front yard
you hired jason danforth for that he's cheap and he can't say no it's the money plus i kind of like
watching him suffer i wouldn't know you know let's walk out of this room there is always a need of a
good private investigator if your father would be okay with you working for someone else call him
i'm my own woman i work for myself but you've been very helpful and i really appreciate it
good well when you solve this case let's talk uh okay what did you mean when you said the people
here oh you probably know you've been around town i have people with minds as small as the town
you can only meet so many with the same mindset before you see a pattern
that's interesting something happened nothing much uh something i just wish this place wouldn't be
a bit something i wish it was a larger town more progressive imagine a revitalized town
okay we can dream you're sure okay bye motive motive we've got a motive what do you mean motive
why are you parked here i don't why are you parked here you know are you are you part of the
protest i knew you couldn't resist yes are correct jason i could not i'm open tomorrow
or tonight no one sits on their car like this
where were you the night of that hot thorn house was burned where were you it's coming to me primal
cut i'm sorry steak house i was there with my dad great steak very expensive hilltops so if we
haven't been on a date yet does that mean we're going to go one more in the future no no thank
another question i have another yes it's true
i was shocking what you were doing three days ago are you sure yes i was actually
digging out a stump in alicia cole's backyard you digging out a stump what that's true not my
favorite pastime but i can't really say no to the money it gives a good damn we have two witnesses
that corroborated the same story that that's supposed to be accurate unless they're working
together maybe you should ride with me to the beach i can show you no thanks no thank you
all right so these two make one pancake why are there protesters in a small town like these
alibis and books that yeah the alibis really are so investigate breaking at the courthouse
getting key to the hot the hot the hot thorn house the hat thorn is it hat thorn hot thorn
hey thorn how do i pronounce this is it hot thorn hot thorn hey thorn what's the big holdup
the parry brat has always been a little fire starter only a matter of time until the neighborhood
watch catches her red handed the system has gone soft lets them off the hook easy then everyone
acts surprised about repeated offenders they better book her before halloween i don't want
to let the kids out trick-or-treating with an arsonist on the loose here's the thing
oh should we take the witch door you're not gonna if they what i don't understand that logic all
right uh where i need to go i did not investigate the break-in good enough i need a key to the house
i where's parry parry where's this person no i'm not clicking her
all right i need to go i'm gonna go to the museum text user has been added to the chat what chat
did i just get dragged into an annoying famous nancy drew finally arrived to solve our ghostly
conundrums what is this oh it's an obnoxious group chat that you can not get read out of
and we're gonna blow up your phone all fucking day there's like 10 people in here
and if you leave this conversation then we all know that you didn't want to be here in the first
place so you have to stomach this every single fucking day every day until you inevitably leave
the conversation and then you text every person that was in that conversation you say hey my
phone was stolen last night i have and i have to get a new phone number
okay i don't know this is just absolutely just gibberish uh we're trying to figure out what
could have caused you to see a ghost maybe an actual ghost like this only in the good days
hey i'm here you know we know we know oh cute uh dude i'm gonna go follow some leads good luck
let us know wasting data this is ready yet nancy hey how's the investigation going it's going good
where were you you know it would really help if i could get may to talk to me she hasn't given her
alibi yet no and everyone seems to have one except her how do i know that i talk to one two people is
it possible that it could be someone from outside of town a visitor or something absolutely but
statistically speaking crime is rarely a random occurrence it's a mystery to me what you have
anything you wanted to talk about crime is not usually a random occurrence is that true
that feels yeah that feels that's like not true the person that like steals your purse on the
sidewalk is an old family friend okay what's the history behind uh the hathorne estate what's the
history behind the hathorne estate that's how you pronounce it right well uh judge john hathorne was
born and raised in salem his father was a decorated military man who had many real estate
holdings throughout new england and when judge hathorne became a justice he tried to expand
those holdings much of the land that the hathorne estate was built on was actually seized perhaps
all right cool is the fire somehow related do you think the fire is somehow related to salem's
history with what do you mean like is it meant as a symbolic gesture that was a european thing
no they were more civilized in the new world no i think they just did it for no reason
it was a random crime you know that most crimes are random right why would you even ask me that
pressed yeah they put a bunch of heavy stones on top of you a bit of days that's horrible she did
not know the way until she felt the freedom scarlet letter also a descendant of judge hathorne
except nathaniel hawthorne was so horrified with his family's history that he added a w
to change it wow the focus on descendants isn't really yep we think our world is so much more
advanced now we have a hard time escaping our past where were you three nights ago there was
this photo tucked away in the guest room there was this photo tucked away in the guest room
now i'm really embarrassed such an awkward age is that olivia and lauren in the picture with you
yeah we were pretty tight back then which is had to take pictures i couldn't tell where it was
taken do you remember there were lots of books and candles i was probably the sour tower diamond
books and candles are everywhere in salem it could be
where were you in the night of the fire where were you on the night of the fire
did salem not have any police watching a movie here this is his number you can ask him have you
been dating damien for a long time yeah a couple years ago i like him i mean i really do he listens
to me yeah he's great was he with you the whole night i mean most of the night i don't think he's
capable of arson if that's what you're suggesting you trust him absolutely 100 call him okay sure
talk i'm gonna um i'll call him right now right now let's see hello is that your profile damian
yeah hi my name is nancy drew i'm a private investigator currently working the half thorn
house case on behalf of judge danforth do you mind if i take up a minute of your time um
just wanted to follow up on some statements statements made by who teagan perry yes your
girlfriend who's that right right where were you sorry but were these statements given to the
um they were given to me willingly yeah sorry i i worked for alicia and i've learned to make
sure that when you're being questioned you always have a lawyer present i don't want to sound like
i'm guilty or complicit i just know my rights of course but you sound trustworthy god oh thanks
how long have you worked for alicia guilty yeah for a while you seem to know a lot about legal
press it press him i'm gone anyway i was with teagan on the night of the fire that's what you
wanted to know right yeah yeah what did you guys do you guys do watch the movie okay what movie
which movie honestly couldn't tell you don't know what movie you watched some kind of vampire drama
apocalyptic teenage angsty things don't tell her but i never oh like this game the hard sci-fi
like the game we're anything else or okay no thanks for talking to me yep sure bye nancy hey
how did frances tuttle come to own the property miss tuttle bought it 30 years ago cheap it was
falling apart the former owners couldn't be located so it was auctioned she was a bit of a kooky lady
living in a ruin like that she was kind i mean she took in lauren like a daughter that says
something about someone doesn't it i agree what were you doing three nights ago what you were
doing three nights ice skating movie i mean movie movie oh no arrest me i'm sorry why you were
working at the museum can anyone confirm that well i'm here but was anyone else here may was
home all day laying low and olivia wasn't here either i don't know where she was weren't you
watching a movie so no one can confirm that and you're sure may was at home she's barely
left the house since the incident people here treat her like she has an infectious disease
it's awful and i don't blame her if she wants to sit at home on her phone all day
i need to come home soon wait what so i gotta ask what do i get out of this you get out of this
i get a lot really justice matters travel around talk to all these people deal with all their
problems put yourself in harm's way not always all right some of the time i don't know it's like
there's these small obstacles that i enjoy working on and they're interesting but what i really love
is the puzzle of humanity what makes people tick why do people do what they do it's always the
hardest one to crack because sometimes we do things that don't make sense we're inherently
irrational you know there's a theory about why this is a great comment i know he's not skipping
lines right now but it sounds like he is in cereal grains might have gotten into the food supply
it poisons anyone who eats wait we got a poisoned food supply relation issues seizures it would have
made people look like they were possessed or made the judges think they were doing god's will or
make the whole town go haywire a rational explanation for irrational behavior just a
theory we'll never know anyway i don't want to keep you thanks for stopping by thank you by the
way teagan don't take this the wrong way but seriously that is the ugliest plant i have ever
seen in my entire life it's awful just put a cactus on here this takes up 20 of your entire desk
it is so ugly i'm sorry i had to just tell you and why do you have two computers why do you
have two computers next to each other gamer no one of this is a cash register all this stuff isn't
wait you have four computers all right have any more information this is a quad monitor
did the exhibitions why do you two chairs spark your interest they did i found this display
showing the ancestry of the accused but it didn't mining bitcoin i was wondering if you had
mega desk stored here somewhere this is so big you have the upper floor
fucking mega desk would it be okay for me to go up there it's so huge a better picture of
the history of say usually we don't allow people up on the second floor your desk is so big you
don't even know what to put on it you've got like you've got like the uh a bible after all
the shoe box is a giant five foot long plant i'll open the door for you open the door really cool
what door what the fuck just happened oh wait wait hold on why is there a secret entrance
was anyone paying any attention i nobody was how do i get back there she's gonna lock me up here
whoa originals these books must be hundreds of years old no wonder they're restricted
i hope their information is still open to the public what do you mean restricted
what is this harry potter what are you talking about someone's a busy bee old court protocols
ancestry records teacan is really digging deep into the witch trials i can't read this
all right so i'll just look for a code scarlet letter sammy and paris perry all right that's all
i needed to hear just those words the highlighted one uh the recipes with pancakes
it's 10 15 always this is freaking me out every clock is 10 15 straight uh there's a stray book
a w7 is expected to be created by uh
the secret underground passage is to smuggle the illegal goods to gangsters
and gain wealth of the illegal beverage the bootlegger's old inscription marked way underground
okay what i was gonna do up here is that all i can do something else with a desk a secret book
no other books or anything nothing nothing hidden the first puzzle of this game was i
had to click on a tiny square on a desk and open it nothing like that has happened since
we learned about the history of salem this has to be another secret yeah there has to be another
secret candles yeah i could do something with the couch why would this be here yuck something
under the couch you wouldn't just have a couch you wouldn't there's no reason for this couch to
exist that's not that nobody would have a couch the video game is telling me whoa originals
these books must be hundreds of years old yeah they're hundreds of years old over here nothing
what's that there's a message there's a message over there what's it say two messages outside
i know like i can see the outline of the door that's back there broom pencils pens anything
whatever let's go found you looking for no i'm gonna come back and pull the right book later
nancy hey goodbye where's the the lady backwards book idiot backwards there's a backwards book
no it's not what are you talking about originals i already did this all right i'm out can't you
can't you put it down we debated him oh wait is the gift shop open the gift shop's open
it's open oh face cave-in rocks i've seen that before where
i just left no go back in oh it's you it's you wait you like pancakes right off the bat here
did you make this for me yes yep and look it's got a witch on it oh witch cake for the resident
which aren't you just the sweetest so thoughtful you know right into the trash i think you might
have some magical energy flowing through you with enough flair and a touch of charisma you could
really go a long way as a witch thank you but my career goals set a little differently get
enjoy the food the fuck out of here let me guess more questions spooky though at home
where were you three days ago well i was ordering pizzas three days ago were you
doing any witch tours three days ago i was not three days okay you were doing actually i had
won a spa holiday at the wayfarer in over in marble head it was amazing they used those
oh dude marble hat i know what that is it was wicked crazy they did their research it was all
expenses paid and i'd show you my back but i'm a quick healer witch powers it looks like it
never happened you know a flyer for the spa but i threw it away this morning you went from boston
to michigan i had okay you are i did have a flyer it was i i had this wicked cool flyer
okay yeah that's a lie so i've heard ghosts are hunting salem it's about you
teagan and lauren when you were kids it's about you teagan and lauren when you were kids why are
you interested in this we grew apart it happens lie i found an old lie that's a lie then it had
the name coven on it look was it the one you talk about in your show you found this photo at teagan's
house i didn't peg her as sentimental so was it the same one well yes same coven we heard about
it as kids i guess we were all into history and witches we still are and yet you've never made up
i don't get why you care can't help it it's a mystery even if you all tell me it isn't
i've been going around asking everyone in town where they were on the night of the arson
the night of the what arson how do you not know this why i have no idea what you're talking
imagine not knowing about a famous house burning down okay i was gonna say no all right
spare me this bullshit don't look so serious don't please i'll hear our investigation here
that night doing my thing i think there had to have been at least 20 people who can confirm that
it really stinks that lauren is going to lose her home well we'll see yeah of course
of course they're ghost hunting of course you believe it how could i not when i've seen them
with my own eyes most people describe what you saw uh sure it was dark foggy i was walking through
the cemetery i was at the town square i don't remember but i do remember a ghost no scary
ghosts spirits how much for the bowling ball near hathorne house as a matter of fact i did
i told you that a coven of witches unleashed them on the town a few years back they will not rest
until he was bored what let me guess you can't find proof of a living soul acdc freak thanks for
the five community cells maybe the culprit wasn't among the living that sounds even harder to prove
have you seen the restless souls of salem nancy i've seen something but i'm not willing to just
believe it's real i need more be careful world of warcraft find you whether you believe in the
trailer for the new human redesign you might read the cemetery okay got it that's what it was that's
what i've been trying to find what it was that's what i was trying to figure it out i figured it
out when like cataclysm came out it was like this like the big redesign of all the models
that's what this is that's been it's been bugging me for at least 20 minutes or so 30 minutes i
haven't even talked about it i know that's not that's no joke i that just i just i didn't want to
bring it up because i didn't want you guys think about like the fuck is he talking about so i know
that should have just kept it internal apparently i guess that was world loads of was it was it then
they start that and um home depot ost no just rewind two days hey there girl can't tell if
you're supposed to be cute or creepy what have we learned get alibis investigate i gotta go back
to the break-in all right let me let me um give me books that i can touch plenty of 1015 clocks
what about this i have to i have to show this to uh i know i know i know all right all right back
it up back it up i know what i have to do i have to go show that to tegan and say hey what's going
on here why did you do all this shit excuse me nancy didger only mentioned it in passing but you
and olivia only mentioned it in passing used to be friends we were and i guess it doesn't hurt to
mention that lauren was a part of our little group as well but that was years ago and you don't get
along did something happen we spread apart i don't see why this is not yeah aren't you supposed to
be clearing my sister's name she doesn't need more blame for things she didn't do what did she get
the blame for before i i would this town wants someone to blame for i want to know more about
anyone who might have a motive for the fire i guess what can tell me about olivia what can i tell you
about i can tell you that i think her schtick is ridiculous okay you don't like that what she's
doing she's doing this town a disservice because selling this silly she's mocking you of being a
real witch in trouble version of witches do you think she would have burned down the house i
suppose it would be good for business people love a ruin especially a haunted ruin she is
pretty happy lighting fires but i don't know she gets happy when fires light i know i can't
help but think about the rumor olivia talks if you shouldn't pay any attention to her stories
it's bullshit whatever she thinks the crowd wants sure real history isn't interesting to olivia
magic like you do this rumor else i didn't say that there are no witches in salem just showy
frauds and stupid kids doing stupid things don't trouble yourself with ancient all right talk to
you what's this you like pancakes okay i've had this rust remover for two in-game hours what do
i need to do with this remove some rust already i'm trying i heard there's a new exhibition coming
up at the museum i heard there's a new cool what about this place oh you're here oh yes i am
this shop is really cool i love the decor thank you it's taken a lot of years to get it the way i
want i kind of imagine this is what an actual is a hand would look like yeah these are minecraft
look st john's wart mandrake root you know witches were just synonymous with people who
used the old medieval ways of working with plants and animals curing ills they were healers shamans
and confessors you can see why some people might have been threatened by them i know right no leech
is here though i draw the line at bloodsucker i'm standing very far away you get it a lot of people
around here don't how so some say i'm cashing okay i could go forward history people get so
caught up in the death and judgment but i was always interested in all of that lost knowledge
that's right a lot of kids used to be okay uh you get a lot of people in maybe uh may perry you get
a lot of people in for instance maybe may perry may why look she's had a hard time she's not the
only one i've been the kid everyone looks at you need friends to talk to she doesn't want any
nancy drew is jimmy neutron teagan protects what's in jimmy neutron the same voice actress that's may
is it no it's not is it though gosh these pastries look delicious
uh okay what are we doing all right we're gonna have the time speedrun speedrun to the next gaming
section what kind of herbs do you have here what
you're completely wrong uh okay what we're doing all right we're gonna have the time speedrun
speedrun to the next gaming section what kind of herbs do you have here what
all right i think at this point we we very loudly explained with preparing the remedies if that's
okay with you give me a break i love learning new things did they just design this this cooking
minigame and they're like fuck that's all we have right now sure it would be fun to pass on the
basics at least i'll be around the shop and manage the counter just let me know when you
have something finished and okay let's make a potion i've prepared the patient notes already
you can find them on the counter reference book to study the herbs
okay all right what how do i cure diarrhea this book looks really worn i need to slam that must be
cinnamon cam meal rosemary garlic yep okay you know eating garlic uh gives you a spider senses
and you turn into leonardo da vinci's painting of the guy that's pointing in like five places on the
clock right okay so how do i make these please don't touch that it's private ask me not to read
this what do you mean don't read this relevant to the case don't read this
crib in the next room you won't have to find any if you do it will mean in person pass down in our
family book written by tituba sentory which trials and roam the remedy all sorts let's make
a let's make a potion i'm gonna do garlic garlic to read the patient's note ah hold on a second
there lauren putting garlic in anything makes it right so excuse me back up this is my potion
okay garlic what the fuck you mean read the book read the book i write this book as a memory saved
that my knowledge gather will live on through you remedies with nature's grace all right well
what do you do a fragrant and costly spice spend wisely profitable for digestion strengthens the
stomach and helps regain lost appetite clears red pimples from the face and sweetens breath
all right so give me some cinnamon oh yeah i lost the key to that one sorry it has to be
somewhere around here i would never bring it home with me oh my god okay cinnamon cinnamon
all right good eat it cinnamon cinnamon did you read the book properly how do i what is this
what's that flowers fever few fever remember to read the patient's
these are the notes she took when discussing the ailments with her patients need to figure
out the proper mix of herbs to cure these moderate nausea slight memory condition
uh cinnamon and uh restless mind okay here we go cinnamon and chamomile
how much is that this is chamomile right fever fever fever what does chamomile look like
done remember to read the patient's
is fever how much of each all pains in the head when applied to the crown
apply directly to the forehead fever fewer apply directly to the forehead apply directly to the
forehead i'm sorry i got stuck all right um memory conditions and nausea sweet memory where's memory
lost memory sage cinnamon sage what is sage sage to read the patient's note carefully
scarcely you will find a better remedy than ginger to correct vomit and loathing
brought up from the stomach if available add fennel or anise seeds to sucor heats the joints
ginger so it ginger cinnamon and
and sage you're gonna have to start over this won't work for those elements what is that
ladies this is just ginger and sage ginger first proper herb mixture no cinnamon congratulations
thank you it's tricky to keep track of everything but the book really helps it's old and worn
from use all right now what moderate migraines and slight indigestion that's cinnamon and uh
cinnamon cinnamon and garlic cinnamon digestion so cinnamon and what was it migraines cinnamon
garlic no what was the migraine one fever few cinnamon fever few
once i've memorized it's uh slight high blood pressure slight liver conditions
migraine liver high blood pressure migraine liver a high fever few migraine fever few uh
uh liver condition fever few rosemary our lady's thistle our okay our lady's thistle
fever few our lady's thistle and uh high blood pressure garlic just go to a doctor what
high blood pressure is garlic absolutely and pulls leeches are scared
high blood pressure that is what garlic that's what garlic is used for
where's the garlic garlic thank you okay commercial grade tea machine what was the
point of doing this gosh are you smoking now no no no no no no no i did the i didn't get
a board out of here unbearable appetite moderate anxiety slight indigestion no get me out get me
out get me out get me the fuck out of here can i borrow the key to the house i was hoping i could
borrow a key key oh i don't have a key anymore you don't no but alicia does okay if you add
thank you i'm sure you've been asked where were you on that mic from work crossing through the
cemetery see the orange glow i need garlic for my unbearable appetite were you the first one to
you got that wrong i need a full bowl of spaghetti and meatballs to cure my unbearable appetite
are you trying to say that i need a two large orders good of buffalo wings
a million times but i'll say it again for your benefit i'm just okay cool is there a kelp in
salem everyone says there's ghosts in this town do you think there are ghosts here
well remember where you were that night i forgot to mention i forgot to mention
i was speaking with alicia and she mentioned that she yeah okay good talk to alicia can she
waiting room ban that person okay alicia hey alicia uh do you have any you know jobs i could
do i'm really good at cutting up carrots and shit if you need somebody to to clean your juicer
fusions president of the half horn estate carriage house so do you know her absolutely
how's the case how's the case but you are the daughter of a lawyer i am so without a will
there is no case and without the will need to get the will good i can try to get okay i promise
let me give you guys a reality here if the next if the next piece of gameplay it's the only copy
is cooking or preparing food items i will alt f for the game i promise might have to say you
stole it i'll make sure to be discreet wait let's get the key hey next time i got the key to the
house let's go wait i need to investigate this more can't use that here what else is there
huh what do you got for me investigate this no we're going right to the house this poor lady
see why are they protesters i feel so bad for that lady okay you've made it to no where am i
going no no no that was the right way go back wow i knew salem was small but i didn't know salem was
two streets although it took a long time to drive here on one road let's go let's go
locked oh it's locked the key should fit but the door and lock are awry the door needs more leverage
are you serious what are you talking about rust the key should fit but the door the door needs
more leverage what do you mean what do i have put another key in first put in two cartridges
one on top of you put one nintendo cartridge in and then push down place and put another
nintendo cartridge on top and then it'll work decoration wouldn't nancy drew series is going
to die at least in america and it may well be deserved i can't see the competitive community
or even the casual player by surviving into next year the reasons are numerous i know that's a you
copy and pasted what you just said and you might have made it up but why do i feel like that's like
like a steam review this ought to help all right get it in there now this is more like it wedge it
in there get that key go there we go now it fits vegetables and fruits i could cut up one of these
secretary desk roaring 20s maybe okay key rust this opens with a button somewhere i know it
those who didn't chat right now no it doesn't yes it does if i don't i'm gonna press a button
somewhere and it's gonna open yes it does it doesn't yes it does the walls are still smoldering
from the fire it's making my eyes water balls are still smoldering from the fire peculiar about this
mirror when painted laurels on the mirror glass
that scared the shit away what is it about a thing ross big on what's wrong there's a
book it has a little etching on it so who cares oh we've gone brand new jacket found a jacket
who would leave this behind the name on this jacket i can't unzip a business card
witch tours uh-oh olivia ravencroft uh-oh olivia ravencroft what were you what were you
doing here what were you doing here dusty what the fuck is this francis tuttle needed this
medical machine to stay alive wonder what will happen to it now have text nope francis tuttle
the phone work scary thing's gonna walk by the woods over there that way that's a perfect place
for it i don't know why you didn't do it quick what the entire second floor has burned down
it looks unstable not going any further than this okay well i got the business card
what about uh on the wall boxes what's this something in the boxes what's the painting
not the painting the you know i'm saying the mirror what's the mirror for how do i open
this i gotta press a button oh okay this is what's what okay wait a minute this is a reflection of
something there's something on here anti-rust on this forever what about on the side yeah
good call oh there's nothing there good call
all right i got the jacket and i got the wall on the left side i don't see anything
what do you what what do you see there's just this etching you have an aw key yeah i can't use it
i already tried that aw key can't use that here see uh the game crashed what is it gonna put me
all right i know i know listen guys everybody everybody listen listen i'm gonna speedrun this
again no stop doing that i got the jacket i got the business card let's go any percent nancy drew
speedrun it's possible i can't go over here anymore all right let's go interrogate uh the
witch lady speedrun of baldi's basics
got you got you got you got you got you got you got you say it with me got you
got you we got you we got you we got you we got you we got you we got you we got you we got you
got you we got you we got you we got you we got you we got you this jacket oh my gosh where'd you
find it i've been looking for this it was in the hathorne house what was it doing there
i've never been there don't know but it had your business card in its pocket so i knew it was yours
what luck that's great that's it i just handed over evidence i found this jacket of yours
at this crime scene oh my jacket thanks here take it back you didn't tell anybody else about this
yet have you no i came right to you and i'm i'm showing you that you're in trouble now
thanks for giving me the jacket i'm gonna burn it backstage like what a dope
let's let's go play by the train tracks what does that even mean what all right somebody does it
i want to speed run this i don't have any evidence here's a business card can i spray somebody's face
with this yet we just want justice there's something that i didn't do here what is it
this is a bed frame i don't get it anything at the house it's the bars on the window
but who cares i feel like it's something with the computer that i can't do it's dusty it's dusty
that's even you needed a key to turn your computer on like a car a map of salem this doesn't matter
what does this matter investigate the break-in isn't that what i'm doing a cctv camera oh there
might be footage from the break-in with all right let's go missing evidence and to get a
list of everything that's missing judge i'm afraid i haven't been completely honest with you nancy
what let's just say i can tell when someone is trying to hide something from me the reason
karson sent you to mosem castle was because i already knew what was stolen from the courthouse
tegan perry had assembled a packet of documents outlining her accused witch's claims on the
half-born house they were compelling and i believe she had a real claim but now missing
someone from sweden i must admit that i've already figured out the entire storyline
i'll hold my tongue for you americans though
oh
uh okay do you remember do you have the cctv footage from the break-in yes we do
huh and completely forgot didn't even turn the cameras off and he broke into his own house
of course oh you see nancy i haven't been completely honest with you
you know how i locked myself in places well i was going in the evidence room to get a snack
and then i got stuck in the cage so i just picked up the computer desk and smashed it into the window
and climbed out i do this once in a week i need help i need to be helped do you remember any
details about the aw evidence i don't remember much unfortunately oh there was this key with
its blade shape to spell aw very not sure what it was connected to like this one yes that's it
where did you find this just missing a ton of painful reverb yeah the theft of the book of
apologies and the theft of evidence from the courthouse someone is going to great lengths
to prevent the aw organization from having a claim on the half-born estate any educated
guess who that might be practically everybody in this town everyone has a carnival attraction
and i'm sure lauren carnival oh i love carnivals have to dig deeper well you'll need to do it
quickly i unfortunately must file the second bugleberry is it audible two thousand people
leave okay what evidence who cares that is a somewhat complicated question so many moving
parts and interested parties with crossover jurisdictions you're the one who decides i feel
like that's like this on the same level as a slap i can tell you're not happy about being the center
it's pretty close well it's muddy legally and complicated for other reasons because it's not
just who lives there is history yes not to be taken lightly okay uh where were you when this
evidence was stolen when this evidence was stolen if you can believe it i was here working i have
no reason to steal the evidence trust me how would you not know this is happening headaches
than i care to admit headaches i got something for that i it's cinnamon and fever few mash it
up into a bowl and then pour it in water hot water and then drink it do you have diarrhea too
i can fix that do you mind me asking what you were doing three days ago
that would be the day you visited mosem castle are you asking for an alibi miss drew i'm just
trying to confirm what everyone was doing the day that the book of apologies this is worse than
skyrim i know it was stolen no this is the same as skyroom except the camera is zoomed out by
about 100 percent right but other people might say they were with you i was at salem district
court let me help you here so unless you let me help you question for you judge do you remember
where you bring dinner with my son very expensive dinner because jason got the 64 ounce tomahawk chop
yeah a little more right thank you judge also i thought you should know there's a car parked
outside in the handicapped spot huh you don't say i'll have it taken care of goodbye now
can i help you miss true can i help you miss true right thank you judge so i thought you
should know there's a car parked outside in the handicapped spot huh you don't say i'll have it
taken care of goodbye now do you guys actually even care if i played the rest of the fucking
game like this yes can i help you sorry i think that's the judges did you know that the break-in
was faked sorry i followed broken and entered the evidence stop moving around i told the judge to
lock that door and considering how lax security is around here it's too loud and then see you later
sick sick sick sick sick sick okay now we have what do i what do we have i forget everything
already it's dust we have evidence that what what what was it it was the key the aw key
but for what what was it for watch the footage how do i do that though i wasn't paying any
attention judge left get cctv can i help right thank you judge huh you don't say i remember
break the windows how uh search gather alibis vcr of the evidence room didn't i try that already
i don't have like an evidence that's not that's not a tape i can't use it you gotta wait a day he
said wait tomorrow so just go to bed sleep a year okay um i just have a couple more i forgot to
mention i forgot to mention i was speaking with alicia and she mentioned that she needed to talk
to you shoot i forgot do you need me to watch you would i have to watch the shop i know where all
the heavy uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh gosh gosh gosh wait i actually have to sit
here commercial great can i open the register it's gonna be something i can do no this doesn't count
i already did it it doesn't count go in the back wait the secret the secret the secret the secret
secret no no no no no no no no no no interesting okay uh what is it you're sleeping in your crib
uh book you have in front of you has been passed down in our family for generations
it's full of herbology uh so much more i want to tell you but it will have to wait until you're old
enough to understand be sure to our heritage lost you leaving this letter you find it remember my
you're loved as always hey what are you doing that's private
i'm sorry lauren sometimes my curiosity gets the better of me so what it's private
adults sleeping in a crib i shouldn't have read it but as you sleep in your crib no this is like
from like 20 years ago you don't have to worry about me mentioning it to anyone
do you know skyrim ai caught you but i would love the first woman in salem to be accused of being
halt practically this is her book all right got the book got the original book are you saying that
book is over 300 years yeah i know but it's for me according to my mother my by a lot she was
all right original we had an original witch original accused
how she learned right wow that's no okay alicia wasn't in her office i'll just play skyrim
what why thank you for watching over my shop and reading my personal belongings again okay
i'll keep my hands i'll keep my hands to myself next time don't worry i promise
now by the way i'll take a couple of those steaks please if you would mind thank you
oh yeah actually you know i'll take i'll take i'll take another couple of you don't mind
gosh these pastries look delicious thank you yeah that was an autoplay uh youtuber video
okay now what there's still clues in that house i have to wait till tomorrow go to bed
the salem it's not my car you can only sleep at night well i'm just gonna drive back and
forth till tonight i'm home i'm ready for bed can't use that that was worth a shot i didn't know if
it was like a secret key oops wrong door the neighborhood a good night's rest improves it's
too early for bed god damn it okay how do i make it bedtime huh no wait where'd she go
oh who's in here hey are you feeling any better about the case progress story to progress time
we're going to find out who did this may i promise if you say so look thanks for breakfast
i just want to say i know you're trying to help but i said you used to hang out with the the
hathorne house right you said you did you ever see any like ghosts were there ghosts there no
oh do you feel ready to talk about your alibi where were you you don't even have a passport
i don't go anywhere so i wasn't in austria if that's what you're thinking and no i'm talking
about the house the house that burnt down people tell me there's a good reason to suspect you
but isn't it obvious we've got a burn mark covering the entire side of my face and like most of my
arms it must be me i'm sorry that happened to you and i'm sorry if people judge you for your burns
i prefer it to pity would you tell me what happened there was a fire i was in it wait wait hold on a
second it's just that so far the main cause for suspecting you of the hathorne fire seems to be
this previous one i only want to understand oh okay yeah i was nine it was an old shed and i
wasn't supposed to play in it it was kind of a den full of stuff like candles i got stuck inside
you can work out the rest so it was an accident you were just a kid harsh to suspect you now
because of something you didn't mean to happen don't make me talk about it more okay talk to you
is that you all right i gather alibis for the search the house for clues
no i'm sick of the house is it nighttime yet it's nighttime no it's not god damn it who have i not
talked to about their alibi there's one person i haven't spoken to where were you by the way
where are you dear dra dear dra fancy zero it's not funny come on because now i know how much you
care of course i care dear don't laugh that despite your best efforts well anyway information i have
some information for you francis tuttle she's the former owner of what well i thought you were going
to read it all goes back to francis it all leads to here she took over the hathorne house estate in
1992 although i found three different marriage announcements in the salem news she was never
married and never had any biological children the only living heir now is lauren holt she met
francis tuttle and was officially adopted in 2006 the judge said there was a will lauren confirmed
that that exactly but as far as i can tell there is no will nothing was ever filed with the town
just repeat the last word of somewhat important sounding sentences it sounds like you're
comprehending what you're being told confused yeah you think that lauren burned down her own house
sounds bizarre i know it's the most likely scenario it is because a historic property is classified
if it's a ruin versus being an intact that's right intact structure
a ruined property is preserved as is so lauren stayed there now living in a chart out building
that's the way to make somebody that's talking to you about things that they know you don't know for
you to make it sound like you actually know it already so you say it at the same time as them
and then they are just like oh you you know this already but you're just letting me talk
about it thanks for the info all right let's go all right i want something has to happen here
i need to have something happen i can't exit the game but i need to something has to happen
right now no herbs no fucking spices no food no pancakes something give me like a give me
like a weapon to attack a monster with like give me the crowbar and let me hit the monster in the
head you don't feel conflicted so i burn it down as revenge for a three tituba seems as much an
influx have you ever seen the capitol building okay no not what not what herbs do you have
all right i gotta go back to the house the road i have that key but why couldn't i use it on
there before because i was told it was gonna work god and make sure you check out nancy drew
and i'm not gonna look at what the name of the game is because i don't know what it is
the name of this game that came out two days ago the new nancy drew the nancy drew and
the shadow the shadow of salem no nancy drew and the midnight at salem did i get it something like
that the midnight at salem salem midnight salem nancy drew salem at midnight what's it called
nancy drew in the half blood prince nancy drew and the sorcerer's stone nancy drew
nancy drew the philosopher's stone can't use that here how does that make any sense
what are you talking about can't use no fucking way no way how do i open this there's a second
mirror uh it's something to do with this this uh this is not even a mirror though
this is a painting well look at it it's like a jpeg rotate the mirror the walls are still
that's not where i am in the library museum right click to rotate the mirror that's not true
it's the middle room mirror middle room mirror mirror by the front door that's not doing anything
what else is there for me to investigate here the other house i can't do anything here a wooden
decker it's a 15-hour game by the way uh somebody said somebody said investigate investigate uranus
um okay
right side
can't use that here this doesn't work there's nothing here to put this in but it's i should be
able to do this use it on the letters the letter there i can't do it on the letters i can't i can't
do it where do i put the key try the lamp what do you mean try the fucking lamp what about back
upstairs the entire second the entire second floor has burned down the entire second floor
what the fuck what's going on what's happening who's okay so i i don't get it there's probably
another one of those desks at the library get me out of here no get me the fuck out of here
use fast travel there's no fast travel in this game
refund the game uh it's been four hours and 15 minutes that ship is sailed that's not gonna
happen let me in here anything i can use where do we see there was aw somewhere before where was
it what can you tell me about lauren lauren is a piece of work olivia may pretend so you i've
never been in but i've had do you think i don't know maybe if she thought it would help her stay
on the ground she certainly doesn't want anyone else having it even if there are historical and
legal reasons but like i said i don't really know her that well anymore can you tell me about the
accident may was in when she was a kid why do you need to know that how was it important i didn't
think it was but everyone else sees reason to believe may is the one who burned half horn house
so that makes it important i know it started with the arson and she has other convictions
on her juvenile record as well what happened it was an old shed near our home may was about nine
or so it was in it candles a lighter i don't know it caught fire she was charged she was so young
i feel responsible she shouldn't even have been there and i'm the older sister it's not your fault
i'm sorry to just talk i need to open a fucking door so bad before i lose my mind closed off
now the new installation is going to be the big reveal that a new installation the whole time back
here we were sacrificing blood and here it is we're revealing it now that's what's going to be i
know it is the person from sweden are you still here that's the big reveal itself we're working
on that project the person that's from that was from sweden that's what your guess was right
can't use that oh fuck off what's the name of this what's the name of this game what's the name
of the game nancy drew aw key this is like 50 nancy drew probably aw keys nancy drew aw key
what's it called uh salem there you go uh okay hold on gameplay tips remove key from
decoration at right corner of desk now that's the first thing we did in the whole game here
we go open window wait this is just a simple walkthrough walkthrough for nancy drew midnight
in salem amateur detective open window take cover off desk read note zoom in on desk click lamp
remove key from decoration at right corner open desk complete labyrinth puzzle find the doctor
and chase the thief that's the end of the game that's the that's the simple walkthrough uh
that this doesn't exist do you think somebody no one's done an actual walkthrough of the new
nancy drew game it's been like it's been two days what do i still search the house for clues but
fuck how do i do that okay i must have an hathorne house hathorne house clues oh got it okay here it
is this video has been removed hello everybody okay hold on it's an actual playthrough okay let
me see please help me please help me help me i got the jacket okay this person has so many more
things than i do where did they get this where'd they get the where'd they get the lighter
i need a lighter how'd you get in how'd you get in how'd you get in the jacket i need a lighter
where's the lighter hold on and then what did they what did they call dad no that's you need to click
the leaf on the mirror i already did that watch the entire thing to know where the lighter is
i can't know there's a lighter there's a pumpkin hold on the lighter wait i think i know what i
think i know where the lighter is i'm not i'm not even fucking around i'm not even kidding
i think i know what the lighter is lighters in lighter in bed no i know where it is watch this
i know where it is i saw it right here leopard print lighter here better hang on to this
i'm gonna do the lighter okay now go burn the down the house it's already happened
oh a lighter sure i'll take that to the house click funny lady no okay can't use that here
can't use that can't use that here you came you came to me in midwinter and made each day the
brightest like a lion i kicked my new cub something about an ox the month of the spring is
yeah yeah remember our ancestors now i wish for you to choose make this house your home will be
free of this burden and the back side of the letter the will is in the house a letter written in
francis tuttle's own hand jesus christ that scared me deegan i was able to rule out some
you need to come here quickly oh something's happened i'll be right there sorry i was dragging
my eyes across a piece of wood something happened what happened did i i was just here did i do this
how did it come to this oh sorry ned come on let's get inside so i didn't tell you everything
of course you didn't you know it's just it's oh when i started working at the museum i was curious
about our town's history because i think history is the most important of course well i found out
something about my family about your family we changed our name we used to be paris okay samuel
paris and his daughter betty were the first accusers of witches they were directly responsible
for the execution of numerous people oh the head of the aw organ i have a key that helped murder
their ancestors which is why i've never told anybody and now everyone knows why do you think
anyone would do this i don't know maybe it's someone else who wants the half-born house
no one in aw is going to trust me after this and the evidence is gone
what is this it's going to be okay this is nancy drew we'll figure it out the shadows of
salem i'm i'm striking by the irons hot this came out two days ago and i'm yeah i mean i
i have a lot of streamers i'm gonna play this i wanted to make sure i was here first
what do you know about this what do you know about this what do you think about this
would you like pancake would you like a pancake okay no frank hey guys can you give me an update
what are we doing out here who's calling what can you give me an update i'm calling me
i have missed talking to you different perspective gameplay complaining about rationality is
inherently irrational we're at the hardy boys pov now everything okay not really i'm at the
parry house someone vandalized it with graffiti really turns out the parries are descendants of
the paris family a family who was responsible for sending some of the accused witches to their
death wow doesn't she run that justice group exactly so looks like nope nothing here we've
not found anything i get it listen things are a little tense here so i'm going to stay with tegan
can you update me if you find anything please what are we doing on here no problem partner
western joke i mean we haven't really discussed the whole detective partnership thing yet so
frank not a good time right if you're done being awkward i could use your help
what who's it all right but who's in joe's phone whatever you say partner let's finish our search
sure sure sure but don't rush we're here to prove the existence of ghosts okay who's in
my phone steady equipment should i call my dad how are we doing on that all set i'll use the
antenna to search for suspicious cold spots while you move around with the ghost wavelength spectral
analyzer 2.5 and look for disturbances from the other side the spectral analyzer anyway are you
sure it actually works of course i built it myself the device has a top of the line scanner that can
detect any disturbances it might not have found anything yet but you have to stay optimistic
about these things and i guess this is $800 paperweight thoroughly researched this shit's
picking up the power lines bro all right let's hunt for ghosts let's hunt for the blood on the
ground that i have to mop up wait 15 what's that mean 15 ghost oh frank frank frank frank frank
got something all right 95 has some traffic on it hey just ghost traffic
and i think about it i what i can't believe it though yeah there's the democrats and the republicans
it goes to ghosts i'm talking politics this is so painful to control this
i feel like it's this one how do i oh give me a break what what does this do
do what what is one one is was two why are there two different settings why are there two settings
they both do worst amazon order this is this is something that you get from like the sharper
image catalog oh wait i got it it's right here found a new cold spot you should move over there
on it we're just we're larping that's what this is we're just bored out of our fucking minds
and i love it's right man alt f4 this is a cooking minigame no it's not not quite a scanner but it
shows no real signs here well it's cooking my brain other signals cooking with 5g i can't wait
until the scooby-doo moment happens when we're just out here pretending and just doing live
action role play and then a real ghost shows up on the screen and it starts going crazy and i go
it's a ghost just wait come on frank stop pulling my leg frank where did he go
where's he off to
he's gonna look up at his friend and his eyes are gonna be bloodshot
i'm gonna put them both at zero because i don't understand like what the fuck is he even doing
zero okay this is zero this increases i wish i could use like the arrow keys because clicking
and dragging this around hurts my brain oh my god unbearable i'm about to alter for
click hold drag up and to the right oh no you went too far look at what my mouse is right now
i want you to watch this i'm gonna let go ready you understand how stupid this is
i should have even asked that question oh no no no oh my god joe there is no setting to on amateur
what's this what is it what is it is it a ghost it's a garage door opener well it seems like some
sort of machine but what's a device like this doing in a graveyard i don't know go put both
your eyes up to it and press it against and press the button on how where does that put your
equipment down your plan didn't work now we're tracking this so-called ghost my way let's see
what else we can find but i just finished setting everything up fine fine my eyes are peeled
how creepy putting a motion detector in a graveyard a new addition and fully functional
it picks up movement of cemetery visitors it's a smoke detector how creepy putting a motion
detector in a graveyard i knew it all right what do you want me to do frank he's like oh we we're
not done what do you mean what are you talking about look for a bakery look for fakery clues in
is a fakery a bakery where they just sell you plastic food what is a fakery should we really
be doing this i'm already having second thoughts of course we should worry wart what is nancy gonna
think if we return empty-handed because you chickened out that's not not scared joe we are
doing this onwards it's just the less effective venture brothers check out the spooky jack-o-lantern
innocent halloween prank or sinister scare in the dark it can easily be mistaken for something
supernatural can use the camera you don't have a camera on your phone oh my wow not even a camera
here it comes i don't know about this we shouldn't trespass onto someone else's property i don't know
about this i don't know about i don't know so what do you want me to do then yes i know i just did
like the spongebob leans over i said the same thing but with distorted text i know i just did that
this was used to make something move to or from the branches that's correct cool um is joe still
watching from in the shower i don't know maybe i've walked in on my son or daughter playing this game
i'd say no no no no close that close that close that here here here's like two or three red and
stimpy dvds check out this watch these quick in the dark dog food there's a strange power
judging by the remnants here's a nintendo 64 take it be something spiritual could be something bigger
there's let's see what else we uh mario 64 ocarina of time play them play them and then say like dad
get the fuck out of my room and i'll be like
no you get out of my room and i'll start crying and i'll leave the room and then i'm gonna fucking
plug in the n64 and just in my own room i'm gonna be playing it by myself just just crying just
fucking dancing through ruining this family guys what do i do somebody tell me quit the game i
can't i can't do it there's a hole in a tree where's the hole in the tree smash on rock what
don't tell him what the fuck really it's a fog machine affordable but effective fog machine
should be able to cover this whole part of the forest in a layer of mist whatever happened to
good old natural hauntings there's nothing natural about our findings here this reeks of foul play
motion detector fog machine pumpkin head the house not burned down incense well you're finally
going to admit you were wrong of course not all we've proven is that there are no ghosts here
so you still think ghosts exist behind you they don't not exist say that again look the absence of
proof does not mean that we can disprove their existence but what it does tell me is that what
nancy saw was not a real ghost so who has something to gain by setting up a fake haunting
olivia olivia that's right there's got to be some evidence linking her to it let's go
about this magic is just aswd i mean clearly i'm moving around in the i'm clearly in a 3d space
right now what on earth would you i can move around in 3d space what on earth would i need to
do mist controls for and then you hold alt to have the mouse on the screen we've got what hey
before we do this shouldn't we call nancy what why because we're a team we should check in with her
let nancy do her thing and we'll do ours he just teleported he teleported is our thing exactly
ghost busting and then we just there's a trash in the place hey look a list of mysterious symbols
okay h o okay then this is h o is that one this is a code to decipher we have our secret do you do
not have your secret decoder ring path to abigail hathorne woodley there's a gravestone map on the
back if this isn't suspicious i don't see abigail hathorne woodley's grave on here though
would have been too easy no matter we'll find her okay so you're this one what else you got
follow the map follow the map
fucking remix on you all right path to abigail hathorne woodley dorothy cromwell
alexander bell so you're this way from alexander bell let's find or just i just tried to wa
have to ride was very upset about it all right let's find that grave who's this alexander bell
okay look um so you are exactly straight diagonal this way you're over there go nope there's dorothy
cromwell you're right next to dorothy cromwell what are we gonna dig i don't understand what are
we doing it's that one over here is that a box underneath the gravestone wait i've got this
picking it up this is good evidence aren't you glad we broke into the museum
but look at this i'm going to go ahead and guess that this will decipher the
you glad we broke into the museum all right here we go device of some sort
time to put you to good use okay so hmm i like to solve what is i don't know donald duck
b h o is okay so it's one two crossed out h o h o uh where's h what the hell are these letters
to jk is this l u v these aren't even these aren't this pie on here q upside down q t u
middle q x w w trident w regular w y z a b y s5 three backwards three this is not real stuff
all right so h o is there anything even looks like an h all right what about t is there a t
there's a t right here t is not that it's got to be this shit with the the toothbrush where's the
toothbrush is that the toothbrush no it's this way t on toothbrush t on do the first block h o t
t i can't move the first block the h on the inside circle needs to be lined up with the o on the
second circle and then put it on where is it this one here no it's not that one where is it
who would even make this jesus christ just just use a password manager it's the double it's the
two lines where is it is it even on here this one right here like that right whoa what select
letters what's going on rotate what are you talking about rotate cipher h o t now the
letters are lined up with the symbols solve how do i solve the puzzle i can't like do anything
nothing i can't click anything start the message part after the h o t okay h o t and then the
this symbol ain't even here have i never used a cipher wheel before why would i ever have ever
used a cipher wheel in my life dude what we never used a cipher wheel before yeah i got i got one
back here where is this double pronged one there ain't even a double pronged one two two what the
fuck are you talking about that's not look at the space there that's one two three four that's not
one two space one two look at that great these are exactly the same all right and then this one
are are uh all right where's this next one it's stupid okay president evil three free master
is coming in july 2021 i can do better than this restock wands and then let's get uh nothing
and t on the second line and then he got the t then uh right facing toothbrush done groceries
you know it's actually this is going faster than if i actually looked and then clicked
grocery shopping this is just a like a to-do list yeah okay cool now this one is uh line up a you
and the other facing toothbrush you and other facing toothbrush you got it okay select the
letters let's go this kind of hurts my head office what is that word seven kiss bic seven
kiss biky bk seven dollars for a king-size burger king what for a big seven seven dollars for a big
kid's quarter pounder meal i fucked it up how do i delete this how do i go back oh no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no a decryption device of some sort it's still just as hard on
amateur it's supposed to be on amateur mode is it different a decryption device h.o.t. time to put
okay i have to i have to see this through you know these games used to come in captain crunch
fucking cereal boxes did you guys know that you used you paid four fucking dollars for the
captain crunch buck for the captain crunch box of cereal and you got to eat the cereal too
and that's something how is it what's what's this is wrong isn't it h.o.t. no no no no that's the
oh that's the symbol oh a decryption device is this still fucking wrong h.o. it's this one
you motherfucker oh you motherfucker a decryption device molding at kids game
yeah and if you yeah yeah if you walked in on a kid playing this you probably would be going bald
all right let's go let's go let's go it's just nothing why this doesn't make any sense nothing
nothing and then t comb facing right that's the one right that's the one right there
t comb is that is that not correct is it this one it's this one oh i just i know what this is
groceries just look to see groceries with c groceries grocery shopping groceries shopping h.o.
pp ing grocery shopping okay now this next one i got it wrong last time this one is the other way
it's just you and then it's left facing three prongs that's four prongs
left facing three prongs are we correct here yes we are it's not four prongs it's three
all right facing three prongs right i need to triple that's four all right let's go
inventory
inventory inventory
buzz use inventory just do it inventory just do it this last one is one prong to the right and
the oh with the hat on one to the right where is it it's one to the left one to the right
there it is no there it is nothing else right just oh oh and then the the that's it car car cat
cat cat what cat food cat mate cat maintenance who calls it cat maintenance it's not a car
okay this last one is b and then comb to the left which one of these is the actual b it's this one
comb to the left how many prongs five right there b come to the left five prongs to the left
let's go get get stove stove cleaner get store get stock get stock what the fuck is going on
get stock friends friend get stock bro cracked it look here cool let me see
it's dated tonight get stock from l lauren holt whoa well boys it's oh it seems you figured it out
what's the rush abigail what are you talking about it's not here
oh we're not gonna just say what are you doing in the graveyard this tastes really good
a little late for high t but it's good quality this is not much of a connoisseur
i'm sorry i don't mean to be rude it's just a bit strong
she gets it from all over the world although i usually use the mail order service she is not
my biggest fan today was an exception you're dodging our questions imagine just programming
in a sneeze okay look i may have helped stimulate everyone's imaginations a little
you know it's good for business what i did isn't illegal maybe but it seems like you're doing it
to keep people away from what are you trying to hide me nothing joe what's wrong
blood's pouring down from his eyes we wouldn't make an accusation like what did you do to us
this do you need she's guilty okay wait a minute
i'll admit a little theatrical and the life actually
no you can't have it both ways joe don't say that i heard something here is it me
who is it who's there where there right there i don't see that it's like you guys trying to
tell me something i can't see on the stream a ghost well i don't see it where is it there over
there is nothing there right there you idiot serious you're serious okay can you look at that
what is that supposed to mean you never believed now there's proof oh please olivia you never
believed in ghosts it did you find any oh what get no one gets scared or hurt in a museum
hey she's in her room olivia it looked real that's all i needed good let's get the condensed
version did you track down any new leads for the arsonist okay i'll go first so far
oh shit so far the evidence seems to be indicating that we should focus on may that we should focus
on lauren that someone is lying about their alibi well that's obvious someone is lying about their
alibi didn't you interview everyone everyone except for may but i don't think she did it
nancy if you're missing an alibi wouldn't you think that that person has something to hide
may is protecting something i think it was two people i need to figure out what i think it was
may and you well don't stop there go on i don't know yet you can stay here she said she might be
late you're now playing as nancy drew nice plan nancy hey hi it's just i already made it
so what time did you get home last night i'd like to just eat my breakfast without being interrogated
is that okay with everyone is it i've already answered a litany of questions from these two
you want to ask them i'm sure they'd love to tell you okay ow what's wrong with you
my hands feel like pins and needles i think i slept on them or yeah me too same what so is
anyone going to tell me what happened yesterday uh they saw it well they saw it it an anomalistic
paranormal projection you mean a goat that's exactly what i mean okay olivia raven olivia
saw it except she claims to have seen judge john hathorne not abigail hathorne woodley i'm gonna
be so upset if this is actually something different than all of you flashlight on his face and that's
the explanation with some fog machines i don't think so dear dra it's not an act she was genuinely
scared ergo no sorry not ergo er gut your hands erget poisoning you really think it's possible
mass psychogenic illness by more than one person hallucination leggo by echo restriction in the
hands and feet pins and needles exactly wait what what is that yeah but half food or drink
has been being poisoned this whole time i'd believe it what are you guys talking about
we could have been poisoned with erget poisoned what the symptoms match and it's not without
precedent especially here it says it here in this book it can actually come from the accusers of
the salem witch trials were exhibiting strange the culmination of the burnt sugars witchcraft
in burned pancakes eaten rye infected by erget spores and not washing your hands after making
food it was also pretty common 300 years ago i had an asahi super muscle builder smoothie for
lunch yesterday i did not eat some sort of pilgrim era right it's not urgot it's how could i get
it's like hepatitis a but i'd like to see if there are any sorry to burst everybody's bubble
here good idea but all the food we've been eating is my doing it's not so mysterious poisoning
you have e coli i touched raw hamburger meat before i made all your pancakes i visited the
hathorn house and i found olivia's jacket in plain view seems too obvious it is olivia has
been involved with some scare pranks in town mostly turning up business for her tour but we
don't think she's a suspect be fair they didn't eat anything you've made she was working working
as was everyone else and that was a will deaf okay no it was written by tuttle a letter written
could have been burned in the fire could be the reason for the fire that's true none of this
helps may that's right we need a perp a perp we should still try to find it it might be motive
i'll start with the judge i should finally be able to get the cctv access we'll figure it out but i
don't even know what an ergot spore looks we'll figure it out deer drove no oh time is running
if we don't clear may's name soon i hate to think what this town will do to
i had to copy that
fucking i hate this game
huh did you seriously cook this for me a friend who likes cat oh now please stop looking at me
like that before i barf all right new friend let's go talk to the judge we're almost at the end of
the game this guy's just still standing out here on his car ladies ladies ladies boy boy boy so
you seem to hang out a lot here well yeah it's a good vantage point of the whole town yeah oh look
i can see the courthouse from right here can you see it nancy i can yeah you can see a lot of
buildings from the square so did you see anyone on the day the aw evidence was no what helping her
run errands what errand dry cleaning uh look just ask her we will ask her jake you know may you know
may perry what may yeah why because she's going to be arrested for these crimes by the end of the
day what are you talking about that's ridiculous there's wait you know may like know her yeah do
you talk to her we know she doesn't have anything to do with these crimes but everyone thinks she
does well that's too bad good conversation i'm trying to condense it a little bit to speed things
up what they're skipping through the halls this time i've just realized that this case has taken
a turn about what i can hear the protesters how do you figure intentional poisoning usually has one
to eliminate the target someone was trying to kill us ergot poisoning at high enough doses ends
and gangrene which yeah it's pretty bad but it's not death you really think this was intentional
and not some you know accidental ingestion if you look at all the evidence yes
olivia's jack at the crime scene spray painting at the perry house everyone's obsession to get
me convicted what all these people have in common what they're women are you saying they're all
witches or that this is a witch hunt i'm saying it's salem where are the protesters where's my
favorite character case solved it's salem yeah okay let's talk to the judge uh oh is the judge
has the lawyer present can i help you miss true i'm here for the cctv footage yes yes yes
you can use this on the evidence room computer you know where that is right yeah i found the
pin code here remember of course you did run along run along the usb stick you know i just
realized i never followed up with you two about what you were doing on the day the aw evidence
was stolen you know nancy this detective thing is really sweet and all but we are in the middle
of something important here okay what what are you doing what is it what are you initiating the
process of handing over a half thorn house to the state so it can be turned into a museum
what it's our only option but you work for lauren it's her home and i'm getting her an extra 90
days before she's evicted which is 90 more than she would have had without me so we're a little
busy right now because we need to file this by the end of the day and may perry what about may
perry is she being charged i won't discuss this it's an active criminal investigation
but from what i've heard an arrest will happen later today so please come on dear dra
can't use that okay distract me drew so i don't go back in there and smash things
with i that's tell me what do you want to tell me some inane detail from your life so i feel
better when were you come off badly i know tell me what ned said when you told him you saw a ghost
oh shoot i totally you forgot you didn't call your boyfriend back a boyfriend drew all right
yes i know there's another girl there's a mystery girl oh come on shut up no you shut up maybe
you're dumb how dare you that actually sounds like i know i hate you oh that's dad
it's been three days only daughter uh at two you okay how's the case coming along not well
i have a bunch of alibis but i'm missing something then there's the book of apologies
that's been stolen and the arson and a break-in at the courthouse and the judge called me an idiot
slow down what no excuse me what happened there what happened honey who's on your judge danforth
judge danforth okay look he's coming on strong trying to pin the crime on a girl without any
evidence it's a bit strange unbecoming he's supposed to be impartial but he's really going
after this one teenage girl may well look he was like a mentor to me in college we've kept in touch
but i do not know all the details of his situation
is he in financial trouble no could you make that happen to get a piece of property
i don't know which would be ironic because that's exactly what judge hathorne did in 1692
but may isn't involved at least from what i can see that's compromised ownership of the house
could be about the people may is related to go after her as means to hurt the ones she loves
it's extremely unsettling for a judge to do that but it has happened before
uh this is where we're supposed to piece it all down i'll talk to you later
i want to go watch this tape well i'm to us i'm hoping the cctv footage will prove it
bad news the footage isn't sorted we need to put it together in a timeline oh no hello i'm cammy
i can see that you're trying to find a suspect select cameras from the video source list add
footage to the timeline one image per numbered step all of your added images need to have a view
of the suspect good luck okay so he came into his office he scratched his head at the window
he went over to the corner sat in the chair is that different person they fall asleep at his desk
who's this who's that all right this is the break-in here's a break-in all right there's the judge
comes in he goes into the cabinet he goes over to the computer he leaves somebody was hiding in one
of the evidence drawers okay is outside gets into a car right there the courthouse i don't see
anything do you guys see anything why is there cameras in the bathrooms these cameras in the
bathrooms that doesn't seem creepy that makes no sense nothing in the ladies room the hallway
there he is did he show up again okay what do we got delete that we have the men's room the hallway
the evidence room evidence room again the entrance to this room outside getting into the car
okay we good what about in the courtroom back left corner i don't see anything hallway was
there one in the hallway too right there at oh at six at 006 i don't see anything you need one for
every time we have men's room hallway evidence room evidence room again second time in the hallway
entrance outside do i have here no i don't all of your added images need to have a view of the
suspect nobody else in the window right no all right all right cammy i got you so how do i do
this now need 14 and 15 yeah but that i think that's just the start at zero i'll look at every
camera you're missing one through five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
okay so where is he is any where is he nothing in the outside you courthouse i don't think to
men's room ladies room hallway missing five to eighteen wait what are you talking about
you changed his clothes in the bathroom is it this person here is jason oh my god yep
how am i supposed to this people just walking around what about like this person
this is like people that work here like who's that all right we need what do we have six he
went into the bathroom and okay we have him going to the bathroom so at six he comes out of the
bathroom so before the bathroom no got him we need two all right he's in the entrance
the evidence room no outside the courtroom the men's room the ladies room the hallway got you
again got you again motherfucker let's go to three three you're in the men's room is that him
in the corner okay four but there's nothing on four because he's in the stall he's changing it
four so what what do i have what do i have to have for a second number four you can see him
we can't in the mirror yeah that's five so i just do four and five all here then six to fifteen
okay so then he goes men's room into the hallway into the evidence room then he smashes the door
from the inside and then uh-oh wait no that's true that's him in the hallway that's him about
to leave that's him leaving and that's him getting in the car and then finally leaving
yes i did it see it's a shame we can't make out the perps face
perp what isn't that what you call them suspect dear dra this isn't a crime show well i kind of
like using it maybe that's my calling card and yours is well whatever it is that you do
thanks for what i think it's down good okay this car looks like our best lead
women hmm i swear i saw one just like this parked outside the courthouse
hacked interview ghost witness hey uh i don't need your help or anything i just wanted to call
and let you know that i'm gonna win the million dollars did you hear that i can't believe it
he actually called his father to tell him that he won the million dollars
how do i leave oh right nice vest found it i found okay so go do something about it what
are you doing what am i supposed to do ladies so whose car is that parked in front of the
courthouse whose car is that that's alicia cole's car oh yeah i washed it last week and the week
before that and the week before that and the week yeah okay we get it see you later
alicia alicia alicia alicia alicia alicia alicia alicia no that's not where oh you're still
playing this yeah it is gripping quick go through alicia's desk bingo a demolition offer for the
hathorne house why in the world would alicia have this she's a criminal demolition 4500
dollars cleanup 1500 equipment set 500 administrative fees 500 total 8500 dollars
darren craig and alicia cole got you this looks like some kind of map the requested section of
the salem water works marked an access point found okay we marked an access point as per your
request would you look at that property law find a salem map to compare i know where that is
a map right mouse button to rotate here if i align the waterworks map properly
i should be able to figure out which area it represents okay okay all right so ah got it
i need to know what's at that mark crunchy i need to know what's there interview ghost witnesses
stop eating your bags of chips so loud the ghost could be a witness
yeah ba-da-ba-doo we know the truth parry paris parry equals paris confess snitch liars we know the
truth paris denounced where is everybody a good night's rest where's everybody they're all poisoned
poop in the kitchen sink uh no i don't interview the what do you mean interview where's olivia
no one said that yes they did how are you i didn't sleep at all bang right yeah
we think we were poisoned we think we were poisoned ergot really what's that
it's a fungus a fungus what did you eat yesterday what did you eat yesterday eat
oh yeah taco bell just humorous well i can't that's not even true i've talked about this
i've talked about this shit remember this conversation chickpeas raisins with thousand
witches dressing not very fungal no i talked about how haha i had i had diarrhea and i i don't know
what i ate oh taco bell gives diarrhea taco bell makes you poop your pants but that doesn't happen
i don't know why is that such a thing why people say that that doesn't happen everybody just says
that i don't know why i just said it because it's been burned in my brain that it hey that's funny
to say taco bell makes you have
loose stools anything to drink yesterday coffee at breakfast fair trade obviously
smoothie at kill me crazy and smoothie what kind of tea it was a matcha from where well i like it
where's the water from excuse me the water something in the water it was just normal
faucet water some people filter i don't have the time besides lauren has the best matcha you can't
tell it's unfiltered who's faucet lauren's i went to try to talk to her about the ghosts she made
me tea it was better than the conversation i took my tea to go and then ended up sharing it with
the hardy brothers i ran into them boys yeah them in the cemetery joe wanted to try my tea
so you all drank the tea yeah was it the tea or was it the toilet water talk to you later
hey i'm gonna do the rounds call everybody you went out with last night
hey frank uh yeah it's jeremy yeah it was fun last night yeah yeah how you doing doing good
yeah i'm doing fine you're doing fine yeah um how the kids did your kids get put to bed and
everything yeah yeah they're good frank did you have diarrhea last night yeah i did okay just
trying to figure out how if ever anyone else had problems because we both we shared the the cheese
plate you and i yeah we did yeah all right um that will problem solved i'm gonna make another couple
phone calls and just see and just need everyone to tell me that they also have diarrhea so i know
that i don't have like a real serious medical problem goodbye frank i can't come to the phone
right now but leave me a message and i'll get back to you take care do i want to get tested
because we shared a cheese plate
hey frank did you have diarrhea last night yeah i did oh well damn yeah you should probably get
tested tested for what i don't know i don't know but i'm sure they'll find something
oh
if you're hearing this that means i can't come to the phone right now sorry
doctor i've got your test results here jeremy and yeah you just you tested positive for taco bell
oh fuck yeah so yeah you're gonna have diarrhea for at least two weeks get plenty of bed rest
all right let's get the fuck out of this how long do i have how long do i have doc well uh see you're
you're fairly healthy otherwise what are you 33 uh you got about another 40 to 50 years at least
okay yeah go get some rest drink some gatorade are they still just standing out here no it's
boyfriend net so glad to hear your voice you have no idea what if it was just really
yes it could be why wouldn't i be well you know we haven't really been talking much lately i know
i know i know it's just it's just that you're busy with your life and i've been busy with mine and
ned i've missed you so much yeah me too can we go on vacation just you and me together for once
uh guys being getting tested positive for taco bell it's just you have high cholesterol
i'd love to i'm there but no that's what that is we'll think of something fun to do
deirdre had an interesting idea i wanted to run by you you spoke to deirdre and about me
i know this is the craziest case i can't wait to tell you all about it you know it's probably
actually really glad that you picked up your conversation with you hey hey what is everything
okay i don't know may seem distant this morning i don't know what to do we'll figure it out i'm
sure this is tougher yeah i was thinking maybe there was something i should do trying to do
anything rash we'll get to the bottom of this yeah thanks this is taking it's okay you guys
had diarrhea let's backtrack what did you guys eat and drink around the time we had tea
yeah we were looking for olivia ravencroft and found her she had tea it was matcha surprisingly
good imagine being out in a graveyard in the middle of the night in the middle of cemetery
that's right and a random lady comes up to you and offers you tea to drink you were barely able
to get your drink down boys focus where exactly that's when you start to run she had just bought
it from lauren holt what about the water for the tea no idea i ask you to keep digging literally
you know we're not boys it's just part of our name whatever you say i read this read it says
the greek god whatever well the roman god what was it greek i've been testing the soil from various
sites around the cemetery so far nothing we'll keep looking but i don't think the source of
the poison is here don't worry about him he's just agitated with all the looks he's been getting
digging in a cemetery looks very suspicious okay bye thanks for confirming diarrhea anything else
okay now we have to go and confirm the person who gave us all diarrhea the source of the diarrhea
is in here uh lauren quick question do you wash the vegetables that you bring into the store
before you use them no okay how's business slow thankfully i felt awful just a couple of questions
for it and we'll get out of here well have you ever had taco bell we know what you're doing
i'm sorry you're not fooling us this whole new age act modern apothecary dear dra this isn't the
best way your family has been here a long you're related to tituba correct yes aha i knew it
tituba is kind of famous around here she was the first accused was so bored from the caribbean
elizabeth paris's father who else knows this no way i don't know but it's not like it comes up in
normal everyday conversation so i've never brought it up i'm not part of that accused
witches organization if that's what you're angling at so you don't get along with teagan we used to
be friends okay and i don't know why you think this is some sort of amazing revelation play
something else teagan works at the music this is we're almost at the end we are right great great
great grandmother was tituba and she knows that tituba was ick are you seriously accusing me of
setting my own house on fire because you don't want i don't care at all about teagan or her
organization this shop is how i remember my ancestors are you accusing me of burning my
house down what do you know about ergot what do you know about ergot why do you ask why are you
being so suspicious why are you being such a enough please we're asking because we believe
the ghost sightings might be related to ergot poisoning claviceps herbaria what i had a break
in a few weeks ago you have any security camera footage which wasn't much but the funny thing is
they also took my ergot it's very convenient of course it treats migraines and cluster headaches
it makes you see ghosts and gives you diarrhea and makes you pass out and you can also marry
people with it every medicine is toxic and high enough dosage why do you ask we think that the
ghost sightings are related to ergot poisoning i don't know do you mind if i ask what you ate
yesterday i do mind that's kind of personal give me it's okay just tell us did you eat any
cereal type stuff like rye bread i'm gluten-free oh good so no grain what is all this shit not to
my knowledge anything to drink salem's finest tap water just like everyone else you were you were
gonna bakery you make what is it made out of what is that that's like a pound cake this is like
cheesecake and pound cake and stuff she doesn't eat it she just makes it cider donuts three herb
bread how do you know your bread tastes good they're poisoning the water supply you have
make this bread but you don't eat it how do you even know it's yeah that's gluten-free
give me a break i don't think so we found a demolition notice in alicia cole's office
demolition yeah as in destroying the hathorn house alicia is your lawyer correct yeah so why
would she have this document on her desk i have no idea we never talked about any kind of demolition
you sure you're not looking to build your dream home it's a great location no i am not looking
to build my dream home what kind of oh no all right what's it what was it what is it called
ergo okay let's go find source of oh oh oh oh i know where to go excuse me get out of my face
herbal tea i don't like her stop i know where it is the paris family history there's a way to go
about doing things dear your dude you probably did this did you hear about the graffiti on the
perry house well sure but that was so long ago it was even cares about that yesterday are you
kidding me teagan had the audacity to found the accused witches trying to profit off the witch
trials her own family started give me a break there's like not even two days ago from the tree
when you put it that way i'm glad the neighborhood watch delivers justice to those who deserve it
feels good to have crooks exposed for what are you sure it was them that's where i'd place my bets
did you hear about the graffiti well sure are you kidding i'm glad ages ago no they're talking
about the graffiti on the house not the witch trials that happened like six thousand years ago
we have to go to the water supply this is it a wooden decoration this is it it's this house
what can you go around the house uh no i can't is it actually in the other house
find source the poisoning get the crowbar wait wait that's ergo right there that's ergo right
there look look at this yeah move out of the way look at this green shit that's ergo right there
move out of the way look green paint there's green paint all over that door i still don't get
this i still don't understand what the fuck i'm supposed to do about this all right did you get
out of my life find a source of the poisoning ah where is it i can't go around the house either
is it like a well this is as far as i can go i can't go further than this this got it someone
has been here recently it's rusted shut
what the fuck just happened that's strange okay i got ergo that's i think this is i think that's
ergo what are you doing we found this in your water supply it's you you're trying to poison
no you're trying you're trying to poison us we found this ergot in your water supply
using blueprints we found in alicia cole's office alicia alicia has been poisoning you lauren
but why we don't know but we're going to find out run all your faucets shower anything with
a spigot for 20 minutes 20 minutes i'm moving the ergot in your supply no i'm getting my whole
house replaced i think i'm just gonna stick to the bottled water that works too
go run your water for 20 minutes teagan hey i'm with your dress she's gone what may she's gone
okay just hold on we'll be there soon we weren't fast enough let's go house burned down
are you still just in that house what are you what she didn't leave a note
no text i came home for lunch from the museum and she was gone gone uh you have an idea where she
have any idea why she would leave juvenile record they published it raining i could have sworn we
had it expunged but someone found it the newspaper highlighted an arson incident what a rag yeah and
now she's gone missing so when they find her they'll really try to put her away may never gave an
alibi because she was protecting someone they both have they both have they both have lego hair
that might be jason i know what it's like wait really yeah may doesn't really seem to be jason's
type before she disappeared i admit i read through her phone she left it in the living room and why
would she do that they used to be friends when they were younger but grew apart i guess they
still kept in touch jason said he was in trouble for something but he never said what she knew
look look tegan i hate to say this it's not true because i was the one who set hathorne house on
fire what it was an accident wait what i was looking for the will the frances's will i looked
everywhere and i couldn't find it so i just started tearing the place apart and i was in
the storage room and there were some paint cans and i knocked over the candle i was using and it just
ignited like whoosh burst into flames why didn't may say something do you want the paint on fire
i'm so sorry dear dra i'm sorry to both of you i don't know what i was thinking bringing you into
this why do you have a candle was going to happen we need to find may please please find her if we
find her if you find her i will turn myself in you should do that anyway i can't believe this
well i have it all recorded on my fucking my like face body can i'm having may take the fall for
this really after everything she's i know i'm sorry i i was hoping it would all just fix itself
blow over they have nothing on her so they can't blame her for it right i thought we could both
just get away from it but she wouldn't give an alibi i don't understand why and i didn't want
to risk my work for aw call the police how did it come to this oh boy this is messy dear dra we
need to go is there any info you can give us on where she might be i know she has secret hiding
places around town but i don't know where they are if you go to a certain part of the map we
just start spam clicking in random places maybe you'll be able to find it what did that say the
storm got worse really as if we need more rain right now we're going wherever may is rain or
not this isn't going to stop us right right hey what's going on long you were just walking to
people's houses set fire to the hathorne house and may is missing what i need you and joe to
just stay with her and make sure she doesn't go anywhere our first arrest private detectives
can't arrest people citizens arrest wait you're going out looking for her the storm is getting
bad nance you want to go arrest i need to set these wrongs right be careful when am i not
hey wait for me nah i've had enough of this what us we don't work well together we just saw the
case is wrong what are you talking about what are you talking about we just solved the crime i called
you because i needed you to connect with may to prevent this from happening i couldn't what the
fuck are you doing she was avoiding me the one thing you've been following me around you you
couldn't deliver dear dra that's not fair you know what it's fine if we split up we have a better
chance of finding her agreed well i guess so just close the door in my face find clues about may's
disappearance can't use that here there are some more things i'd like to look into before
we're gonna go into her room oh i probably shouldn't be in may's room without an invitation
can't use that can't use that hold on wait i'm supposed to find out we're supposed to find out
why she left and where she is but keep out no parents no adults is still in play i probably
what if she what if she's just in there nobody can go in there what if she's just in there reading
a book what's this may forgot her phone are you fucking kidding me you'd rather go through her
phone than open her door to her room to see if there's anything in there but this is this is
okay hey what's up gonna head out to the house wait seriously wait it burned exactly you want to come
hello uh no you know i don't go there uh right thought you'd be over it by now the house is
barely standing sorry just think you'd get over it if you came with once it's a cool place think
about it hey you okay i saw the papers what do you think you want to meet up i'm going into hiding
meet me there in this weather hey hey you there i'm coming over meet me outside okay and head out to
so you're just in the house isn't that the easiest place the kitchen what did you just add
oh all right holy shit freddy you shouldn't be out in the rain it'll ruin your makeup
freddy what are you doing out here jason i should ask you the same thing freddy i'm looking for may
perry she's gone missing freddy just gave 25 000 bits let's talk in the car 25k they say love you
germa thanks for making this year funny for me i've been friends for years you never mentioned
her since when do i have so much ready that's a fucking crazy amount of money you know she's
missing she's not missing she told me she was hiding where i think it's about time you that's
a lot of fucking money true hold on hold on i'm trying to get a print screen of somebody that's
driving by no fuck come on all right get up i have to go you're going to kick me out in the rain
wait but it's my pleasure for making the year funny for you thanks for the insane
contribution and thank you for watching at all money aside what the fuck is going on now
that was a phylacter lich just matched freddy dreads 25 000 bit drop with a 25 000 bit drop
holy crap hey germa the mcdonald's gift card should be there soon have a great time
thank thank thank you so much by laughtery and freddy both you back to back that's 500
fucking dollars in like two minutes and then chunky baloney with 10 community subs
you gotta be kidding me oh my god no no bit and sub fights abe abe just came in
abe had a big contribution earlier but 50 community subs and 10 from chunky baloney
50 community subs five from nearshut oh no no no no jatooty 10 community subs
sometimes it's just just the water pressure just you you it just goes but abe that's that's
fucking a shitload of money with 50 community subs and that's 20 from mgs fan
10 or more from jatooty do booty five more from producers sand it's being rained on oh my fucking
god visual warlock 10 i'm cauliflower 10 gray blob 5400 bits what the fuck are you guys doing
i'm not even playing the things this nancy drew gray blob 5400 bits i want in on this
uh this is visual world warlock 10 i'm cauliflower 10
thanks for 10 thank you guys all right that that was fucking insane thank you everybody
for the subs i really appreciate it and the huge amount of bits that just exploded right now that
was that was a bit and sub explosion thank you now back to nancy drew that's a shitload of money
thank you guys what does this mean north west north north northeast east east and then right
at the end here produces produces sand thanks again for five more i'll be at the museum today
as usual hey please consider talking to nancy and dear dre they're here to help you don't have to
say much just something i'll talk to you later don't you know i have a phone you know i have the
phone didn't you know that why are you texting me oh this is yesterday okay phylactery gave
oh my fucking lord holy shit another 250 dollars 25 000 bits from phylactery tis the season germa
thanks phylactery that's you're at another insane amount of fucking money
i hope you make a lot of money holy fuck dude thank you nancy drew new money stream i got 35
of these games i'm just gonna play them i bought all the bundles i already told you
all right so here we go let's uh put this down but thank you everybody again
sometimes i don't really know what to say besides that's fucking insane thank you
how do i get out of the car no i don't want to turn around i probably look so stupid right now
hey turn up my hazards i'm sorry i just i don't know how to get out of your car
how the fuck do i get out of here
you okay how's the case coming along dad i'm i'm stuck in a car i want to talk about jason danforth
the judge's son he's a real piece of work i think the judge probably agrees with you
i don't know him personally but i've heard stories he claims that during the time in which the accused
witch's evidence was stolen he was helping alicia cole i guess he does work for her
claimants against the hathorne estate they're trying to take control of the property as
reciprocity for their ancestors having that land and life stolen from them by the original judge
hathorne and that's valid according to the judge yes but back to jason sounds like he's short of
cash constantly but i see him driving a fancy car around town looks like he lives a pretty
comfortable lifestyle to me money is always a prime motivator he could be receiving money from
someone to commit one of these crimes or he could have a financial stake in the property
but if he was tied into the he keeps looking up for it when she starts talking i can only
imagine that it's through his father the judge is he on your list everyone is a suspect until
they aren't you taught me that right okay who else put it on your little list the queen and the
other people all right bye dad thanks how do i look in your car how do i search your car pixel
mike thanks for five more subs five more community subs from pixel mike on top of the fucking
absolute shit load this is yeah this is a nice car oh found it hey look at this it's his 3d
movie ticket for yeah this is the p this is what i needed bingo yo what do you think you're doing
you can get out of my car now man this storm is bad huh this is interesting turns out we were in
austria at the same time huh wtf strange coincidence you didn't happen to visit mosem castle
on your trip you did this wrong nancy okay nancy nancy nancy you gotta go in the house and yes i
was at first and i hang out and just don't bring this up yet grab a candle holder who bought the
tickets what you flew first class you didn't pay for that alicia cole
well okay did you steal all that evidence did you steal the aw evidence too
explain i want my lawyer sure who is your lawyer alicia cole whoa i've done it now she's not going
to help me is she you can get another one what's the point yeah i stole it from my dad's office
it was easy enough the guy doesn't lock his door like ever and then i gave it to alicia i don't
know where it is now oh my dad's gonna kill me so you flew to austria to steal the book of apologies
so you flew to austria i want you to say sorry so you saw me there yep does alicia have the book now
actually no where is it it's somewhere safe i need it to you need to hand it over i don't have it you
need to do it now i don't have it all right am i supposed to believe alicia is behind this you
want proof yes chad nancy versus the virgin chad alicia knows about my financial situation once
she squeezed and never let go that's perfect tell my father jason you committed a crime in
another country how bad could it be i know i know it's bad why would alicia do this no idea
she never told me yeah i i know i screwed up why did that come from the other side of my head once
i thought she was your friend she has the book you need to tell me where she is jason
every minute that goes by with her on the run is bad for her and you in the tunnels underneath
salem go to the little liberty statue and light it up you'll see the way in she's down there thank
you jason thank you everything promise thank you fine may it's not safe down there with the rain
every time it rains a tunnel caves in why don't you show me better hurry up i have to look for my
dad tell him what happened you can do that i'm not i'm not a good person okay i'm scared
i don't want to go down there i'll find her come on dear dra
come on dear dra you've reached the phone of she's not next to me i'm working on an important case
and can't come to the phone right now usually she's right fucking behind me right please leave a
message after the beep shoot yeah you heard from dear dra no well i know where may is
she's underneath salem underneath i'm gonna need your car meet me in the cemetery i need your help
to find her don't follow me okay we'll be right there what do we do about teagan this is more
important she's not going anywhere and frank don't tell her about may i don't want her trying to
come with us this is going to be very dangerous copy that hey we're here what do you need us to do
we could get umbrellas yeah i was gonna say thank you joe i appreciate it i was gonna say that
right there is gonna say thank you joe for saying that thanks guys that's the smart one that should
be the leader that's what makes decisions around here that should be the one that has the uh
didn't really say how bring the light into darkness i think it's a metaphor of course
the light is the truth and the darkness is the night i would think we need truth during business
hours as well i need a source of light did you bring any you didn't bring any flashlights
don't have any we don't have any flashlights yeah we spent all of our money on expensive
ghost detecting electromagnetic equipment we can borrow one yeah i don't own a flashlight
where's my lighter bring light into darkness open way into the tunnels doesn't have your phone
fill the dark with light yes i know hey who is this nancy i don't know who this is
sorry got your number off tegan hey who is it it's olivia oh great please come talk to me
at the shop use your move sorry for bad spelling too much cola you don't like drunk text people
when you drink soda where are you what's up hey nancy olivia i'm done with tea gave it up now i'm
just straight cola all the sugar all the caffeine i am wired up like a 10 000 volt power line but i
have not seen one single ghost today that's great olivia hey yes can you do me a favor i found
something and i uh can you give this to tegan for me please we used to be really good friends and
maybe this will i don't know remind her of that can you give it to her i can't do it i'm i need
your help um oh sure sure oh thank you i just want her to know she isn't alone okay give that
to tegan all right thanks for the uh little tip there and olivia i know you're doing drugs just
stop okay just stop not the right path trust me on that but because you are uh what do you got back
there out of curiosity where's tegan the salem take a lamp
plus two then minus two
i can't take the lamp i know it's right in front of me how do we light up dark stuff
i think it'll be a mystery the whole day what are you talking about
um hey olivia can i borrow one of these lamps sure yeah of course guys they're everywhere
those ones are electric where do you get oil here i'm going to give it to the the hardy boys
here you go no you're both worthless apparently why would you like just charge it do i have to
like is it like a pull and push do i have to do that really really fast really hard for a little
while and then it'll be charged like an led where is it it's an oil lamp what do i get oil
i need oil put pancake in it pancake is not fuel there's zero nutritional value in pancakes
it's just it's just a sauce that you heat up that has it's like bread sauce it's not there's
nothing in it oil where is where's t she's probably in the secret passage just light the
lantern please god she's probably sitting on the couch light the lantern god please light the
lantern please god light the lantern please god light the lantern i have to go to work in 10
minutes please oh god please where do i get oil for the lantern i don't know just use it at the
statue oh my god please i have to go to work all right you have to crack the lantern like a glow stick
okay get that here that's a deep dark hole yeah look at this place what hey guys hold on one second
hey i'm at the entrance to the tunnels jason says may is hiding down here and you're really
going down there everybody's in on it yeah look i haven't been fair to you it's okay dear dra
you don't think that aren't in on this no the two like malnutritioned hearty boys that don't
be that teagan lied to me dear dra i understand but i really have to go wait person darsin that
caused me burns there's meat i was literally getting this right now she left and i didn't even
notice teagan was with her friends so i was supposed to watch her i was stupid what the what
i think either of them will ever forgive me you exposed it you didn't check on her once
how were you well i didn't check on her once and now she won't talk to anybody one time
i didn't come home like i'm being in the same room as her and dear dra were you were you under
anesthesia i promise i don't understand it well how did you do that make any sense all right where's
where this passage is a secret passage does everybody see a secret passage i don't see a
secret passage is there something what's wrong with it it's right there come on use our cell
phones as flashlights let's go it's covered with it covered with like twigs and shit we need to
make sure we don't get lost down here one misstep and we might never get out deep breaths we have
directions to follow everything will be fine how what oh okay north are we going this way are we
going this way so we got to go north and then this doesn't seem right what wait what are you
talking about north north how do i turn okay north west this seems right south west north
north are you sure this is the right way oh fuck you you're not helping north west
south west north west north north east north east getting closer east oh should look at
may's directions more closely what the fuck are you talking about wait what hold on wait wait wait
wait where am i getting closer okay eat where am i east eat where am i which east is this this one
wait my ears i'm deaf sorry sorry sorry that one got away from me hey did you hear that what
is it jeez sounds wooden all right coming from that way but the directions go this way
why they're on it bit messages don't work down here and that sounds really angry it could be
here but if we go that way we might not be able to find our way back look we'll follow the signs
okay good luck hey joe if you guys get in trouble just scream i'll be able to hear you
very funny b follow the aw carvings you are now playing as frank hardy
okay just relax shoot out of the fucking way carvings anybody see any aw carvings darn darn
shoot joe yes frank so we're wading through this water yeah and it's in tunnels underground
i know what you're asking i'd rather not think about it oh i don't understand you do it i'll let
you take this who's behind the door you have five seconds to answer me or what you're gonna come in
guns blazing deardra deardra the door is locked thank you i know i locked myself in here accidentally
okay guys you're gonna get in here i'm being it's some sort of lock i'm being crushed that's
i think you'd have a lot more to say than that i'm being crushed to create the key all nine parts
need to be properly assembled the result the resulting icosageron is then inserted into the
lock open the key is modeled after the common convex type with 20 triangular faces five faces
meeting at each point the parts can be hidden or distributed to make sure the door is only
opened when all owners of parties are present even a single part is missing the icosageron
cannot be completed hold on deardra we're coming yeah but how i don't know we gotta find a way
you want to die stop this is gonna be germa please hurry my macbook is heating up
you're gonna be fine hurry i need the instructions
get out of the way corner piece okay this big chunky piece and then
top left is a regular triangle all the right is a regular top right top right and then top
left is regular triangle let's try it hold on deardra yeah but i don't know i can't swap this
and this why don't you both your femurs just broke i need this this is like an
ed but it flips like that i'm coming can this go up okay hold on germa hurry i have five minutes
for my dad gets the what so this is it a does it make us it makes a circle
that's correct so then i need like a let's see what's it look like a little wedge
now one of these down here will that do it
is that no is that it no hold on it's got to be like a flat piece going that way
hurry please operator hurry going
i came to the middle piece hey what's taking so long the balls need to line up
okay um i did not even know that they were indents i thought it was just balls i thought it was just
balls that there are there are indents i thought it was balls okay it gets enough ow it hurt
she's gonna be just mush when i get in there all right so that if that's the case then
that don't work up there we need an indent up here no it's gonna be flipped that do it
that'll do it that'll do it hey what's taking so long ball over here i need an indent right there
i need a ball over here oh would you look at that got it this one don't move that piece
okay yeah now he's kind of gets it he's sick
it's this one hey what's taking so long sure sure now let's get on with it come on
get them all in there is that even possible i mean look at them hey guys i can't take this much
longer what's the hold up ow it hurts it might be alive got it we're coming in grab her grab her
uh-oh what the heck are you doing down here i'm fine thanks for asking are you okay
it's a sacrifice board my leg it's just bruised i think i'll be fine i thought you were dying
well i could have died if you hadn't saved me i would have been trapped down here for days and
starved to death where are we we're in hathorn house i came here to try and find the will
that was a secret entrance the rain is really doing a number on what's left of the place
i managed to get past the stairs but that bookcase can't skip well sorry i'm just glad you two were
here who knew that old furniture is really heavy not for me man strength
yeah right it was all stop worth it you know secret room i bet you this is where abigail was kept
imagine all the bad memories of this place that's not okay look down don't move yeah i'm not moving
it's a puzzle captain obvious reporting for duty these these are i've seen them before
look around frank maybe there's a key or something what's happening i got electrocute
sam hayne arrow watch your step is there a book all right the book of magic spells
i think i found something let me ah it's a riddle probably i can't believe you can actually die
why don't move yeah i'm not moving it's a puzzle captain obvious reporting for duty
these symbols i've seen them before look around frank maybe okay so i gotta read this fucking book
we all know life to have as many faucets as there are stars like water flows and changes with
yeah that's water all right triangle down water triangle up fire anger and lust like fire raging
is not enough to find fulfillment settling down into the stillness and safety of a home like the
resting earth below is it equal value yeah yeah okay so down up down up what are you doing down
up down up aries the ram is located in the northern celestial hemisphere between pices
to the west and taurus to the east virgo the virgin lies with leo to the west and libra to
the east is the second largest monster energy drink in the sky cool libra laying scales lies
with virgo to the west and scorpius to the east libra is sometimes known as the claws of the
scorpion scorpion another another brand of what's the clue though like i don't know who cares
date do i have to do who are these what is this belvane who's belvane is there any info
just google it so i have to pick the sign okay so this is water and then pick the the symbols
of water what are the symbols of water pices watch your step that's not pices that's gemini
where's pices just open the book oh ostara let's do that first celebration of the radiant dawn of
light of blade is the spring equinox in the northern hemisphere where light and dark meets
in a perfect balance belvane marks the halfway point between the spring equinox okay so this
is the date ostara spring equinox spring what's the what's the spring equinox
three is it march april okay and kill this don't move yeah i'm not moving it's a puzzle captain
these look around is that not the equal is that not the equinox 321 is aries
what are you doing yep that's right i agree 321 is aries scroll down
aries the ram is located in northern celestial hemisphere between pices to the west
and uh huh aries is the ram located in northern celestial hemisphere between pices to the west
northern celestial just give me the solution i don't care i don't care i hate this
i don't like this who cares stereo aries 321 that's what i just did this place is going to
come down on our heads fire 321 aries all right fire 321 watch your step doesn't mean it but just
because i'm an adult read the letter wait how come we have this can we have this i like riddles
wait why do i have this oh oh shit that's probably important isn't it stop daydreaming guys get
cracking on this thing you came to me midwinter and made each day feel brightest like a lion
so even though sometimes she could be stubborn like an ox in the month where spring stirs i
revealed your heritage to you on the day of the samhain we remembered our ancestors now i wish
for you to choose make this house your home or be free of its burden like a lion you came to me
midwinter cold cool by the way the will is in the house like a lion you came to me at the fucking
the dumb riddle at the end of the game yeah it's mid it's midwinter lion ox spring midwinter
which is 1221 december 21st that's midwinter winter starts in oh would that be february
no winter winter is uh what three months let's see december you'll you'll lift a leo taris idiot
ban that person for life you'll you'll you'll you'll you'll you'll you'll please click you'll
okay clicked you'll just tell just tell me the rest i don't care you i don't care about any of
this just give me the rest just just say it just say it it's not even backseat gaming this is just
like we're all sitting behind the captain crunch box in a fucking family room with 30 people there
we're all doing it i don't care who cares what is it he doesn't deserve it you'll gemini 621
thank you that's a lie what is it really holy shit there's a lot one two three down yes this
four another circle bites the dust let's figure out the next one this is going pretty good
did you ever uh we did it good job everyone yes perfect now take more time to celebrate and
we'll have the ceiling joining us whoa cool i like the crush to death ending better yeah me
too inspect the small house within the house just punch through the roof and then we're going to
look up and a fist is going to be up there and then he leans in and spits and a huge gigantic
water ball just lands on top of us something moved this is so exciting this isn't what i'm
talking about this is a this is a true puzzle this is what i'm talking about well what is it
what is it it's francis tuttle's will it's gonna be worth like 2100 bucks i know it may may come
on hurry is just dead may may may say something is this how is it like paint can you hear me
my head she's down here huffing paint you were unconscious the paint for you i'm okay i think
you have a concussion i'm gonna move you over to the wall that's why you have to do this in
a ventilated area guys okay okay don't fuck around with spray paint all right um
how did you find me jason your sister is really worried about you i'm sure she is
we need to get out of here wait not yet didn't you literally spray paint your teeth on stream
what it's a very important book that i need to find i can't leave without it do you know anything
about that if it's here you can look for it i hope you don't mind if i set it out
it's not take too long okay i keep trying to think of the context of why you would spray paint
your teeth on camera i couldn't tell you what you would do that for find the book of apologies
movies movies what's this old chest doing here what the hell do you have all this here for
this isn't a chest it's a puzzle box some of these are you a hamster if they are forced open
need to be careful this is like your hamster or your a bird stole a bunch of shit and hit it away
you're a squirrel oh great this is gonna be great okay hold on let's see here this is the slots
slot on the top and the right how does that not go in there oh it's a circle circle
are there any circle slots that's a circle where are the circle slots square circle
there's that one all right now this one ain't square square square square i need
fuck no no get out of here get out out i need a triangle on the edge and there's only one
so it has to be this one do this edge first triangle on the left we are circle square
circle square circle square we don't have one oh shit uh-oh circle circle can i rotate them
you can rotate what the fuck are you doing put it away stop stop oh my god place where's my
circle where's my circle all right there's a lot for this who cares it's wrong it's wrong
now we need a square and then a slot we got a square and then a slot down here i think
no fucking dumbass and then we need a slot slot right there no we need plus
last one over this way that sounds good this way we're gonna have a triangle go into here
what is it i need a triangle slot are they not three where's the triangle slot
i'm fucking stupid fucking idiot fucking game fucking dumb i need shit shit do the edges first
like you said i know i know that's what i should have done i i'll get it okay edges first edges
first did you check total to the right did you check total to the left i need a slot i need a
arrow pointing that way and is this a arrow pointing that way and down
arrow pointing that way and down is it okay circle pointing right and one pointing down like this
right yeah okay i mean now i gotta do this at the bottom so i need a circle and i need to circle
just square square square square all around open squares by the way don't don't ever fuck that up
and circle by the way circle down there it is now got no oh shit and then this is a this one's up
and then right on this one maybe this way there's one that's all four this is probably right in the
middle somewhere i would say it's probably this one right here oh you bet your ass i just
did i get it shit i need to switch me now where's this one go i need a left right and then one out
free up top this one here this is it the book of apologies to think i had to follow you all the way
from austria to finally get you back sounds great really are you done yet i can't even
pog anymore let's get out of here now read can you walk the book of apologies yeah i think so nancy
no problem why though why did you come down here you know what you don't deserve any of this doesn't
deserve it neither did those people back in 1692 they were victims thanks they went we're just going
to leave her down there she can take care of herself is that what you told yourself when you
climbed down we left her down there what would have happened if we hadn't come along we have to
give this will to the judge by the end of the day otherwise this whole thing was for not and if we
leave her down there stuck in those tunnels much longer we'll have some actual deaths on our hands
and if we go down there it's going to be all of us that's all right we gave her we gave her plenty
of air why nancy's here we poked a few holes i got into this case was because i care about my cousin
okay but this is what we have to do believe me i don't want anything to happen to me or nancy
or nancy either fine i'm trying to do one right thing in this whole mess are we going to see the
first time we've been lied to and i am sick of being lied to now i am taking this to the judge's
office because that is what nancy would want me to do listen i may not always be her biggest fan
but if there's anything i know about her it's that she's going to get herself in may out of
the tunnel safely at least she's gonna come up with like a fire extinguisher and be pointing
it out it's like i'll do it your choice i hope this is a very a very large irritant that'll get
in your eyes where we're not gonna get jumped on escape the tunnels it's never happened before
why don't we just leave with them is there any other way out we don't know she's dead
i think she's dead she's dead did i just miss a jump scare wait we're on drugs did we get the
tea fed to stop you would think at this point you'd stop drinking tea that people gave you
in town keep moving keep moving are we breathing in gas you okay where are we what is this place
oh paint huffing right i can't see a thing are you okay no what's the matter why did you bring me
here what do you mean you saw them they're coming and now we're trapped who's coming what do you
mean i know what i did you're going to die here you know we're about to get the supernatural
i'm the witch i'm the ghost or something and i've been the ghost the whole game
and i like burned in the building i burned up in the building and i'm the ghost and no one could
hear me but you you had the only person i could talk to and if you go back and play the whole
game through it's like wow that's right nobody ever did address her ever no one is going to die
please you're hurt i need you to calm down because you're the one who knows this place
and can help us get out of here why would i help you you don't care what happens to me
i couldn't leave it alone everyone has addressed her yeah of course i care people have name dropped
her and spoken directly to her like a thousand times with them see you now which they sent you
to hurt me you're the one doing this i've been called many things but i'm not a witch
i don't have special powers and even if i did i would never use them to hurt you
let me help you but i did i did do wrong the fire everyone knows i did it that's why they
problem solving wasn't your doing it was teagan's she told me herself teagan told you
she did and i believe her teagan shouldn't be speaking to you don't listen don't care about us
you just made everything worse i'm going to die here and you don't even understand i deserve it
me not her i did it doesn't matter we have to get out of here otherwise we're gonna keep getting
high on glue solvents whatever they are i didn't imagine it i know it's okay but now i need your
help to get us out of here i don't think you understand or want to understand okay fine
but my leg hurts and i'm still seeing freaky things so i'm staying right here good idea sit
tight turned around pretty quickly we'll get out of here soon i promise she's back he's back
okay whatever i don't care like whatever who cares looks like an old oil lantern if only there's a
match do oh yeah i have i have one need a light for some kind of carved inlay some kind of
intricate it's gonna burn the wood we're not getting out that way need a light need a light
for can't make out looks like an old oil lantern what does it match anybody see a goddamn match
what is the lighter we've traded inventories a couple times should try to light up this cavern
should try it's not there what is the lighter do you have a lighter on you
nancy drew smokes um only when i'm on fire whatever some other time perhaps sure just
okay but i i had that lighter cooked hot dog try to light up this still works should try to light
okay like the oil barrels on fire yes this box can't open but i can't force it
i have a key even with a set of tools this box can't open abigail woodley's sign
abigail woodley should look more closely i would love to oh you fucking dumb game not as elegant
i accidentally did that this box can't don't want to break it wow it's beautiful
yeah why why do you care that much can't use that can't you can't i am just the shadow
shadow of what shadow of salem the title of the game huh can't use that here huh can't use that here
here stuck
what this doesn't feel right i know but no you don't understand i know this sounds strange but
the accident ever since it happened whose footprints are these bad things before they happen
like premonitions yeah my scar it hurts right before the tunnel collapsed and it hurts now
look this isn't some ergot hallucination i'm telling the truth and i'm telling you that if
you tamper with these bricks we could be in danger okay do you believe me let's just keep going you
know the effects of ergot poisoning can last up forget it i owe the wall seems unstable the wall
the wall the wall seems unstable stuck stuck stuck the wall seems got it you know i clicked
that fits into the panel i clicked that like 30 fucking times okay you've seen me click on that
a shitload even when the room was lit up like i tried clicking on this well it's dark so i
can't pick up the item i can see all right what do we do i am just a shadow all right so where's
the shadow we have to make a shadow let's see what happens if i try to put this back in the wooden
panel now we're getting somewhere just need the other piece this box behind one of these stupid
ass bricks the wall seems on letter on the what do you mean letter scratch on brick what are you
talking about letter on brick i'm just a shadow find the brick in the shadow is that what you
want is that what i'm supposed to do hey hey can i have a lighter may yeah oh fine i used to come
here as a kid with jason after we were told we couldn't hang out anymore by his father
we met in the tunnels and came in here before it was blocked we'll hide out remember something
a panel with a carving find a different game incomplete it made me scar i couldn't my own
don't what do i'm not just give me an item what i'm done okay good they all the bricks they have
aw on them aw aw aw don't touch those don't touch those don't touch those don't touch those
the wall seems this is a a and this is m are there any over here that have that on it you gotta
spell out a word uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh what are you talking about spell word
wah wah wah wah spell out i want to it has to do with i have to make a shadow i have to
this the candles are here but that don't matter don't i don't want to take them out one by one
so where's this this there's a brick here somewhere that i can pull up first somehow
the wall seems not that one is it one like above you the cross marks the desired brick
turn to the wall to the left of may there are two horizontal stripes of bricks
three i got a copy and paste this in my own thing cross marks the desired brick
i have to like put this in my own notepad over here okay the cross marks the desire brick turn
to the wall the left of may there are two horizontal stripes of bricks three in each
with the initials aw yeah i got them right here one two three use a metal object on the
middle brick in the upper strip okay the wall seems on the wall seems on three in each with
the initials either we use a metal object on the middle brick in the upper strip a niche will open
take out a thin tablet from there install it the upper strips the wall seems on
aw aw aw aw aw a a that's it i've done i've done this on all these the wall seems unstable
the walls the upper strip there's no there's nothing i can click on in the upper strip
upper strip what the fuck seems unstable use the metal object what do you think i'm doing
the walls the wall the wall i clicked there's six bricks i clicked on every single one of them
put off the candles you need a reason to do it use note on candle something's different about
the note my fucking god you've got to be kidding me light the note on fire and it turns into a new
note i am just a shadow no no no no no light me on fire looks like a map of some kind x marks the
spot here goes nothing yeah i it's the right one got it let's see what it fit it's covered in a
thick layer of dust should wipe it clean first oh would you please why is everything so dusty
in this game it's dusty what the hell could it be the same height they're all going to be the same
height i get it this moves these two almost almost i feel like after you make like 60 nancy drew
games you just at at at 2019 you're just like i have no fucking idea what we're going to do
for puzzle number 492 that's right that's right that's right so what's what is this
wait what supposed to be mirroring this well i can't even pull this one up come down here
that's correct there this moves these two independently why didn't you just play the
older ones because this is the new one and i had to painfully cause myself pain first click on the
left side i can't i can only manipulate the right side they have to be in a row like that but wait
there's like this two on here though one of them's try dusting it is am i actually supposed to be
i have to be i have to be mirroring this i'm bringing this down to here go like that
this needs to come up this comes up and then this goes up oh you motherfucker you're right here this
comes up no put these up too i can't go up any higher that was not even accurate what i was
trying to do i wasn't even trying to do that so there's some please be a door you actually
did it let's get out of here now where the fuck are we did you take you three tries to open the
door see boys you look dirty i'm fine we need to see the judge now yeah us too we found the
the will no need to recap let's go nancy are you all right dear dra can you frank and joe
wait in the hallway bugleberry he's got the reverb now my pleasure judge we need to talk
what i hope he leans into his light and goes yes it looks like it is it a confession maybe judge
we've been here all night i think it's time we retire you're not going anywhere perp excuse me
your honor it's become clear to us that miss cole has been the perpetrator of numerous crimes
here in salem including attempted murder murder judge please that's a very serious claim nancy
and this is a serious case people's lives hang in the balance this is very cute and all but
we have to do adult things now so run along everyone before your pb and jays get cold
i have proof it's all related to the hathorn house the future of which rests in your hands
so i think you should hear me don't i want to see the end wait show me the end what you can't be
serious judge this is clearly a half-brained attempt to delay what we have determined to be
a sound judgment that the half-born house should revert to the state we have spent most of this
evening going over all possibilities for how to decide the rightful owner of this house
and you've been very adamant that the state should handle it but we should probably on rush any
evidence to add i'm willing to hear her out unbelievable well you see alicia's been poisoning
lauren hult water supply alicia has been poisoning lauren hult water why is it so echoey in here
that's just too much after interviewing lauren hult and experiencing some negative it's so
echoey drinking her water i discovered are we underwater had been tainting her water supply
with ergot well that would explain my client's erratic behavior over the past few weeks
she lost her mother months ago and that woman wasn't it was raining give me a break
it was raining outside that ergot causes echo inside of your house you said she was poisoned
wouldn't that affect anyone's behavior what exactly are you insinuating that you know how ergot
affects its victims i'm not answering these questions i happen to be well versed in biology
all right but any tidbit of knowledge i have you'll just try to trap me with it use it against me
i don't need to do that because i found in your office a map of the hathorne house so i was i
brought what i was here miss drew your coat looks pretty soaked and muddy shoes water is wet and
it's raining outside are you satisfied with the ridiculousness of this yet how much longer are
you gonna let this go on it all does seem circumstantial is that all you have can i
refund no i can't you can't play an entire game and then refund it it's almost eight hours of this
oh yeah i just gotta say i'll just steam refund i've i've i've i've done everything i've beaten the
game you can't you can't go to a movie watch the movie and after the movie's over you sit through
the credits you even watch the last extra end of credits scene after the credits and you get a
refund hey i didn't like that movie i want my refund can you do that no you can't you can't
do that it's final sale if you're annoying enough you can you can't watch a full movie and then
leave and be like that movie's i didn't like that movie i want my money back just finish it just
finish the game finish the game finish the game just finish the movie don't walk out of the theater
by the way you walk out of the theater now you don't get a refund you gotta see the whole thing
i just ran 60 seconds of ads are you seeing them nobody's seeing these there's 32 seconds
remaining no one's seeing ads imagine if ads appeared in the movie holy shit no one would
ever go to the movies can you fuck can you imagine this universe is finite its resource is finite
what i'm doing it requires back lobster fest is on at red lobster with the most lobster dishes
what do you choose how about lobster lovers dream more like a lobster dream come true
a butter poached maintail roasted rock all right let's end the game did anyone actually see an ad
no one saw an ad alicia was responsible for stealing aw evidence yes and i also paid 250
oh that actually hurt i spoke with your son jason he claims alicia forced him i'm sorry
is a grown man his actions are his own alicia lent jason her car then jason broke into the
evidence room and stole the files i have proof on cctv so what it actually sounds like
he runs errands for me all the time and how did he have access to the evidence room
only you and the judge had the code look you made 250 dollars for this movie and then you got an ad
probably apologies judge but your carelessness is the reason this happened in all probability
jason and i've been talking over the whole movie the movie was eight hours i doubt that he barely
spends any time this is i have been speaking over the entire movie you left it out for anyone to
see if he didn't know the door was unlocked how hard would it have been to find your key
miss cold that's enough anything else miss true yes alicia was behind the theft of the book of
apologies alicia was behind i've never been to europe how did you lie passport i heard the
judge talking to you about i never said that's not strange plane tickets in jason's car he admitted
to stealing the book of apologies on alicia cole's order order how did i order little jason
because you like when he cleans your pool or something right she likes to watch him
cleaner pool i don't really know to be honest with you i know he's always looking for money
he's in debt badly a fact alicia uses to her advantage oh this is absurd how did he buy a
first class round trip ticket to salzberg when the crime occurred because i pay him for doing
errands for me why is she reading this money however as if she's reading shit off of a bingo
card in a giant auditorium i don't know how we could prove that all the airline you can use the
plane ticket reference number call the airline they should be able to check the payment i bet
you it was paid by alicia cole credit card there's no way jason would have that much cash to buy a
first class ticket he obviously stole my credit card so you admit that your card was used to make
the purchase where are the police i didn't say that where are the police there's been no police
at all that he stole it the credit card company would have notified you for making a large
there's no there's nothing here how large is this is this room being recorded thousands of dollars
hmm miss cole if this is a court of law and the police were asking for probable cause
i'd be hard pressed not to allow it do you have anything to say i told him to get those tickets
you know your honor your son is a real idiot truly a world-class moron he couldn't even follow
simple instructions i would have had better luck writing them in crayon and this seriously this
is the kind of stuff i have to deal with i went to law school i have three degrees and now i have
an arsonist two ghost hunters a wannabe detective and her assistant hey what no trying to screw up
my plans all the people you pointed out didn't even have to take a mask off no the reason i
am going down is that this stupid little town is stuck in the past oh my great great great
great grandmother was accused as a witch i want repayment because i'm lazy she loved me so much
that i want this disgusting ruin of a house for free so i can run my luminous vegan tea grocery
store that is what pathetic looks like a bunch of whining moaning little people whose worldview
is infinitesimally small why alicia i just told you i just went over it to do something for this
town i care about salem more sorry i wasn't listening to anything teagans and lauren's
combined i care the most i was locked inside my own head leveled that old house a long time ago
and built new houses with all that land we could have a real community here we could bring in new
business that isn't completely relying on stupid scary stuff i am talking about economic development
on a level which salem has never even seen and who would be the owner of these new houses
hold that thought for a second okay the um looking at the economic outlook for salem to see if she
was right so there has been a 3.2 growth in payroll growth general fund okay current revenue growth
does not keep pace with the growth and current operations costs growth and property tax revenue
year over year ranges between three and a half percent and three percent still below historical
levels of 5.5 percent lower than predicted compression losses beginning in 2014-2005 are
expected to continue which improves the city's forecast for essential resource for years two
through five of the forecast uh per s rates are assumed to exceed the current advisory board's
recommendations hmm okay here it is forecast the general fund what 134 dollars that's not right
beginning working capital current year revenues beginning working capital 21 dollars and 98 cents
current year revenue 112 dollars total resource 134 dollars that's not this is am i is this like
a different thing is that supposed to be million i think it's million yeah value in millions by
the way value in millions 134 million in revenue by the way 2018 to 2019 136 million dollars in
revenue so estimated uh estimated ending working capital is 15.4 million dollars well after knowing
this case inside out it wouldn't be hard for me to get the land out of the grasp of the state
after all i've done for this community some recompense is in order so you're saying you
poisoned lauren so you could build and own a housing complex it's always a housing complex
and give me you were gonna level the national park to put in condos
money in real estate you know you have no idea how much money i would have made with condos
there is absolutely no way you could control it's always condos in apartments you could have done
irreparable damage so fuck that tree fuck that big tree it's been 100 years i don't care i've lived
for 100 years this town needs me no it doesn't i already have the papers and i am taking them
to the state office and none of you are going to stop me you can't cut down that tree yes i can
and there'll be big expensive condos it's an average price of a condo in salem massachusetts
so you admit to all of it yes
oh there's other people in the room fuck i didn't even see them for them to arrive
this is unbelievable only wanted to make salem this is really disturbing i am shocked
very shocked at what has occurred here miss cole will be held accountable for her crimes
i will make sure of it but as much as it pains me to admit she is right we do not have a legal heir
yes we do we found the will we found francis tuttle's will and according to her lauren halt
is the sole heir of the hathorne house estate i believe the will supersedes all other claims
to the property unfortunately the accused witch's organization has no evidence that says they have
any claim on the property it is what it is okay well what about the hathorne house hog champ
legal air twist three messages down resident sleeper had nothing to do with the fire you're
sure how do you know because i have a confession from the person who did really
me teagan perry intentionally set the fire to force out lauren and let the aw organization
take over the property that's surprising you say it was intentional yes i believe it was
and i believe that because anything less than intentional would mean people conspired to
withhold information about who was responsible and who might that be you should just play the ace
attorney i couldn't say it doesn't matter who knew what it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
then she will also be held responsible for judge did you ever interview may get a statement well
so you just assumed she was guilty of the crime a case needed to be built there was no case because
you never miss true i asked that in this office you treat me with respect you deserve as much
respect as i'm currently giving you judge nancy maybe we should you made this poor girl's life a
living nightmare because of something she did when she was young she was a kid your honor
her entire life we're not in a courtroom you know the lawyer in a courtroom can you imagine
there's no jury here can you imagine what that does to her family to her well that is a bit
unfair you know this town has a history of judges not guilty sound jurisprudence
thanks for coming nancy tell your father i said hi you would be able to write that wrong
perhaps but my concerns are not unfounded you think jason is a screw-up now what would have
happened if he had been friends with her he is friends with her judge what how is that possible
i i thought at least i would know a judge is supposed to judge people on their actions alone
not the people they call their friends i just hope you remember that when you sentence jason
because his crimes aren't imagined does it be a real better audio book they deserve
real punishment just take away the puzzles and make it audio only i did it say goodbye
fuck these people i just wanted to say i'm sorry for what we always promised that a secret was
the most important thing in the world and we would never break it and i did you saved my life
nancy hadn't found me well why is my such a blurred vision for a while you screwed up still i know
who you are there's a good person hidden below this pretty boy exterior
you may go away yeah that's true every time i've tried to go to bed she goes
nah i don't think i'm gonna go to bed to be expected i've tried to sleep a few times
it's locked it's
well it's over now so i don't have to put up with you anymore
leave me alone okay bye case closed hey there how are you holding up i can't believe
okay yeah that makes sense imagine playing royalty-free party music at your party
holy shit how boring is your house
sounds fun i'll be sure to stop by and stir the pot
if it isn't the insightful red-headed witch herself i thought you were the only real witch
around here there's always room for another witch in the cabin nancy drew
and i have to say someone with your magical insights clairvoyance even would make a great fit
nancy so glad you're here crazy party hey shouldn't you ask her you know the thing we
talked about oh i can't okay wild party man wild fucking party it was great working with
you again let us know what you think about the detective agency i will it was great working
with you let us come on dude it's a crazy party
take this guy out of the house this guy someone is to get this guy out of here
does it sound like your style is it the bathroom upstairs
a few days in the end
that's water oh dude what happened up there dude
hey yo yo yo hey what the fuck are you doing up here all right i have to stop
i'm already parked a car in the bedroom i still can't get in here all right say goodbye
okay leave it's i need car keys what the fuck this crashing sounds no that's not that's still
that's the game i got it ready austria really get to enjoy it much i feel like
like there's a lot more exploring to do there did you know it's a trash all over the front
lawn it's a kid you know what's all that fucking trash i'm gonna throw the trash all over the
front door i'm sure we could find something okay yes that's the end no cases this time
just the two of us that's the end oh my god betty paris father samuel paris was a um betty paris's
father samuel paris was uh a merchant i failed that after the credits quiz oh well who the
fuck is this since moving to this nowhere town i'm still waiting for an ounce of excitement
this is a game nancy drew check it out the creepy twin elms house has gone viral finally things
are about to get a little more interesting the legend date it's an ad for the new show
what network is this on the cw this has a 50 on rotten tomatoes it's apparently five out of ten
that's not bad that means 50 of all people liked it that's kind of hard to do i'm not going to tell
you what happened but i'm going to type in nancy drew every spoiler i'm just going to read it i
don't care okay how many seasons are there season okay season one episode 10 ending explained i'm
gonna watch it not now all right i'm out of here i did not i did not think we're gonna play this
eight hours but that was um you know okay well you like rating for nancy drew midnight in salem
okay you know when you go like that you go to the doctor and you have like that pain meter
and it's like the the default face the smiley face the really happy face and then the
sort of like slightly like ow and then like below is like really huge huge red face screaming out
i would point at somewhere between that those two well it's my pain index he loves nancy drew
i played the whole thing by the way i really hate to tell you guys this but i own
uh as of right this second nancy drew last train to blue moon nancy drew sea of darkness nancy drew
secret of the old clock secrets can kill treasure in the royal tower warnings at waverly academy
i bought the bundle i mean you're not gonna see it for a while how many games are there in my
whole library well 30 25 of them and nancy drew team fortress 2 dead rising dead rising 2 and uh
the dark souls and that's it all right that's it that's the end of the stream i'll see you guys
tomorrow tomorrow we're going to try uh if it works if it doesn't work then i don't know we're
in non-canon week welcome to non-canon week everybody the streams that aren't canon
dostane that's gonna be tuesday but uh me uh me star and italics gonna try to play this game called
tools up the three of us are gonna get together hopefully we can do it it's a local only game so
we're gonna have to try to finagle with the steam remote play feature the three tools that's right
if it doesn't work i'll be doing something else that's what we're gonna try have a wonderful rest
of your night that's gonna be the end for me see you tomorrow and if you're sticking around
we've got bits to do oh all right let's go back to uh i'm not gonna check check it
i'm not even gonna check it because stream labs obs doesn't work so
now why even check it why even check it anyways uh we had a ton of money coming today we have
a huge amount of money new obi i'm gonna be used regular obs tomorrow i'm over this uh but thank
you to everybody that was a huge amount of money there was a ton of gifted subs it was a shit load
of bits that were throughout the whole stream here especially there was one part where i was
sitting in a car and like a thousand plus dollars that then came in in less than 10 minutes thank
all of you seriously thank you thank you thank you uh but before that we had uh 300 bits here
from sad vega can i germa one guy you by saying that you should play the megaman legends series
megaman legends one misadventures of tron bone and megaman legends two they're an amazing series
and still for what they are look pretty good i even remember playing megaman legends that's
the third person camera one right i remember they were pretty good put it on the list those
are that you does have a playstation right playstation 1 playstation 2 put it on the list
atma starfish thanks for the thousand bits how is this the stream that you stop using obs and
stream labs if this stream isn't canon i know right but it is thank you for the thousand bits
atma starfish chowder soup thanks with 300 bits these hearty boys have a raging clue
this is a south park reference 25 dr peppa thanks for the 250 lizard tier list when the next the
next time there's a tier list i hope for some of you guys saving some of your favorites because
i'll be doing it again i have a lot of fun doing those they're just it's just fun to sit there and
do it hey wasad thanks for the 250 played nancy drew but not ace attorney and then the face that
like that i'm right in the middle but slightly angry about it uh in the pain index yeah i know
but the thing about ace attorney is ace attorney ace attorney is just i i the ace attorney is not
like a crappy game this grabbed me and i think a lot of other people in the first two three hours
because it was it was a little crusty plus ace attorney does this thing and i know it's it's a
thing that it's just a thing that i don't like about it it's the thing that i don't even know
if you can turn it off i've tried the game flashes you act with white flashing every 10 seconds it's
like that was all the time there is this white camera flash that does the whole screen
and you can't turn it off and it actually kind of bothers me you're afraid of the light why didn't
you tell us sooner well i i told you that i've just i didn't think i wanted to stream it
and also that's like that's like just don't look just blink when those flashes happen put on
sunglasses we would have understood no i brought this up before i i definitely brought this i
remember talking about this how i was hoping that when the the new remastered version came out that
you could turn it off and i don't think it did i remember yes nancy drew is more germa's speed
uh are you sure about that because i think for at least three or four of the major puzzles in
the game i just looked it up on the guide or asked you what the answer was but uh thank you
wild hubbutty for the 500 bits thank you for letting me be the germa one guy with that great
skyrim routine that great that great skyrim bit you proved me wrong sometimes i prove people wrong
sometimes i'm proven wrong happens a lot thanks to the 500 bits a lot of times you've proven
wrong ban that person for life it was cad oh still do it hey abomination zero thanks to the
420 bits why isn't this week canon um well the first stream was not canon because joel and i
had some scheduling conflicts we were going to play halo reach on uh the first stream of this
week was supposed to be halo reach and then i mean joel talked and there was some stuff uh he was
busy with some stuff and we were like you know what fuck we'll just do it the next day so that
was the first strain that was just like whatever this is i'm just gonna stream because like i still
plan to stream i was gonna do but this is non-canon stream the next day um me and joel did play halo
reach but it was a disaster uh it was an absolute 100% completely unmitigated disaster uh so that
was not canon because it was uh all over the place uh so i figured okay that's two streams in a row
that would just sort of just literally throwing up dice in the air uh so we'll just keep the whole
the whole week is non-canon it was very good oh let me do not mistake this these last three streams
i have had a absolute goddamn blast on every single one of them i mean that doesn't mean that
they're canon streams i think it's still best you can have fun in non-canon streams was simpsons hit
and run canon yeah you know no no no no no you know sometimes like you do there'll be a piece
of media that's created and then they make it canon retroactively the nancy drew stream is canon
yeah yes no yes it is yes it it absolutely is it's happened in the past i can retroactively
i can make it canon if i want but thank you abomination thanks for the 420 bits thank you
dark soul for the 250 bits hope you realize that you streamed this with 500 more viewers
than the next person yeah but do you i don't do you really think that anyone's gonna stream
the new nancy drew game it's not like you got it's this is not like the star wars game coming out
it's nancy drew midnight in salem apparently at least two people did i did yeah but what so
everyone put the stream in the next tab while they were doing other stuff yeah i knew that
i did a poll before the stream started i said is that what you're going to do most people said
uh yes i will have you in a third or fourth tab i said okay whatever
but no i know hey silent serenity thanks for the 250 holy moly i know you'd like to talk to
transformer and this is going to blow your mind it uses the same ai model to generate an infinitely
complex text adventure what ai dungeon are you kidding me all right hold on to this is that for
real hold on to this on the next like fuck face comb stream i'll definitely do it hey spliceable
spleen thanks for the 500 bits fuck all the haters germa this stream has been fantastic
and your comedy in reaction to this strange game is exactly why i tune in
germa hard also thank you for a solid year of amazing content entertainment
thank you spliceable spleen thanks for the 500 bits i i don't think there were that many haters
i don't think so i didn't get that vibe i didn't get a bunch of like people a hater vibe i thought
that people were having fun i hate you in general mod that guy just getting down to that but thank
you no i had i had a great time i loved it hey checkers 8 000 thanks for the thousand bits
is this how you do it that's how you do it that's how you give bits and that was during
the insanity a few hours ago thank you so much checkers and to all of you that just
dumped a huge amount of money into the stream thank you silent serenity thanks for the 250
germa bores his audience into donating we were so bored that we had to donate to you
to get something going slow update thanks for the 250 hey germa so glad to watch you embrace
your heritage as the son of nancy drew glad you accepted who you are also thanks for making 2019
such a great year ever since i started donating to you this year i felt happy just talking to
you and chat peace and love and i can't wait for germa rumble merry christmas happy holidays
talking to you and chat yeah it's i have a lot of fun here sometimes too much fun
sometimes way too much fun but no i'd i'd love it it's a lot of fun fun fun fun fun fun fun fun fun
fun too much fun that your rib cage cracks and your stomach goes up into your esophagus
hernia levels of fun but thank you slow update hey uh cloudiest nights thanks for the 500 bits
there's no message just 500 bits thank you dais mortay thanks for the 300 bits you say this is
non-canon but this has been one of my favorite streams of yours this year i don't think i've
ever given out this many plus twos i'm sad i've retro i've made it canon retroactively
thanks for the 300 bits seriously thank you dais mortay goo berry juice thanks for the 300 bits
no message just 300 bits and we're going to see some very fast credits here they are going to
fly by very very quickly this is going to be here they go all of you a lot of you uh may have just
been subbed for the first time today from a community sub welcome hopefully not very many
of you got cut off from the crash that happened earlier because remember we play in the game for
about 30 40 minutes and then the stream turned off so sorry to those of you in the first 20 30
minutes of the stream that may have gotten cut off thank you everybody again for your ridiculous
generosity and support of this live stream how's your razor mouse germa uh it's not good it's not
good i don't like it but again thank you seriously seriously seriously seriously there's still some
more bits to do thank you mostly lost for the 250 hey jimbo any hey jimbo any updates on that
community meetup in vegas or is that just another thing we can throw under the pile of things that
you lied about jimbo um i mean you you can add it to the list you can add it to the list i
i want to do i would love to do that but i it costs money and i've like i i i keep spending money
on other things for the stream so not now not yet so that i i think like having a big private
like party is is uh it might cost more than i think he spent that money on nancy drew
that's true that i some of your bits have gone to me purchasing nancy drew
uh that was an investment i very much resent that all right i just said that but people
people make like me me jokes about oh oh he if i told you that i spent 50 dollars of your bit
money at the roulette table people would be like oh gambling what the fuck oh he's gonna be rolling
that but that's but that's better than me buying the nancy drew bundle are you sure
i wouldn't mind it to be honest you didn't waste money how is gambling not wasting money gambling
money is wasting money with the hope that one of the times that you're actively wasting the money
that you'll get some money given back to you if you lose confirmed nancy drew complete bundle worse
than going to a casino confirmed anyways all jokes aside we'll see you tomorrow whatever uh
happens tomorrow i'll be live making some of that sweet sweet non-canon but finally
we had actually two or three more came in uh siku thank you siku for the thousand bits less than
five minutes ago i still keep rewatching your old videos they've gold that means a lot uh because
90 of every video i made on youtube was designed in a way that i would want people to be able to
watch them more than once and maybe still think they're worth watching i that's was that's part
of the reason why i made some of those videos was i want you to be able to watch them again maybe
come back and watch them again if you thought they were funny maybe miss maybe you missed an
easter egg that you caught this time maybe you have to go back and watch the whole thing check
out the easter egg there was at least two or three easter eggs in each video no that's not
that's not that's not i know people are gonna be like what the fuck and they're gonna go back
that's not true some of them maybe acting acting like you designed the videos i did i sat there
for weeks at a time sometimes on some of those videos people always wonder why did you only make
a video like once every like four or five days i was sitting there in the editing room with the
lights off just trying what what do i want here what do i want to do is it i do is that fun
that's i think that's really funny i like this it's fun and then you go back and you listen you
watch the same part of the video like four 10 20 times in a row and then when i'm talking about
i'm talking about like like a five second segment that you watch like 50 times in a row
ridiculous not every single video was like that but most of them were the developing room skipping
each frame of film from your camera in front of your projector that's right the the old way
that's true but yes uh i'm happy that you still like them because that's another part of the
fear of making videos or making any kind of content is is if people can go back five plus
almost seven eight plus years ago like if somebody comes back and watches these videos is this still
going to be will does it stand up i don't know hopefully it does it's part of the thought
process i guess but uh thank you cq and thank you cq again for another 500 bits
say for the nancy drew fund by every nancy drew game see you tomorrow have a wonderful night
nancy drew the newest we're going newest and then down to oldest good night guys let's see you tomorrow