Listen, that's not a defeat for me. Listen, I will be fucking doing cartwheels
In my fucking apartment knowing that you're not as smart as me when I do the fucking bomb game with you
Listen, you all right. When do you want to do it? When do you want to do it? When do you want to do it?
Whenever you're ready. Well, not today. That is but you know next week
Yeah, i'm down with the clown at some point next week. You want to keep talking nobody explodes not halo
Not not halo
I think i'm never gonna fucking ever play halo because of you
I didn't do anything
Because of you
Oh my god
Did I ruin halo for you? I wasn't the one calling me at like 2 a.m. Saying
Hey gamer, listen, i've been thinking a lot
And you know, it'll be pretty fucking pretty fucking hello gamer
Halo legendary and I I told them guys this is this is true fact. This is not me making the whole bullshit up
I told germa
first of all
I don't I don't really play that much halo and you kept lying to me for weeks upon end saying
You know back in the day halo was my jam. This is verbatim, by the way
germa germa
threateningly
uh recommended
Halo to me
and
I said maybe maybe and then we get around to doing it and you've been doing nothing but insulting me
And saying mean things to me my favorite part of the sir my favorite part about this whole two-hour broadcast so far
Absolutely. Is this is may is it gonna make me laugh for the next probably three straight days. Is that
That you didn't want to even do like a halo at all
And we're like, let's do halo halo legendary and you're just right that you're just sitting there going. I fucking don't want to be here
That's so fucking funny
Okay, well i'll tell you what i'll tell you the analogy here, right
This is a little story. I'm gonna i'm gonna open up a medieval while we talk
Okay, imagine
Paling around with friends you really like these friends, right?
Mm-hmm, and you think they're funny. They're great
And then you follow them underneath the bridge
And they all pull out syringes
They stab themselves in the genitals with syringes
and
You like these friends
But you don't like what they're doing
But you you keep going on with it and then you stab yourself with the syringe and you smile through your teeth and say
Oh my god. Yeah, I like this
And you you and you don't know if they're enjoying it. So you're just kind of going along with it now
At this point i'm bleeding out of my cock. So what what what?
When what when did I
So i'm saying no more halo not tonight maybe at some point next time we're doing this
We're not fucking playing a game. We're unfamiliar with and we're not putting it on the hardest difficulty
All right, how about how about keep talking and nobody explodes
uh
next week
Yes, I think that sounds like a great idea
I i'm quickly learning something. All right, let's see. We don't interact too much on stream
We wrestle sometime
You know, but
I don't think fps games and us. It's like orange juice and toothpaste. We need
logical games
We need big brain games we need games for big boys. All right
Where's my save?
We need games like portal
math games
I'll take a math game
You good at math?
Uh, not at all
Like as as zero as you could be at math
What about the pogo game? Oh, yeah, that's right. We never did the pogo game
Have you played a video you played dusk?
They're very good
Uh, i'll say it one more time. It's been my favorite. What was my favorite? What?
Your favorite video game. Sorry. This game is pretty fucking loud
All right. My favorite video game is
uh
Diablo 2
Diablo 2 is my favorite video game. You like diablo 2. Yeah, it's like the best game ever. Well shit
Let's let's let's wait. Are you fucking around with me? No, no, no, no, that's my favorite game ever
Like that's my that's one of my top five favorite video games ever made. How come how come people in my chat is like, uh,
Doing a little funny like well, what's going on here? What was it? What was it? What's the funny?
What funny?
No, I don't know something's up here. What's what?
guys
Does germa hate diablo or something like that? No, no, I guys help me
That that's like my favorite game ever
What game are you playing right now? Uh
Shenmue and pokemon, I think yeah
did we just
Play co-op halo and then both just go to different games and play different things and do different streams in the same call
That's fucking hilarious
Oh, that's awesome. Oh, that's that's what being a gamer is all about you improvise
And you learn that you hate fucking video games
Well, I I like video games if they're uh brain related
And they're good
What time is it? What time is it?
4 a.m
What the hell are you doing up so late?
We'll fucking play halo with you. What are you what are you what are you doing up so late? It's like 4 a.m
Fucking oh my goodness. That's so late
You you are you saying this past my bedtime?
No, i'm just pulling your face
Okay, okay. Okay
When do you usually start streaming?
what fucking
But but i'm not what i'm not like
Intimidating to playing halo at fucking four in the morning
Why do I have to be the bad guy
Because you were the one who was like I was like
Okay, verbatim i'm gonna read this. All right, i'm gonna read this right now. This is a horse shit
Don't believe a word. He said i'm pulling up this card right now here. Here we go
Hello germa today at
1 29 a.m
What's up nasty gamer pussy? Would you like that halo hole to pop tonight?
I gotta get I gotta delete him. I gotta get rid of him. I gotta get rid of him. I gotta mute him
He's muted
Not right now germa
Hold on wait, so I actually do have to mute you for a second. Oh god. Wait
Uh ben folds just gave a hundred dollars
Thanks for the 10,000 bits ben fold. Hey joel. Love you streams. Could you let germa know i'm a huge fan
Hey germa
Joel is a huge. Uh, this is a huge fan of yours in here. Did he leave did he abandon me?
You guys hear
I hear you someone on discord right now
Do you guys hear someone on discord?
It's the sound of a coward
Hold on telling me i'm a coward and you were saying you didn't want to play halo on legendary difficulty
Somehow i've turned into the coward
so I only really speak game around these parts, you know if you
If you guys know anyone who would like to come forward and admit
how much
non-gamer they are
What's your favorite non-gaming activity? I'm just saying
I'm just saying that
I'm gonna play with the big boys
You have to step up. Oh somebody said germa and joel no longer friends in this call. Oh fuck
Uh-oh
That means we have to settle this in the fucking ring
Yeah, I hope you hope you know that you're gonna be i'm not gonna go down that fucking road again
I'm not going down that fucking road again
uh
I'm talking about that next like off on this end
Oh, you got you got you got anybody you'd like to have participate and on this end here?
Hello
You guys just don't we're just rationing each other he started it
Yeah, did you guys see did you guys see what he said to me on stream? Oh, no. No, no
I got my hand. I got my hand over the the panic button
You guys remember all the awful things you said to me
Do you remember when he said all those nasty things to me?
Yeah
When where?
I've never said a nasty thing in my life. You you said you said you said so many bad things about me and my family
You know cover his mic
Like we're in the same room like no i'm gonna come wait, why do we have two mics?
I don't know. Can you reach?
How tall are you?
May I ask? I think I think it's time to end this call. How tall how tall are you?
Five what how tall are you?
Five what do you five five? What do you five five nine? Have you ever have you ever gone on a roller coaster?
Yeah, what do you feel when you go on a roller coaster?
I feel great actually
Oh, yeah, tell me about it every time we go on a roller coaster. I get off and i'm like, oh that was fucking awesome
Did you try getting on one?
You're not gonna tell me like reach my hand down into like the the drain penis thing, right?
That's not what this is. It's not what's going right?
Listen, I just I I just wanted to play some halo tonight
No, you didn't no you didn't that's a lie
You pressed the button you didn't want to play any
That's that's not the point here. The point is you're being very mean
All right
I
Okay. Listen. Listen. Listen. We need to we need to put this one in the play
tonight
Because you've been yeah, you've been throwing these bullshit comments my way you've been exposed
You've been saying these things to me. I don't appreciate it
None of my viewers appreciate your hostility. All right
I don't know where the fuck this this anger and resentment from you is coming from but are you watching the stream right now?
Look at this. No, no, no, i'm not watching this. What are you fucking doing? Put on my stream. It's good
That's what's germa's channel called
Are you still you're still streaming
Yeah, he's still what what are you doing? Like what's on the screen?
Like okay when you're in a situation, let me let me give you a real scenario, okay
You know and you turn you turn stream on
And you know, all right. I got this idea. This is my plan. All right, cool
This is plan a and I got like maybe a plan b too in case something goes awry, whatever
So plan a and plan b both seem like they're not going to work
And then you're sitting there and what?
Go watch my stream. I put a put a little surprise for you
I'll put a little surprise for you and it's just for my old bunny germa
You might like it
How's the squad where's the squad streaming? No, we're not. Why are we not squad streaming anymore?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to like you trying to break my computer stop breaking my computer?
All right. I'm here. I'm here. I'm looking
He's ruining my stream
Okay
All right, are we i'm back are we are you
Why can I hear myself through you?
Hey, welcome back to taze on day gaming today. We're gonna be playing germa
Uh germa is is a pretty exciting episode. Uh, there's a bit of a glitches on it
It's not the most valuable level, but I like it a lot
uh
Wait, you're just you're streaming my stream
That's illegal
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no pretend you're playing the game
Guys, i'm i'm about to like do my best germa impersonation
And just like record his gameplay and just i'll meet this
Germa where you're from again
Uh from cincinnati, but what's what's that famous word?
Uh, it's in the southwest of the united states. It's you you don't know like the other states, right?
It's the fifth of them. Yeah, that's it's it's it's there somewhere. All right, what about
Oh, I need a gold key. Damn it. Okay. Well, what's your like defining accent? That's uh, new england boston
accent
Yeah, you what are you what are you guys famous for like eating clams or something new england?
Uh, I mean, I I don't think we're famous for eating clams. I mean this is
Yeah, new england they're all famous what like i'm famous for eating clams
Like when you eat a clam all of a sudden you you get popular. Well fucking I I don't know about your culture
right
But yeah, but it's it's a boston accent. All right, I need help finding this key. Okay. Well, uh listen I like
For me, let me say three american accents in my head
one that's just like
uh valley girl
two
redneck
Slash stone cold steve austin sure right and gap and gaba ghoul
Yeah, like new york
boston is close to a new york accent. It's their most east coast
Yeah, but you don't you don't you don't like tell people a you're walking there, right?
No, that that that's that's from a movie
A movie that's from a movie
That's from that's from a movie
Not everything seen in the movies is real
All right. Sorry. Hold on. I'm i'm concentrating
This game is a hard game
So you're saying that the boston accent is from a movie as well
I mean
Not really but sort of
Okay. Well, i'll be uh, i'll be renting lord of the rings on netflix later on
Anyway, uh, I think it's time for us to go. Uh, I uh
Yeah, everybody special. Thanks to joel
for coming out and
Pretending to like halo for two hours
Uh, very special. Thanks. Uh, thanks glad to have you and i'll be i'll be sure
When we do keep talking and nobody explodes
To kick your ass. I'll tell you what though. This this might have been like
The absolute shittiest slash best stream ever done
It's like I I don't know what quality is anymore because I don't have any like quality control
but i'll tell you what like
I I think this is cock and ball torture
You know, you know what cock and ball torture is
Yes
You know, there's there's an element of like well, yeah, i'm not saying i'm into that stuff
but i'm saying I relate more to that stuff, you know, because
Then to halo
Hold on you relate more to than to halo reach
I'm just saying that listen the deal is or well, whatever it is
I hate pain
But I feel compelled to come back. So who knows?
Who knows?
Uh, anyway, I loved it. It was fun
This this okay in all seriousness not like all shit aside. This was a lot of fun. I think a lot of the uh,
The fun inadvertently was derived from the fact that
It was a shit show
Uh, we came in so underprepared and well
But how do you come and prepare to like just pull
halo
We don't have to like read a bunch of books to play halo
Well, it took us like three fucking hours to get into the menu and then after we're actually starting streaming then you know, hey, so
So
No, it was a pleasure
We'll see we'll see you next time
No, no. Yeah for real though, like let's next time
We'll actually set something up that we both enjoy
And it's not fucking 4 a.m in the morning
And it's not me like having
Having an episode
All right
Like I I need an epi pen after this fucking stream like I I feel nauseous in the best way possible like i'm gonna
I'm gonna vomit my asshole off after this like I need a deep cleansing after the soul here
but um, regardless, I want to say
I need to say that uh, this is a this is a lot of fun
I want to say thank you so much for taking time out of your day to uh ruin your stream. Uh
And uh, I wish you the best of luck sir with your uh,
Lack of video gaming skills and uh
Pompous attitude
Oh, i'm gonna take the higher road
Thanks for hanging out
Thanks for hanging out and spending the time with me together
and
I want you to have nightmares tonight
About chewing on tinfoil
And that horrible horrible like weird feeling it is I want you to have a never-ending tinfoil chewing dream
You know what? You know what though?
I have something worse than that, right?
I have something worse than that
tinfoil for me
it's
Not that bad. I've heard this analogy before and it hits me going telling stories filling
You got you got filling. You know, I think it's you know, I think it's actually worse than chewing on
I don't know if you're gonna relate to this or whatever it is
But chewing on cotton
Chewing on what?
Fuck I haven't saved that. I haven't wait. Wait, hold that thought. I haven't saved
All right chewing on one
cotton cotton like t-shirt wool
And then like grinding that stuff in between your teeth
You guys I feel like I know what you're talking about. I feel like I if you I feel like I could think about what that means
Yeah
Are you making fun of my fucking accent?
What?
Hey Joel, I have an accent too
We both have accents
We don't you don't fucking have an accent
Name name one thing that that's accented when you're speaking. Uh
Okay, what is the thing you drive around in?
a car
Okay, that's a car drive your car. There's like park
Hold up, what are you saying? Hey, where are you streaming from right now in your
Gamer zone. No. No the the box that you're in with the door
An apartment no the
deeper
the basement
Oh my stomach
Okay, the four
The pieces of drywall that are up around you and the door encloses you into a
what
If you were to go looking for a new apartment or a new house you would you would first want to ask how many bed
There were
How many bed this there were?
uh
What cave?
Room your room
See I I
Room, right? It's your room. I say room. I I say like roof roof
Oh, holy shit. I've been fucking wondering what this is. Okay. Like oh, hang on. I fucking really gonna understand. Okay
Question. Yeah
Some people in new york pronounce roof as rough. Yeah, you do that
No, I don't know. No, I said I was answering. I was answering
That was a lie
A great fucking proof. This is it all these fucking years. I was thinking no
No, nobody does that joel one fucking guy you're crazy joel you're fucking nuts nobody says rough
You say fucking rough
You guys got fucking call jerma's fucking living proof. He's fucking living proof that that that that's relying to me
Does somebody from new york like
Pee on you or something or like like shit in your cereal. I don't understand
No, no, i'm just saying chad has been crapping on me for years for saying
In new york, did somebody from new york pee in your cereal or something?
No, no, no, i'm just saying chad collected a little peed on me because they pronounce roof as rough and people are saying like
no
Screw you joe. You're dumb ass sweet. You don't know shit about stuff joe. I'm looking for the door
What was that? I'm looking for the uh, the gold door. Can you help?
I forget where it is
It's right in front of you. I thought you were serious. You're not even watching me. Why am I asking you?
Yes, I am fucking watching. Are you?
back where you came
right
No, no, go go. Okay. Okay. Okay. Here's what we're gonna do. All right
Just just here just follow what the fuck i'm saying. All right. All right, i'll follow it. Wait, hold on. All right now i'll follow you
forward
Forward right there's nothing there's nothing here. What are you doing?
Right, wait, where's the gold door? I know it's it's down here
Thank you. Thanks. I appreciate it. Actually you did you actually did just help me. I'm still in halo reach. I know I have to change that
Listen
I was supposed to like end the stream like hours ago now and i'm still here fucking arguing my roofs and
and
Whatever the hell we're talking about
Um, this is this is the post halo reach meltdown
This is the rehab part of the stream
Anyway, once again, I want to thank you for taking the time out of your day. Thank you for a wonderful evening
severely, uh
scarring the stream with uh
New low in stream quality, but there was
Some pooh-pooh talk and stuff that I wasn't a fan of either. I'll just i'll address that with you off stream
Everything I see
um
anyway
anyway, uh
I'm gonna try to fucking end this now, but I want to say in all
Seriousness though. I think and i'll need more
absolutely, uh, this is one of those like first date things and you're like
Like
Are you fucking the first date too? Okay. Well, i'm ready to get to fill my gamer hole
So we should we should definitely we should definitely cut his mic
We should definitely uh stream more and I look forward to uh
Solving brain puzzles next time and that'll be fun
i'm looking forward to that
I am I am too, but let's not do it at fucking 4 am because it's it's going to give me
Fucking nightmares on week 7
um
I hope you get a good sleep
Chad make sure you get put your head on that pillow and rest
And have a wonderful rest of your night and everyone that was uh
Uh on joel's stream
Have a great night, too
All of you
Well, this is my cue to leave
Uh, yeah, it is actually
You want to pull the plug on ending the call
Uh, I i'm currently, uh fighting monsters
Well, if you're a gamer you would have been able to do it
You've seen a game like this before it takes a lot of focus
You're playing with four hands
That would be actually kind of cool
Does you really make a game like that where you hold down right mouse and it's move fast and then left is
That's kind of cool. That's not a bad idea
Jerma, how about this? Tell me a story
I thought wait, are you still here?
Jerma you just tell me any story you want and um
Okay
Once there was a once there was a boy
named
Let's just say his name was dave
dave
God, I can't do this while playing this game. It's not gonna happen
This is two of my hemispheres are fighting each other
How about this for a story?
Oh, he's gone. He left
That's what though. That was what it was. He wanted me to tell a long story
I'm glad I couldn't come up with anything because he left
Yeah
I I know your little game. That's why the story sucked. It wasn't even worth listening to because I didn't even tell anything
All right. See you later. Joel
All right. Okay
Cool. All right. So that was hey, let me change the game name from halo reach
dude
The best part about this whole stream
Is how he was just humoring me playing halo
He just didn't want to play it and took him two hours to be like I fucking can't do it
And I don't I don't want to play anymore
That's the best part, but I ain't going anywhere. I ain't going anywhere. I'm gonna stick around
We will play something again
That was a good introduction
Right. I would say so
Let me leave the let me leave the squad so we're not squad streaming anymore
All right, let me I gotta change the people think i'm playing halo reach and they're like, what the fuck are you doing?
I almost just clicked raid channel and raided shul
Imagine if I did that
All right. Let me change uh
Let me get this on envied evil
It always ends in viscera cleanup detail, doesn't it?
I told you hey
But hold on a second here. This is actually really really interesting
Didn't I say yesterday?
Or the day the yeah yesterday. I said a medieval. He's a fucking what the hell is going on
Jerma's foolish. Holy that scared the fuck out of me. I thought I was not even in a call
Holy shit, that was terrible. That actually scared me. I thought somebody was like coming to kill me or something
I thought someone was going to kill me
Oh my god
all right, you know when something like that happens and
That you know that nothing can hurt you but like you're the room you're in just became like
dangerous
That's what happened. My room was just dangerous for like a half a second. I was like hands are about to go around my neck
uh, but I uh, I did say
that
Nothing can hurt you. Yeah. I did say that I was never gonna play this again
I was like, yeah, i'm just gonna say i'm gonna play it i'm never gonna play it and here we are
Uh, you know, i'm into it for a little bit. I'm into it
Dragon quest builders that I just hear are very quiet and nothing's going to hurt. No. No, I I made sure I left that call
Am I gonna do halo again?
Yeah, you know what? I might just
I kind of want to play halo
Like I want to I kind of want to play halo. I might just play it
And put it on like a like a heart
What if I went back to halo right now? I feel like that's I feel like I can't do that today
I feel like I can't do that today
That's uh, that's like tomorrow
Do it with somebody else
Okay. Now that's fucking funny
Just do it do it just don't tell them don't tell them. Okay
Whoever is whoever does the halo campaign tomorrow
Do not tell them that like I got abandoned because they'd uh, no
It's as if we're starting it over
It's very important that nobody says anything
Call me
Ha ha ha imagine if I get a
Imagine I get another two hours go by and it's like, ah, I hate this. I have to leave
And I can never play halo
Oh, that's fucking funny
I'll never see the end of halo reach
Everybody that ever I ever try to play with just humors me for two hours and then doesn't want to play anymore
That's that's very funny
We'll see what happens tomorrow. I'll put a few lines out
That's making me laugh though
I'll throw a few lines up tomorrow. We'll see
That's so fucking funny. Yeah, that's me somebody that hasn't played it
Hey, yeah, I decided to play it. Wait, where are you gonna play? I heard you can play halo reach yesterday
No
No, I I decided uh, they were unforeseen circumstance. I know
And I don't want to tell them anything and I and I really I really think that
I might get abandoned again, and that's funny
What if I ask joel to do it again tomorrow?
Oh fuck i'm dead
What was the last thing I did?
I didn't I didn't even save it. Did I? Yeah, I did
Just play solo
I can use a better weapon. Give me what's six. I want this thing. Yeah, this is better
Isn't it great? So I remember keep this in mind. You got to keep this very much in mind
I have never played halos before
My first experience that was my actual first halo experience
That's like going to buy all the best ingredients from the cake store
You go to the best bakery in the in town
And then you instead of following the directions on the back of the cake mix thing with all the best ingredients
You just put it all into a bowl
Mush it up with your hands
Taste it say this tastes fucked up and gross and then throw it in the toilet
That's that's the equivalent
You're just sitting on the toilet
Right didn't get him. Oh my god. How can I not hit you?
Wait, what happened? What do you say? What do you say?
What do you say?
Joel's in the chat. He called you a toilet
What do you mean? He like he called he just called me a toilet
Or did he call me from the toilet?
I i'm confused
I didn't even say fuck
All right. I gotta focus. I guess this is a hard level hard level focus. Get out the grenade launcher
Oh, you are the toilet
All right big room opens
Got it. Wait, what what is he is he is he?
Even off even off stream. He's terrorizing my live stream
Even off even well off camera fuck that shield get down
I deserved it. I didn't do anything to deserve it
Let's play halo
everyone says
Jeremy you gotta try halo. Oh, it's so fun. What like it's like one of the best
Games ever this franchise is so good. I just wanted to play halo with a friend
That's all I wanted and then I was and then I was called names
two hours
Nostalgia goggles, but okay that might that might be true. Maybe I don't know but I don't have any of those goggles
I never I didn't I didn't play it
I don't own a pair of those goggles
I'm coming in with a pure
No bullshit attitude
No, like oh I did this already and it's that was fun. I know I got it
They're not the best games ever, but they're great
Yeah, we'll find out
when I
Convince somebody else to play it tomorrow
And pretend like it's the first time i've done it
Or no, uh, uh, here's the here's the play
I just load it from my game
That I heard and just say that I did a little bit of it off screen
right
That makes sense
He's still in chat
What do you what do you want from me?
Haven't you done enough?
MonkaS
All right this way this way this way say sorry
Since when do you have to apologize for things that you aren't real?
You're a booger streamer
Hey
easy
Wait, they never even played halo
No, that was halo reach
first ever experience
And you know what? I probably wouldn't have it any other way
All right water release
Good good good good good over here
I love the little spots to go in
this way
No
It was just a prank
I got ah, damn it
Damn it. I got pranked
Where's the camera? Where is it? Which one just point? Where's the camera?
Right there. Okay
How are you still awake? Holy shit
You're still awake
It's late
Joel is drunk. Wait, Joel was drinking?
Hold on. I
Joel was drinking
I don't play with streamers that drink. This is a i'm a dry channel
Why wasn't that not told to me before?
Actually kind of like annoyed by that in a way because why wouldn't somebody tell me?
Not be like serious like be serious
Was he actually drinking and and participating in a duo live stream with me?
I know maybe somebody came over from from Joel's stream, but we don't mess around with that
Next you'll tell me that he's listens to rock music
And then okay
Okay
I'll believe that when I see it. Bye. All right. Bye
Is this door open? Wait, don't open yet
Now he's saying bye, but he's he actually he's not leaving see right now
he's going to take a shower or going to the bathroom
And he brought his phone with him into the bathroom and this stream is still on and he's right now going like
But you'll never know that
I right now i'm on the floor at max volume
While he's taking a shower because he doesn't want to miss a second of germa 985
So he turns the shower on so it's very low pressure and turns the volume up and puts the phone on the ground
So it reverberates on the ground so you can still hear while you're in the shower
and then you get pissed off because
God damn it. I don't I I i'm watching this and
I'm thinking about just not cleaning myself to continue to watch this thing that i'm watching right now
And then you go. No, no, no, no, whatever. I'll catch up later and then you you know
Shower's too loud
You're gonna do that's why I propose the next big thing
Is gonna be
And i'm not talking about this is just for the rich like rich rich rich people. I'm talking about a monitor
Like that like an ipad style tablet that's in your shower
That is completely waterproof
And it's like 60 bucks
That's the next step
It exists. Yeah, but was it like a grand or something was it like two grand?
i'm, not gonna buy that
I would buy it if it was like 40 bucks
What's happening what's happening seeing a lot of i'm seeing a lot of laughing faces
Just put your ipad in a plastic bag
And what hold it?
Put your ipad in a plastic bag and hold it with you in the shower
Yeah, but that's messed up
Taking a shower with a monitor is normal
Taking a shower with an ipad in a plastic bag is fucking weird
No, if you have like i'm talking about if you had like a monitor like just in front of you
Where you you know, you got like your bar soap is right there
Next to the bar soap is you know, your hair conditioner your shampoo and then there's just like a seven inch screen
That's embedded into the wall
This is a bit. No, I mean I would want that
I'm getting one
Oh my god, there's a trap in here
You have to be rich
Uh, how do I get this?
And you didn't think I could do halo on fucking legendary
You know, I think it's possible
Hmm. This is me in my true environment
Look at that one hit
I used to believe but not anymore
This is a really good just kind of background game, isn't it?
The less I think about the game the better I do when I play it
That's it
Now I know a lot of people will definitely think that that was on purpose and I don't blame you at all. I really don't
Because of how perfect was that for me to say that and then fall off the cliff
I know that everyone thinks that that was on purpose
so the only way I can avoid from being called up being like a
Wow, nice like tuber joke you fucking loser
I'm gonna just say that I did that on purpose because there's no way I could say they didn't
And I didn't know where to start
Reverse psychology
I could prove why it happened, but it won't be enough. It won't be enough
I would never be able to get away from the sea
the sea of germa iq span and lul
It won't ever it'll be there and I will never be able to get away from it
Joel versus germa doom deathmatch I would win
I would win. Absolutely
You guys see I you guess I have experience so far, but
Do you really think that I I don't think you don't you don't think i'd be able to do that
Like did you see when I played I played dusk?
And I played it at the hardest difficulty and I did and I remember people in the chat going like holy fuck man
Like he actually is pretty good at this shit
Like usually he falls off the edge and you can laugh but not this time
Are you an egomaniac?
I don't think so
Is this a trap?
Wait, go down. There it is
All right. That is the gold key
bombs even bombs
Actually, you know what?
No one said that
I've
I have logs
Of every stream. I have a log of every single thing anyone's ever said here
if I type in
the exact quote
I didn't think he was going to be very good at this game. He actually is doing really well end quote search. Oh
41 results interesting
This is the gold door. Oh, wait, wait, wait, save it
Omega lol results
Whoa, he just went real fast
Excuse me. Excuse me
All right. What's your guys favorite weapon in the medieval?
Mine's the sideways sword
Or uh, also known as green door
Grenade launcher. That's pretty good, too. You're right
Wish me. Good night. Have a great night
Good night
And we're we're we're lost the way got you
Oh shucks. Thanks. You're very welcome
Have a great one the golf club
What's the golf club?
When I when you when yes when I sneeze you don't say bless you
I can't hear you sneezing
I don't know if you're sneezing or not
Get up here. Yeah, I opened the green door. So what?
Where do I go now?
Just say it every few minutes just in case
I mean that would probably work but
Did this open now?
I think I didn't press a button. I saw one and I didn't press it
No, it's this way
Germa am I am you okay?
Yeah, i'm good. What?
He's not all right
That's what he would say if he was not. All right
Oh shit
Joel's still watching. Yeah, Joel's phone at this point. He put it in his toilet
So the reverberations from the bowl in the water
Fill up the bowl and then it's like a big speaker aiming up like a satellite into the bathroom
He puts it in a plastic bag though. So it's fine. Don't worry
Wait, hold on need help
5g toilet
I mean you guys laugh, but don't you think the most important place for you to have
Better wireless coverage is in your bathroom
I'm going to be completely and totally real with you here. This is this is not made up. This is not a joke
My cell phone
Is used I would say me actually taking my phone
out of my pocket or
Just looking at my phone screen
happens
50 to 60 percent of the time when i'm sitting on the toilet
That's a fact
I need silver key
That's because
No, no, I just that that's just the only time I use it. That's that's the time where it's like, all right
What's going on right now?
I don't have to pay attention to anything
It's not like i'm doing something that's the time where I have that's my telephone time
If you've had a conversation with me on the phone
There is a very large chance that I was sitting on the toilet while I was talking to you
And then I get a little self-conscious about it because you can hear the echo of you're in a bathroom echo
And you try to mitigate that a little bit by there's different techniques you can use
Oh, man, it's time. It's time. It's time. It's time. It's time. It's time. It's time. It's time. It's time
Here we go
Keep going move move move move move who else you
Oh, I just fucking yeeted that guy
In quotes and brackets. He says that to be
Look like he's part of the younger generation
Okay, wait, I need that. There it is
All right back to that little pod
Well, i'm not allowed to say yeet
And why is that
Things I can't say some things I can say
What does this mean? That means it's like a secret over here, right?
It means yes
That's pac-man lol
You know, what's really weird about the word you just said lol
If I say lol
Everybody laughs at me and they go wow. Look at this guy trying to use lol. That's
That was like the internet slang when I was like younger
Why am I why can't I say lol
That's a word that I should I should be able to say that because that's like what we said
Well, it's old internet slang. Yeah
It means laugh out loud and if I say laugh out loud people go wow
He's actually he said lol and then I go. All right. Well, i'll do l u l
Get away from get away from me in my generation and I go fuck. Okay. Haha
That's sarcastic
No, um
I'm took I thought that was funny
All right, where's that silver door over here? There are rules
Who am I talking to?
um
Shit, I don't know
So what did that do?
Yeah, nobody in particular
I'm just sort of speaking
Oh, let me get it
I missed it. I missed it twice
I mean that would have been great if I got them all if I bowled it in the right
Oh, I did it zero secrets. God damn it
You're talking to yourself
What's the title of this frame?
right now
Oh
Reach with training wheels on
You could describe this stream as that
You could that was what this what that was
Okay title change the title to
um
Should I make the name the title see you tomorrow? That's kind of accurate
All right. How about um
play reach
How about just?
uh
hopping around
with
My stick no hopping around fps
fps indie game
old school style fps indie
game fps styled
shooter hard game
Wapping around
That's good
Wapping around is fine. Now. What am I at? All right, let's go
I like this level. This level's big
Is it difficulty on here?
uh
hard
Just on hard. I think there's one after it, but I didn't I couldn't find it
It's legendary
legendary halo
It's on baby mode. This one's not on baby mode
I can assure you
Prove it. How do I?
How do I prove that?
Any news on the king stream? Yes, I do actually do have something to say
it is on
schedule
So there was a thought that maybe it would have to be pushed potentially like a week or so maybe
But we're still on schedule
And next week is going to be the real
testing and setting up the white listing stuff
It's actually apparently according to what i've been told it's probably gonna be pretty easy to do
So they're working on it should be good to go
What do I think will happen?
uh, I have a few theories on what I think will happen on that stream, but
let's let them let's let them just let them be out there right just
I'd rather it happen naturally and occur the way that it was going to occur
Oh shit
Open
Oh, that's it. I need this
I haven't even used any of this
once
This is gonna be a month in the making for a five minute stream
I don't I don't think so
I don't think so
regardless of what happens just
just know
is uh
It don't matter. It'll be fun regardless
I would use yeah, let's just use it didn't kill him. What that should have killed all three of you
That's bullshit
Who's coming who's here?
How's the server info gonna work?
um
Not 100 sure yet and I don't want to give info that's inaccurate so
Next week around i'd say like six or seven days from right now. I'll have more
actual concrete information
So I don't want to be like, oh this is how it's going to work and it's like no that that is not
How it's going to work?
so
I'd rather give you the details when they're actually they actually exist
You need a king stream explanation. Sure thing
so
Uh, it is set for
December 15th is the first one
It is this it's going to be a potential series
where
the goal is to
Just exist in a town
Uh in a 500 to a thousand person minecraft server
concurrent connections
and the goal is for me to just exist as the king and for people to be uh loyal subjects
And if I die then it's over
so
And there are things in place that I don't want to talk about
to
People think oh wow, you're just gonna die in two minutes
Not so sure about that
It's not just i'm gonna turn the server on turn around and run in the direction
No, i'm gonna have personal bodyguards
There's gonna be an aging system in the game
Uh, where's this gold key? Have I not seen it?
And i'm told all this stuff that's happening is doing very well and it's on point and it's almost ready to go
How did I miss a key? Where did I miss?
this way
How do I open that? How do I get up here?
I had to have missed something
Minecraft. Oh this here gone
Minecraft boomers
Well, minecraft is the only game where this can probably physically work
I was looking at a lot of different titles stuff like
arc and conan exiles
Minecraft is one of the only games that would probably even have the capability to have more than three four five hundred people
In the same spot concurrently at the same time
And this is also the first one the first attempt to do this
If it works out well, and it's really fun this plans to add a shitload more stuff to it and do it like on a once a
week basis
Yeah, this like rust
gmod
But minecraft is so easily easily manipulatable with plugins and mods
That we figured it might be might be the easiest one to start with
And we're gonna go from there
Press this button. Yeah, and also everybody also does have minecraft like if
if
If you have a computer
And it's played a video game on it more than once you probably have minecraft on some account somewhere
It also doesn't take very much to run it. Uh, I need to get up there
How do I get up there? There's a button. Where's this? Where's the button? There's a button
Minecraft is very laggy
Yeah, i've been told
That there are going to be things to uh help mitigate that
I've been told there is a bunch of things to selectively render things and free up space
These these these guys seem to know what they're doing
We'll see
Look, it's a big experiment
But it's one that I I want to try
I feel like it could be fucking fun and hilarious. No matter what
He's been told by insider sources. That's correct. Who are these guys? They are minecraft
server and
mod plugin developers
That's what I refer to these guys. All right, let's get in that door
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa, where did you come from?
notch cameo
I'm gonna be surprised if notch didn't remember his minecraft password
No, no, there's no that's not a thing. Let me quell that
shit
I am an account
What is notch up to these days? Is he making any new games or anything?
He's living he lives alone in his candy room
What what do you mean you mean he had like a room willy he had a house willy wonka style made out of candy
like an edible home
Probably
I love that's not real but that answer to that is probably
Oh man, he took off my fucking head. All right, don't fuck this up
Give me give me the stick the stick. I want the stick
Give me the stick
No, the wrong stick. I don't have any ammo for the stick. That's why all right. I get it. Let's go
Room in here shit
two
Three
All right. Good. He beat halo. It was really good
Now I understand what the hype is all about
This room is moving now
Oh shit
Really kind of a short game
What was that an hour and 40 minutes?
I was I thought it was gonna be a little longer. Don't worry. We had we had the medieval backup
What really happened?
Oh, you may not have been here. Uh, joel hates halo
Uh
What really happened? You know any explanation as to what actually happened?
Can just get muddy to not even being real
That's the weird part
Any way to explain why i'm not playing halo reach right now could come off as not even real
Like oh, that's that's made up joke. That's a joke. Okay, that's funny
All right, this guy's pissing me off
Oh this place is stupid. Okay
Looking for a key
German turn on warrior mode it improves the game
What does it do?
Was it the latency?
Yeah
Yeah, do you want the real of the real answer?
the p2 the p2 pants latency was like a lot and clicking your mouse and firing the weapon happened like
like
Probably a half second after you did it
That's the real answer
Oh, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa, where where where where where?
Don't die here
please
I need that help
Oh, okay. These jumps are a little tricky
Didn't make it
The game has a bug where p2p has a lot of input delay
Yeah
So it's probably for the best
But still but still
Uh, can I make that jump? Let's find out
Well, we'll find out in a second
I didn't even get it. How did I not get it?
This my body's too big. My body's big enough to
I gotta make this out of
I'm gonna die. Just kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me
Okay, let's do this first
Where is it right here?
125 health wow 200 health actually. Holy shit. That was very that was very worth doing
Very much. So give me my stick
Bring me um here
That's the best boss ever in a video game
It's pretty close
All right. Now we're gonna do this again
All roads lead to this over clean up detail
Not today though. Where is it? Get oh shit
the original spill joke
joke
Where are you? Get up here
I knew I knew you I both of you I knew you were both coming from here and I still all right
My hand's getting stuck under my desk
Somebody knows what I mean by that
so
Uh, I have one of those pull out things under the under the desk that you slide in and out
And sometimes when i'm gaming really hard it pushes back in
So then I end up when I lift my mouth up it on the top
You know underneath the desk
When you're gaming really hard
Okay, this is gonna be speaking of hard
This looks like a really shitty room that I wish I had held on to most of my
Stuff I like to use
Because there are arrows just flying over here
Oh, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah
I gotta go right down a little
Don't block it back at me
Oh, never mind. I thought these were all enemies aiming fire arrows at me
I'm good
Is german like anime?
Uh, yes once a year look at that fucking kill
Once a year
I'm just kind of i'm just i'm chilling right now. This I feel actually I feel pretty good
You know, you just hit that kind of mode where you just you're just chilling
My utter and severe and sheer disappointment with playing with Joel is not I feel pretty great right now
Uh-oh
What happened?
All right. Here's what really happened. Oh my god
You know what? Let's see if we can get it
You should see my face right now
What are you doing over there?
He's face cam face cam tease
I don't want to pick that up
Should I though? I mean no, I that's a that's a free refill
Why would I pick up a free refill right now?
I don't think I maybe I can't come. I don't know whatever just get it
What?
I oh it's a fly. I can fly
Oh
I get it. There's a timer on this too
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on
I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do it
It's all right
Just wait for it to respawn
Sequence complete. Can I like leave?
What did that do?
fizzy lifting drigs
Well, not quite
up
I ran out of gas
I have like no ammo for anything
Excuse me
Oh fuck. I forgot I was floating
No, no, no, no, no you stop moving you die. Just stop moving you die
Let me pick up all this shit
I'll get it back immediately
I need ammo
5g wizard wand
That's the one
I like this room. I like this room, too
I like this whole level. That's probably my favorite so far
There's a lot of verticality
As they say right
Bounce it around and then
They do say that yeah, they do
I'm giving the wings
I like you. Hey, thanks
You're not so bad yourself
How does that sound?
Jeremy you have to be funny or your sponsor is watching
Why would my why would my sponsor want me to be funny?
Do they they only pay me sponsorship money if they think my stream is funny?
Imagine the rules imagine what that contract would be
Yes, uh, the ceo of the company's gonna come into your stream every time you stream and at least once he has to audibly laugh
In the office
Or we rip your contract in half
That's some weirdo billionaire shit
Hey Jeremy, i'm frank here with
In warrior mode, you don't keep your weapons on each level and each level has their own weapons
Oh, I see what you mean. So you don't get to just play with whatever you want. You have to get with what the level gives you
That's it
This is a boss
Has to be right?
All right, let's go
Solar saint
Oh, where's he going pick up everything got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it
Oh
Help I have 20 health
Where's he going?
Okay, where is he?
oh, man, that's
That was really
That was
If you touch it, you're dead
I'm not sure I even like that
I'm not sure I like that one. Hold on. Let's try this again
Maybe I should just buy this item
No, this ain't working. No, that's the right idea
Uh kill me, please
What should I use against him?
I feel like this is probably gonna do the most damage but hold on let me go this way
Yeah, this is it
And no explosions to kill me instantly
Help dude, this is a little quick little head bash. You can't get that close
When does he do it he's gonna do it now just run in a circle
Oh
Oh, fuck. Okay, you gotta back up
You gotta back up. It's all about backtracking
Don't run underneath
Maybe just run by him
Stop shaking my screen
My face is itchy. I don't know what to do. Fuck
Holy fuck he just I can't believe he just timed that perfectly that sucked
How did he time that how did he time that so well?
Oh, fuck. I got him. God damn. I collect all the stuff. No, it doesn't matter
So should I try warrior mode? Should I activate it? Oh, damn it. That boss took me 60 tries
Hey, thanks for being a quote. I can pull later
This looks like we have what two or three more areas?
All right, so warrior mode, huh?
I'll give it a try
Warrior mode start each level with only the x
Oh, you have to in every level you have to pick up the weapons would you look at that?
All right. Where am I going?
It gives each level a unique flavor
I like flavors
All right. Oh
Sacred path sounds good to me
That sounds good to me
Taste the level journeyman's way
Oh, okay. And look we get my favorite weapon right off the bat
It's it's our what a delicious green apple flavor. I'm so happy to have this
I love that artificial almost poison like taste of green apple artificial flavoring
The best green apple flavoring is the one that you can taste in your nostrils
All right, so we're uh, where am I going? Am I gonna die if I go in there?
The journeyman's way leads to the apostle's shrine. Um, that's cool, man
But how am I supposed to get over there take the big bridge?
Uh elevator
Well, I got another weapon
Oh wait
He's not aware. No, I'm not
Can I kill this thing?
Shout out to all the weirdos who like fanta green apple
Yeah, that that does make you a weirdo. Doesn't it?
Yeah, I that's a weird. That is a weirdo barometer. You're right
random
green apple fanta
Yeah, um
Green apple fanta. I don't think i've even ever had it before
But I know it probably tastes
Like a liquid cold version of a jolly rancher
the green apple jolly rancher
You know that exact flavor i'm talking about but I feel like it's thick and syrupy and shit and I wouldn't want it in my mouth
Gotta find a gold key
What do we open? What do we open here? Ooh?
There's a timer. There's a timer on this
gold door
Where do I go from here?
No, there's no timer on this
Fanta is exotic
Uh, I don't know about Fanta exotic
Right. I want to get that right here
I missed it. It's like I was trying to go around it
All right. So where the fuck do I go?
Am I there? I guess I could go up here. This is where I came from. I think I go
Where no this way no
No, no
I don't want this way. And this is this out the back entrance
Wait
I can go up here. Did that move the shit around on the sides? I think it did. Yeah, it did how do
Yeah, I moved a bunch of shit all over the place
We're good. This is the second bonus stream
Uh, it kind of feels like this whole week so far has been uh
Just wait bonus stream
That's been the first couple streams this week
What is that noise?
This is not a cannon week
No, this is week. This week is not you're right. It's not canon
Well, I mean, you know you yeah you could yeah, you know, it was it was
We played we played with joel today
And he was very very angry
Those who are lost never look upwards
Except for you because you're playing the game
That hurts
We heard joel scream today
screaming
So we oh, I don't really like this weapon
I don't like this flavor
See that if this thing is um
If this is like a green apple
This is like a crystal like rock candy
Crystal rock candy green apple
this thing
It's just like that sour paste like blue raspberry sour gel that you suck on
This stuff is gross
I would eat this
If it came down to whatever
I can't press this button
Blue raspberry is the best. Yeah, but not once that like gross gel
like
Oil that they put sugar in
And whip it up
It like uses cartilage or whatever the hell it is
Can I get up there? Oh, there's the key shit
Nothing to do. I can't get up there. This looks breakable. Can I blow this up?
That looks so breakable though, doesn't it?
What are my thoughts on sour candy?
I'm not a big fan of it
it's
I gotta undo that
Because sour is cool
But after you eat sour candy
you don't
You kind of just feel bad
for
Like at least 10 20 minutes after you eat it
Just something something feels off
The sides of my tongue
Underneath my tongue at the base of kind of where my jaw is connecting my tongue to my in my mouth
Is sore like I did a workout inside of my mouth
If I eat a really sour shit for more than a few minutes straight
Holy fuck this level is confusing
Uh
I think can I jump from
This is in here
Then we go we just keep going up
Don't kill me. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no stuck in the wall stuck stuck stuck stuck
Well, there's health here good. Of course you did that you fucking idiot
I don't even remember how to get up there load game
All right. Where's this person invisible? Where are you?
Oh fucking stupid fucking dumb idiot fucking idiot fucking dumb idiot
Now what did that do? The protectors cannot stand weapons of chaos
They can't stand it
Can't can't get them
Now what?
This is one of those puzzle levels, ain't it?
Well people spawned down here. So I think that's where I need to go
Right now what what did that button activate? Not bad
Did something else open down here?
Oh, here we go
No, wait, wait, wait, wait. I want to get up there. No, I don't that gold key got it
Holy shit
That's a lot of people the line streamer misses button
No, he didn't what the fuck was that? All right. I gotta get out of this. I got the gold key now
Let's go
Back up. Yeah
Damn it. I have to beat it up there. Don't I?
I gotta get up there. Go go go. I don't know which way it is. I don't remember
I don't know this way. I missed it. Have you tried spicy skittles? I don't know. I've not
All right. Well, I know where this is. No
Just go back down
Press the button
Beat it up there
Good. Look i'm smart
sometimes
It's not making me hungry
I think
If you don't talk, what do I go? No fucking god damn it. I started talking. I lost my opportunity now
I have to do this again. There's a little sliver right there
so smart
Hey
Distra you can be smart and get distracted
Being distracted does not equal low intelligence
It means i'm over here and then i'm over here and then i'm over here i'm over there and then i'm over there
Is there nothing up here?
uh
Now what? Freedom. I can't jump that high
I'm gonna go out to the main area. Oh, I got the key. I got the key key key key key key key key key key key
I got the key
Key is over there. You press the button and it takes you up you get to go across
I remember I got the key. Don't worry
Here we go open
Good. There's the sword
Nice
I I like I really do like this the best
I like the green apple
shards wand
It's the most concentrated
What the fuck was that?
It's just super concentrated damage. Can I walk on this floor?
Can I?
Nope, I mean I can but not for very long
Wait, oh
No shit, you're spawning
Get out of here
Uh, keep scaling it
Is that enough?
Uh, i'm gonna I gotta get it. I have to try to get that
Yeah, I needed to
run out of ammo
I gotta get that health, too
Look, i'm gonna play on warrior mode
And there's nothing else up here
I can there's probably a secret room
cool
Very very cool. I didn't bring oh
I don't know why I decided I didn't bring
What like a underwear towel? What am I talking about?
Derma, you can't just Derma I what what's wrong?
You're my I haha. Just kidding
What are you doing?
Unless what?
That's
In the last haha. I don't uh, yeah, you're doing that thing
You're doing that thing
Now I know i'm aware now
Silver key, there's the silver door
But wait
Fire makes the vine creature stronger
So don't use fire use electricity
The way is clear yet murky
All right. Uh, anyone know what that is?
That's out in the main hall and it's connected over there and I don't know. I'll find it
Oh shit
Auto flame
Yes auto flame
Oh, I wanted to ask a question
Does anybody have any experience?
with
dog
Ancestry dna kits
Are they real?
Or is it just pretend?
Sounds like bullshit
My co-worker used them and talked about it for months
No one knows
Human ancestry kits aren't real. No, I think if i'm dog ancestry kits, i'm by the way
I don't see the appeal
I don't for me
I don't want to send in
My like saliva or my blood to some company
And then they have a genetic dna profile
They have my genetic code
Well, why are they collecting this info? What are they doing with it? What are you doing with my info?
Twitch has that already
You think the twitch has my genetic dna makeup?
What what do you mean?
You can request the destruction of dna
The path before you must be you must descend
Oh fuck
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, i'm fine
White fire makes the foes stronger
Munkah
Should I have my own munkah s emote?
Would you guys use it if it was called germa s?
There we go
All the way up. You already have one and nobody uses it. Yeah, because the emote doesn't look bright. It's like tiny
It looks strange
Plus there's a close-up of it already. That's another emote
That that fear emote and mars
They're more surprised than they are scared
That's a disaster
Wait, I have to press that button. What hold on? Oh god. Dammit
You die
the heck
All right. This is a fail safe good
I thought it was a
I thought it was a straight run. I didn't I think it's I didn't see that there was no ground
Okay, I was blending it
nice
Keep going. Keep going. Keep going. Keep going
Pretty good spill joke
Whoa
Oh painful
This is not a place. I really want to be fighting anybody
I need health. Give me please
I am in a lot of trouble if I don't get any health right now
shit
Thank you
the giant
protects the way
Get a mini boss
Something like that
Who's left the giant? Is there a giant?
Oh hi on the corner
Yeah, there's a giant there's a giant there's a giant
I wonder if I should use explosives
Dammit
All right explosives
Did he just kill himself?
I think he just killed himself
He did a huge wind-up and just instantly died
I think he threw that into the wall and fucking killed him
Ah, how you guys doing tonight? What was the last time I checked in?
How's everybody?
You guys doing good? How you guys doing? For real you guys? How are things?
I'm done with classes
Until the 14th. That's good
Feels better watching your stream. Hey, thanks
Glad to have you
Thanks for watching
Oh boy
um
This thing
The bubble gun is the best the path opens from below. I'm sure it does and this is a big scene here
Oh
We kind of go
That dead so that that one opens and I go to there
Yeah, I just I just grinded them up
I feel like i'm playing overwatch again
This kind of hurts my eyes
One more did I not get the other one?
rock and stone torture
Get ammo. Yeah, I need ammo. You're right. I do I do I do you're right
All right, everybody in chat everybody in chat do your best winston impression go
Your imagination is the essence of discovery. It's fine. All right now do
What?
Holy shit. All right huge raid just came
uh
box box
Box box is raided with like 3 000 fucking people
What's up?
What's going on? How are you?
Welcome to the stream
Hopefully didn't say I was playing halo reach. Did it say I was playing halo?
Uh-oh box box. Did it say I was playing halo?
Keep doing impressions
No, thanks a lot
Welcome everybody
Uh, whatever you're doing on your stream. Hope you had a good time
we're playing a medieval right now, which is a
A first-person shooter old school indie
Uh almost an rpg. It's not an rpg. It's it's about moving fast
And if you ever played the game dusk, it's by the same publisher as dusk
It's not halo reach. It's not halo reach. No, I was
Until the person I was playing with abandoned me
And now I now i'm sad
But yeah, this is a medieval we're like, uh, maybe halfway through the game maybe something like that
All right. Now, where do I go? Where do I go?
But yeah, huge. Thanks box box. That's a fucking lot of people welcome everybody
I'm ready
I activated the two buttons
I missed a button
Fuck I was walking in the circle. What do I do? How about over here?
Did I just go all the way to the back of the beginning? No, I didn't did I? Yes, I did. No, I didn't
I'm going i'm like going all the way back. All right, go back
follower only mode
well
Yeah, follow holy, but that's that's just that's
What do you mean follower only mode lol?
Wait, what?
All right. How I don't even remember how the fuck I get back over there. It's a little tiny little thing
No, this is all right
All right. I'm paying attention trying to pay attention to the video game. I'll see you three two one go
Because the other way is this way
Got it. Joel turned your brain into mush
Dad, there is another one. You're right
Have a grenade
5g
It's that tower
All right. Now what opened from that button?
Back in the way. I can
I don't know. Ah, there it is. Okay, cool. That's what that's it done
You should get a 5g emote already. What would it be?
All right. I have it on warrior mode. This is gonna be interesting
I actually have to be good
Then get hit good. That's good. That's good. That's good. All right. I need a weapon
Just have it be three squares
Turned off follower only
All right. All right. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. All right. Hey, uh a mod turn off follower only for five minutes
What follower only?
follower only mode
Oh
Hey, hey
Welcome
Look at that ball. Look at all those box box emotes
Hey, thanks for the raid all of all of you have been
Has a of a muzzle on
Everyone's just trying to be like
No, no, no, no, never mind. That's uh, welcome to the stream everybody
But yeah, what's the emote?
There's a cool
Sword somebody's behind me somebody's behind me. I like this level but it's um
It's the verticality that causes me issues
I know that I said that's why I like the level but you can like something and not like it at the same time
andros
What the fuck?
No, I keep trying to I keep trying to quit that's not gonna work
new enemy type
fuck
Dude, there's a new enemy type. Fuck
Why does germa always embarrass us in front of other streamers?
So i'm gonna i'm sure I should go down
Is it gonna hurt?
I gotta lodge out
Get out of the water
Yeah, why can I not get out of the water?
Jump out of the water
Can I be cool?
for once
All right. What how do I do that?
All right. So you guys gotta give me some coaching here. So next time there's a raid that comes in
That's the first thing that I should say
What do you think?
Well, what do you think is like a good approach? What should I say turn the face cam on immediately?
Can you imagine?
If I didn't have a face cam on all of a sudden a raid came in a bunch of people came in like some of you
Guys that came over and I immediately just turned on the face cam. I'm like, hey, hey
I just pretended like it was on the whole time. That's just
Huh? Yeah, those for those of you that don't know this is a I don't do face cam on this stream
Unless it's my birthday
We do a face cam birthday stream every year
And that stream is 24 hours
I do a 24 hour birthday face cam stream
And I read letters that people send me
I get a stack of them. I gotta get up there
You can't even stream for six
I like the I like that person to check take a look at the data
My average stream time is between the six and a half to seven and a half hours
I'd like them to check the data. You could just check on that data
Should I go back down?
Wait a minute
Ah, there's a button over here, right?
But what does this do for me? I went up this elevator already
The visage of fire not is not to be trifled with
What does that do for me? I don't know any idiots here that can help me
Did I what remind me did I pick up a key?
All right. Well, at least I got that
Is there a way I can check my keys?
Is it the silver key? Maybe I just don't remember
There are no idiots here. I know
Sucks sometimes man. I just wish there was like stupid people here besides me
It sucks
silver key
Go back in the hole
I could go this way
Show the slap clip
I'm surprised you guys weren't quicker on that one
That's usually the first thing that happens
Finally my favorite item. Yes
They spammed us like 30 times did they?
Oh shit, that's what I get for not paying attention anything fish in here
I haven't saved in a long time
No, don't touch that
All right. So this is
Probably get the person. Ah, there's the key right there. Damn it. All right. How do I open that?
Can I swim up maybe?
Well, i've just I got it. Whatever
There we go. But what about down here?
This is light coming from
It's a fish
No filter what?
You guys have to keep linking shit from my birthday
All right made it wait
I need the gold key. Ah
I need the gold key to get in here
I need that key. I gotta
There's probably an activator I can do over here
Scream if you see any buttons
the reflection of water
Only shows the surface
No shit glass will cut you
I know
Damn it. I don't see anything. Do you guys see anything?
Don't get smart on me. What are we talking about?
I don't see anything
I can't go back down. Where's the deep end?
Oh, there it is
Like I just got that. I got it. I got the key. I picked it up. I got it. I have it
All right
I I would not have found that we've been here for a long time
All right, open it
Are we still in his follower on the mode off?
If we put it back on we have to make a joke quick
What do I do?
What should I say?
Turn off slow turn. Okay turn off follower only turn off slow mode
Now you're asking too much. You're asking way too much
Wait
And wait, is it the anarchy is on again?
No, no, no slow mode. No follower mode
This is dangerous
Dangerous waters are crossing here
I'm gonna die
Oh, by the way, this is on hard
Those of you that are wondering give me more. All right, what's the what am I going to eat today? What do you think?
The first thing that somebody says in chat. I will eat it as long as it's actually edible
Anarchy can't eat that
So is it pizza? No, i'm not gonna do
Wings. Eh, no, i'm gonna do it
Need a ghost pepper. No
Big chicken. Hmm
No, no, no, no, nothing. No fast food today. Nothing. No fast food. I don't want that
sushi
now
No, no, no raw food. Not right now
low-made and general chicken
You're almost there. That's pretty that you're almost there. That's close
Pad Thai
I would say that that is probably accurate
Very accurate out. Yeah, that's accurate
nice work
Yeah, excellent job
That sounds fantastic
Oh, I can already I I can already see it on the plate steaming
It's so hot
If I when I just slurp up the noodles it just they whack me all in the fucking mouth and it's like fucking burning me
But it's where it's worth it
Uh, I can't go through there
I don't think there's anything else. I don't want to jump around on these things. It gotta be a button to press
down here
Didn't do this yet. Did I?
Well, I guess we're going up. No, we're not. What is this for?
Button is that for
Yeah, I want to show up on stream tomorrow with just these small
thin
red
Lines all around my mouth
And those are just like noodle burn marks from me just going too fast and eating it too when it's too hot
That way that way that way that way. No
Yeah, I'm just going in here. Fuck it
That moves
That's my birthday tomorrow. It's my birthday tomorrow. So we're gonna do a face scan tomorrow. Happy birthday
What's wrong with me? What's going on? Why am I getting hurt by it? Oh, it's fishes in here
Give me this
All right, three more to go apparently
So where those are, I don't know
And those one up there
We can just go like this
Two more
There it is one more. It's up there
Ah, you gotta get that one exact. Don't you?
Buy us a cake
No, I have to get this
Damn it. It's gonna be perfect
There it is. All right
So sequence complete that means what exactly?
We want ice cream instead
It's this turn
Oh
That's what that did cool
Turned on the fountain
That'd be a really expensive birthday
when their tv show about they've exactly what we're describing having like 5000 people go to a birthday party with a bunch of stuff and cake and
like
ponies to ride and
There was a thing about this. It was a tv show
It's called like my big birthday. What was it? It's on like mtv or something
And these people spent like seven or eight million dollars on their kid's birthday party
My it was my yeah my sweet 16, right?
That's what it was
Oh, I did it in the same fucking spot concentrate. Damn it
Yeah, that celebrities would come perform
At their birthday parties in a private concert
I'll tell you this right now
There's no I would never
I would never go. Okay, it's a somebody's house and do like a private germa stream
When that I think that would be sort of strange
Well, how would I how would that work? Why just get go in your house and set up a computer and just stream from your house?
You would what if you were paid? No, I don't think I could do that. That'd be fucking weird
But but where do you come in?
What's your what's your play on this? What is this?
Do you watch
the stream from a different room
You just have your ipad and you're just watching it from another room
How much money are you gonna give me for this what what how how much should I be charging for that?
$5,000 I'd rather you just buy a car for your
your
Just go buy a go buy a car
a
$5,000 car
Hey, you can probably get like an old honda civic
Those things gonna have like two or three hundred thousand miles on them and still run like they just came out of the factory
I would know
All right, then here's how I would do that
I would do that for a
$5,000 mcdonald's gift card
And those of you that are asking I can't that's impossible. You have to call and special custom order that
And if they if they won't do it for you, you have to find a way
You have to call corporate and somehow put $5,000 on a mcdonald's gift card
My civic has 208 000 miles on it or something, right?
You you get it
You get it
Did I fall off in the worst possible spot?
I did didn't I?
What's that?
Omega lull ruined
The streamer owns a civic laugh out loud
Uh, yeah, that's not what you said. I'm paraphrasing
Oh super
but
All right, save it here 29 health. This is bad
Ask and you shall receive can this streamer drive a stick? No
and
Why would I want to?
Let me let me demonstrate the life of a stick driver
Imagine doing that for like two hours straight
Imagine you had imagine you was stuck in traffic for like three hours
Everybody i've ever been in a car with a drove a stick
It's just like it was a full-time job to drive that car
Guys I have problems turning on the wipers in my car. You think i'd be able to drive a manual
I've driven the same car for a long time and I still
Still when it rains which uh, what what setting does the one how do I go halfway?
So it only goes the blades go up and down every like half second. I don't I don't know
I'm just gonna guess until I get the way that I want it
You think I can handle a manual?
Oh, he just directs him with that god damn it
That sucks
I headshot him. That's the only man saving
You wonder what am I actually what hey, I have actually a pet peeve for automobiles. Would you like to hear it?
You guys want to hear it? Yeah. Okay, i'll tell you
so
when somebody has
a horn
That is not a regular horn
everybody knows what a car horn sounds like
when you have a car horn that just goes like
Universal everybody knows what that sound is
When somebody has a custom car horn
You i've heard it. I feel like my car exploded when I hear somebody use a custom car horn
If they're near me
And it's like uh, it's just like something's i'm gonna get hurt
or like
It's like
I it freaks me the fuck out man. It scares the shit out of me
And nobody's prepared for it this one time I pulled up to a red light
And i'm not even kidding
The guy held his horn down and it was the peewee herman lab. I don't even know how the fuck you did that
fake fake
fake
He left this place, but what?
Holy shit, that is insane
Well, that wasn't the actual peewee herman lab. No, okay, you got me but it sounded like it it was like
I can't even do it
It was like
It was crazy
it's like
And then they they beat it really quickly. So it was like
I was like that's peewee herman
Literally right next to me
Can I get some goddamn help? What if it was just peewee out the window? I don't know
Somebody's doing drive-by peewee hermans
No, it was definitely their horn
And they may have had a regular horn that just sounded like shit
Or I may have dreamed this
I don't know
I got fucking dead
Shit, I didn't know you were here. No, I walked into it again
Softlock? No, just don't get hit
See now here's a follow-up question to those of you that have any idea
Are there any laws or regulations on what you can and cannot have?
For a custom car horn if you spent the money to have one
Could you have
Like for instance like a like homer simpson
Like a doe could you have that?
Actually, yes
So on in what legislation did they have to write down?
A wuga is okay and like
Is okay
That's how that's written down somewhere like submarine going down
That somebody had to write that right? So what's another what are other ones that are illegally allowed to have?
the awuga clause
a police siren
Uh, that's not
Why what if it's my custom car horn? I just want everyone around me to think there's some fucking emergency
You can't have a train horn. What did I open that came down something came down that I wonder
What is a lot? I need to look this up after the stream
What custom car horns are allowed and are there only two of them?
Okay, wait every motor vehicle when operated by a highway
Must be equipped with that. I didn't see it
Look up right now
Oh, you you actually mean look it up right now not look upright
okay, um
What is legal for a custom car horn?
Existing law require a motor vehicle when operated upon a highway to be equipped with a horn in good working order and capable of emitting
Sound audible under normal conditions from a distance of no less than 200 feet but prohibits a horn from emitting an unreasonably loud or harsh sound
This does this does not say anything about homer simpson
Laws on car horns. Hold on
Okay, so the law today
Yeah, yeah, it is it is it is illegal to use a car horn for any purpose other than to express warning
In the state of washington for instance
The law reads the driver of a motor vehicle shall when reasonably necessary to ensure safe operation give audible warning with his horn
But shall not otherwise use such a horn when upon a highway
Well, this is this is bullshit because drive by literally any local politician
uh
Group of people holding signs
Yeah
Hey, yeah, I agree with you. That's not real. It has to be on there somewhere
Penalties
Do you know anyone who has ever been busted for honking?
Probably not can you get arrested for like using your horn when you're not supposed to this doesn't say where's the homer simpson line though?
custom car horns
Can you replace a car horn? No, this is how to fix a broken car. Is this even on the books?
I don't know about arrested. This is important though
Are train horns illegal in my state?
There isn't one as long as it isn't extremely loud and it yeah as long as it's used to alert others
If you're impersonating emergency vehicles or breaking sound laws, then yeah
Okay, but what if I had a perfectly legal sound?
audible level of
Let's say
gordon ramsay
Saying like fuck off
Is that could is that does that like is that a loophole?
You could argue it but a cop might stop you
All right. Where do we go this way this way this way up? I can't go through what?
All right. I gotta pay attention. No more car horns. What if it was what if you did what if you did the dark souls?
Hey, hey
And by the way
why
This is important. This is important discussion. Why is there only a horn to say?
Fuck look out and why is there not like a you go ahead or a
Hi or a be careful. Why how come there's only one horn why this shouldn't be like two or three different horns
like a gentler one that's instead of being like
it's like
What what and that means something that's not like a hard horn like hey, you can go ahead you go first or
your
Your brights are on yeah, just something that's softer and nicer
Where the fuck am I going? Um, all right, I think down here
There's a fish in there
Flash flash your lights, but you could distract somebody that way
if it was very clear that like the
Was something very light and like oh, hey, you gotta turn your lights on or
Where should I go?
Go to bed scream out your window
No enough people do that already
I'm turned around here. I gotta go the right way. All right, found it. Okay, I found it
He's like people yelling at each other screaming out the window and shit, but that didn't solve anything
But you never you're never gonna see the person ever again. You'll never see that person again
Like you know, you're a fucking idiot. You know that
Okay, i'll never see you. I will never see you again. Like I don't that that carries no weight on me
See for say see you in court
Those doors are gonna open
People behind the wheel
Something happens people go people go fucking nuts when they're like operating a car
We already talked about like the speed thing
But let's refresh for those of you that weren't here for the class
When people go like 20 miles per hour over the speed limit
And they get to the same red light as you
it's just like don't I wish there was a horn for like
Like told yourself
Like oh look look how far that got you
Why can't there be a horn that that everybody knows is
Look how far that got you. I would love it
I would use it fucking all the time
Oh, I had to like change lanes like
Rip around you know
Oh is that your car
It in the at the same red light as me and i'm driving normally
I imagine that person just sitting behind the wheel just gripping the wheel going like fuck
Fuck
I feel like those people don't want red lights
Why can't I just drive through this?
I just want to just let me go. I don't care
and then like
They just blow a fucking snot rocket like in the bottom of their own car. That's what I pictured
And they try to get out the window
They rolled the window down
They're trying to blow a fucking snot rocket out the window and they miss and they hit they hit the same spot
Where the handle is for the door that they've hit
50 times already and this just stains there from them trying to do that
Go fast. Oh, there it is. Oh, I gotta go fast. All right, hold that thought you have the rovers living in your head rent free
I don't know. It's i'm telling you something happens to people when they like get wild on the fucking wheel
And I feel like that same person if you were to bring this up to them
In a conversation about like and you and you don't know that they're like one of these like crazy drivers
They would say the same shit
They'd be like, yeah. Yeah, I really hate that. I really don't like people speed value and scream out the window and blow snot rockets
It's just it's just not okay. It's not okay
You're you it's you
Well, it must then it must be you because you're talking about it i'm the one doing it
Hey dude, i'm high as fuck. All right
Good to see you
Oh, right. I don't have my weapons
Saved did I save it yet?
Living in your head rent free
Yeah
Because what it happens you're like what the fuck is wrong with this person?
Dude, I have seen so many people drive around
Remember remember the two places that I have been living in in my life
boston
Like east coast and then las vegas
I've seen so many people on the highway just fucking ripping around lanes driving like a psycho
screaming at each other
Cutting each other off
playing cut off tag
With each other. It's like what the fuck are you people doing?
Have I you've never had road rage before
Oh, i've been i've had like my share of i'm upset at something going on and on the road
But never like i'm upset at something going on in the road
So now let me accelerate to at 30 miles per hour over the speed limit and overtake three people
While I blow snot rockets on my windshield. He's obsessed with this
This one I just want goddamn safe driving I just want safe drivers
It's even worse when you pull up behind those people
And they've got those stickers on the back of their car that show I how many children are in the family
Oh, yeah, there's me there's dad and there's there's one two three four children. Oh
Are you in the car now?
What do you okay? How many children are in? Okay, I gotta start shooting things
Oh, this is tricky
I need silver key
Remember that these guys are hard to melee
Silver silver remember silver silver
Anything I missed down here?
What stock superpower is the best?
uh
well, there's there's a lot of loaded question because
Is this superpower that you have that you're the only person that has this superpower?
And if you choose flying all of a sudden you become
Like public enemy number one. There's a person flying and we have to do something about that person
Or is it like we live in a superhero society?
Just like we're in a superhero
world
uh the best stock power
No, it's not. It's not invisibility. It's not
Guys, you could if you're invisible you still die
Like if you're invisible, you can still step on a landmine
So no, you still die. I would say
I'm dead. Yeah
Like hypo just said time control
And nothing too extreme. I just mean like
being able to rewind
maybe like
Maybe like like 10 minutes
Right 10 minutes you just can you you can make the universe go back 10 minutes whenever you want
Nothing bad happens. It's just you have control over this device that makes it so the whole world rewinds 10 minutes and nobody knows
You know how many times i've like left my wallet somewhere or like oh fuck my keys are in just rewind and just grab them
Or like if you ate something that you didn't want to eat and you didn't like it if you went to the menu
And you said okay. Here's um, uh
I want the steak, please and you order you get the steak and you eat it and you don't like it
Just rewind and order something else
You seriously wouldn't want that power to go to a restaurant and be able to eat and then rewind to pick something else
Okay, adam sandler, by the way adam sandler is up for an academy award probably
So all of you adam sandler haters out there just know that that dude is
Is going to potentially win the best actor of the year award
Go look it up
You think we're in the darkest timeline?
You a lot of you guys talk a lot of shit about mr sandler
And now he's up for fucking one of the most coveted acting awards potentially
that exists
Okay, i've got i gotta kill these fucking things. I need ammo on a weapon
There's no weapon ammo line around here. These guys can just aim and shoot
He's not gonna win
You know what?
I kind of hope he does
In in some weird way. I hope he does
I hope adam sandler wins best actor
You know those like events that people say is the event that happened
That really crossed us over and that was the turning point
Adam sandler winning best actor at the academy awards might be that event and I can't fucking do this
Turn around
What turn around?
That's that's the start of the world ending events
No, i'm just gonna go buy them
It was open
God give me a break
um
Shit sure, but joel is behind you
Is it wait what happened over here? This is this the turn around thing?
Turn around turn around
Oh
That's what I did
I get you now
He's still here
Wait, is joel bit? I talked a lot of shit about joel. Is he still here?
Yes, he's still in the bathroom
No, he definitely left the stream on and fell asleep. It's like six o'clock in the morning over there
Should I try to wake him up? All right, i'm gonna wake him up. I'm gonna wake him up
No, i'm not gonna peek his mic
Okay
You ready? Let's see if this works
joel
Joel joel get up. It's time for school
You're late. You're gonna be late to the bus joel joel. The bus is coming. You're gonna be late to the bus joel
Get up. You're gonna miss school
For the second day in a row, you're gonna miss school joel get up. Oh fuck. I didn't know this is gonna be this intense
Oh and anthony anthony anthony wake up anthony wake up. It's time for school
Just for anybody named anthony in the chat here
There it is. Save it. Do me next to me next to me next to me next
Oh get up. They hit me
No, it hurts it hurts it hurts it hurts
Save fortnite
fortnite why who cares
Um overhealed
Would you guys be mad at me?
Tell the truth freely. Would you guys be upset with me?
If some random billionaire paid me a million dollars to stream fortnite 10 times in a row
Would you guys be angry if I did that?
Would you be upset with me?
All right, any millionaires here?
You ever think how many okay, how many people here do you think are millionaires?
Do you think if there's like let's say there's 36 700 people here
Statistically speaking how many people here are a mill have a million dollars in their bank account right now. What do you think?
Okay
There's definitely a millionaire in this chat and they're sitting there going like talking about me. All right, don't say anything
Don't say anything
favorite weapon
Not me
It's it's only jerk. It's only you
Haven't we already gone over this? I don't have a million dollars
And if I did you think I would tell you about it?
I don't know. We already went over this
A million dollars just came in
one million
Jeremy, how about I pay you not to play fortnite? That's from volemme. Thanks for the million dollars volemme
Seriously, that's a lot of money. Thank you
Uh, don't worry your money went to good use. I will not i'm not gonna be playing fortnite
You did it
You're welcome. You're welcome
You live in vegas. Yeah
I do
What is that? Oh, you know what I was gonna do. I didn't do it though
Because i've done that like three i've done like three or four times this stream already
Oh, that's a lot of acid. I died. I just comboed myself
All right, what's better? Come on. What the fuck?
I need a break
Oh, this one sucks ass
Oh, this sucks ass
I have to stay at range on this one
i'm gonna say
I'm just gonna launch grenades
From a safe distance like here
Ah
What the fuck did you throw like a water gum at me? What the hell was that?
There's a power up over here
Oops, I already had one kill me kill me kill me just kill me
I already have one let's do lightning. Oh, all right now get in there
help
Whoa
Are we good?
Damn, that was tricky
Now you're gonna press all these buttons, huh?
Oh is fishing here
You can rocket jump
Yeah, but I i'm terrible. It's not I can't do it
I'm, not sure if you were here like a half an hour ago
So maybe 45 minutes ago, but I was trying over and over again to get this to work
I couldn't get it to work. So I I was getting so fucking just actually not even like joke angry. I was just getting like
I just like not I wasn't feeling it and I was gonna turn the stream off and shit. So I just figured
Just don't don't even get that far, you know
I just feel myself getting actually just truly annoyed and it was just like
This is not fucking the way that I want to be
So I just I just gave up on it and I said I wasn't gonna try it anymore
And I know that I know that I lost a few people today with just how fucking
Seriously, just how annoying and angry I was and I I know
Two or three messages came in about like dude
Like that's just just you need to shut the fuck up and chill out
And i'm just like I told him to shut up and shit and it just got ugly
Now like after like 40 like an hour later, so it's just like I shouldn't I shouldn't do that
Web of lies. No one knows what's actually real. No one knows what's actually real
They don't know which way we're going
All the while the water's flowing
Is it raining? Is it pouring?
And it's certainly not showing
any charge that
What if I just fucking started screaming that
You gotta get him with a tube get him right in the hands
What's with the explosion?
Get the fuck out of here
All right, these guys seriously
They they're they take too much damage
Cool. Oh boy. This is a room
Oh, this is a room
Kill kill kill kill kill kill
kill
Uh, oh who's spawning in here?
Fucking andro space
I'm dead. What's the last time I saved the fuck go down
They can't come to the water. They're like bees
Yeah, oh, okay
Through them through them
Good night, germa. Good night
Thanks for hanging out. Maybe we'll see you again
It's dark over here
All right, andros's get ready
cool
Imagine coming back. Yeah, imagine coming back
You guys you guys you guys have fun. I don't do I have another soul drainer thing
Already damn, okay
Hey
tape
What the fuck you're still alive
um
I haven't been streaming that long
started later
But i've only been streaming for five hours or so
Come on anymore enemies
Spawn something hurry up
spawn something
How's my chest doing tonight, um, i'm all right i'm fine
i'm okay
I know the way that I just said that made it seem like no I did not
No, what i'm starting to do is i'm starting to do some uh
some stretches
So i'm specific to rib and back
costochondritis
Stretches and I got this little device
that helps you put it under your back and it helps uh stretch out your muscles and
You lie on it for a little while. I'm gonna try it and see if it helps
Also, well at the same time
Uh, i've got like other appointments to go to and everything but
It is not quite a foam roller
It's almost like a little wedge
That you have to kind of lie on to help stretch your back
All right, somebody just wrote something so
fucking crazy
I can't even
All right, here comes
A I don't know boss fight maybe no possible. Where are you all the way over here?
Testicles in stomach
Yeah, I have to have this I have this uh condition guide guys called costochondritis
Is when your testicle sucks up into your stomach?
Yes, that's what it is
You don't even have to google it to know that it's not true, but you don't have to have to do that
I googled it for you
That was the thing people were saying, uh the other night the pilgrims what?
Stop i'm trying to read
Get out of here. Oh my god, go back to tekken
What's that character's name bill?
The pilgrim path. No, it's like seven pages long. I can't I don't want to do it
Billy tekken
Whoa, you guys take a lot of explosive damage
Oh, no, he shot earth
Does that mean i'm huge?
How many you got in here?
You're gonna you're gonna fuck up my save state
Why am I killing these guys? I don't know
Why do you kill anybody in any video game?
It's because the computer decided that they were gonna be in front of you and they were a monster that you are
a bad guy
Oops
We're good. Uh, let me show you this way
this way
This way looks pretty ominous
What's over here? I was just here, right?
Yeah
I can't see shit
Good who else
Hey, wait, hey, hey, hey, hey, somebody just said game sucks. That's not fair
Why did you say that? That's not true
What's your reasoning what's your reasoning the floor is yours
I think that was the death
That's it
They don't say anything else. They just come in and say that
What's this gonna do?
What did that do? Oh, well did that?
Uh, we're up
Just running around and attacking things
You know
They don't make them like they used to anymore. They don't make them like this anymore
They don't make them like this anymore where you're just you're dead
It's just a game and I need to stop fucking like making little jokes
And get back up there
Those these guys live here. Why are you doing this?
Because it's like an evil castle or something with like demons and shit
Yeah, demons live in hell
What's the point there?
Load your quicksave am I am I fucked right now?
No, this is the the
Where's the elevator come down?
It goes down to where?
Where's that elevator?
Hold on. I'll get another 30 seconds and i'm gonna load the quicksave
30 more seconds
Hold on. I know it's like I can get there from here. I think
No
Stop wasting ammo too. What are you?
Insane
All right. I think i'm almost there
I'm gonna get there just in time
I'm gonna go
That was a bad idea
And now i'm way worse than I was off before
Everybody else left alive
So that's the way we gotta go
What's down here? Ooh green candies
One more out of both. How could you not like it?
It's got candy
I think the best part about this game is probably
I like how the weapons
The variety of weapons is pretty good
I think my favorite weapon is probably the
Thing i'm holding right now
But they're all good
Found it
somebody
I think I went this way already. Oh, there it is. Holy fuck. I almost just died dude
If I remember if I was standing over there it'd be like Neptune Mars Pluto
Mars
Uh, I don't know green
Nothing else up here. No sequence. Can we get an actual Neptune? You already have it. It's the worst emote on the channel
I know that's very debatable. But still that's a pretty hot topic
If you truly think that germapop is the worst emote on the channel, I i'm sorry, but we completely disagree
it's so much so
that I
That's like you telling me that almond joy is your favorite candy
I'm gonna say this
What are you talking about? Like like Reese's peanut butter cups exist. That's not possible. We just will never agree on anything
boss time
This kind of just looks and smells like a boss
What does that say?
You are being watched. I know
But by how many people do you know? Yeah, this is a boss
All right. Here's the deal
I know I hold on
This is going to be the last thing I do on the stream today. We'll see you tomorrow after this
For I don't know. Maybe maybe I'll convince someone to play halo
maybe
I don't know
It's possible
um
There's also
I'll be here before the stream starts tomorrow. There's a couple of games that i've been waiting to play
We'll see if I can get somebody to maybe play it if not if maybe i'll just
It's such a sour note at this point that like a halo I go
It's just I think it might need to exist as that whole it might just have to exist
That way. Oh, yeah, I also have a device. That's interesting that I want to play with
We'll see
I'll just do the campaign solo. Yeah, I might just like I don't know. We'll see it's gonna it'll be a game time decision
We'll figure it out tomorrow
But i'm still doing this
The corrupt spirit. Oh, it is an eye
A lot of health. Oh boy. All right
I think i'm just gonna dodge
I didn't have enough. Okay, you know
Ow
Am I even hitting him?
Ow, he's just throwing fucking cinder blocks at me
Ow, ow, ow
You can't really dodge him either
I think I just have to stand still and like just go back and forth like this
That's the play
What's phase two?
Is there a phase two?
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it. Damn it
oof oof oof
Did I actually get hit by that fucking thing?
Oh, man
I'm out of ammo
What do I have any ammo for any weapon?
I don't this is really bad
run away
Oh, I have to go up
Ow, please
No
Ben, how are you actually getting those in here?
I actually would rather be up here. This is a good spot for this
All right. I'm staying up here
Let's heal and let's use these
Are they reaching?
Here they come
Give me some help
Is he burning me?
He's putting fire down
Shit that hurt
Oh fuck this fire everywhere now. All right. Don't fuck this up. This took a long time
Oh fuck
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, no
Did it just don't die
Star of torment
I didn't even know this existed. I probably would have should I should have picked this up
Would have helped
You can die. I guess this doesn't matter the level's over
All right, get out
What about a secret though? I may have missed a secret
Not like it matters
I don't have I gotten one secret on any of the boss fights. I don't think I have
That's for another playthrough
And let's go
No secret
killer
Scholar
See you guys something not to read this stuff would you get achievements for it?
There are two more areas to do
I'm not gonna lie
I kind of like it medieval
as
A yeah, we can just keep playing that and just keep like slowly finish it. I like this
Up at the next time I play this it'll probably be over. It's a pretty fun. Just chill game to play
What are your first impressions? It's pretty it's good
Arcane expanse is the best area
It's a time for cleanup detail. No
No, we'll just look we're gonna start fresh tomorrow
If you missed the first part of this stream, it was a absolute shit show
But in somehow the best possible way, I think
It was a fucking disaster
But uh, we'll see you tomorrow
Thanks, uh again for uh box box for the raid if any of you guys are still here
Thanks for coming. Thanks for sticking around
See you tomorrow
What happened? We I just got here
uh
It's it's it's it's impossible for me to explain
the first two hours of the stream
it's kind of just
It was just it was
A wonderful disaster. We'll put it that way
Thank you for the halo diarrhea. You're very welcome
All right. Let's uh, let's call it a night
Start fresh tomorrow
Thanks for watching good stuff
Hey, let's just check it and see hey, who's top sub gifter richard nixon. Yep
Top bits I like to relish and top bits, too
Uh, I can't even read it. It was too small
Richard nixon. Thank you. Richard nixon for always giving 50 subs to stream somehow
I
I don't know. All right, let's head back to the
bits
Those of you that don't know
If you are a new viewer, I do not read
Subs or bits or donation or bit messages during the stream. We do it at the end
Let me just hang out for like 30 to 45 plus minutes and just chill and talk
That's how it works
Let's go back. Thank you to sad vega
for the 300 bits
Howdy germa just doing that reminder that we'd love to go through some emote options with a vote sometime
Still really looking to hold out for that weird emote of where they photoshopped the eye. So you looked
So, oh, yeah
Yep
The one that I thought was a real picture during the thing
Yep, it's a great picture. It is
It has to be an emote. It will
Thank you though
Lazy look. Thanks to the 250. Hey
Hey, how are you? That's it. Hey sad vega again for 300 bits. Thanks sad vega
I've said it before and i'll say it again house cleaning stream when
Just go pro it and clean your house
You seem to love vis or cleanup detail so much
You could easily make a joke video of you just cleaning a place with a mop and a bucket and chat would eat it up
Honestly, it doesn't even have to be your house. You can make like a joke studio set where you screw up
I think we've actually talked about that stream before
Of just cleaning a house on stream
What that's but it
Every time I think about how funny something like that could be
Like yes, imagine a scenario where I rent out a studio
And just make it just a dirty office or just like a dirty living room
Make it all dirty. So then I just clean the room
That stream would take
Hours to make it dirty and then hours to immediately clean it up would be so fucked up
But it would be fun
Maybe for a little while
vis or detail warp. Yeah
No, there's a lot of things that are in front of that that need to get done first before something like that would even be thought about
two or three fake rooms
Yeah, have like a fake house, but then I would rather just do the sims thing
All right, I told you about that how I wanted that
Just make in a studio
A big fake house and you guys control me and it's i'm just it's sim
I have to like pee and shit
I have to be I have to be like social I have to go do things. I have to like call people on the phone and stuff
We talk about a lot of weird shit here, but some of them actually turn into streams
Hey flug boy. Thanks for the 250
I honestly saw this from a fucking millennia away when you said joel was playing with you
I knew this was going to happen. I knew joel would have the attention span of a goldfish
But I love you both for this. Thank you for the stream reach is probably like one of my top 10 games of all time
That's so funny, I love it he foresaw it they both have the same attention span
Yeah, you just gave you gave two children the keys
But thank you flug boy. I still had a lot of fun
Hey grapple mace. Thanks for the 250. Jeremy, please play picross again sometime
Well, depending on how the stream goes tomorrow
You know this this this home. This might be an entire non-canon week
Depending on what happens tomorrow. We'll see
filler content week
We'll see the extended universe
I love picross. It's like it's one of my favorite
Lie down with your nintendo ds and do
It's like the reason why I even owned a ds was to play picross with the little stylus on the little screen
I didn't play a zelda game on that thing. I didn't buy pokemon
I did not own pokemon. I did not own I just
I bought it for picross
And there was another game too
What did I play on the ds sometimes?
Play pokemon tomorrow or riot lose 95 percent of your viewer base
If you're still here after the last two streams, I don't think I would lose 95 percent of you
Yeah
Let's be honest
Let's go. That's it. Let's get out of here
No, actually i'm i'm of the opinion that I I thought I thought the last two streams in a row were like
Fun like really fun, even though there was like a diarrhea
I thought I just I still had fun as the thing
Thank you post for the 500 bits
Has everyone been watching since the early tf2 days and you never failed to make me laugh
Your huge inspiration to me
as another guy with adhd
While I do respect it seeing you make the decision to move
To hospice care after your hernia really hit me hard. Here's to you
Jeremy will never forget you
Thanks a lot. Appreciate it. Thanks for the 500 bits
Hey, good night, man. Thanks for waking me up by my name a little while ago
That actually worked
Thank you post though for the 500 bits. Did I miss a 100 dollar bit donation? I missed 10 000 bits
long time ago
how
This is me and joe were arguing
about
Who was bullying the other one to play halo, which by the way
Like five days ago
I was like, hey you wanted to play let's play halo. Okay, sounds fun
And then he's and then he just fucking I could hack it
He did the thing on discord when it was like
You see, oh joe joe is typing
Not anymore
Joel is typing not anymore
Okay
Joel is currently typing and not anymore
And I got this this huge like holy shit, man, I really want to be really here like hey
I fucking don't even like that franchise
I'm gonna be i'm gonna be pretending
I know it's your favorite franchise of all time
But I can probably only I can probably only pretend for like two hours tops and I was like, it's all good, man
Whatever like you i'm sure you'll have fun
And then I was like I was i'm pretending too like i've played all these games already
I've beaten halo reach like 15 times like 10 times at least it's like one of my favorite games and i'm like
Oh my god, we'll just we'll just both pretend doesn't matter and he's like, all right, cool
I hate halo, too
That's my first experience with halo
Besides being on a college dorm room with an xbox chunky controller in my hand for five minutes
I wouldn't have it any other way. He thought you were a halo streamer
The whole thing is funny so it doesn't it's fucking hilarious
But i'm jared and gave 10 000 bits earlier
Thank you so much. I'm sorry. I missed it
There's a huge amount of money to miss and i'm really sorry that I did
I think that was in the middle of the crisis we were having
They said this has been the absolute best podcast i've ever listened to you. Thank you so much for this amazing time
We covered a few topics. Yeah
Hey smelly boy. Thanks for the 250
Hey germo, what's your opinion on sitting on the toilet looking at your phone and ruining?
the
Wait, what what's your opinion on sitting on the toilet looking at your phone and running the hair dryer on yourself all
At the same time when nobody is home
What like blow drying your hair while you're on the toilet?
What's my opinion on that?
um
You only have two hands
So if you're on the toilet and you have the iphone in one hand and a blow dryer on the other
How are you?
My opinion on is you don't have a third hand. What do you do you put the phone on the ground?
Do you don't have a pocket?
Put the blow dryer down on the floor
My opinion is
I don't like it. That's it
Uh gtx 1080 quad sli. Thanks for the 250 bits
Hello, jeremy. What's your recommended method of consuming a Reese's cup?
And why is it your favorite candy?
Anyways, can't wait to squad up with you in fortnight 2 tomorrow while eating the 25 meal deal
from burger king cheers
From that's not who sent the message
Uh, well
The how I eat Reese's all in one go
Open it up
Take the whole uh Reese's paper off and put the whole thing in my mouth
And slowly enjoy the the whole cup
And oh, there's no wrong with it. No wrong way to eat a Reese's. Yes. Yes, there is
I like oh, I put my tongue through it and push out the peanut butter and then I put with my hand
I put up my nose and swallow it through my nasal cavity. That's a wrong. That's wrong. Don't do that
What why do they people don't even eat Reese's like that?
There was a whole ad campaign. It was like well, how do you do it?
Well, I peel off the edges and then I dunk it in milk and then I I squish it between my teeth
No, you just eat it. You don't know. It's a candy. It's a fucking chocolate bar
Is it's not yeah, it's not an oreo. It's a Reese's
And by the way, there's only two ways to eat an oreo three what you either eat it just bite into it
Or you like do the turn and then you like I well what I do
Is I turn it and I look off the cream and then I that's what I do
Okay, that's the that's the second and out of two
ways to eat a oreo
Okay
Let me show you how a real man eats a chocolate sandwich cookie
That's all right. Here's how you do it
You take you grab the oreo
With your forceps and you know what that means. That's thumb and middle finger. Don't use your index finger
What are you out of your mind?
thumb
And index a thumb and middle finger
Grab the edge of the cookie lift up
Your fingers should be no more than halfway down the cookie
Okay, you then dunk that cookie
Not to the point where your fingers are touching the milk
a little bit less than halfway
Just let it sit there for about one. This is sippy two
three
Four lift it out
Tap tap tap on the edge to the excess milk bite into that
That's how you do it. Then you grab that little half moon that you have there hold it the other way
So it's you're holding it long ways now
And keep doing it in half and then you eat the whole thing
You do it for four seconds. No, just like bang bang
Bang done lift it out
On the edge. There you go
I will say that I don't I don't know how people eat oreos just dry
out of the can
Eating oreos is like eating saltines
It's like
I feel like I could cough and dust will come out of my mouth saltines are good. Yeah, I know
that but
It's like eating a saltine if you eat just a if you eat a raw oreo cookie
It's just like it turns into this weird sandy dusty mush
I love these hot take sections of the stream
What do you think a cookie is
Okay, let's go another layer. We'll go one more step here
uh
should a cookie be
soft
Or soft and chewy or crunchy and brittle
This is going to determine how many of you get removed from the channel
Well, most of you get to stay
soft and chewy cookies
are just
the best
crunchy cookies
No
No, I wouldn't
I don't hate
hard and crunchy cookies
But there is a line
Where if you bite into if I bite into a cookie
And it turns into five cookies that's unacceptable and that's what happens a lot of times
Soft chewy you can just bite into it. It's it's
moldable
They're durable
If you drop a soft cookie on the ground, it's not going to shatter
If you drop hard cookie on the ground it shatters and then you're gonna you can't eat it anymore
Shatterproof this idiot eats cookie dough
uh
Is that some kind of strange unpopular opinion?
to like
cookie dough
Cookie dough. It's a it's everywhere. It's in every ice cream shop. It's the most popular ice cream
flavor, it's the most
Every cookie dough is like synonymous with a lovely thing that everybody likes. That's like saying you don't like bacon
What are you not epic?
Hey a pink iru. Thanks for the thousand bits
Thank you
They say thank you for providing a ton of laughs and giving us an escape from reality
Life can get us down sometimes but a laugh in a tough moment can make all the difference
Going through a rough bit a bit of a rough patch and your streams are always the highlight of my week
Watching you and Joel interact made me laugh the hardest I have in months. I can't wait for the next one
Neither can I
Should be a lot of fun
Thank you so much for the thousand bits. Thanks for hanging out
I am
Absolutely honored to be the highlight of your week
Thank you
Thank you for the one thousand
Bits
Let's get the credits rolling
That means we change scenes
I know how to stream
Thanks for watching guys. We'll see you tomorrow
Thank you for all the subs all the support as always much love to all of you. Thank you
Whether you sub today or whether you've been subbed for six years
Thank you. You haven't finished the bits. Um, I will don't worry
Don't worry. I've been subbed for a year and I just realized I need new sub
I need new sub badges. It's just coming up on that point where I never thought that was even going to be a thing
Looking down that way. Oh three two three year sub badges
I was like, I don't think that'll ever happen
I don't know. I don't think people will sub for three straight years, but I guess it'll be here and now it
that's a reality a lot and
That you could do four five six years in a row
Holy shit
Who would sub for that long? Ew
one of our founders
grump clump
49 month subscriber
That's a long time
But thank you again. Seriously, let's continue with the bits. We still have a little bit to do
Uh syroc. Thanks to the 250 they say oi
I am les francais
Yeah, we say bieux instead of bia
Wine bieux cheese bieux french fries bieux ratatouille bieux
Thanks to 250
Thank you the thrill for the fifteen hundred bits fifteen dollars from the thrill
I expect that this was going to be a flawless stunning playthrough of halo reach instead
I watched over an hour or so of what was a hilarious chaotic and truly beautiful disaster
One hell of a 26th birthday gift
Let's love friendo
Thank you
Thank you so much
somebody mentioned
uh something
They said that one of the levels we were on had like a par of 15 minutes and we had just been doing
Nothing for I think 30 or 40 straight minutes
but
Happy 26th birthday. Hope you had a good one
Thank you so much for the 1500 bits
Happy 26th birthday
He's gonna forget the birthday again. It's not time
It's not time
I still have a full day and a half. What do you mean? It's not time for that
I remember
Uh eugene. Thanks for the 250
When are you going to apologize to fortnight jimmy?
I already did
Sergio, but thanks for the 250 sergio, but serious question. Do you eat starburst with or without the paper on?
you just
unlocked
in my head
Something that I haven't even you've unlocked something. I don't know what it was you unlocked
I did do this
But well, I don't think it was with starburst. What was it with?
I had this very very
Distinct memory of chewing on paper and moving it around and moving it
What was that?
No, not tootsie rolls not tootsie rolls
What was it? It was paper and I remember
No, not cupcake wrapper
shit
the candy dots
I think you got it
Yeah, I used to I used to tear off a piece and I would just put the whole thing in my mouth and chew on it
And just pick it off and spread it around
Yep. Yeah, that's what it was
I would just
Tear off a piece and I would just stick it in there and just slowly
Mush it around in my mouth and gums and stuff until it popped off and then I would move the paper to the side
Anyways, um, no, I didn't I did not do that with starburst. I did that with the dot the candy dots
Yeah, yeah the candy buttons that were on the sheet of paper
Those things were awesome, too. They even still make those
Probably buy them on amazon or something
Also, praise that son bro. Thanks for the 500 bits
Jeremiah passed my cdl test today
Thanks for being such an awesome streamer watching your stuff always manages to put me in a great mood
cheer 100
Past your cdl
Well, would you look at that?
Pass my cdl
What's what is that cdl?
Is it like sat's?
Is it a driving test?
Driving your cdl driver's test
It's for a driver's life. Oh, well fucking hell. Yeah
You can use that five thousand dollars and get yourself a honda civic
Well, you you were here earlier, right?
You had to have been here it allows for trucking and taxi driving. Oh shit
Well, nice job
Get the tesla truck. I have not you know, you want to talk about hot takes
I've not even given you my take on the tesla truck
But it's it's at this point. I've already i've said
I just imagine the words that I would have said you already know the people have already made the jokes a thousand times
I I can't it's been too long. I I could say oh yeah, nintendo 64 car. You've seen that on twitter probably a thousand times
I could say it looks like it's made out of aluminum foil
You've probably heard that already
So there you go. Just that's what I that's my take
Please only original jokes and the windows. Yeah, I know the windows though
You can't break them. I broke it
Right. Yeah, we all know this already
They don't have any wait, hold on for a second
I I was about to get really really really crazily upset about what you just said
I thought you said they don't have any cup holders
It's like how do you make a but what do you mean? No cup holders in the whole car?
Not having a cup holder
You drink from a hose
There are no mirrors. No, there there has to be mirrors as it gets illegal
No mirrors or what's what the crumple zone?
What is a crumple zone?
Crumple zone that sounds like a section of like a disney park
Like crumples zone. It's like a gnome or something crumple zone
So it's like a crash zone
It's for crashes so you don't fucking die
Well, okay, welcome to the crumple zone
Yeah, guys the if you get a tesla truck, you know, it's gonna just sit in your driveway
So people look out the window and go, ooh
You know what? You're gonna be you're not gonna be worried about crumple zones
Oh, that looks dumb
Oh
I'm worried about crumple zones. You're a pluto
I think it looks cool. You know what?
Let me see tesla truck
Okay, I wish I could see I feel like we only have one angle of this thing
Do they have any video of it driving?
I feel like i've only seen an image of this thing from the side. What does this thing actually even look like?
Oh shit, this thing is actually kind of cool
That's what it looks like
No, that's a different company
That's a different company
Okay, never mind
That one looks cool. That's a cool looking one this thing called called the
the neuron
the neuron ev
That thing is fucking sick
Look at this thing. Yeah, i'll show you here. Let me put it on
This thing's called the neuron the neuron
That's pretty cool looking
Look at that thing
That's ugly. No, not the one on the right. I'm talking about the one on the left
You're a fucking neuron
What?
You don't think that that's like that?
That looks better
That one doesn't have any doors
How do you get in?
It's remote controlled
You sit on top of it. It doesn't have any doors
You sit in the back
All in the back of the pickup load part you sit back there with a wheel
I think that's a cool. It's I think it's all right. Look at what's what look that actually has like a back
No, there are no crumple zones
Looks like mario kart. We will I mean, okay
It looks it does look like an upgraded thing you can get in mario kart
That's the cool car that you get in mario kart. Yes
All right. I will agree the one on the right the one on the right is a little is a little weird
it
Is that even a is that a okay? So take a look?
the one on the right
Is that the car or is
It's just a giant shark fin. Why would you do that? Why would you drive that?
that's
That's really stupid
This is huge
You're gonna go through like a drive-through and you're gonna hit the top of the sign that says like please god
Don't fucking drive a car here if you're larger than you know what i'm talking about that sign
I would go into tunnels and scream going through the tunnels
It's a semi
Also, it goes back. Okay. I thought it was just like a flounder. I think that one looks all right
electric
Truck, it was that the only two of them. What about this one?
the rivian r1 rivian r1 t
Let's see. What's fine. When you guys like
This one's uh, all right. Okay. Hold on. Hold on a second
Hold on. What do you think about this one?
this one in particular is
You you had to create a character
And you took and you went to the part where it said nose
And you dragged the nose just forward
What do you think about this one? That's got a is that a crumple zone? I think that might be a crumple zone
Is it I see mirrors and I see a crumple zone
Is this truck even electric?
It's got a big nose. Whatever
I mean the truck look the back of the truck doesn't look very big
You I think you can only fit a refrigerator in there and you have to stand it straight up
This is the car that bugleberry would drive
Why do I know what you mean?
I like that one
five
Buy a fridge and then go through the drive-through to hit the sign is that your goal is to fucking wreck the sign
anyways, um
I don't even we're okay. So we were
All right, right praise that son
Congratulations on passing you cdl
Thanks for the 500 bits
Thank you put that put that license to good use
And then finally we had uh
psychilos for the 500 bits
Jerma jeremy and the jerma and the baby is my favorite video of yours
And I was wondering when we can expect the sequel i've been waiting for six years
I'm not having any kids
No children for me
No, baby albertson. No not in the plans not on the plans
I'd rather be the the fun uncle that everybody likes
That works for me
Auto is all we need
I don't know. You're not gonna pass on the funny jeans pepe hands
No, i'll freeze it. I'll freeze them
What? Okay, let's keep going
That was weird
a bro bought
I'm just gonna freeze myself so I can like
That's not what you were saying i'm gonna freeze myself
And uh in a thousand years
When they're going through we're gonna go find like the funny people where were they here they are
Well, we still have it's still available. Jerma 985 is still available. We can we can keep that line going
Your humor will be too outdated
That was a good attempt, but uh, the ship is sinking. Oh, you better pick up a pail and start dumping water
Uh, but uh bro bought formerly soft boy. Thanks the 251
Hey jerma reach was hilarious a hot mess
I'm looking forward to what you and joel do together next
When it when it comes to halo i'm kind of glad this stream turned out this way
Reach is amazing, but it has heavy themes towards the end
The first halo game halo combat evolved is pretty easy to set up for pc would really recommend playing that one first
Reach wouldn't be a bad way to follow it up
While you're waiting for two and three the main trilogy is comparable to star wars
Do hand sim co-op with joel?
Okay, and by the way, we can we can get tired of that in two hours. It don't matter
We got a halo expert. Yeah
No, that's good to know
That is good to know
And you know what else you're about to know?
That we've reached the end. Thanks again for watching. Thanks for participating. Thanks for hanging out in this
messy non-canon
uh stream
I'll see you guys tomorrow. The plan tomorrow is wherever the wind decides to take us
Because there are a few things we can do depending on
Who or what is doing things tomorrow? I might try to do maybe we'll try halo again
That's kind of funny to me that I just pretend like I didn't try yesterday
um
There's also
Well, let me just rifle off the things that are on my mind here
All right, are you ready for this
there is
Dead rising 3
I still have to play the rest of the fear stuff
fear 2
The dlc for fear fear 2 has a thing
We'll see
No, please no, please not dead rising 3
I did say that I had to beat it though. I had to do it
Play the new nancy drew game
I promised when did I promise I was gonna play nancy drew?
What are you talking about?
Nancy drew dead rising 3. Yeah, that's I know that's what i'm saying
No dead rising 3. Fuck that
damn
All right, just because one guy said that i'm gonna look up nancy drew games that have come out on steam
This is non-canon week. So
Get out your non-canon streams now
We'll see
We'll see good night everybody
I will see you guys tomorrow
Uh, we'll be starting
Not at four
We'll probably come back to the normal time tomorrow
Somewhere around one or two o'clock pacific
See you soon
take care guys
Raid vinny raid is vinny streaming right now
Raid raid raid raid. Uh, yeah, we haven't read. Are you right? You're right. We haven't rated anybody in a while
It's been like at least a month
Okay, fine. That's cool. That works for me. What's that? What's Vinny doing?
What's Vinny up to?
Super mario maker. Ooh
All right. Here we go
See you guys
Tomorrow let's queue up the raid. I'm sorry for being a meanie. What are you talking about?
All right. Goodbye
Take care. Good night