Disney Infinity 3.0. Those of you that don't know, I said to somebody, somebody said,
hey would you ever play Disney Infinity 3.0? And I said I would rather show my asshole on stream.
So, I guess I would rather do this. I have no idea what this game is. I have absolutely no clue.
I just know that somebody said, dude play Disney Infinity 3.0. And it just hard crashed.
Disney Infinity 3.0 is not responding. Let's try that again. Disney Infinity 3.0 Gold Edition.
Okay. Can I put, this is taking over my whole computer. It's on the, okay I have three monitors.
It's on that monitor now. Over there. Why is it on the other monitor? This game uses an auto
save feature. Do not power off the system while this icon is shown. Streaming videos not rated
by local rating boards. What? What does that mean? There are videos on here that have not been rated?
Is that what it means? Or does it mean that it's, if you're watching a stream of somebody
play this like me, that's not rated? I, you can't see it but I don't want it on this monitor.
I'm trying to capture the game.
Give me a sec. God, I can't move it. How do I move this fucking thing? Why are there no options? How
do I move this to another monitor? Shift and arrow key. Windows shift arrow key. That did not do
anything. That ruined everything. I have, it's a mess now. It's a fucking mess. I can't move it.
I'm just gonna play it on the other monitor. It's not, the game's not even being captured either.
So get it. So capture it. It's not gonna happen. This game was, okay they made this game for like
consoles and then they just, they just dragged the folder over to a CD and then they were just like,
just to do that. That's it. There's no options. I can't do anything. Alt plus enter to switch
window mode. It's not working. It can't even, okay I'm done. That was Disney Infinity 3.0.
Game can't fucking be played and streamed. It has to be played on a monitor that it chooses.
So I'm gonna get up and show my asshole on camera. What if I, hold on, let me try this.
Yeah, we won. We win. I'm gonna try this one more time. It's on this monitor now. It's okay,
it's on the right monitor but it won't capture. Capture it. Dude, and now it's on, I'm done.
Fuck this game. Wait, I'm, okay count to 30. I want everyone to count to 30 because in 30 seconds
I'm moving on to the next game and that was fun. I played Disney Infinity 3.0. It was a fun game.
Count to 30 seconds. It's not capturable and it's fucked up again. Yeah, fuck this game.
No, no thanks. No thanks. Fuck that stupid ass game. Okay, I'm done. That was fun. Cool.
I'm uninstalling it right now. Literally manage. Uninstall.