I was looking for a health pack. What did I do?
Hold on, hold on. I found a wild Shpee. He's a baby. He doesn't know where he is.
He's figuring out how to use the disguise kit. I figured out how to use
the... I just killed a baby Shpee.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
Oh, I think this is him. Oh no. Did the baby Shpee make it out okay?
I need to check on him. Where is he? There he is. Okay, baby Shpee.
Are you alright? No, that's not a baby. That's not a baby Shpee. That's an adult.
That was an adult. What are you doing, baby?
What are you doing? You can't get over to the tires. What are you doing?
I have to go into the tires. I need to get this way.
I am a Shpee. Ahhhh.
How could you? He was a baby. So while you are
baby Shpee watching, one thing you really have to do, guys, is you have to protect
the really young ones, the ones that just got out of the nest.
They're not going to be too sure what's happening.
You have to be there to protect them, to lead them in the right way,
because their mother is not here. Baby Shpees leave the nest at 11 days old.
And you see this one right here is walking all over the map.
He's not exactly sure where he's going. I'm not sure if he's looking for food,
if he's trying to scavenge a rat or a mouse somewhere. That could be the case.
His legs are not strong. As you see here, he's standing still.
He doesn't get strong enough legs until he gets to adolescence.
So that's something to keep in mind. We're going to hope he gets his first kill here,
because if a baby Shpee gets his first kill, then they can get their wings
and they can start to fly. And I'm really hoping.
I don't want to mess around with nature right here, guys.
I'm going to try to lead him in the right direction as best as I can,
but not a good idea right now. He's coming back to the enemy spawn.
I'm not sure what he's disguised as. This is not a good situation.
I might have to come out here. Hey, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't, don't, don't.
So I have made it my mission to be able to protect the baby Shpees at all costs.
I'm going to go heavy. I'm going to protect this guy at all costs.
No matter what happens, I am going to protect that he's dead.
Hi. Hi.
Set up time. Hi.
You want to play spy? Yes, we're supposed to be.
You want to Shpee? Yes. Yes.
Okay. Sniper, hi.
We both die. We'll walk out spawn and die.
I die. This is walk out spawn, same time, die.
I love you. Okay, we'll walk out spawn, same time, die.
Okay, I follow you. We both go.
I'm really happy about this one, guys. I'm so glad we found this.
Statistically, about 700 Shpees are born every minute.
And unfortunately, only about two will ever survive leaving the nest.
We have found one of those spies right here.
Looks like he's got himself a good job, maybe a wife.
He probably even has a nest of his own.
He has reached spyhood. He is no longer a Shrey.