Let's put on the game. Is it on? I think it's already open. Is it? Is it open?
Hey
Duck game goose game. Okay, I'm gonna keep calling this duck game. I'm gonna change the title of the stream
Well, no, actually I can keep the title untitled goose. All right. Is this game actually fun? What? Yes, it is. Okay
It's very fun. Really? Is this one of those sleeper hits that everyone's gonna think is like the best game of the whole year
This is one of those scenarios. I got my controller. I'm ready. All right, I'm gonna use a controller
This is like goat simulator
Yeah
So in like three years you guys can rewind back to this stream and laugh at me for my embarrassing goat simulator video gameplay
Save one. We're gonna go here press b to honk
It's auto
Oh, it's already fun. All right, hold a to run. Can I get those does someone have to do to get them?
What was that? What was that? That was mario. You got it. Nice work
All right l t to be to be friend to bend forward. Okay, so you can crouch do a sans joke
Okay, use your beak x to use beak you can pick stuff up that's cool no, give me that
This is fun
This is like I like this. Okay, should I not do I need any of this stuff?
Bend down to pick things up off the ground. So if it's on the ground you bend down just go like that
Can I throw?
Maybe I need to do this, you know, maybe I have to use this like a rub goldberg machine
I guess not
All right. I think I got it down
First puzzle of the game
What am I doing?
What the fuck did I do? I didn't do anything
Spread your wings. I can you fly
How do you fly?
Oh food. How do I eat the food?
Can I eat the sandwich?
I don't think I can
eat it
He thinks geese can fly. Yes, they can
They can fly for like a short distance
Wait, is somebody hungry?
I don't know what to do with any of these things. What's the goal?
Zoom in and zoom out. Oh jeez. Okay
What the fuck? Wait, there's a keyhole
There's a lawnmower
Can you die?
wait
Get into the garden. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait get into the garden get the groundskeeper wet
steal the groundskeeper's keys
Make the groundskeeper wear his
Sun hat rake in the lake
Have a picnic bring the picnic blanket sandwich apple pumpkin carrot jam thermos radio and basket
Okay, get in the garden. That sounds easy enough
Fly
You can't fly. You just can spread your wings like a dickhead. Okay, I got it
All right. Let me like let me move the picnic basket
I need the picnic basket the apple the sandwiches
I need it all in the right in the same place. So that's that can stay let's go this way
What if I go up? Okay, there's a spot to go this way. All right, I can break in here. Can I break in here?
How do I get that?
I can't get it. I need to stand on something
What about this way?
All right. I'm in the water
Can I go in the pipe?
I love it. It's so cute
You can't hate this game
I'm trying to find a thing. I don't like I can't figure it out yet
You just exist
Oh, what's that? I'm gonna go all the way up. This is huge
There's a lot of stuff over here. All right, hold on
What's it? Is it a is it a baby binky?
What do we do with binky? Is there a baby that needs this?
Okay, what am I supposed to do with this stuff
Oh shit
Do I need those boots for anything?
All right. I think I need to collect the two boots
Can I open this door?
Can somebody come open the door for me? All right. I'm gonna take the baby binky
I think i'm gonna need it
Because there's gonna be a baby that I have to give this to probably
Jerma geese don't help people
This one does
Uh, you you get to be you I get to be my own goose
And I want to be a friendly goose. Wait, i'm gonna go down. What does this actually end up is what I want to know
Nothing down here
What was that? Why do I hear bells?
Bells bells bells why?
It's anorlondo
All right. I I brought a binky back, but this doesn't help me at all. What can I go? I'm
I can't get up here
Get in the garden
Huh? What's this?
Huh?
Turn it off. Where's the gardener?
You wouldn't go over there
I would be like something there's somebody in a well somewhere. This is some lassy shit
Are people friendly?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, turn it on
Turn it on. Wait, wait, I gotta get the key. He's got a key on his back
This is so stupid
Like sneaking behind him
Oh shit
I wish there was a piss button. I don't know why I just kind of do
Hey
Give me that fucking key
Give me the key. I'm gonna sneak around. All right
Fuck I had it
Here it is. It's mine now
How can you water without the thing you need to water
Hold on. He's got a he's got like a knife
I love this. It's just so this is a just cute game
You know when it is adorable
Try to backstab him. You can't kill people in this game
He's he he's chasing me
He's faster than me. He's faster than he's faster. We fly fly fly fly fly
No
Come on. I have to make it. I have to make
Okay, I gotta get the keys
They really nailed how geese move around too. I got it quick quick quick quick quick quick
This this kind of shit was on pbs, man. There's no dialogue but there is you know
What do I do with this?
Make the groundskeeper wear his sun hat
Rake in the lake have a picnic
How do I make him wear his sun hat?
Those are his boots. All right. What does he have here?
All right, let's just hide this so he'll never find them
No, that's okay. What if it was his dick
His jam
Oh, he found the keys good for you
Rake in the lake rake in the lake
Hey, I can get up here too
Okay, can I I can I not fly over this?
I have to get the rake into the lake. No, I got hot. Where's the sun? Hey, you got a hat somewhere
Is this his hat up here?
No, I think that's a brick. Hold on
Can I do this?
Fuck I had it too. I was propping myself up up there. I know I can do it. It's got to be right there
I just have to be able to reach it, right?
If you saw this shit, uh your backyard window
I would definitely think that this was a rick moranis movie where he was transported into it goes
I can take these two away. Can I I can help
This is not true to character
I told you I wanted to do like a fun character that helped in the children's book that this would be a part of
They would be counting these right now
There see
Where's the barking?
Oh, sorry
All right. How do I?
I need to see where his son hat
Get the hat
Give me the keys. I got the keys
How do I get the sun hat get that back? I need that
Get up. What the fuck are you doing?
Leave me alone. I'm just trying to get the
All right. I'm running
Jump over the gate with the rake it might be possible get on the chair. All right. Can I bring the chair?
I don't I don't think I can drag the chair guys. Okay. I want to see what he does. No put this down
Can I move the pot?
Oh, okay. Hold on get this out of the way
Oh fucking fine. Take it. Just i'm giving you wait a minute. Can I get on top of this just bite him
He leans down over there. I think I just need to stealthy sneak up behind him and take his hat
Yeah, i'm going for the hat. I'm gonna hide in the fucking cabbage. I had to I just did that because I felt like it
There's there's no other reason
All right, is he coming back? What's he doing? All right, he's got the soil. What's he doing? What's he doing with the soil?
He's getting
He's moving the bucket now. He's getting the pale
What is he doing? He's burying bodies. I don't think this is a garden man. He's not what are you talking about?
Does he have to lean down for that?
No, he's got to do something
Can you see me? Oh shit, he can see me
Perfect for bodies
So what is it? I need you to lean down
Go garden somewhere
No shit, I had it
That was so rude
Hold on
Throw it into the lake
Look, you can have this back
He's bald. Yeah, that's not a hat. That's a toupee
I try let me can I run this over the lawnmower?
Aha, there it is. He puts it on rake in the lake
You got it. I gotta steal this way so he doesn't see me
I can't take that hat. Never mind
Rake in the lake here it goes. Oh, this the pic the picnic is right here a new to-do list item has shown up
Here we go. Hold on. I have an idea. Can I get it up there if I can turn this?
This might work. Come on vault over this fence. Now. He's just flexing
To who there's nobody watching
Doesn't a flex require somebody else to flex on?
That's all right. I'll just leave it in the lake. All right, have a picnic make the groundskeeper hammer his thumb
All right, let's get a picnic going first
There's the apple
Streamer hates his viewer. Wait, what are you talking about? What do I do?
Uh, I said highway to backsplash. Thanks for the five thousand bits
From a little earlier. Thank you
Five thousand bits fifty dollars coming in from highway to backsplash. They said
Jeremy you completely outdid yourself with the carnival stream
However, I was disappointed to see that you didn't put your middle finger out the window during the clown car crash like you promised
That's all right, though. It still happened
Who's calling me? I have no idea who this is
And when we don't know
we button
All right. Now I need
Blanket pumpkin. Oh, all right. I gotta go back in this garden get the pumpkins and shit
That was rude
I don't know. I don't know who that is
It's probably a scammer
All right carrot pumpkin jam
Thermos radio, I gotta take all this guy's stuff
Just take one of each
Wait, doesn't he knew I took how did you count them? How did you know I took one?
Is he going to the picnic to take wait a minute? He's not actually gonna do that, is he?
Get out of here what's more important what's more important pumpkin of the rose? Oh, yeah, so i'll just take this thing then
My dog does this shit
Hey, give me that back now. Give me this and then let's go grab something else completely unrelated and run away
Feels like a toy. Hey, give me that toy
Okay, fine. I'll take this
Wait, I got it. All right, I gotta steal I gotta get pumpkins gonna be hard to get
uh
Now this would be cute if I invite him to the picnic afterwards, right?
That's the last panel of the book
And he goes what is this? What happened? Am I these are my things these are my things
No
Okay
Picnic blanket and I need jam
That's jam, right?
And thermos this is a big picnic. All right thermo. I think this is I gotta make that look nicer than it does
It looks terrible right now
Wait and his toupee
And the rose. No, i'm not gonna do that. It's weird
Where's the picnic blanket?
You have a sign that says no ducks, but i've been here the whole time just hanging out
Why would you not be freaking out that i'm in here yet?
How do I get up there?
There it is
Don't certain animals do this shit though? I was really
There's an animal that actually comes and steals stuff from your house
What is it?
I need the radio and picnic blanket
crows
They'll take like bracelets jewelry
What is in here? I can hide in this
Good luck finding this
Well, what how did you find that?
All right, which blanket picnic blanket?
Is the radio?
Can I not pick the radio up?
Okay. Well, this works
Wow, this is the blanket. All right bring
To the picnic blanket make the groundskeeper hammer his thumb
How do I do that? How do I get him to hammer anything?
That duck
So does he is he doing like a ai loop? Is he gonna pick the hammer up?
Wait, how do I get him to hammer his thumb? Do I have to scare him before he swings?
No, look what I look what I did
What no, this is working way better than I wanted to come look over here
All right, you know what i'm just gonna let him finish what he's doing he'll see it eventually
Was he gonna hammer the shoe
What are you doing, man?
All right, this is it. This is it ready
He's gonna hammer i'm gonna scare him right before he swings
That's really hard
He that's not a broken thumb that is a shattered hand he was aiming for his hand
I did it
Nice. All right. Now what I did it all
Level two. Oh, yeah
Nice. That's awesome. All right, let's go
shortcut
Damn it. It's a shortcut. I can't do anything
Turn on the radio
Okay, i'll turn the radio on
Hey what I was doing something. Hey, I was doing a thing
I was walking with the music. How dare you get that back?
Go get in the water. He's scared of water. Did I break it? Oh fuck
Say all my stuff my rose
My rake
Everything is in here
All right, it'll dry right? No, get the fuck out of i'm trying to do something. Look. I have a rake. I have a rake
Don't you want to take that rake back?
Yes, get that rake out of here good for you. Just give me this fucking thing
I'm just gonna get away from him. He needs this clip for the second germ of a video
Now somebody gets it. I need at least five seconds of a transitional piece
Wait, he's gonna see well he remembers the rose. All right. See you later
Okay
Here we go. Here's the edit point. I need a new song. This song's hard to time
But it's a new person. I gotta say hello
There it is. Here's the this is halloween. There it is end transitional piece. All right. Ooh new stuff break the broom
Trap the boy in the phone booth. Oh, okay. That's easy. I just have to push the ball into the phone booth
Boy has glasses on by the way
All right, what else make the boy wear the wrong glasses make someone buy back their own stuff get on tv go shopping
Okay
Break the bris- where's broom?
That's important. That's the first thing
Make boy put on new glasses. Wait, can I steal his favorite toy?
Yeah, just just shatter this thing
Okay, uh
Wait, she's got a weapon. She's got a weapon. They have weapons
Okay
They actually fight back
Break the broom. Okay
I did what I wanted to do. Uh-oh. Yeah, let's go. You want to fuck with me? I am unhittable
It's like oscar the grouch get over here. Let's go. This is not working. This is not doing what I want
There's nobody around here
Oh well
Apple what else is in here? Oh, no, no, no, no, no. No, there's a toothbrush in here
But can I do something with the toothbrush? Can I mail the toothbrush? I don't know who I'd mail it to but I could mail it to somebody
I put it in the mail
Is that a game or is that in real life? All right, here's the shopping cart. I got okay this
This is a nightmare
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
We're getting overconfident stride
All right. I get on the phone booth. How do I
All right. If he's he'll run in the phone booth. He scared of me
this way
No, no, no over here over here over here over here
into the phone booth
Yeah
You bet you're scared, huh?
i bet you're scared oh fuck i should call the police on a bird
another thing to look out your window and see yeah that's odd all right am i safe i think i'm safe
okay so now make the boy wear the wrong glasses let me i gotta observe the boy
okay he checks his glasses and then he walks over he plays with the ball for a little while right
he brings the ball over here he wipes his mouth and he kicks the ball i think i have to explore
because he checks his glasses what else is there make someone buy back their own stuff
is it broom all right so i'm thinking i have to go shopping so where's the checkout connor
he's got the toy too rake and bucket no i don't need the rake what do i need the rake for
i'm just walking through wait you don't know where the broom is all right i'm gonna keep
exploring i'm opening the garage keep going this way there's the trash can there's these walkie talkies
wait a minute okay so let's put these maybe i can trick the lady i'm putting it down here
okay maybe i can make the lady think there's a goose over there this is metal gear kind of
except not really it's just it's a i don't know what the hell is wrong with my brain
but i was gonna say it's not it's no snake no shit did it work okay it worked now what uh take
the radio just take something break something okay give me this i don't know what this is to
give it to me okay now um no listen over here he stole the cash register yeah i so i can unplug
that glasses how do i give these glasses to the kid give me 20 dollars thanks for the 10 community
subs thank you for the 10 community subs give me 20 dollars how do i break how do i break his
glasses to can you run to the pole or something like smash his glasses he does have big shoelaces
no i don't do that do i are you kidding me do i have to sneak up and tie this person's shoelaces
up when do i have a chance to do that wait what what i can hit him in the head pin man just gave
10 community subs too thank you pin man back to back both of you i figured it out no get in let's
get in here quick run get out get out quick oh leaving the scene of a crime how do i break
the broom you can't run from your sins have the kid fall on the broom has he still not figured
it out are those the right glasses oh that's not gonna work make him run on the rake head
you guys are sick i should boost him out of the map get the fuck out of here i'm busy
i'm gonna sneak in open the door how do i break it i can't like wedge it at a door or something
call the police or something all right i don't know how to break it i still need to go shopping
all right i'm thinking buy a toy with like a scanner she just scanned these items all right
let me see uh she put a price tag on it where's her scanner i have to go up and weigh it i just
want to go shopping so that's how you weigh stuff but how do i can i print a receipt no shit i want
no am i overcome wait do i just leave with an item make the shop scales go ding get on tv
get on tv how do i get on tv is there a camera where's the camera i demand to be put on television
put me on tv there's a button right there all right i need to scare i need to get the police
called because i gotta press the button over there you're gonna call the store the guy comes
out i press the button get on tv we got it open the door fuck you can go ahead no no
i was trying to get that's where i call them yeah you get in there too
prop the door open with the broom will that work and i'm over here too i don't think i'm fast enough
to get in here i think i think i do have to prop the door because every time i run over there it's
um let's try it again get in no you went the wrong way get in that telephone booth oh my god
move out of the way the lady's been looking for a broom go in the booth where's the walkie talkie
i'm putting it over like right at here come on get in the phone booth now i just want to turn the
t no stop stop stop there you go there you go there you go good ha ha where's walkie talkie
what the fuck is going on right now i can't go in she blocks the door i can't go in the doors
block she don't even stand when she walks out i can't go by her what your tv quick
how do i break the broom oh i would like to pay for an item please no she's just got a
that weapon's better that's a better weapon all right let me ring this up real quick there's no
padding on it anymore uh oh this is not good i think i'm stuck yeah i'm stuck my head's being
squished into the door okay make someone buy back their own stuff put in the basket too i'm
overthinking it i'm overthinking it i'm overthinking it didn't read the instructions
one day i didn't read the instructions that in the basket okay loo paper hairbrush
i need toilet paper
what else hairbrush food i was trying to scan objects okay hairbrush food cleaner
fruit and vegetable does that count as a that's a fruit and vegetable okay cleaner food hairbrush
cleaner distraction how did you fix the broom oh i think the jig is up she saw my shopping cart
no give that back oh fuck i have to no no no no no no no no put
she doesn't know where i am don't make any noise
no why did i do that that was really stupid
it's like a laugh uh i would be a very bad villain i would just it would be terrible oh shit
just i gotta move this out of the way if my plan works for even a tenth of a second i would just
start laughing like that that's a scooby-doo villain yeah that is a scooby-doo villain all
right what else do i need cleaner hairbrush where's the hairbrush uh up here i don't know
is that a hairbrush cleaners up on the rack cleaner right is this cleaner where'd she go
hey she went back took her orange no you can't get in i'm sorry but if you find this
if you own a store and you find this basket with these random objects this is a baby came in with
their parents and they did their i'm pretending to shop you wouldn't do anything about that you'd
pick it up later no one's getting in trouble here i don't have a broom no get back in there
good hairbrush i need fruit go get the broom fight me let's go no fight me go get the broom
you want to go let's go then let's go then go get the broom that's what i thought
you bitch that was rude it's like now i'm like i'm supposed to be playing a nice person
you already did you give me an option to move a mouth by pressing a button i'll do it every
time i don't care i just need a fruit where's the i don't i do not see a hairbrush i'm not kidding
hairbrush glasses umbrellas toilet paper fruits vegetables oh i dummy that's this that i get so
that blends in it literally does oh it literally does it literally blends in this is like a bath
this is a shower scrubber it's really gonna chase me all the way over here huh you lead near to the
stash not on purpose this bait will she take it yes she will idiot well i mean it would have been
smart but i didn't i didn't get back here fast enough hold on take the bait come over here
just drop an oil behind my car quick it's too heavy it's too heavy i gotta get the last item
does she know what that is no she doesn't how would she know what that is what is no wait wait
wait wait wait wait yeah i'm not gonna do it absolutely sculptures all right what's next
trap the shopkeeper in the garage i don't understand to make somebody buy back their own stuff then
oh i have a new place i can be can i get out what is she looking for what is that what is she
looking for what what is that chalk oh it says no geese this is like scary all right i did it
she's trapped now make someone buy back their own stuff buy back their own stuff try put a
a price tag on his glasses wait he always wants to play this so put a price tag on this
this is my store now wait and i can't i can't get like a price tag on it oh no i need the
shopkeeper because i put this in here and then he looks for it and then she makes him buy it
can i let her out what you got on what you can just leave oh how do we open the door all right
get out should i grab the chalk all right i have the chalk now look open the door please the trash
can is blocking her is it hey it worked she was getting blocked with the trash can all right
oh i'm stuck on the pole i'm stuck in the pole you saw that you saw that close up here we go
now we just watch the mayhem that we've created my she what is she doing what's going on
hey look for your toy it's over there somewhere come on she's gonna put a price tag on it tag it
up let's go um i'm not even close that's then you have to price tag it why is she going back in the
garage oh all right kid come here that way into the store there it is all right right in front of
you turn around your toy what about your toy she just takes a swing can he not see his glasses no
wait hold on wait should i give him his other glasses back all right i'm gonna give him his
glasses back he doesn't give a shit both shoes on time that's dangerous here all right now you
can see again go look for your toy toy there it is everyone thought i was fucking stupid
everybody said he was dumb he doesn't know what he's doing he's twitching the glasses again
somebody somebody call his mother is he actually going to buy this he doesn't remember that it's
his who he's looking left and right is he gonna steal it
yeah maybe just sing um can i buy this this is sad i did this i did this i'm the master of this
at the end of the twilight zone episode the guy steps out all right now what
i did it all let's go what's next see you later all right it counts straight or right
hmm hmm that's a good question let's go let's go right you look you can't see well
has he seen me through the gate well i found the entrance hold on wait wait wait wait wait it's
through here i'm too big i'm too big to fit in there now what make someone break the fancy vase
help the woman dress up the bust make the man spit out his tea get dressed up with a ribbon
make the man go barefoot do the washing okay i went for the tea one first that's not spitting
out tea do i have to fill it with something else maybe to fill it with like bath water or
something or like dirty water dish water not fucking bath water oops that was loud
okay help the woman dress up the bust no um make someone break the fancy vase all right um
where's the bust which one of these is this is the bust there it is all right dress up the bust
how do i dress it up what do i need to get some kind of clothes
that hurt my ears and i'm the one playing the game all right that's how you make us
put the tea out good to know all right with the tea once he goes up to sip i'll ring it
dress up the bust that's something i don't understand oh can i ruin the painting
oh i can't paint the paint i can't use the paint brush shit i'm trying to uh oh
wait there's some clothes you can have this back i don't want it it's stuck it's not a duck ah put
socks on the on the bust make the man go barefoot okay i have to wash i have to wash these we're in
the water over here i'm stuck over here now wait i haven't eaten all game is she listening to me
she made a squirrel how is that not a that's not a secret that seems kind of oh oh what about this
one over here all right wait for me to get the tea i'm not causing any problems i was waiting for
this guy to drink his tea so i can have him chop down hard do you have to picture over here what's
in here oh do you have to re way you got lady i'm sorry but you need to put screws in you don't
just hold it up i know it looks like you can cut corners on these ikea builds but you can't you've
got to put all 425 screws in what's this i don't i guess when i break the vape wait get the teacup
right yep fill it with fucking dirty water shit he found me no give me that back i need that
just i have to poison you please leave me alone all right get in i gotta get in through there let's
go this way does this gate open it doesn't what's over here no this route here we go this is what
i'm talking about fill it up with like the dirty well how do i put the how to get the well to come
up wait i didn't unlock this so i'm just gonna fill it in the fountain that makes sense thank
god the well is idiot proof aha i use the blocking of the newspaper here we go okay here you go there
you go take it back now drink out of that somebody's to break the vase
dress the bust wash the clothes there we go i'm just gonna take it off the second you put it
i'm gonna take that off immediately like that's just gonna happen so no fuck you i'm gonna take
it off again let me in give me the sock you know what's over there now open it for me
well i guess i could go wrap around yeah that's what i'm gonna do i'm gonna grab it and run all
the way around hurry up get up there quick go go go yeah
we're just gonna go around the circle he's like that's you wait wait wait wait wait get you're
gonna return it you're gonna return the sock you fucking dick are you serious i didn't know they
did that that dirty t i know the bell let me do this first jesus all right sock one being cleaned
no what oh i'm good i'm good hide okay wait till he's done looking ball socks and the bra
are now clean good now i need to do a slipper and a bar of soap oh i know where i have to get that
off of him and then make the man go barefoot so i have to steal his slippers off of his feet and then
he has to have no shoes on so i have to wait he's gonna pull up the thing wait till i gotta get an
opportunity here he's gonna look and i'm gonna go right for it he goes huh ready here we go three
two one didn't even know haha i didn't even know get the other one does he not know wait he's not
how do i get the other one hmm he i think he has to cross will he cross his leg the other way go on
do it come on man he scratches his legs oh all right he's looking he looks to his right
i think they can cross around here hmm how do i do this all right now we ding him when he sips
and then we're good to go what the fuck what did you just throw that at me he just threw the vase
at me why are you getting the what are you doing why is he throwing everything over
i did it again i hope they get a fight they are gonna get a fight wow
that's so fucking loud he needs to spit the tea out i think i don't think can i not do that one
anymore all right dress up the bust get dressed up with a ribbon that's a ribbon
i love that's a stun watch this oh shit they're immune to it now okay how do i put this on
get dressed up with a bow oh shit quick stun him okay so how do i get dressed up get dressed up
with a ribbon all right so if i if i'm got soap he got both of his wet shoes back hooray did it
it's in there wait a minute oh fuck it doesn't just complete it does that count oh no i have
to get them all in there at the same time well that's good to know all right i still need to
figure this out vase is broken dress up well let me see the tea thing is like i'll just do the tea
right now she's going to get she wants the soap back from him
is this any significance in the ladder what do i do with this get dressed up with a ribbon help
the woman dress the bust i don't know i have no idea fuck what else is over here what about the
frog should i bring the frog over here i know what to do i'm sorry i was talking i was talking
to somebody else no no wait no stop stop stop stop and stop it just how are you gonna know
which one is the real one i'm gonna fucking mess it all up just you don't know
perfect distraction excuse me i think i'm in need of a bow he's so confused
no wait don't uh i gotta play a song here right no i gotta get closer no it's done
i can't do it i can't do super fucking mario i tried just give put it down uh
uh okay now she's gonna this is gonna be perfect i think her brain is gonna be too
ai stupid to understand now she's gonna go get the ribbon okay this is the opportunity here
what did you fall on the stairs where are you going now i'm fucking over with it
holy shit that was angry okay this is where i pulled this up here i'm getting rid of this guy
you aren't gonna be able to find it
i fucking tricked you you are so gullible it's unbelievable that's right i'm the fucking offer
here of chaos in these times i get way too into this i really do don't ever give me a
fucking button to be able to talk okay now i gotta wash uh wait i still don't get this one
dress up the bust but with the clothes there's only the only clothes that exist the ones that
are on the rack right there's a hat on the frog there's a half of the frog holding the pole
frog is sitting in the log on the stone there's a uh there's a windmill there's a there's a
there's a hair on the flea on the board of the frog in the bog i tried but i couldn't get it
i forgot i actually forgot it i probably just disappointed a lot of people give me the hat
no what about your hat i thought i could do the paintbrush but no and then i have to get
everything the slipper the soap and all the clothes over here have to go into i just don't know
maybe something with the water fill up the water dish help i have to help her see the glasses and
figure it out again you've been foiled by the ghost this is two times now can he make it a third
what a tuber joke make sure you know look what i found get these oh she figured it out i'm not
doing anything you're fine all right now i gotta get the hat and the pipe i think that should do it
and then i really i gotta have a nice route you know what let me see if i can get there
i just got a fucking big host halifax just hosted me for like fucking it was a thousand people
welcome thank you halifax and all the viewers that just came over nice to meet you my name is
jeremy currently playing the duck goose video game if you don't know what it is
i'll give you a really brief description of the whole game
i have controlled everything so far it's pretty much all i've done that's the whole thing that's
everything i've done that's the extent of every joke that's the extent of every reference i've
made so far this stream and they're all gone i don't know why i have to i have i just the
john lithgow i don't know why i have to turn into john lithgow i don't know what happened why
at mary oh he's an alien mary i do believe that you guys don't know who that is how old am i
i've walked in a circle twice all right wait what's up welcome to the stream all right let's go
but no sir thanks for the thanks for the host it's third rock from the sun that's john lithgow
come on don't make me walk in a circle again trying to explain to everybody what's going on
all right and lord focwa that's a better one that's right what do i do what am i doing oh
yeah i gotta get his hat no it's mine you can't have it it's mine god damn it don't make me do
the fucking voice again don't make me do this again i don't want to do the john lithgow again
but you know i'm gonna
no oh she can see it she'll forget a fair time how could you humans be so incredibly stupid
i made his vocal play the lottery with my chances no no no this is mine you can't have it i'm not
gonna do that four times uh it's right i don't know i gotta get the pipe newspaper is the best
thing because that this is my i this i get it right here already it's gonna pull it up
and turn there it is okay let's go now what how the fuck did you see this that makes no sense
didn't get it in the bowl oops pretty good not bad i got something else to do make someone prune
the prize rose isn't he just doing it right now uh what are you doing no oh no they don't want
ducks in here anymore prune the prune the rose ah to do shit yeah be careful though careful
don't cut too high here we go now it's really all about getting the okay i have to get this
shoes oh he's looking for it should i joker laugh in front of this guy so let's go ahead and do
where is she let's just i can do this quick right they argue they're gonna argue about everything
quick you cut my rose down no i didn't yes i did what's he doing she gonna throw that at him
i thought she's gonna bash him in the head with it where is he fuck up and by the way your bra
is in my fountain really man you're not gonna lie i've done that a lot of times how many times
you've like thrown something away in the trash and you just don't give a shit and you miss like four
times throw your phone on your bed you miss the bed twice that happens a lot i can't talk shit
it why would i throw my phone it's protected i have to do this without this guy knowing so i
have to not alert this guy ever because he'll keep throwing him over so we have to wait i can't i
gotta do this slow very very slow why am i stuck i love when you run the music plays does that cute
music all right i gotta get in and out here she'll notice it doesn't matter she can put it back up
she wants he didn't see me did he no good all right this is which ties it back up she'll go
up to the top i can grab the sock and get around and then it's a bar actually i can get bar soap
right now come on be smart about this shit now i have to wait i gotta sit here for a long time now
come on she doesn't know where the soap is this is bad soap in now i just need the other sock and
the slipper shit that no you go ahead put it back up okay now go do something no don't paint
whatever i'm just going in oh okay we gotta act i would laugh right now but i don't want to lose
smooth got it done i can't leave this way we're out of where do i have to leave i got the way i
came in somebody's house i mean i do i want the ball it goes with my outfit i'm taking it
you know i'm saying so now back up this is the only place i haven't gone to the well
oh it's almost i can't i tried all right wait how do i get it in there i don't get anything
to do in that okay no way to escape this gate so i'm gonna bring it down oh look at that look at
that one go ahead and open now where does oh i see we're back out here this is the beginning of the
game shortcut no i need some more to-do lists you know that's not a bad idea i'm going for it
i'm getting in that well okay come on get me in there i know it's possible i'm gonna find the
right spot with the rock wedge it in the rock see you later shit's gone i can't go in it though
i can't get in there all right let me try to go back up here the gate you can open the gate
wait a minute hold on wait a second i need to look over here that i can go this way this is
the very beginning what else is new what's going on over here no this is super locked
wait it goes down here oh i thought a well was a well didn't think it was a well okay well the
rake still exists all right let me go back up here a stove is a stove yeah a well is a well
a bench is a bench i can't go that way only so is it the only way i can go uh am i missing
something here i'm back at this house and this is wrong let's move streamer watch out for the goose
i am the goose something's wrong why did i lose control what okay apparently my xbox controller
is messed up that's all right so is there something another thing to do over here in
the house or something lose my ribbon is there another way for me to go oh shit can i go ah
all right there we go are you kidding me did i actually lose it oh that sucks i'll play bad
bitten all right can i go home sorry uh there's a package here i'm gonna deliver the what the
fuck is going on if i could why is this happening is this thing dead so deliver the package to the
other person's house switch their mail you got it cool this is a crime you can't arrest an animal
that looks good wow this is this way i remember this really is a shortcut so one of the first
one of the first thing i saw this looks dangerous this is cars that's you're about to witness a
robbery music something dangerous is gonna happen here uh wait can i hey holy shit you knew there
was a fucking animal in here what's wrong with you you out of your mind you're fucked up you know
that okay so i have to get delivered somewhere where though get out of my way uh i'm gonna go
over here this is a good view look at that guy's shoes hold on i gotta open another shortcut nice
so what's this uh tackle box for somebody i'm gonna leave it here so i'll forget
i don't want to forget and mess this whole thing up all right the buoy in the tackle box is over
here you can't fish can you hey doesn't hurt me can i take it he has a bald head should i put
something on his head can i put a cone in his head let's see let me see what happens when i go in
here i'm waiting for that person to come back all right you load me in the truck and then you take
me where i don't want to open it
that was weird i wonder if there's an animal in the box get into the pub this place is huge
thank you for you again these humans are so predictable one day i will rule them all no get
out of there so what's in here break the dartboard get the toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat
toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat fuck make the old man fall on his bum be awarded
a flower steal a pint glass and drop it in the canal set the table okay knife fork plate pepper
candle i got the plate i got the dumpster this looks kind of shitty though i want to make this
look better plate pepper boxes what is this this is jet pack no i'm sorry that's my mistake this
one of those mario boots i don't know what it's supposed to do with this i laugh my ass off another
goose jumps out of there and starts fucking talking you're still here hold on oh there's
pepper right here all right pepper how do i get up there oh shit i would laugh my ass off this is
gonna be hell all right i have to sneak up there and grab the pepper don't turn around do something
all right i'm breaking the dartboard
one note hey he's gonna throw to me let me try here you try it again do i want to try to get
him to win i thought you had a goose that just fetched you these things by the way if anybody
has a dog in the room and they have speakers on i would turn it down a little because i'm about to
do uh is the owner no no he's not gonna stop i have to run away and hide no he sees actually
zoning me out you gotta be kidding me he just zoned me the fuck out your keys weren't in there
i'm trying to get them to not pay attention bingo he's sniffing it with the butt there it is nice work
okay i'm in let's wait yeah over here what is wrong with me i don't know i like honking
i need to get in here without them seeing how the hell am i gonna do that they turn around right can
i go over here let me try to get in here okay i'm going this way uh all the way around but do i need
a tomato pepper make the old man fall on his bum get awarded get the toy boat break the dartboard
no nothing to do with a tomato i feel like i'm gonna need it though why do i feel like i'm gonna
need this i don't know oh shit are you gonna come get the tomato maybe she'll come down and pick up
the tomato what do i need i need a knife fork pepper candle okay all right wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait throw it can i throw it up there i can't like dump it up there damn it i can't
throw it over that sucks i know get uh get the toy boat i know i pull a table over or why did i just
do that what was the point of that i think i have to do that to somebody wait a minute is that going
with the water that's awesome when i get the toy boat what do i do with the toy boat do i just
win no give me that back i'm too small you can't get in here oh all right i have to have to wait
till she opens the door again no i did it i don't have to get it more than one break the dartboard
though is gonna be tricky i think which you know where i am uh well i'm in trouble i think
okay oh that was easy haha candle knife and fork i still don't understand this whole bucket thing
oh shit there's a candle don't zone me don't zone me don't zone me don't zone me out don't
zone me out give me the candle don't zone me out they're zoning me out it's desperately trying to
zone me get over here stop oh no is the owner here yeah you can't come under the table fuck off
all right now i need knife candle and that's it the table will have been set by that point
i can put it away give me the knife he's got a knife he's yeah he's got a knife and he's
putting on the table candle it only took up 10 minutes of boomer goosem that's true it did
you can zone me all you want i'm just gonna go around out of the way get out of the way
oh my god you idiot with the box you idiot that's just a wall in front of me i need that candle
get it just go in it what am i doing the table has been set all right steal a pine
class and drop it in the canal make the old man fall and break the dartboard all right make the
old man make the old man fall how the hell do i do that this game is fucking hilarious
it's just so stupid i'm taking this very seriously too i'm just ready that's the face of something
that's going to remove the stool from underneath you who's waiting for you sit on break the dart
board i probably have to maybe give him something else that's not a dart but it looks like a dart
if you have a dog turn you never mind all right how do i maybe i should scare him when he throws
the dart break the dart board okay uh what be a what oh flower there's a flower flower right there
do you think that's funny cool give me a flower there's a flower right here
yay thank you very much got it steal a pint glass and throw it in the canal
okay i got it back in the bar this i'm gonna keep this it's mine actually i'll give it to the old
man you can have that that's for you here that's for you i wonder what do i need to do about this
let me do the pint glass first that's the last thing i have to do over here let's
throw it into the canal do i have to take this all the way out of here and throw it into the water
all the way down even clean the broken glass so shit how do i get over there i can't screw
that up again what oh i just i could drain the beer i just went on the bucket
i there's only two pint glasses in here fill the mug with beer that's a task that you're
going to be given to me that i don't think i'm going to be able to accomplish can you move out
of the way please that's the sound a cat makes before it pukes that's fucking that's the funniest
thing i've heard all week go underneath the tables you can't get you
does anybody have to clip who has the clip of what when i was like drunk being a weirdo and
i kept doing the fucking like like fucking i'm gonna puke it does anybody have that
somebody does i just want to watch it i kept going just like boom like puke an insta swallow thing
and i everyone was so concerned hold on i need to listen to this this is really important
wait wait wait i just i could drain the beer this is the one there's like four of these
this is not even the one i'm thinking about making any uh chicken marsala tomorrow you know what i'm
saying boys and girls this is not the one how many times have i done this
i do this shit all the fucking time apparently hold on a second oh my god hold on a second
well it looks like you can't make it if you're making any uh chicken marsala tomorrow you know
what i'm saying boys and girls well it looks like you can't make it if you're making any uh chicken
marsala tomorrow this is disgusting that's not the one there's another one where's the
other one it was a front-facing camera boys and girls this is i think this might be another one
can't make it if you're making any uh chicken marsala tomorrow my favorite streamer oh
this is fucking disgusting
looks like you can't make it if you're making any uh chicken marsala tomorrow
give me another one have i done this looks like who's my favorite streamer
chicken marsala tomorrow you know what i'm saying boys and girls he's talking about talent are you
talking about like who i think is the funniest and what's interesting well looks like kim aiken
if you make it i do that more wait wait wait wait wait uh vinnie joel hold on a second
they're always doing something fun always doing something different i do it like three times in
this clip who's my favorite streamer oh you're talking about talent are you talking about like
who i think is the funniest and what's interesting what do you think who uh vinnie joel they're
always doing something fun i don't do it again here do i no i'm fucking done i'm done oh
the cat puke i'm gone i think i'm hold on i'm gonna take a break
that was just that one just happened all right hold on i gotta figure out my scenes here
i need to i'll be right back i'm i'm gonna get a water or something i'm fucking all over the
place i'll be right back i keep thinking of the cat puke thing i've been making that noise for
20 years never once has anyone ever told me that that was the cat puke sound i don't think
you found another one you that you found more of these i'll see you guys on fucking monday
i did the whole bottle that's hold on a minute i don't want anybody in this chat to ever tell me
again that i am not a fucking actor okay i would have won i would have won at least a high school
competition with this type with this one here don't you understand i mean i'll see you guys on
fucking monday i did the whole bottle holy shit just keep the clip that clip it somebody
yeah i mean i'll see you guys on fucking monday you guys are fucking crazy all right anyways
why don't we go back to the game that we were just playing i have a lot of tabs open of
various times where i've made that noise i'm going to close them
and we're going to get back to normal thank you though let's go ahead i by the way i've been
excuse me why don't we get a little whoosh here oh interesting it's only taking you
six years on twitch to have a transition between your scenes whatever all right i gotta unplug and
plug back in what am i looking for i look for the uh pine glass right here get it all right
what do i do with this thing i don't want to break it i throw it in the river drop it in the canal
how do i get from here to there though how do i get by the guy he chases me wait is this is this
a canal does that count i can't believe nobody posted the derma slaps himself yet me neither how
do i leave without this guy seeing me i have to get by him and i don't want to break the glass
though because that's it fuck how do i get out of here okay can i just if i just place it a little
break no okay put it in the box maybe i think i get in the box no maybe i just have to run
try yes should i reverse trojan horse the untie shoes here's what i'm gonna do untie his shoes and
then i'm gonna get the bottle and i'm running out let's go untie shoes get it i got the double there
he's running with two untied shoes good all right where do i go how do i get out here where do i go
where do i go where do i go where's the canal is this canal confirm with me this is a canal
drop a bucket on the burly man's head early man's head is that the burly man he wants the flower
oh i've already got this under control check this out there it is this guy is fucking screwed
watch this all right i have to give him a trail he's gonna come get a tomato where is he come on
get that flower flower go get it no no no no no no you don't need that oh i'm an idiot
he just i gotta get all the tomatoes in the other room all right give me that tomato god damn it
oh shit oh no no wait wait wait wait wait stay there stay stay there no no no no no no no no no
no no you idiot oh you piece of shit get out of my way he's in the right spot right now
no he's just no he's zoning me no don't let him zone me don't let him zone me no he's got the full
zone technique no i have to go up okay he's gonna get it he wants to get the tomato right he's like
where would i find a tomato on this night over here there he goes he's gonna get the tomato in
the other room up the stairs bucket on head he's going for the flower go nailed it now i just need
break the dartboard break the door i still don't get this blow the horn when he throws
that's possible what oh uh-oh big guy's back i didn't see his back
you don't blood on his ass is he gone yet no he's putting it in he's washing it and putting the
single tomato in this box his tomato box okay what why did i all right i kind of just spun up
this guy hide over here no i don't want to play with you i don't want to play that game with you
stop is he actually coming over here to put that flower back in the vase over here i was given that
flower that's not yours to take is he gonna stand up there and start waving his arms okay play the
harmonica get up there i can just chill nice work now give it to me yes your back hurts yes
it does hide can you see me here we go with the darts turn around and too early yeah just a little
bit did it all all right now what where do i go from here how do i can't leave
wait wait hold on wait give me that i did it yeah why this house is so tiny
why am i a fucking monster that's pretty terrifying well i can't go that way yet
so we'll go this way wait let me rinse off okay this is a model village steal the beautiful
miniature golden bell why would i do that this doesn't sound very nice oh wait this is this is
the whole world oh and that's me that's on the left that's me looking into the model playing
the game with the goose in the middle there whoa whoa that's cool what else is over here i don't
remember this lady rip it out oh that's satisfying it is come on yes feels good remember this is the
that was like opening a wine bottle yeah can i get the well this is the pub so what if i go
over there what happens am i i'm it's avatar being faced with reality this is not good
it was how back to the future four is gonna end off hold on i can't i find move it hurts
i'm fucking pumping into shit put me down put me down i'm not doing that again wait if i lean
down can you this is gonna be fucking weird can you hear that i have to eat the building i don't
it's a what is a sand castle that was i need to uh if there there is probably some new viewers
here i need i am about uh one or two clicks shy of beating the world record for clicking
with one hand as fast as possible i almost beat it on stream just in case anyone was curious
pull it why am i destroying this this doesn't seem right i have to get the bell do i need to
break it down some more what about this side no i'm just too weak come on i can do it let's go
oh that was loud oh get the fuck out of here man
steal the bell and then take it all the way back home
let's go give me the bell give it about wait i'm gonna alert everybody
i don't like awaken everybody and they turn get out of the way is there gonna be some like
meta like bioshock thing is it like fuck out of here
oh right why is this so scary the music is scary music i can't open this why is this locked
what where am i oh let me out no don't let me out no i have to bring the bell all the way back and
it alerts everybody of course it does give me that i distracted with megalovania it works every time
yeah no they can where they're gonna bring it where are you gonna bring that bell to untie
his shoes no i need that get the get out of my way god damn it trip just trip and fall and break
your face come on who has the bell good he's got blood all over him okay i'm not doing that again
let's go i'm stuck on give me the fucking bell give me the bell give me the bell give me that
bell she's holy shit she gave it to me go please ah you don't have oh why what's the problem over
here looks like you don't have jurisdiction i may as well have crossed over to mexico
you're fucking idiot ding dong ding dong ding dong you're gonna lock me out of this one
how would i do that i just i rang the big one what am i thinking what are you gonna do
we're gonna bring it huh what are you gonna do with it i'll play along for a little bit what
are you doing are you okay fine oh my god i'm so stupid
give me that sign oh not my sign oh he still has the bra
he's been trying to get that over there for a long time
oh what's the matter it doesn't look like
i gotta get the bell back gotta get the bell back gotta get the bell back
uh-oh later the broom he thought he was brave for a second but he's still scared of geese
so he ain't gonna do anything
oh the final boss he was waiting at the door let's go i think i did it yeah i think that's it
i made it what where's my home ah let's see i have i remember so i spoiled the whole game when i
looked at everybody was like why did you look back there you weren't supposed to do that
wait a minute is that why i have the bike over here
because i love that sound oh wow okay let's see what the climax is good night so that you just
taking bells i can't honk during the cut scene well there's gonna be an after credit scene
she finally got it this game was good it was they took a concept of i just be a goat
and they made it just that was just adorable that would what i would classify that as a cute
game i love what was it like three hours like that it's a little short but i mean it's still
14 15 bucks goose right i don't know it's been a long week oops what happened some people are
linking i clicked it i clicked it i clicked it look this is from joel joel said also my
message earlier got lost in the fray of comments but i wanted to shout out how talented and creative
you are you're making the rest of us look bad i don't know about that that means a lot though
thanks a lot joe seriously that means a lot coming from a fellow fucking comedian you know
what i mean somebody as funny and talented as you saying that means a lot it does what
hold on wait wait there's new cabbage picnic
you just unlock more things to do get thrown over the fence score a goal
reset to give this a go complete the garden to-do list before the church bell rings that's what the
bell was remember earlier i was wondering i'll set everything on the to-do list so every area
now has like an extra little thing to do lock the groundskeeper out of the garden so it's just
another day the last one is impossible collect the five flowers in the basket over by the well
a tulip a lily a rose a daisy a chrysanthemum sail the toy boat under a bridge oh i have to do that
perform at the pub wearing a ribbon steal the old man's wooden hat rake in lake really fast
there is no raking lake oh it actually is new game plus it's everything is the same
that's i thought it was a reset no it's not all right open an umbrella inside the tv shop make
something from outside the high street buy back their own stuff what uh cabbage picnic is easy
no it's not not even close it's gonna be very hard actually cabbage pick this is gonna oh shit
do i have to get them all there's one or two how many do i need this is hard did you just take a
bite out of it all the physics on this is so difficult let's see if i can keep it just through
the gate i wonder if you need more than one come on cabbage picnic i at least have to get one of
these go don't roll too far don't run it easy easy easy cabbage picnic beautiful
trip the boy in the puddle okay what's the other stuff catch an object as it's thrown over the
fence all right i know how to do that one score a goal so i have to get the soccer ball from the
kid all the way over how do i get thrown over the fence yeah you can make the kid fall so trip the
kid right here so you have to untie you have to scare him so scare him back this way
back this way uh germa sucks just gave 20 community subs thank you germa sucks
appreciate it that's a lot let's see right in the puddle boom and now come there it is
streamer sucks no thank you it's a lot of subs open an umbrella in the tv shop one of these
umbrellas the hell do i open this in here can i grab the other side oh shit okay can i close it
close it up how do i close the umbrella i can't okay well i know how that works though i got
three chances here does it count does it count does it count does it count does it count oh you
closed it for me thank you do this one too please oh my god jeremy sorry i want to do with the this
one anyways with the rake in the lake i'm not doing the rake in the lake no no rake in lake
now where's the kid can i pull you over here please get out of my life see you later i can't
do rake in lake guys the rake doesn't exist that was a great parry move that she just did
lock the groundskeeper make someone from outside that okay i gotta score a goal
score a goal i can bring it over here shit get out of the store out of the store no shit why
did i roll it this way that was a mistake there's a rake right there i can't grab it all right i'm
done i'm out i'm out you did it good congratulations no stop get out get me this break it for all i
get good no it's almost there it's almost so close just move penguin let the penguin do that for a
move okay bye almost there so now the soccer i think soccer's up here i think right don't
kick it back this is so cute i love both not once i mean besides this the arms just never come up
not a bad dribble no it's not it's pretty good actually it's not bad where's the which way is it
it's a left no where's the where's the soccer net i don't remember i hope it's this way well but
those of you that um we talked a lot about the carnival earlier and i wanted to reiterate one
more time that you can expect something like that to happen every few months now that shit is already
we're already starting to work on a talk on the next one not carnival life i'm just saying just
something like that and i brought this all the way over here oh this is bad you're gonna get hit in
the face of the frog every couple months maybe depends on what we do all right is he going to
steal the soccer ball if they see this will they take it dude don't take the ball away from me
take out your cell phone videotape this and make like two hundred thousand dollars by this youtube
video that would have a billion views film it sell it to a news agency license the video out
put cat food out now or bird food out in front of your door to bring this fucking goose back
to get new videos every day carry the goose you would be worth millions of dollars
why would you be angry at this this is just depositing free money into your checking account
all you have to do is film it it's an awesome goose it doesn't understand what money is
and then you could just buy the goose a gigantic goose house and put all the things that goose
love the most in there that was not a bad shot there it is don't roll all the way down where is
it this one sucks i'm going the wrong way the net is right over here is this not the correct net
this has to be oh boy there it is hooray all right catch an object as it's thrown over the fence so
here's what i'm gonna do i'm gonna put the bra in the water guy's gonna throw i'm gonna catch
it when he throws it over yeah why was she watching him that was weird yes easy no he's
gonna throw it over i'm gonna put it right in front of him i'm gonna wait for the newspaper
watch this newspaper goes up he's gonna look newspaper goes check it out i'm gonna drop it
right in front of his t here we go one two three go unavoidable now i'm gonna get back over wait
i he's an idiot i forgot that didn't count why did that not count that should have counted
come on that's that is technically he reached his arm over and let it go he threw that over the
fence it's vase yeah i think the vase will work getting scammed by technicalities all right where
is it where is he where does he throw it right here where does he throw it oh no
over here shit will he do it again he throws it like right here i'll be ready oh fuck me
no don't throw it yet don't throw it yet throw it now that don't count i think that counts i don't
know about that one that was pretty good perform at the pub with the ribbon on that isn't that
impossible no i have to get it and walk all the way around where is the ribbon it's stuck it goes
in the bush over here right oh all right no let's see i can do that let's go all right she sees
isn't this kind of sad like i want to be the thing that she loves i'm the real one it's me
and i'm taking it away throwing it away standing there showing her i want to be your friend this
is sad shit she's on me just just put the fucking thing on my neck please it's right next to me
no stand there what are you doing don't move she just puts the sock over my beacon head
perfect don't see it don't see it don't see it don't see it don't see it don't see it yeah
so now i have to go all the way back almost the whole way right well not all the way
can i get there from here because then if i wrap around this way here's the pub
um good to go is the person not delivering you know oh his ass is still all red why is it coming
in blood because there was this crazy weird really really kind of screwed up part of the game where
you put a bunch of glass down you break a bunch of glass bottles and you make him walk in the room
and you scare him and he lands and he sits on them it's horrible it's kind of out of place in
out of place in a game like this weirdly i don't know all right excuse me
i have some performing to do i've got the ribbon i'm ready for my close-up
i'm done with the game i think i think that's the end of the game i've done what i wanted to do
that was very fun that was a great what about the mail that's one thing there's probably a secret
with the mail right there are a lot of random stuff look at all those where's the secret menu
it doesn't even show up what about the boat oh wait let's try that you just wanted an excuse to
do your funny voices oh yeah i had to do my my voices i'll get the boat i have to let it go on
the water i guess okay is this a cartoon if i remove the no duck sign does that mean that
ducks i can go in there oh looks like ducks are allowed in here no problem at all if only there
was a sign that said no ducks could come in here i would not even have attempted all right well i
was if i gotta sneak in no no get out i'm not going near that box if i from you take this box
back but what catch an object get thrown over the fence dress up with things steal the old man's
wooden hat so there are speed runs to be thrown over the i don't think i can take this is can i
take this what what kind of magic trick did we just do that was an act huh all right i'm just
gonna leave there we go use her to get thrown over the fence all right um i need a toy boat
i'm not even in there anymore don't worry well i can't get on the first step i'm not
allowed to step on the first step that's not even your place of business shut up that's
enough falling fall down all right i got the uh okay you're just really you're pissing me off
now i'm just gonna go right for the night well i almost got toy boat it was close it was close
all right let me see if i can um i'm only gonna do this like one more time toy boat toy boat
let me see i just i'd warm it up let me see if i can do this like three or four times fast
so
good please give me the boat please give me the boat please give me the boat please give
me the boat i just want the boat that's all i care about no she's going for the boat i gotta break
shit i have to drop stuff all over the place i gotta make a mess i made it easier piece of shit
no i don't i didn't i i yes i put a plate down one level i know all right i should have it all
right toy boat goes in the what was that i keep this guy is the hardest enemy he keeps kicking me
out oh all right now i just gotta put it in make it go under a bridge this bridge right here
sail the toy boat under a bridge which way is the water flowing fuck aha good good good good good
good good get thrown over the fence and i'm in the water though kind of went all the way back
didn't i whatever works that's true i still i can i not can i not go in here all right i'm gonna
hide that there that's fine all right that might be it it might be time i was trying to get it as
close to being in without it going in rake in the lake there you go the thing you wanted to see so
bad i don't know why why why is that the thing in this game why is that the thing oh okay wait
what did i even examine this stuff i got my collection of cans and i want i kind of want
another one of these games i want another one right i want i want another game like this i'm
hungry for more can this be one of those stories where the developer made this just goofy game and
oh that was fun just a funny little game and then they get like three million dollars in funding to
do it again do it with different animals yeah do like a bear untitled bear game what would wait
probably not as a rat you can make a lot of fun scenarios instead of a little squeak it's that
loud bear scream i would love to just eat out of people's trash and by the way there's i'm
gonna give you a i'm gonna call the back of the box the tell us how we're doing comments that's
on the back of randomly for some reason like drinks and sodas and shit you don't remember that
stuff all right you there's a honk button there's a grab button that needs to be also a swallow
button i'm gonna be able to eat this stuff like i need to be able to chew this and swallow and eat
it that'd be fun no no dedicated shit button that's not what i mean i'm just i want to be able to
just chew stuff up i'm gonna be able to pull the slipper off the guy's foot and just chew it up
have i played the cat lateral damage i actually have this i like this more than that though that
game is more just to make a mess for 30 seconds this is just walk around and be a duck and this
is more charming to me than the goat simulator was you know i i'm gonna give you a stamp of
recommendation on this one this it's cute it's cute enough but that is probably it's actually
probably gonna do it for today i have a couple things i need to get done i have to get ready
for twitchcon i have to pack i am going to stream tomorrow so this is not just the only stream we're
gonna get this week i'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow is it kind of also up in the air this
was just a random game that turned out this is i had a lot of fun this is great uh tomorrow is
going to be similar though i don't really have much of a plan haven't really been around i just
kind of got back been out of i've been out of the i don't even know what games have come out i don't
even know what's released in the last like week and a half or so so we'll do something for at
least like a good five six hours tomorrow before i have to leave i'll figure it out community
content stream tomorrow uh i don't think so i think it's too early for that i want to give
people at least a few weeks at least a month or so to really get the first one nice and meaty
we'll figure it out but again i want to make this very clear too my stream schedule is pulling back
remember four or five months ago when i talked about after the carnival stream
i was going to start to pull the streams back an hour or two streams are going to be starting
an hour or two early than they are than they happen so instead of like three to four
pacific it's going to be somewhere around like two like one to two pacific so between like four and
five eastern is where i want the streams to start from now on and i've talked about a little bit
more the streams because i'm on pacific time if i stream till like 10 11 12 at night it's really
really late for everybody if people watch from europe there it's like six o'clock in the morning
eastern time it's like two three o'clock in the morning so i'm going to pull it back
and with that guys we are going to transition to uh hold on a second hold on the new outro screen
thanks for coming everybody appreciate everybody's uh coming in good shit oops i
fucked it up i screwed it up you weren't supposed to see that hold on there we are
everybody welcomed uh please don't throw your popcorn at the screen
i appreciate if you wouldn't please make a a formal exit on the left side there are your exits
and uh thanks for coming up i need to figure out how this works because this is the first
time i've tried it don't throw tomatoes at me either either hold on peter let me figure this
out because this name is up here i don't think this is i think i screwed this up
did i screw this up maybe not oh i definitely messed it up somehow i'll figure it out next
but this will have all the the highest bit tip of the day whoever gave the highest
and then on the right side it'll be the whoever gave the most during that
period and then the top sub gifter on the left i actually might try to cycle these out too
maybe i'll do like today's bit leader and then have like longest running gifted the longest running
sub or something like top sub gifting so many people give gifted subs that it's almost like
it's its own category 10 000 but this also this track loradale made all this i've been sitting
on it for a while i love this out this song is great i will get these correct here's the
cool thing about this though everybody has left see you later guys only a few of you still in
here i can also get rid of those people too it's a rat then we can hang out here by the way the
screen up there i can drop the music and we can put something up there pictures random videos
stuff like that how cool is this though the germaplexis cinema is the janitor
you wait yeah you guys could do a webcam in there too yeah there's the rat still clean it up and
then janitor can finish up over here and then take a look at this it's over why are we inside of your
mouth that's a great question so this is the first of quite a few of these i gotta get back in touch
with loradale and we'll do the next few parts there's gonna be a lot of tracks a lot of audio
a bunch of new transition scenes i'm trying to really get it going but yeah i will figure out
how i messed that up somehow rip the old outro that is not true still here because that plays
when the stream is actually over and we can come back over to here while we just hang out i do want
to add a bunch of things but these are fucking fantastic as they are now get a couple more
scenes in here some more cleanup you but my burping is annoying what do you mean burp my burping
you need to hire a new janitor no did the intro screen change not yet i plan on doing a whole
thing but uh why don't we do the bits thanks everybody for watching that's gonna be it
the transition is scary well good so all of you get to get out of here i love that all the
everybody all the people leaving the theater he's actually going to be switched around
they all came back in i can leave that up for as long as i want to but why don't we go ahead and
go back uh earlier today thank you everybody again first stream back from the carnival
i'll see you tomorrow we'll do something else before i go to switchcon and then i'm on another
fucking airplane it is what it is though busy but excited to be busy so thank you to
where we had there was so much money given earlier to like a ridiculous amount thank you to bake me
home for the 15 we both know this is for the carnival stream that was insane i'm glad you
delivered can you tell us what you said to stir back in the germa watchers old video stream you
told him something about mutant star said there's no way that's working i believe i told him um how
many games were going to be played and i think i told them how much money it cost i believe that's
what i told him but thank you the 15 dollars appreciate it that's you're under no obligation
to pay me money for the carnival i did it because i wanted to right smelly boy thanks to the 250
goose game is goat simulator 2019 edition i i disagree i disagree i think it's a little more
charming flug boy thanks with five community subs appreciate it thank you thank you thank you
that was flug boy also zake thanks to the 250 one time i was at the beach skipping rocks and
eating a sandwich and i threw my sandwich in the ocean and bit the rock i hope your teeth are okay
doesn't not sound that does not that sounds like it hurts sorry to hear that wolf gang thanks to
the five dollars wolf gang germa you better have um x vacation john adams and me in the next germa
rumble me there are a lot of characters now i told you that there was going to be another germa
wrestling event before the end of the year and i still mean that so there's a lot to choose from
now got my new favorite character tooth prick is it going to be a christmas stream i don't know i
don't know i don't really plan on it if i have an idea for something that i think is fun that just
i'll do it i would assume there'll be something i've done a christmas themed thing that was an
elaborate thing the last two years in a row so kind of have to make it three in a row right
we'll see i'll pj ffs thanks for the five community subs earlier i missed it thank you
thank you to peaceful hailey for the 250 hey germy happy birthday you're getting pretty old
but you still look the ripe young age of 33 hope it was a good birthday it was it was great
yeah i don't look a day older than 33 34 by the way yes yes i'm 34 years old the thing 35 is the
real the one that sits in your brain and you just go that's old between 30 and 35 you got time to
still because i gotta i'm gonna say it again every drop down menu that you can think of
where you have to pick your age range it's always 18 to 34 i don't get to be a kid anymore at 35
i have to go up to 35 to 55 that's not gonna feel nice that's no that's one that's less than a year
away oh well tried and jacks thanks with five community subs trying jacks you're getting out
of your own demographic shh don't say that don't say that too loud but thanks for the five subs
trident uh you five zero or you fo you five oh thanks to the four dolls my fail my favorite
elberton boy streaming again for now tomorrow also streaming and then twitchcon i won't be
streaming at twitchcon i will be there but i won't be streaming from twitchcon and when i get back
we will get back to normal for a little while nothing major is really planned in october
besides maybe a halloween maybe we'll play some scary games or something but we're gonna go back
to normal for a while it's been a busy few months thank you uh grimmy for the five dollars i went
through some really tough emotional things recently and your videos helped me through them so much
thank you whatever it is they were i'm really sorry to hear that thank you so much for the
five dollars i'm glad you like the videos in the content and the community too this is a great
community people here are great that's pretty fucking rare don't forget that it's important
but seriously thank you so much for the five bucks oh right i'm sorry i'm supposed to be putting
things here i gotta make some stuff to put in there you need to shave my face cam that's right
uh i gotta stream labs obs is kind of weird i have to figure out how to do this stuff
because it's when you add a source the sources already exists it's kind of i think it's gonna
take some getting used to oh yes uh by the way this is i i didn't this is how i've been sitting
in here for a very long time i'm just realizing this right now so uh this is a fucking this is a
weird movie hey all of you come back in the theater it's not done yet um we had alchemy can
thousand bits from alchemy can 10 bucks thanks for the carnival man here's for you and your
team's work we all appreciate it a lot of time went into that and a lot of people were involved
even just the robots alone trying to figure out what i wanted to do and could that translate to
actually have it on video and camera we when we were when we were setting up the inputs i remember
just going uh to the one of the engineers i was like so um how much can that handle how much can
you actually handle in this thing how many inputs per second i was like because it's probably gonna
be like it's probably gonna be like a thousand inputs a second and i remember his his eyes kind
of widening him going oh shit okay so we should let me see if i can figure that out god i think
that it really and that was by the way probably two or three hours before the stream started
because we were planning on thinking how we were going to do it should i have sub only turned on
no i don't really want to do that because that's i'd rather have as many people participate as
possible because it's more chaotic right it's more fun that way but do i need to mitigate the amount
of inputs that come in because the machines physically cannot take it chat went so fast my
feed was buffering yeah i put on a little slow mode just to try to help there was a couple of
points when i think this you guys broke the server they were connected to and that's when i had to
kill time for 10 straight minutes sometimes but it was worth it it was worth it there was more
than 16 000 people there i know it's a rat um yeah i think it was it was almost at 16 5 17 000
concurrent that's the highest i've ever had ever i think it just blew it completely blew it away
where did you find those clowns they were they were in the area the old one was like 12k now it
it blew past my previous high of viewers that came in a lot of new people too and even i mean
if you if you're new here even today um there was like 62 6300 people here today that's a lot of new
viewers i think so hopefully you like it here maybe you were just checking out the stream i
followed just to see what it was all about hopefully we see you again because there was
a lot of new people here i think today yeah i'm talking about the old how what the record was to
break the old one viewership wise the official twitch uh yeah i saw the tweet too they tweeted
it out they and they like censored it too that was that was that's my favorite part it's like
you'll never dunk me you'll never do it and then i like it dunked i said like the f word fucking
three times they like cut out the swear it's all right whatever i gotta clean up my act a little
bit anyways is the stream ending the street yes this is the new stream wind down screen there's
going to be more additions to this we're going to add more stuff what happens if i do this oh i'm
gone now you can't see me at all remind him to cut his nails thank you i don't i'm okay with being
look i'm okay with being toothpick guy but i'm not okay with being long nails guy because that's
something that people talk about because you're gross right i don't want to do that all right let
me uh let me go back to where we were cool cool cool make sure i didn't miss anything from here
up that got that that came in it was alchemy can that's what it was for a thousand bits thank
you alchemy can we had coca-ronas for five dollars do you remember where you got those toy frogs in
the frog game um no that was actually andy mark andy mark had those so because they were doing
testing on how heavy things needed to be and apparently those frogs were the perfect weight
to launch uh i'm not exactly sure where they got them only knew is that frogs needed to be involved
because you know i'm a frog or i'm a rat you know i'm a frog i'm a rat i like both those animals
like they're both i think toads are cool too no i'm not turning the light on it's this is how
it's gonna be i'm gonna be the weird floating head goats are cool too i like goats i like geese
after today i mean i kind of really do but yeah andy mark supplied those so i'm not sure where
they exactly where they got them but thank you tried jacks for the five dollars uh didn't leave
much of my last year just want to say how much you've positively affected my life thank you for
being you much love it's amazing how you continue to grow and evolve with your comedy while you
still remain completely insane while still remaining completely insane uh much love i
i just i just kind of do the things that i'm gonna do i look like snook from the last jedi
young so i'm gonna be young snook but anyways thank you uh for the five dollars trident jacks
if i can be a positive influence or affect you positively that's i i'm floored and i'm shocked
i'm happy that you can get anything out of this at all anything it surprises me every day that i am
a positive influence to some people i hope you turned into something good right like i hope you
turn it into something good influencer i don't like that word i like the term what was it sidewalk
clown what was it we came up with the term sidewalk clown right yeah yeah yeah that's what it was
but yes thank you fat hector for the thousand bits ten dollars from fat hector hey germa the
carnival stream seemed too good to be free so here's what i can give thanks for the laughs
carnival stream um i would not have put a payment on that there's no way i would have done that
i wanted as many people to come check it out as possible i'm not putting a pay to watch
or pay to participate i just i don't want to do that i'd rather have as many people as possible
see it that's more important to me than trying to make extra money i i guess i don't really
that doesn't could i have like sub gated that or something but what the fuck do i carry you
know i mean i don't i don't i'd rather have people watch it than have um it be sub gated or
something more publicity yeah i mean i guess that's normal what i was thinking of when i wanted to do
this though was not how do i i want to get all of it everywhere how do i get on the front page of
every page that just was something that i wanted to do i'm happy it was received well i'm very happy
i mean if it was received really poorly then that's a completely different story
and then i have to come up here and embarrassingly turn this stream on and say yep uh
didn't really work out that well now did it so i'm glad it went well but thank you fat hector
appreciate it uh germa saved the game gave five dollars germa saved the game you remind me save
the game all right local eccentric millionaire arrested and declared insane after hiring a full
production crew to film himself completely alone in his illegal backyard carnival
when interviewed he stated that 10 000 people were in attendance uh despite neighbors claims
to the contrary well i mean they technically were 10 000 people not in attendance but in
digital attendance digital attendance it still counts backyard illegal carnival hey germa
thanks for the 250 germa peaked at four foot six inches i'll see it i'll see it twitchcon i'll
fucking be taller than you i shouldn't say that because that's not true but i won't be as tall
i won't be as short as you think i am hey infinity reese thanks for the six dollars all the bits i
own just to make the echo stop make the echo stop is it was that the goose thing was it one of my
head was in the thing make it stop i didn't do anything but thank you for the six dollars 600
bits that was five hours ago yes it was it was a long time ago so that's true but thank you
infinity reds i'm gonna call you infinity reds or it's infinity reese it's not throwing tomatoes
you know you can't have very many left oh muffin thanks for the five dollars 500 bits i love how
dedicated you are to making people laugh you're honestly my favorite streamer thank you for
helping me out in hard times and just being you yeah i'm i would say i'm more dedicated to
trying to have a good time you know i i put how do i how do we collectively have a good time
i don't know let me think right if i come up with something that i think will solve that riddle
and let's go like i said that's not the last time you're going to see something like that
that's the first time and not even the first time we've done stuff like that before not to that
scale but we've still done it but yeah i'm i'm humbled and shocked every day and thankful every
day that there's people that think that this channel is funny enough to watch all the time
and to participate in crazy fucking ideas like i want a twitch controlled robot carnival
you know i mean i am absolutely fortunate that people think that this shit is still interesting
so that's all i that's really what i have to say you have to make the funny streamer noise now
now that only comes out when it comes out i don't even control that it just comes out
but that was uh oh muffin thanks for the five dollars 500 bits door cube thanks for the 250 bits
recently watched rewatched a vod in which i told you in a bit message that you had peaked with tf2
boxes but how howdy was i wrong you're not only a god of a gamer but a god of an entertainer
love you jerry that was a good one though jerry i like the new setup yeah i do too i think it's
great i think it's very fun i like the whole you were watching in the theater context thing
10 000 of you were watching in this theater just don't just don't close your but we are inside of
the mouth you you're right that that's a mouth yeah that's that just put another layer on top
for me that was great that's awesome that's fucking awesome unbelievable we are the mouth you are no
this is just inside of somebody's mouth i don't know or an animal i could be we're just germs in
here or you are i mean you're just you opened some wherever this person is opened their mouth
and i'm standing in front of them just doing a show and you guys are all in this person's mouth
and seats this person's been keeping their mouth open for a very long time i'm the dentist i'm the
comedy dentist open up i would be a pretty good dentist no i wouldn't i'd be a terrible dentist
i got my hands are like so shaky i wouldn't be able to ever do anything like that
but i'll store h2o thanks to the 250 i know you probably heard this a lot over the past week but
the carnival stream is probably the best stream that's not the best piece of media that i've seen
all year you and the rest of the team did an excellent job and i'm glad it was able to call
all come together get that stream nominated for an emmy i'm so fucking happy i i'm so happy that you
guys liked it there's always this little demon in the back of your head that even when we got
up to like like the day before is just sitting there going you know this whole thing could just
go completely fucking wrong and nobody will think it's funny and nobody will think it was interesting
and i'm just sitting there going get get up get out of here the asmr demon now obviously there
was so much that went into this that i was that was not really on my brain at all i was we were
too busy and too focused on trying to get it to get together and as time came forward we realized
that it was going to be a lot of fun so but it doesn't matter like i always just want to make
sure that people regardless of how much money the stream costs or it doesn't matter if it's that
stream it could be this stream too the one that you just watched the one that you're on right now
now i just want to make sure that it's something fun something interesting something people don't
take away something that they didn't like or that sucked i don't want you to think that
now go ahead no spit please go ahead and rinse and spit oh wait and we're in a dark room too
imagine going to the dentist and it's this dark in here would you leave all right what if it was
like five star rated dentist on yelp would you go to this dentist yeah it turned out the dentist had
this weird thing with like light he just just dude they just couldn't have light on it was something
with a it was a some kind of condition or something with light you couldn't be in light but he was
like the best dentist in the world would you be in like a dark room dentist thing who rates dentists
on yelp you rate every people write every business on yelp don't they where's the whale right here
are those whiskers wait does whale lord have whiskers or is that no that's like that's the
grill okay that's like the whale's grill get some dogs on there uh but anyways what the hell was i
just saying i don't really i have no idea thank you to rvm for the 5000 bits they said yo merry
christmas 5000 bits 50 dollars from rvm i think you were on the screen already but something was
weird rvm gave a hundred dollars actually here almost in a row they say yo merry christmas and
diarrhea every morning that's an old one that is an old that's that is an old reference thank you
though for the 10 000 bits a lot of money thanks whale the whale's fine i'm gonna i'll bring that
everywhere i go because i had to bring something as much of a pain in the ass as that was to bring
from airport to airport and carry it around and stuff and like the terminals i wanted to keep
something from it that was i have i do have an andy mark goat as well but i will never get rid
of that i'll have that forever i really don't think i'll ever get rid of that i told you now
you have to delete that username there's two or three people that have those usernames
now you gotta now you gotta get rid of them where are the pikachu socks i wore them that's all that
matters i wore them and they were in that container what about the goats you can buy oh wait are they
still available can somebody confirm is that page sold out or can you actually still buy them i know
that they were um somebody can somebody link that prove it what do you mean prove it prove it yeah i
wore them on stream for almost two hours yeah they're still available okay but thank you for
the 10 000 bits rvm really appreciate it heat legend thanks for the thousand bits
happy birthday funny streamer man thank you it was a good one it was a good one uh grow
lith thanks for the five dollars only managed to watch the vod of the carnival but i loved every
second of it and i could tell you did too thank god your creativity didn't go to someone with
their head up their ass love you jeremy germa hart yeah me too me too uh somebody that was
working on the project actually brought something interesting up and they said it's really awesome
when everybody that is working on a project and there were more than 10 people that had a hand in
this so every single person that was working on it was having a great time and i was so that was
insanely important to me was i want to make sure everybody is comfortable everyone's having a good
time that everyone you're like passionate about this project and then you really really like it
and you really want to give time to it and care about it and all of them did every single person
that was there was just having such a fucking blast and that's when it clicks like that no
there was no scenario where it was oh i really got to run this through this guy and oh no no i
don't know about i don't know i don't like what she said to me earlier but at the set meeting no
it was none of that not zero oh nobody was like i gotta have to i'm gonna have to ask germa about
this and he's a fucking diva he's probably gonna like take a swing at me no it was just
fun when people have egos like that for something creative it's the worst i don't want that that's
like why it's bad when that happens i don't want that to happen maybe not to your face
they're all i got it they're all i got dinner sitting around oh man that was horrible he was
the worst with a capital w don't look straight into the camera it's creepy why i can't look
over i can't look right i can't look you in the eye i can't look you in the eye when i'm talking to
you turn around i mean i'm looking at chat but when i want when i address i'm not when i'm not
addressing just one message boom we're up here and there you are i'm talking to you that's who i'm
talking to tell lord out uh his work is lovely i will i will if you didn't get to see it there's
here's the other one this one's great this is i love this it's so wonderful it's just so cute
but thank you too that was a growlithe everybody clicked it was a great set it was a great
because we were kind of just absolutely just ass to the ground running since i left on that
last stream you saw me stream before the carnival it was just bang bang bang bang bang bang let's
go let's get it done i'm very happy with it ecstatic with it and some of them are actually
going to be at twitchcon so it was great it was hey that was really fun we worked on that and
you're gonna be at twitchcon are you serious nice let's hang out i want to keep those relationships
going thank you kitty rocketeer for the thousand bits germa that carnival was one of the best
things i've ever seen thank you i'm really glad you think so thank you gnarly for the thousand
bits as well carnival stream was a ton of fun loved every second of it thanks for being the
best content creator on the site also by the way don't forget to cut your gross fucking nails
before twitchcon thank you i would have forgot somebody did it 15 minutes ago i would have just
forgot thank you that was gnarly for a thousand bits we also had okay ice cream for two dollars
and 50 cents 250 bits hi germa me my friend wanted to buy a goat but shipping was like
70 feels bad man holy shit uh also the carnival stream was amazing i loved it
70 dollars yeah that ship shipping from america overseas always is an extra at least one to two to
300 percent wherever it's going i wish i could change it but that's another reason why i like
to keep my t-shirts cheaper i like to keep all my t-shirts at like 18 to 22 dollars because i know
you're gonna spend like 30 fucking dollars to have it shipped to you if you're from another country
so i completely understand those who they bought your shirts from uh from eu how much was the
shipping is there a like an average 50 20 20 bucks 50 bucks two roblox well i think we got
two actual answers in there so i think that maybe even one how many people like this there's like
3200 people here and i get one real answer wow damn all right but thank you again that was uh
okay ice cream i'm really sorry that you have to spend that much money to get anything shipped
i wish shipping wasn't so ridiculous for some places hey uh ov peel thanks for the five dollars
no message just 500 bits egg johnson 500 bits hey germa been watching since 2012 when i was like
15 and seriously man you've gotten better in your senior 60 plus years you do some avant-garde shit
and it's insanely inspiring also how do i stop uh cutting myself with a safety razor i do it every
single time but i've been using it for like two years well it's here's the thing you gotta be very
very gentle and careful when you shave with a safety razor you gotta let the weight of the blade
do the work you don't push you don't drag let the weight of the blade do it slight angle gentle
i know that some people have places to be you got time i don't want to shave it's gonna take 20
minutes to shave just relax and let just work it gently you don't have to go fast when people
shave their faces that's why some of these brands they do so well because they have the 12 blades
and they have all the jelly shit all over it and they've been engineered in a way to make it so
you can shave your entire face in the same amount of time that it takes to brush your teeth no you
that should not be what you do that's how you get irritation more blades reduce irritation i'm telling
you just rip the hair out more blades reduce here too i yeah but they've been engineered and designed
that way to make it so people just you get i used to know somebody this is fucking crazy by the way
and this i'm not making this up i knew somebody that shaved with water and it was it was impossible
to me it was impossible to shave with water they had to have been lying but it wasn't a situation
where somebody was gonna lie it was just really randomly off the cuff just not being pressed on
they just mentioned it without it we weren't even we weren't even talking about shaving really
well i just use water it just came out like oh we talked about just it randomly popped up somewhere
it wasn't like i can't wait to lie about how i shave my face i use ketchup soap maybe they
talk maybe they do soap i couldn't do that either though the soap in water i would be so scared i
have to have a big santa beard of cream before i even begin i thought you meant they shaved literally
using water no blade no no like they put like they put water on their face and shaved
their face with the water on their face how that's not even possible what's wrong with just using
water are you you shave with just water you gotta fill us in that's it freaks me out you do yes you
do i do i do yes okay how do you not tug it doesn't tug it tugs doesn't it when you shave
it's like you just do it but you have you just have to pressure the blade carefully you just do
it i don't i would never shave with just water i would get to a point where i would you can hear
it it goes like and then you feel a tug and i stop and i go i'm not doing it yeah i don't i
could never do it but thank you egg johnson for the 500 bits appreciate it where does face go oh
it's gone let's do this i love that little i love that like the close-up of the janitor
that's wonderful hey mini clips thanks for the thousand bits just use a lighter to burn off all
the small hairs cheap and effective uh well here's the thing cheap yes effective no dangerous yes
should i do this no should you have read that message out loud no did you do it anyways yes
why i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know no just whatever razor you use
just be careful it's it's still a blade you just be careful with it be gentle take care of it use
an adequate amount of cream he doesn't know maca s what does he not know what if you heated the
razor you kind of do i i run my razor over the hot hot hot water but what i do is i have like a
little thing where i just put hot water in it and just go and so the blade is nice and
warm and hot feels great no not glowing hot you guys are fucking crazy so there's a blow torch
and get it like red hot you just burn your face don't listen to the people in this chat they're
just being weirdos hey grapple mace thanks for the 250 hey germa was having a very anxious day
saturday and the carnival stream put me in such a good mood and pumped me up so much
i had to dance out the excess energy later that night it was one of the best streams i've ever
been ever been to thank you so much for doing it love you dancing out that energy nice i've been
you know it's been a long time since i've really danced out some energy maybe you know i'm maybe
i'm gonna i'm gonna dance at twitchcon okay i'm gonna have the i'm gonna be tooth prick and i'm
gonna dance and the second that somebody pulls up to the camera to film me i'm immediately gonna
stop and just stare at them one of you guys better get that out of them thank you sad vega
with the 250 streamer german n85 uh dies from a tragic toothpick related accident streamer
german i5 is is here right now fine german tooth prick i don't think i can put i don't think the
word prick could be used in an emote sorry to say but thank you uh sad vega thank you to
feitoru for the five dollars they say honk thank you feitoru maverick thanks for the thousand
bits love your videos man born and raised in boston and moved to the cape and now i'm stuck
in the eu let's meet up and share a firm handshake and cheers at quincy market by the way i have some
bits what are you doing in the eu how'd you go how'd you go from boston to the cape to eu i wonder
what the i wonder what that journey sounds like but yeah i do not i'm not sure i do not live in
boston anymore i live in las vegas they're using fast travel viva las vegas that's right really
like uh that's another thing the internet it's been pretty good almost no drop frames like less
than 500 that's pretty good hey evil crucifix thanks for 1500 bits never forget the seal left
behind well yeah you guys gotta fill me in on this because i leaned into the chat and everyone
was screaming during the stream about seal seal seal i don't know what that means didn't the
carnival stream end because of comcast no no no no we just got to the end no there were no internet
internet issues at all he fell out of the claw machine he bounced off the pro okay we grabbed
a seal in the claw but it dropped before dispensing oh no that's not good that's too bad you guys got
a triple at the end your last grab was a triple you guys were very good at that game you guys
reached down probably 20 to 30 times and i think at least 10 to 15 times you picked something up
go back and get the seal maybe maybe i'll get shipped to me but thank you evil crucifix for the
1500 bits errorless thanks for the 250 your larry david impression sucks not really i'm just trying
to trick you in doing the voice when did i do larry david today i don't know marvosh magali
thanks for the 500 bits i was planning to donate this during the carnival stream but ended up
forgetting while in the middle of spamming commands that was for sure the best project
you ever achieved i'm glad you got recognition you deserve for it keep it up i'm looking forward to
the community content stream stay tuned that's all i gotta say we got way more shit to do there's so
many more streams like that that i want to do that i've had ideas for for years and now they're
finally going to happen things i've never even talked about that are just sitting around waiting
to be done stay tuned thanks for the 500 bits give me 20 dollars gave 10 community subs and pin
man gave 10 community subs back to back i remember that thanks both of you and then we also had i
forgot this scene had my face on it welcome back hello we also had uh okay ice cream for 250 bits
do you have any words of wisdom yes drink way more water than you do uh drink more water and
eat better food eat better food better does not mean more expensive just eat better drink more
water and eliminate some of the sugar from your diet and you don't even you might not even know
that you have you consuming way too much sugar cut back a little on the sugar it's not necessary
and eat some better food and stretch every so often that's right good call just eat better
forehead i mean that yeah supplement look instead of getting like the hamburger and french fries
get the hamburger and the broccoli instead of getting the hamburger instead of getting the
hamburger get the fish no no not every time not every single time you go to like the grocery store
or you go to get food but sometimes like once a week once it don't mcdonald's doesn't serve broccoli
shouldn't be eating mcdonald's more than once every like six or seven years i know this because i
eat it two or three times a week that's a lie that would make a username uh no just just like
honestly like the without like fucking around just just treat your body better like i this is coming
from somebody that didn't for a long time i would drink fucking sodas and this is i'm talking like
15 years ago it catches up with you you just don't realize it cut out the cut out the sugar
and drink more water you better i've just almost hurt myself by laughing again speaking of like
health i almost just laughed and hurt my stomach uh anyways thank you to shoe shroom for the 500
bits you make the goose in my heart do a happy honk that's cute that's a very cute thing to say
thank you shoe shroom for the 500 bits that's a very cute thing to say adorable almost as adorable
as the game how do you guys like this track and this good it's a pretty good chill track i think
oh by the way i'm uh also going to have lord i'll make like 10 more of these stay tuned also thank
you too i love germa and then something else after this 1500 bits here 15 dollars i love germa
thank you i posted a picture of your feet on i got a thousand upvotes okay that's great that's great
i'm not i don't even want to click this image how do i delete somebody else's username why
am i okay as the broadcaster right why can't if somebody has germa in their name why can't i like
why can't i just change their name to like i what's the one guy's names i okay i love ice cream
okay ice cream i'll make that person okay ice cream too he's not a power trip how do i delete
somebody else's username and then replace it why can't i have a society where i just rule
completely no i'm kidding around uh thank you for the 1500 bits i don't i don't even know how to
respond to what you wrote so i'm just gonna say thanks for the 1500 bits i appreciate it that's
very nice of you uh for litty thanks for the five community subs five subs thank you john mert
thanks for the thousand bits they say pogchamp pogchamp that's a that's the viewer on power trip
that's power he didn't even link me i what what is this what do you mean he did he what do you mean
he didn't link me anything he did it's a black screen says you fell for it can you tell that it
was a black screen oh no you fell for it full thunder split it's thunder cross split attack
oh so they were lying thank you too uh bingo bango for the 1000 bits thank you so much then
they say moon moon two pregario is that an emote what is that emote it's a pregnant mario wait
there's a front there's a pregnant luigi as well no that's not why why is there a pregnant mario
and a pregnant luigi that's fucking insane i i can't even i can't even like look at it
it's freaking me out why am i saying it out loud i don't know because it's all it's all i could see
you're here too who's gonna pretend it doesn't exist i'm here you're here and it's every it's
every other message in the chat that's stop making them all right all right all right listen
that's fucking like it's i mean come on i don't know why it's still i don't know i don't know
what the context is on that but like i'm i'm laughing at it i don't even know what the context is
i don't even know what that is all right anyways this guy this guy fucking sucks
at sweeping up popcorn well somebody out there in the back keeps throwing it
he's really good i was rolling my eye what the fuck was that did you see that
why like i got sucked in it was like holy shit that hurt wow he's a lizard he's coming out of his
lizard skin that's probably loud i'm sorry did you reverse it i guess i did that fucking hurt
anyways yeah i'm good now uh we had freudian weapon thanks for the 250 bits from freudian
weapon hey germ just want to wish you a happy belated birthday i've been falling behind on the
strange lady but did manage to catch the carnival stream though loved it can't wait to see what you
and the team do next me either i can't wait i am ready i am ready hey springfield thanks for the
250 bits hey germ i've been a long time fan was wondering if there was a gonna be a follow-up to
the story of my old bones the greatest video ever created there will never be a follow-up
video to that because the story that has been told the story has been told already there's no need
than that guy uh that captain uh i don't know the story he's already told it i like how german
moves out west to do more projects but did a project out east the project started in the west
by the way hold on a second here it wasn't the east coast okay it was eastern time but it was
it wasn't it wasn't it wasn't in matt it was not east coast it was like middle of the country
it was not on the east coast it was eastern time in a central location that would be central time
no that's not true because in some states uh county by county it changes from central to eastern i
don't know why so you did it in england you got it is the beautiful great state of indiana this
guy has a lot of tomatoes why indiana well because it was easy for us to transport the robots
very very easy there's nothing here there's plenty there what are you talking about
why not do it indoors why would i do a carnival indoors that would be scary an indoor carnival
it would be like this if you come into indiana from chicago it smells like a paper mill
i don't i don't even know what that means do i like west world i love season one of west world
that's about it the mall of america is basically an indoor carnival yeah but i
come on i'm talking about like an old midway all right let's can you guys you can't even see what
i'm doing i'm doing like a funny fucking like look at anything and nobody could even see it
all right hey hey hey hey hey hey hey future gamer thanks for the 250 i'm gonna need you to explain
this image explain what image glad i caught to see cool things at blizzard hq take a look
is me puking into a toilet um do you really need context for something what context do you need
here because uh did it did did he post that like two or three times i don't remember was there more
than one of these there might be like two or three hold on i'll put okay why can i show this one yeah
it's not it's fake um so i would start i thought it would be this really funny thing you know i'm
not gonna link it just in case somebody fucking gets upset uh go to go to that link if you want
to see it uh yeah so um star and i had this idea where everything you know people go to
events hey i'm going to twitchcon i'm going to blizzcon oh see it packs and they take pictures
of all kinds of stuff oh look it's the guy from borderlands whoa whoa holy shit it's so cool let's
pan over here what's that oh my god is that thrall get a photo of it selfie like did people post
shit like that all the time to their um to their feeds and we thought what if your feed was like
things that you saw at blizzcon wow hey look what i saw and it's just me throwing up into the toilet
every single time that's i think star has on his phone probably like i mean i don't know about
anymore but i think we did that like four or five times with like me i had different clothes on and
stuff like oh dude i just checked out like holy shit what what like this was this is so cool like
at blizzcon it's just another photo of me like sick in the toilet he still has them he shows
them every stream why would he show them every stream but yeah if if i'm remembering that's what
we were doing there i i you know the funny thing is i actually like slept through most of that
blizzcon i was on a really backwards schedule i was dealing with like some like i think i was
going through like some medical stuff too and i like i fucking slept through the first two days
i didn't even go to blizzcon for like the first two days he has a picture of me in the hotel bed
just sleeping in the bed hey what'd you do at twitchcon and it's and not even like oh wait did
you have a hangover or wow you must did were you like actually sick no not really i mean i
that was such a i remember that too i remember it being like two like one or two o'clock in the
afternoon and i was just sleeping and i rolled over and looked at my phone i was like i don't care
i just we would i wanted to see the overwatch thing and that was it i think i rolled out of bed
at like seven o'clock but yes uh i don't know it just kind of happened but yeah that picture
there's your explanation hopefully hopefully that was uh exact my i was just about to do the thing
again did i turn 34 and got saggy ass eyes what happened i don't like that i don't like i don't
i got i don't want saggy eyes hey oh my god taeyon thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents 250 bits
germa you are a treasure i'm glad you think so glad you think so thank you so are you you're
a treasure too thank you we also had those 20 community subs from germa sucks you have given
a lot of money though germa sucks you have how do i make somebody's username all capitals because
i don't i'm not gonna change your name it's good the way it is thank you though for your 20 community
subs you gave earlier thank you back in for the 250 bits you always fill my day with happiness
germa even if i'm getting to be really uncertain on life i adored the carnival stream by the way
keep going you keep doing you germa heart i'm gonna keep going as long as i am able to do this
uh i told myself a very very very this is you know this is real talk i told myself a very very long
time ago this is like probably 20 30 years ago i was a young young kid that if i ever made it
somehow doing something that i really wanted to do like this that i was going to do everything in
my physical power to try as much do as the best i could and try as hard as i could and do as many
things regardless of if they were good business decisions or not i want i was going to do the
things that i really wanted to do and i'm here now so it's a it's a weird feeling but i'm not
gonna stop so i plan on doing this for as long as i can play spore you got it let's go right now
right let's play spore right now what do you think oh that's gotta download it i want you know i'm
gonna see if lordel can make tomatoes like that go this way to hit me in the face so i can like
react randomly to like tomatoes being thrown at me we're not gonna play spore right now germa lied
about playing spore next username but thank you uh back in for the 250 thank you devakitty for the
250 germa you should play dark wood tomorrow it would be super fun muck ass um wait till october
wait wait till we get october here how are you doing i'll cut him once october rolls around i'll
play some scary stuff like the week or two before halloween oh if i only i could do the thing that i
wanted i said i wanted to do last year on halloween and i don't i'm not gonna have time and resources
to do it oh well maybe next year maybe next year but thank you yes uh we'll do dark wood probably
a week or two before halloween uh i'm gonna probably say your name wrong hopefully i get
it right elixi elix o u l i x e s we'll elixis elixis i'm gonna say elixis thank you for the
thousand bits hey germa someone previously made that statement they one of the greatest entertainers
of our time and i find myself agreeing with them completely that's i that is a huge huge thing to
hear i don't i am that's very very humbling i'm so happy that you have that opinion if you really
think that then there's much more i could probably i could do i there's we're not even started yet
you know like we're just getting up to like the top of the hill it's not even it hadn't even
started yet so thank you i don't even know what to say if somebody really thinks that uh your
originality and humility know no bounds and you inspire me to be more like you each and every
stream the world is a much better place knowing that you are in it much love from across the pond
if you get anything if you if i can inspire you to do something fuck yeah like if you take take if
you take something from if you take anything from here take something from here you know what i'm
saying try to turn do try to turn into something good make somebody happy right do something fun
i um that's the only thing that i fucking care about it really is hopefully i've proved that over
the years uh i don't want to just kind of talk bullshit and nonsense like oh all i care about is
all i care about is the community yeah like thought bubble like no i don't that's a lie i'm just
saying it i hope that over the last like four or five years he lied about spore though that's true
you can hold that against me i ain't perfect though you know what i mean like i ain't fucking
perfect i'm not even close just be real is all i can ask that's all i want to do that's all i
can do i can't pretend i can't do it you'll know you know easy just to see through somebody when
they're just beating you dog shit like i can't do it i could never do it i'm not smart enough
to convince you otherwise you know that's i'm not i don't want to look at you i'm supposed to be
looking down here i'm describing somebody else he's not pretending no i'm not going to pretend
like i'm somehow it's i'm the only person i'm the only person in the world that is genuine
now there's tons of people that do this shit that feel the same way you probably watched some of
them already there are a lot of people that that do think that so this is not a trying to stand on
a pedestal or something i'm just i'm really happy that people think that this is still a good fucking
place to hang out and still growing and people still have fun and i'm able and capable to do
stuff like i did a few days ago because there are people that watch that care about this channel
you know like i put him on the pedestal but he's still short don't make me scream into this i will
i got a limiter now though but i don't want to get ranty we have this conversation sometimes
you know once in a while every like couple months and just just know i'm just just know one thing
okay sick what's the song's name um i think it's just called gerbil plexus maybe the theater his
iq is too high no but i like i don't want to i we i don't want to come up it's like a preachy
dick either because that's that's like annoying too you know what i mean oh okay because i know
i don't i don't want to sound like that i don't want to sound like i'm like preaching i'm just
trying i'm trying and i hope they're fun and uh anonymous just gave five community subs five
community subs from anonymous don't know who you are but thank you if you say sp i will give i will
do twitch prime okay i know i can see your name right now let's see it i held up my end of the
bargain right now that person's going fuck got scammed it's all right scam me it's all right
that's all right he did it did he do it he did it there it is there it is all right all right
not scammed now once a month remind me to do that so you re-up your subscription hey pretender thanks
to the 250 i don't have a lot to give but if you're going to keep doing these high production
streams i want to contribute what i can keep on being the best entertainer out there thank you
pretend dear appreciate it kid thunder five community subs from kid thunder thank you kid
thank you i'll be taking that one thanks for making my night with that sp you got it
absolutely but thank you pretend dear thank you flug boy for the 500 bits hey jeremy i literally
have no words for the carnival stream other than incredibly proud of you keep amazing me every
elaborate stream also you should totally throw borderlands 3 on your off stream games and also
was wondering if you were gonna stream or play death stranding also happy birthday thank you for
the birthday wish i appreciate i appreciate that thank you i don't know if i'm gonna play death
stranding i'm probably not going to play borderlands 3 i didn't really play borderlands 2 i played
borderlands 1 you know what there i think there's a video of me playing borderlands 2 for like 10
minutes with like three or four people that's buried somewhere on the channel there's a border
lands 2 episode 1 let's play how many episodes other this probably two or three two no i just
have i'm not really into like the whole loot shooter thing anymore i'm looking for something
else borderlands 3 is a mess right now i i would not know i've not been around but yeah um probably
not gonna play the uh death stranding on stream i don't think i would do that that's more so that's
probably something that i would want to do just on my own and just kind of enjoy it kind of like
what i'm doing with god of war i know i know people can be very mad about this i'm currently
well not currently but i was currently playing through god of war off stream it's been great
i know i know i've been there's been a lot of times where i've gone you know i really wish
stream was on right now because that was awesome let us watch no no because i'm i'm me and kim i'm
playing it for kim kim er is uh will come up and go hey can you play god of war and it's like yeah
sure i'll play i'll play god of war it's kind of like a little thing that we have right now so
she's currently enjoying her personal playthrough of god of war yeah it's fun uh we're getting up
here to the end we got probably another five ten minutes left still a lot of people here too those
of you that are new uh give you maybe kind of curious of what is going on here but probably
should have said this in the very beginning of this kind of wind down uh at the end of 95 percent
of all streams i don't read bits or subs on stream so at the very end of a stream we'll just kind of
hang out and i'll go over what's come through and respond to messages and stuff like that and we then
we'd run uh sub credits at the end so that's probably if you were curious as to why you didn't
see any notifications or you didn't see i wasn't talking to or reacting to any bit messages is
because i i do i do not do that i also have a twitter too somebody's linked it is my name
brad no my name is uh my name is jerry elbertson thank you but we were down here at where were we
yes that was flug boy uh that gave the happy birthday 500 bits and they talked about the
carnival stream i really appreciate it thank you dubski dude thanks for the 500 bits five dollars
from dubski dude hey germa i heard you were strapped for cash so here's five whole dollars
to pay for the carnival stream that should cover most of the expenses no need to thank me but for
real though i can't believe you pulled it off i was very impressed with the sheer creativity of it
and i'm not kidding when i say you're a visionary it's great to be able to watch you progress into
bigger and better skits but the real question is germa tv show when you're watching it right
now you're you are currently watching it right now you're on the channel this is the channel
you're on it's germa tv germa 985 tv tv's yeah uh oh so much more goes into tv i i would rather
just make a few phone calls and say here's an idea that i want to do let's make it happen
from my channel not for anybody else's i'd rather do that than have like a tv show which this is so
much more goes into that i'm happy that you liked it i'm glad that you enjoyed it i'm glad that
people thought it was fun and i'm glad you got to at least win some of the games because i really
was concerned that you weren't going to do any of them but you did almost all of them i don't think
there was actually that that kind of knocked the clowns down uh you only got two or three of those
but i guess that you got the the pain so that was enough for a uh a painful hurt myself dab so
that's all right you didn't do the first one that's right the bottle did you no you didn't do the
bottles ring toss no you didn't do ring toss right oh shit you guys didn't do ring toss oh well
we're sorry the cans yeah you guys you guys tried you can't you gotta disqualify yourselves though
it's okay hey mostly lost thanks for the 250 happy belated birthday happy belated birthday
jumbo uh all the clips earlier reminded me of this classic germa bovid it was that was a that was
what a classic moment the cat puking so i was laughing downstairs taking a piss that was so
funny some of the shit that you guys can come up with you guys talk about how funny i am that's
what it sounds like when my cat is puking why is your cat puking too like i would like when did it
happen i imagine your cat just started puking and you're sitting there going oh shit no no
and then that happens on screen hairballs yeah i know that's not what i was going for but that's
funny regardless thank you mostly lost for the clip hey goop snatch thanks for the 1500 bits i
appreciate your streams dude recently i've been going through financial and emotional stress
and your carnival stream was the ice cream on top of the cake i've been watching for a long time
and wanted to give back to my favorite streamer don't worry this didn't harm my wallet too much
i'm that's that's good to know because if you're going through any financial
problems i really do not donate do not give money to me take care of yourself but hopefully
whatever stress you're going through as well is solved thank you so much for the 1500 bits
much love to you you don't have to give back i know a lot of you say that but you don't have to
it's not necessary but thank you regardless even still when i when you see messages come in
you see money come in i'm just i'm floored i can't wait to do the next one that's what's going to
happen with all the money that comes in it's going right to the next one so thank you mr
comcast hasn't hurt for you in a while mr comcast 300 bits for mr conk a germa john comcast here
well interesting uh just letting you know that i went to your carnival you went to you with you
went to you were at the carnival you went to the carnival i want to say hi but i also didn't want
to interrupt you as you peed into the dunk tank i also found it quite disturbing when you demanded
that the anti-mark crew members empty their wallets and put their money into the machine
so that you could win it all i was going to leave but not before i saw you ddt the werelord plushy
into the frog leap table and get a ticket for illegally parking thank you uh thank you mr
comcast for the 300 bits appreciate it also thank you to mostly laws again 250 they say also pigeon
says you missed their bits from earlier i am going to go back uh at the very end here so i'm
gonna go back and uh catch the few that uh fell through the cracks at the end or at the beginning
actually so we'll do them we'll see them we're almost to the end here so it's the franco the
franco 1000 bits from the franco hey germa me and my dad watched the carnival stream together and
we loved it it was my dad's first time seeing anything from you so it was cool to see he enjoyed
it now here's the interesting part halfway through the stream he turned to me and asked hey do you
remember that guy from the spider man movie the guy that flies around on the thing he looks like
him i couldn't believe it anyway thank you so much for these streams your stuff has been making me
laugh for years thank you it's the franco hey you know it looks like that guy that flew around on
the uh wait he may have been talking about spider-man hold on remember that guy from spider-man the guy
that flies around in new york city flying around spider-man he looks like him all right nice i'm
really glad it's not that guy with the scary mask on that flies around and what's his name i'm glad
it's another guy that if not if i'm not that one not the green one right yeah not that one
not that one hey thank you though thank you thank you thank you thank you apple shift for the two
dollars 50 cents 250 bits hey man i was wondering this other day have you ever been noticed in public
before also the carnival stream was absolutely incredible and we as a community could not be
more proud of it thank you uh yes it's only happened like two or three times it's happened
i think three times total in places that i you wouldn't think i've got recognized i've got
recognized in a mall before walking around a mall it was just and you know you know and you you know
right you walk it around you know you walk by somebody you make the kind of like just like
random eye contact for a second and it's just i know who you are do i know who you are i think
i know who you are hey is you and i'm like all right holy shit it's william da foe and then i go
no i get i get that a lot and i keep walking yeah but yeah it's happened a few times it doesn't
happen that often maybe like once a year once every couple years something like that will happen
at a convention though something like twitchcon or pax or blizzcon it's happened maybe a dozen
times or so on the show floor people just kind of walk by you and they go hey and i go hey
and it happens there and that's fun a dozen yeah it happened a dozen times no i i very much enjoy
it so if you do see me at twitchcon pull me aside and say hello uh sarin thank you sarin fp for the
two dollars and 50 cents 250 bits yo germa loved the carnival stream to me felt more like a love
letter to your audience rather than your magnum opus loving the streams more and more keep it up
i mean i tried to throw as many random little references in there as i could like the cash
machine and whale lord and pokemon stuff other little things too like clown car and
stuff that i've been saying i wanted to do for a long time so yeah um it was a lot of fun
but see in a few months this is going to be a regular thing how much was the clown car
that clown car was very very inexpensive it just needed a little bit of spray paint
that's all it was not 400 but i don't want to give you any come on let the let the magic speak for
itself i don't want to ruin any magic that was my actual car yes but thank you to uh
thank you do sarin fp so now we are going to go like this let's settle it down a little bit
we have a little bit more to do theater is emptying out was it loud my ears what do
you mean oh ouch what happened what was that was loud what happened did i bump you guys
where the transition is loud oh okay i'm stupid stop hitting me let's keep going jake
thank you jake games stumbled across randomly germania 2014 in early 2015 seeing you start
streaming and then take your streams to a whole level has been an incredible experience
i every video that i made and every stream that i do i try to have it be as fun as the last one
in my head internally now i know it's impossible but i try once you start bringing in production
and money and huge ideas you can't but i still like to try hey effect tater thank you effect tater
for the 500 bits thank you uh just want to remind you however grateful i am that you and mac gave
me a chance thanks to this editing job my life is really on track jeff just moved in with my
partner this week and i got my first prescription to start transitioning and having sufficient work
made it all possible thank you germa thank you mac and thank you chad thank you so much effect
tater seriously good luck on that journey because that's a new book that's a new page to turn
i wish you the best you've been incredibly talented coming in in the clutch so many times
i really appreciate what you do thank you is the game over yeah oh shit it's still on the it's
still on the goose game right uh-oh well i guess no that's okay i mean technically it's okay
because i mean what is that i this is just the end kind of the end i need to no i gotta like change
that i can't just be sitting in the goose let's just put it at uh just chatting is fine all right
and my sister's barking at people that's not accurate either but we are going to move to a
screen that you are very used to this one i'm gonna move back to boston no oh no it's too loud
i'll fix it thank you everybody for joining me on this return stream we're gonna do one more
tomorrow tomorrow stream is not gonna be that long sorry that it's been sporadic but it's been
insanely busy the last couple weeks try to do something fun tomorrow but we're not quite done
we still have a little bit more to do thank you mr picklesworth for the thousand bits germa just
want to thank you for being one of the most genuine people on the internet you deserve all
this fucking support you put so much time and effort into these huge projects you spend literally
thousands of dollars just to entertain people you're my favorite person of all time thanks for
inspiring me and so many other people keep up the great work boomer though that time you hit me with
your car and drove away wasn't very cool what that was a small tonal shift thank you for the
thousand bits i appreciate it hey apple shift two dollars and 50 cents one more thing i bought
myself an andy mark goat yesterday what should i name it oh garry of course gets insurance money
yeah those are still available they still are there i don't know how many they're gonna have
but they that was just kind of randomly they just were like hey we're gonna put them up
and yeah if you want one grab one but thank you apple ship thank you
calusia for the three dollars hi germa i probably sound like a broken record at this point
but i really want to say i love the carnival stream it was amazing to see everything come together
really admire your dedication and creativity for these kinds of things
looking forward for more things to come and i can't wait to see you at twitchcon all right hell yeah
see you at twitchcon i don't have any official meet and greets by the way so i'm gonna do the
thing that i always do and that's i'm gonna pull up a table or something in the corner like where
and wherever i can find a place to do it i'm just gonna like eat a couple cookies and
hang out there nightbot isn't always accurate not really he's gonna go sit
next to the why would i sit next to the bathroom oh wait i have done that i think i did that like
two or three years ago at pax east yeah yeah that was just right in front of like the bathrooms
oh shit you're right well uh i will i don't know i have no idea where i've been i don't know
or maybe not maybe i'll just maybe it'll be like a where's waldo scenario maybe you gotta find me
maybe i'll like tweet like a hint out or something of like where i am
but yeah you're going to switchcon track me down i'll be there on saturday i'll be there on saturday
morning that's kind of where i will be it's saturday morning into early saturday afternoon
is where you'll be able to find me but thank you uh colusia maybe you see there
hallelujah thanks for the 250 hey germa happy birthday it's been amazing seeing you continue
to push your creativity and make innovative experiences i traveled and got to watch the
carnival stream with the person who first introduced me to you years ago through castle
griffinsteed it was great anyway i'm so happy for you and i wish you nothing but continued
success germa hart ps i'm working on a retro style poster to celebrate the carnival
thank you for the constant inspiration my video was so much fun to make i can i it's funny i can
always look back at videos or streams that i could just go oh that was so much fun to make
it always turns out to be some of my favorite things i've ever done thank you i'm going to
continue to try c4g thanks for the 250 they say pride 250 pride bisexual thank you so much
thanks for the 250 the end of the stream is so wholesome i mean i'm just kind of i'm just kind
of hanging out you know what i'm saying just if that's what i'm saying if those of you that were
maybe new to the stream this is we just kind of just wind down here just chilling just hanging
up the stream technically ended like an hour ago but this is the second post stream that i do every
single stream if that makes any sense i think it does feels like dad is reading me a bedtime
story have a great night but thank you to birth yogurt for the 500 bits oh germa the old ones
smile upon the old ones but like cthulhu cthulhu i mean old ones that's freaking me out don't say
it what do you mean don't say it it's not beetle juice thank you devakitty for the 250 hey germa
i think you lost my early bits i'll just send you some more nevertheless i love the carnival
stream even the weird uh kids hospital clowns you hired thank you for always being a fun
streamer and a good guy you've helped me through a lot of depression and dysphoria so thank you for
carrying me this far because i'm actually trying i'm actually having my legal gender and name
changed tomorrow so here's to my new real name luna transgender pride i've said this a few times
before and i want to just reiterate it again whoever the best you is that's who you should be
and that's who you are so thank you for the 250 i wish you luck thank you so much devakitty
thank you to gnarly for the 250 as well so when is the next hearthstone stream never that's not a
joke question i thought it was all right and i'll answer that i'll answer that for real now okay
when's the next hearthstone stream that's not a joke question i'm one of those sick
fucks who actually liked that stream and the new solo content came out well doesn't that kind of
answer the question i'm one of those sick fucks who liked that stream all right so i'm so gnarly
i may as well just stream it to you do they have passwords on twitch password controlled streams
i'll just give you the password and whatever at that point it's like 87 percent of every human
that sat here and watched that stream begged me not to do that ever again you're gonna give
him a private snapchat let him in no i can't please don't see that's only one person that
wants that a true one guy stream maybe i'll do it one day that's funny to me for some reason i
don't know why let's do a private stream to one person it should be a contest that would be a
really really funny contest set up some type of competition or contest or something and that
person wins a a private full live stream that would be so awkward yeah i mean it it kind of would
but that make it's making me laugh right now so i think it's something i want to explore
i don't think i could handle that what if they don't show up you know i all right i'm gonna
tell you this because there's no way it's gonna happen ever that's not true though i have to
hold on to so many ideas that i if i ever use them i can't let them out but when am i gonna
have time to do this though that's impossible i can't no i can't just in case years down the
road this is something that i do i can't you know i think there's one person that knows about this
maybe like two is lucratius here is luke here lucratius definitely not eu i think lucratius
is the only person that knows about this idea and they have been sworn to secrecy it's pretty
good though i'm not gonna lie it's pretty good it's something i've no it's nothing i've never
talked of uh so far no it's nothing that you've ever heard of before i've never talked about it
but we can move on we're uh we gotta end the stream here i didn't think i was gonna go for
seven hours but i haven't been i've been i haven't been around for like a week so
i'm cool to hang out and chill for a little bit so it's fine he just said you can tell us
no no it's not even it's not it's not gonna happen but there's no way to live again out of
me or lucratius what it is three hours of game four hours of chill yeah sometimes it's like that
though i'm okay with that sometimes but snoozing coffee thanks for the 250 hi germa the carnival
stream was exceptional i cannot wait to see what else you have in store for us in the future you're
the greatest thank you really and now to something else i'm on vacation in dallas and currently got
hit by a car on sunday that's not good i was on one of those electrical scooters in a car capped
me from behind well the mirror did holy shit i got away with a big bruise and some scrapes so i got
pretty surreal though you ever had any big accidents or injuries i've never been i never
been hit by a car like that before that sounds horrifying hopefully you're all right big bruise
and some scrapes thankfully but i've been i've had car accidents before i don't know if i've
ever told you this one time one time i got the worst car accident i was ever in in my whole life
was i was at a red light just sitting at a red light and somebody drove into the back of my car
going 40 or 50 miles per hour and and it was in it was horrible they just weren't paying attention
i was sitting at a stoplight for probably 10 seconds and this person i don't know what they
were doing i don't know what happened but holy shit they i thought my car exploded i'm just sitting
there at the light and then boom i thought i was like the car i was a car had to exploded it had
to have right how else would that have happened that was the scariest thing that was probably top
five scariest things in my entire life that was in my car was totaled that was it what's top what's
number one i i don't know i'm just saying that's up there somewhere i don't know what could possibly
be top above that um let me think what could possibly be above that i don't know that's why
i put i said it was somewhere in the top five it could be number one no this there's other
dangerous awful shit i'm trying to think like of my whole life i don't know i it's up there
somewhere i know i know there's other stuff that's happened that i could put up there
no no no there's more but now that's probably number one now that i'm really sitting here
thinking about it i just remember i don't i it's like when something like that happens to you
i can remember every second of that experience that's how crazy our brains are i can't tell
you what i had for dinner two days ago but i remember every second of that car accident
but man yeah i i don't want to go into like obviously grisly details but that was that
screwed me up for a little while it was really really fucked up but i was all right i was okay
the way that the car hit me the guy flipped over so he actually flipped over the right side of the
car and i think they were they were in like an suv so that's horrible because i was in like a
little tiny little i was like a chevy or something trying to remember what the car was yeah no it
was ridiculous and it was on one of the busiest roads too one of the busiest just actual roads
it was fucking crazy and i remember just getting out of the car and looking at this
what was left of my vehicle the whole back was crushed in and the whole right side passenger
was all messed up too and all i could think of over and over again was going thank god there was
nobody in my car thank god i wasn't driving anybody anywhere thank god i didn't i wasn't
with any friends or anything i was just alone so thank god you see people need to understand
power of a fucking car yeah and cars cars are dangerous man people you gotta be careful you
see people flying around driving like assholes like you gotta be fucking careful man seeing
people going 10 20 miles per hour over the speed limit and shit it's like just you gotta fucking
relax like what are you doing see people going there's just whizzing by going like 50 in a 30
it's just like what are you what are you thinking vegas has some bad driving nah no they do people
gotta just relax a little bit you don't gotta you don't gotta go that fast that's why i don't
drive anymore i walk i take public transport if i have to yeah i could i'm trust me i get it
he was gonna be he's gotta be more careful i don't know why some people just think they're
invincible in that thing you're not let me make that really clear you aren't that's kim say it's
worse than boston yeah we've been we've been on the highway before just driving and kim and i will
just be driving and all of a sudden you'll just see somebody just just going like and there are
other cars on the road too you've got like two three four five other cars in the lanes on the
highway and they just changing lanes back and forth back and forth left right right right left
right it's just dude what are you doing what are you thinking there's no reason to go that fast
look we're all going to baskin robbins they're still going to be open don't what are you doing
people just drive so fucking fast i don't understand it they close at eight on sunday
you say yeah and and the and the worst part about it then this is this is real talk right here
you know it really really irritates me in a car so if you're driving and you're on a road let's say
the road is 40 miles per hour okay and you know you're going 40 you're going you know i'm going
38 40 41 42 and 40 going 40 39 right okay all right okay settle down right cool
once you have somebody that passes you that's going like 60 in that 40 and then you go up to
the light that is less than a mile ahead of where you are and that person you look over to your left
and they're at the same light as you it's like you got real far didn't you think what you didn't
gain any time haven't you read the tortoise and the hare they wrote that fucking book like 75
years ago and it still rings true you're not gonna win a race it's we're just going to the
you're i you're not making time he's doing splits i that always just that just grinds me i get so
irritated i'm just like come on just think of like the danger that you're putting your fellow
drivers in and and even yourself for you to look over and see the guy that you passed at the red
light should be like an internal scenario where you go okay i'm kind of fucking up here i kind
of probably should think about what i'm doing people people are stupid yeah but i'm i'm just
venting at this point i'm just venting about drivers defensive driving is mandatory yeah it's
a temporary lack of empathy or consideration i i mean even i just don't want to get a car accident
i don't want to get in a car accident if i go 20 miles per hour over the speed limit i am
exponentially increasing the chances that i'm going to get into a car accident by tenfold why
do i want that should it be harder to get a driver's license i don't know if it should
be harder to get a driver's license or if we should i don't know what the answer is i think
people just like systematically need to get like taught fucking manners i don't know like that's
kind of what it is learn manners well because you don't cut the person off unless you you know
unless you just be kind of being a dick i can i can look if somebody if the speed limit is like
30 miles per hour and somebody's going like 20 like 25 it's like okay you're going slow here
you're going really slow if there's a passing lane then you're okay whatever but if somebody
like me i go the speed limit i do i go i go like within five miles per hour of the speed limit
whether that's okay it's a 30 i'm going like 30 like between like 28 and like 32
right i try to stay within about five miles per hour the speed limit plus or minus five yeah once
you start to get over about five miles per hour over the speed limit you really want to you don't
you want to slow down i'd say it like three or four miles per hour over is when i start to go okay i'm
going to pull it back a little miles per hour yeah which we are we are talking american in here
32 slow down there you're crazy 32 you know when it's a 35 i like to go my age 34
but there are smart ways to to drive the speed limit if you're gonna go more than 20 plus miles
per hour for the speed limit you are just putting everybody in danger and it's just not that's not
cool that's a real monka s like don't do that that's just fucking reckless and people do it
all the time but i consider and talk about how people driving around like assholes is annoying
for the next two hours we are getting close to the end here don't even know how we got there but we
did oh right snoozing copter was talking about how they got just got hit by a car i'm glad you're
okay but yeah kind of we talked about kind of accidents and stuff so thanks for the 250
appreciate it hey the fax machine thanks for the five community subs and kid thunder five community
subs uh amutsu amutsi amutsi i think i'm saying that right thanks for the 500 bits jeremy you make
my endless hours at work fun and enjoyable you're incredibly funny and i cannot wait to see your
next endeavor happy birthday love you to bits thank you endless hours at work glad i can be
a part of it thank you for the 500 bits thanks to five bucks go dot thanks for the five dollars
hey germa i know you're busy but do you think i could ask you a few questions about yourself
this is for a school project where we interview our heroes and then write about them anyways
hope these bits go to the next carnival stream um i mean i kind of just i kind of just answer
questions from anybody but that's um i'm interview our heroes i can't believe i'm your hero
uh yeah i mean yeah i'm like i'm gonna i'm not gonna be around for a while
after tonight i actually haven't gets getting late too so i'll be gone for twitchcon but i
tip if you have a couple of questions yeah fuck it let's yeah sure um hit up one of the mods and i
will answer a couple of your questions stream from twitchcon last stream before retirement no
thank you to low fat sugar for the 1000 bits 10 bucks hey jerry it's my birthday today happy
birthday september birthdays there's a lot of them the carnival stream was a delight even though
it started at 2 a.m for me thanks for being the best streamer of all time love you thank you
thank you low fat sugar happy birthday hope you have a good one thank you too doth doth my
doth my nuggets like the thief me what is this username thank you for the 250
what is this doth my nugs bequeath me i don't know what this means bird it's eric andre oh okay
by the way i heard his live show is insane i was told go see eric andre live because i think his
show was hilarious i was told to see it live because it's insane live it is it is okay that
means i have to see it i have to see it okay but thank you they say hey germans want to say thanks
to the content over the years when tf2 is at its peak me and my older brother watched your videos
and hung around since then we've gotten older and he has a wife now and we've grown apart but
watching your streams brings me back to when we were closer so i appreciate that it's a long time
i think some of you guys forget that this is all going on almost 10 years eight nine years
that's a long time thank you for the 250 and thanks for sticking around for that long because
it's been a long time when is season 10 i gotta be careful going over season 10 that's when all
shows start to suck i've got to be very careful i gotta work on that thank you wembley for the 250
hey germa started watching your streams a few months ago after youtube recommended me your
stuff that's cool i wish that i was following years ago love your stuff one of the best
entertaining streamers on here thanks wembley i'm glad you found the uh channel hopefully you
stick around hey zoidberg thanks for the five dollars zoidberg can you say hi to banana fish
they love your content hey what's going on banana fish i heard you love the content sick thank you
zoidberg for the 500 bits thank you hey docs for the 500 bits it's a lot of money tonight
you can always when when this when the after stream hangout session is like more than an
hour too long you guys are just so you guys are showering me in like money and praise thank you
guys seriously sometimes i don't know what to say so thank you but hey docs uh no message just
500 bits from hey docs thank you flug boy thanks for the five dollars i was remind i was just
reminded of the hospital clowns i actually had clown doctors perform in front of me after i
donated my bone marrow and i honestly thought i was fever dreaming but one of them was actually
the one that operated on me still a what the fuck moment for me wait what hold on he thought one of
the wait what did it was it real wait what happened a clown hospital clown doctors clown
doctors are a thing it was actually happening okay that's interesting thank you flug boy for
the five bucks thank you vol pixels for the 275 carnival stream was insanely good i haven't been
watching for long but i can honestly say you're the best streamer i've watched so keep it up dude
however long you've been watching thanks for watching as long as you have whether it's a week
a month or 10 years thank you hope you stick around freddy dread thanks for the ten dollars
no message just thousand bits from freddy dread snoozing copter two dollars and 50 cents 250
bits your accident sounds even more horrible than mine i don't know about that because
being in a car with the kind of that shell around you i don't know getting actually hit by a car
out of a car sounds insanely traumatizing so uh sounds like you got really lucky too i did
what i forgot to mention by the way is that the person that hit me didn't even stop or get out
maybe they stopped but i didn't see it because it was dark but i even had to cancel the trip
on the scooter and stand there wait for the app to authorize it wait what you do stand there and
wait for the app to authorize the trip on the scooter what and somebody just did did you end up
catching them did they find out who it was that's fucking horrible god what's wrong with people
but hopefully you did not get too badly hurt snoozing copter seriously and i would do the
necessary things to try to figure out what happened there because that's not that's not
all right they might be that might be a camera there somewhere that's possible to pull don't
let somebody fucking get away with that that's fucking horrible i'm all right i can walk etc
well that's um hopefully you don't have anything that comes out of that it sounds like it you're
you're gonna be all right hopefully you wish you a swift recovery but thank you mostly lost
thanks for the 250 somebody said the stream's been over for two hours sometimes it happens like this
usually this is about 30 to 40 minutes somewhere between 30 plus minutes or so but i've been gone
for a long time but thank you mostly lost for the 250 hey jeremy i was driving through dallas the
other night thanks for the 250 appreciate uh that thanks for the 250 thank you smelly boy for the
250 thoughts on people who ride their bikes in the car lane um it depends if there's a bike lane
they use the bike lane you got to be careful with cyclists though some cyclists are really really
really good and really smart sometimes sometimes that cyclist doesn't have reflective gear on
sometimes that cyclist is kind of just riding their bike on the road you've got to be careful
especially at night you share the road and if you're a cyclist you know you got to share the
road too we're all just we're all just trying to get to fucking baskin robbins all of us
to get those delicious 250 flavors share the road hey
dc pro thanks for the 265 206 five cents hey germa fantastic fucking carnival dude
i live in san diego so let me know if you need a good tour guide i am not going to be in
san diego for very long unfortunately because of the trip that i just was on and because of
the nature of the last stream that i did before this i didn't want to take that much more time
off because i there was a almost a full five days before the carnival where i just kind of
wasn't around and then i didn't want to have it be ah so okay thursday i'm gone and then friday
saturday sunday monday i wanted to be back and plus i've been traveling i've it was a lot of
work that had to get done last week i have a lot of real life shit that you guys don't really even
know about that i have to do too so it's been very very busy and hectic um so i can i really
i'm only going to be in san diego for like 24 hours essentially because i didn't want to
disappear again for like five days but like i said saturday is the day saturday morning into
saturday afternoon is when you'll find me there's a lot of other stuff that's going on that i haven't
talked about at all nothing bad these are good things but still it just lots of stuff this has
been like the busiest september i think in the last few years without a doubt it is i need to
run the credits but i have a new setup here can i even run these credits i hope so really
it's just here that's not the credits that is a goose in a lake let me delete that
well you know we'll keep it here all right here come the credits if the if you don't know what
the credits are the credits are these subs that were on this stream holy shit holy shit that's
the fastest it's ever gone this is the fastest it's ever been ever since i started live streaming
no way that's too fast oh my god how many subs we're in today that's going 100 miles per hour
somebody keep an eye on that because that really might be the fastest it's ever gone
thank you so much everybody new people old people especially the old people because i'm old
you get to be 34 with me no some of you guys have subbed for years and some of your new subs just
came in maybe you'll maybe you'll stick around maybe you won't appreciate it nonetheless thank
you so much for yourself the uber pikachu thanks for the bits what's your opinion on the original
spider-man trilogy one and two are fantastic three is not very good at all hopefully that
answers your question leather jacket thanks for the thousand bits one of our mods here
leather jacket one of our original mods sorry i didn't get to talk to you the day the day of
hope your birthday was awesome it was it was great thank you and thanks for the 10 bucks too
thanks for being a fucking sick mod i mean that snoozing copter thanks for the 250 i wasn't even
done with my last message and the bits cost so much more now i didn't even know 5 000 bits
cost 100 euros now what wait 5 000 bits cost 100 euros are you serious instead of it used to be
70 oh my god why is it let me ask you this is this why is it always na to eu just costs way more
money to ship things to you guys is like a shitload of money to sell things to you guys is a shitload
of money if you're what is going on with na to every other country on earth it used to be good
i was here all the time oh hey man uh got the t-shirt oh cool yeah it was uh it was 86 dollars
what that's a expensive t-shirt i had to pay 20 for shipping on the dota 2 special edition
that was 80 to start with that's fucking crazy hey guys do you i mean we're at the end of the
stream here pretty much but like do you really need me to go on a cryptocurrency rant about btc
do you really want me to do that do you really want to hear that right now no you don't thank
you but snoozing copter as they say that's the first time in american hospital so after all it
was an experience worth telling about and my girlfriend supported me through the whole thing
the reason i even came here and i'm very happy i did life is full of surprises she still hates
you by the way happy belated birthday you rock old man what did you tell him not to hate me
what did i ever do i didn't do anything bit connect yeah but thank you snoozing thanks
to the birthday wishes and i really hope that you have a swift recovery here because that's
fucking crazy hey the uber pikachu thank you for the 300 bits hey germa just want to let you know
you want to know your opinion on the original spider-man trilogy what also a really good
pogchamp stream keep up the great work um i i want to the first the first one's good
second one's great and the third one's not good at all didn't i just do this
did i am i losing my mind hey go 90 thanks for the 250 i was hoping my six four boyfriend could
meet you at twitchcon so you could finally prove you are indeed a six foot plus gentleman
unfortunately his trip has been cancelled uh after the thomas cook collapse hope we can see
you next year also holy shit the carnival stream was amazing what wait what happened
what hold on a second what so wait they just like shut it all down it's an airline that just went
out of business and that's it no the airline shut down before doing any return flights how's that
even possible aircrews were stranded after thomas cook collapsed so what they just like they just
said that's it and that's it and then what would that's so fucking that's insane well hopefully
maybe maybe you'll see you next year that's not that sucks that's really fucked up i'm gonna look
more into this after the stream i'm gonna read about this this is crazy hey pigeon thank you
pigeon for the 250 i donated at the beginning of the stream and you have yet to read it not like
this yeah i was gonna go back and scroll but you guys just continue to shower me with
fucking cash and i can't say anything but thank you you guys are just tons of money tons of subs
you see the subs that went by it's fucking insane it's insane oh shit this shampoo is great that's
an old one i like that oh wait i gotta go back to uh there's the janitor cleaning it up over 800
subs today are you serious my fucking god what the fuck
i'm telling you less than a few months are gonna go by before you see another stream like this
quite the amount yeah for real it is but anyways they say uh to reiterate i'm so goddamn excited
to meet and follow you around it's gonna make my year also i recently found the amazing world of
paid clown jobs and i absolutely loved the dynamic duo you had on stream i'm assuming you
hired them yes they were incredible any chance you can give them a shout out i'd love to look
into them and what they do i'm probably what but there's gonna be a stream where i want to bring
on some video some uh behind the scenes pictures and stuff i think that we're taking this is after
twitchcon because i don't have time to really set it up right now but they were fantastic they really
were and to answer your first question um you will be able to follow me around for about two
three hours because that's as long as i'm gonna be on the show floor because then i fucking leaf
and twitch gone that's as long as i will be at the show essentially i but what if i just like
fucking sprinted away and like darted behind a bush or something all right yeah i'm going this
way the dot like like i'm playing a fucking like stealth game hide from everybody he's about to
he's gonna head out just be the goose he's scared of meeting fans no if you think i'm scared of
meeting fans you know i've done this you know it's been almost 10 years now right i've done
probably a two a two dozen meet and greets so no i'm just not going to be there for very long
you don't want to meet us sad it's me face i'll be around saturday all morning into the early
afternoon then i gotta get out of there because i have some stuff to do stuff that i haven't talked
about may be beneficial gonna be meeting people gonna be greeting people not just fans of the
channel other streamers maybe some networking i'm gonna i'm you know what i'm saying let's go
secrets no no secrets hey nori calm thanks for the thousand bits how was burger boy by the way
burger boys i think doing pretty well he's got a family he has children but i am gonna go back
because that is the end of the bits that is the end of the stream but let me go back earlier here
make sure i didn't miss anything else which i don't think i did because it was right about here
yeah yeah i remember bake me home i remember smelly boy i remember zake uh the cap david gave
646 bits i think i missed this one from earlier this happy belated birthday hope it went well
second the carnival stream was the most amazing thing i've seen ever and i don't know how long
you nailed it seriously kudos it was super fun dunking you three times and third thank you thank
you for all those years of entertainment thank you for inspiring me thank you for helping me
through those very tough times in my life thank you for everything seriously dude thank you for
watching and thank you for enabling me to do this thank you for allowing me to do this when
thousands and thousands of people all give their hard-earned money to this to one person
that's how i'm able to do that you know what i mean and i'm gonna do what i can you know as long
as i can and that's gonna be my time for tonight kind of a long one today but kind like i said
earlier sort of had to be you haven't seen me truthfully i haven't sat down here and truthfully
hung out for about six or seven days eight days so i love doing the long ones i need to get some
food i have some packing to do and then tomorrow we are gonna do a shorter one tomorrow i gotta
stop clapping what am i clapping for why am i like clapping we're gonna do a short one tomorrow
less than probably a few hours three four five hours something like that tops cut his mic what
do you mean cut my mic why would why do you want to cut my mic fingernails fingernails
fingernails thank you thank you all right i'm out of here i will see you guys tomorrow take care
much love thank you for all the insane support i'm glad you liked the fucking carnival stream
see you soon raid raid somebody raid italics raid raid you know what here who's streaming
right now who's streaming right now what do we have it takes so damn long for my page to open
we got everybody's streaming right now vinnie criken italics who else is streaming
hey you know check this shit out raid somebody with one viewer uh no i that's i don't know i
don't know if i want to do that surprise somebody that would that might freak somebody out i can't
imagine if you had one viewer and all of a sudden like a thousand fucking people showed up it might
scare the shit out of you one no no no no no go say hello to italics we'll write italics
what's he doing kenshi should be interesting all right i'll see you guys tomorrow short stream
have a good one by the way this is i think it's alex this is like late game kenshi by the way
i'm gonna clip my nails i will don't worry i've got it i got it under control see you tomorrow
did it not work okay that was weird all right goodbye see you later take care and just like
like swear in his chat just say like shit and like piss you guys are all gonna get fucking banned
all right good night see you tomorrow