I am back. So we got, I don't know, yeah, which, maybe you guys can help me and go over which
one of these are any good. Because I really, I have no idea. I just got keys for random cases
that I still had in my inventory and I, you might look at this and go, holy shit, this guy's stupid.
He got keys for the winter 2018 case. I just, I don't know, I didn't want to give, I wanted
just to open them. That's the good one. No, that's the good one. That's the good one. Well, we'll
find out. Okay, you should be able to see it very shortly. Okay, here we go. You ready? So what,
what's, what do you think? What do you think? I got 25 cases to open. How are these? Are these
all right? This is Blue Moon, Tough Break, Rainy Day, Abominable, Scream Fortress. Is that 12?
Winter 2018, Winter 2020, Summer 2023, obviously. That's the, these are the new ones right here.
These four are for this update. Winter 2020. That's a lot of winter and a lot of Scream Fortress,
Jungle Jackpot, Eternal Reward. All right, we just, we're just gonna go? Facecam? No, no, no,
no facecam. Just imagine what I look like right now. You get scammed, scammed. Will he unbox at
least one strange item? I kind of feel like that's gonna happen. Okay, you ready? Let's just start at
the top. I made it nice and clear. By the way, this is what I was talking about. This is just
all the Scout primaries, all the Scout secondaries, all the Scout melees.
I like them to be some separation here. By quality. Notice how this is by quality.
Soldier, right? That's a Minimal Wear. What are my best items? Let me see. It's Factory New.
I have, yeah, okay. I've got, this is a Factory New Warhawk Flamethrower. This thing is pretty
sick. Nice organization. Yeah, oh yeah. I have a really good sniper rifle too, or is it? Yeah,
I got a Purple Range Factory New. Cool. I also have a field-tested one. Why do I still have this?
I don't know. Where's the skip button to the unboxing? Okay, all right, all right, all right.
All right, Blue Moon. Let's see. Are we ready? Here we go. I could get any of these. We're looking
for the Robin Walkers. Why are people omega-lulling? Is this a bad one? Let's go. Oh, I got an Assassin's
attire. Nothing else. Oh, a free ticket! I don't want to do this anymore. I think I'm done. That
was all right. Cool. Wait, let's look at it. Okay, I put the gibbous on because I didn't want people
to be mad that I was a bad spy player. I forgot. All right, I put this on to like hide because I
didn't want people to, because if you're in like full cosmetics, if you're like decked out a bunch
of crazy shit, people are like, oh, that's, look at all this cool stuff the spy has. I put the gibbous
on because I want people to go like, oh, that's like, I don't know, that he might have been playing
for very long. All right, let's put it on. Ooh, I like it. Cool. Okay, cool. Let's do it again.
I got two items again. What is it? Sky high fly guy and a backpack expander. That's cool. Those
are like worth, aren't these like five bucks? These things are like five or six bucks, aren't they?
LOL, no. No, no, no. They're a dollar. They're like five cents. Oh, okay. Well, that's cool.
Yeah, I already have. I don't really need to use this. Who's this for? Soldier. I like it. Cool.
I'm gonna keep it on. We're gonna be here all day? No, we're not. Let's do it again.
What's the good thing from this? This is the last chance. Oh, it's another blue. I freaking
love gambling. I kind of just want the cosmetics, if I'm honest, because I've given my backpack away
like three times over the last 10 years, so I don't really have very many like cosmetic items.
I kind of want to like just get some more. This is heavy, obviously, right? I mean, I don't think I
can take off the parted wig. That's just not going to happen. I got a genuine pounding father, by the
way. Jealous. I like it. It's two jackets. One of them is just ripping through the other one. I like
it. It looks like I don't know what I'm doing. That's perfect. Two jacket Andy. Yeah, I'm keeping
it. All right, now that's all those. So those are gone. Tough break. We're looking for a well-wrapped
hat. Okay, let's go. What's that? Ooh, what's that? Is that good? Should I even care? Winter backup?
What was that? Was it good? It's an engineer item. I love the engineer stuff.
Uh, where is it? That's kind of a rare one. I like it, but I wish I want the hair still. That's not
the worst thing you get. Yeah, it's pretty neat. I like it. I'm not taking the level three chin off,
though. Or the stomach. It's important. Good. This is exactly what I wanted. I wanted just to get
items to put on to wear because I want to be able to have different outfits. All right, so what
about? Let me see. What else is in here? So that was a good one. That was winter backup. I could
inspect them, but I don't want to. I like to be surprised. Another backpack expander. Okay. But
what's the real item? Uh, ooh, this is another one. A bonk, batters, bat. So this is a backpack.
This is another kind of kind of rare one. That's cool. Let me see it. Oh shit, that's like one of
the better ones. Cool. This is not a bad drip for the scout. This kind of like hooded sweatshirt with
the bonk on the back and the sneakers. This is a pretty good outfit. I like this. I'm into it. Nice.
All right, one more of these. Also, I'm not, I'm probably not going to do this again. This is kind
of just like a one and done kind of deal. I just want to get some more cosmetics. So don't expect
like, oh yeah, I'm going to open like 50 cases every week. That's no, I just had a bunch of
inventory and I'm just kind of clearing it out and I was going to do it off stream, but it's like,
you know what? Why don't we just, why don't I just do it here? So this is probably not happening
again. Kappa, Kappa, Kappa. Well, it might happen at, so I don't know, but it's not like I'm not
just going to open cases. It's not a regular thing. It's a demo. Medic. I like the chef hat.
Oh, it's a, that's cool. Okay. I'll keep it. All right. I only have one of these. I have one rainy
day. So it better be good. You do not think that's cool. This is the best one. Rainy day is,
rainy day is best one. Actually, unironically, for real, people are saying this is like the
best one that I have. All right, here we go. What is that? That's cool. I like this one a lot. I'm
going to, I'm going to wear this right now. It's going to replace the gibbous. Oh, this, I can't
have the sunglasses on. It's perfect. All right. What else? Do I have anything else?
I don't know. That's not bad. Do it with the gibbous? No, I'm not putting the gibbous on with
this. I like this because it's got the microphone. All right. I'm keeping it. Okay. So I also have
one of these. Abominable cosmetic case. Drip or drop? I don't know. Explain the stream title.
A mod did it. I don't know. I cannot condone anything that the mods are doing right now. I have no
idea what it says. I can't even look over there because it's tabbed out. All right. What's in this
one? Let's get a red. Can you guys even hear it being opened? I'll take a Manco ticket. Why not?
Sniper? Barely. Eh, it's all right. That looks like a cool sniper hat. Kind of low on the tier
list, but see, I got a red already. The sniper outfit, I don't think can change. It's too good.
You know what I mean? I'm not sure I can take that off. It's too good. Skibbidi toilet looking
motherfucker. It works. I could put it on a different loadout. Yeah, look at this one. Skibbidi
toilet. Oh, come on. All right. This, we'll do the war paint after. I feel like that's, we do that
as a follow-up. We'll do the cosmetics first. All right. This is winter 2018. I was told that
don't do these because they're terrible. Well, it's too late. I already have four keys for it.
So we're just gonna, we'll get through it. This is winter 2018. I only have two of these. How is
that terrible? That's awesome. I have a little like engineer thing now. Are you serious? It's
for the pyro? By the way, imagine this motherfucker sitting in spawn AFK. This is the actual loadout
caught red handed. This is the loadout. This is it right here. This is my loadout caught red handed.
I love my pyro loadout. I think it looks great. I love the glasses, but that's cool too. Mosquito
face. Yeah. I painted it white. Yeah. That's funny. I'll keep it. Got one more of those. So
what's the good stuff? Dumbbell, millennial mercenary. I'm very curious about that. Breadheads. Oh wow.
And I got a festivizer. Uh, engineer's my favorite class too. So this is great. I'm glad to get this.
Well, I can't replace anything. Shit. It works. Cool. All right. I'm liking the NG stuff. All
right. Now we're going to teleport two years. This is winter 2020. I've never opened one of these.
I don't have anything. Are you using the pompson? Cause a lot of items got changed and I was just
curious as to how much. All right. 2020. Give us something good. That's, that's pretty great.
I can wear those right now, right? Can I wear these right now? Who can wear these?
It's an all class. Oh God damn it. Oh damn it. Oh damn it. Okay. That's exactly what's going on.
I think this is a perfect loadout now. Put it on every class. Put it on the fat guy NG. Oh,
that's a good idea. Hold on. I need, I need to get rid of the helmet though. That's going to be so
annoying to every single person that plays the game with me. It looks awful. I think it looks
great. What about a blue, right? Ooh, cool. Yeah. I love it. Remove the tracker. Uh, I like it. Those
are all the way down. I would put those up at pink. Those are, that's a pink item. That's not a blue.
Oh my goodness. Oh my goodness. It's perfect. And I can wear this all year. It's all class.
Am I going to really just be like the Christmas dickhead? I guess so.
Hey, Merry Christmas all year. Put it on the soldier. Yep. It works. It works pretty well,
especially because the Santa, um, the heavy would be great. Okay. Not bad. That's phenomenal. Just
put it on every single character and just be Christmas on every single character. All right.
Let's keep going. Uh, I'll do these last because these are, who cares? Should I just do them now?
This is this year. This is the cosmetics for right now. The patch. Should I just do them now? Do it
now? Do it last. All right. We'll do these both last cause this is also the Warpaint from this
update too. All right. With that being said, this is Scream Fortress. This is Warpaint now.
So Warpaint is the factory new minimum, a minimal wearer field tested, like you probably used to
being seen. They changed how this works. I kind of understand it now, but let's find out. So I
only, I don't have very many left, so let's go. I only have one of these. Oh, this is X. Let's go.
What is it? It's, it's really scuffed. It's one of the good ones, but it is fucking destroyed.
Dammit. Is that the worst one? Is that the worst quality? Field tested. Dammit. Uh, let's put it on
like something. So you can put this on any of these. That's really cool. And I think it randomizes.
It's a puke weapon. Yeah. What about the Ubersaw stuff looks really good on shotgun. You can't go
wrong either because so many people can use it. I mean, it is, it is a booger gun. What about the
mini gun? Mini gun always looks pretty cool. Too bad it's field tested. Field tested is the second
worst, right? Dammit. It's one of the good ones too. So it goes battle scarred field tested, um,
well-worn, minimal wear, factory new. I think that's correct. Let's do it again. Something good,
at least something with higher quality. Oh, look at how awesome that one is too. And it looks
all fucked up. Dammit. This could have been my favorite paint. Field tested. Dammit. Although it
is a Halloween kind of weapon, the scuffed in the blood actually kind of adds to it.
Trash this? I don't think it needs to be trashed. I kind of like it on the wrench.
So correct, from my understanding, when, when this is put on, it, it gives a random pattern of this
paint. So it's kind of just showing you what's even possible, right? I'm seeing a lot of nos.
You choose the pattern. Oh, somebody said, who cares? Yes, at the end of the day. That's right.
All right. This is winter 2020 paint. We got to cross our fingers here for this one because
we have the full Santa Claus outfit. And if we get like a cool,
kind of like candy cane paint. Manco ticket. Okay. That's really cool. But how cool is it?
Field tested again. Looks great, but another field tested. Gosh darn it. I would put it on a blade.
Ice blade. Not bad. It's cool. Starlight Serenity War Paint. All right. So that's the one you want.
Ooh, that looks pretty good. I don't see very much wrong with this and a strange count transfer tool.
Oh, here it is. It is factory new. All right. It's one of the lower tiers,
but that's fine. It's factory new. Holy shit. I'm going to be so annoying. That's really annoying,
but I think it kind of has to be there and put the festivizer on it. Yeah, that's funny.
Okay. That leads to this one. This is another Scream Fortress 14. Cream corned war paint.
This is beat up a lot. That does not look good. Well worn. Yeah, it doesn't look terrible.
It could work on something. You can put it on the fish. That's funny. It looks sick.
Yeah, no one's going to get that close to see it anyways. All right. So now we've got
down to the last little bits of war paint. This was jungle jackpot. I don't have any of these.
Give me a, give me like a factory new. Give me a fact. I only got one factory new. Shit.
Bamboo brushed war paint. Yeah. The scarring on it looks a little weird. It's the weed one.
Yeah. This one's kind of, this one's kind of junk. Although it's really not that bad.
It's a little junky. It's a lot junky. That's a lot junky. The scuffs messes with the pattern
because without the scuffs, it would still have this, at least this shading here.
So it just makes it look kind of all broken, but it's art. That looks pretty good. I think
that's a factory new and it's a leopard print. Oh, nice. Okay. What else? Another Manco ticket.
I want to see. It is factory new. Nice. All right. What am I going to put the
leopard print on? Damn. Wait, it can be different colors. Whoa. That's cool. That's really cool.
Everything looks so good on the mini gun. There's just so much surface area.
All right. That's, I'm going to have to, that's going to take a decision
because it works on almost everything. That looks awesome. Cool. All right. I got a good one.
Even if it's not, it's a low rarity, but who cares? Again, I'm not looking for rare. I'm
not looking for unusuals. I'm not looking for anything like that. I'm just, I just want more
cosmetic items because I just don't have very many. All right. This is Infernal Reward.
I don't know what this is or what year this is, but this is, we got two more of these.
Yeah. I don't even care if it's like field tested as long as it looks kind of cool.
Okay. Strange part. Tanks destroyed and merc stained war paint. Tanks destroyed.
Man vs. Machine. It's going to be field tested. No, that's, that's fine. That doesn't look like
minimal wear. That looks kind of beat up. It looks pretty beat up. This looks beat up.
I'm surprised that's minimal wear. What do the other ones look like if that's what it looks like
for, I like that. Cool. It's too bright. I think it looks all right. All right. This is the last
one of these. And then we only have the cases that are this current event. Cardboard box,
minimal wear. So this is just a cardboard item. Put it on the black box. That's a great place to
put it. Cardboard rocket launcher. It's the Labo. It does look like the Labo. Cool. All right. So now
we just got these four left and it's the summer 2023 stuff. So what do I want from here? Put that
on the wrap assassin because it's not always the red rare items that people want. Do the war paint
first because that's less exciting. Okay. Let's go. All right. This is it. This is this update.
Let's see what happens. That looks pretty new. That looks pretty new. What? I didn't see. What
was it? It is factory new. Nice. Inspect the cases to see the options. I like to be surprised
because I don't, I don't want to see what I can get because then I'll go, I don't want that. I
don't want that. I don't want that. I don't want that. I want that. And then my brain is like,
you're opening this case to get that item, which is not going to happen. Right? It looks great on
the degreaser. That's a smart gambler. I don't know if that, that's not, that statement doesn't
hold on. Okay. Smart gambler. Oh, oh, it's a good one, but it's all fucked up. Where is it? No,
that's not bad. Minimal wear. It's kind of just like steel. Yeah. Just stainless steel. Scatter
gun. Put it on the fish. What about the knife? Flamethrower. I like that a lot because a
flamethrower would be kind of steel, wouldn't it? Like a propane tank. I kind of like that.
Put it on the fish. Let's see. Stainless steel fish. Yeah. That actually is really,
really cool. That's pretty cool. All right. Here we go. This is it. This is why you all
waited this long for me to do this. What's in the cosmetic case for 2023? All right. Okay. Okay.
That's all right. It's pretty cool. I don't love it, but I don't hate it. I just wanted more
options. All right. And this is it. This is the last one. No more cases after this. Here we go.
No unusual. Oh well. It's not what I was looking for though. I got a couple more heavy jackets,
the frayed edges. We need to make the call. Does the strange part count as a strange? Um,
I don't know. Can you open, can you unbox strange versions of items? I don't think that counts. No,
you can unbox a strange. So a strange part. I don't think it is like a strange item, right?
You can get strange war paints. Okay. Yeah. I don't think that counts. I think we were referring to
like orange letters out of the box. It's like a strange part, strange weapon not part. All right.
Well, there we go. Cool. I got a new, I'm so glad that I got this. I only had to spend, um,
that's kind of like a lot for a pair of fucking shoes. Yeah. That's fun. You should buy 50 more.
No. If, okay, if I collect some more, I have some other cases like old crates, the old crates,
but maybe another time crack them open. Nah, maybe another time. Maybe another time. All right.
That's going to be it. Uh, before we go, I do want to bring something up. So if you're just still
hanging out, let me just head over here. So I want to bring this up. I want to talk about this is
really actually very, very serious. Um, so I'm not, this is no, no joking around right now. I'm
talking to you pretty real. Uh, those of you that remember the Nevada Science Center, Science
Center Nevada, remember Science Center Josh, remember? Well, we, we got word. We heard that
Josh was in a pretty, pretty major accident and it's very, very tragic. It's actually really,
really sad and really awful. And they have a GoFundMe to try to help out. And those of you
that don't know who this is, if you watch the archeology stream where Grotto Beast was from,
he was on the stream. He was a big part of that. And if the, can the mods link it? Can we get it
like pinned? That's really terrible. So if you can spare anything, there's a link. It's a really,
really sad, really tragic, but he was a great guy and it's a great family. And it's a, it's a really,
really terrible tragic thing to happen. He made that stream so much more fun. So hopefully,
you know, we can help out a little weekend. Yeah. I just wanted to kind of bring it up,
put some attention to it. Yeah. Yeah. Cause when we, when we heard about it, it was just like,
like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, that's too good of a fucking family, too good of a people.
It really, really is just so, it hurts. I didn't, I don't know them very well, but they came out and
they really made that stream something special and it makes me feel terrible. Yeah. So if you can,
it's there. Yeah. It's a terrible situation. Yeah. We're, we're, I'm just, when we heard about it,
I was just devastated. I said, how do you, how do you even, what do you even say when you see
something like that and you know, it's just so, but we can help. We will. And I, I want to at least
make sure that I talked about it because I know a lot of people really found that stream to be in
Grotto. It's like a Grotto beast. Grotto beast has become like a really great success. Like it's been
really fun. I'm very fortunate over here to have that project be a success as much as it was.
So we're going to ping this in the discord too. We're going to do an announcement in the discord.
Yeah. And best of luck to that family recovering as best as they can. But yeah, I will see you guys
later. I'll see you on, Ster's going to be hanging out for a little while. So probably next week,
I do have some stuff that I have to do for work that I need to make sure I take care of. So next
week, keep an eye on the sus. Ster is going to be here. Yeah. Take care of yourselves. It's great
to hang out. I know this was a short one, but yeah, just it's fun. It's fun just to hang out and just
talk. Relax. Have a great week. I'll see you all very soon. Take care. Cool crates. Yeah,
that was kind of fun too. Opening crates is fun. Now I got some new outfits. Yeah. See you soon.
Take care. See you next week. Oh, I'll, there'll be some Grotto beasts digital tabletop simulator
news. I know people have been waiting for that. Been being developed for a long time. So it's,
we're going to have some stuff to talk about. So Grotto beast, Grotto beast is going to be
coming back in the digital space. Are you going to talk about it next stream?
Maybe. That's very possible. Pog, I got no clue what's going on.
Thanks for the support. Thank you. All right. I'll see you guys later. Take care.