PlayStation stream? Go to the PlayStation? PlayStation Direct?
No, no, no. No, I'm not- I'm not watchin' another Direct.
The last one disappointed me. I'm not- What? For me to learn what?
What are we gonna learn on this Direct?
PlayStation Direct. PlayStation Direct.
It actually is called PlayStation Direct.
Play the- PlayStation Direct.
No, this is like a shipping company.
Wait, PlayStation Direct.
Limited time only. Free shipping on your entire order with any accessories.
Purchase of $60 or more.
Must meet order threshold of $60.
Some customers may be affected by- Oh, okay.
Watch it.
No, I'm not gonna- I don't wanna watch the PlayStation.
Okay, when did it start? When did it start?
30 minutes ago? Alright. And how long is it gonna go?
You give me updates, okay?
When the Ratchet and Clank IRL movie comes out, you just let me know when they announce it.
I'm not watchin' another Direct.
Not unless it's the one I wanna watch.
And no more of those.
It just ended.
You haven't missed anything?
It ended when you started. Oh, so you've just fucked with me, okay.
It was a Crash Bandicoot.
Yeah.
It's prob- They're gonna keep- They'll keep making Crash Bandicoot.
I never was concerned they wouldn't do it.
Ever since they did the- The Insane Trilogy.
Come on, of course they're gonna do another one.
Elden Ring?
No, there was the- Hold on. Was there an Elden Ring thing?
What has it been on the PlayStation one?
Elden Ring leaks posted by impatient fans.
Ha ha ha. Are fake, okay.
Elden Ring Insider shares update.
Okay.
That's- That's not real.
Whatever.
You tell me what happens.
You know, sitting there for 60 minutes with my fingers in my mouth just biting my fingernails, are they gonna announce?
Are they gonna announce Super Street Fighter VII?
No, I can read it in a tweet.
Five minutes.
After the thing's over.
I'd rather relax.
And just like, make chocolates and then- Oh, wait a minute.
Elden Ring has an announcement?
Date?
Oh, okay. I can be in the bathtub and read that.
That's too much. Too much stress.
I'd lived through that. I did that shit. I'd lived through that and I don't want to live through that again.
I remember Super Smash Bros. Brawl.
Sakurai would do weekly Friday updates.
Announcing a new character or a new thing that was in the game.
And that was what you did.
It was at three o'clock in the morning.
And it was all I cared about.
Oh my god, is this the day?
Are they gonna- Is- Oh my god, is Donkey Kong in this one?
It consumed like four months of my life.
And then I played-
I played Brawl for probably a total of-
Oh, no, no, no. That's the one I played a lot of.
Yeah, that was worth it.
It's so funny because Brawl is the one that I put all the time into and it's the one that everybody says is the worst one.
Right? By a lot.
I thought it was fun.
But I know that most people say that that's the absolute worst one.
It's the one I actually played.
Meta Knight was in the game.
Oh, yeah. I remember people playing Meta Knight.
They just turned into the drill and just flew around and just won every single match.
I remember that.
Brawl was the best casual one.
Yeah, I mean, it was fun.
I- That's the one I put all the time into.
Why don't you stream the awful PlayStation Direct?
I'm not- No, we're not doing that.
We are gonna- I'm gonna just change the camera because-
Wait, I didn't even tweet this. I'm not even here. I'll be right back.
This shit ended an hour ago.
You liars. This ended like a full hour ago.
I'm sitting here being like, eh, maybe I should stream this. Eh, maybe it's almost-
Maybe there'll be an announcement at the end.
There's nothing on here. It was- This was like over.
It ended seven minutes ago.
Well, then look. Then, good, it was fu- It was good I didn't stream it.
Because guess what? I don't see anybody talking about anything in this Direct.
I've seen like two things that people thought was cool.
I would've- It would've been spammed if something huge was announced.
So, what? Whatever.
Alright, I'm ready. I didn't- I didn't- I didn't even tweet anything. I'll be right back.
Do I not know how to spell chocolate so badly that my iPhone thought I was trying to say cholesterol?
How do you spell- It's choc- col- choc-o-late, right?
Choc-o-late.
Factory.
Entrepreneur.
Holy shit.
Chocolate. Fav-tory.
Entree-an-or-near.
I can't type. I hate these fucking things.
I hate phones.
I hate them. I don't want them anymore.
I don't want to use this phone anymore.
Fucking try- Get me by goddamn-
Send to Telegram.
I'm gonna give you guys a stream notification by Telegram.
Alright, hold on. I'm almost ready.
PlayStation Direct.
You- I- I can't- Dude, what would- What- Okay.
What do you think would happen if Super Mario was announced for PlayStation?
What would happen?
I think Twitter would go down.
Like, if it was like, Super Mario!
It's 8! Or something.
Like, Super Mario Galaxy 3 was on PlayStation 5.
What do you think would happen?
Talk to the factory entrepreneur. Alright, there we go.
Alright, we're gonna pick up where we left off yesterday.
I really like this game. I think it's fun.
That would make no sense.
I know, that would make no fucking sense.
It would make absolutely no sense.
That's like a dream that you have.
Right? What I just said was so stupid and just so, like, I'm just stalling to make a tweet.
That- You have a dream where that happens.
And it's a dream that you forget when you wake up.
It's so asinine.
And just so- Just-
Not important at all.
That's the ones you forget.
What the fuck was that dream? I don't know.
Something about, like, a game? I don't know.
I forget it. It was so fucking inconsequential to me.
Alright, let's go.
Is camera not on right?
I'm always so paranoid about this shit. I swear to God.
Oh, wait, hold on.
Did it go into full screen, man?
Ooh, I remember this music.
What the fuck? Naked.
Yeah.
You wish.
Alright, so, where we left off, if you missed the last stream.
Wait, this is Chocolatier.
I forget- I don't know what this is a hashtag.
Not a hashtag, it's a colon.
It's called the- It's just Chocolatier.
You make chocolates.
You have to fly around the world, buy ingredients, make money.
If you weren't here yesterday, you missed a lot of money.
The last thing I was doing- We have a quest log here.
Right, okay. I remember.
It was gambling? Yes, there is.
But I'm not gonna go do that right now.
I'm gonna just chill and play- I gotta do my quests.
That was disgusting. I'm sad that that got picked up by the microphone.
Alright, so, I got coffee here.
This is my Cuban clock cleaner.
It's got cayenne pepper, Cuban coffee, and honey.
If I'm not mistaken.
This is a huge seller.
And then I'm making the special reserve.
Right, I'm making it for a reason though.
I have 40 cases of Arabian Bolden Inventory.
I'm gonna go back to this fine coffee maker here.
I have two cases- Oh wait, this guy.
The guy that gave us the tip.
I forgot about this guy.
He doesn't want very much.
Okay, we'd have to give him two cases of raspberry.
24 cases of Cafe Con Leche.
Alright, 34 cases of special 66% African cacao reserves.
Which I should have.
Talk to-
Oh wait, we have to go back to this person?
This guy wants to bring two cases of raspberry.
And he gave us a recipe.
But he also wants 34 cases of the special reserve for a recipe.
So I gotta make the raspberry ones too.
I can't go back empty-handed here.
Alright, let's go back to the chocolate factory.
Leche means milk.
Why is that confusing you?
Look, it's been a day.
The chocolate ark.
That's right.
Alright, so what do we got?
I have 30- Okay, I need 34 of the special reserve.
I have 34 Cuban clock cleaners.
This is gonna be a fucking huge sale.
Oh, that's not good.
No, no, I'm not selling it here.
Get out of here with these low prices.
What else do I need to make?
I need to continue making this.
Almost out of peppers.
We- I gotta change what coffee I'm making.
But first of all, I'm gonna make-
I'm just gonna make this right now.
And I'm gonna change it to raspberry.
Because we need a bunch of these.
Make it.
Here we go.
Let's see how rusty I am.
Poison in the coffee.
Well, you're a psycho.
Hey dude, I got a wicked good idea of how you can really grow your business.
Put poison in the coffee.
I think your business would not last very long.
You'd be out of business very shortly.
Put poison in the coffee.
You spend all the time.
All the money, all the resources to get the factories, get the permits.
And the first thing you want to do, the factory's ready to go.
You got the chocolate.
You've got the recipes.
It was passed out by your fucking grandmother.
Spray Windex and all that.
What the fuck, dude?
No, what are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
What the fuck, dude?
Fuck you.
All right, well, that's the end of that day.
Like, oh, we got our chocolate spinning in that big vat
that you see on every single one of those How It's Made videos.
With the churning.
It's a big bowl.
That's sideways.
That's spinning.
And some guy comes over the ladle and he drops like flavorings in it.
It spins around.
And then the CEO comes over with Windex and goes.
Fuck you.
Get out of here.
I'm doing shit here.
We just opened the factory.
Get the fuck out of here.
Go home.
He throws cigarettes in.
He just has a lit cigarette.
That chocolate looks really good.
Imagine being the chocolatier and being like, you fucking asshole.
Now we got to shut the whole thing down.
God.
Well, I'm not that guy.
He's actually mad.
I am mad at this guy.
This guy, that was stupid what he did.
He shouldn't have done that.
He sprayed Windex into my chocolate spinning undulator
and it's making me very mad.
This person doesn't exist, but I hate them.
I hate this person.
Oh, we're out of coffee.
Okay.
You mad at a made-up person.
So what?
Could be real.
Okay.
Now, okay, we need to change this.
We need more of the special reserve chocolate.
I love this game.
This game is so cool.
All right.
I need to do a change recipe.
I need a raspberry.
Ooh, look at that.
How many cases do I need?
Just two, right?
But we could probably sell this for pretty good.
All right.
Let's go for it.
Beef in the chocolate.
I mean, I don't know how the in-depth the game gets later,
but I know for a fact that
we have at least four of the pages that we have not made chocolates on.
That's a full stack.
I'm really happy about that one.
Really happy about that turned out.
I wish that I wish that I didn't want games like this.
I don't care about any other video game.
You guys wanted me to watch the fucking PlayStation Direct.
I care about this.
I want I'm gonna play this.
Like PlayStation could have come up with a press release that said
if you watched the direct you got $50 deposited into your bank account
and I would be like I'd rather play the chocolate game.
I don't care.
Be like, no, I don't care.
I'm busy.
I'm very busy.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Rich Stravers.
No, I'm am I the am I the weird CEO?
No, I don't want to be the weird CEO guy that like just I'm playing my
chocolate game.
Leave me alone.
Get the fuck away from me.
You're a millennial CEO.
I've got I've got like a fucking Star Wars t-shirt on.
I'm wearing slippers and like jogging pants and I like skipped out on
my company meeting because I'm playing an old nostalgic chocolate
making game.
Oh, no guys.
This shit like kind of happened.
I've got like important stuff going on.
We got I got a huge fucking stream coming up and I skipped out on
a fucking meeting.
It didn't happen today, but it may have happened.
I lay yesterday.
It's real.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't worry.
It's okay.
I'll bring myself down a few pegs when I do the Catboy stream, right?
Down a few pegs.
It's a term.
It's cleaning your clock.
It's down a few pegs.
It's getting knocked down a few.
You have no idea what my plan is for that stream.
I'm going to tell you one of the plans and I can't do it and I
it's a hold on.
I have to ask if I can do no.
All right.
You know, I'm going to tell you one of the things I was going to
do you don't think I'll be knocked down a few pegs.
I wanted to have should I tell you should I tell you should I keep
it a secret for the Catboy stream?
That's something that'll knock me down a few pegs.
Hmm.
Maybe I'll tell you now.
No, I can't tell you because if I can do it, it's worth it.
Secret.
All right.
It's fine.
Fine.
All right.
How about this?
If I can't do it, I'll tell you if I cannot do the thing I want
to do on the Catboy stream after the Catboy stream, I will tell
you what it was and then you can decide if it was a bad or
a good idea or not.
Okay.
Deal.
All right.
Cool.
So I have enough.
All right.
So let's go deliver this to this the guy he wants the raspberry.
I'm going to see.
He wants to raspberry.
So I'm going to who likes row.
Ooh, it's 17 sell 15 of these raspberry cases.
That's 8,800 bucks clean right there.
Bring those two to him.
He needs I can get what way more for this coffee.
I changed the coffee to any cayenne peppers, but I'm flooding
the market with Cuban clock cleaners.
Remember, it's two Catboy streams.
Yeah.
Well, the first Catboy stream is going to be a little wild.
The second Catboy stream of us.
I don't know.
I'm not going to say it.
Just wait.
Maybe.
Maybe you're like a year.
I'm just kidding.
It'll happen in like a few months.
It'll happen in probably like three months, four months.
All right, let's go.
I need to travel to where was this guy?
Okay in years.
It's not tomorrow.
No.
All right.
Here we go.
Hey Steve.
So that was the two raspberry.
Oh, so we got this guy's a contact now and then 34 cases of the reserve.
There it is.
I trust Felix had something to do with this in which case it's
my pleasure to give you a new coffee recipe special blend.
And of course you can find the Moroccan coffee for this recipe
at the market here in Tangier's.
Stop by in a month or so.
I hear all kinds of things down at the port.
Ooh, special blend.
I got I have a lot of this.
Should I make some special blend coffee?
No.
No, what was that?
That was a weird voice.
I had a fucking dream about SpongeBob.
What was it?
Oh my God.
What was the dream about SpongeBob?
I had one of those stupid inconsequential dreams and
remember we talked about how Super Mario was on PlayStation 5
and that's like a dumb dream that like who cares and you wake
up and you don't even give a shit anymore.
You forget it in an hour.
I had a SpongeBob on TV did something dream.
That was so dumb and inconsequential and meant nothing.
But what was it?
Oh my God.
What was it?
It was so inconsequential.
It was stupid.
Okay.
I think the reason why I said the imagine if Mario was on
PlayStation thing was because I think the only thing that was
weird about the dream was SpongeBob was on TBS or something.
That was it.
It was like, oh why SpongeBob's on TBS?
That's he's not on this network.
I think that's why I said that today.
Is that really what happened?
Am I just retroactively adding that memory in?
I don't know.
I think that's what happened though.
Okay.
Let's all right.
I need to sell fine.
I trusted you with a recipe silly zonka wonka.
I also trusted the next time you darken my doorway.
You'll have 40 cases of Arabian bold.
We agreed upon.
That's not a bad price considering I flooded the market with this stuff.
No, no, no, I'm not going to sell it here.
Let me say play the game.
This is playing the game.
It's fucking talking and making deals.
That's the what is we talking about play the game.
I'm talking and making deals with people Jesus.
That's so expensive.
All right.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to go sell this.
You have peppers.
No.
Okay.
I need to get peppers.
Let's see if we can sell this Cuban clock cleaner for like 150 grand.
I can.
All right.
I can get about this is cheap.
Fuck.
I had an opportunity to get rid of all this.
That's not a bad price for this though.
Yeah, I'll sell it.
Not a bad price for the raspberry either.
I'm gonna sell it.
I want someone to previous to seem for 15 to 45.
I could have sold it for 2238 in Tangier's fuck.
Did I hear that you might be able to move a bit on your offer?
But that's still not enough.
Is that the best price?
I'm going to get for this until I have to change coffees.
We're like, this is the among us guy.
No, you keep people keep confusing me for that person.
People confuse me for that person all the time.
I don't know who that person is.
You're a liar.
They used germa sus at the Sony conference.
What the fuck are you talking about?
No, they didn't.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Fuck.
I just exit of the game.
I did.
I'm good.
What do you mean?
Show me.
They did.
No, they didn't.
I don't believe you.
Which master grill xbbq has been banned or whatever.
Good stream of it.
But why are you linking me this?
Why are you linking me this?
Give me the real one.
Give me the why are you linking me this shit?
Okay.
So for like the people that have told me please play the game
and let's hang out you have to blame not just me.
I'm making deals.
You got to blame the people like the 5,000 people that sent
a link in the chat saying please click germa sus is here
and it's a streamer band fake streamer band thing.
We do talk about wasting time.
This is like the ultimate time waster.
It's all right.
I'll be here for a while today.
I'm not was ain't going to be a three-hour stream.
You're enabling them wrong link.
Well, what's the right one?
I haven't seen it yet.
Google.com.
What is wrong with you?
You do literally have an Among Us command sus.
Oh my god, bear that person for a six minutes.
I have a yes.
All right.
It's time.
It's time for me to go off.
You know how I have a sus command.
I do I have a sus command that is sense danger.
It is from sorcery.
I've had that command since like 2015.
That's a command from it's a spell in the game sorcery way
before all this among us shit.
I said shit with a like an angry mean voice, but I meant to
say like among us shit like all this among us stuff had that
for like five years and I ain't changing it.
All right.
Well, it's a black screen right now.
Thanks for the link the PlayStation Direct.
Let's can we let's go back to playing the video game,
please going on with you guys today.
Hmm full moon.
Is there a full moon check?
I'm gonna check and see if there's a full moon tonight.
Is it I bet it is I bet it is okay, so I can I don't know
if I want to sell this for 1887.
I can get a better price somewhere else.
Although I should buy some more peppers.
Are you is this price final here?
Is there a little bit of wiggle room here?
Thank you.
What that really is a little bit.
That was like a dollar off.
That was three dollars off the full moon tomorrow.
Yeah, I know.
Trust me.
I know.
Well, whatever I need enough to get rid of the honey.
I'm going big.
I'm gonna sell a shitload of these.
All right.
You might think that but it was a bad idea, but I needed the
peppers almonds are pretty cheap here.
Ooh, that's cheap friends.
These are really cheap.
Yeah, I'm gonna get a bunch of these two.
Let's get a hundred of these.
I got tons of sugar already.
All right, that should continue to produce by the way, if
you don't know why I did that if this is me that weren't
here yesterday every time I travel or make a new batch
of chocolate a week goes by so this is not producing
chocolate right now.
It only starts to produce when I cycle through time.
We have not done that yet.
It's every every time I do a task.
No one cares.
Oh, okay.
No, no one cares says Jerma zerked on stream.
Jerma zerked on stream says hey nobody cares.
Should we mod them for an hour?
No, I can't see back.
All right back like back like years ago like all mod
that guy ha ha.
Oh, yeah.
I modded that guy for like 45 minutes or something.
There are whole systems in place now across like the
discord and the channel.
We're modding somebody for like 30 minutes might pose
complete disaster to detonate the entire community.
They could just they could cause mayhem if they really
wanted to so like I can't do that anymore.
It's a funny thought though, isn't it true?
So do it.
No VIP them.
There are whole systems in place.
Now.
All right play the fucking game 13% of people that watch
the stream on the census want you to play the video
game.
I have to make them happy.
Holy shit.
I gotta take a picture of this.
What the fuck is going on?
Quick quick quick quick quick quick quick quick.
This battery just is standing on end.
This is like a magic thing.
I have no idea what's going on.
I don't know how this is happening how this is how
this is happening.
I gotta get a picture of this.
Oh my fucking God.
What is doing this floating?
I have a floating battery in front of me.
Why why holy shit?
Why is that happening?
Okay.
I have to let me get I have to shut I'm gonna put
this on the discord or just I'm gonna put it on
here the cam on no no no I can't I'm naked.
Why did this happen?
You guys have to see this.
I gotta get this.
I'll tweet.
I'm gonna tweet this out.
Here comes a tweet.
I'm just gonna I don't understand why this happened.
You tell me what's going on here.
This is probably so easily explainable, but I can't
explain it.
So I'm gonna delete this tweet in like an hour.
Okay, here it goes.
Tell me what's going on here.
Did it go through?
Why did that happen?
Why is this floating?
It's a magnet.
This is not a magnet.
That's a base of my that's the base of my monitors.
That's a monitor stand.
It's dusty.
Come on.
But what do you mean magnet?
This is this is the bottom of my monitor stand.
This is not there's not a magnet right here static
electricity.
Why is the battery stuck?
I don't know.
It's stuck hard.
There's a magnet in the battery.
You can't see the magnets in the monitor.
What your monitor has magnetic properties.
I'm gonna put it on stream.
You guys see it.
It's all magnets.
This literally has to be a magnet in there.
Why would there be a magnet on the bottom of my
monitor?
What the fuck would the point be having a monitor
stand with a magnet in the bottom?
Why would you tweet this?
I don't know.
I'm deleting it.
Batteries are magnetic.
Yeah, but I have like a plastic stand.
I think that's magic.
Okay, that's this.
That's the image you send like to your mom being
like mom.
What the heck is going on?
And she's like, oh honey, that's really really
interesting.
No, there are magnets battery is magnetized
and it's sticking to the metal base of your
monitor really neat though, really really cool
that it happened that way.
I didn't put it there.
I'm telling you I just like I took a sip of my
coffee and I heard and I looked over in this
fucking Duracell just sticking out of my monitor.
That was weird.
It's neat.
Okay, neat things.
All right, clean your desk.
It's dusty.
I live in Las Vegas.
It's dry and dusty here.
Dust it.
No, I did.
I do and none of that.
That's oh no, I see what you guys are saying.
That's just like a weird finish on the bottom
of my monitor.
I see what you guys are saying that like the
dust on the thing is not actually dust.
It's like a it's like just speckled for some
reason.
That was your fucking desk look like okay right
now at least 5000 of you just crumpled up the
fucking like McDonald's french fry container
you have on there just sitting there with like
three just dead gross fries at the bottom that
you didn't eat and you just like I threw that
away.
That's not on my desk.
Sure, but I have a little bit of dust on my desk.
I am not allowed to sneeze.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's go.
You're projecting.
No, I it's called I am leveling with you.
We're not American but only Americans eat
McDonald's.
This person is lost by the way, they just keep
driving around in a circle.
I feel like I want to come to stop this person.
How much cocaine do you do?
Zero.
I have no drugs in my system and I never have I
am naturally fucking out of my mind.
Okay, it's natural.
What about red wine?
No, I just today.
I don't know.
I'm just like I'm like I'm uppity today.
You know, I'm very up up here.
I don't know why let's go.
What happened today?
Cheap you're kidding.
These are laughable.
This coffee sells really well.
Let's get 200.
You're absolutely on something illegal.
I wonder how can you know, it's really funny.
I've had conversations with people in the past
and like, okay, let's be let's just truly just
take a second here and just talk about this.
I've had people in the past actually tell me.
Yeah, dude, like I thought like maybe at some
point maybe you were on drugs at some point.
I'm just like really you actually fucking thought
that like yeah, I like figured maybe you could
have been I'm like no.
I've not at all like get out of here.
I've had that asked before like dude.
Like be honest though.
Like you like you've dabbled a little while on
stream.
No, absolutely not at zero.
Never in my life in my whole life.
Like that's okay.
And it's almost like more bizarre to them.
But that's the case.
Like wait.
All right, man.
No, but you have though, right?
Like I you can tell me we're like clothes.
No, he's just fucked up.
I'm not even fucked up.
I'm just like I'm just uppity today ADHD prior.
That's what it is.
Yeah, that's yeah, of course uppity equals high.
All right.
Let's play the game.
That's a bad excuse.
I'm not even making an excuse.
I'm just having fun, man.
Okay, so I have enough coffee.
Let's go to Australia because I know there's
no this note.
I have a feeling that I can go to Kona and sell
this incredible coffee.
It's a big trip.
I'm willing to take it.
Let's go.
I have ADHD.
I'm not a weirdo.
Wow.
Why do you have to be a weirdo?
If you have ADHD we're talking about.
Oh silly zonka wonka.
I have heard from Alexandra.
She needs to speak with you right away.
She will wait for you at the Hotel de Cuba.
Please go see her.
All right, cool.
Somebody I have 110 cases.
I'll take two grand for this.
So expensive.
I'm almost out of raspberries.
You have raspberries?
Damn it.
What a waste of a trip.
I hate that.
I hate it.
I should have sold it.
I need a rock.
Okay, let's do Arabian bold.
I have this Kona coffee.
Moroccan coffee.
Okay, I've used them almost all my Cuban coffee.
Who would buy?
Maybe if I go to Cuba, will they like that?
I'm just gonna go to Cuba.
Cuban coffee in Cuba.
Have you not been to Cuba?
Have you not met Gina Famosa?
Have you not made me my cafe con leche?
This is the person that we owe like 40 cases of coffee to.
What happened to all your limes?
I still have 880.
All right, come on.
Old Havana, Hotel de Cuba.
Here she is.
Silly zonka wonka.
I could not be more pleased with your progress.
My search is proceeding.
Pace?
I fear that we are dealing with some pretty shady characters.
Do be careful about who you decide to trust.
But Link, hold on.
Just hold on, hold on, hold on.
In any event, my travels have taken me to Bali, Indonesia.
Sean and I spent quite a bit of time in Indonesia, you know.
And you, too, will now be able to visit this port.
Find Kintamani Plantation.
The owner is a fan of quality confections.
Be sure to see him when you're able to make the trip.
Cool, new area.
All right, hold on.
I have to do this because I can't...
Blinks have to be really worth it, by the way,
because alt-tabbing is horrible.
The sign's gone too far.
All right, it is pretty dusty in here.
Now, you know what this looks like?
This looks like you put, like, an old filter on Instagram.
You put film grain on this as an Instagram filter.
Is this image real or fake?
93% fail this quiz.
Would you?
It is, it is speckles.
You get too...
Okay, I have to be really honest with you.
If you get too close with anything, it looks like this.
Ever seen what one of your skin cells looks like under a microscope?
This is flash camera.
Like, you have any idea what you look like right now?
You understand how many dust mites are all over your body?
Same exact deal.
It's a flash camera that I took a picture of this.
Right now, there are billions of just, like, bugs eating skin cells on your body.
I know I just freaked you all out, but go look it up.
What do you look like under a fucking microscope, I wonder?
There are dust mites all over us.
Yeah.
I cannot do any more alt tabs.
No more alt tabbing.
This game is like 15 years old.
Irma has an attitude tonight.
What? No, I don't.
What are you talking about?
Okay, come on.
I'll take it.
I have 142 cases.
This is 21.
This is the best price I've seen so far.
Let's see if I can get a little more.
Are you here to do some business?
You must do something for me here.
I'll be taking my wares elsewhere.
What are you trying to do here?
Rip me off?
That's so much money.
I can't blow this.
This is breakeven pricing.
What are you talking about?
I got this is $300,000.
I'll be at more than half a million dollars.
Done.
I need that.
The price is going to keep dropping.
I flooded the market.
We're not going to see $5,000.
Cuban claw cleaner ever again.
Come on.
Honey, honey.
125k.
Let's go.
$125,000.
I'm almost at a million.
I'll get there.
We're taking this out of circulation.
I'm going to change my coffee to something else.
We're going to take this out of circulation too.
Let's go back to coffee town.
Cape Town.
Change the coffee.
All right, change the recipe.
Coffee.
What do we got?
I could do special blend.
I have enough.
I have enough to make.
I'm going to run out of Cuban coffee.
The person we need Arabian bold.
We need 40 stacks of Arabian bold for one of the quests.
Well, this game is about chocolate.
It's about chocolate, coffee, lattes, and all kinds of other stuff.
Raid?
What raid?
I don't see a raid.
Oh, it's because the thing's fucked up.
Hold on.
I got to connect these.
I want a huge one.
Nope, not yet.
Look at how big this is going to be.
Oh, I missed.
It's okay.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
I hate its weird lag.
It's almost like I shouldn't be using a mouse to do this.
It's weird.
It's really weird.
With 30 cases in that a week.
Raid, raid.
I don't see anybody.
Okay, we got that.
We have 30 of them.
Need to bring 40.
Let me just check a few things here.
That's a good price.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Is it going to get me?
$23,000.
Nice.
Because I'm taking these out of circulation.
Obama raid?
What are you talking about?
What are you guys doing?
All right, we have to go.
Welcome.
I'm now stocking whipped cream.
It can be kind of pricey, but I recommend you pick some up.
$64 for whipped cream?
That seems kind of like a lot.
I'm going to get some.
I can top that.
I can put that on top of stuff.
Buy like $10,000.
Should I buy more than...
I'll buy...
No, no, no.
It'll go bad.
I won't even use it.
I'll buy $200.
Anything else worth picking up while I'm here?
I'm going to do enough raspberries.
I'm going to buy 17 raspberries.
Because I want at least one week of production here while I go back to Zurich.
Thank you.
And that's it.
Because I'm going to change this.
I got the 40 cases.
Have you not been to Cuba?
Have you not met Gina Famosa?
Have you not made my cafe con leche?
I have not.
I have not made it yet.
I'm making something else.
Good price.
Change that recipe.
All right.
What do I need to do?
Anybody have anything for me to do?
Caribbean bold.
Cafe con leche.
All right.
I need...
What should I make them?
What do I have?
All right.
I have the Sprite Sponge Bar, but I have no lemons.
I have 880 fucking limes.
What a waste.
What an absolute waste.
These are going to all go bad.
I guess I could just not make chocolate.
All right.
Cafe con leche.
I need Cuban coffee.
I'm about to burn through all my Cuban coffee.
This factory is not equipped to make this type of product.
Oh.
To make this product, we'll need to equip the factory to make coffee.
It'll cost $250,000.
You want to purchase the machinery.
That's a lot of money.
Maybe over the...
Coffee is...
No.
Not worth it.
How many oranges do I have?
188.
Mint.
Honey.
I can make these.
Yeah, let's make this.
We're going to go for a lot.
Honey, people love chocolate and honey.
Shit.
I missed.
Come on, come on, come on.
Give me something.
Better than that, please.
Oh my God.
This is terrible.
Got it.
Nice.
Full stack.
Give me a full stack.
Stop screaming.
What are you yelling at?
Give me a full stack.
Jesus.
He's going to make it faster.
I got to concentrate.
Okay, that's fine.
Oh, give me a full stack.
Okay.
Now we're going to change the recipe again because that's all I can't make anymore.
And we're going to make it something.
We do oranges.
Make.
Oh, it's not.
I can do better than 19 a week.
Can I?
I could get that to like 25.
Can't I?
Make lime chocolate.
Back it up.
Come on.
I need a stack, please.
Shit, I missed.
Give me more nuts.
Come on.
That's good.
That's better than 20.
That's better than 19.
That's 24.
There we go.
All right.
Now let that just run.
Well, I'm going to make a ton of orange chocolate.
I have enough for six weeks.
I need more Moroccan coffee.
We need Moroccan coffee and I need to go hand this in to Tangier.
All right, let's go.
You're ignoring chat.
Yeah, because like all it is is just people saying like Obama raid.
What do you want me to pull out from here?
You want me to just stare at the chat while I just say Obama raid, Obama raid.
Look, it's Obama.
Obama's here.
Obama raid.
What kind of what am I pulling from the chat that I'm not seeing?
That I didn't see eight minutes ago.
Oh, hold on.
Good to see you back in Tangier, silly zonkawonka.
Listen, there will be some mighty fine cinnamon available here soon.
Now that's an ingredient used in loads of delicious coffee recipes.
In fact, I've got one such recipe for you here.
I give it to you now.
Will you be willing to do something for me?
Yep, cinnamon, cinnamon coffee.
People go nuts over this shit.
It's gonna make a regular coffee with a regular like just Folger's coffee beans
and then just tap two things of cinnamon on top of it and sell it for nine bucks.
Oh, wow.
Cinnamon coffee.
Yep, that'll be nine dollars.
60 cases.
No, they're not smelling.
No, it's not sniffing it.
They're not going.
I mean, they could be.
I'm sure that some people that buy coffee do that.
Swell brings 60 cases of chocolate with caramel here in town.
Oh, okay.
So I have to make 60 cases of caramel chocolate to get to unlock cinnamon.
Okay.
That's a lot.
It is here.
I delivered my 40.
Ooh, another recipe.
Coffee mint, coffee with mint, Colombian coffee, Moroccan coffee and mint.
I don't have any mint.
So whatever.
I think we should explore entering into a partnership for this shop.
It would be many benefits for you.
For starters, I'd always offer you the highest prices for your wares.
More importantly, I'd be able to start taking special orders on your behalf.
Really?
Special orders work like this.
I'll accept orders on your behalf and then send you a telegram with the details of each order as I receive them.
You can decide whether or not to accept each order, but I assure you special orders command the highest profit margins you will ever see.
I will incur some startup costs to get the special order system up and running.
If you're willing to share these costs by bringing me some products,
we'll be square and I'll be ready to enter into the partnership we discussed.
Deal?
Deal.
Splendid!
While I don't carry chocolates in my shop, I love them all the same.
First, bring me 100 cases of special reserve 66% African cocoa.
Holy shit.
This goes for a lot.
Oh wait, we're in a partnership, aren't we?
Oh, not yet.
I need, um...
I need Moroccan coffee.
Yes, it's true.
I'm expecting a new spice soon and I'd be happy to offer you for sale.
As soon as you show up with 60 cases of chocolate with caramel.
I need, um...
I need more coffee.
I need more, um, Moroccan coffee.
Okay.
That's a lot.
Yes!
Good deal.
So I need a lot of Moroccan coffee.
Let's do 200.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's fine.
I'll make it back.
Can we get a battery cam?
No.
No, you can't.
No, there will be no battery cam.
All right.
This is going to keep producing.
I'm going to go.
I need it.
I'm going to go make a reserve recipe.
Hold on.
This is...
...Dualan cocoa...
...and sugar.
I have a ton...
I was prepared.
Remember I bought this at a discount and everyone said,
Jerma, don't buy that.
What are you buying that for?
I bought it at a discount.
I haggled with the guy.
Now I have a shitload of it.
I need a hundred of these.
Let's go back to Zurich.
Good price.
That's a good price.
That's a good price too.
72 cases of this shit.
Nice.
I'm holding onto this.
This is going to be...
I'm going to make so much money on this.
This would be, uh...
This would be like 50 times what I put in.
All right.
I need to make the...
...this one here.
26 cases per week.
I don't need to do the thing.
That's good enough.
We want to see the battery.
No.
You don't need to see the battery.
All right.
Should I...
Do I have space to do?
No, I don't have any room.
Why can I delete these?
These are such junk.
I want to delete them.
Maybe I should just keep making this.
Open up a new factory.
What do I got for quest right now?
A new spice.
Okay.
I need 60 cases of the chocolate with caramel.
I'm doing this first.
Because I'm bringing 100 cases to this guy.
So then I get a partnership with this guy.
And then I can sell this Arabian Bold...
...for the maximum profit to this guy.
Oh shit.
I forgot.
I need 24 cases of cafe con leche.
Shit.
I keep blowing that lady off.
Okay.
How much...
What does it take?
Cuban...
I need more Cuban coffee.
It's Cuban coffee, milk, and sugar.
All right.
Let's go to Cuba.
I don't have it yet.
Oh, wait.
Silly zonka wonka.
I understand whipped cream has recently become available.
I have a recipe here that uses that very ingredient.
Coffee with whipped cream.
What a recipe.
Wow.
Coffee with whipped cream on top?
What's the secret?
What are you holding back from us?
Holy smokes.
What do I need to get the secret from you?
If you'd be willing to take 28 cases to...
...Nino Brager in Zurich...
...he will pay you well for the goods.
Sure.
Oh, boy.
The secret recipe.
It's brew a coffee...
...and then hold the can upside down and go...
...only your great-great-great-grandmother knew that.
So expensive.
Although this is actually on the low end.
Last seen in...
Okay.
The last time I was here, this is $515 a stack.
Do I dare try to come down?
I mean, this is on the low end.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's already so good.
Here we go.
All right.
That was $100,000.
$100,000.
There's $520 grand in here.
There's a hundred fucking thousand dollars on the line.
Just do not...
There's three Whammies here.
Don't click a Whammy.
All right.
Okay, we're almost...
I'm up.
One more.
I'm done.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Oh, hell yeah.
That felt good.
I haven't really used any Allspice.
Let us choose.
It's gonna be really hard to do.
I would...
I really want to do that, but like alt-tabbing and turning on the extension and getting it to be in the right spot might be hard.
We'll see.
Maybe I'll do it later.
Thank you, James, for the ten community...
Oh, sorry.
Thank you, James, for the ten community subs.
Thanks a lot.
Ten fucking subs.
Thanks you.
I thanks you.
He hates us.
No, I don't.
I just hate alt-tabbing.
No, don't sell.
All right.
I have to bring $100,000 using whipped cream.
Yeah, this guy just...
Don't you feel like you want to go visit this guy and just pull him aside and be like,
Nino, just buy the whipped cream and just put it on top of your coffee.
You don't need me to do this for you.
I don't...
You don't have...
I don't have to do this part for you.
All right.
So let's do...
We're looking for $100,000, which we have $26,000.
It's gonna take a few weeks.
I need to just...
I'm gonna just travel around and get ingredients.
What am I low on?
I'm about to sneeze again.
I didn't even sneeze once today.
Why am I saying again?
What about the lady?
You got her killed.
Somebody came in here and like killed me and muted the microphone right by...
How?
I would probably have made more noise than that.
A dagger thrown into me?
Yeah, but wouldn't...
Okay, if a dagger was thrown across the room, like into my neck, I wouldn't be...
I would be like...
Wouldn't I?
It was a laser weapon.
Yeah, it was like a vaporizing ray.
I look over, I see this big green alien with like a big like Mars attacks head.
He just goes like...
I see him and I see the beam.
That's all you get.
I got discombobulated.
Okay.
Oh, I can go here.
I don't have to bring something here though.
All right.
This is a new area I got and I have $600,000.
Island Temple.
Oh shit.
She's following me around.
She's getting on the same planes as me now.
Just loading her bags in the overhead.
Oh, hey, have you been to Cuba?
Have you met China Famosa?
Oh, yeah.
By the way, I'm in 24C.
Have you made my cafe con leche yet, motherfucker?
She's following me around.
The shadow market?
What did that say?
Click on ingredient.
Allspice is gonna be real cheaper.
I know it.
Sweets.
I can't sell.
Hold on.
Welcome to Indonesia.
Will we cultivate some of the world's finest specialty ingredients?
Your reputation precedes you.
Silly zonko wanka.
I've heard tell of some of your creations.
Tart of the Moon and Sprite Sponge.
If you were to bring me just 10 cases of each of those delights,
I will not only make our wonderful cacao and coffee beans available to you,
I'd also hand over a couple of recipes that take advantage of the same.
What say you?
Um,
No, he's heard of some of the creations,
but he doesn't know how they taste.
Word has not
gotten
here.
Of how bad they are.
So,
I'm going to,
hopefully,
over the next few weeks,
bring you these things, get your recipes before you take a bite.
Please make the con leche.
I know, I have to, I've,
I've got to do this first.
I will, that sounds good.
So I just have to bring 10 cases of Tart of the Moon and Sprite Sponge
to Santoso
Devi in Bali.
Okay,
Tart of the Moon.
Oh, I can't do anything here until I bring this guy
my specialty treats.
All right, I'll get you your cafe con leche.
I promise.
All right, back to,
all right, is that
78,
88, 90, okay, yeah.
Here we go.
We're going back
to this guy.
We have to go to Tangiers.
It's time.
What a scrumptious cake.
Is that what it was?
Holy shit, you just like triggered a memory.
I think it was SpongeBob was doing like a scrumptious cake
Neelix bit
on TBS
in Star Trek.
I think that's what it was.
You just like triggered it.
I think that's actually what happened.
He was like, Patrick,
I just made the most scrumptious cake.
Ah, I actually think that's what happened.
All right, here we go.
Just about got everything in order.
All you need to do is bring me the hundred cases of mocha
and hundred, what?
I have to bring you a hundred cases of mocha
and a hundred cases of Sprite Sponge?
You fucker.
Well, I need to get rid of this stuff.
He's got 25 community subs from Nuclear Waffle.
That's a huge subs.
Thank you.
Thank you for the absolutely gigantic subs.
Huge community subs.
Okay.
So what is it?
What is let me see Sprite.
What does it need to make Sprite Sponge?
I don't stock this.
I don't.
Oh, they're going bad.
A hundred and eighty have gone bad in the last couple of weeks.
We have to get rid of these.
I need lemons.
I don't want you to put these in stock though.
No one likes this.
You're a zero factor.
I don't.
Okay.
So we have to get lemons.
I have plenty of milk.
Obviously plenty of limes.
And now I need a hundred lemons.
Mocha is
I need Kona coffee.
I need a bunch more milk.
God damn it.
Why would I put milk in this recipe?
Now?
I need to have like 200 more milk.
Milk Kona coffee.
Lemons Milk Kona coffee.
Lemons milk.
Kona coffee lemons milk Kona coffee.
Lemons milk Kona coffee.
Lemons...
No, all right. I just said that for like a
16 hour flight in a row would not want to be sitting next to that person milk cone of coffee
I need a shitload of this
Don't you think like at some point through that flight you turn to that person and go?
Open up your fucking iPhone and open up the notepad and write them down
Just give me your phone number. I will write them down and I'll text you in a six hours after we land
Okay, I I'm gonna do honey. I you know, I always need coffee. We're doing 200. All right, but what milk I could sell this
CEO of big coffee company flying coach wrong that subs of web didn't miss subs
We had 10 from Admiral Green. Thanks for the 10 subs. It was with a large ones and I missed along
I missed huge subs. Well, I did it's 15 community subs from James Morris
50 from nuclear waffle. I only saw the first one. No James Morris gave like
55 community subs blackout gave 30 what's going on here? Holy shit. Thank you guys
That's a lot of subs 10 more from James is on completely unnecessary. I was this is insane. It was coming from there's a lot
This is hundreds of subs. All right, let's go. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Well, you're good mutity subs. We have another 10 from chef Lazarus. That's 10 community subs
Hey Jay jubber, thanks for the 10. No, it's five that get mutity subs. Hey, I'm sorry
I'm making this like a joke
Bully him. What do you mean bully him? Oh, thanks guys. Seriously slow mode isn't very slow. Um, no, not really
I mean, there's a lot of people here. All right. I need a shitload of milk. This is cheap
This is a good price for it. I need like 200 milk more than that. I think I need like 300 milk
I have Kona coffee. What was it? I I set it on the airplane for six hours Kona coffee milk. I forget it
I forget the last one. What was it lemons? That's right. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I
Actually forgot them. Thanks to the 10 subs st. Velez. Thank you for 10 community subs
All right. Can I do anything else here? I could sell these here. Yeah
Alright now we're gonna go back to Zurich get the lemons and then we're gonna change the coffee
I'm gonna go to K. I should have gone to Cape Town first. All right, I need lemons
Okay, of course your prices went up. I need a hundred lemons. I'll just get 150
There we go. All right. I am now able to make or okay. I can make I can make a hundred. Oh
Hurry up and make them hurry up and make them there like the 500 went bad. I gotta make them now
I have to I can do better than that. Come on second stack in a row. Good start stack in a row. Good
That's pretty good. That's really good. That's my I think the highest I've ever had 29 cases a week
I've
Please don't have my lemons
Rot to the point where I can't even make a hundred best game or moment 2021
I missed I'm too many the minigames too stressful it I know it is kind of stressful
You only have to do it once per batch. So if you really don't care
Lemons can rot and lemons go bad in real life. Yeah, they can eat a rotten lime on stream
Why do I have this weird thing in my brain that lemons have this self
sustainable internal
Like it they like back to like a lemon juice is so sour and so acidic
Like it cannot go bad because it kills all the bacteria and germs in the middle
Why do I have this weird thing that as long as the skins on they have like a whole ecosystem where they can be?
Like clean in there. I know that's not true. But why do I think it could be?
immortal lemons
Because you're dumb. No, it was it's just a little thought project. I know that lemons go bad
I'm just saying like I why is it my mind a lemon is like this ecosystem that is
Immutable, you know, it's kind of like blockchain technology. You've heard of that yet because you're two feet tall pan that person for at least an hour
What's that have to do with anything? All right, I'm gonna
Please have my limes not go bad. All right coffee coffee coffee coffee. We're gonna mocha. Do I have enough for mocha?
I have so many coffee beans. No cocoa beans. All right, we are ready to make
Mocha at the coffee factory down in Cape Town already almost had a lemon. Okay, let's go change a recipe
Mocha use this recipe 32 a week. That's fine. Look at how much of this I have
359 Arabian bold cases, but that's not single coffees. That's stacks of this those cases
How many coffees are in a case? I have no idea trying not to burp on camera. This is like
3500 coffee. Oh black tea is going bad too. Great
Whipped cream I need to get that secret whipped cream recipe. What about the cafe con leche? I'm that's not
That's not a precedent right now. That's the wrong word. Okay, I got that going. Let's head back to
Need a hundred sprite sponges. Wait, doesn't somebody else want sprite sponges too? Oh tar the moon, right?
This is what this is the most important one is something else I can do
I'm trying to find cheap
I could use more. Oh, I could use my dwelling cocoa or I have I don't have any Cuban coffee
Let's go to Havana. No links tonight. Nope, not right now. Holy shit. Holy shit. Holy shit. Holy shit. That's $400,000
Oh my god, that's 400 grand. Holy shit. I must get a million dollars
Wow. Oh, wow. Okay. Don't I'm never gambling ever again in the game because that's like half a million dollars almost
It's a lot of coffee. Why is tea so expensive? Listen friend. I just harvested it. Oh
Like I just walked into the store and bumped my elbow on the like the side opening the door to the shop
It's the dagger the reaction instead of being like
No, no, no, it's how
Then I'm dead. Listen friend. I just harvested a bumper crop of coffee beans here
There's not a whole lot I can do on the price, but I'd be willing to trade
5,000 sacks of
Cuban coffee for 75 cases of special blend. Are you kidding me? That's five
Okay, hold on. It's like 300 to 400 bucks a sack. I need to do some calculation here. It's like
$340 a sec to 340 times 5,000
That's one point seven million dollars of product for just 75 cases of special blend
How much does it cost to make special blend? Isn't special blend just all three of them? Holy shit. That's incredible
Why would you be giving this to me? That's four hundred times. This is two million dollars in inventory. Why would I buy this? No
Excuse me. No, I'm not gonna buy any of that from you. Amen
Please talk about the donkachino al donkachino the king of the coffee
Oh, wait, are you referring to isn't gonna get a ton of minus twos and a bunch of people gonna be cringing over this
I know a donk a donk a donk a donk a donk a donkachino a donk a donk a donk a donk a donk a donk
I don't care. That's the only part of the movie that I even watched. All right, 75 cases special blend
I came here to get coffee and I have I'll come back later for it. Are we doing on inventory?
All right. I'm almost at the sprite sponge, which I probably should go
Alright, I'm gonna go to Zurich and I change this to tar to the moon. No, not yet. How many does he want 10?
Let's go to Zurich. Anyways, that was Bernie
I like to call a meeting I would like five minutes of time. The senator from Vermont is being recognized for five minutes
I just have to say that the donkachino from Dunkin Donuts is the best coffee that I've ever had
Is that all from the senator of Vermont? No, of course not. Fuck all you everybody here
You all fucked this whole thing up over the last like 25 years or a bunch of fucking idiots
Okay, that the senator's time is up. Okay, you tell him birdie. You're based Andy. Oh
What that's political streamer is it and by the way, he's waving around
Extra-large dunk a donkachino the ones that aren't even on the menu the ones you have to actually order special and it's spilling
Oh, this whole thing got all messed up. Let me tell you why we have
We've got banks that are just the rates. We gotta chase the rates of the banks break them up
We have to do hold on let me put this stuff
I'm getting really heated you guys have a drink an extra large coffee before I have they're fucking huge
there's too much have you guys ever gone to Sonic and
Gotten one of the large Sonic drinks and then imagine you get one of those huge Sonic drinks
But it's coffee in there. I've gotten that before you ever order a Trenta from Starbucks
And then you kind of are in the line of the Starbucks you get the Trenta
And then you like turn around and you're the guy with like the comedy fucking sized thing like
From 7-eleven in your hands
Everyone's getting like smalls and regulars. You know, just like yeah, I just got my huge one
Hey, and you almost feel like you have to be like, oh, hey, it's gonna be a long night. No, it's not
That's just a regular coffee for you. People go. Oh, yeah, it's gonna be a long night
Okay, you must be up all night doing some work for some reason. You always have to be like tell everybody. Oh
Huge huge fucking drink. It's gonna be a long night. This is not normal for me and it's gone in 15 minutes
That was a family guy joke. I don't care
That was a mad TV coffee guy joke minus two
Mad TV coffee guy joke you're assuming I watched every episode of mad TV
Although there is there's a part in that the the I've never seen a clip of a guy getting hit right in what's it?
Will will Sasso getting hit directly in the face of the huge tree branch and I remember thinking it was funny
somebody like throws a tree branch at will Sasso dressed up and it hits him like directly in his face and
It's not like they don't cut it literally hits him directly in his face like right in his mouth. You're a sadist. What?
Kenny, it's a jackass thing. I
May think I don't even remember
Lemons are spoiling. They've no they're not they're fine. Oh, okay
What'd I say? I want to get to one
I want to get to a million a family guy the quest for stuff on stream you coward
No, this guy's got this guy scares me didn't we think this guy was a scammer and he just keeps saying the same thing
All right. I how many do I have I have enough? I need to change this to Tartar the moon, which is also lemons
I need ten of these so I'm just gonna check I'm gonna make the chocolate
I'll have enough do a giving birth live stream. There's any like youtuber tried to do that yet
With like a beginning of the video
There's like a referral link or like a hey tell me in the comments like what do you think we should name the kid or
Something like a seven minute intro to like a giving birth video. How do I feel like that might be a thing shit?
I missed I only need ten of these anyways. That doesn't matter. All you have to do is look and you will find what you seek
Like the guru on the top of the mountain
The little the YouTube guru just type into the Google search bar what you seek you will find it
Log cutting videos ASMR to Elsa eats whole plate of spaghetti
I don't know why they exist, but they do
Everything is there. I think that's enough right? I need a 1010
So let's go 75 case of special blend
Alright, god damn it. I need one more week. So I'm gonna go to Cape Cape town
I'm gonna change it to special blend. Do I have enough coffee to do that though? I definitely don't what a special blend take
Okay, special blend is just all of them. I need 75. So I have to get 100 Moroccan coffee 50 Kona coffee
I have enough Cuban so we need Moroccan and Kona. Okay. Let's go to Tangiers
Remember should I go do the dishes?
That's a bloated question. It depends. Is it your turn to do the dishes? Do you live with more than one person?
Have you not done the dishes in like two weeks and other people in the house have and you are supposed to do them now
Absolutely, or have you done them pretty much every time for the last week and no one's done them
No, it's not your turn you live alone
And if you say yes to living alone, how high are they are they over the lip of the sink?
If the answer is no, you're good for another couple days if the answer is yes get on that. What are you doing?
All right, we need to what is it? What are we bringing out with the caramel, right? We go
Alright most excellent. I'll take these products and it's my pleasure. Let you know that the shop is now yours
Not only will I always offer you great prices for your coffee products, but we are all set to start receiving special orders
From time to time. I'll send you a telegram
With the terms of the special order
If you accept it
It'll be up to you to deliver the specified number of cases of each product of the current person
The correct person in place within the oh number of weeks this time limit. I'm confident that filling these orders are cool
Do it bring to the next level. Here we go
Here's the big ticket sale. I get the most amount for this. Can I haggle with them? This is them. Oh, wow
Okay, it's the free
159 cases that is we're now one we're over a million dollars now
1.4 million we made it we did it we did it over a million
I told you I want to do it by today now, let's go for 10 million end of the stream. What we're just getting started, dude
Okay, I need coffee. We need Moroccan coffee
That's expensive. I need it though
Have to spend it. I got money. I'm good
Okay, now I need kona coffee kona coffee is where's kona kona coffee from uh in kona
Right. Oh shit. She's there. She's again
what's this
Silly wonka zonka. You really need to speak with uh, uh fine goods in kona. She's got an offer
Wait, who's gonna give me the 5 000 cases? Oh cuban coffee
That's a good price for it. I'll take 200
All right
The only thing left is now
I've got 100 Moroccan
240 cuban
200 kona
I'm ready to make the 75 special blend to get the 5 000 cases of cuban coffee in there. What else was I doing here?
Okay, i'm gonna get this out. I'm gonna do this now
I don't have to make any chocolate, right? Oh, no, okay chocolate with caramel chocolate with caramel and cafe con leche
All right. We'll do the cafe con leche. Let's do let's let's get this out of the way
Oh fuck. I was supposed to talk to somebody. What's this?
western union telegram
western union
To silly zonka wonka from
Zachariah tangi location morocco fine coffees special order
20 cases chocolate bar with honey for earnest will pay 48 000 dollars required within 34 weeks
That's so much time. You may as well just say there is no time limit
That's oh, that's oh, that's more than half a year. They're willing to wait that. Okay. Yes. Sure
Change this to special blend. No cafe con leche
How much does she want have almost two-thirds of a year to do that order. They don't want it very timely
Where's the music go
Where's the music hurry hurry hurry hurry stupid cursor thing sucks. Oh my god. The cursor sucks
I'm trying you know what i'm trying to do. Oh my god. I hate this one. It's so sloppy. You have no idea
It's so sloppy. All right. How many do you want 24 cases? She will track you down
I have 85 cases of mocha. All right tarred the moon. Did I already turn these into this somebody?
Yeah, I did that one. She's gonna track me down. Oh, okay. Very very very we're gonna go to um
folly, but first take this off change this to uh
Special blend there it is. All right, we need a hundred of these 75 of these
Dun dun dun dun. I feel like the mask is gonna do something really funny right now with this song
And here here here here here we're here here we gotta make this a big one
It's going faster it's going faster faster. Oh faster
Oh
38 cases, holy shit
That's pretty great. Ooh
Silly zonka bonka. I most pleased is your progress. You've earned my complete trust as you're well in my I want you to be the
CEO of the company you go you're gonna go to tokyo soon. Oh
I have enough for
What's the quest?
75 cases I have I have enough all right now
I need we need to go to bali
Let me go to zurek first this i'm not this thing's i'm not producing anything. Oh wonderful
I knew I had picked the right person to introduce to my friends. Thank you for the cafe con leche
I'll be in touch again soon cream
It's by 60 cases of chocolate with caramel 20 cases of chocolate with honey
All right, the caramel one's probably what we should do now. All right chocolate caramel. I don't have any caramel
All right, I need
Caramel much care. I'm gonna get the exact amount
60 caramel not a bad price for it. I'll take it
Start production, please
Found you from your interview with this. Well, that's fake. I don't have to I don't have to read anymore
All right. Now let's go to uh
bali
turn in our
Specialty treats your confections are even more delightful than I was led to believe you are now welcome here anytime
I'm proud to offer you the finest cocoa and coffee beans in the world
As promised here are a couple of coffee recipes that utilize my beans. Okay, this is breakfast blend columbian
balinese and kona
Oh coffee with amaretto. Ooh
I need amaretto
Subtly sweet and superb. I would probably like that cinnamon coffee. Oh, I need cinnamon with cream. Whoa
Balinese cocoa balinese coffee. This is so expensive. That's so expensive
But you're a you're a millionaire. Yes. Okay. I am a millionaire, but if I buy 200 cases
I won't be a millionaire anymore. I'm not gonna be if I buy 200 cases. I'm not a millionaire anymore. Not true
Math no, no, no. No, I'm I'm buying 200. I have to i'm buying 200 of each
There's two things to buy here and they're both expensive. I have to buying a bunch of these two
Will I still be a millionaire? Oh, thank god. Thank god. Oh, thank god
Your factory's net worth is probably in the millions. Oh special blend is ready
All right
I gotta go back to the guy to sell the coffees
Who else do I need to bring stuff to 60 cases of caramel and then bring the special blend?
I have 75 cases just go to cuba anything else I can do here the temple spend the rest of your money on lemons
Just buy a million dollars worth of lemons just corner the entire lemon market
It would be the stupidest thing you'd ever do. Uh, I need to change. Let's change this recipe first
What do I want to make? Um, I could do the coffee and whipped cream. Oh, hold on. Hello again
I see you have acquired the recipe for coffee with amaretto
I've got over 100 sacks of amaretto here you could use would you be willing to complete an order for some of those products?
Yeah, sure. Here are 160 sacks of amaretto
Rufus loddington will be staying here in town at the longshore lodge for the next few months
If you can bring him 80 cases of coffee with amaretto before he leaves he'll pay for the products
Okay, I want to do this one. How much do I have to make? I need 28. I just need to make 28
Okay
Take the bag and run I own the establishment. That would be very bizarre
If the ceo had like product lined up meeting one of his employees and they said hey
We have a bunch of the truck just came in with 200 sacks of amaretto and I grabbed them and ran away
It'd be like, okay
Well, he's coming back because he owns this place fuck fuck fuck running away. It's like running away from your own house with it
Where are you gonna go? You don't have a plane? I need a hot dog hot dog hot dog
All right, there we go what I needed 28 almost got it exactly that order is done 28 at the bank in zurich now
We need 80 cases of coffee with amaretto. I got a lot of inventory. I gotta sell some stuff
I'm gonna go visit my brother Dieter in tokyo. He was not too wild about my coffee idea
But seeing the success you have with these products, I think he's come around. He's got a pretty nice factory over there
I believe he's also to manufacture infusions. Oh, yeah, all right, who wanted what amaretto use that recipe? Let's go for it
Hmm. All right, let's make more
Uh, I need to make a bunch of these. I need 80 cases. Oh shit. Come on. I gotta connect these. Come on
No
It sucks. I hate this thing. I'm trying to go so slow. Holy shit. That's really good
What did I get 37 38 39?
Holy jesus. I thought that was way worse than what I was doing. All right, I've got need those 80 cases
He's here. I gotta pee. Let's take a pee break. I'll be right back
See you in two minutes in fact for someone to say rtx on this is very detailed really good shit
Superstar streamer germa 985. I think he's gonna break your kneecaps. What? All right, let's keep going
Awesome artwork as always. We'll see one more
All right good shit as always let's go, okay
You've built like a camera tripod
Whatever. All right. I need how many I need to make
80 all right complete all tasks before november
With honey, okay. I got it. First of all, let me go to cuba
Let me go to cuba and get my 5000 sacks of cuban coffee
There we are. I'll take the special blend and hand over the beans. I'm glad this worked out so well
I can't imagine you need any more cuban coffee at this juncture, but it never hurts to review prices
You're right. Can I sell it back to you?
5000 cuban coffee beans
Oh, that's a lot
Oh, that's a lot too
All right. I need to go back to where's the guy where's my guy that takes all coffee
Look, just take these just take these gross things from me
Wait, did I do the thing and yeah, I did okay
I need to keep the caramel
I have 60
All coffee now is gonna get sold to the other guy
So now where is this?
Okay, whipped cream that's zurich and this is in
uh
Tangiers, okay tangers and then zurg. Let's go
Okay, make sure that you're continually introducing new coffees. Here we go. These chocolate bars of caramel are simply scrumptious
So they are scrumptious. Of course they are I made them
In exchange, I'd like to present you with 200 sacks of a wonderful spice cinnamon
Eppin you won't find finer cinnamon anywhere in the world. Be sure to come back. You need any more nice. Holy shit. That's good
200 that's 157 000 in inventory for free
I didn't do anything
Very nice. Welcome back to your shop. Silly zonka wonka. It is always a pleasure to see you again
All right, let me show you don't screw this up
80 so the coffee with amaretto off off tape. No, I can't sell it coffee whipped cream and amaretto off the table
Everything else is fair game
mocha fair game
That's a good good price
Sell it special blend
Sell it that's another big take. All right whipped cream and amaretto leave them alone
Why do you type the number when there's a giant sell all button you can use for each item?
It's a very good question
I'll tell you the reason why I do that is so I can see the number the actual number the actual amount of money
I will receive because if you hit sell all it does not tell you the number
It's nice to kind of have a visual of how much money it's going to be worth. I like to kind of see it
I don't like corporate germa. Yeah, he went off corporate
All right, uh, we have the we can go back to
We'll go to zirk first. We'll start some new chocolate
Make a chocolate called when the imposter is sus
All right, amaretto. All right. This guy
Was the whipped cream?
Coffee with whipped cream. Oh, what an incredible luxury. Here's
$45,000 for 28 cases also
If you find your way to tangers one day, I understand there's a new spice nutmeg
What a dope that's the guy running the bank this is in charge of our money that should scare you
Nobody else has a uh, I've said quiz. Nobody has a quiz for me here. Let's do
Um this special order 20 cases of chocolate bars with honey
Do I have enough honey?
Oh, I just buy one honey. Here we go
I'll i'll bang this out right now chocolate with hazelnut
Almonds with honey with honey. Here it is
All right, cool. Let's make it good stack. How did I miss that bullshit?
How did I do that?
Come on stack. What the fuck just happened? Give me the stack
Okay, don't do not fuck up. Whatever. You're the king of clicking your little mouse
Okay, this shit is pre-recorded dude. I know it
Spaghetti spaghetti tone spaghetti tony six six six at four
34 pm pacific time made a comment that said that what I just said. All right, you accepted a special order
Talk to earnest mimbo at casino national in havana. All right, let's go to havana and then we're gonna go to
um
Uh capetown havana capetown tokyo done change this what do I have in my inventory? Okay, I could do oranges
almonds hazelnut
peanuts
Caramel. All right. I got oranges use them
Havana, I can't believe you shat yourself on stream for 500 community subs
These chocolate bars of honey are perfect feeling lucky
Yeah
oranges oranges
Last one i'm done
Fuck how about a pick? No, we're done. I happen to have a couple of coffee recipes that use cuban coffee
The finest coffee in the world
I'll give you one now
If you agree to make and bring me 15 cases of the new recipe as well as 15 cases of a coffee with whipped cream
Okay
Coffee with nutmeg. Ooh, that's probably gonna be expensive
You want coffee with whipped cream? Don't I have some of that already?
Is that what i'm currently making? No, i'm making this i'm making way too much of this
All right. I'm going to capetown anyways
How much whipped cream do I have?
I got plenty. All right. Yeah, let's go
Whipped cream use that one 33 a week
Sure
Oh almost out of coffee
How much uh, how much do I have?
Uh, oh, I need to go to I need to go to kona to get coffee. Here we go
Here's a fifty thousand dollars for the coffee with amaretto
Thank you
Doi boat
I can't do it
Uh, I was just making these to make them. That's a good price
17 351 i'll take it
Okay
now
We go to Tokyo
Not yet
Not yet. I need to go to kona
Is it grandma game? This is a pretty damn fun grandma game. I don't care grandma games can be fun. Are you kidding me?
You are a grandma fine
Hans silly silly wonka
Zachariah tangi is a friend of mine and I understand that things are going quite well with you in the shop in morocco
I too am interested in forming a partnership
Ooh, are you willing to fulfill some orders for me in exchange for my signing over this shop? Yep
Take 120 cases of your tart of the moon to zach. He really enjoyed those
One guy that's ordering these
a one guy on the app store
That really likes my iphone game
Everybody else hates it, but he's keeping me in business
120 cases. Well, I have to get that ready
God damn it. What do I need?
Tart of the moon is so such a pain in the ass. Is it? No, no, no, it's lemons
Okay, I need
125 lemons
fucking lemons
Okay, let's go. I'll take lemons, please. I need 125 of them
Change this to tart of the moon
What I just buy
This just looks like a lemon
It looks like a lemon I I just clicked it and said go whatever
It's cheap. I got 80. I got 860 000. Who cares?
At that i'm making tart of the moons
I can do better than 21 though. I seriously can that's
Okay, come on
Stop lagging. Stop lagging
Holy shit. Oh my god
too fast
Way too fast and laggy
Way too fast and laggy, but I got it
29 cases a week. That's good. I have 29. He won 120 or something. Okay. I got these chocolate bars with orange
You'll get you'll take these for a lot
Oh, yeah, if those somebody wants these somebody wants. Oh, right, right, right
Okay
Coffee with nutmeg is next
We're going down to capetown coffee with nutmeg
and then we're going to
Go to cuba and then have 120 cases tart of the moon in
Morocco. All right. Hi jerma. What are you doing?
What? Hi. Hi
Hi, why am I saying bye?
All right. Hi. Bye. Hi. All right 120 cases tart of the moon will be there by the time we get to
Morocco in the meantime, we're doing nutmeg. We're doing 15 cases of coffee with nutmeg and then going to cuba
Where's nutmeg who sells nutmeg?
I have not priced this ingredient yet. Who has it in morocco? All right, we're going to morocco
Where the hell where's morocco? That's not morocco, but I want to go here
I can't blame alex
I would probably be doing the same thing myself if I were in her situation
But does she really think she's going to be able to find her husband? It's been quite some time
Hello partner of my friend leo aloha at kona mentioned that she had entrusted an order with you
Do you know what she was speaking about?
I I have no idea
But I got a lot of amaretto coffee for you
Okay, 15 cases of coffee with whipped cream
120 cases of uh, okay, so I just need coffee with nutmeg who sells nutmeg
You do 1500 a piece
What heart of the moon is still being made
Haggle haggle. I I know it's gonna get higher
Okay, so I have this I can sell five of these
I got 15 of these. I want to wipe out my coffee inventory. I had a lot of it
Okay. Now we're gonna be off to
We need to go to havana
after
We go and change this over in
uh
cave time l2 to parry
Okay, change this recipe to
Coffee with nutmeg. Fuck. I need moroccan coffee
Uh, okay. Where's moroccan coffee?
Where's moroccan coffee morocco?
It's in morocco
It's in fucking morocco. Yeah, I know but I where's morocco
Morocco is in north africa. Wasn't I just there? Oh, I was yeah. Okay
I don't know. I thought this was a peanut
I don't know why I just thought it was a peanut
I got so hell bent on getting this. I thought this was a peanut. All right
We're gonna haggle
Uh, what are you trying to do here rip me off?
All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Okay coffee with nutmeg
That's gonna be done
Moroccan coffee cuban coffee and nutmeg. I'm actually gonna get more nutmeg
Yeah
I want to make this for a little while. This is gonna be very very it's a very this has been an expense
But i'm gonna make a ton of this stuff and i'm gonna sell it for a shitload
He flew across africa twice
Whatever. All right. Now we're gonna go make the coffee. I'm going up and down
Change recipe coffee with nutmeg
Use this recipe. Let's go. I'm gonna make like 100 200 of these not a millionaire anymore. Oh, I hate it
What the fuck was wrong with that? Oh my god, it sucks
No
It's so painful to do this
You have no idea. You don't know what it's like. You don't know what it's like to be to do what i'm doing right now
It's so painful
Whatever. I hate that thing
Have you used the arrow keys i'll try you know i'm gonna you know what yeah, I can do better than that
Arrow keys, let's try it stop doing two by two
Pretty good. Oh my god. Stop. Come on. Is that 29 30? That's much better. I'm more happy with that
All right. I need some more nutmeg
I got 52 coffee with nutmeg. What does that go for?
a lot an absolute
Metric shitload
But i'm gonna make a hell a lot of these
Make sure I have enough
Uh, what do I need? I need more nutmeg and I need more
Um moroccan coffee. I have enough nutmeg
To make another 63 of these. All right
And I drink you
What in hell are you talking? What in the god's green earth are you talking about?
All right, I have the tower of the moon coffee with whipped cream
You can sell that. I don't need this anymore. I need 15 of these
47 minus 15 is 47. This is diana. It's 47. This is
36 35 34 33 32
Hold on to these
That'll be good for a little I need some more nutmeg
All right. It's time
To go to havana. Where's this hawaii? All right, we're going to havana and then we're going to hawaii
Wait 20 cases chocolate with peanuts
30 000
No, get out of here. Let's do it
Wonderful. I'll grab my 30 cases and here silly zonka wonka is the second recipe I promised an irish coffee
Perfect way to unwind cuban coffee cream and then I just need whiskey. I have cube. I have cuban coffee
For years I could just have the place make this for years. I just need to get whiskey
All right 120 cases of tart of the moon to uh,
Hawaii get out of here. I'm the king of the boxes. I'm the king of the fucking boxes do it again
No, I just made like 110 000. Why would I do that again?
All right. Now i'm gonna go to
Yes, wait, do you have nutmeg you don't
Here we go
Wait, what's going on?
Why did I need to come here? I thought I had to come what what there was a reason why I wanted to come here
For coffee, right?
Why did I wanted to come here for a reason?
I think it was to buy coffee
It was okay. I'm not out of my mind previous 12 to 74 dollars. Can you come lower than that?
Please give me a break
All right. I'm gonna buy a shitload of cream while it's low
Let's buy 500 cream
Oh, it's cheap
Gonna go bad
No, it's not
Okay, here we go. I'm delightful. I'm pleased to know that you are working together. Believe me
She will make another great partner for you. Go back to hawaii and meet with her
What?
Holy shit. It has a lot of money. Hold on
I knew yeah, I would talk I was supposed to go there
All right, let's dump this
100 cases
That feels good. That feels really good to sell at that amount of money
450 1000 dollars
Just dumped Moroccan coffee. We could use a little more
nutmeg as well
It sells for a lot. I'm just gonna let it produce
You're gonna people think I'm fucking crazy for this
People are gonna be like holy shit, dude. You are insane. Am I though?
Because this is just gonna produce
For the next like three or four weeks and i'm gonna be able to sell it for like a million dollars
This would be my first one million dollar drop
A million dollar drop over here at the Moroccan coffee shop
guaranteed
See in like two weeks when I do that
Uh, this chocolate needs to change. This is horrible
But I I mean, come on change that over what I have no idea how but
Oh kawaki kawaki over at uluru managed to get a hold of 7500 sacks of cacao
She's trying to offload bring her 100 cases of irish coffee. No get out of here. That's like wait
I already bought look
See what you don't know
Sorry lady
um back like before this took off before
Um, like before cocoa took off
I got it at like five bucks eight bucks. I bought 2000 of them. I don't need it. The milk is rotting. It's fine
All right, we're gonna change this something that I actually have
Milk chocolate. Well, I bought a shitload of caramel. So I mean, maybe i'll just do that
I my accidental care accidental caramel purchase might come in handy here. Okay. Yeah use this one
I can do more than 18 a week the kind of guy that eats monster cans
Eats the physical can of monster energy drink. Well, i'll tell you i'm a guy that doesn't drink monster energy drink
I think you got me wrong
No, I just eat the cans right as I know that i'm not even looking at chat and I know that's what you're writing
This lag is pissing me off. It makes it hard to do
This is kind of hard to do with the lag being like this
Yeah, this is like annoying to do with the lag 20 cases is better than I had before
All right, take a look at this 62 already. I haven't even done anything
Sell this tart of the moon. It's fucking useless
Okay, I am ready to go to kona
and talk business
uh
Silly zonka bonka. I couldn't help but notice that you've got chocolate bars with caramel on hand
I happen to have a craving for those chocolates right now
If you'll give me 25 cases, i'll pay you 10 000 extraordinary price for those chocolates. I'm sure you agree
What do you say 25 cases for 10 grand take them? That's a lot for just chocolate with caramel
Did I get scammed? No, I didn't 25 cases of those just chocolate caramel is probably like
It's probably not more than 10
Zach was most pleased with your delivery and I thank you for that silly zonka bonka next
I'd like to ask you to bring me 60 cases of cup of joe and 60 cases of mocha
Okay
It's 60 cases of cup of joe 60 cases of mocha
Have the ingredients for that, right?
Cup of joe good thing I bought the cream
60 of this and then sick. I have all the ingredients needed to make all this. We're good to go now back to
Cape town. Oh wait, hold on. We're gonna we're gonna go here first. No, we're not. We'll go to capetown
There you go. Is the inventory just getting smoked? How much do I have?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, this is a has a million dollars. This is a million dollar deal right here
It's a million dollars i'm gonna get would you be willing to fulfill a large order for me 210 cases?
You'll receive a hundred thousand dollars for your trouble and the product's time is of the essence a hundred thousand for 200 cases
No
All right. I better hurry up and sell these
All right, that price is gonna go down more and more and more every day. All right
How much let me do this first inventory? I have 14 nutmeg left just
All right, germa tokyo tokyo. No, just wait. I'm about to get a million dollar deal right here. We're changing this over
to
Papa joe
Use this recipe 28 a week. That's fine. And now i'm gonna check this out. We're gonna go to
Tangiers then to tokyo. Let's go welcome back
Okay, are you ready everyone that said what the hell are you doing here?
What am I doing here? I'm making almost a million dollars in one trade
That's what i'm doing here. That was my omega low. Not a million
That's okay. Well, no, no, I didn't make it big boy coming in with the big bucks. Yeah, i'm gonna do it on moroccan coffee
I feel like i'm such a guy. I was like a deal wheeler and dealer
I just had a coffee in my hand like was ice. I took a little sip
And my god, how am I doing on moroccan coffee? Let's take a quick look
Get some inventory up there. Let's uh, let's get a little bit more inventory. It's good to me 100
You don't have to make caramel left. Shit. What do I have?
Oh, i'm out of like candy material. I don't have any more candy material left. I need to what should I be making?
special reserve lemon
raspberry
Probably special reserve
Or is it a coffee time? Is it time to go back?
I think it's time to have coffee. It's straight coffee right now. I think so
Because I have this guy here, but I also am about to have somebody else tokyo go to tokyo
All right. I'm going to tokyo right now go. All right, here we are
We're going to talk to you
Hello, silly zonko wonko and welcome to japan. We have a fantastic factory here set up to manufacture infusions
You'll notice that if you're able to make complete trays with ingredients all the same color you'll earn a significant production bonus
Get you along here's a recipe for dark chocolate pecan infusions complete tray with ingredients all the same color
Nutty pecan filling encased in the finest chocolate. I want one of these
I am willing to consider your candidacy to become our ceo
But i'm a man who likes specific goals if you're able to learn at least nine infusions recipes
And are able to take ownership of the second retail location
I'll be convinced that you have the skills to lead the company incidentally if you look around you should be able to find pecans
You'll need for that recipe
I gave you and it seems that bianca
Rabiti over in tangiers is very interested in getting her hands on some of our dark chocolate pecan infusions
She'll pay twenty thousand dollars for 32. Oh, I can't say no
Splendid i'm not sure why she's so interested in our wares
But her money's as good as anyone else's take those 32 cases to her at the lookout in tangiers
Uh, hold on. I need to mark it look on an ingredient
wasabi
Oh my god wasabi chocolate. Are you kidding me?
I want wasabi and I want uh, I want when I make my own
It's going to be chocolate with wasabi in the middle
pumpkin
ginger
Damn it station. You'd be wise to make sure that you're continually introducing new confections. Sure
Here's an offer. You won't want to refuse the chance to get two new infusion recipes
I'll give you the recipe for milk chocolate infusion with allspice right now
There were 50 cases as my gift to my friend
Uh, daisuke daisuke says daisuke seto here in tokyo station
I'll hand over the recipe for vanilla cinnamon infusion. It's a deal. Okay. It can be a smart move to haggle at markets silly
Zonka wonka as long as you've got a sense of whom you're haggling with and a good idea about her his or her current prices
I've seen i've seen this lady before
Is this lady just on permanent vacation around the whole world? I've seen her in like two or three different places
Tokyo tower
Silly zonka wonka. We are constantly offering official tours of the tower and I need party favors
I've heard wonderful things about a couple of products of yours chocolate bars with raspberry and cinnamon coffee
If you promise to bring me 45 cases of each of these products, I will not only pay you well
But also present you with a pair of wonderful infusion recipes that utilize fresh fruits
You can count on me. The fruits you will need can now be found at the market in tangier
The more chocolate I eat the more I seem to crave it. Okay, I need
I need pecans
Change recipe
I need allspice. I need I want to make my own
I have tons of that. I need a bunch of pecans
All right. Where do I get where were the last place to spit pecans were available?
previously seen
In kona for 229. All right, we're going to kona
I gotta change this
How much no is 60 cup of joe shit. All right, I gotta go. I gotta fly across the entire world
Wait, this is so many quests now. Hold on 50 cases milk chocolate
infusions
32 cases of dark chocolate, but can infusions
45 cases of cinnamon coffee 45 cases of chocolate with raspberry
All right, I need
Chocolate with raspberry we gotta get raspberries where raspberries tangiers. Okay, let's go to tangers
cherries
blueberries
raspberries
Three weeks. You must be taking a zeppelin
All right, I need a hundred
Let's get that going and then cinnamon coffee
All right. We're gonna do that next
It's definitely cherry. I definitely need cherries. I'm gonna need them
It's probably it's either gonna be blueberries or cherries with a secret ingredient
I'm gonna get them now
You're rolling get them both
I'll get even more
All right. I have a shitload of cherries now
Uh, I need to change this coffee to cinnamon
And we're gonna change the chocolate as well. All right, i'm right here. Let's go change the chocolate
What are we doing for chocolate bars? We need raspberry chocolate bars. Let's go use that one 17 a week get the fuck out of here
Make that better
I'm gonna be laggy
Remember the type of guy to eat nuggets without sauce
I mean
Do you eat every single nugget with sauce?
I don't I would say 60% of every 70 to 60% of every nugget is dipped in sauce. Sometimes you just want a nugget
Not every single one has to be dipped in sauce
How many raspberries?
Cereal killer behavior. I I don't dip every single nugget into sweet and sour or something usually I do
And by the way, how many sauces?
Are we talking here? Do we do you guys do one sauce? Do you do two sauces three different sauces? How many I would say two to three?
Usually it's about two
Usually it's for me. It's if uh, if it's a like McNuggets
sweet and sour sauce
and
Maybe honey mustard barbecue
Depends on how I feel the sweet and sour sauce from mcdonald's is the best that you can find anywhere. It's based
Well, no, that's yeah, of course it is
There it is
There's the whiskey. I am about to do something insane
Okay, so
We got irish coffee
300 i'm gonna get are you ready for this? Are you guys ready?
We're gonna haggle. I'm gonna I don't imagine you're doing much business with these outlandish prices
Again, hey, here's how this is gonna work you help me a bit on your price. I'll buy the ingredients
Thank you
400 bottles of whiskey make a custom. That's just three whiskies
In fact, we're gonna do 500 bottles of whiskey. I got a good deal here
Do I need any more of this stuff? Maybe some more cherries?
All right. That's it
22 sacks of milk. That's a good deal. I'll take
I'll take 500
Alcohol doesn't go bad. And what kind of coffee is irish coffee?
Alcohol just gets better with age
The recipe for irish coffee is 600. I need cream
I don't even need to look at the coffee. So I just need a little bit more cream. I need like 200 300 more cream
Good. All right
We've got this being made our quest is for 45 cases. It'll be done
We're gonna go down and make cinnamon coffee down in capetown right now
Cinnamon coffee plenty Moroccan coffee plenty of sugar plenty of cinnamon use this one. Here we go
Ingredients that are not alcohol will go bad
I'll just i'm gonna put it in like a bunch of oak barrels. I'll just put it back in the barrel
Oh my god, you know, I what do you think I was?
So annoying
Oh my god
No, i'm trying to go here. All right. These are among us kill sounds
All right. So by the time that I fly
To back to tokyo
I will have the inventory that she requires what else I need to go back to tokyo with something else
Okay
I need 60 cases of mocha shit. All right, we're going
We're going going back to tokyo so I can take I can trade this in I don't have enough
Okay, I was gonna say what?
Trade these in there you are
It's fifty thousand dollars and a couple of fruit recipes. This is blueberry
And cherry. Yes
I knew it. I told you guys it's gonna be cherries. I'm gonna make a shit load of these
I can make these now
So i'm gonna do cherry we're gonna make a ton of cherries ton of them
Like a 300 of these i'm gonna make them right now if we often host special events here at the tower
In fact, I could use 45 cases each
Of the infusion recipes I gave you that's not enough a hundred thousand
Make that a million 45 cases each
That would be almost a hundred k that's 90 cases of what she just did
I can get way more than that. No, thanks
All right, let's actually do the uh, let's get it rolling the things about your success
All right, change that recipe. We're going straight up cherries use this. Oh, this is four
No
Oh, no, this is gonna be so much and they move around and they have this weird coloring system
um
Oh, they're just trying to fuck with your head. That's two
Um go. Oh
Man
Um, wait, why is it color coded? I'm so confused
What do the colors mean I I don't know
17 cases a week
That's it
only a thousand
I see my delicious cinnamon coffee
Same color gets you a bonus. Oh, okay
All right. I'm ready to i'm just gonna i'm not gonna dump this, uh cinnamon coffee
This is gonna be worth way more at my uh place
All the cup of joe as well. I got a cup of joe and now I have to do mocha
I gotta bring the cans back here
Go to the imperial palace. All right. All right
Where's the pair? There it is. I understand you have been having good success with infusions
I have a friend named suzana
Van agas in central america
Who has a couple of fantastic infusions recipes she might be willing to barter for
For ten thousand dollars i'll be willing to secure passage for you. Yeah, let's go make your way to begota
All right
These are just gonna be made. Uh, this i'm gonna have probably a thousand of these
So we have production in tokyo good
I need to
Mocha, okay
Mocha call me crazy because what we're gonna do we're going to begota first
I don't give a shit about the chocolate right now
custom house
Silly zonka bonka good news. I have a message from alexandra
She and the rest of the board are excited about how well you've been doing with your launch of infusions
They've award you another space in the recipe book. Be sure to visit the secret test kitchen soon
Nice. We got a new one. All right, I can make my own infusion with wasabi
and okay
Often you'll find special orders
And here's the market. All right pecans pecans haggle. Come on prices are good, but you can do better. Yes, you can. Thank you
I'll take 200 of these
And holy shit. Look at that allspice price
I'll take 200 of these too
And look at that pumpkin price. I'll take 200 of these
Make a pumpkin spice latte
lumbia and that's where this is columbian coffee
Holy smokes
Well, this is this is like the best stuff on earth. Yeah, this is this is the real shit
I need a lot of this ng was correct. I have infusion recipes to share
I've heard amazing stories about your sprite sponge bring me 25 cases and i'll give it to you. Okay
Everybody always wants to try a taste of my sprite sponge
Nobody ever asks for a second delivery
Unfortunately, all right now we go back
We make we go to the we're going to go to capetown. Let's change this over to mocha
I got a ton of those. All right, change this to mocha. I have enough
Okay, use this recipe good to go
um
68 how much mocha did I need?
60 do I have enough to I need more? Okay. I have enough to do this so make that
All right. Why am I going broke because i'm fucking spending money. Did I put a new chocolate thing in?
All right. All right. Let's go to
All right mocha who needed that? Oh, right. Yeah. Okay go to kona kona that'll complete our
Mocha. All right, that'll complete it for us. Let's go up to zero change the chocolate. Whoa paragraph
I want to tell you about a pretty nifty gizmo the remote telegraph once hooked up
You'll be able to reconfigure your factories without needing to travel there. That's insane
You can reset factories to any product they have previously produced. Believe me. This is well worth a hundred thousand dollars
You oh you bet. Oh my god. That's so much better. I can do this remote now
I don't have to fly across the world to change recipes. Perfect. Awesome. All right
All right, i'm gonna pee again. So we're gonna pee again. I'm gonna restart the game because it's feeling a little laggy
So i'm gonna save the game and quit and then restart it. So i'll be right back. We're gonna pee see in uh, like two minutes
Can you guys just hear me eating? I thought the mic was muted
I thought the mic was muted
Right when the cat boy comes up you just hear like
Oh my god, i'm so sorry. I thought the mic was muted. I'm just sitting here like enjoying the art
I'll be back in a second. I shook up this huge thing, dude
You
Just silently this is how I watch like movies I must be so loud just shake shake shake shake
Stop
Don't ever do that again. I do that like once a week
Actual worst noise for real. I do the cat puke noise like once every three days
I'm just munching on beef jerky strips. Oh, man
it's so funny because I just look over I have the
so on my
obs I can just see the mic indicator
And i'm just sitting there just looking at the artwork just sitting there for a few minutes and I just noticed I wasn't talking
But the indicator was going up and down
I'm like wait, what that was just me eating food. All right
It's silent, too
It's so dumb. Haha. Yeah, that's so funny. It's not that funny. Okay, I know I get it
I know what you're doing there. I get it, but it's slightly humorous. Holy shit. Oh my god
Jesus
Oh my god
Oh
I feel I that's baby chills down my spine
That actually gave me chills down my spine when I was not expecting that. All right, let me reopen the game
You go very mr. Green and cat boy. I'm glad I caught that mute. That was a disgusting burp. All right
Are we doing we're doing good
I think we're ready to come back
We are here we go
Please let me throw the grenade down here. Just oh, yeah, I forgot about that
I want to make it really dramatic
All right, let's move
And there it is. Okay
So we were in the middle of what we're going to be in in zurek. Okay, I need to change the chocolate recipe
Something I actually have and then we're going to go to the test kitchen. I'm going to make my own chocolate
I don't think I have any ingredients to make chocolate. I think I can just make milk chocolate and that's it
I can't make anything else this basic chocolate bar make chalky milk. I could just make milk chocolate. I guess
Need to make the sprite sponges
I don't have any more lemons
Make tar to the moon
What's the actual thing I need?
No, no
No
Okay, 25 cases of sprite sponge
God damn it. I need to go get limes from that one place on earth
Uh, let's just do 100
I'm gonna get 100 limes
And I can switch to this
from here so
What else what I'm gonna do on the way mocha is being made here back. Okay here. This is what I want to do
I need to go. I need to do this now. Let's do it now
He's sitting down
He was standing last time. It's been there for a while
Okay fruits
sugar
infusions
Coffee, okay infusions
How about we have cream?
We have sugar
We have where's wasabi?
Oh, I need to taste that
Just four whiskies just a shot of whiskey is it what you sell for a candy black tea
I want to do whiskey
wasabi
columbian
columbian cocoa you ready for this and cream
wait sugar sugar columbian cocoa whiskey and wasabi or
Whiskey columbian cocoa and blueberry sugar. That'll get that's a little zing
Blueberries had a nice touch to this one disgusting or how about how about blueberry cherry cream?
And sugar it'd just be like a delicious
Berry taste. Oh, they wanted to be chocolate. Hold on. What else we got? How about columbian cocoa?
columbian cocoa columbian coffee
Whiskey wasabi columbian nutmeg and cinnamon and milk cream make it rich
There's no sugar in it though. It's like a coffee chocolate nutmeg sugary
Coffee chocolate chocolate coffee. That's too basic though. Is it too basic nutmeg with a cinnamon challenge
nutmeg whiskey
Sugar and columbian cocoa bingo. That's gonna be delicious. We're gonna call what we call this one
You just made an old-fashioned
Put in windex. No, I like this. It's he likes it. We're doing it. I'm going for it. I like it
It's like a whiskey. It's got the the hints of the whiskey
It's got the hints of the nutmeg just put everyone will think you know what you're talking about
If you say that something has a hint of this and it just was in it try this try this. Yeah
Oh, yeah, what's in that? Oh, you can taste the hint of the squash
You can taste the hint of the nutmeg like oh because that then yeah, this is not making it
Yeah, I get it. All right, there's no sugar. What do you mean? No sugar. I want to be sweet
What do you think instead of sugar instead of sugar? Hold on a minute
What if we do whiskey nutmeg columbian chocolate and lime and spice and honey?
Oh, man, honey sounds good
That would be yeah, that would be very good
I would I want to eat this right now a hint of bleach. I'm glad somebody said it
Frothy morning piss noise. I said that yesterday. Okay, taste it do it
Okay, so what was in that what was in it?
nutmeg
What's the style? I want the shaded one. All right, so we got a base of rich deep columbian cocoa
We have
On top of that. I want to make a watermelon. Can I go back make a walnut watermelon candy?
We have the nutmeg
Is that shit from a sand aquarium?
Level three insane aquarium the things that spit up the stars should have made one of those. All right deep rich columbian chocolate
Mixed with the nutmeg, which is not that would be on top
I'm gonna sneeze again and i'm gonna try to get away
Word soup deep richest color of the nutmeg with the
Picket all right nutmeg is like this, right? So this I want that to be
That what style do I want this to be because there's whiskey in here. Okay, the whiz. Whoa
I like that definitely that's the whiskey infused. Oh wait, so the whiskey now the whiskey is a dab on top
That's a dab of whiskey. It's like a toothpaste
Yeah, there's the whiskey dab right there and then that means this needs to be like this. Holy shit
There's your nutmeg. There's your columbian cocoa. Wait, that's honey. Where's the whiskey? That's nutmeg right there. It's ground on top
It's nutmeg shavings nutmeg shavings a drizzle of honey
Whiskey infusion drizzle of honey whiskey columbian chocolate. It's a ton of nutmeg. You can never have too much nutmeg
Let's get this guy out of here. What are you saying? All right, this is called the uh, I don't know
I don't know digging for gold because it's like honey. That's like gold
There's whiskey which is kind of like gold nutmeg is gold digging for gold. This is fucking gross
This is one of this is one of the most normal yummy delicious candies
I've made of the four things that i've made
This is the one that people would actually probably eat digging for gold columbian cocoa honey nutmeg whiskey. I love it
So let's go back to tokyo
And I think I want to get this in production. Oh, right. All right, we're gonna go back to
I need limes to fly across the damn entire world for limes
Jerma, I did the dishes. Are you proud of me? Yeah, nice job
Wow
Remember how much limes were before?
Did the dishes? Yeah, nice
Back up to xeric
Wait a minute 60 cases chocolate peanuts for a hundred thousand dollars
All right. I need to dump some inventory here. I've got
I need lemons. I got the lemons. I'm ready to turn this over
the sprite sponge
Go for it. Use that recipe 29 a week is fine
Does the game sort of like this but it's lemonade
That's kind of cool
All right. So this is mocha. I don't have any I can't do any more mocha, but I needed 60 mocha
Did I get 60 mocha? Yes or no?
I do. All right, we can change this coffee
We're gonna change the coffee to irish coffee
Here you go
Oh, I have to go there to do it
Anybody want any coffee?
I'm ready to go back to kona with this shit
But I have to do this first
Let's start making just a absolute shit load of irish coffees. We're in sub only mode. Why?
Oh, I need milk. I need milk. I need milk. I need milk
Oh shit, it's going too fast
All right. That's a lot
That's a decent that's 35 cases a week nice
Only 35. That's a lot
And there's enough for me just to just keep this on forever
All right. They are making these how many of these do I own now a lot probably
187 who wants these who would buy these at a decent price?
Not here
All right. These are doing well. How many do I more do I need? Let's go now. Let's go to kona
Oh the cherries cost more than the chocolate. Yeah, that sucks
Oh, you manufacture at least 10 different coffee products. Nice
All right, here we go
You really know how to work wonders of my beans. Stop by and see
Lialoa next door. I knew this was gonna work out swimmingly
Trust me having an outpost here in hawaii will be great for your business
We see a lot of tourists, especially tourists with disposable dollars for confections. There's one last thing i'll need to you to do
Bring me 50 cases each of chocolate with honey arabium bold
And you're the cuban clock cleaner. Oh my god. That's so much
It sounds like you had to look down
i'll take a 50 cases of chocolate bars with honey arabium bold and
You're the cuban clock cleaner
God damn it. Okay, that's a lot
I'm just i'm gonna make irish coffees for a while. I need money
I have enough for this special order of peanuts
Oh, okay. We got to go to begota
And we're gonna start doing infusion stuff for japan. All right, let's go to begota
Here you go
I take it your sprite sponge products are earning a healthy profit. No, not at all actually
Excellent. They are even better than I had led to believe
Here's a recipe I mentioned for refreshing dark columbian cocoa lime infusions. Nice. Okay
My infusions are way better though. Can you bring me 45 cases? I'll give you a second one. You guys like cherries
No
Why does nobody want these?
My god, I got 200 200 i'm all right for now
There is a bad for you
There is a bad and you should feel bad
What's wrong with you today?
Okay, I have to do
This order is absurd
Chocolate bars with peanuts
I need peanuts. Where can I get peanuts?
capetown
You like cherries
Fuck. All right. Give me the peanuts
Here's how this works. Give me help me out a bit. Fine
You need you wanted a lot of these right? Let's just get let's just have let's get 200
All right, turn this off. We're gonna be making
Chocolate peanuts. Thank you
Only 18 a week. Holy shit. That's horrible. It's 60 cases
All right, is it time these cherries? Why don't nobody like them?
I'm missing like this is such a horrible loss
They keep making irish coffees. They're probably worth a shitload
They are
Okay
Just keep making them. I am gonna go I have to sell i'm going here irish coffee only
2,000
cinnamon
Are you kidding me?
Cinnamon coffee is worth more than an irish coffee irish coffee has whiskey in it
Is this spices?
But joe make sure I don't need any of this stuff. I need okay. I need arabian bold
Okay. No, I don't need any of this shit
Get rid of the cup of joe
Take some money back here mocha don't need any mocha
irish coffee really
That's it
I mean, that's a uh, that's almost half a million dollars, but I feel like I was gonna get more than that
Hmm
He's not so he's still not using the sell all button. I know I told you why
Look if I hover over sell all it doesn't say how much I get
I just do it
Putting in the maximum that I can do or putting a price it shows you and I'd like to see it
Uh, i'm gonna hold it for now. No, i'm not get rid of all of it
That price is just gonna drop. It probably will
Uh, I need
All right. We're gonna I gotta change this
Special order. Yeah, the peanuts order is coming
50 cases milk chocolate infusion with allspice
Milk chocolate infusion with allspice
I have the necessary ingredients
But I cannot do it because I have to make it and oh, I hate that thing. I gotta go back to japan
All right back to japan
We're making some new confections
I mean do I hold on to these nobody wants them?
That's such a low price. It's a thousand bucks. It's like 1300 bucks for cherries
Can I just take a loss here?
I'm sure I just hold it
All right, the rest of this junk we're getting rid of
No more sprite sponges
Peanuts we need do we need caramel? We don't think I don't think we need raspberry anymore either
I have the peanuts chocolate caramel. I don't think I need these either
I need to make new infusions though. All right new infusion
What do I want to do?
This is the one with allspice
Let's do this one. All right. I'm gonna try to do this right
All right blue blue is gonna be over here red will be here
We'll have two red
And then it's um milk over here
um
Whatever. Oh shit, this sucks
um oops
What do I need milk? What the fuck 35 cases? I thought I was doing bad
All right. It's really important just to do that. Okay, you sell cream. No
Oh, that's what happened
I bought the cherries at the most expensive they ever were in the course of the game. They're
474 dollars now they were
1300 like a month ago in game
Well, then i'm just gonna i'm gonna the price is probably just gonna keep going down. Just sell them all sell them all
The price is gonna keep going down get rid of them. I don't even want them
Raid song. I don't see raid
I need 50
I'll have that in a little bit
The special order will be done soon, too
All right, we're gonna start working on this arabian bold
I need kona. Oh, I need all I need coffee
I need coffee now
We need moroccan coffee. We need kona coffee a shitload of it
Go I managed to get a hold of 100 sacks each of cayenne pepper and anise
And it just so happened to have on hand an infusion recipe that uses these spices
If I gave you the recipe as well as the ingredients right now
Would you be willing to deliver your first 75 cases of the product to me? Sure. Okay
Ooh, that looks good. That's like that's what I wanted to make
That's a really good like sith candy
Somebody just give 50 community subs lenny the person just gave 50 community subs. That's insane what on earth
Quick shit your pants
Thanks, that's so much money. Thank you
I can make a sith candy
No, I want to make mine mine is probably gonna be worth more whiskey and nutmeg honey and columbian cocoa
That's gonna be insane a solstice haze. Thanks for the five subs. Welcome back to your shop
Yeah, i'm selling them get rid of them. I don't want them anymore
Oh my god
What are you guys doing? That's another 50 community subs from vin smoke. That's ridiculous
It's ridiculous
That's insane
Well, thank you both of you guys. It's all you guys giving stuff. Not just people giving 50
Uh, thanks. That's a that's a ton. That's a shitload. Can't wait to spend it on fucking nutmeg
All right, I need coffee haggle
What a marvelous day
Imagine raising your prices to somebody
because they said
What a nice day it is out today
What the fuck?
It's such a beautiful day today. I have to come back now. All right, we're gonna go to
I need to let's go to kona. I'll be back because that was a fake friendly small talk
Uh, we need all right. I have the 50 cases of the allspice one. Let's change this to
Oh, I don't have the honey. Am I about to be out of ingredients? I have 10 cherries
No, i'll just keep keep on this one. All right out of a cream can't make any more irish coffee
So what's the other coffee I need to make rabian bold, right? Okay, rabian bold just put it on
I'm gonna get the kona coffee right now
Hey, uh, I truly expected to see a better price today. All right. I'm not gonna push my luck
Whatever just buy 500 of them now. I need to go back and get moroccan coffee how much is cream?
That's too high. Look at cherries. Oh my god
Look at that. Look at the range
I bought all the cherries when they were about 14 1500 dollars. This shit is now 384 dollars
No wonder
And I bought so I put like half a million dollars into buying 300 cherries
I'm running out of just regular cocoa. Oh my goodness. Oh shit. Okay
What sugar do I have?
All right, i'll be good
This is actually a pretty good price. Yeah, that's a really good price. I'm gonna get more. All right back to um
Back to here. Fuck you didn't forget
Your prices seem pretty fair. Can you offer me to you? You're nuts. You think i'm paying you
You're you're not here to lose money
I can't believe I have to actually buy this
What a marvelous day
Now a week later. Yes, it is a nice day, isn't it?
Uh, let's get more
Anything else here worth buying my milk? Yeah
almonds
They call them the deal maker
Oh, I still have plenty of sugar
All right. Now I can make the arabian bold
I need i'm out of allspice
shit
Go to pagoda talk to salwa tumor
In capetown. All right, let's go to capetown
Thank you. Silly zonka wonka. These chocolate bars of peanuts are perfect to look forward to ordering from this company again
That's a clean hundred and twenty thousand dollars
nice
Irish coffee. No, it's still cheap
I'm gonna hold on to those
They're junk, right? But whatever
All right. Do I have enough arabian bold?
No, I need 50 arabian bold one more week
Let's go back
to tokyo
Turn this in a gift from yoshi
Kawai, how wonderful he must have known i'd give you this recipe for vanilla cinnamon infusions
Note that the vanilla you need for this is now available in duala had vanilla, but I had an opportunity to give vanilla
by the way
We got an unusual situation
uh reiko
Sonata over at nakamise market has gotten her hands on a thousand sacks of cocoa
She's not going to be able to sell here
If you bring her 31 cases of vanilla cinnamon infusions within two months, she'll give you all that wonderful cocoa in exchange
Wait, that's ten thousand
That's ten thousand sacks
I'll take it. Yeah, sure. That's insane. That's ten thousand sacks
I'll never have to buy it again
What do you got? Give me wasabi. I want it in my recipes
And ginger I want to be put ginger in my recipes
I have 200 pumpkins. What am I doing with these?
I got the arabian bold. I can stop with the arabian bold
I can actually sell the arabian bold here if I wanted to
But i'm not going to we're going to keep making it. What was the other thing that she wanted the cuban clock cleaner
I need
Cayenne pepper. Wait, somebody was going to give me cayenne pepper a lot of it. Where's that quest?
Can somebody give it to me?
I don't know. She didn't give it to me
I thought she gave me a hundred
You have to make it. Oh
All right. Well, how do I make this shit? It's this one
Okay, I can make 25 25 25 invest use this recipe. Let's do it. Get this right
um
Uh, I can't throw this away. Whatever blue. It's blue. It's blue
ah
Um shit. Oh boy. That was bad. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Shit
Um
Come on come on come on come on come on come on come on come on how many cases how many 50 cases a week
Jesus. All right. Um, I need anise. We're gonna go to duala
We're going to duala and we're gonna bring a ton of peppers and anise. I thought this was gonna be cheap
I want to see you do something with your prices for me. Might there be a little bit of wiggle room?
You're charging torus prices here do something for me or I take my business somewhere else
Yeah, that that was a torus price
I need cocoa. I I have to just do it temporarily. What about vanilla get the vanilla?
Oh, this is so much money though get vanilla
That's so expensive. Should I get 200?
Okay, that's good. That's good. That's good. That's good
What am I making over here?
This is uh, okay, very curious
31 case of vanilla cinnamon infusions vanilla cinnamon infusion. So I need cinnamon. How much cinnamon do I have?
Not a lot. Let's buy it here because it's cheap here now
Okay, vanilla cinnamon cinnamon infusion. All right, then you're gonna make something else here. What do I have? What can I make?
I have a shitload of lemons. Why do I have so many lemons? Just make them. Whatever. Let me keep an eye on you
Jerma, this is joe ziden not to be confused with joe biden
I'm willing to take one billion off the debt if you let chat create their own candy bar
All right, wait that coffee pasta really
Jerma, it's me joe ziden not joe biden
Let chat make a candy for a billion off the debt joe ziden
That's it
Uh, it's gonna be hard to do that
You bought a thousand lemons from that lady to spite her the other day. Oh, right. Okay
I need wait there was something else I needed to do before I got sidetracked you. Okay, that's going good
What do I need for coffee?
Anything else for coffee chocolate bars with honey you sell honey here you do not
Okay, where do they sell honey? Whatever funds he has at the end of the game
He gets off the debt times 100. Oh shit you guys on you guys ready for that one deal deal deal deal
All right. Hold on. How about this? Whatever I have at the end of uh, the stream tonight times 100
But I have to scroll my mouse
Over the casino at least once a month in game. I have to I have to I have to click on the casino
At least once a month. That's so easy
Every once every two weeks. No, that's I have to be able to play the game. Wait, wait, wait
Wait, you must have more than two million in profit. No, no that's that because I'll I just have to not gamble
Which I could just I mean that's debt money. I can do it. Oh, no deal. No deal. Yeah, it's too easy
No deal. Let's go to the coffee shop and sell our arabium bold. They have too much of it. It's worth a lot though
I'm just gonna keep making it
There's anything do I have enough to make something that's worth more that you sell nutmeg here?
Holy shit, we're gonna get a nutmeg. I'm gonna go to back to tokyo actually no
Oh, that's right cuban clock cleaner. I need to make sure I have enough for that
I need honey and I need I need more peppers and I need honey and kona. Let's go to kona get the honey
You only have two months to get the 10k cocoa. Really december 3rd. I'm all right. I got time
All right, we need to do the hell am I doing here? Right honey, can you got any wiggle room?
These are there's a reason this is harvard. You probably suck. I don't care. Fuck you
I need 50 cuban clock cleaner and 50 chocolate bars with honey. So let's get on that now. Go for it. Here it comes now
back to
Tokyo talk to uh, no into alla. Okay. I have no more cocoa left marvelous
Thank you for tracking me down here and for bringing the spicy dark chocolate infusions. Oh, the recipe serves you well
Thank you. Wait, what do I do that for? Shit? I gotta pay premium on this 100 million for a jar jar binks impression now
I'm gonna go back to tokyo. We're gonna do vanilla cinnamon infusions. Okay quest, please i'm going i'm going i'm going
vanilla cinnamon infusions
We held it we held it it became no, no, no, wait, hold on how many spicy dark infusions did I make?
Way too many talk about with lemon talk about with honey. All right, I
Made 50 a week
Right, that's why
Okay, what can what do I not want to sell?
All right, got it. I got it honey
I can go back and we can finally have this stupid partnership with the with the hawaiian. Um shop
Or what? Okay. Don't sell the honey. Don't sell the arabian bowl. Don't sell the cuban claw cleaner
Everything else can go. Oh the chocolate with peanuts get the fuck out of here
Irish coffee. Yeah, I sell this shit to milk chocolate with allspice
Who wants that?
Why do I have so many of these?
All right. Here we go
Change recipe
Vanilla cinnamon infusion. I have enough. Let's get it use this recipe
And yes, i'm giving it away
What is that?
What is that from? I know that why do I know that?
Why do I know that I fucked it up?
Come on, man
No
Come on, come on
Whatever 31 cases how many does she want?
All right, oh I got it
Your fusions look delicious silly zonka wonka. Here you go. Here's 10 000 cocoa
Like a scam. No, there it is
10 000 stacks i'll never have to buy another one
All right
I have reached my limit here
I need to go back to kona wait dark chocolate pecan infusions
I feel like these are gonna be worth a lot of money
I'm gonna let this ride for a little bit. This is probably gonna worth a shit load of money
Let's go do the um, the like partnership
We got here for coffee that I can still make
I could do arabian bold. I got plenty of coffee for that
Yeah, let's just throw an arabian bold for the trip. Let's change this over to uh,
lemon for the trip
Let's go
One time I was at a candy store buying a nice treat for my son germa came up from behind us and kicked my son like a football
This shop is now yours
premium prices for all your goods
oh
my god
That's the ticket right there
Oh my goodness. We're about to make lots of money
So this is i'm gonna wait
This is 93
$100,000
Let's go
Give it to me. I'll take it milk chocolate infused without why is this so cheap?
sell it all
Where we just crossed two million
sell everything
That's 2.2 million
I'm gonna load up on uh cinnamon and vanilla
We're gonna go to duala
Go to duala. Let's buy a shitload more of this go to the casino. That's not a bad idea, but not yet
Silly zonka wonka
What if I told you that i've just come from a special place a magical place a place not on your map
Where fortunes are won and lost and perhaps more importantly for you a place where one can find fresh beautiful strawberries
Would you do something for me if I can get you such a place? Yeah, you won't be disappointed. The place is las vegas nevada
There are riches to be had there
But beware. I nearly lost my kimono. All I would like you to do is to get me 100 sacks of strawberries
I'll find you in a couple of months. Oh, we gotta let's get your strawberries right now
We get a ticket to vegas
I'm going home
What are you trying to do rip me off?
Don't get sucked into a war hole
Come on hurry up and make these he's in the game
You
Okay, have a hundred sacks of strawberries where do I get the strawberries did she tell me
Where do I get them you get them in vegas?
But like it says have a hundred sacks in your inventory. She'll find you
I have to have the strawberries in my inventory doesn't don't I you're so stupid. You're so vain
Probably think this song is about you about you
You're so vain. I actually should get some of this. Yeah, why not? Give me some all right. I have some quests
45 dark columbian cocoa lime infusions. All right. Do I have any limes? Holy fuck. Yeah
78 cases, but just honey two hundred thousand dollars. Let's go. Okay
Dark chocolate cocoa lime infusion
All right. I need some more columbian cocoa. We need to go to bogota
Not yet. Let's go to tokyo get this started
Go to vegas now
I hold on. Let me I know just give me a second. Just give me a second. I I've got i'm gonna go home real quick
I didn't know that vegas is in this game. There's probably slot machines fucking everywhere. I can't wait
Okay, i'm gonna make these first because I want to get this out of my inventory
What I didn't miss
Uh
Whoa wait, I see five hundred thousand dollars silly zonka wonka
I'm sure you're aware of how high travel costs have gotten bad news is that this trend is likely to continue
The good news is that I am here to offer you a corporate airline
For an investment of five hundred thousand dollars
You'll be able to fly direct from any port to any port and all of your future travel costs will be zero
This certainly makes a difference as you fly in and out of secret ports
And this is not even considering the bump to your style and grace. What do you say?
I'll take it. It's half a million dollars private airline. Let's go
Think about how much we lose going back and forth
It's like two or three thousand dollars a trip
My corporate airline is ready to go
All right. I got 154 cases. Let's change this to the one with the lime use this recipe. Let's go
And then we go
bang
bung
It it shit shit
shit
Shit shit
No, I just messed it up
Oh, I the one with the doubles just fucks up my head
I don't
Look at this dog shit we're getting
I need limes. I haven't seen a lot of like two years. I didn't see no do that again
Look, I did no lime came up. The rng was terrible
I just got electrocuted
I just put both hands on the stove
Limes limes limes limes limes I need limes
Whatever
That's fine. That's good. Actually, is that enough?
32k. Wait, where is it?
45 cases. Okay. Well, whatever
I need columbian cocoa
Okay. Okay. What am I need to i'm running out of coffee
All right. We'll just make a cafe lonelier for now
Throw this on
Yeah, we'll just do secret whatever that is
And we'll keep what do I have for recipes what I actually have do I have enough to make anything?
Accounts. All right. Let's make the accounts. I don't have chocolate
All right. That's fine. All right, let's go
It's time to go to las vegas
You ready? Let's go
Wow
Here we are
Welcome to incredible las vegas
They sell strawberries here
That's quite the investment
1700 bucks. I need a hundred strawberries
All right, fine
All right golden dollar. Oh, no
Come on coin. Wait, what happened? That was 900. I just made a million dollars
Holy shit
Okay, this is
go
Okay, this is a 300. I just made a million dollars
This is a
$400,000 box play this two million dollars in prizes here
One more one more box
That's it
All right. I'm back. I didn't do anything. I'm back to where I started. We're fine. I'm back to where I started
I'm gonna pull one more slot machine
One more that's it
All right, that's there you go 180 000 bet which means we can do the box one more time
At a fucking 400 000. Let's go. Okay. I'm done. Fuck this game. Get out
Oh my fucking god
two
This okay. I let me see something
Three six nine twelve fifteen eighteen. There's twenty one boxes
And you're telling me that there's three faces
In the box and what's the chance that's three out of twenty one?
There's a one in seven chance that you'll get it
Shit, where's the lady that has the strawberries that she wants?
Not gonna lose it all I one million i'm good and look at you understand how much fucking coffee I have to sell
Not very much. Okay, we're fine
I am not concerned at all. I'm not concerned at all about this
Check this shit out. You guys are concerned about this
Oh, are you concerned about this this?
770 000 back. I didn't even nothing even went wrong
I got super reserved chocolates
Chocolates with lemons in them. I'm fine. I'm almost back to with two million arabian bold
I got 130 cases of this shit now way over two million again
Yeah
Okay. Now what do I do? Okay, she's gonna track me now and I got the strawberries
All right, we need chocolate bars with honey
Uh, we need to go to kona
Well, I I need more sugar. I'm running out of sugar. Somebody said you turn everything into gambling. How do you do it?
There are slot machines in the game
I didn't like code that into the game
Just like pick the box for five hundred thousand dollars. Like I didn't turn it into that. They put it in twice
uh
Plus how could I not do a five hundred thousand dollar bet in my hometown of las vegas nevada?
Whatever i'll take honey. So how many do we need?
We need a lot don't we i'll do 200 just make them. Uh, we got coffees brewing here. I need more
vanilla
and
cinnamon
That's a little high
But you know what it sells with so much
Let's go get cinnamon. You're from boston
Fuck which casino were you born in?
All right, so we gotta go to tokyo. I have 28 weeks to do it. I did that already
Oh, I didn't make enough of the lime
Uh, what should I do now?
I kind of just need to exist for a little while
I mean there's always we kind of have to just burn a week or two. There's always las vegas nevada, you know
We'd always go to las vegas strawberries nectar of the gods and here's a recipe that makes the use of that perfect fruit strawberry
And ice chocolate infusions. Oh shit. These are gonna go for a absolute shitload
Ruby and cocoa. I don't even have for ruby and cocoa while i'm here. I'll get some moroccan coffee
Get some
Here everybody. I have enough cinnamon make an infusion with up dog
What's up dog?
You just made uh, like the lemur behind me laugh
I didn't die. I just I forgot to tell you guys. I got a lemur
Millionaire andy because I have a lemur
I mean that is like a weird that is like a weird millionaire pet right I guess to have
Uh, I need more sugar. I'm just gonna buy a ton of it. What happened to have an almost three million?
Oh, did you leave for a little bit? Did you come back?
I went here
And by the way, i'm going here again
I want these
I need to make strawberry shit right now
milk milk
475 000
One more i'm good. I'm good. All right, we got the honey going. I'm gonna go to kona. We're gonna sell these. Uh,
Watch how much money i'm about to make are you ready again bang?
Almost half a million again
It's got a durasoul ad what the fuck you did
All right, I have to go. I got okay
Once i've run out of vanilla, i'm gonna change this to the lime thing. Which coffee do I have? That's a good price
I'll take it. Hmm
Is a battery update it's just still sitting there
I haven't moved it. All right. I have to go back. We got to do how many lines do I have?
Way enough to do this. Okay. I still want to make my actual product that I got
My secret product. All right. I need to buy a shitload of nutmeg a shitload of honey
I need to I need 100 honey and 200 nutmeg
And I need 200 cocoa i'm going to begota
At least onka monka. Did I hear correctly that you recently acquired a recipe for milk chocolate infusions with blueberry?
I simply adore blueberries
If you'll make me 26 cases, I will find you in about a month and by that time i'll have gotten a hold of a new
Recipe wait only a month if I get this fucking coffee from
Wait, what? I gotta go to tokyo. All right, where am I? What the hell is going on here? Hold on
Oh, I need colombian cocoa last seen in begota. That's where I am
Where is it? I just I just clicked it like three times
Now I can train. Okay
back to tokyo
we got
60 of these in my inventory
let's make
some I sell this uh
cafe
But the honey the chocolate bars with honey somebody wanted these bad you did. Here you go. Here you go
Thank you. Silly zonka bonka. These are perfect. Here is
$200,000. Thank you
All right. We're getting close to being able to
Change this to the lime one
Make 41 of these. All right
Let's go to begota
Because that's where I need to do this. I want to make sure I get this shit ready to go
milk chocolate with blueberry
Oh, it's an infusion
Shit, okay. I need blueberries
Oh, I think i'm screwed here
I'm gonna get blueberries
And is this enough time?
I'm gonna go to tanger
8 by april what when when in april
What the fuck?
This is outrageous
Absolutely fucking outrageous, but I need them
Shit what oh not two
uh
Here fuck throw it away. Uh, whatever whatever. Uh, come on
Come on really
Really really really really dude, really?
Really? Can I please have it? RNG was dog shit. It was dog shit RNG. You know, it was dog shit RNG
That was like look at those five snowballs in a row dog shit RNG horrible. It was awful truly
Terrible truly awful RNG right there. It's truly awful RNG right now. Oh, whatever. Just I need it
All I ever hear from this clown is whining and complaints ban that person right now
I don't want to see the person in my chat ever again
Uh market is finicky hide him hide that guy
Hide him
How many did you need?
There it is. He will track you down. All right. I got I got it already
He's gonna give me a recipe
I have this now i'm gonna go to begota
Dark chocolate pecan, what does that take?
No cinnamon
Oh, it's the first one. All right pecan is in
All right, we gotta go to begota. I'll keep the blueberry one on for now
I gotta go to begota coming back. Anyway, it's begota
cool
Stupendous here's another infusions recipe that takes advantage of our marvelous local cocoa
specialty cocoa and macadamia infusion
Look at the macadamia nuts in hawaii. Oh, that looks really good. I need peruvian cocoa though
Where do I get peruvian cocoa?
my hero macadamia
All right, uh no more
What about breakfast blend? I feel like this is sell for a lot
I'm gonna go get uh, i'm gonna go to bali
I'm just gonna make this a shitload of this. I'm gonna get some balinese coffee
Holy fuck. That's a lot. It's an investment. This is this is all an investment. Okay
What about the pecans? Shit, whatever. I'll get it. I heard a new rumor that
A new ingredient mangoes available in duala go visit the port again. Okay
Oh shit, I can go back. I'm done. I gotta go back to tokyo. Wait something important. I needed to do
I need pecans. All right
What do I get pecans?
In begota. Was that just in begota? Oh fuck whatever
I'm so thrilled your milk chocolate infusion with blueberry delicious. I was indeed able to put you here
It is there's a recipe for it dark chocolate infusion with ginger
Ooh, nice
cloves
Agle, holy shit. Look at these people. Holy shit. You knew I was coming. You knew I was coming
I god damn it. I was here
I was on the phone with my agent
I'm like, I gotta buy 5 000 things at pecans. Where do I get them? I'll pay any price. I don't care what it is
I left he had a week to get ready and then I came back
Holy shit
That's absolutely
absurd
Truly fucking absurd that i'm gonna pay this but i'm gonna do it
Because that means that these all right hear me out. That means that this shit is worth a ton of money
That means that right now pecans are anything with pecans
Are going to be worth insane amounts of money
I'm gonna make a ton
Of those pecan chocolate infusions, but you hear my voice crack. I just broke because I just did a million dollar dump. Okay
My lot is that's how it's not how it works. What do you mean?
That's not that's not how it works in the game. What do you mean?
What do you mean? Why are you saying that? What are you talking about? What do you mean? Buy high sell low just wait
Hold on a second. Go back here
Holy shit, that guy was a fucking idiot. He just he just gave me a million dollars for like a hundred pecans
This guy didn't we got from failed every economics class. He ever took in college. What a fucking moron
You've done it
You've earned my endorsement
By showing me your ability to accumulate recipes for infusions way to go
There's still plenty of work to be done, but you are making excellent progress. I have no doubt you're going to succeed
These are currently worth so much money use this recipe. Let's go. I'm gonna try to get a huge amount
I thought you went to harvard if you were born in boston
No, not everybody born in boston goes to harvard. It's just a thing that people say that are from boston
So you think that they're smarter than they actually are?
Yeah, we got harvard here. You didn't go there. Yes. Well, I know but it's here. I mean we're all intelligent here
That's not what it means. You didn't go to harvard
Yeah, throw it away. Oh my god. I try to throw it away
Fuck I need another do that again
Jeremy you're bad at this dude. It's how fucking hard this is annoying
This is not this is like a ton of brain power. It's like it hurts my head
Look, not everybody that lives in boston went to harvard. Okay, we just went over it
Fuck fuck brought it back. That's 50 cases. I'm good. By the way, all of us went to harvard every single one of us
Oh, I just wasted like five hundred thousand dollars
God damn it who wanted this?
I gotta go to tangiers. Okay, whatever
I don't have any more quests. I did everything i'm the fucking master of chocolates
Time for you to meet another board member time for you to go to san francisco
You need to meet with a woman who was responsible for the early success of the company
All right
San francisco is unlocked
Let's go. Wait, what am I missing? I need to do yeah breakfast blend. What are you dumb?
Go to capetown
Why is san francisco in alaska?
Is it I hate that
Did I not even get credit for those?
What happened there?
Why am I not getting credit for these?
Bonus before or more i'm gonna get 30. Come on. Come on. All right. That's fine. I can just go forever
Tokyo is making uh pecan infusions
They're gonna have to make like a thousand of them for me to make any money back now
We have to go to san francisco, but first we're gonna go to tangier. I'm out of honey. Oh shit. You're right
Tidings silly zonka bonka
Soup market has recently begun stocking cloves here in town and I understand that you have heard
There are wonderful mango to be had in cameroon
I've been saving an infusion recipe for you
It offers a unique combination of those very two ingredients. I'll give you the recipe you bring me 40 cases
Sounds good
Holy shit. All right. I got a lot of breakfast blends. That's holy shit. That's gonna save my life here
Breakfast blend isn't gonna save us
I'm not gonna sell it. Yeah, i'm gonna hold it. I'm gonna wait till I have like
200 cases
All right, isn't there something here that I wanted?
What did I want here?
Not meg
What am I doing here? What do I want here?
Oh, okay
Where is she?
Look out
I didn't know this existed
Your proficient infusions as well. You're doing quite well over there for bowmeister confections. I hope they are treating you well silly
nice
Greetings friend. I happen to have on hand a hundred sacks of honey
An ingredient not easily had these days
And hearing good things about your prowess at turning ingredients into chocolate
I'll tell you what
I'll give you my 100 sacks of honey if you agree to bring me 25 cases of chocolate bars with honey at your earliest convenience
Well, isn't that funny?
Because I literally have them on me right now
Thank you
I have no ingredients for chocolate bars
Just keep
No, I need nutmeg
Nutmeg nutmeg nutmeg nutmeg
Tons of it haggle
You take me for a fool
You do whatever
All right. What's the actual recipe that I feel like this is gonna make a ton of money
Colombian cocoa honey nutmeg and whiskey i'm gonna go make start making this but first i'm gonna go to san francisco
Oh cool. All right
market street market
Welcome i'm so glad to see your old company back in the black as it were
You know, I personally have always been partial to truffles
I have no doubt that you'll earn my endorsement
I want to make sure you can handle their ins and outs and you've been able to collect all 12 recipes for truffles
Has taken ownership of a third shop. You'll earn my nod
san francisco chocolates
Makers are here in town has already set up to make truffles
My nephew chas
Is running things over there and he has even implemented that newfangled recycle that was developed in zurich. Here's a recipe for white chocolate truffles
a lot of ingredients
Bring me a case from your first batch of white chocolate truffles and we'll take things from there
By the way, you'll now find the truffle powder you need for truffles everywhere. Cocoa is sold. Okay, let's
Got truffle powder here
I need milk
I need truffle powder
watering hole
All right. Well, I can't do anything here. I need to go to
All right. We got to go back to tokyo
um
Where can I get some honey? Oh, no. All right. We're gonna go to kona
I'm gonna sell some shit
Oh, yeah, that's that's two. I just saw 240 000. I didn't care what it was was lime
cashews gross
Academia nuts
All right, there's truffle powder haggle you're nuts
I'm running low on capital here
Oh damn
That was worth it. Talk the parts with honey. Honey is going up
That's a good. That's a good haul
Breakfast blend is going to be a major sale
I have it. I how many how many what does he want?
Now hold these
That's that's too cheap
And you let us bet on something. I need to feel something
Jesus
This is going to be a huge money here
I'm gonna hold it though. All right back up to 1.2 million you want
68 cases of dark chocolate cocoa lime infusions
I have 62 so that's going to be very easy to do
Sweet and spicy
I need to make truffles
All right, it's all about making the last thing of lime
And then starting to start the truffles
I need milk. I still need milk. How I 500 milk. What the hell are you talking about?
Back to san francisco
Here we go. All right, use this recipe
Oh my god, this is gonna be hell
What this is horrible?
Oh, no guys
Oh boy
And it's color-coded
Um, okay
Uh, what's left? I don't even know what's left
Milk over who needs milk
Who needs I don't even I don't know what anybody needs
um
What the can somebody take one of these?
This is horrendous
Everything takes two snowballs
One meatball
I don't really I know recycle but look see I can't recycle because fucking thing spins around it gets in the way
I just tried to
Uh here
No
Meatball milk who needs milk you do you?
You who needs a meatball who needs a meatball anybody need a meatball?
Meatball who needs a meatball?
This shit is hard
Okay here here
Uh here here
Right there
Right there over this way you got it already there bang. Okay. Good. Keep going
Milk right here milk right here
Meatball here
Uh, I need uh this way this way this way
That way
This way that way
This way recycle
Get the fuck out of the way
Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. That's on look at it. I can't
How am I supposed to decide you can't recycle it's impossible not on this to be comparable thing
Oh my god. Damn it. This sucks
I I gotta have it be at least 20
I gotta lean all the way back for this
people here
Right there right there milk milk milk milk milk milk
Two right? Yep
meatball
Milk who needs milk?
Um
you
You you
Need a meatball over here blue meatball bad
Blue meatball need it bad
Come on. Where's the meatballs?
Where are the meatballs?
What the fuck?
Whatever 21 cases
Gordon Ramsey
Where are the meatballs? Where are the meatballs? These fucking meatballs are terrible you donkey
Uh, look raw disgusting
fucking donkey
21 is fine. I don't care
You wanted the first batch?
Here are the handful of truffle truffle reference whatever i'm trying to even say I don't even care cool bowser bowser treat
Bowser treat
I thought that was raw meat for a second
Uh, here's the deal each of the other members of the board of directors some of whom you've met
Some of whom you haven't is holding a truffle recipe for you
We need to present each member with a case of truffles to exchange to their recipe
The tricky part is you need to figure out which recipe goes with which board member. Oh boy
Each of the ingredients you will need to make each of the five truffle recipes are at a market somewhere
What the hell are you trying to tell me to do?
Travel to toronto and wellington now where you'll meet the remaining members of the board
Each board member will yell you know and give you you know around but how do I know what they like?
When you show up with the correct type of truffle in your inventory
Whatever go to hell
How many do I have 21?
But for now I got to do the lime
I'm gonna get lime chocolates
Yeah, let's go do let's get the lime thing ready
Well, this is the i'm almost done with my shitty pecan investment
Go ahead and change it to that so I can and then where does he where does he live?
Uh pagoda and then we're gonna go we're gonna just go to toronto and then wellington see what happens
Thank you. It's like three hundred thousand dollars
That's that done
I need to get 11 truffle recipes
40 cases of mango clove infusions
mango clove, huh
a clove
I need mango
Who sells mangoes?
I don't know 100 million if you do the truffle shuffle
I'm not gonna do the truffle shuffle. Sorry
I have 100 strawberries. All right
back to tokyo
No, I need to have some type of chocolate production going here. All right, i'm gonna do raspberries
There are raspberries here. They're not raspberries here. What the hell even is here?
pumpkin chocolate
Hazelnut i'm gonna do hazelnut chocolate. Let's just buy a shitload of this
Yeah, just use this one
And that's a horrible are you kidding me do I really have to travel back there to make that better?
I was thinking about it. I was all right toronto
big town market
Nothing really here
waterfront sweets
It's true. Indeed. I'm holding onto a truffle recipe for you
And it's also true. I'm looking for you to have a particular truffle on hand before i'm willing to hand it over
Okay, these are still worth a lot
Breakfast blend. All right. I gotta
I gotta say I gotta go to breakfast blend
dark chocolate pecan infusions
I gotta dump a bunch of stuff. I have to sell
All my quests are done
Yeah time to sell a huge bunches time to dump
Oh
As long as you're using an ingredient at one of the factories it will not expire
After a number of weeks of not using it. However, the ingredient will expire. Okay, that makes sense
I need to go sell
Let's take a trip to uh, let's go to tangiers
I'm gonna dump everything especially the coffee here. Look at this
bang
680 000 dollars
And I still can keep making it. It'll just produce money forever
Uh back to oh shit go to kona
I represent a rival chocolate maker chocolade weltrich
Perhaps you've heard of us
I understand you're making a good name for yourself with this business
But in terms of alex and her personal problems, why are you poking your nose into business that's got nothing to do with you?
Uh, hey wiggly joe. Thanks for the 25 community subs. Thanks for the 25 subs, dude
Appreciate it. Thank you. It's a lot of subs
I gotta get to five million
Eat the breakfast blend here
Oh, no, just sell it. I got enough. Yeah
You're gonna be a five million subs. No, not five million subs. I want to get to five million dollars
That's a lot. All right that can
I i'm
Hala
Yeah
All right. I have enough i'm
Going back to cave town. I can this can be better
28 that's not enough. I can get that to like 50
Give me a case of delightfully sweet try. All right make this coffee
Come on, I can do better than this
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry, go. Go. Go. Go
Come on, give me something
I didn't want to do that again. I can do it again chevra
Come on connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected connected
What's that? 40? All right, that's 37. What was it before? 20 something? 21, 22, 37. Whoa!
Are there hot dogs? Because this game sucks. I'm sorry. I don't know what's wrong with me tonight.
I don't know what's wrong with me. I'm just like in a weird mood.
I've been in a weird mood all day, haven't I? I want sugar. Gotta get to five million dollars.
Is your hazelnut? Is your hazelnut chocolate? That's good. I can produce money forever.
I'm gonna keep my breakfast blend up. This, however, needs to change.
Ginger. Let's go to Tokyo. Yeah, how about we discuss a reasonable price? Fine. Let's just produce some...
I've got a recipe for you. All right. This is dark chocolate with ginger. Let's do it. What happened to digging for gold?
I think it just sucked. I didn't get a chance to make it. Oh, for the love of God. What a shitty RNG again.
Terrible RNG. Just awful. Really awful. It's truly terrible RNG. Like, what a disaster.
Let's do it again. Much better. Much better RNG. So much better! Oh, it's like the God run.
Come on. Something, something. Please, please, please. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right. 40 cases a week. That's good. Let's get a shitload of ginger. That'll produce for a long time.
They are worth a lot. So that's good.
Breakfast blend is still just cranking out at 37 per week. Hazelnut chocolate bar. Look at all these white truffles.
I can just sell them. All right. So here's the plan. We're gonna go get more Bolognese and Colombian coffee.
Finally found the mangoes.
There they are. Finally.
What was it? Mango what? Mango clove.
Have 100 clove. Let's get a bunch of cloves. Let's do it. Let's buy it. Let's make a ton of these.
I'm gonna get 500 cloves, 500 mangoes.
Can you do something for me with these prices? God damn it. We're gonna make a shitload of those.
So mango clove infusion.
I'm just gonna make a ton.
Oh, these are going. They'll be going for a little while. We can sell the hell out of them.
I feel like Jerm is streaming this game to himself.
I mean, I'm just trying to play the game. I'm trying to make money here.
I'm streaming.
I'm just like talking. I'm not even streaming. I'm just like, okay, so we're gonna go over this way.
He read chat for once. Yeah, I'm making big fucking bucks about two million dollars. I'm up to two mil.
Chats are sitting here doing Jupiters.
Yeah, well chat's just sitting there doing Jupiters. I'm making big money.
I got almost 200 breakfast blends. Are you kidding me?
Now we're gonna go get uh, Colombian coffee.
To Bogota we go. Honestly, it's been five hours. I feel like I've been sitting here for 10 minutes.
This is his new favorite game.
It's a new yeah, a new mango. All right, let's keep that going. I'm gonna go to sell
in Kona.
It's over here.
This is my new favorite game. This is like my new favorite. It is
close.
All right, check this shit out.
Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. You guys ready to cross at least the three million mark?
Here it comes.
Look at this breakfast blend. Dark chocolate infusion with ginger.
Let's cross three million. What do you say?
Don't sell this here. The coffee shop guy has a better price.
Yeah, coffee shop guy has a much better price.
Whatever. I just messed up. I was gonna do 200, but I did 320. Don't care.
The rain streamer is panic selling all of his stocks. I want to go change the recipe to this.
So we have to go to Tokyo. First we're gonna take a stop in Cape Town. No, why am I going to Cape Town?
Where are the new recipes coming from? I don't know. I didn't want to go here.
Messed up.
Over three million dollars.
Today was supposed to be a fun connect stream, not some shitty chocolate game I'd find on my grandma's PC. Band that person.
Or at least an hour.
No, you know what? We'll dial it back to
20 minutes. You have to face the truth.
What?
I'd like the chocolate money making simulator.
If I'm playing connect tomorrow, it's okay. Look.
This is not okay.
I didn't say guys today we're gonna play chocolatier again. Oh, and by the way, I've burnt the connect.
I put it into a giant fucking steel trash can along with all the connect games and I light them on fire.
I smashed it. I stomped on it like grapes and I made fucking connect wine. That didn't happen.
It's right behind me. We're doing it tomorrow.
But now
I'm
enjoying making chocolates and getting five million dollars.
So here's what happens. Once I get to five million dollars, I'm going to go gamble until I get to 10 million or turn the stream off.
That's what's gonna happen. I'm gonna save it first because I like this game. It's kind of fun.
So now we gotta we gotta do the- what are you doing Otto? Almost running out of breakfast blend. Let's take it. We'll go to Tokyo.
Yeah, I want to do the mango.
Oh, nice Otto. I want to sneeze. I'm not about to sneeze.
Here we go. This is gonna be a big big money maker I got. I'm gonna make 500 of these. I need snowballs.
They're trying to make it harder on me. They're trying to make it harder.
Shit. Okay. Come on. Get me higher than 50 cases. I just need the cases.
51 cases. Bingo. There we are. 51 cases. Time to go
turn this in to Tangiers. Breakfast blend.
Come on, give me five million.
You silly zonkawonka. You're a gifted chocolatier. Here's the recipe I mentioned.
It may be a while before you can get a hold of all these specialty Cocos, but it'll be worth it.
Ooh blended cocoa dark chocolate infusion.
I'm not- I don't- where's Peruvian cocoa? Oh need more Moroccan coffee. No, we don't.
I need Bolognese and Colombian. Bolognese and Colombian. Okay, Bolognese coffee. I need hazelnuts.
Fuck, that wasn't a hazelnut. That was a nutmeg.
That's a lot.
Can we make a nutmeg chocolate by any chance?
Oh, thank god digging for gold is nutmeg. I need hazelnuts.
All right, Bolognese coffee, Colombian coffee.
Go.
Uh, give me better deal where I'm getting out. No.
God damn it. I need it. I have to do it. I- it's- I'm gonna- I'll make it back. I need it.
We need Colombian coffee. You got owned. I did.
Okay, maybe he won't be mad at me anymore if I go back there. Let's see.
Can you haggle somebody until they give up on their business?
Oh fuck, let's go to Wellington. I haven't even been here yet.
I didn't even give up on their business. You're doing swell silly zonkawonka and I very much look forward to working with you soon to launch our exotics.
God.
What do you mean launch your exotics?
Past the whiskey. It's all- wait, it went bad.
I had 500 whiskey and it went bad.
I bought these for like
$200,000.
I'm very bad at this, but it's still fun. It doesn't matter. I'm just losing money.
Hand over fist. Whatever that saying is.
Should've done some good success.
What else do I have to do here?
All right, here we go.
I'm going all the way back to flying across the whole world. You seem to be in a big hurry.
Three million, four million. Let's go.
Come on.
Four million coming on. There's so many truffles.
That's four million. I'm- we're almost there.
Somebody tell you the casino guy looks like you.
The raid? Did I sell everything? Was there a raid? It was. From the gray fruit.
Hey, I got- I got plenty of gray fruits on me right now. Thanks for the raid, dude. Take a look. Wait, that's not gray.
That's- do I have a gray fruit? I thought I had a gray fruit. Well, this one's kind of gray. Thanks for the raid.
Welcome everybody.
We are getting, uh, to- we're trying to get to five million dollars in the chocolate game.
And in the chocolate game, when you get to five million dollars, you go to the casino and you spend it so you get to 10,
or you turn the stream off. That's what's gonna happen. You're losing your vision? That's gray right there.
I didn't say the whole fruit was gray. That's- this is gray. Right there is gray. That's not green. What are you talking about?
This is
orange, like a red orange
into a peach color into gray.
Are you- is your computer screen okay? That's not green. That's not- that's gray. That's like a- that's like- what are you talking about?
That's not green. Are you- okay. That's green. That's gray.
This is green. That's gray. This is green. That's gray. How is this- how is what- where my cursor is right now?
How is it green? That's not green? You guys have liars. You're just fucking with me.
All right, what was I even doing? Oh, right, right, right, right, right. Getting to- getting to five million dollars.
What- okay, I need to- truffles, truffles, truffles, truffles, truffles, truffles, truffles, truffles. Here we are.
All right, I want to make the Bowser one. Spicy current truffles. I'm going to currents cayenne peppers.
I'm going to go to Wellington. Wellington, we're going to do this. Screen cap it and eyedrop tool and paint it.
Look at the RGB value. One of you will do it and then I- I'm gladly- we'll show it on stream.
What are you crazy? Okay, is that what I needed? Two hundred, two hundred,
six thousand, six thousand, seven hundred. All right, I need a button. I'm gonna get five hundred, five hundred, five hundred.
Let's go for- how many do I have? Come on, one more. This- this is gonna be the big ticket. Now I need powder.
It's hex zero, zero. Put your money where your mouth is. Let's be a hundred million that it's green according to an RGB value.
But here's the thing though. What if it is green on the RGB scale, but it's like a gray green?
Take- the RGB is
has- is hash.
Hold on. Green is- that's still green. But wait, wait, hold on. But if it's- if it's green-
But if it's gray too, then why am I wrong?
How come you get to be right if it's green in there, but I get to be wrong if there's gray in there?
That's not fair.
Because it's green.
Why can't it be- I can't be both color? It's green. It's gray. Life isn't fair.
You said it was gray. Show it to me. Give me the RGB value. I want to see it. Gray isn't a color, buddy. Oh, sorry.
Sorry. Gray is not a color, I guess.
It's- what is it? Five five something? Give me one sec. I'm all tapping for this.
It is
hash five five?
Oh, do me again? Turning links on. Does anybody have it? Five e-
Five e five seven three d. Is that a lie? Is that the right one? Five e five seven three d. Bullshit. That's not even right.
That's not even correct.
That's a troll color. You're fucking with me.
That's not what color- that's not the right color. By the way, that's like yellow.
That's not even- you guys were- you guys were wrong. If you think it's that one, that's yellow.
It's five five- somebody got the right one. Let me see it.
Five five five twenty three e.
I don't- no, that's not right. You just picked it.
Give a discord- I want a- I want an image. I demand it. I command it. You changed- that's not what it looks like on my screen.
Can I screenshot mine? Is my color wrong on my computer?
It doesn't look like this on my screen. That doesn't look like that. Why is yours way darker?
Does it look like that?
Mine is- mine's way lighter than that.
I'm gonna take a screenshot. Everybody hold on a second. Print screen.
Hold on. I'm gonna put this up next to this.
I feel like this is- I think that this is- this is- this is a lie. Hold on. A crop? Is it the same picture?
Um, so the- my monitor- my monitor's colors are
fucked up bad. It is not- it is incredibly- it's five times lighter when I look at it. Boy.
This is the image I just took.
And in fact, I think this is darker.
All right, but just do me a favor. Do me a quick little favor here, and I know you say green, green, green.
Green, green, green. But what is right- what is that? What's that right there?
That little sliver there? That little white area? What is that? What color could be in there?
Gray. My monitor's fucked. It's way lighter on my screen.
That's mold.
Whatever. I don't even care.
I was- all right. Well, a good thing I didn't bet- I didn't bet any money.
What- what the fuck happened? How did we get here? What's going on? Why am I doing this right now?
Why do I care about the grapefruit?
Oh, that's somebody's name! That's somebody raided the channel! Hey, that was the grapefruit raided the channel!
Thanks for the raid, dude. Appreciate it. We're gonna, uh, keep going. Close that out. All right, let's make this bigger.
Oh shit, I have to close this.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
All right, we're back. What was the last thing that I just did?
All right, I need a shitload of truffle powder, and I'm good to go.
Truffle powder. Give it to me. Who's got it?
This'll take us
over five billion,
and then-
Oh, yep. This'll take us over five million, and I'm ready to spend money. Let's go back to Tokyo.
Tokyo. No, San Francisco, right? San Frans- no, we need to go to Tokyo for a second.
San Francisco. So in Tokyo, I wanted to do this.
I got a recipe for you. Whatever.
I need
strawberry shit.
Whatever. This was a wasted trip. I didn't mean to come here.
And then mangoes in Tokyo?
I need mangoes.
We're gonna get mangoes. Who's got mangoes?
Who's got mangoes?
Wellington.
Raid song. What raid? For what?
Now we're going off into San Francisco.
No, get out of here. I'm only working with big bucks now. Let's go make the- go to the chocolate building.
Change recipe. We're making the spicy Bowser.
Oh, fuck you.
Sell all this?
That's a lot to sell here.
400,000. Back over 400.
Breakfast blend. That's a good sale here.
4.3 million.
Ever closer to 5.0 million. We'll get there right now. Watch this.
Trying to make insane truffles. Back to San Francisco.
Bang.
Spicy.
Spicy current truffles. Let's go for it. This is the hard one.
Meatball. It's two, uh, these. One of these.
And then a snowball.
How we doing? How we doing?
Good. Snowball over here.
Current over here.
Pepper. Pepper. Pepper. We already got a pepper over there. Throw it away. I need to throw that away, too.
Pepper over here.
And then we got, uh, boom. Good.
Current.
Um...
Shit. Oh, it's alright.
I need a ball over there. What am I missing? What am I missing? What am I missing? Pepper.
Oh my god. This is impossible.
This is impossible.
Uh...
Meatball. Pepper. Pepper. Pepper. Pepper. Pepper. Pepper. Pepper. Current. Current. Current. Current.
current current current current current current current current snowball snowball snowball
you said snowball snowball snowball snowball snowball current current current current current
i sound like i'm playing fucking counter strike hurry hurry hurry whatever 35 is good i need more
sugar all right that is going to be a huge money maker i need to go we get to do coffee again
so i gotta go get what do i need bolognese and columbian coffee let's go get columbian coffee
go here and then go to bali and then we're going back to tokyo and then i'm gonna have
five million i'm gonna go gamble fuck you you didn't sing the raid song who raided the fact
that you're actually enjoying this game is hilarious somebody said why can't you kill
somebody oh okay sorry there's no like explosions kill someone holy fuck these are worth so much
money i'm gonna be more than five million guys i should just sleep for a week and wake up and sell
mangoes and hold on mangoes and hold on can i buy these here i need mangoes let's go get some
mangoes we need to go to wellington and then get coffee and then we need to go to bali wellington
yeah nice give me that bolognese coffee this is going to be the trillion dollar sale
uh out of hazelnuts well what can we make instead honey mint reserve raspberries
we'll go to wellington on to wellington by we're okay now we just have to make money
do a poll that says we do a poll to decide who likes this game um okay fine i'll do a poll who
in the room in here currently that's sitting at the desk likes the game i do and who's currently
streaming the game i am done so that's it i'm done i did it should i go i need to make at
least some kind of chocolate or something come on lemons honey yeah let's get some honey let me just
fuck over here honey start making that look at this just cash rolling in here this is gonna be
insane i'm not i don't even want to look at the price right now because i want to be surprised
when it's a million dollars okay bali back to bali you played this more than yakuza well look
if yakuza if it was just the one giant minigame and no fighting i probably would play it
and that's not even true by the way i played yakuza three times this is twice all right now
we just collect money we just make a shit load of money i spent 1.5 million dollars to get here
we're at the end game now peter game almost crashed to punish me for doing what i just did
and saying what i just said all right now we're going to fly um yes we're going to fly between
bugata and havana for like six times i'm gonna make so much money low on sugar let's see what
happens are you ready are you ready for the big oh yeah this is gonna be wild oh shit no no not
yet not yet not yet not yet now we do it we're gonna go small first i have 11 hazelnut chocolate
bars that's 10 grand i have 207 honey chocolate bars 185 000 i have 370 cases of breakfast blend
which as you can see this is goddamn our first ever 1.0 million dollar sale i've got holy shit
i've got 600 cases of mango clove infused infusions we're at 5.0 million and that's
not even it this is the big boy here we have one two three four 455 cases this is 1.8 million
dollars our goal of 5.0 million is crushed we're at seven million dollars okay i'm not done i want
i'm making i'm getting this 10 million hold on everybody we got a huge money maker here
we're gonna go get sugar doesn't matter how much it costs who cares we need i got honey i got plenty
of honey i need this weird fucking powder doesn't matter how much it costs who cares
i get 500 of them i need mangoes this is this stuff sells like crazy i need peppers
currants we need coffee i need where can i get these bali bali wellington wellington and bali
is where i need to go we need a balinese blend anyways okay mangoes damn these are expensive
what god damn it worth it we need hot peppers we gotta go to wellington god damn those were
expensive what the fuck columbian coffee have i already gone through the 5000 holy shit i got
5000 beans for free really do you feel good or what yeah i feel pretty good peppers here we go
okay it's time to do the final sale we need columbian i'm gonna stop to get columbian coffee
on the way to kona this is not even what i need what do i need no it is what i need why
oh this is cuban coffee fuck i need columbian coffee not cuban coffee shit nothing about the
militaries involved i'm almost a 10 million i don't care all right now i need sugar this is
gonna be massive i need mangoes again all right we're gonna fly to get mangoes
so i have no idea it's gonna be a thousand i'm gonna be i'm gonna have to sell a thousand of
these back to uh begota and then we're gonna go and fly and this is it this is the final haul
that's it done fly back and forth from havana to begota and then we're selling i think i'm gonna
have like a thousand of each thing this will put me somewhere around 10 million and then that's it
i beat the game otherwise that was my goal i don't even care if i'm the ceo that's a lot of money
cinnamon no i'm gonna get to 10 million i'm gonna save the game and then i'm gonna gamble and try
to get to 100 to 100 million and we 10x by gambling i'm gonna save the game to see if we do it
this is it what do we got i went from seven something million to 4.6 oh lord okay here's
your uh chocolate with honey breakfast blend 1.4 million just from the breakfast blend
is the mango infusion 1.3 million from the mango infusion this is it does this get us to 10 million
it's gonna be really close oh no wait wait wait wait wait oh
can i do i have enough for anything just to make anything while i fly around here i can't make any
coffee what about infusions can i make any infusion no almonds no cherries no nothing
i have to see the 10 million i have to see this i can't do it i have to see no i'm not gambling
yet i have to see the 10 million number i'm going and i'm just buying coffee coffee coffee coffee
coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee coffee just just 500 coffees there you go now we're gonna
get balinese coffee then columbian coffee okay i just have to see the 10 million balinese coffee
this is it this is good we're gonna be fine now that should be enough we're gonna get a ton of
coffees from this and i'm selling it at the coffee shop that's a that's a huge premium
why from zurek back and forth doesn't matter we're gonna we're gonna just make a million
dollars right now can you do an easter egg hunt stream this year um i don't know probably not
way too much going on maybe all your ingredients are expiring uh i don't really have any i got
rid of most of them i've been using them all imagine your boss flying back and forth while
you make coffee for him well in the plane here we go price went up yes 10 million 500 thousand
dollars hooray i did it 10 million i win okay now let's go gamble it all away i'm saving the
game because i like playing this and maybe i'll play it again off stream well i'm like
you know freshening up a little bit give me one second i'm just gonna save the game
aim is now saved okay hold on coming back and now i'm gonna see if i can turn 10 million into a
hundred million uh by playing the box game let's uh let's see what happens and then that's gonna
be the stream and i will see you guys tomorrow for connect we're gonna start with a very very
important one i'm gonna start with connectimals i would argue is probably the most important
connect game that i did not play the game crashed when i opened it okay here we go 10 million
dollars going to las vegas let's go golden dollar i can do one million dollar spin or i can do
i can do a one million dollar box search or a one million dollar spin there's five million dollars
here okay done done done take it take it take it take it take it away we're at 11 million 1.1
million dollar spin hot dogs okay wait i broke even we got three hot dogs do it again people
broke even again 1.1 million dollars spin come on something huge coin okay that was
that was almost 10 million dollars we're at 20 million dollars this is now a two million
dollar spin or i could do okay you can only do a one million dollar box let's do it almost
1.8 million dollars spin coins coins 30 million dollars 30 million i'm saving the game i'm saving
the game i want to start with 30 million if i play this again okay i wonder if i keep saves coming
can i get to a billion dollars forget about being a a chocolatier what if i just make a billion
dollars by playing slot machines this is gonna be like a five million dollar spin all right let's
go three million dollar spin coffee coffee yeah good good good good good 35 million let's go
3.5 million dollar spin coffee oh oh that was done come on bangos broke even three and a half
million dollars come on give me those coins okay that's 28 million fucking dollars we're at 52
million 52 million save the game if i can get to 100 million doing this cool i mean honestly this
is safe scumming but i haven't really needed to use the save scum yet notice that that doesn't
happen it auto saves it definitely does not auto save it can't i don't believe it it's a grandma
game yeah it's a member of the grandma game thing all right let's go 52 million dollars what's the
next spin 5.2 million dollar spin three two one go bangos mangos yeah 60 million let's do another
one a six million dollar spin do it again coffee coffee do it again honey honey oh broke even with
that many honeys fucking machines rigged oh that many coins come on another six million
coins coffee oh we're losing bad here we just need one huge one coffee beans we're good that's
that's 15 million again parents we're staying alive we're back at it 42 million let's go
honey coins coins coins oh man coins
oh yeah
we're all you probably didn't believe in the machine we're back six million dollars
over what we came in with 6.6 million dollars spent there it is broken come on points coin
oh come on come on no no no no no no mangoes more mangoes
oh shit okay we got uh hot peppers we need a bunch of coins coins pepper yes we're not we're still
doing just fine the house always wins yeah here we go 63 million i told you i have the game saved
i'm going for 100 million come on i need one line of coins and with a six million dollar bet and
it'll be over there it is okay there it is i went 100 million dollars goodbye see you later that's
fucking 100 million that's a 100 million dollars in my bank account right now good
you didn't trust it you gotta trust the machine sometimes you can only do one million dollars in
the box 100 million steve steve get over here well okay how about we'll do now because i won
i beat the game i win we're gonna do a 10 million dollar spin why stop there why not go for a
billion why not go for a billion why not do a 17 million dollar spin and go for a fucking billion
dollars what do you say about that that's fucking pure mango right there i'm looking for currents
all right we're taking this down to 100 million and i'm done currents it's all right we're taking
this down to 100 million we're good there it is we're good 166 million dollars 60 million dollar
spins let's go points 282 million dollars how about a 28 million dollar spin what about that
what do you say about that video game okay we're almost 300 million dollars you have been thrown
out of the casino by now that you're gone you're you're long gone coins coins 500 million dollars
yeah it's uh yeah it's jeremy uh jeremy uh well you know all of us on the board uh we're thinking
making you ceo but we want you to do various tasks could you give me 60 cases of hang up on
that fucking guy i'm not going to talk to these people ever again i'm not even going to fucking
reach out to you anymore i'm done i'm out of here it's a 50 million dollar spin snowball we're at
552 million dollars 55 million dollar spin we just need coins just coins all around the
line as a billion dollars come on give us the billion give us the billion give us the billion
give us the billion we ain't leaving till we get to a billion points we ain't leaving
come on big money hello uh jeremy uh look just find another ceo don't fuck yourself i'll give
you 50 million dollars to take the company wherever you want don't ever call me again
meatballs oh come on come on we need one big one we're staying alive again a line of coins
right now is what we need no no no no no no no no no come on come on come on come on come on come
on come on okay that gives us 55 million we can do it again no balls we're good we're good we're
good everything's fine save the game one more and i'll save the game hang on come on yeah
coins meatballs back up to 500 million save it save the game i'll be right back
save game we're gonna get to a billion dollars it's gonna i'm gonna hit it honestly what kind
of absolute psycho would you have to be to have 500 million dollars and do 55 million dollar spins
like at some point you should probably take 100 million just take like 150 million and just
bury it like in like the backyard just bury a check to yourself for a hundred million dollars
put it in a different bank account so you can't use it all right let's go we ain't leaving till
a billion you heard it here first you know you don't think i'm gonna stop at 400 fucking million
dollars nope let's go coffees coffees bingo we're back to 500 million all it takes is one
major coin pull and we're done it's all right it's okay bangos oh come on give us another one we're
gonna get to a billion come on there it is 700 million dollars hold on a second i gotta make
i gotta make a few phone calls hello this is uh greg's chocolates hey greg yeah it's your
rival from down the street you know from boom onto yours chocolates i don't even i'm shit
faced right now i don't even know the name of my own fucking chocolate company greg hey how many
how many outstanding shares do you have uh last time i checked i think we had five to ten million
outstanding shares well guess who just put an order in for market buying all of them tomorrow
morning um i don't know i don't know jeremy who was it it was me mr fucking green my first name
is jeremy apparently i see you in the morning when i make the decision i'm gonna start having you guys
make fucking ice cream cones made out of paper and then you're gonna liquidate you oh that's great
thanks a lot yeah fuck you too that's what you get for spitting in my coffee 20 years ago
asshole 71 million spin please fucking count it give me that come on 71 million a spin and that's a coin
oh
that's a billion dollars why even play the game anymore i can't even what am i gonna do i know
what i'm gonna do oh i know exactly what i'm gonna do you know exactly what i'm gonna do with my money
my billion dollars i know exactly what the plan is hey remember me you can't do you even have this
lines one two three four five there's a hundred thousand lines i can't even put any that's all
that that's all the room they have no i don't want zero no i don't want zero why is it zero
that's 3.1 million lines hey and get yourself something nice i've got so many drugs
when did i end up where am i how much money do i have my wallet 120 dollars
the fuck am i excuse me what state am i in um you're in the middle of australia what are
you talking about mike australia oh i have to go with interest this is why he's green
that's all he's eaten for the last 25 years you just eat a shitload of limes he's lit he was
living off of limes somewhere in the outback of australia and like had to catch like rabbits and
stuff do we have a deal yeah jesus christ 3.1 million lines where do you put all those
wait she's just giving me money hold on a minute wait a minute you're in another pickle i see i'm
able to help i'll loan you 5 000 you will owe me 10 000 i will loan you 5 000 but you must repay me
20 000 okay listen i realize that the only way i can hope to see any return on my loan is to help
you once again i'm not happy about this here's another 2500 here's another 2500 okay listen
here's another 2500 five more lines listen here's another 2500 i'm gonna give you another 2500 don't
buy any more lines please what do you say buy lines and market value here's another 2500
make sure you have 70 how much do i owe her all right i need a few more limes
i'm done with the limes yeah i need i thank you for the 2500 yes thank you i'll get back on my feet
thank you wait is this her i thought she met me there i can make it back to a billion if i want to
oh shit come on yeah all right so i i made a billion dollars on like december like 29th 2020
and like like january like a second 2021 comes around and i buy a million limes
i have i have like a 400 million dollar tax bill that i don't have there we go don't tell me she
gives it to you again can i just sit here and gamble forever that's a good start she's just
depositing money into my account i could just say forever why is she doing this oh my god i'm
gonna get back to it if i get to a billion dollars again i'm gonna shit my pants oh i think she does
that forever there we go there we go i cannot fucking believe i got to a billion dollars in
the game like i now i even play the game ever again i've had a billion that's so stupid you're
financially ruining this person look i'm just trying to hit the big bucks buy a billion dollars
of every ingredient i keep losing she wants to give you infinite loans all right we're going
for the box all right it is the same person it's the same lady it is it's the same it's the same
lady it's the same person loaning me money what's going on wait what's happening right now
wait i thought i thought this was i thought this was the i thought that was alex from the beginning
of the game that's i thought she was like oh hey why did she call me i was in australia i ran out
of money and the casino person called me what i thought that was the person that i did the work
for that was like oh you're down on your luck i know you're running out of money you're supposed
to making all these chocolate factories and i told you too i thought that that was like a i'm
why is it the casino person you called me in australia after i bought limes how did you know
my phone number and why does she keep giving me money she's just getting it back this is money
laundering all right but am i insane or i when i bought the billion dollars worth of limes i got
a phone call from her that was like oh we know what you're up to you're doing that was what the
fuck is happening my brain is fried you don't even have a cell phone she had to telegram
without the lime lady she had to send a telegram to the lime person check your quests wait wait a
minute have ten thousand dollars have twenty thousand what what if i don't pay her back
i'm out of here i'm going i'm flying to cuba i'm going to cuba hey everybody here in evanna i got
three and a half million limes we can do whatever the fuck we want with these just take them we can
use them for anything we can build we can like we can i don't know we can use them what do we
use them for i don't know i probably should have 2020 hindsight probably should have uh probably
should have got like milk and like something i don't know sell the limes you can't sell limes
we're gonna be lime city oh what you got a casino here ah of course can i use limes to play the slot
machine make a lime recipe that's only limes oh my god oh wait okay i just paid her 7500
and then she just paid me 2500 she just paid me another 2500 she gave me another 2500
what is your lady what the fuck is wrong with you what i so badly want to do this and just make
like a thousand of them come on i need to get another spot no i can't delete a spot i can't
make just a fucking all lime truffle i need truffle powder flavors where's truffle powder
do a new bar i can't i don't have any more slots and i can't delete slots i i have to do this whole
quest it's gonna take hours come on really you have to fill all the uh come on start over your
lime locked load the save i didn't make my own truffle yet i didn't unlock it see i have not
unlocked the uh the truffle load the old save my old my old save didn't have the billion dollars
you owe me ten thousand dollars if i were you i'd get the dough together
just reminder you owe me twenty thousand dollars i'll find you this is a friendly reminder uh you
owe me ten thousand dollars i'll be seeing you around just reminder you owe me ten thousand
dollars get that dough you owe me twenty thousand i'm gonna find you you owe me ten thousand i'll be
seeing you around hey uh neat lime get the dough together yeah i i'm gonna find you what do i buy
like a fucking gun or something to protect myself i gotta hide somewhere just coming after me with
like hitmen i'll find you okay sure you will i'm like one of those famous people on earth i'm the
guy that made a billion dollars in three days and then bought a billion dollars worth of limes i've
been all over the news and you'll know where i am maybe she can't find me if i just fucking
fly everywhere i got a private jet she won't find me she's just following me around that wait hold
on hold on wait a second that was one billion dollars in 1952 what's that now was it was it
was there even a billionaire in 1950 what would that be was there billionaires in like 1930 1940
ten billion dollars is howard hughes what was howard hughes worth back in like 1940 1950
rockefeller was before that how much was was rockefeller worth he was worth three million
limes so rockefeller was worth ten billion dollars so i was worth more than rockefeller
nine point eight billion agent 47 this is jeremy elberton also known as mr green yes wait i can't
read this i can't read this going too fast agent 47 this is jeremy elberton also known as mr green
he has been known as the lime salesman he who owns over three million limes his debt is high
but the price is higher to work 47 you'll be able to know who he is
by his very very quintessential lime green skin some say it's from eating 200 000 limes over the
last two years 47 he's very dangerous and is always surrounded by his henchmen who are also
lime green skin imagine playing like this just find the guy if i like the lime guy his henchmen
the banana bros are shaped like bananas they've also been eating fruits only i don't think this
lady does anything i think it's just only threats yeah she's gone i think i lost her the benefits of
having a private jet so you can't find me yeah i lost her she's no idea where i am you're gonna
have to get it hey you're gonna have to get a bunch of fucking sixth graders to try to find me on a
game show where in the world could i be you're not gonna find me honestly i really think that
she's gone i think i win january 12 1952 yeah it doesn't matter i win she died trying to find you
i win i escaped oh no i didn't i i want to i want to know if she like kills you
oh by the way these are gonna go bad i've been flying around in a jet a cargo jet with three
million limes just panicking and by the way they're going bad in a week which she's giving me more
money listen silly zonka wonka i'm gonna take that ten thousand dollars that you owe me you should
do better job minding your finances i'll be willing to loan you money again of course but
my interest rate's going up get twenty thousand dollars together okay i get i'm gonna get it from
her this lady's nuts she just paid herself the loan back maybe she was a stick of me
coin coin coin yes all right i know i owe you money coin there it is all right is she gonna
take the money well hello there silly zonka wonka i'll take that twenty thousand dollars
we agree to goodbye oh silly zonka wonka fancy seeing you here i'm gonna give you ten thousand
dollars here of course take ten thousand dollars do i owe her money still did i finally get to the
end i did that entire fiasco netted me ten thousand dollars that i don't have to pay her back
that's the scam just fly around the world for three months to make ten thousand dollars from
somebody just scamming oh no these are my limes no one's getting these i'm i'm done all right just
for just for shits i just want to see if i reload the game um if i have like 500 million dollars
let's find out if i just force quit the game don't save it just quit the game just force quit the
application because you have to save and quit if i just force quit do i still have 500 million
okay here comes a moment of truth does the game auto save if not then i win i know and oh oof
oh it auto saves that's a big oof oh that's a big oof that's a huge oof oh well so i still have my
limes i do i'm good i win uh that's it i'll see you tomorrow we're gonna play connect tomorrow
we're gonna play connect the most first i'll see you guys later thanks for joining me for
that was chocolatier decadence delightful decadence i don't know it's a great game
made a billion dollars actually surprised we got there oh this is where i get the phone call from
the guy that i yelled at that said i was gonna buy all the shares of his company and he heard
what happened he calls and he just says hey you want 2,500 dollars i got you yeah you shut up
i'll get you i'll see you guys tomorrow let's do the credits have a wonderful rest of your evening
that's probably the last time you will see chocolatier it was a good one there were a lot
of community subs today as you can see by how insane this is going by thank you oh my goodness
i just burped i have a longer one tonight but i feel like we had to see that through we will
catch you tomorrow connect i have let me see how many games i have one two three four five six seven
eight all right there are like 10 connect games that i have to play i'm gonna spend a bunch of
time in connectibles though that's the plan so in the meantime let's see here uh we are going to go
i'm gonna send i'm gonna send you guys to vinnie let's see what's vinnie up to and no and no
raid songs okay stop the raid song people if somebody all right here we go if somebody's
like busy and they're like into something and doing something they're talking about something
you know don't force people to do a goddamn raid song you're making us look like assholes
you know i've gotten dms from people saying hey man what's the fucking raid song
stop doing this fucking raid song thing and i'm like i'm sorry dude he's like no it's your fault
don't fucking talk to me anymore don't talk to me anymore and i go dude what the i'm sorry and he's
like don't i i just told you not to talk to me anymore who did that no one i made up a person
again but really though like let people like stream if somebody doesn't want to do the raid
song don't like demand they do something but they're gonna be mad at me it comes back to me
all right i'll see you guys later let's go raid vinnie go say hello i think he's doing a podcast
talk shows and podcasts honda fantasy 7 stuff mario 3d world ftl okay cool i'll see you guys
tomorrow good night goodbye take care of yourselves have a wonderful rest of your evening good night