You're my stab. You're my slash. You're my grab. You're my block. You're my shield.
Maybe I should just do that. It hasn't been a new emote on this channel in
a year. A paid one. I've always made it various forms of attacking and defending.
You guys could just kill each other in chat. You guys could have giant medieval wars.
Violence. Medieval violence. Oh, I didn't say hi. Hi, everybody. Welcome to the stream. Good to see you.
We want the dump truck. I'm going to make you guys wait for the dump truck.
I said this weekend, but it was a lie. Everything I say is a lie. 99.9%
of all the germs that come out of my mouth are a lie. You motherfucker. Oh, all right.
How is the virus you downloaded? It's pretty good. Hey, thank you, John Cena is killed.
For the five community cells. If you don't know, in pre-stream,
something wild happens in pre-stream chat every day. Sometimes pre-stream chat is
more wild than post than Western Pennsylvania. It's the most god-loving patriotic part of America.
Current stream chat. Current stream chat. You did this joke already. I love it.
What I'm saying is pre-stream chat usually has something crazy going on.
Why don't you just hang out there? I know there's a little pre-stream chat versus
Discord users, like LOL. I'm a pre-stream chat user. I'm not a Discord user. I don't go to the
Discord. All those plebs in the pre-stream chat. They're in the Discord, are they?
You don't have to have two completely set. You can all act as one.
Where do I stand on that matter? Where do I stand on that issue?
Well, Western Pennsylvania is the most god-loving...
All right, we're gonna play House Flipper. The DLC came out. Stop doing that.
If you don't know what that is, I can't even explain it to you.
The DLC is Cyberpunk. I think they made this DLC because a Cyberpunk is coming out and they just,
I guess, want people to download this too. They even say in the patch notes,
I know you're really excited for a game that's coming out soon. So are we. So here, download
this too. I mean, it's pretty... It's actually called the Cyberpunk DLC. Oh, look, that's fine.
They're jumping on a little bit of a trend here, but House Flipper is one of the best games
ever released. That's fine. That's okay. I'm okay with that. I won't be able to play
Cyberpunk 2077. I don't even know if I'm gonna play Cyberpunk. It took me like a year to watch
Infinity War. I don't know. I feel like it's something I... Everybody's gonna be obsessed
with it. There's gonna be memes everywhere that I'm not... I don't even want to look at them.
Is it weird that, like, there's so much excitement around it that, like, I'm losing excitement
because I know that there's so much excitement around it and I know that if I'm not as excited
as everybody else, that I'm gonna get let down because I'm not as excited? That's not even a
hipster thing. I think I just... I don't want to be so excited for something. That's contrary. No,
no. I didn't say the game was not gonna be good. I just said, like, it's... It's like, okay, if,
like, God was... Okay, if we heard that God was going to open the clouds in a week and talk to
the people, we all knew it was gonna happen. God in the fucking sky was gonna part the clouds and
be like, ladies and gentlemen, it's me. And everyone's waiting, like, holy shit, here comes God.
And a week goes by and here... Everyone's outside with their binoculars, here he comes,
this is the day. And, like, the clouds part. It's like, holy shit, everybody, like,
everyone's holding their hands, it's God. And it's like a... It's like Mr. Peanut. It's like a
peanut with googly eyes. Like, falls down, like, into the... Like, into the stage. And it's like,
it's me, everybody. Mr.... It's like a big peanut. And it's like, oh, is that real? It's God. It's me.
I don't want you doing any fucked up stuff anymore. Like, oh, you're supposed to have, like,
a big beard and, like, huge, like, Zeus with lightning bolts and stuff. Oh, that's cool, but
you're a peanut. Is that a South Park joke? The Family Guy joke. The Simpsons joke. That was a
South Park episode. That was a Family Guy episode. That was on an episode of Friends. I actually... I
was actually talking about this. Like, when are they gonna add Ross from Friends to, like, Smash
Brothers? Or, like, Mortal Kombat 11? They so... They so badly want to put, like, every TV show,
the Ninja Turtles are in smite now. Can you imagine his intro? Like, do-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no.
And he throws up, like, the... Here's, like, my invitation. He's already in. All right,
let's play. Let's go. I'm already ready. Wait, can I get... I could get DMC'd for that?
No, I couldn't. If I went... Do-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no. Is that... You just triggered it. Did I try?
All right, if this part of the VOD gets muted, then we all have to laugh about this, like, tomorrow.
Let me see if I can get this right. It's gonna be hard. So... Everybody likes to sing this first
part because it's, like, the one that... Look at how good of a singer I am. So... So no one told...
No, I'll get it. So no one told you life was gonna be this way. So no one told you... I would laugh
so fucking hard if that actually got claimed. If it does, if it does, if for some reason that could
happen. Fuck this whole thing, right? If it gets claimed. Like, who cares? I literally just said,
like, four sentences. I said, like, a sentence back to back. If you can get claimed for, like,
humming a fucking song, when are they gonna start, like, bolting our chairs to the ground
and putting fucking VR headsets on us and, like, you know, you stay in there and just enjoy,
enjoy the virtual world? Don't say anything. Don't do anything. It's a Black Mirror episode.
They did it on South Park. Yeah, okay. Who cares? Why's there no audio? Do you guys hear anything?
Oh shit. Okay, that was really, really odd. I don't hear anything, right? And then I went...
It's like somebody's, like, walking in my room. Making too many South Park references. Get them.
Sneak in. All right, so this is the DLC. Thank you to... What's the name of the website that I
got this from? The name of this save file is the website name where I downloaded it from.
I didn't even explain that, by the way. Okay, so listen. So in pre-stream chat, I've realized
that when I reinstalled Windows, I lost all of my save data. No, no, no, no, no. Stay.
And I couldn't get the cloud to download anything. I gotta turn this shit down. It's gonna be so loud.
So I couldn't get... I couldn't download my cloud save. I don't know. I have no idea why.
Right? So I had to go on the internet and download a fucking save file that had all the stuff unlocked.
What is this? Is that music? Yeah, the family guy house is gone. My garden house is gone.
Let's take a look in here, though. All right. This is the cyberpunk house.
I'm just waiting to look out this window and like... Bang! It's a bird. Like a seagull that
smashes to get Keanu Reeves' face. Hey, see you next week, man. Oh, that is gonna be so satisfying.
Yes. Yes. This is the kind of YouTube video that I watch. Those of you that are saying,
why do you watch like... Would you watch wood cutting videos? Yes. If there was a
clean Windows video, I would watch it. These are kids' videos. No, there's no surprise eggs.
And those are stupid. This is cool. This is adult surprise eggs, okay?
Don't you guys agree? Like power washing videos? It's like, oh yeah, really get in there and like,
get that grout. Oh yeah, get the grout, man. That's the same thing as, open that thing. Open it.
Oh, Spider-Man's in there. Yes. Open another one. How is it different? Humans are so... We're just
a couple of math problems up there. Everybody likes stuff like this. It doesn't matter. It's
just different versions. Are you high? No. What? Are you? He's not... I'm not high. I swear to God.
He's... I am not. I really am not. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. You're freaking me out, man.
I'm not. I'm not. You're freaking me out. Stop. I'm gonna turn this free mode off, I think. You're
freaking me out. I'm freaked out. What the fuck, dude? I thought I was just looking outside of my
own like apartment window. What the fuck, man? You guys are freaking me the fuck out.
No one told you life was gonna be DMCA'd. Let's try to get the whole thing muted. It's like these
record companies are stuck in second gear. Minus two. Stop. Come on. I'm making like a fun DMCA
joke. You don't think that's fun? Don't stop. These windows are so big. I don't... I really don't like
windows like this. I'm sorry. I don't... I... There has to be a curtain here. The amount of times
that I've like passed out on my couch just like naked. Everybody can just look into your entire
house. I don't want you to see me cooking like macaroni and cheese and shit. Like get the fuck
out of here. Who wants to like be watched eating a box of pizza? Everyone's like, oh wow, look at all
this open light. Yeah, that's cool. For like 10 minutes, close the fucking blinds. I don't want
people looking in my house, looking at my apartment. Oh shit, I gotta get even higher up.
First of all, hold on, let's take care of these wires. What kind of soda is it? Why are you always
naked? Don't you... That's the way humans are supposed to be. I swear to god, I am not high.
I don't... I don't even want to get into this. I don't even want to get into this. Let me clean
this shit up. Why is it so dark in here? That doesn't turn light on. This is just like what's
behind every streamer. They have like all these cool things in the background. Just like the lights
and like blinking things and shows and stuff. I need one of those. Oh, the lever? Wait, why did
that just turn on? Wait, I didn't even do anything. Chill. This is not. That looks bad. This apartment
is from like 2100. They have an air conditioner from 1980. Interesting. Look at the fridge. Look
at this. Look, you got like a grandma radiator. Oh, turn that off. Horrible. It's vintage. No,
vintage in 2100 would be like 2150 or 2050. You can sit in the gamer chair too. All right,
clean this place up. Hold on. Just delete. I don't want like toxic waste in my room. Why are these
here? Why would you have that in your house? That's because it's punk. It's punk? What is it? Maybe
it is a YouTuber house. Because what the fuck do these people even do with all this slime video
shit? It's just a ton of slime videos. What do you actually do with that stuff? So they make the
slime video. They make like five tubs of slime. Then what do they do? What do you do? Where does
it go? Do they just throw it away? Do they pour it down the drain? Isn't that like horrible? They
sell it in smaller quantities. Sell it? They sell, they, they slime tube. I don't, what do you mean
they sell it? What does this say? All right, get rid of it. I don't want it. I have to make my cool
gamer apartment. I'm actually into this. All right, hold on. Sell the pizza. Sell the pizza.
Energy drinks. Disgusting. By the way, stop drinking those. Just please. Just don't drink
them. Just stop drinking them. Just not, don't do that anymore. I'm serious. Oh, don't, stop doing
that. Says the guy who drinks truly. No, no, no, no, no. Let me, let me, let me correct that. Says
the guy who drank truly one time ever in his life on stream or off stream because he got so involved
in the idea that it might be funny if he drank them on stream that he ruined his reputation.
That's the only time I've ever consumed one of those. Ever. I've never, only ever.
Old, old, old. This is trash. This is like junked. Okay, is this even a sink or is this a big fake
wood sink? This is wood. Get rid of this. It's not futuristic. How is that futuristic?
What? Cold, cold plus ice, water, temperature, temperature in a jar, fridge mode, thermometer
mode, or shopping mode. What kind of fridge is this? I don't understand. All right. What else?
We've got an empty container, a takeout container. This needs, this property needs to be cleaned up.
What do you think I'm doing? How do I get up there? Oh, I can just fly up here. All right, here we go.
Put it in fridge mode. Your milk is boiling. I only buy shelf stable milk. So, okay, kid.
I only buy shelf stable milk, like shelf stable almond milk. Shelf stable. Hey, you know, those
are you guys that are from England? Oh, you English. Isn't that, don't they keep milk like room
temperature or something? Isn't like milk in a box? You know, the drinking cold milk is weird
to Europeans, right? Isn't it? Oh, that's France. There's one of the, there's a European, yeah,
there's a European country that thinks that like Americans drinking cold milk every day is just
weird, right? Putting eggs in the fridge will make it low. Right. Boxed long life milk exists. Yeah.
Why does everybody think I'm so weird? This is like a thing. You are. I am not even weird. I'm not.
I talked to my mother on the phone last night and she told me I wasn't. She said I was perfect,
I was a perfect special boy. I said, thank you, mom. So, sorry, my mother knows more than you.
After I told her that I peed all over my iPhone. Oh my God. I have to get mad about this. I am very
mad. Very, very, very mad at Apple. Apple, that's right. I'm coming after you with a little bit of,
with a little bit of fucking problem here. A little bit of a rant here. So did you see what
they announced? You see, they announced the, the iPhone 12 mini, the little phone, the little
fucking phone that I talked about how badly I wanted. They made the, they made the iPhone SE.
Okay. iPhone SE was a iPhone 4 chassis, right? They come up with the iPhone SE 2. Uh, we're not
going to make it that smaller chassis anymore. It's now a big chassis. Okay. Well, what the fuck?
And I got that one. That's what I got. I got an iPhone SE, the new one, because that's the
smallest we're ever going to make it. Then these fucking, God damn it, they made it a tiny phone.
They made the little one, that iPhone 12 mini. Why did you do it? I just got the SE. What the
fuck are you doing? Why did they make the iPhone SE 2 bigger, but the iPhone 12 now has a mini
version? Why did they wait so long to announce that? Like, why don't they announce that shit
like a year ago? Like, what the hell? I'm so annoyed by that. First world problems. Yeah,
I'm just saying, like, why would they do that? They came up with the SE and then they'd be like,
oh, by the way, here's the little one that you wanted. And that's, by the way, it's like,
it's like 1,100 bucks. I don't even know how much it is. It's probably that much.
Are they just trying to bleed out just phones? Just like, just, just have like a trickle of
new phones every three months for people to buy? Is that the, is that the plan? It is. I,
when I saw that, I was like, I can't even believe it. I mean, how have you not realized that? No,
I, I mean, ooh, I like this little place, except I don't like all these. I actually hate these signs
and they're everywhere. The amount of those like chill, good vibes, relax, love, eat,
eat, play, relax. Like what, is this a Dave and Buster's? Why do we have to have signs that say
like, oh, eat, relax, play, game on? No, get rid of these. I don't want that. Chill. It takes up so
much. You could put something, a big cool painting here. That's what I'm going to do. Is there a
mirror? Eat and then sleep. Imagine just having one that said that. What, oh, just having one that
just says, I am alive. That's it. Ooh, a little shoe rack. This is cool. Did I clean the whole
place? I did. Oh shit. This is like almost over. This is like almost done. I always beat the level
and this is the only level that exists. Looks like I have to go back to the, oh, the family guy has
this. Wait, we can see with the, this save game company. The DLC is almost over. It was free
though. Let's be clear. What about the toilet? Yeah, I got it. I got it. I got it. There's mold
everywhere. Oh, this is good. All right. What else? What's dirty over here? There's new items too.
I'm not giving up. He hates free DLC. No, I just making a, just making a point. iPhone 12 mini. Get
the fuck out of here. Like, come on man. Okay. I have a question. If I went into like the Apple
store and I said, Hey, uh, I, I broke my iPhone. My iPhone's broken. I have like Apple Care. I can
get a new one, right? Can I, can I, can I, can I like get a new one? Can I like get a new Apple
mini for free? Is that how that works? Well, uh, that depends. What happened to it? I dropped it
down the stairs. Oh wow. That's exactly what we cover. Yeah. I dropped it. I fell down the stairs
and went crashed. See, look at the broken screen. Are you sure you didn't piss on it? No, no, no,
no. Of course not. Why would I? That's disgusting. No, I didn't. You're trying to give me a piss phone?
No, no, of course not. Of course I wouldn't. I gotta move this. Oh shit. No. What? No. I have to
every individual book has to be moved. Oh my God. Just burn them. I, I can't.
No, I gotta get rid of my Funko Pop collection. This is a lot of books. How many of you guys are
like me where, uh, you have like four books that you've owned for 10 years and you may have read
the first four pages of one of them? I don't know. There's a lot of books. Okay. What's dirty?
What's dirty back here? Nothing. I mean, this is, this washing machine is pretty. Where's the dryer?
I don't have a, how do I dry my clothes? All right. Well, we don't need this anymore because
I don't have any more books. Wait, you put the TV above the washing machine. Uh, that's, that's,
this seems terrible. No, that's gotta move. That's gotta move. And the couch is facing this way
towards the staircase. Um, that's, uh, odd design. TV on the stairs. Yeah, we're gonna have like a
little TV station over here. Wait, dirt. It's called House Flipper. I know. We're gonna get
something better. That doesn't match anyways. We need something, we need something metal and
like we need like stainless steel floor apparently. Is this steel floor? It's like
aluminum floor. Shit. I gotta get up there. Can you play the arcade machine? I don't think you can.
Maybe let's just make this place an arcade. I just sleep up here and then I charge people
to like come into my apartment. Almost. Come on. Where's this last piece? No, I don't want to move
this. I will if I have to. Wait, here we go. Not again. No, I'm gonna actually make an apartment
this time. This doesn't work in here either. Why is it cappa? Okay, why is it already capping?
Cappa, cappa, cappa, cappa. For what? Yeah, this has got to go too. Like, get out of here.
If that's where the washing machine is going to go, then the desk has to move somewhere else.
Upstairs. No, it could stay there, but that, yeah, that's not going to be there. I feel like
this is taking up a lot of space. Rip apartment. What do you mean rip apartment? This scares the
shit out of me too. I feel like at like two o'clock in the morning I'm going to walk through here and
this thing's going to just like chop my like fucking nose off. That's not what I said. Okay,
everything's clean. Now I need to furnish and move some stuff around. Let's move some shit around.
I don't even know what this is. What's the practicality of this thing? Get rid of it.
I don't want this. That's a laptop. Laptop with, holy shit, that's awesome. Do they make those?
Little tiny extra monitors? They don't make those? Well, they absolutely should. That's a really good
idea. Little pop-out monitor. So you could, it would be like a second and third monitor. You
could put little things on it. Like if you're working on a project or something or you...
I actually like that idea. They could, and they could go in, right? They could fold kind of into
the top of the laptop. That'd be pretty cool. But for what? I don't, because sometimes you want to
have like more than, oh well, never mind. I don't need that. All right, well then explain to me why
you need this. Those of you that are saying, oh I can't believe he wants like a small extra screen
on his laptop. So why would there be seven or eight fucking monitors? Stocks. For his Zorn. Oh yeah?
You're gonna, you're gonna have eight different windows open for Zorn?
You sure about that? Because uh, Nancy and Greg in apartment fucking, floor fucking 20,
apartment A, can see what you're doing in here. You want, and you're sure you want to do that?
One for Zoom calls. I'm gonna sit here and I'm gonna really try to figure out what I would do
with this many monitors. Okay, here we go. I have three, by the way, right now. So this is like the
main monitor where you do all, okay like let's say that you have like a game or a project or
one. Okay. Okay, let's say this is like chat. I just have one monitor for chat typically and
maybe like a preview window, okay? Other monitor is for miscellaneous. Like if I have like a YouTube
video or something that I need to grab quickly is on monitor three. What would go on the other ones?
Okay, so you have necessity, practicality, and fun. Okay, let's just, let's just say that there was
porn on this one, okay? There's porn all over this one. What do you do with these ones? Okay,
let's say the stocks on this one. There's like a, like a few stock tickers. Let's just say,
let's just say, let's just say, let's just say, right? I know, I said that a lot. What about this
one? Music. Why can't you have music on this one? Just minimize with like a Spotify playlist. You
don't need a, you need a full monitor to listen to music? News feed. I need to see the queue. So
you, okay, let me, you want to see the queue for Spotify on a full monitor with it powered on 24
7 while you're here. How much does Spotify cost a month? Was it 10 bucks, 20 bucks a month?
It's 10 bucks a month. How much does it cost to leave a computer monitor on 24 7? Monthly,
you think? Two dollars a month? Dollar a month? Two dollars a month? So you're paying like 30%
extra for your Spotify playlist essentially. Nothing. I don't pay my electricity. Okay, well,
I don't know how old you are, but eventually you're going to. Wait, do you have like solar?
Are you one of the houses that has solar that always talks about,
I haven't paid electricity bill in four years, dude. I got solar. You are? Oh god, that makes
me jealous. Yeah, my electricity bill last month was two dollars. Yeah, yeah, it was, wasn't it?
Don't you, can't you get like paid to have solar and like energy producers too? Electricity is
dirty. Yeah. All right. Well, when are we going to move away from like tubes that push gas into
your house? I'd be happy about that one, but I don't, I don't like gas. I hate it. It's scary.
Right now there are a series of tubes that are pushing gas into your house. Just it's waiting,
just ready for you to call it in. It's like, wait, it's like, come on, call gas into your lines.
Right now there's like bubbling, burning hot oil, just sitting somewhere in a tank,
just like I'm ready to explode somewhere in your house. That sucks. Actually, this bet's pretty
good. I was, I'm sorry, I can't help it. I just did, I know, I didn't mean to.
Okay, I've been picking up the same items and putting them down. Let's get some, I see dirt.
Okay, very important. Let's get a couch. They added a bunch of new items too. This is cyberpunk only.
Bathroom, a cyberpunk bathroom? A dentin shower? This, I don't think, this looks like unsafe to me.
I feel like this thing's going to close me in and just kill me. All right, yeah, I want,
I want that shower. We're going to have to cyberpunk this thing. You know, cyberpunk's
coming out in a week or so, man. Everyone get, I'm so, I'm wicked excited for it. I'm not going to
play it on this stream. You probably won't see it ever. Let's go! Hype for cyberpunk 2077. I might
though. I don't know. I'm thinking about it. Let's go. You think it's a game that I would like? Oh,
shit. Ah, you can't even leave. Yeah, you can. You know, I used to have, I used to have a fridge
that was like this, where I, it was way too big for the space, but they got it in, they put it in,
and I was like, it's too, but I don't even want to go through the trouble of having you take it.
So I don't care. It's a little too long, but I don't care. I guess I could crush the walls,
but how am I, I don't have any, I can't crush this wall. This place is not even,
it's not big enough for me to build a big one. We got a, what, we got a link? I don't understand.
This is Elbertson's class. I don't like, what the fuck are you doing?
Okay, we have our shower. What, there's no special toilet? I don't like shit like this,
because you know, the bigger the thing is, the more of a hum it has in your house.
Very important knowledge for you guys to know. The larger the appliances, the more it's going to go,
and you're going to, you know, you're going to notice it one day, and you're going to be
so pissed off. Click the relevant link. That was the wrong link. What?
Choose your seat. Pre-order now. What? Is this, could you do, is this actually, this is cool,
actually. I don't hate this at all. I think this is actually really cool.
Pre-order. Now that's a collector's edition I could get behind. If the collector's edition
just gave you a new toilet that you could install, I'd actually be into that. It'd be kind of cool.
Free toilet. Well, no, a toilet's, what, how much is a toilet? That would make sense for
a collector's edition. A toilet's like two or three hundred bucks. How much are collector's
editions of games? Like five, six hundred sometimes? Three hundred, two hundred? You know,
just give me a copy of cyberpunk and the toilet. That's good for me. Yeah, but does it, there has
to be a big, big asterisk there that says you need to install it yourself. You need to hire a plumber
to install it. Imagine being the plumber that installs the cyberpunk toilet. Yeah, I'm going
to need some work done. I'm going to need a plumber to come over here. It's like, okay, what do you
need? I need you to install a toilet for me. Okay, that sounds easy. I feel like this would be weird
as a plumber. Be like, what the fuck is this? A cyberpunk collector's edition toilet. What else
I got here? Keanu Reeves shows up to do it. Keanu Reeves doesn't even, doesn't know how to do that,
though, does he? That collector's edition would be like twenty grand. Hey, I'm here to install
your toilet for you. Make sure you download cyberpunk the second it comes out next week, man.
I have no idea how to install toilets, but I'm going to try. I'm going to look at it and do it
a little bit, man. He comes with like a hard hat on and a bunch of like wrenches. He walks in and
he just introduces like the install and then the actual plumber comes in and installs the toilet
for you. That might be, that would be worth it. All right, I need a bed. Furniture, here we go.
Ooh, I like some of this stuff. Some of this stuff is cool. I would get that this would be an awesome
bed. Well, no, not really, actually. Does this fold down? Okay, if the top part folded down,
it would be like a futon. Armchairs on a bed. No, it's not a germo bed. It's a bed that would
if it was bigger. I thought it was bigger. I didn't know it was that small. Just leave in here.
Put like a little pillow and a blanket in there and like crawl in the cubby and like lie down
lengthwise. No, no, no, no, no, no. It's got to be one of these. Just how about line up 10
gamer chairs and take the arms off? Ooh, I like this. I actually really like this. Okay, a mattress.
Let's make the mattress a blue. It's an Alienware bed. Yeah, the big alien head symbol is right
there on the sheets. I like that. No, not that. I like that. I would sleep in this. But unfortunately,
it's too big. Or is it? Or is it? Hold on. I don't like that. Get rid of that. Get rid of this too.
What is here? It's outlets. Okay. It's too big. It's not too big. Just wait. Get rid of all of this.
I don't want any of this shit. I'm redoing this whole thing. You have to go off this way to get
in and out of bed. But people get to see you sleep. No, get a big curtain. New offer. Add
GermaSus as an emote to double your debt. I've been seeing this picture a lot recently and I don't
get it. I don't understand. And you know what? I'm actually happy this picture is making the rounds
and you guys are memeing the absolute hell out of this picture. Can anybody tell me why?
Because this looks better than the original. So by all means, please, please spread this around.
Please make every meme possible. Make this the top search thing because that looks better than
the actual original picture. It looks worse. No, it doesn't. What have you done? New emote. No,
a new emote. That would be so terrifying. Maybe like a BTTV emote. Any that- here's the problem.
Any emote that's added that's a real sub-emote, you can use anywhere on this website. So I know
you guys will spam that in channels and you'll give- you'll give us a bad reputation. Like,
oh, here's like this GermaSus emote fucking smile like scary community again. Well,
can't wait to like pretend to like like these guys until they leave. You think people do that?
I don't think so. I think we've got a good community here. But like if you spam the Germa
fucking scary SCP emote enough times, maybe they won't think that way. I want a painting right
here. A big one. Painting. What's something futuristic looking? It's like every single-
hold on. I want to put another picture here that's a face. You know, or like a bod- like a head lying
this way. TOS? What do you mean TOS? This is clearly a dog bone. It's a dog bone and it's
somebody just holding onto it. What are you talking about? I like that so far. I need something here.
How about um, something nuclear? I said it wrong, whatever. Scream in my face. What about HGTV?
Oh, nuclear. Yeah, the walls have to change too. All right, installations. All right, hold on.
Are you sure- are you sure you want to come over this guy's house? Would you sit in this seat?
You tell me. You're gonna sit in that chair? Why would you have that though? I have my electric
chair. That's a hot seat. What the fuck is this link? All right, what is it? Okay, we're getting
some weird links today. What the fuck? What? Oh, ah, this makes me uncomfortable to look at. I don't
even want to put this on stream. This is like- this is weird. It's like morphing. I don't want to put
this on stream. This is terrifying. Why is it- what is it- what's morphing? Ah, ah, ah! Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I know. Why do you guys make this stuff? I'm supposed to be the weird guy. I'm the- I'm the
weird guy, right? All right, well, yes, I did make like a pretend electric execution chair in
my apartment. Yes, but I didn't finish. I was gonna put like a nice picture of a bird up here.
Okay, see? That is what would happen. It would use all the power in the building. The building
would turn off. Why would I have like a death chair? All right, what happened to all the lights?
Vending machine outside? It's for your enemies. It's for me to convince people to come over and
sit in a chair. Why would you- why would you want- okay, if you had an enemy, how would you
convince them to come over your house? And I know we like fucking hate each other. We- I- and we're
dastardly villains to each other, but come over to my apartment and come up here. Come up the
stairs and come sit in this chair and don't move like a little bit and just hang out on your phone.
Okay, I need more furniture. This sucks. I want- you know what? You know what I've always wanted
and you guys can think I'm crazy for this, but am I? I've always wanted to be lying in bed and
have a sort of a lower ceiling and have a big TV up here. Is that weird? Fuck, I can't do it.
Damn it. I can't do it? Why? Why? Let me live my fantasies. Uh, TV. I mount this TV? No, I can't.
Damn it. I really have always wanted that. I feel like that'd be so convenient.
But it would- what if it fell and- and crushed you? You'd just lie in here. You'd lie in here
just like this, watching like a nature documentary.
There's monkeys are funny. And the thing just- that would be so horrible. Yeah, that's kind of
scary. We'd need to be bold to do a stud. There are no studs in the ceiling. I don't- how would
you get it up there? What if you- you're doing something else? You're lying in bed looking up.
There's your use- and it comes crashing down on you?
The police find you? What the hell happened here? Why is he lying on his back? And he's- see,
uh, I don't know. How did this- how did this happen? I cannot see- we need to get like
three of the top FBI detectives to come out here because I have no fucking idea how this dude died
here. Okay, I can't put the TV on the ceiling so whatever. I'm gonna put- uh, get rid of this.
I don't want this. I don't want this. I don't want this. I don't want that. All right, what else do
we have? Doors and windows. Just put these everywhere. Just be that person that has the
uncomfortable amount of like kind of lewd artwork all over their house. Everywhere. In the dinner
table- it's in the dining room. It's- it's the dinner table. The dinner table is that. Kind of
just paint it onto the wood. Now, I need a cool couch and this TV sucks. I'm sorry. Wait,
that had an arm on it! Oh! Microwave cyberwave crane monitor. Oh boy. Shit. Okay, well, I could
do this and tilt it down, right? Like, technically, I could lie down like this and like tilt it down
upside down. No, you would install it upside down so then when you- you would arrange it away so
when it's face down it was the right way. You know what I mean? So you'd have to arrange it away
where you would lie like this and it goes face down that it would be the right side up. So hold on.
This has to change. Okay, so then now- yeah, there. See? Now the arm bends down like this.
It's a guillotine television. You better pray this arm is strong as hell. Yeah. Extend it down.
That works. Ban Discord users. Ban Discord users. Why would I do that?
All right, here's the- they already gave me the cool mouse and keyboard and desk. They already
furnished it. I want- get this out of here. I don't like this down here in the living space.
I want this up here. This is a cooler up here, I think. Yeah, like right there. That's cooler.
Let's move a couple of these. I don't need this one. Get rid of it. This is wrong. Who needs more
than six shelves? Let's be real. Make it flush. Nice. All right, cool. Reddit shelves. Hey,
Reddit shelf is cool. Down with Discord Dave. I don't know who that is. I like this. I mean,
this computer is cool, but it could be better. Oh, shit. Let me see. I got subs coming in.
We had five subs from Lime and then 25 from Freddy Dread. What's going on, Freddy? Thanks for the
huge amount of subs. I want to make this clear again. I want to make this clear. We have maybe
some people that- I have to change- I didn't change the fucking rules. I'm so stupid. I no longer read
bits anymore. In fact, I probably am going to make the bit minimum to give to the channel like
something that's impossible. Should I do that? One, five million? No, people will do it. That scares
me though. You're right. If I make the bit minimum, like $5,000, somebody's gonna do it, aren't they?
What happened with the bits? Well, to give a long story, a shorter TLDR here. I want- I kind of want
to get rid of the bits to be read on stream kind of thing because I got rid of the bit reading at
the end of the streams and you don't know if you're new to the channel. I used to read all
bit donations over 250 on stream at the end of a stream and what I ended up doing is because I had
a lot of medical problems and I used to sit here for about four or five hours and then it'd be about
an hour or two of a wind down where we did the end of the stream. So I decided that because it was
better if I could just sit here and stream and then be able just to get up whenever so I didn't
have to potentially put an extra couple hours to the stream. I could stream for a little bit longer
until I was like, okay, I gotta get up. But what happened was I still was doing like- people were
giving $50 and $100 bit drops which is huge and insane and I can't even imagine giving that amount
of money to anybody. But I was still reading those because they were so large that I almost felt like
that's so much money. I kind of have to respond to that, right? So now I'm no longer going to be
doing that because I didn't want to put a precedence in place where pay $100 for the streamer to
actually read it and because I feel like that's unfair and I don't want people to think they have
to do that. So like I said before, if you want- if you want to support this channel, which people do
and I- every day I wake up in the morning and I go this is- this is- this is a stupid amount of
support and money. I can't even believe it. It's- it's uncountable in my brain. Just sub. And you
don't have to give hundreds of dollars on a stream. I would much rather you take care of yourself
or support some other potentially smaller streamers that are out there. That would- I would- I would
make- that would make me feel better about that. I think that would be better. So bit readings are
gone permanently and they are never coming back. But I still call out sub gifts because the theory
behind that was it was something that people were getting and it wasn't just- I mean obviously it's
me getting money from those subs but people are getting them and they can use the subs and it's
I think it's a little different. Greed. No one gives the slightest of fucks resident sleeper. Well,
I mean if you gave $50 today and I didn't read it you're probably going like oh what's the- he
didn't- what the fuck is going on here? What do you mean true? I'm getting trued right now?
I gotta be clear. I gotta be clear. I want to make sure I'm clear on this. And look, just relax and
pull on. True, true, true. Don't- don't true me. I need a couch. Ooh, I like this but I want it to be
blue. Like super blue. And yeah and now- yes I said the word sub and here comes a shitload of subs.
Okay I'm- I'm never gonna say money on the- of course I am. Why blue? Because like teal is my
favorite color. You guys know that. Teal aqua light kind of greenish green aqua blue. It's beautiful.
All right let's make this interesting. In here? Okay if I put it- where'd I put the TV? I don't
even need a TV. I got a TV up there. This is a fridge. All right fridge is going over here.
Why not? Fridge is going over here. Because then you can just roll the chair back and just open it
up and grab whatever you want. Shit. All right this is cool but it's too big. It's gonna be really
loud next to your ears. Will it though? Okay I- that's not- this is not bad. How would you even
get up there to turn these on and off? Did I ever tell you guys that I didn't have heat
or air conditioning in my old place in Massachusetts? In- in where- no wait hold on.
Let me- let me fix that. Where I- the place when I was streaming there wasn't AC into that room.
There wasn't heat into that room. So every day I'd have to like- how did I survive in there?
With body heat because I get so hot it didn't even matter. During the winter I would just
generate- I'm my own heater. The computer in the hot room it would just make the room like 70
degrees every time. Okay I want a- I need like a lamp or something. Dude I can't even break
anything in this one. Yeah I can. Uh well dude- oh let's make it like modern. Let's make it like
postmodern. Watch this. There we go. Nice. Just have like you know bricks and like broken bricks
and shit that people come and go oh wow cool postmodern. I can't even break this wall. Open
up the bathroom. No I just- I want a postmodern bathroom entrance. That's it. I break this. What
can I even do in this room? This room is so boring. What do you put in here? Oh this- what am I doing?
Am I stupid? This is the TV room. This is the entertainment room. This is too big though.
Wait is it? No it's not. It's perfect. Nice okay and then like the TV can be right here.
That's awful. All right what's too big? So I'm gonna put this back. You have a flat. So I'm
utilizing the space. That can stay there. What goes in the middle? Like a dining table. Is there
a cyberpunk dining table? Holy shit there's pinball. No no there's nowhere to put this.
I guess I could put it over here. That's kind of cool. Oh the fridge is too-
please listen to lego rock raiders 2 soundtrack while you play. It's quiet.
No it's gonna DMCA the stream. I hate this thing. Seriously I don't- all the gaming chairs I think
they're so ugly. I'm sorry. I think- I really believe that. They're just huge and bulky and
I just don't- I don't like them. I really don't. Some of them are okay. There's actually a couple
that look all right. I just- no they're too- they're huge. Huge huge huge huge huge. Remember when
you're gonna post your fire watch photos? I already did. Hmm well I don't like it. I don't- I just-
I'm not into it. I like more stuff like this. You know some of that like post-modern kind of style.
But it needs to be more comfortable. I thought- okay I thought this was a cauldron. Like a
witch's cauldron. This is a seat? Why is this seat squished? All right yeah yeah yeah come on.
Shit. I have to assemble this? That's a pain in the ass. Real stream setup. Cool all right and
it can swing too. Can I use it? I want to sit on it. Oh but it's too impractical. Wait I can't
even move this. I can't move it. Shit. It's a sex swing. Put it up here. Okay I don't know what
happened. I've- I talked about this a month or so ago or a few weeks ago. This stream has become
just- I never used to talk like this before. Never never never ever. Think back like a year
or two ago. Never would you hear these words coming out my- I would never say the word
sex swing on my stream a year ago. I'd be like holy shit I'm not saying that out loud. What the
fuck? I think you guys may have like infiltrated my brain but I'm putting it up here. Wait I don't
know about this though. Sir like you've got like the electric chair like the z- the zex swing.
The- how do you explain all this? Oh it's for- it's for decoration. Oh you have this like
electric- a chair that you set and you turn it on and electrocutes you. Yes it's for decoration.
What's the swing up here for? Like this like sex swing? It's for decoration. What are all these-
you have you have like a modded arcade cabinet with like 10,000 porn games on it. Yes it's for
decoration. Oh okay. The tv that bends down while you lie on your back in bed is that for decoration?
Uh yes. But it functions and you watch tv on it. Yes. So it's not a decoration. It's- it has a
practical use. No. Yes. Well um it's been fun. Maybe I'll- maybe I'll call you later. 700,000
Zorn games. This is the kind of place that like if you like if mom comes over she can't touch
anything. This is why you can't have any of that shit man. Oh I have like porn here porn stuff porn
thing porn sex this sex that. It's like oh mom's coming over. Well mom you can't touch anything.
You have to literally sit in the waiting room and here's- I'll put a bed here. Like there's- you
can't have all this stuff. What is it a porn fridge? Not everything has to be porn fridge,
porn swing, porn cabinet, porn bed. I like this spot so I'm putting a shelf here.
Porn stairs. What do you mean porn stairs? I just want to see.
Mom you- mom you can never come over my house. And this is an apartment too. This is a smaller-
this is kind of a small apartment. You have like the living area and everyone can see everything.
You can't- no one can ever come over your house. You can't have like a porn swing. Small in the
sense that like everything is visible from everywhere in the entire- besides a bathroom.
You can't have a porn swing just in your bed area up here in a loft in an apartment like this.
He's a millionaire streamer. Okay so hold on. I'm the millionaire streamer but you guys are
talking about wanting to install a porn sex swing up in your loft. How much do you think a like
professionally installed porn swing costs? It can't be less- it's probably more than a thousand
dollars. Way more probably. It's probably- yeah it's probably like three to five K. Why do I know?
I don't know. I'm asking chat. You guys are the- you guys are the Zorn Masters. It's six thousand
dollars for that. Okay but I'm the millionaire streamer. You guys are the other six K porn
swing streamers. Well you know what? I said streamer. You get the idea.
A porn swing streamer. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. I gotta
move on. I gotta move on. No I'm not putting- I'm not gonna do the porn swing. I'm not doing it.
It's too much. My mother's probably watching. Okay what do we got for a table? Something cool.
Something modern. Something contemporary. How about- oh just a boring wood table. I love wood.
Wood is so easy. You need to put a fuck table in. You don't even eat food. Why is this one dirty?
Oh it's not. There's like a design on it. I'm corrupted. I've been corrupted. Total
corruption. Total corruption. Total power. No not- I don't need a changing table. I don't even know
what to put in here. This place is done. I don't know what else to do here. All right I'm just
gonna pick this one here. Whatever. Whatever. Who cares? That's so big. It really is. Do the arcade
house. Yeah but if I do the arcade house it's over and it's just gonna be arcade cabinets everywhere
and then my like porn room loft 2.0. I already did the porn room last time. Kitchen? I don't have a
kitchen. Chat has collectively lost their mind. Okay you know how they say that the streamer
influences the chat and your chat is sort of an extension of you and your personality in a way?
It's the opposite here. Absolutely. I have been consumed by Twitch chat. Where's the bathroom?
Right here? I'll add a little kitchenette. There's a bathroom right here. Okay this sucks. I don't
get rid of that. This is fine. I can just like I don't know I can run around in a circle here
really easily. That's good. Nancy's looking in there right now. Greg come here. Come here. Come here.
Greg come here. The dude in that loft that we can see is like fucking running in circles right now.
What? No he's not. Look. Look dude. Look. Look. Holy shit. What the fuck is he doing? I don't know.
He does weird shit in there all the time. He's putting up like a swing too earlier.
The call of somebody? What are we gonna call? What's our jurisdiction? I don't know. I just
feel like maybe we should. No. No. No. No. We're like two miles away Nancy. Just stop looking.
Just stop looking in that window. He's going up the stairs. Stop looking. I don't want to even
know about it. Don't tell me about it. He just turned his tv on. He's lying down I think. Why
does he not have curtains? This is so fucked up. He didn't have curtain. No he doesn't. He's weird.
He's putting the tv down. Okay. All right. Okay. I'm not looking anymore. What? What? What? What?
Let me see. Let me see. No. No. Don't look. Don't look. It's fucked. No. Wait. No. No. No.
Don't look. Let me see what he's doing over there. Oh Jesus. Why does he? I told you to stop looking
through this guy's window. I can't. What do you want to do? I'm sorry. You do this shit. I'm not
doing this. We're moving. Look. We don't have to move. We don't have to move. Yes we do. The
temptation to look at this guy doing crazy shit is off the charts. We're moving two floors down so
we don't have to see him anymore. He's inflating his cheeks on the window. He knows we're watching.
He's doing the thing that the kids do. I don't know what else to do. What else do I do here?
Oh lamps. We need. Oh bro. How about relax. Chill. Can I spell another word out? Chill.
Hold on. How big can I make this? He's actually. He's not even putting up curtains. He's installing
a shitload. Oh hold on. Where's my build tool? I don't know what he's doing. He's building. He's
building a wall. This would be. Have they made a movie like this before? I think they have. Right?
Haven't they? Well like the guy across the apartment is doing crazy shit
and it's like they keep looking through the window and seeing him. What is he doing? Oh my god.
Nancy. Oh my god. I don't know what he's doing. I think he knows we're watching. Nancy. Nancy.
Nancy. I think he's looking over here. He installed a thing on a wall and it says relax.
Why do we need to relax? Is he talking about us? He must be looking. Why would he build that?
Nancy. Nancy. Nancy. Nancy. We gotta move. Oh that was a weird sleep. I didn't get much sleep.
That was terrifying. Nancy. Wake up. What's going on out the window? What are you talking about?
What do you mean? He's standing there still. He's still standing there looking out the window.
No he's not. No it's impossible. He was doing that last night. He hasn't moved.
What do you mean he hasn't moved? Nancy he hasn't moved in the full like seven or eight hours.
He's just looking right over at our window. Jesus. Wait he's moving. Nancy. What's he doing?
Nancy. I think he's leaving his apartment. Nancy. Nancy. Nancy. I don't know what to do.
How annoying is this really though? This is a mix of rear window and cape of fear.
Bar. Chill. Relax. Okay that was fun. I had fun in the DLC. How do I get over there though?
Can I? Hold on. Is there like a- you gonna play more tear down? Uh probably not. No I'm
leaving. I'm leaving this. I'm leaving. See? No I'm moving to a different house. I want to
do a different house. That was fun little DLC but I'm moving to a different house.
And just- no what? Uh none of this shit. Look at how- look at how nice this looks. None of this
is mine. This is a downloaded save file. Actually you know what? Owned. How many- aww. I thought
we'd be able to see his uh his progress. Just married house. What is- I don't remember this one.
Yeah we did the moon already. I don't think I have enough money for this. I remember I did the moon
base. I did the man cave. Which one have I not done? Variable woman's house. What does that mean?
What is a variable woman's house? It's code? What do you mean it's code? What the hell is this house?
Wait what? This house is very strange. Did I do this one? I think I already did this one. Why is
there a sliding door here? Wait this house is already done. It's just dirty. I did do- no no no
this is a save file. This looks like a dark RP- yeah we made the FPS house already. What about
outside? Hold on. Let's flip it harder. Okay well wall mom time. I- I- I- okay I'm not going to look
at the mini map. I have no idea where I am. I don't know where I am. This is a bathroom here and then
there's- this is a- what? Okay this is bathroom- I don't know where I am in the house. Hold on. Okay so
you have the entrance then you have a hallway leading to a hallway leading to a bathroom and
an outdoor. This wall has to come down. Just gut it. Let's just make a game show house where you have to
pick a certain door and there's like traps behind one of them. Just make a giant game show stage.
We're gonna have like a sign too. Like a sound stage. Make a saw house? I mean what do you mean
it's a- wait every room has a new- a different trap in it? Let me clean up the bugs first.
You know what the worst part about this? Oh you all know. You all know what I'm about to do and I
know it's gonna make people really really uncomfortable. Here we go. You know that it's
not gonna be that simple. It's gonna be this. Stop stop stop no. All right I will. That was awful.
Can't I have this cool thing in the saw house? I don't even know who the fuck I am. All right I
have to destroy everything. I was making a sandwich what did I miss? Bug noises and like bugs suck up
kill with vacuum noises. So I'm glad you weren't here. Unless you're eating a bug sandwich
then you probably wouldn't care. Bug snacks that's right. It's bug snacks. Kind of bug and kind of
snack. Kind of bug and kind of snack. Kind of bug and kind of snack. It's a bug snack. Oh somebody
checked did the vod- did the friends theme song get claimed? Oh yes. No it didn't. Keep roaches for
the saw trap room. Oh shit. Oh my god why am I cleaning for? Yeah I gotta move trash and stuff.
Oh shit what am I doing? I gotta keep trash and put it in different rooms. Oh shit. Any more bug
clusters? Yep okay good. This would be like this would be like the you get eaten alive by bugs room.
The best part about this is the fact that you can't remove windows in this game.
So hell make your choice here in a room with bugs you're gonna eat your eyes until you get the key.
This is like in a suburban neighborhood. Board it up. I need to clean this though I love that sound.
Saw's in here right now getting ready. Hey you clean up the windows. Looks good. Very very good.
Excellent. This is what he does. All right there's there's a room right here.
So it's gonna be we'll need a wall. But first of all let me get the actual- let me do- I gotta
destroy everything. He thinks his name is Saw. No I know his name is not Saw. I know his- it's
Billy the Puppet. Jigsaw is the name of the killer. Billy the Puppet is the name of the Puppet.
God damn it he's too smart. Yeah I think I really am. I really do. I took the do you know your saw
lore quiz and I got a 60. I mean you could watch those movies a hundred times in a row and you
still wouldn't know what's going on. Oh definitely gotta make like this weird trap with like a saw
like a blade comes out of there and like hits somebody the head right. Oh this is like the gas.
Okay hold on keep that. How about just a tub? No no I'm gonna leave that. And there's bugs in here
too. Good. Okay how about like you have to fold a certain amount of t-shirts. You don't fold
ten t-shirts correctly like they do at Old Navy. Two minutes the room will fill with gas.
All right that's- I like that. That's it. Saw. This this saw like sucks. Living with Saw.
Living with Saw. Kylo Ren. No not every low voice is Kylo Ren. Not every low kind of mumbly voice is-
You know what? Why don't one of you make an edit where you just- listen listen to me. Make an edit
with Saw talking instead of Kylo Ren in different scenes. You could probably find plenty of clips
that would make sense and do the vice versa. Do it the other way. You could probably replace
Saw talking with a bunch of scenes in Star Wars and it would probably go seamlessly together.
The other way it could be true too. Oh look at this. This is one of those like
best part about the Saw movies is when like they go they open the door. They open the door like this
and they see kind of whatever it is and it goes it zooms in like all sepia and fucked up and it
like shows all the like the wires. Yeah I like this already. And then it zooms in on their face
and they go like and like they the head ghosts a little while they shake it around. Yeah they
don't used to do. A mirror. You need to beat yourself in a staring contest. I like it. Yeah
yeah yeah unwinnable unwinnable. Oh yeah? Well somebody just said it. You break the glass with
your fist. You have to break the glass and take the mirror out. That's winnable. All right so we
have look at the mirror or the you'll get killed. We have the waiting room and obviously how do these
people they have to be put somewhere while the stuff is being made. He comes in it's like a
doctor's office. Okay it's time for uh Mike. Mike come with me. Yeah oh yeah how you doing? Yeah
we're gonna be on this one on the left. Yeah sunny day yeah it's very sunny. Yep go ahead and sit in
there. Uh yeah don't mind the bugs. And these be waiting room. Cry cry cry. It's an escape room.
I don't know what that what's the what's the trap gonna be in here? Saw waiting room. I gotta hold
on. When are you gonna do a tax stream? What is with everybody wanting to see like people's like
but why is everybody obsessed with tax stream? Do your taxes on stream? Is it okay is like a do
your taxes on stream thing a way to be like oh hey huh I can't wait to see like literally your
social security number your address everything that huh yeah I do your taxes on stream that's
like like show the first page though can I see the first page yeah I would you would you spend
money on this year hahaha what's that in the top let me like screenshot the top right for a second
be serious just to do it in a dark room why you want me to make like a doing my taxes on stream
a scary stream you don't want that that's like that's weird I already have to do the family guy
Peter Griffin family dinner stream I'm gonna do that by the way I'm I will okay I promise
before I don't stream ever again I promise before my final stream whenever that is I'm going to do
the family guy family dinner stream because you know what like eventually what what if I planned
on like retiring right what do I say to myself okay like I'm gonna do the family guy family
dinner screen stream because like what the who cares what if everybody fucking hates it and you
lose a bunch of like respect what whatever like I'm retiring in like six months anyways
don't retire idiot hey what don't ever retire I kind of want to put surround a room with these
yeah that's another trap room surrounded by glass very breakable but we don't know is all the glass
when it breaks will trigger gas in the room something something something something gas
something something this is gonna be something gas something gas you have 10 minutes you have
five minutes gas yes you have five minutes yes you have two minutes yes what does it sound weird
yes yes oh wait wait wait yes in 10 minutes yes we fill the room with sewer gas it stinks
in this room yes in this room and it's full of fart gas don't breathe in the gas pooh pooh funny
haha I can't get rid of this fucking toy okay so yeah um what about this room this room have gas in
it oh okay I I know what I'm gonna do in this room this room is gonna be the room with the
gross trash all over the place and disgusting things you must sit inside of this room five
minutes without all right I didn't let's go let's go let's go I'm distracting myself this is just
his bedroom okay this is where he sees everything from we're gonna put like tv monitors everywhere
in here we're gonna put like a control room and a microphone on the desk here's the control room
we have the waiting room is over here we block this off new skill point on saw on a budget just
guess I feel like that would be hard to do though all right we did so this is the this is the
entrance this is the house this has to be like red blood red or like just black right and then
this takes you the waiting room this is gonna be a wall here okay so they're gonna be a wall here
we need a let me block this out this is a room over here with bugs in it show your ass so this
is pre-recorded um no board the windows up I gotta pee I'll be back pee time oh fuck I was
oh fuck I have it I have shit oh fuck I forgot I have a new thing oh shit I didn't get it ready
fuck I I did get it ready yes I did ladies and gentlemen I am pleased to present I am pleased
to announce a new brb screen lots of people are asking what was gonna happen to the community
content artwork well ladies and gentlemen may I present to you the new and improved brb screen
with artwork that cycles what do you say about that I'll be right back yes you can thank lazy
luke uh for putting this together and you could also thank uh yen wen for making the animation
here this is gonna cycle through artwork take a look at that I love it it's beautiful it works
flawlessly too so here is how we will get a bunch of artwork how awesome is this how good is this
isn't it insane I'll be right back enjoy the art oh shoes there's a there's a lot of shoe
artwork backlog is that another shoe I love it it showed porn no it did not uh lazy luke is the one
that's programming all this it's so good too you know what I mean like can we give a huge
huge shout out to lazy luke for doing all this it's so good it's amazing because there's so
much artwork and some you guys like you guys are so talented so many of you guys can make such
crazy shit I I wanted to find a way to at least showcase it if I could I disappeared for like
three months it was a huge backlog huge creative uh community content night that just it could not
happen videos for community content night I'm gonna have to figure out a solution for two because
I don't think I can do those on twitch anymore but I wanted to have something and this is the
something and it is awesome too many of you do too many awesome things to not show why not well
uh the DMCA uncertainty has kind of thrown a wrench into that so this is either gonna have
to be a lot tighter rules on what can be shown or why is this a family tree it's art breeder
don't make them clippable or vaudeville but if I stream them they still exist and they can still
be pulled right I have a couple of solutions in mind when I'm ready to talk about those I will
all right I I'm back but I just I wanted to let this play out a little bit just so we could see
how cool it was and the best part is this is constantly updated so it should pick up kind
of where I leave off which is awesome I never ate ass from the start the truth is that's true
wait did I just oh shit I just give a definitive answer the two three year long question oh shit
all right let's go let's go let me I want to test them I want to see if I want to see if I
screw something up I might have messed something up let me see if I got it right I might have
screwed it up oh would you look at that it works perfectly it works absolutely fucking flawlessly
it picks up exactly where the last image left off look at that wonderful wonderful wonderful
okay uh it's I'm so happy about that it looks great it looks so good it's so dark so the idea
there are hundreds of images that are in the backlog the idea is over time you can enjoy them
during a BRB segment right because I don't run ads so if I don't run ads when I go BRB then show
those and that's much more interesting right all right here we go we need a big lamp too not these
I'm gonna leave these for now just because I need light in the house I just got a hearthstone ad
I don't I don't think I can control that that didn't twitch make it so like ads just have to
get shown or something I don't I don't want to do that but it might have to be like that okay this
is the puke room this is the fold the t-shirts or else uh you know that certain fluid will enter
the room yes all this why is this here that needs to go away here's this door hang your coat up
yeah I hate your coat up if you are when you come in please not gonna need it trust me yeah it's a
weird door I don't like it coat hanger of death what a welcome rug oh there is a welcome rug
all right that's my favorite warhammer faction the tau all right that's warhammer 40 000 uh the tau
just because of like the hero the best I just like their units I like their the infantry units
they're awesome you know it's the worst part about the tau they put the tau in a game they made that
warhammer 40k the real-time strategy game right added a couple of expansions to it and then they
they never put them in anything else ever again I would have played dawn of war 2 if the tau were
an actual playable faction and then they made dawn of war 3 and nobody played it so they like
canned it right stop cleaning fuck you're right sorry sorry sorry sorry I can add dirt don't
worry and now they're probably never going to make it on before forever okay let's go
get rid of this doesn't need to be here all the rooms are going to be so ugly don't worry
this is okay this is the puke room this is the another torture room this is okay what is this
this is the bedroom this is where okay we're gonna let's do this room now this is the saw room oh
sorry this is the jigsaw room I need a nice big computer desk hmm he just sleeps on a bunk bed
give him a ceiling tv no he's gonna have a have a corner desk here we go like he's like like nice
dark right here well I gotta move the bed this is too bad it's too big okay here we go now we need
a bunch of devices we need a bunch of keyboards and mice and oh we need cameras right there's no
like security camera really there's no security cameras give him a sex swing no webcam
webcams all over the place this is so stupid I need to sit on a shelf okay we'll put a camera
here what's my favorite warcraft faction um I don't know I don't know I don't know the um uh no
it's not orcs not humans goblins it's a goblins it's that's really I don't know why it took me
that long to say that goblins don't we're not talking about warcraft right now I didn't buy
shadowlands I'm not gonna play shadowlands I don't own shadowlands why would I buy shadowlands why
would I ever play shadowlands what would the point be I'm not gonna I'm not gonna play shadowlands
are you serious no fuck that you know I'm never gonna play that game never gonna buy it I didn't
buy it why would I buy it I've never bought it I've never I don't own it oh you bought
shadowlands I of course I didn't why would I buy shadowlands okay
like ban that person like actually ban that person like you've got to say that to me
okay he bought shadowlands and he plays it no he doesn't oh my god ban everyone that says that
I buy that shut up huh oh no he's he's he's lighting us in this room I can serve us
uh I need one of these I wrote it so many times no this is just this is like propane
that's not even the gas that we're talking about this is just actually gas for your grill if you
don't cook that steak perfectly on the gas I'm not I'm not gonna do any more gas references anymore
no more no more no more no more no more no more no more no more no more no more no more
no more you know the best part about this whole little routine here I don't think I've even said
it as amount the amount of times that they actually say it in the saw movies if you count
the amount of times the word gas has been said this stream I bet you they said it more times
over the course of that series why is it so hard to bet okay this bet is weird because somebody's
gonna have to watch all 18 saw movies back to back and put a time stamp if every time they say the
word gas who the hell who's none of nobody wants to do that it's like 30 hours of time
just control f the script I will I'll do it no no that's too much but what if the what if
there's ad libbing of the word gas what if it's not the whole thing you gotta what if it's ad libbed
there's definitely a few ad libbing times with the they walk in the room they go
buff smells like gas in here and that wasn't in the script all right okay okay all right but
who I don't want you all to do this because if you all do it and that means a bunch of you are
like spending 30 hours doing this we have to designate one person to do this I'm willing
to put up I'm willing to put up okay no no no two um all right I'm put this is two this is 250
million dollars if I'm wrong add it to the debt if I'm right pull it and I get to I get that
250 mil oh is that deal is that deal all right who do we who does this who who who's going to
be doing this I already did it you did maybe in the discord like you got maybe some of you guys
like corroborate on like one doing it gas doesn't appear once in the original movie's script what
okay home this is the this is the first part of the script welcome I trust that you are all
unfortunately since you arrived that counts as gas it counts nerve agent counts as gas
that counts we you gotta give me a little feel yes it does yes it does breathe okay if you if
he says the word breathing in if the words breathe in a certain fume that is a gas like fume nerve
gas come on he probably says that like 30 times throughout that movie you have to give me that
one it counts it does count it totally is a gas chat yeah come on no that counts the word breathing
comes up eight times and isn't it's a gas yes it is why would you say the words breathing
what is he saying what is he referring to what you're breathing in russia are you kidding me
no every time he says the words breathing in that counts i'm sorry that i'm gonna pull the deal
that's not true what else would you be breathing in in the saw movie franchise it's not a car
air freshener oh that counts that counts breathing in fume breathing in gas breathing in nerve agent
those are all considered gaseous gastric like objects they're not breathing they're dead right
okay what what that you can take that one off but if it's a reference to inhaling a fume that will
hurt you that is a reference it is a reference and you cannot tell me it isn't if whatever you're
breathing in hurts it's gas you're gonna lose immediately come what wasn't part of the deal
no it's part of the deal you've said the word gas yeah but like we have to adjust the deal was
about the word no come on sorry sorry nerve agent agent playing semantics with this one you know
exactly what i'm talking about tinny pike saw house nerve agent is not gas yes it is it's a
that's exactly what i was talking about if he says the word nerve agent 20 times in that movie
and you don't give it to me i'm gonna be very upset with that you said it more than 20 times
yeah i said over the course of the entire franchise i didn't say install one saw filter play the game
and with the soft filter no no that's gonna ruin it it's on oh shit
it's oh fuck oh i thought you're talking about turn it i thought you're saying turn it on for
the rest of the stream and it would have stayed on oh shit all right we're good we're good we're
good we're good we're good you're arguing with saw about how he lost a bet that he didn't say
the word gas or nerve agent in his own movies what a bizarre stream this turned into okay
i need a door they gotta be yeah like scary metal doors and they're like a scary door yep
scary metal door not big enough what no tomorrow's thanksgiving happy thanksgiving everybody oh shit
tomorrow's thanksgiving tomorrow's thanksgiving oh it was a month ago in canada oh well happy
thanksgiving in canada you mean pre-christmas well i mean thanksgiving all right so now i gotta open
up this wall a little because this is the waiting room right i like thanksgiving people hands okay
there has to be cameras in here too i'm thankful for this stream hey thanks i'm thankful for you
being here and hanging out here thanks for hanging out here and welcome thanks didn't even buy
shadowlands one but should the waiting room have a normal door what's over here oh wait this is the
this is the secret room no no this is the puke room i gotta get rid of this the waiting room
should have a normal door didn't they make a new saw but it's not called saw it's part of like the
saw series or something right it's coming out soon what's it called it has a completely different
name not jigsaw no no no spiral yeah the movie's called spiral and it's in the saw universe but it's
not saw spiral not spyro it's got chris rock and samuel jackson i feel like i kind of want to watch
that movie was i doing our door door uh how about this this looks nice it's terrible too many buttons
too many buttons i don't like it too many buttons too many buttons that looks nice this is the
waiting room should there be tvs that showing everyone else getting like tortured no no no
that's the spoiler okay i need some paint let's make this look nice what's the waiting room what
color is the waiting room where's the paint i have the paint brush oh i don't have the paint brush
oh you do okay okay where's paint balls right okay waiting room would be uh like a white like a beige
biscuit natural beige there's a virus link don't link virus links dude i i gotta tell you we have
a lot of there's a big i've got to be one of the only people on twitch that allows people just to
put links in chat you guys have been very very good about it don't ruin it now i got a virus
what the fuck no i you didn't because i know that didn't happen i got a virus i did i don't get a
virus go ahead i know i just said that i know but just just hear me out don't click links don't
click random links is the new like don't answer the phone that you don't recognize don't pick up
your phone if you don't recognize the phone number if they if they'll leave it they'll go to voicemail
if they're so important like oh let me look at my phone who is this calling uh it's a random
number from an area code i've never fucking heard of not gonna answer that that's clean window
paintings and stuff i want better couches in this they're people looking to line up to buy this
house why can somebody look at my twitch statistics and see if this is the most time i've ever played
on a game on stream i'm curious if it is i feel like it probably is all right uh i want i like
different lights somehow i think red dead redemption 2 is high up on that list i don't know how
different couches do i have a nickelodeon snick couch we've got an epic link in chat do we right
but no this is not fair this isn't fair number of times a character says the word gas in all the
saw movies saw one zero saw two four they don't say it again till saw seven and they say three
times but what about the other stuff like nerve agent or fumes or toxic fume it's got to be like
20 times no no that come on that doesn't count you need to verify your sources yeah like this
is an english project somebody just did do it again but then run it through to see how many
times the word nerve agent nerve fumes uh fumes poison toxic there's a poison crossing through
your nose right i come on do it somebody do it gashes yeah they only use gas in saw two
no they don't they use gas and like the whole franchise he's always picked making people smell
gas they either smell gas or they have to get a key out of their stomach this is a dog coach oh
never mind give me something else here this is nice i'll make it a nice wood color
wait do you have another one did somebody do it i don't know what i clicked on i don't know what
i clicked on i don't know what i clicked on i don't know what i clicked on
can you hear me
is one is this and welcome yes two is important salvation if you earn it three hours from now the
door to this house will open unfortunately you only have two hours to live right now
you are breathing in the deadly three since you arrived here those of you familiar with the tokyo
subway attacks oh it's devastating effects on the human body the only way to overcome it
yes and walk out that door or is to find an antidote several are hidden around this house
one is you okay that's not fair it's not fair it's a nerve agent they he probably says the word
nerve 2500 times in that movie i should have said anything like nerve gas nerve agent fume why why
all right the waiting room is good i need a little table here how many okay how many times
you say the word fumes how many times to say pain fumes you stay in this room for more than a few
minutes he probably does something like that right god damn it whatever three billion no it's like
2.9 billion whatever i don't have that much money whatever i don't have that much money fumes
in this room 16 pounds of regular smelling smell down the stairs only to be locked there's probably
something like that in those movies he definitely says like how many times did i do it like 100
there we go cool i thought somebody was out the window very cool nice little waiting room
cool oh what's in this room oh this is the staring contest with yourself where you get
shotgun in the head right okay this room needs to be way smaller hold on i i can i'll change this
this room needs to be 10 times smaller here gas gas gas gas it's like a soundtrack it just linked
me a soundtrack it's like an hour and 30 minutes here i'm a noise mixtape this video is three
minutes long i've actually seen this is every noise i've ever made do it at times two speed
i feel like i'm hurting people am i hurting people i think this hurts is everyone okay
oh somebody let out all the bugs somebody let out all like the cartoon bugs
i can't i can't listen to this anymore i can't listen to this one anymore
i can't this is too there's too much a little 0.5 for a second what did he say this video has
10 000 views and it was uploaded yesterday what here it is if you want it i don't know
if i can't handle the other two three minutes of that video all right back to what we were doing
that's my workout jam we have a link wait wait wait wait hello we're getting swarmed with links
it's a new offer all synonyms off what i need to look at this this is a new offer am i gonna okay
hold on let me see if i want to take this or not new offer all synonyms of or and words related to
gas count as gas in the saw movies but it's only 75 million instead of 250 million and the saw guys
must say it more than half the number of times you've said gas for you to win i'm getting a lot
of no deals here sorry i gotta change this i gotta i gotta move this that sounds like a good deal
for me i need to shelf this is so stupid you could just lean back when it fires it's gonna
have to be a wall shotgun come on what the fuck it'll be bigger i'm not opening up any more links
okay when you're sitting down like this you'd be sitting like here like this there needs to be more
than one shotgun all right that's fine fucked up okay this is fucked up but it's a saw room okay
there's a sink over here okay now i can let's make this room a lot smaller it's gonna go like this
i mean if you'll get in this and sit down so let's go over here you're ignoring chat i'm gonna yeah
i'll put a bunch of tvs in the saw room cringe mode activated me what i do what i do what i do
okay here we go okay this firm is almost done just need to make you gotta put a bunch of gross stuff
everywhere okay fall off the window you cringed by being yourself you want about the shotgun's
a tad too high oh yeah yeah let me let me lower it a little bit that's thanks for uh thanks for
pointing that out uh let's do paint we need something that's dark and mysterious scary
blood red new deal no new deals don't make any sense unless all of you agree to the new deal
you have to all agree to the new deal especially if you're throwing around two three four five
hundred million deals yeah what was it anything over 500 million has to be voted on a straw poll
i'm gonna make this i hit i'm gonna make this a different color red and something else gray oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah finish jump king dlc for a billion i'm not i'm never gonna open that game
again i'm just being real with everybody i beat the main game i tried the dlc for like 40 minutes
and it said i'm never opening this again okay that looks fine did this be black yeah no this
should be black actual good deal incredible deal real deal good deal this is not even a deal all
right this the final link i'm clicking on i'm not clicking on any more links this is the last one
i'm clicking on okay so this is a deal or no deal what is that link play one round of deal or no
deal and get whatever you win off the debt no fuck that that game sucks it's gonna be a hundred
dollars the chance to win on deal or no deal is so bad it's such a dumb game there's one one million
dollar case one 500 000 one 750 and one 250 right there's 30 cases isn't there it's statistically
you're never gonna get those cases statistically you're gonna get something less than two three
thousand dollars i don't know how that show exists you would win winnings are times 100 really
winnings times 100 are we okay with that games lol dot net i don't want i that feels like a fake
website games lol all right i'm taking that deal i'm taking that deal i'll stream that this weekend
i'll stream that this weekend that's what we'll do this weekend we'll do some more game show stuff
right now what do you mean right now right now it has to be now it has to be now right now what
is that website safe hold on deal or no deal game it's msn.com
hahaha msn.com has one you know what's funny i don't even know which one of those websites
would be worse okay fine we'll do it now i'm gonna do it right now fine let's go i'm gonna turn the
volume down on this this is weird fucking loud no it's i and of course it's like a loud construction
ad what the hold on oh my god damn it i knew it ah turn off the music before i get in trouble
okay deal or no deal let me get it set up so many ads on this website fuck me dude hold on
what the fuck why is it not even capable i can't even capture this window chrome.exe there it is
where what the fuck where is it where the fuck is it you guys can't see it new offer come on capture
it why are you doing this no no no i'm hold on this is annoying better offer no no hold on i'm
currently working on another offer right now there it is all right i'm good i'm ready okay i'm about
to i'm about to turn the music down here can i get dmca'd for the deal or no deal soundtrack
is that possible am i gonna get in trouble for that i mean that's possible right i can't believe
we have to like think about that that's so annoying where's this where's this window all right here
it comes i don't know why this computer is just so fucking terrible i forgot i gotta like crop out
the ads hold on it's time for deal or no deal this is for 100 times right okay i'm ready i'll
do the music with my mouth do a face cam face cam oh put a face cam on everybody loves face cam
all right webcast not even plugged in for one million dollars are you gonna keep that case
oh i don't know chat help me help me chat should i keep the case or should i get another case
where's this webcam he have wires down here where is it i got it okay it's in controller has been
disconnected i don't care let me put my headphone back in oh shit i think my computer froze
don't freeze okay hold on i don't have any of this shit set up ever oh my god my hair looks so bad
i got a haircut too and it looks terrible i gotta put a hat on for this i know i'm stalling but just
give me hold on no hat no hat hold on okay it's off i gotta change that all right let me let me
get this ready bad hair yeah well i didn't think i was gonna be on camera today all right that
should be better if only i had some hair gel okay here we go this is for times okay i'm ready
are you ready to go this is the i have to pick my case i'm in i'm in the way of the money but
whatever do you really care that much about how much money's left you probably do all right i'm
right where can i i can't even go anywhere can i even go that's not in the way it's a huge delay
i just turned it off look up right okay okay i'm ready here we go i'm picking case number one
choose six cases 20 all right which that's okay 21 that's a five dollars that's it get it out of
here 22 here what are they fighting in the audience 23 i still got 750 500 one billion
i'm good six excellent that's 50 get over get the low numbers out of here oh that's a hundred deal
that'd be 380 000 right well i can do a counter offer and i counter offer a hundred million what
happened oh no deal no deal 19 nice one that's not really nice one that's not you know that's
that's a lot that's a good amount of money i don't want to lose that one 15 500 get it out of here
two nice one excellent i want to get rid of one cent eight excellent that's not excellent
that's not excellent that's terrible that's horrible no deal oh very brave time for the
next round 200 000 losing 200 000 cases of that's a that fucking sucks 11 nice one oh my god okay
five nice one that's better better that's better 26 25 25 excellent deal or no deal so that would be
hold on that would be 1.3 million no deal get out of here very brave million still on the table
if the million's still on the table you don't take that free good very good very good we still have
all the big numbers left that's awesome four ten bucks get out of here nine there goes one cent
that's two million dollars i wonder if i should take it no deal i'm gonna have a fucking million
dollars in this case no okay all right this is big this is a big deal this is a big deal
or no deal no deal oh very brave time look at the stats on this one look at the stats on this i got
this is i got this in the back holy shit or no no deal no deal i'm gonna be good this was times
100 right unlucky 13 get rid of it very prime for the next round get rid of the 25 16 get rid of
25 nice one all right all right or no there is a there was a 33 chance to have 750 000 times 100
24 get rid of it or no why would i take the deal no deal let's go it's time for the next round
i'm keeping my original case oh it's all right that's a lot that's a lot that's a lot that's
times 100 what's that 50 million how much is that that's 50 million off the debt just like that
good because i uh just put on an extra billion so whatever what was it 500 million double or
nothing i mean double or nothing you mean like you mean times 200 or it all goes away yeah i'll
do that we're gonna get loud add loud double or nothing times 200 or it's all wiped this is it
let's go times 200 born in september is nine i'm 35 years old 35 minus nine 35 34 33 33 31
30 29 28 27 26 auto is 10 years old 26 16 my favorite meal at mcdonald's is the number one
let's go pretty good start right up the bed it's good to get rid of these kill all these tiny
numbers we said no deal what are you talking about no you didn't we didn't no deal wait what
this is a deal this is deal no this is deal this is deal this is deal one guy i got one oh one
guy is just trying to mess it all up i see okay we continue i'm not even gonna look nice one
straw pole what do you mean straw pole all for the double or nothing no no we don't no no no no no
no this is not a five this is not 500 million no pole we don't need to do that nine nice one 400
gone what is double or nothing if you don't know what double or nothing is well when you uh say i
want to double everything that just happened or i lose everything go ahead get rid of this entire
column no deal oh very brave time for the next round what is the nothing in this case losing the
50 million that i just shaved off because i just won i just i just got 50 million shaved off the
debt i doubled nothing which says this is the one it's times 200 times 100 nice one good keep a
million oh fuck you how do you lose though well i lose by getting any of these because that would
be so much less so it's times 200 of what yeah it's times 200 whatever this game is all right
anything lower than your previous number what no nice one oh that's like impossible isn't it
or no very no deal time for the next round two excellent good good 12 it's okay all the big ones
are still there that's fine i gotta get rid of one dollar okay no deal no deal no deal very bad
odds next round very bad odds nice one get rid of the things around my case this is like minesweeper
get all these things away from my number they're bad no deal no deal that's the spirit time for
the next round okay good good no deal there is a one two three four five six there's a
there's a i gotta get rid of another one of these if i get rid of one or two more of these
that's a 50 50 shot to get something good oh fuck you the million's still there the million's still
there still there no deal that's the spirit time for the next round okay no deal one in
four chance that it's a million which is 200 million off the deck oh very brave time for the
next round or no deal it took the deal for 700 what is it 1400 dollars with 10 bucks in the
fucking case 1400 dollars taken off the debt it would have been 50 million stop what do you mean
triple or nothing i just got nothing triple or nothing how do i get how do i see anything bad
from that i went down to 1400 dollars triple or nothing but double the debt if you lose oh
but what is losing what what's losing in this case what do you mean if you lose anything less
than what something if something on the left side is picked it's a lose okay anything on the left
side this is bad oh i'm in 300 times whatever it shows if i do not if i get something on the left
side the debt is doubled from what it is right now if i double this debt i'm leaking a picture
my ass that'll shave at least five billion off number four no it's shit on the left side not
this side 15 oh my fucking god come on no don't do this don't do this 21 good there's no audio
oh sorry i was muting the ad five excellent no not excellent excellent good i'm gripping my i'm
gripping the armchair of my chair right now i'm gripping the fuck out of this
excellent good deal or no deal okay what if i take a deal that's bigger than anything on
the left side no deal that's the spirit time for the next round doesn't count okay i have
i have to see it through nice one no three oh nice one no that's not nice it's not a nice one dude
nice one no oh very brave time for the next round excellent no that's not excellent
i bet a million better be in this case i'm gonna be very upset no this is bad oh my fucking god
i'm ruined i'm ruined but i still i get 200 000 could be in that case
oh very brave time for the next round nice one i have faith in what i've decided to do today
nice one come on i'm holding the 200 i'm holding it nice one i'm holding the 200
or no deal no deal spirit time for the next round oh shit this is looking really grim boys and girls
nice one deal no deal that's the spirit one two three four five six one of the six chance
that i have the 200 000 case excellent okay one in five now or no deal no deal that's the
spirit time for the evil number oh deal or no deal no deal that's the spirit time for the next round
all that i could have just said no and nothing would have happened and it would have been fine
i could have just said no i had a 50 million dollar win and then i it's over i just i doubled it
no oh no oh well oh well yeah yeah i'll i'll find a way fuck i really thought i was gonna do it
so does everybody that sits at the fucking roulette wheel by the way i can't believe i
just doubled it now i'm hungry that just made me hungry i'm gonna eat a bunch of food later
i'm gonna eat so much food later you have no idea all right this room is done that's the camera
there's a shotgun staring contest whoever blinks if somebody blinks you die stop ignoring the ass
pick look i'm holding the ass pick in my pocket because it comes down to it and that's like a
two and a half three billion shave off the debt i mean like come on really all takes do it now
i'm not gonna do it now i don't i don't need to do it right now all right we need to put a
we need to go back to the saw room wow this is puke where's the saw room i don't even know where
it is here it is all right we need monitors okay bunch of monitors so you can like look around and
see he's his computer to control his cameras it's mcdonald's menu room yeah it is isn't it
that really is god why'd you just have to say that now i want mcdonald's right now
this is my first stream ever hey well welcome welcome cam welcome to stream everybody welcome
cam t please their first stream ever welcome what's going on every new viewer we single out
every viewer that's new my first stream my first stream was the 3do i can't believe you came back
so i guess nothing can be worse than that so you'll i mean i don't think anything will make you
upset i think you're around forever you're gonna be here till i'm done all right so uh i need a
computer monitor computer hey how weird desk is this that's weird isn't it it's weird why is it
like that he left oh sorry come on back next time i hope my mouse keyboard i didn't even say i was
gonna say happy thanksgiving how do i spell this fucking word it's an rgb keyboard he's got a bunch
of different connections here tons of hotkeys a bunch of macros and you can just kind of look
over there and yep okay oh wait i spelled tricycle um i guess that's not i guess that's
billy nice but how do i spell tricycle tricycle tricycle bicycle there okay what he wrote he wrote
like one of these he's like remember to get on my bike and do that it just rides down the hall
and rides by the opposite door and like rides by all right that works hey there's the bike i need a
chair all right uh he needs a mouse okay cool there there that looks good very bad deal
germa it's there's a homeless challenge if germa posts on twitter i have a big dumpy
and doesn't delete it then all offers made today are off the table if not they stay and an extra
hundred dollars are added wait if i tweet right now i have a big dumpy how much does that remove
i haven't tweeted in four months i have not tweeted in four months and i'm gonna write i
have a big dumpy but i can't say anything about it and i say i was put up to it by chat they put
me up to it but i can't ever speak of it again so like i have to i have to write i have a big dumpy
and if i bring up the fact that i was put on to do that the deal gets pulled away like i have to
act like i wanted to write that if i say well because chat made me and then i tweet later or
like in another stream or something uh no no deal nope no deal now that means i have to tweet which
i fucking that's not gonna happen i gotta i gotta fix this okay so this is the fold the t-shirt room
like a suit or like shirts this room can stay like this there's the gas right okay i don't even care
they can stay clean up the bugs no there has to be like bugs and weird shit in here oh it came out
too far no no no no no no there's no room i'm talking about is there is well the doors go in
there then fuck it where's the scary door i said shelter why this is oh fuck you why
germa punching punch this door punch it there we go ah i can fix it omega low chad you and me laugh
sometimes yeah sometimes well yeah well yeah yeah wait hold on move this this is like the you have
to sneak in and sneak through like the chicken wire they're electric yeah this is like i don't
know there's like apple over here or something these are all bad deals no no more deals i'm not
making any more deals today no more deals all deals are done i've made enough mistakes this
afternoon no more no more deals they're done they're over no more deals no more deals it's
over i'm not making it um no no no more deals they're done i want the door to open here right
there okay oh that's i don't want anyone to peeking on each other anybody else's torture
hey what do you do what's going on in your room the full laundry or it's i get gassed
oh dude i gotta make it through this like razor wire i get gassed any food in there i can see you
no notes in the classroom you know taking notes all right these rooms are getting close to being
ready fake laugh ha ha ha the walls need to be kind of all messed up though something would
yeah like wood panels okay let's go can you buy dirt um i don't maybe you can i don't think so
in terms of read this sneed haha okay whatever i don't know what that is they did add the garden
flipper thing right maybe i can do dirt or grass i need more panels holy shit you go through these
quick play left or dead with the bb boomer mod or debt no you guys are gonna have to come to a
decision sometimes you you can't just yell out deals that aren't gonna happen just alone you
guys have to come up with a solution for that you have to come up with a degree bathroom tile let's
see if i can put grass in here make it a google doc i can't get over there okay can i make a new
bet in the new saw not saw movie spiral within the last 30 minutes of the movie will
don't play i think it will of course it will you think so it might not it's not a saw movie
only suffering pace for the debt now fool okay anime villain all right it looks fine i need
fluorescence i need yeah green fluorescent lights all those movies have are green all of that weird
green fluorescent look okay what would it be lamps ceiling lamps hold on i kind of put this
i kind of put this in one of the rooms okay good vibes is the waiting room this is the don't blink
shotgun challenge uh whatever this is okay over here is the what is what is what is this i don't
know i haven't decided yet oh the puke challenge right is there a garage with a bunch of like
trash in it holy shit there's a ton of moles whatever leave them just make it a closet
what do you put your car there's no garage there's no driveway this is stupid remember things
everyone can afford a car i didn't say that i just said that there's no driveway and there's no
garage this is a house i don't know very many houses that don't have a driveway or a garage
at least or some kind of like driveway at least what do you put your just parked car on the street
yes nobody has a driveway you millionaire what are you talking about no what a lot of houses
don't have a driveway or a garage not an eu you monster i live in na actual billionaire what it's
a bill it's not you don't determine who is a billionaire by who has a driveway i like this
room so i like this room they could use a little decoration you have a helicopter pad too a driveway
is not even close it's not even close to a helicopter pad all right i need this to be scary
oh this is my room right okay this can be fine this i like this way it is this looks good all
right so then we gotta i gotta do some paint uh black just black paint you have a helicopter pad
you can't even pay your debt i don't have a helicopter pad i don't i don't know i don't have
any of these things no if i had the money for a helicopter pad this is why you guys are this is
you guys are bullshitting yourselves if i had the money to have a helicopter pad danny devito would
have been on the stream already you understand that i don't know how that's so hard to believe
i would have paid like i would have used that money to pay for like a full danny devito
pretends to be me streaming as me but it's not me it's him it's danny devito but he's still
saying my lines and stuff it's scripted i got my lines here all right this is looking a little more
saw like i gotta put weird lamps and stuff in here too german why are you painting the house black
isn't it gonna be really hot in here i'm fucking torturing people in here mate i'm killing people
in here i do do i care about how hot it is in the house why'd you just say mate i didn't
forgot about the good vibes with the gas machine above it oh sorry the machine it really is so
dark in here though i'm gonna need some lights he's talking through the spirit box don't put
in any lights force them to bump into the walls well no i want to be able to even see what i'm
doing it's gonna be lamps stream phasmophobia vr for 300 million hmm that means i have to get
back in vr which i can't really do right now no deal no deal sorry no deal play some music
for a million off i know that's fake that's fake this is starting to come together i know i gotta
i gotta close this this is a this is what's happening here though what's the chair for what
is this this is i mean there's obviously there's something in here there's a fluid in here that
if you breathe in it's gonna hurt but what happens in here we have a theme on every room this is the
wire room you have to sneak in and get in there and where you die this is the old the amount of
t-shirts you can fold in like 10 minutes if you don't fold 20 then you the gas kills you you don't
make it through the razor wire the gas kills you so what happens what happens in here gas no but i
mean but how what's the chair for hold on eat my high score in pinball where you get gassed cook
me a perfect thanksgiving turkey you get gassed uh yeah that works put a bunch of cookbook food
items in here replay the what song i need a counter one of these has to be a pool related
one hold on there's got to be a pool room which one of these can be the swim challenge hold on
all right get rid of the bugs dive into the pool of needles that's so stupid this is a halloween
party with a saw theme well not quite considering they'd have to be jello shots in every one of
these rooms even likes jello shots they're disgusting who's the first person that thought
that was cool to do that no who eats them and thinks they're good they're terrible and they're
always made by somebody that you know oh i made jello shots and it's just like pure just straight
fucking vodka doesn't even taste like anything it's just like you just put like ground up jello
in like gelatin with like vodka with like you did you made this wrong you made it wrong it's gross
and it just it's jelly vodka oh it's disgusting it's horrible i don't think i've ever had a jello
shot in my life that i didn't want to immediately spit out into like the toilet and the and the and
the jello they always they're always they're always not ready yet what's up with that even
though you go you go to like a halloween party and they're not quite fucking ready yet like they're
just barely being taken out of the fridge and they're not ready oh yeah and they're still in
the in the jello tray so oh i gotta like dig my you gotta dig my finger in there and like pull
one out and it's bleeding over the top of the tray uh thanks i guess and it's kind of already
melting in my hand oh this is horrible this is gross oh cool jello shot thanks dude airplane
food bit let me get the microphone to stand up for a sec halloween's a fun time but i mean come on
what's going on with those jello shots dude i know this guy knows back here this guy yeah the guy
that just screamed you like those i got something to tell you man sit down for this one i have to
do the stand-up comedy uh open mic night stream it's gonna be so embarrassing it's so horrible
but i have to do it i have to get permission to go to like a comedy club and i don't have like
any material i'm gonna come up with some shitty material and go to an open mic night get permission
to stream there and just do a set and see what happens i'm gonna be like a full suit with like
slicked back hair i want to have such slick back hair that like the slicked oil is like kind of
going down the sides of my face the joker no no this would be different this would this would be
different that would wipe the debt well that's easy all right so now i need a table i need like
counter top let's go to kitchen here we go here you go here's your food preparation area he said
he would do it for free i did say i would do it for free is there a turkey no there's no turkey
this food items though isn't there what about the microwave supplies oh here you go like tomatoes
canned meat i'm gonna make a thanksgiving dinner with what's on the table and if he doesn't like it
then you get chopped but getting chopped means you get gassed and there's no other contestants
there's you and the judge oh would you make a thanksgiving dinner with who puts tomato paste
on your turkey whatever okay here we go that looks good now we need a like an ac unit i need
to come on i need installation oh there's just these shotguns all over the place oh shit gas air
gun screw that in screw this in happy birthday to the guy in chat hey happy birthday to the one guy
in chat hope you have a good one birthday before thanksgiving double play among us let's go let's
go all right let's seal this up we need a table to put some more just like a like just a little
table so you have some room to work that's a coffee table but whatever you can bend over
seal it up reinforce door door
back at dmca'd i don't know probably i don't know probably what does dmca stand for
digital millennium copyright act cringe oh cringe millennial cringe millennial this is the only
normal door and it's my battle station for jigsaw okay we'll get our trap rooms are looking pretty
good so far this has got this is just a closet oh the puke bathroom what are some of the gross
things that would be in here that would smell okay we're gonna have an old an old jar of soup
oh a large food container that's just open with like rotting food in it okay jar of soup
okay what about the nuts no food tuna fish opened just canned tuna okay gasoline no all right how
about let's go back to food just like pickled like old pickles bugs everywhere peanut butter
smells good i don't know what you're talking about no forget that another another ac installation
right here okay if one of these turned on wouldn't he be gassing himself in his own house
you can't really turn this shit off you would you just you twist the valve a few times and he
but you have to leave the house too you gotta get out if one person fails their challenge
everybody's dead somebody instantly fails the challenge like the the razor wire guy just runs
in and just everybody just didn't even get to listen to their tapes yet i would need to be
dangerous looking i need what do i need oh wood paneling wood paneling is scary isn't it why does
this feel like a halloween stream it's not but it is kind of put in mirrors everywhere
thanksgiving saw trap well that's technically themed a little bit this is the smell room so
hello again david you can't puke into here or you know what happens put carpet all over the floor
yeah sure carpeted bathroom you already pukes and you need to smell anything that's disgusting
this door has to change this is just next to a normal closet no this has to be something
i mean maybe it is just a closet make it a snack bar it's just a little walk-in closet this has
to close just put a skeleton in there uh look go to decorations need one of these what can go in
here occasional um wait there needs to be a speaker in every room so they can be communicated with
let me do like a lip yeah there needs to be a tv
yes perfect there needs to be a like a counter or something or shelf or uh no what would
let's see something to hold this like a tv stand tv stand this is massive just stack the tvs like
oh hold on that's not what i do ah you can't you can't nightstand there's no such thing as
a nightstand in this game what furniture i mean this is small yeah that's fine
this guy's gonna be able to hear this guy's tv oh is this guy even gonna be able to hear his tv
where can i even put this oh wait wait wait there you go all right nice oh shit okay looking good
this one needs a tv too there we go perfect spot for it right here saw three but everybody has
their own individual room all right forgot you to make the dinner okay here so i'll put one in here
this room has to look a little more evil it's not evil enough yeah not evil enough it needs
to be look a little more evil eat box the bart man through the saw filter um okay i guess like i
don't know why i guess you made me do that for like i did it thanks for the sub or thanks for
hanging thanks for being thanks for following for the thanks for hanging out on this chip thank
bye this has been on the whole time here's the entrance there's a waiting room wait the waiting
room is far away from you just hear people screaming in these rooms where's the waiting
room oh it's right here okay oh yeah yeah all right so i can i'm gonna go like this
wait this is torture room right here this is the kitchen torture so this is the front door you
come in here we are somebody being tortured in there this is your waiting room the way to but
i gotta block this off somebody which one is this one right i bring them from the waiting room to
their designated areas this is fine yeah i just need to the walls need to be painted isn't it
paint on the ground yeah why does he sound high i don't think i do i would tell you guys if i was
i'm not no i've learned my lesson i got i look if i'm gonna do like cbd or something before stream
i gotta i gotta be very careful about the money that i take because otherwise i can't read an
analog clock and that's clipped forever since that happened i have been super self-conscious
about if i'm going to take that any cbd or anything before stream because of that
oh all right this looks all right waiting room so he has to walk from here so when somebody he's
like dies or whatever it's like okay that one's done okay uh tim come with me all right tim yeah
we're gonna be over in this door here and go ahead it's a sprint around the house all right i like it
so now i have to just do a little bit of cleanup we have to make some rooms a little better than
others decorate the entrance way clean this up i forgot there needs to be a tv in here imagine
the realtor trying to sell this oh that's right i think we're gonna get it before and after too
god come on i can't put this anywhere move the tuna cans and the jar pickles or whatever the
hell this is he bottles are he pissed in the bottles yeah i gotta move these sorry we have
to remove some smelly things otherwise i can't put a tv in here where's the camera these oh i need a
webcam he wants to get a really good view of him puking too he turned tvs on no okay are we almost
at the conclusion of the saw house i can't believe it yeah it's pretty much done i'm gonna wait i
gotta paint this room i'm gonna do teal or something sky blue do nuclear green the good
vibes in the yeah oh yeah that's a good idea i'll put the good vibes in the waiting room
this is actually creepier because it's like this i didn't clean this window what how good vibes is
going in the other room no that's his room over here i keep forgetting where all these rooms are
a good vibes coffee maker arcade cabinet oh you have to you have to beat pac-man you have three
lives sewer grade everywhere where's good vibes where's good vibes gas lights pretty good pretty
funny pretty funny what you just said i need to change this door too no actually this is fine
oh yeah i need the gas mask like the pig mask right does he have a clown mask kind of yeah he's
ready to put that on and then go into the other rooms i didn't realize what this said chill out
in your man cave okay looking good what the fuck is wrong with me no light in here i want this to
be um there's got to be like tv's everywhere right it always says zero o'clock in the man cave
it's always beer o'clock yeah nice nice gift shop nice back wall of every gift shop in every
hotel i've ever been in by the way only two things i require beer and football and it's a
like a bottle opener all right this is scary and horrifying and i'm 35 and think this is like cool
okay cool nice hold on i need some scary paintings uh i don't know no i don't know
what that is that's not scary painting a horse you got like a weird horse picture it's not big
enough to put clown masks everywhere i think that's overdoing it that's overdoing it just a little
it's overdoing it that's overdoing it man i hate when it does that oh there we go put in custom art
like i mean i could put just a bunch of pictures of like the actor like the jigsaw actual like
mask off and stuff just everywhere how do i upload custom photos is it other custom pictures or
where do you do that the thick ass everywhere use this one that's an mp4 that's not a picture
camera oh okay all right so where where is the um was the what's the file it's the actual file
path to upload photos these are just gonna be everywhere oh my god why would you have these in
the house when isn't this like telling people who you are hold on i'm saving them okay so where uh
what's the file path where do i put these i think i'm probably gonna have to restart the game too
right scary don't watch it scary scary scary scary i'm not clicking on it sell the house not yet
you don't need to okay so let me get this file path then so what are we looking at uh
uh just let's go to steam apps this is gonna be worth it don't worry steam apps house flipper
um i don't see it anywhere house flipper data resources no he won't click it i'm not clicking
it not in here click the mp4 no no no more links no no no what's the actual path what's the file
path well i'm just gonna well i'm leaving this on for a second hold on that's just a flashback
oh shit okay here we go i think i got it yep i got it you can just do it through the game
i don't want i i'm not gonna show you because i want them to i don't want to spoil them
okay so now that i have that get rid of this and make painting and place it on the wall how big
should it be oh god that's huge that's too big i can't even fit this anywhere oh no wait hold on
put it outside wait wait wait wait wait wait
i feel like we're watching we're watching the movies this is just stills of different huge
home theaters that are playing the movie this guy's an ego maniac yeah this is just playing
the movie hold on hold on hold on this we're gonna put a couch over here
when you come down
all right one of the editors you know what to do that's gonna get dmca'd but who cares
hold on hold on a second hold on me out of photo no don't auto fit hold on i want to why is it
doing that uh here's a here's another one this is just like a head shot this is just like his
head shot i can't i can't i can't hold on i can't do it let me do it no let me do it the way i want
uh i think it's done i don't think there's anything else i want to do this i don't think
there's anything else i want to do this anything else so so much for the secret of who the jigsaw
killer is it's this guy oh because i'm gonna wait my turn needs to be on this side
i'll tell you though i he's great as jigsaw he really is he was fantastic look after they
got to like movie four or five yeah all right you'd be pushing it but i mean like come on he was
great he's awesome okay i think i think i'm done with the saw house what no i can't save these
photos what do you mean what is a web of p image what the fuck is web p welcome to my saw house
oh i love it okay okay make it what no all right i'm done before i ruin it it's over before i ruin
it i gotta put a couch here though before it's ruined no no stop stop i'm gonna ruin it okay now
it's good it's perfect it's perfect now sell it oh shit shit shit shit yeah yeah sell sell sell
okay how do i sell the house wait yeah we first have to do a tour come in the front door
here we are oh already what is this a mirror for you to a mirror to face in life you will sit
once your name is called you will open the door so your number four will sit down and look in the
mirror the first roses your skull cap outside into the window outside the open window that shit's
gonna go all over the neighbors pretty ups will bring you to the entryway for more torture and
it was used four or five of the movies sharp object next room is disgusting dastardly t-shirts
the way they do that oh they do not have perfect square shirts yes we fill the room outside here
then we gather couch area which will allow you to sit and watch free am i still in the movies as of
saw six seven eight keep using my acting ability because i'm the only motherfucker in this entire
series that anybody actually thought was interest of course they gotta keep me in every single movie
carry the entire fridge in case you need to put something in there if you do put it in there the
final test the test is a very interesting one indeed because this is your test michael this is
your test the same exactly entire reason why i brought you here in the first place the door
is just locked behind you you thought this is a tour your test begins now i know how much you don't
like smelly smells i know how much you think it's disgusting beetles and bugs you wouldn't touch them
when you were a child now you must because if you cannot be in this room for more than one minute
yes yes yes yes the gas will start flowing only after you puke though i gotta make that
really clear i've been talking for a while only after you puke if you puke into that toilet
make your choice will you stand the smelly smells for 10 minutes or will you puke into the toilet
gas gas make your choice no no i just wanted to play a game of house slipper what the fuck no dude no
all right let's sell the house now that's like a thousand people probably just left
i was thinking about turning the stream off right there but i want them i want to help i want to
sell the house i need a light in here did like 3000 people leave i need some lamps so you could
even see anything i don't even give a shit what they are who cares if they're like golden i don't
care these need to work that's a ceiling lamp bitch okay i was like what ceiling lamp bitch
i was like what are you what are you talking about i seriously i was like that that's one
look at two or three pixels off okay hold on i need to ceiling stars oh this is stupid all right
hold on i need to see a ceiling lamp there no what that's not a lamp a ceiling light what the
hell is all this here we go i just need a couple so that we can even see what's going on there we
go okay that's good right there and then that's good right there so you can see the movie that's
fine in there who cares who cares okay who cares i'm ready let's sell the saw house you didn't show
off the turkey room well look it must it must not have been interesting enough for him to even
remember it existed he forgot he's gonna go in there tomorrow morning he's gonna make dinner
he's gonna make breakfast and he's gonna die he's gonna forget okay let's sell this it's time to
sell the sell it sell this house i think there may be too many sofas i need a bedroom but there
isn't one no kitchen wonderful we need a place for books i need one only one bedroom thanks to
this huge amount of pictures this house has its own character there's a lovely living room in
this house there are too many rooms there's no bathroom there's no kitchen there's no plants
okay there is no kitchen there is no bathroom this is the biggest scam ever all right i accept your
offer here we go wait wait wait whatever who cares who cares all you what's wrong otto you
want to go aside oh well there it goes i was sold and uh game crashed oh no it didn't all right let
me uh i you know i think that's probably gonna be it i think i don't i think i have to call it
on this one why did you put you put why'd you put george carlin in the hallway no that was
no that was saw that was tobin yeah i gotta go auto want something and i want to i want to get
up too i want to stretch and eat something i was hungry two hours ago that was tobin saw yeah it
makes all right that makes me want to go back and watch saw one through four doesn't it don't you
just want to go watch saw one again no what saw one is good so what's wrong with saw one it was
great they just made 10 of them after that you guys didn't like saw one i thought it was all
right i thought it was fun it was like well fun hold on i thought it was a good movie not fun
i'm talking about it like it's the super life of pets or whatever it's called two was all right
i forget every single saw a movie after five i've seen them all they're all the same movie after
five in my brain all right i'll see you guys you know i probably i'm probably not gonna stream
tomorrow tomorrow's thanksgiving i've just completely forgot about it we'll probably pick
back up on friday we'll do probably friday saturday because there's a couple there's i've
there's a few family oriented things i might want to do tomorrow afternoon i need i need to do
facetime family dinner with my parents that's what i'm gonna do we'll see but plan if i if i'm here
tomorrow then i'm here but plan on friday saturday yeah thanks for watching ending a little bit early
today but you know it's all right i think i got what i wanted out of the dlc the next thing we're
gonna play uh i'm gonna play sly cooper as the next stream so sly cooper won the ps3 remaster
hopefully it's good i'm looking forward to it a lot of you guys have been trying to get me to
play it so we're gonna play it i will see you guys soon have a happy thanksgiving if you're
celebrating it tomorrow i said yakuza well yakuza was going to be is going to be saturday remember
we were going to go uh house flipper sly cooper yakuza i still don't know which one probably the
new one these are all the subs that sub today thanks guys there were a lot there was a lot
of money to thank you guys seriously when are you going to do the auto stream um at some point yeah
all yakuza games are the same game it doesn't matter oh maybe i'll play the new one what's
it called the yakuza the dragon or something i'll try it the new one is an rpg it would the new one
is way different oh all right well pre i'm gonna i'll do we'll do i'll go back to zero i'll do
yakuza zero it's boring i try i played yakuza zero for like two or three hours and i gave up on it
and i think everybody was very very upset by that seven is good what the fuck i don't i don't know
there are as many yakuza games out there saw movies that's it the german 985 subs for me
that's not even that's a fake person it's me but yeah i'll either do zero or if people
i'll probably just do zero or seven or well i don't know i'll do zero i'm doing zero seven
is based well if i like zero i'll do them all i'll see you guys later happy thanksgiving everybody
see you soon take care yes