So I just went I just want to put on undergarments, right? I've put I picked up a pair
I have a lot of just black underwear, right? So
I'm putting on the underwear and it's I pick up a pair of black underwear and I get into it
Ripped here. It's so tight. What's going on? And I was like, this doesn't feel right on me. It was Kim's underwear
I just ruined them. I just I just put them on it. I was like, this doesn't feel right. This is weird
I like it was like a cartoon like Jerry Lewis putting on underwear. Okay, what was what were we doing?
What was I doing? Oh, I'm gonna save this game. This is to dereal
It was gonna hang out. It was asked me literally anything who cares home stream
I don't think I even have a comb right now. So anybody cares about just this space right here
Wait, I don't want to reveal any games. Wait, do I let's see. Hold on. You ready?
I'm gonna show you guys the shelf and you're gonna see how many games are on there
I want you to take a look at this. This is important. Check this out. Yeah, how many games are right there?
No spoilers. No spoilers. Yes. Yeah, I'm I display see man. I don't I don't want you guys see any spoilers
Where are the Funko's? Don't worry. They're fine
They're fine
Roger rabbit
Slimer
Hubert
Charles eat cheese. What's going on? Why am I? How's my seat so far down? I was wondering what felt weird today
Holy shit. My seat was so far down
That was comically down. There we go. All right, so
Now what now what you want to do? You have to put the booster seat on about lunch. What am I gonna have for lunch?
I don't know. Okay cheat. What we're gonna do. All right, let's go over this because
What do you guys want to do tomorrow?
Saturday is community content night part two. What do you want to do tomorrow?
Not nothing I can do about that. Okay
I'm sorry
I'm sorry that God decided that I was gonna have that for a hair. I'm so what do you want to say?
We want to apologize
Tomorrow I can't even fix it. It refuses to not be a mustache. I'm just I'm buzzeted. I'm buzzing it
It has to be wet for it to not be mustache hair. I asked me anything. Let's go. Let's do it
Ask me they'll even in the right category
No, all right. Let's go
It's your favorite color teal
teal a
large is your
Index finger, I don't know
Two and a half inches when you play super monkey ball very soon on the Nintendo GameCube
When you're gonna get sponsored by Chuck E Cheese, it's not gonna happen. You'd like their establishment though. What's my ones that I can answer, please?
Are you gonna play metal gear? Uh, maybe that's the last time you peed your pants an hour ago
When are you gonna do birdwatching?
That's a good question. I have no idea. I have absolutely no idea. I want to do the birdwatching stream, but I want it to be
Good. All right. Here's my fear about the birdwatching stream
I'm out there and I got binoculars and you guys got binoculars. You guys have your own binoculars for chat
So you can see too, you know, so I can like put you in the right spot
I want there to be a camera that's binoculars in the camera so I can when I look at it
You'll see it too. But the problem with that is what if no birds show up?
And it's just me sitting it under like a tree
Like four or five hours. Did I grow a unibrow? No, I think it's just the
Thanks. Just did I I try I usually Kim gets in there and she and she plucks it for me
Is it there doesn't look like it? Maybe it's like the bitrate. It's been a while though
No, it feels pretty bare in there. Maybe like right here. It's a little thick
It could use it. It could use a little cleaning
You're a mess
Am I actually that there's a car? Okay. Hold on. Here's the thing if when I go like this, am I?
One or two frames in there make it look like shit
That's the thing you could pull even if I look at you like this and I'm talking like very normally and I look fairly
normal one of these
Frames is gonna look wicked
And which one is it? I don't know. Did somebody do it? Let's let's do I want to I want to do this theory
Okay, I'm gonna say a sentence and I want somebody to just take a screenshot of me in the middle of talking and I guarantee
You my eyes are going this way. My nose is like going like this. My mouth is like this
They ready. Hey, welcome to the channel. My name is German on eight five
I hope you're joining us for some cool adventures and some great video gaming join us today
Good, let's see it right now. Somebody get it. I want I want you to pull one just any frame from there
I can't click that I can't I'm not showing that I'm not showing that I'm not gonna show it not showing it
Why did you make this okay this somebody's got one
I'm not I'm not showing that it's okay. Look it look at how fucked up I look
This is just a random frame
Let's see
I want to see if I can match how I look in these weird screenshots that you take in the middle of me talking
Doesn't like something looks strange. Something looks off
Normal my eyes look too big
All of a sudden the one on the right just goes man just jumps at the screen. Oh, that'd be awesome
It's the real one. Yeah, perfect. So I've here we go. I need to show you guys this because this is so important
when people
Show a funny picture that I did look at how funny and weird he looks
Look at this like crazy streamer. He's crazed
No, I think you just take a frame from in the middle of a normal sentence and I look I look insane
Gray hair. I don't have gray. It's the light above there. I'm cheese to meet you. No, I don't
Yeah, here's another one. This one's the worst. This is awful this guy. I used to do this
I used to do this shit for a living
This is every single photo of people at the wedding that are not the bride or the groom that are in focus
This is every single other image
Whoever is not directly in focus. You're this guy and you might just be eating he made money from this
Yes, I did. I did I did wedding shit
Because that was the job that I could do I knew how to edit I knew how to film
I I knew how to do these things. So I what can I do? I'm gonna make some cash. That's not new lore
I've yes, that's been known since like
Chuck left. It's okay. I feel like this is not real
Is okay. Here's that let's play a game. Is this a real image or not? I don't think this one is I do not believe
This is a real screenshot from the string. No, it's not you can tell look at the nose
It's not real because look at the nose and look yeah, this is that this is not real. Sorry and incorrect
Rotate not real you can tell by the tip of the nose and you can tell by the eyes
Not a real image. My eyes are too. The eyes are too close together in this one
Hey
Incorrect. I'm going up next on is this a real screenshot from the stream? This one is okay
I'm gonna my vote on this one is is yes
This is a yes from me. I think I think I believe this is probably a real image
Maybe not. Yeah, it's really look at you. See that. He's a space here
Okay, they were smart enough if they doctored it to put that in your dinosaur. I don't know though
This looks a little fat down here
like right here this looks I
I don't know. I don't think that's real. Maybe it's not I'm gonna vote real though. I feel like this is real
It's real. Okay, got it. Nice Raptor tooth. Hey. Hey, let's see your teeth. This one's also real
Let's see, it's also real. Yeah, that's a real image. What else we got?
Let's see this one this one. I I you know, I'm not I'm actually not sure about this one
Is this one day is this one a real image or not? Let's see. I wonder um
well
Mmm, it's hard to tell cuz like down here is the way that it seems pretty similar
Yeah, it's real. I think this one's probably real pretty close
This one's tough though. I don't know
The left one's the fake one I know this is real
You know how I know this is real I
Can tell you immediately because this is the exact face that I make in that germ of log thumbnail
Where I'm going like that. It's the same exact face. Somebody want to get it because it's we can verify the image
It's like handwriting like the way that your mouth moves when you talk is
Your handwriting that you it's handwriting like you can be identified. That's not a that's not a soy
Face, okay, that's me talking
So when I just said the a in talking talking go ahead ready when I say the a and talking
Talking sure. Let's see what it looks like show it to me. Let's see
Nice gnome. You got me. That's not even close dude. All right, it's it might it needs a little work right here
But I'm working on it. Where's the one to be talking? It's not this one. All right. I'm not I can't I don't want to show this on
It's this one. Give me the real one, please
People that are coming in and they said somebody just said this is so stupid
Why can't we to watch the VOD you have no idea what happened during the stream?
Could you like if you explain this to somebody would do you think they would even believe you? I
Don't I don't think I would believe somebody if they said this that's not even me. You're not even linking me pictures of me
I'm gonna get this off my computer
I gotta get this image off my fucking computer and off my hard drive
And then I have to fucking then I have to get a new hard drive, okay
Where is this picture? What's wrong with this one? Wasn't on fucking purpose. I swear to God. I swear to God. I swear to God
Why are you doing this?
What file is it? This is real, of course
I'm still being hosted
Shit. Oh
No, no, no, we have to abort immediately
This is an immediate this is an immediate abort scenario if I'm being hosted still
Okay, this one's like funny, but this is not even this is not even the same stream. This is a different stream
This is a different. This is a different place
Is this a pog? No, this is not a pog. I know there's noise coming off of this though
You want to know the noise coming off of this? This is the sound that this is making
Oh
That's what that emotion is that's not going like like oh no, no, that's very very energetic
Kind of energy behind it. All right, what else you got? This is too big. Oh Chuck E Cheese is offline
That's just a before-and-after photo
Alright, that's just that's one of those like this is what happens when you do drugs for a long time
The only thing it's missing is it's missing like four or five other pictures
That end up here. Maybe you shouldn't watch this stream. What else you got? I will add any more questions. Anybody got any questions?
Anybody have anything any questions to ask? Oh
This is okay. There's a shitload of people here. Let's talk about this is actually really important stuff
September 13th at
3 p.m. Pacific is
FTK that's what's coming back. You only need to be subscribed to the channel
No, no more of that two three month active bullshit. It's just not gonna work
I wasn't around for like months so I cannot expect people to sub through my absence
So September 13th put it on your calendar at 3 p.m. Pacific. Why is it happening so much later now?
I'm noticing the unibrow now. I'm noticing it. I see what you mean, but it's not there
It's really not there though. It's like something to do with how this shadow is gone
What the fuck happened
Okay cheese did something what happened we're talking about
Lucky cheese. No FTK FTK. You got it. Got it. Got it. Yeah
Alright, so it's not gonna be what you expect this time. It's gonna be a lot different. It's gonna be a
100% reimagined game. It's not gonna be just shoot arrows at him until he fucking gets drunk and
swears
No, he's blitzed
I'm not
100 of what what shoes I what shoes size do you wear 10 and
I bought seven and a half sandals and I just squeezed into him and it's and Kim laughs. Oh Kim laughed at something
Listen to this. I can't show this image, but it was fucking funny. She took a picture with her phone with my phone
So I was in the bathroom for a really long time yesterday
And I was just hanging out in there just like I was on the phone and like after you go
I don't know. I do this all the time like after I'm done using the bathroom
I just hang out in there even when I'm done like clean. We're talking clean and done completely
I just I'm just be I'm in here
I'm on the phone still like another maybe at least five to ten minutes. Sometimes a little bit more sometimes less
so I get out of the bathroom, I've been in there for about 30 minutes and
Kim is laughing her ass off at me. She's just cracking up. I'm like, what is so funny. What are you doing?
And she just she was dying laughing. I could not get it out of her
I'm just like what why are you laughing and she's like just wait, wait, wait, and she took her
She's like, please turn around and she took a photo. By the way, I'm just I'm in my underwear, right?
she took a photo and
The photo is of my backside. There is a toilet seat. That is a perfect toilet seat
Line red under my like on my legs
It's a big perfect toilet seat that's indented into my legs and I was really it was fucked
It was so stupid. It was funny though. That's why my back is fucked up
No, it's not
It has a toilet scar
Okay, you know how people when they play games a lot they get this like the little redness here with the mouse on the keyboard
I guarantee you I have a red ass. I guarantee it. I guarantee it
I have like an indented like inflamed red like ass and legs because the toilet seat
I have like the the gamer sore here
Whatever it's called on my ass because I spend a lot of time on the toilet like that. Prove it. Hey
Just gonna have to take my word for it. I get this off the fucking screen
I don't want you to see the shelf because it was spoilers from the cam off
But when this cam turns off the streams turning off this this got destroyed
Started off playing a game Chuck E Cheese became my new best friend
This has been weird, but I'm cool. It's fun
Draw it, but he hates you now. You missed a Chuck E Cheese comment
Okay
Anybody have any more questions, but no, I know FTK FTK shit. All right FTK. So FTK
Back the last time we did it, which is like four months ago. Now. This is gonna be completely different. It was
Kind of haphazardly organized. It wasn't a good set up. The servers got hammered this time this time
It's gonna be completely different. We're gonna have like a ton
There's gonna be like seven or eight servers linked together to make this happen
It's gonna be people you don't have to be subbed for more than two or three months. Just active subscription. That's it
There's gonna be a period about a three or four days before the stream happens
Well, we're gonna start to try to bring in like white list people and get them white listed
So we don't have the server get dumped with thousands of connections at the exact same time
This is what German plans when he's on the toilet. Yeah, no it is. You're right. This is you have that exactly, right?
Explain FTK
Well, it was called fuck the king and the goal was I was gonna get as many people as I possibly could again
Do a minecraft server with the goal is just whoever could just try to kill me
I had god armor on and they were all children
They were all babies and they would they would have tried to kill me like three or four hundred of them
But then it did that didn't happen
I don't have dying like three times
the server went down like ten times and
Um, that's all I remember I
Remember walking around singing and there's like just 60 people standing around me and just looking at me
It's changed. This is a full three to five hour experience. It's it's a full game. This is a game
This is not just like a okay. We're in
Fucking just walk over there and just try to catch him. I guess no, there's a full game. It's September 13th at 3 p.m
Pacific the server is also gonna stay up by the way
So when this is all done the server stays up for at least a month
So people can play it that didn't get to play in the server. That's really important. I will I will crush it
Please don't
Arm of death is back, but it's changed a little bit
You don't get banned from the server you get kicked back to one of these hub cities that they're gonna have
They're gonna have multiple servers that I have gonna have just be hub
Places for you to requeue to get back into the game
So you're not banned but you drop to the back of the queue
We want to try to cycle in as many people as possible and no gosh darn it
Let me tell you there's gonna be quite a few people being cycled out this y'all ain't gonna live
I can I just I can assure you that so like those you that are like, yeah
I'm gonna fucking live the whole time. I hope so. Good luck. Good luck. Make the germa is tiny sign again
I just like that person in the back of the queue. You're going to germa hell
It is kind of like a purgatory thing
Because you don't get booted out of the client or anything or out of the server you go back to one of the other
Queue servers. So how do you get in the queue? You just connect you just connect and
Then you get to you're gonna be able to you're gonna do a little thing
There's gonna be a slash like authenticate thing where it just checks to see if you're a sub and apparently it works very very well
They've been testing it for a little while
All it does is just is this person's subs to germa 985 actively right now. The answer is yes
And you can go in if the answer is no if hey, hold on if the answer is no
You still hang out this hub server. You that's shut
Speaking is difficult when you do it for a long time in a row. That's been about four hours of speaking in a row
And you'll die. No, you can hang out in the hub city. You don't you can be in the hub cities
You just can't join the FTK game
There are hub worlds people computer play can queue to play
I actually don't know exactly how the hub world like the queue world is going to work
but I'll obviously over the next three or four days, I'll get some more details on it and
Like not even like three or four days before the stream happens
There's gonna be a lot of testing on this as well
And I'll be in the discord asking all kinds of questions for people if they want to try to jump in and help
So that's a curse length where?
I thought that was real. I was like, holy shit. When did I show that much like underwear on stream?
I've never shown underwear like that on stream. I
Did ruin a pair of capes underwear though
I just put them on cuz I was freaking out and they just didn't fit right and I just ripped the room
Yeah, I didn't mean to wear them. I was I have black underwear. She has black underwear
This is a really fucking hard thing to explain
This is a really weird thing to be hosted by a family restaurant that serves pizza and as arcade games
I'm talking about tearing through my girls like friends underwear. Why do I put it on?
I'm not sure like anybody should be here right now, you know
Do you think that I don't think anyone should be watching this
We're gonna put like a family restaurant
Do a podcast. What do you want me to talk about? I'll do it right now
Give me a talk. Give me a topic and I'll talk about it runescape pretty cool. You can hey, how about that latest runescape update?
2.4 point to talk about the stock market. No, we don't talk about the stock market anymore
Thought after Beyond Meat, I don't talk about the stock market anymore since Beyond Meat
I got burned on Beyond Meat real bad. Yeah. Yeah, I was like, there's no way this is like a fucking $300 a share company
This is like more the way this was like more than Apple. I was like this is coming fucking way down
Like there's no way this is it's a fucking it's I did look they're good
I like them, but it's like as expensive as like Apple
I was like this no way you win some you fucking lose some you lose most of them
You lose almost all of them. You lose almost all except for maybe one
while doing that, okay, so
How much did you lose? Not enough to be upset about
enough to be irritated
What modulator voice modulation do I use well, it is a go XLR and it actually works pretty well
It seems to be very cool. It's pretty easy to use
Is you just plug in your mic I'll get into your computer and it's a compressor it does everything for you
I don't want to have a a compressor a noise gate a
End up like it's like an airplane up here. It's really really easy
Is that an ad no, I don't do but it works
What am I gonna be a VTuber? I'm not a VTuber. There's somebody else that might become a VTuber eventually, but I'm not them
Yeah, give me the image. When's the rumble the rumble is gonna be we're gonna be 2020
rumble will be on
January 1st, but December 31st. I'm gonna count down again like we did last time and in between
Matches at the rumble. We're gonna do a few categories for the worst and best of the year
I'm gonna do kind of a combo stream on New Year's Eve this year. That's right
combo German rumble Awards stream
countdown New Year and I figured we could do it like that because as
You all know I kind of disappeared for like two and a half months
So almost a full quarter of the year was kind of removed from this channel
So, I think we're gonna just kind of put it into the rumble I mean we're gonna do halo reach stream part two
I'm not ever doing that again. Make the nominees fight for the award
That's gonna happen at least once that will happen. I promise it'll happen at least one time at least once is
What that's gonna be a long stream? No, I don't think it will
Just think about it. All the rumble streams are all less than three hours long
It's just we watch it we do it I make it and we enjoy it and that's it and it's like two to four hours
It's not usually more than three hours
So you put some categories in there you have like 10 15 plus categories being add another hour or two to the stream
It's a four or five six hour stream. It's perfect
Okay, if you go to Chuck E Cheese, I think they give you one of these so this doesn't mean anything to me
You can actually get one of these
And I mean like that this is not that this photo I mean, that's really great
But this I feel like this is he writes BFF on every single selfie that people take with them
How do I know that I'm special? How do I know I'm his real BFF?
How's that? How am I supposed to know that he probably writes that on all of them, but if you turn it over
There's a note on it. You don't do that for everybody. See what it says on the back
that's the thing where you're walking towards somebody that's in the same fucking lane as you and
Like you've dealt you both move at the exact same time like football players trying to avoid each other
I just did that and I'm trying to
This what does it say on the back? I think my hands too small
God damn it. Hold on. I want to do this is a color corrector. What the fuck is this?
This is fucked up. Sorry. My OBS is fucked up. Why is it not showing me that? I can't like the scroll is so weird
Why is it doing this? I was gonna make myself black and white forget it. It says it says we're best friends. Forget it
I can't I thought I was gonna do something funny. Why this is annoying me. Why I wish I could show this
Now this whole thing is fucked up
What the fuck just brought like a bunch of little ants in my computer to do all this work for me that like that's behind
The scene stuff
I mean don't you wish I could just about have a computer with like an ants in it that could like they had lived like a
Really comfortable life in there and they can like control everything
And everything's messed up now. I don't know what's I don't know how to fix this. I
Opened up the fucking menu and now my camera just went down like ten points in quality
What is happening? Harold Albertson 9a5 just gave 20 community subs. I fucking hate this not you giving those subs this
Okay. Now this is the final picture. I have to like redo this. I
Don't know how this even happened. I touched the gamma once and my in cut my computer exploded
Don't look at those fucking spoilers back there. Get out of here. I
See you freaking like what's over there? What games that what's the next game? I don't even think about it. What happened to the camera?
Where did I go? Where am I? Hold on. What? Oh, I should the red I changed the resolution. I brought everything's broken
I actually broke it. I don't know what I did. I have no idea what's going on
Where is this picture? You guys can't see it, but it looks even worse. I don't understand
Okay, let me change this
All right up the stream is over the stream ended 30 minutes ago. I don't know what's going on now
I've lost it. It's I've lost control of the stream home again. Well, I'm working backwards. Hold on
This is just every FMV video clip on the Sega CD
HD Jerma add scanlines to it. It's been for I I'm gonna go I'm gonna go I got nothing else planned
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Tomorrow we're gonna it was it was Chuck E Cheese man Chuck E Cheese. It's just I feel like I'm in a fucking dream
Can we nominate best one guy moment? But when Chuck E Cheese derailed the whole stream?
That's my nomination. All right. I I don't want to hurt anybody's eyes
Yeah, I'm gonna call that. I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. It's fast credits. Holy shit
How many people subscribe today of a lot of very large amount of people actually?
This is almost a thousand people. Oh, yeah. Why did I do 50 community subs?
This one's just lost in my brain
fell right right right
Alright, so what are we doing tomorrow? What's the deal tomorrow? Saturday is the DLC part two
I mean we could do more of that game the ship one if not, then
We've got pick custom robo. I got custom robo. I got a bunch of Xbox stuff saw too
We you know what we might be able to do soft
Let me let me see if because I have saw to know how much time and wouldn't remember how much time was left in
Saw one like an hour, right? It was not ten hours left. There was probably maybe an hour in the first one 45 minutes
Yeah, I'll think about it. We're either gonna finish saw one and move on to saw two tomorrow or
I'm gonna play custom robo or
Mystery PC game anything about that. Oh that a lot of fun though. This was fun got a little weird, but it was fun
Thanks for watching as always guys
again
September 13th mark it on your calendar
3 p.m. If you're an active sub you can play in the FTK server. It's gonna get streamed
It's gonna be all kinds of fun. I am looking forward to it. No more euro streams. This is a euro stream. Yeah, it is
Started it like around noon, right Pacific. That's pretty euro friendly, isn't it?
Where's the radioactive skeleton pick I will show that the minute that I actually have it to a raid raid raid raid
All right, who do you want to raid?
We rating who's available right now. Chuck E. Cheese Chuck E. Cheese is offline
I don't think Chuck E. Cheese is streaming right now. Do it. Anyway a
Raided offline chat. I've seen a lot of Limmy Limmy Limmy Limmy. Who else we got. He's a cool dude
Tomato tomato tomatoes a cool dude, too. Yeah, that's too. All right. I I don't know. I don't know
What in half? All right half of you go half of you go to tomato half of you go to Limmy
How's that sound lame? Don't split us up. All right
That's not how you do it. Are you do it? You do it. All right number generator 1 to 2. Here we go
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
All right, we're gonna let me it was fucking awesome too though. Go watch him too
And go watch all these people they're all fucking fantastic. I wish you could split the raid. Wouldn't that be cool?
If we could like just like spread out a bunch of like it's for a bunch of different places
That would be kind of fun. Is that like too dumb of an idea? Is that like a stupid fucking idea?
I go tell go say hello to Limmy. That's a stupid idea. I wish Chuck E. Cheese is alive right now
We would just dump on him. All right, the next time Chuck E. Cheese is live
I want to make sure I want to dump a raid on Chuck E. Cheese. I'm starting that I'm going for it
Keep an eye out. All right. I'll see you tomorrow
Is this the second time I've rated Limmy, right?
Has he does he like look back and go like who the fuck is this guy?
Like let me we're coming to say hi. I
Don't know if he doesn't know me at all. It's just like we're arriving Limmy
Okay. Okay. Hi guys. What's up?
That's it Vinny. No, I said Limmy didn't I?
All right. See you guys later. See you tomorrow
Around the same time. Goodbye. Good night. Take care