Hello, good afternoon everybody. Uh, sorry I'm a little late again today, but Otto seems to be on
this, uh, new bathroom schedule, where at 12 o'clock, he's like, I'm, it's, I'm gonna go outside,
I have to go outside now. He's like, all right, let's go. So he's, uh, he's been on a different,
like, pee and poo schedule. Guess like clockwork. Yeah, actually though, but actually. Do I remember,
do I remember what? Wait a minute. The 21st day of September. Of course I do. I get it. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Oh shit, now I want to listen to that song on repeat for four hours. I do remember,
yeah. Do it. I'm not going to do that. That's, that's not good content. That's painful. It's
one of the best songs ever made, but that's, nobody wants to hear the same song for the whole
stream. It would be horrible. Do it once. I will. We're going to play Super Monkey Ball today. It's
been a long time coming. I'm ready. I've been told that this game is very fun. I've been told this
game is very hard. Uh, the how to beat has this game at four and a half hours. So you can assume
that I'll get stuck on like level four for about four hours. So it's probably going to be like a
eight hour experience. Who beats this game? It's first try in four and a half hours. I don't think
anybody does that. Sometimes I'll look at like the how to beat. I know it's an average, but then
you'll look at kind of, you go down to the, to the actual menu that shows the times. Like completionists,
first timers, right? Can't you see that? How the fuck do people do that? Oh, Dark Souls. Yeah,
I beat Dark Souls on my first attempt, my first playthrough in 18 hours. No, you didn't. You walked
around the fucking swamp for four hours at least in like Dark Souls two, Dark Souls three. Who,
how do you do that without a guide? I mean, that's normal. That's not normal.
Should be playing Super Monkey Ball 2 or Deluxe. I'm really sorry to tell you.
This is just Super Monkey Ball for the GameCube. I asked, I made it really clear. I said, hey,
what version is like Super Monkey Ball 2, PC, Mac? And everyone screamed at me. They said,
oh, Super Monkey Ball for the Nintendo GameCube. Don't play anything else. And I was like, okay,
fine. This is boo. It's not Deluxe. Does it need to be Deluxe? No, fuck Deluxe. I don't want
pepperoni, olives, onions, anchovies. I don't want that all over my pizza. Just give me the,
like a pepperoni or like just pepper and onions. I don't want your Deluxe pizza bullshit. That's
too much stuff to put on a pizza. That's too much stuff to put in Super Monkey Ball, the original
GameCube version. Let's go. Here we go. Here. Are you watching? Are you ready? Which says you're
playing the one for Vita? What? Okay. Okay. I looked over here and I see that stream preview.
I see a game called Hamster Ball. I was like, wait, that's not this. Is that the Vita? No,
that's my title. It's Super Monkey Ball, not from PS Vita. Super Monkey Ball Banana Splits.
Shit. Super Monkey Ball. There it is. All right. Refresh. Well, I, okay, I don't want it to be
Banana Splits. How do I make it just the regular one? What the flying fuck is all this?
Super Monkey Ball 2, Super Monkey Ball Ticket Blitz, Super Monkey Ball, Super Monkey Ball 2,
Sakura Edition, Super Monkey Ball Adventure, Super Monkey Ball Deluxe, Super Monkey Ball Banana
Blitz HD, Super Monkey Ball Banana Blitz Splits, Super Monkey Ball 3D, Super Monkey Ball Step and
Roll, Monkey Ball Junior, Monkey Ball Banana Blitz. How many games do they have? I thought
there was two. Super Monkey Ball. I just, okay, it should be, I just clicked Super Monkey Ball,
but it's just, it won't, it'll only do Banana Splits. Why I wanted, what's going on here? Why
is it doing that? I select Super Monkey Ball and it goes Banana Splits. Is it fixed? Who cares? Let's
go. It don't matter. If you see Super Monkey Ball in the title, just know that it's one of the
apparently 15 fucking Jason movies this game has. Let's go. Super Monkey Ball.
Main game, party game, mini game, main game, right? Make sure to guide the monkeys in the balls to
the goal as quickly as possible. There's no sound. Oops. We're good. I just played the game
completely with no audio. Okay. Main game. Yeah. Main game. Normal practice or competition.
All right. So let's do normal. This is definitely a Sega game. I can already tell. It is, right?
It's a Sega game. That's the Sega guy that talks after you touch stuff on one player.
Okay. I, I, me, me, baby, or gone, gone. Okay. I think it's going to have to be baby.
I, I, or it's going to be baby. It has to be. But do they have powers? B add X. Beginner 10 stage,
advanced 30 straight, expert 50 stages. Let's do beginner first. What? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
I have a question. Is this like Mario party where it's just adding more stages on top
or do the other completely different stages? So I got to go through beginner first.
They're all different. They're all different. They're all. All right. Let's go. I'm ready.
So there are fucking like a hundred stages. Oh, well, this looks easy. Ready? Go. All right.
That's fun. So it's like, it's okay. But it saves the replays. Bananas, three out of a hundred.
You just got to collect the bananas. Do I have that actual time limit or no?
Yeah, I do. It's right there. Oh, my like audio is so fucked up. Watch the replay for a second.
Hey, I got to get new. Okay. I swear to God. Go. Where is it? Oh, sick. This is cool. Yeah. All
right. This is like playing Sonic, but you actually get to watch rather than go. Did I make it?
Is there a jump? How do I jump? Oh, so there's no camera either. It's just whatever way you're
going to go. All right. Okay. I got 40 seconds of plenty of time. Oh, shit. You go fast. You'll
bounce. Oh, it has a miles per hour. That's cool. Bonus floor. Collect all the bananas. All right.
Okay. I got time. That's why this is beginner. I get it. Shit. I'm doing such a bad job mowing
the banana lawn. I can do better than this. They'll have dole on them. Wait a minute.
Is this a sponsored video game? Dole bananas. All right. I got them now. Oh, partially. Yes.
Oh, no. This looks like it's a little more complicated. Okay. So this one is,
how fast should I be going? You got to take corners tight.
Okay. This game's fun. I like this game very much. It's okay. It's all right. It's fine. It's fine.
It's going to happen at least once. Wait, do I have lives? Wait, when I run out of lives,
do I run out of lives? Yes. But you know what I mean? Do I have to start over? You do. Wait.
Oh, I missed one. No, I can't get it. I hate it. I hate that. I hate it. I have to get it.
Whatever. That sucks. You can continue. Okay. That's good. Shit. Can I go back and play that
one again? All right. How many bananas are here? What happens when I get 100 bananas?
Did I miss some back here? Get these. There we go. Okay. I got to make this cleaner.
No wonder I'm going to fucking throw up. Oh, that's a bunch. You definitely will need those lives.
Okay. I'm going the goal yet. Get it perfect. Perfect. Missed one. I'm good. Or eight. All
right. We only have two more floors. Oh, this is bad. Okay. Let's do it slow. No. I don't know
what I was thinking. I don't know what I was thinking. I thought I could go. I don't know.
Holy shit. No, this is hard. I'm okay. It isn't. Yes, it is. All right. I'm going to wait.
Poor baby monkey. You are on the dole. What? What do you mean I'm on the dole? What does that mean?
Can I go? I'm not going to go. I'm not going to go. I'm going to wait.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Rolling. Stop. Rolling. Stop. Rolling. Don't. 15 seconds. I know I'm going. It isn't just for lives.
Yeah, but you have to get them. Okay. Floor nine. This one looks cool. This one just dumps you down
there. All right. Don't go that fast. What? You have received 228 play points. You now have a
I have a total of 228 play points.
I'm gonna go again.
What do you mean sad? Why is that sad?
I'm just my first time
playing Super Monkey Ball 3D.
Are you fucking kidding me?
This isn't 2D.
How did I fuck that up? I don't even know. I don't know how I messed that up.
I don't know.
Oh my fucking god.
Why? I need some coffee.
I gotta get coffee. Let me drink some coffee
for a second. Just wait.
Okay. Get some good cider.
Stop.
Let's line it up.
I took way longer than it should have.
This is it. Final floor of Beginner.
This is to teach you how to play.
Oh. Thank god there's
bumpers. I wish I could turn
the camera just a little. I think I'll be
fine on this one. I'm not gonna fall.
This one has divots.
My chair was just shaking too at the same time.
I was just rolling down the
stairs in my chair.
Oh god damn it.
It says no. I can't even fucking do it.
Don't say hurry up.
Don't listen to them. Just go normally. Do normal.
Normal. I'm fine.
Alright. I got here with 30
seconds the last time. I got plenty more time.
Alright. Line this up. Don't be a fucking
idiot.
This is hard.
This is very tricky. It's tricky.
Okay. Do you guys know that game
where you have the marble in that little plastic
device and you have to tilt it around and put it
inside of the hole in the middle of the little device?
I was never any good at that. I always
freaked the fuck out. I always went over
it. Went over it. Went over it.
Went too hard. Went too hard. Went too hard. Went too soft.
And then I would just throw the thing in the trash.
Like who even cares?
That's not gonna impress anybody.
All that does is just take some
annoying time to get that right.
If you show somebody you do that they just go oh yeah
I also one day was
a fucking asshole and spent
45 minutes trying to get a ball in the middle of a hole.
He hates this.
You know what's funny?
When I was just being annoyed
I almost did the whole thing in one go.
I can't focus.
I don't want to focus on this.
Games like this if I don't focus I do better.
Give me a talk. Somebody give me a topic.
Right now. Give me a topic.
Oranges.
No oranges are gross.
I'm one of those people that thinks that oranges are gross.
I actually like clementines though.
Clementines are exactly what you want.
You want just a little bit of orange.
They don't get slimy. They don't have that weird white
film on them.
You can peel them so easily.
Alright. Didn't work.
It didn't work. It didn't work.
Just relax. I'm gonna get it right now.
This is beginner. Great.
I'm gonna be good.
How long has it been? 20 minutes?
That's like a good
meaty stream right? 20 minutes?
How long is this
Joe Rogan podcast? 40 minutes?
Alright. I'm good.
My computer just crashed. I'm good.
That was really weird. My computer just hard
crashed. Like it was hanging.
Exposed. What do you mean exposed? I only got
14 seconds!
Hey! You guys have clementines. I like how you can peel
them with your hands. They're much much
softer than a regular orange.
If you agree with me give me a fucking retweet!
Yes! It really is an ad.
You got 100 points altogether. You have
357 points.
Only 2143
points left to unlock
the next
game. Remember when people
used to try to pay me to talk like that?
I just did that for free.
What's this? Oh
this is cool. It's like Sonic
if you touch anything you lose them?
Okay so nobody can say I didn't beat Super
Monkey Ball. We're not talking about
difficulty. We're just talking about completion.
None of you can say I didn't do it. Super
Monkey Ball. I can't believe there
are this many. I really can't.
I was always under the assumption that there was two.
That there was one for the GameCube
and then one for the iPad that
nobody liked. Or Dreamcast.
I always thought that Dreamcast
came out with one and then they came out with one like a remake
for the GameCube. What's your high
score here? Huh?
What's your high score here huh? The iPad
fucking sucks. Alright can I skip this?
I know everyone's gonna be mad if I do. But can
I? Just quit back to menu.
Well let me just say how much I can get on my first run.
Skip it! I
can't! There's no skipping!
It's a forced cut scene
guys. I can't skip it.
We're almost done. Look in the
credits. You're losing bananas.
Alright how about this? Whatever
I have for a total banana count at the end is how many
community subs I will give.
How's that sound? That sounds good to me.
I hope we're
not near the end of the
credits. How much of roll
is over now?
How many do I have to...oh so far?
Oh shit!
Huh fuck! I'm hitting
things. Oops!
Oh don't
crap!
No! I really don't.
Hold on. I don't want to give
like...wait wait wait what does that
mean? What does that mean? What does that mean?
Minus...wait that's how many subs I
get now. No no no
no no no no. You're gonna twist that on me somehow.
You twist that on me. I gotta get it to
zero. You guys are gonna twist it.
They'll be like, no no dude because you went negative
now it's like you've minus...you have to
like deduct those subs into our count.
Let's just stay at fucking zero.
Let's go to
minus two.
Come on
perfectly balanced is how things should be.
Shit I'm really not trying to hit this
thing. I'm really trying to get it to...
Oh no. No it doesn't
go the other way. I didn't make that. I gotta make
that really clear. Let's be very
clear here. No it doesn't
matter if it goes negative. It doesn't mean anything.
No I don't wanna.
I don't wanna. There's the goal.
Alright come on. Perfectly balanced is how things should be.
Okay.
Oh wait. Fuck you.
No. That doesn't mean anything.
That's one two three.
I went minus one two three.
I was just trying to get to
dash one two three.
That's not one hundred and twenty three.
Unsub. Oh shit.
One hundred and twenty three of you guys have to
unsub. That's not good.
No no. Whoa whoa whoa. Hold on. Wait. Don't do...
Don't get too hasty
here because what's gonna happen is like
okay if I say press one
in the chat. Hey ten of you press one in the chat.
Two thousand of you are gonna press one in the chat.
If I say oh a hundred of you
need to unsub. Five
thousand of you are gonna unsub.
Let's not get
too hasty there. Don't get too hasty
there. What does this want me to do?
Oh.
I don't care. Enter your name.
That's my name.
Hi. Everybody
unsub. If you don't unsub
you're encouraging bad behavior.
Don't do that. You're going
over it. You are messing with
things that you are not to mess with.
What's like the villain say
in the movie when things are too powerful?
You're messing with forces that you do not know.
Something like that right?
Alright. Should we stay with...
Let's go Mimi. We'll do advanced.
I thought you guys said that it wasn't
just packed on levels.
Wait. Did somebody just gave a hundred subs?
Wait. Hold on. Somebody...
ZombieEater just gave a hundred community subs.
That's a lot. That's a shit
low sub. Thank you for the hundred subs.
Okay. Now those
hundred people delete them. Like just take
off your sub. Right after getting it.
Don't do that though.
Money. You know what I mean? Money.
Mini golf course.
Okay. A hundred
from...hold on.
A hundred from ZombieEater and
twenty-three from FireLactors. You guys are fucking crazy.
Thank you both of you. That's
an extreme amount of money.
How did I not get those? Got it.
Okay. Good. Quickly. Quickly. Quickly.
Quickly. Quickly. Quickly. Quickly.
I didn't even know that's what they did.
I don't know the game mechanic.
And by the way. Stupid game
mechanic by the way.
That wasn't me. That was the game mechanics.
Bad because bad. Mad because bad.
But no seriously. That's fucking hundreds of dollars guys.
We joke around. But that's a lot of money.
Thank you.
Just moving my rubber duckies around.
I'm the number one streamer that streams in a bathtub.
Oh shit.
Okay. That's not what I wanted.
I don't care about bananas. I care about completion.
I didn't get any. But I don't care.
Do you care? Do you actually
care? I don't. I care about completion.
I'm just holding up.
Didn't move fast enough. Nevermind.
You received 69 playpoints. You now have
a total of 426
playpoints. What are the party
games you can unlock? That seems kind of fun.
Alright. I'm going to wait and go now.
This one's going to be tricky. Okay.
This one's going to take me a while. Just a
minute. It's going to be like five minutes.
Come on. Hurry up. Go back.
Can I do this in one go?
I can. Imagine
there being a casino minigame.
Is that your way to tell me that there's a casino
minigame in this? Is that the way
you're going to let me know? Do I get to bet
my dull bananas?
Like a slot machine?
I see. Okay. I'm seeing the grins.
This is the most inefficient way to fucking
do this level. It's unbelievable.
I almost didn't make it either. Each
time you fall, you
what? I want to spoil it. I'll get them all
here. Spiral. Just do a spiral.
I don't have enough time.
Sorry. I had to let all the air out of my body for
a second. Okay. Good to know.
You got to wait. You know what? I think
I have to go around the whole thing, right?
You got to wrap around.
What happened? I won?
Oh. I'll take it.
Oh shit. This is a silly straw. I don't like
this one. Oh, let me tell you guys
something real quick. I bought this elaborate
silly straw glasses thing where
it was a big straw that wrapped around my whole
body and went up around my eyes as
glasses. And I was going to turn it on
and drink stuff out of it.
I think it was funny.
I snapped it in half accidentally because it was so brittle.
I was setting up to do it.
I was putting it all around my body and shit.
And what's wrong
with my computer? I like need
a new computer. My like
Windows is crashing. What the
fuck is happening? Shit.
Why? He's getting
hacked. I'm not getting hacked.
What happened? Oh fuck.
That's not good. That's
not good. That's not good.
I swear to God every time I download a
Windows update, my computer gets
worse and worse and worse and worse and worse.
It's like I'm taking my car to the mechanic
and every time
I go to the mechanic, he unscrews
something else.
Hey, man, can you replace my
windshield wiper fluid? Yeah, I sure can.
And he puts
like a little bit of windshield wiper fluid in and
unscrews something underneath.
And then I come in to ask him, hey, I'm hearing like a rattling.
Let me check that out. And he opens it up
and just fucking, he just like pees in
the gas tank or something.
My gas tank smells like pee. Yeah.
Let me fix that.
And he pees in the wiper fluid.
He takes a hammer to like the tail light.
Like every time I get a Windows update, my computer
gets worse. My computer just
gets worse every time I download one.
And there's been a bunch of them lately. Like I caught
up. I caught up.
Okay, let's go. I'm ready.
Gotta love those monkey balls.
Yeah. Hey, what's the
like I'm asking because like a
friend of mine asked me one day like
yesterday, he said, hey, dude, what's the button
combination if you have
like a computer and you
have a program on your computer that emulates
video games? He's like, hey,
what's a button combination to save a state?
And I was like, I don't fucking know.
Leave me alone.
I was like, why would I know that? Leave me, shut up, dude.
Alt F4. Yes.
Yes, I did. Yeah, I know.
I just learned what a computer was yesterday.
What emulator is it? I don't
know.
Sea bass or something. It's some kind of sea
animal. He's like, yeah,
uh, fucking like swordfish like
2.1 or I don't know what the fuck
that is, dude. Get out of here. Get the fuck out of my house.
What would it like
if you asked, what could I tell him?
Shift F1.
But like make sure it's like right though because like this guy
This guy's really like powerful and I don't want to make
him like mad. What if he gets angry?
Report him.
Shift F12. Stop
it. Okay. Okay. That was Arnold
Schwarzenegger exact cadence.
But not doing Arnold
Schwarzenegger's voice. It's like somebody
pitch shifted Arnold saying that like
stop it. All right.
I gotta pay attention. Yep.
What's the shift F12?
You better not be lying to me. You better not be lying to
my friend Dave. Don't listen.
It's Alt F5. It's not
Alt F5. That would be stupid.
That's close your computer's
desktop. Shift F1.
You know what? I'm going to look it up for Dave.
He needs me. I'm going to look it up over here.
I don't trust anybody.
Dave's pissed. Dave's like a
wicked powerful senator.
I get this wrong.
Like introduce a bill to remove my fucking
stream. Oh no. I'm dead.
play point. Okay.
Yeah. You guys are right. It's
Yeah.
I got it tested for him.
I want to make sure it was correct.
Go in the goal.
Good link.
I did
a hee hee. I went a hee hee.
I never hee hee on this stream.
Okay. I'm not going to fucking
Why is this one messing me up so much?
What is load save state?
Oh my god Jeremy.
Fucking just go in the goal.
F3.
Just F1 is load. How's it?
Hey like that. Tried.
I tried. I tried. I tried. I tried.
I was going for the Super Mario skip.
Click the link. Hold on.
I'm busy. I can't just click
any link that pops up in the chat. I have to play
Super Monkey Ball HD remake.
I was speaking to HD remakes. Holy
shit. Demon's Souls looks insane.
Demon's Souls looks so
completely different that
it's like it's going to be
like playing a whole new video game.
Even though I've already played through it within the last
couple of years. What? Last two or three years or so.
It don't matter.
It's going to be like Dark Souls 4.
I really thought I was going to get that one.
Yeah. This game is fun as hell.
I'll click the link. Hold on. Just give me a second.
What is it? The Chuck E. Cheese
thing. Yeah. I saw this.
Charles Entertainment Cheese.
But it's not. Where is it?
It's kind of scary.
It's huge.
It's too big.
Oh. Go smaller.
There we are.
Chucks VFF.
Too big. Too big.
That's pretty cool. Yeah.
That's a cool image that somebody
has made of me. That's not
me.
You know that guy Dave we
talked about? The powerful senator from fucking
I don't know. Whatever state.
He also said that he was having like graphical problems
in his game.
He's texting me right now.
He's spamming me. And he's saying hey
what the fuck dude. I started
saving my state but then my graphics are all messed up.
Fix it or your stream is over.
I was like dude
I'm working on it.
So what should I do if that happens to Dave's computer?
Tell him to stop breaking
the law.
Hey fellas.
This guy
wanted me to tell a senator
to stop breaking or bending the law.
Can you believe
this guy? I hate
these ones. I hate these ones.
These ones are too hard for me. This is on advanced.
I think I can still pull it off.
Well hold on. Let me see. What's going on with my voice?
Why am I turning into this?
I don't know why I'm like this now.
I'm just going to beat the level because I don't care.
Fuck the bananas. Fuck the
bananas. Nobody cares about bananas anyways.
They're radioactive don't you know?
This is water. Okay that's going to hurt my head if I continue
to look at that. Hey
we're getting text.
Hey Jeremy I got
really, my aspect ratio
in Swordfish
1-2 is going
crazy. Fix it.
Okay I think force 4 by 3.
I think that will help if you do, if you open up that program.
Alright I'll try.
You little fuck.
I think I'm just at this guy's mercy every day?
Jeremy, is it
still safe to drink almond
milk if it's two days after it's expiration?
You better fucking tell me.
How do I end? Oh it's
okay. I'm just like
yeah
we're
unstoppable now. Oh
fuck this level. What is this
point 1, point 2, point 4?
Point 4.
Just hold forward. Oh
that didn't work. That's the thickness?
Oh let's go with the fucking
hardest one there is.
You get more bananas. Oh sick.
It's going to even get
I failed the test.
This is fun. Okay I like this. I'm going to stay here
for a little bit. Line it up.
It's impossible. It's not possible.
You have to go fast.
How would you go fast over this? Really?
I have to go fast? No.
I can't do it.
I don't think it's possible. I don't think it's possible to do this.
I also have to go straight.
Yeah I also have to go
straight. That's right. You're right.
Just balance.
Pepe laugh. I can't. I need
the upgrade. Just go forward.
Look at all those bananas too.
This is awesome. What the fuck
is going on? Just do the easy
one. I'll do point one.
You can't even go on them.
They're covered in oil.
Just do the easiest one.
No I can't do blue.
I'll do green. I'm never going to
get out of this. I'm never going to be able to do this.
I won't be able to.
Alright I'll do teal. That's my German 985
colors. That's fine.
What? Wait wait wait wait.
Is this the end?
Shit. Game over.
What do you mean game over?
Save state. No.
Save state. Give me a fucking break guys.
You think I'm some kind of asshole?
No I have six game cubes lined up here.
All at the same level.
Lined up in different parts of the game in case
I get stuck. I have
physical hardware save states.
Is that okay?
Don't fall off the easiest one.
Okay good. Blue.
LL. Fuck you're right. I'm going to do it right.
Oh my god I can't even.
What the hell is going on?
Fell off. I didn't fall off the easiest one.
I deliberately fell off the easiest one.
My fingers are like sweating and cold and shit.
My hands are sweating
and cold.
How? Why does that happen to me?
How can you be sweating and cold
on your fucking hands?
Rage already. No. Why would I?
I mean
of course I'm getting a little frustrating
to play.
I didn't do the easiest one.
That's all I care about.
Oh look at this one.
Don't forget the hardware save state.
Oh this is awesome. I love this one.
It's not even hard. It's
fun. Come on dude.
Multiple Dave states.
Senator Dave state.
He's a statesman. Holy shit. Okay.
Game sucks. Game sucks.
Game sucks.
Hates the game. No actually I really like it.
Imagine how much of a pain in the ass that would be.
You'd have to plug in different audio video cables
and a different HDMI source.
Here we go.
Oh there was one over there at the end.
What was halfway through advanced?
Do these move?
How do you not get that banana?
Dave states Davegate.
Davegate. I understand how this
works but my brain is having trouble still.
It's going with the moving
of the game board.
I don't care. Go in.
That time bonus is
trending.
Do you think I have that much influence that I could get something trending on Twitter?
No.
It would take like
50 times the amount of people that are here.
Why can I not do this?
Why the hell would I want that?
Why would I want that to be the thing that trends?
Hold on.
Let me just plug
in my other
gamecube number four here.
Get it plugged in
and turned on.
Davecube.
Senator from
Miami please step forward.
Yes, it's me.
Dave. I'd like to introduce
Bill number
S2101 to rename
the gamecube, Davecube.
I find this to be incredibly
important to our country's security and to
my ego.
I'm looking at you over there right now.
I just realized something. We're like up in space.
We're looking down. That's kind of insane.
Can the
Senator from Miami please step forward?
Yeah.
I think it's pretentious that I
put forward Bill
S2101 to
rename Dark Souls
to Dave Souls.
It might as well be this stupid shit.
I'll be honest with you.
If that was on C-SPAN today, I probably
really wouldn't be surprised.
I'm so not good at this.
These curves are tricky as hell.
I've said that two or three times
today already. Oh, this is like
fun as hell. Why am I doing that?
Is the level moving on its own?
This is fucking hard.
Why did I think that was going to work?
Dave State.
Those of you that are joining us,
you have to understand. Do you think
that I was going to be able to play
through this game
and get to this point
like 50
times?
Do you think that was going to happen?
We're already here 50
times.
Please stop pretending
I'm banning you for life.
You completed The Simpsons without
save states. Because I didn't know they
existed. I mean, I knew
they existed. I knew they
existed. But I wasn't
using them. Oh my fucking god.
I didn't know. I knew what they were.
Hold on. Let me just take a quick sip of something.
Okay.
God damn it.
I was out of the GameCube.
Just fucking out of the GameCube really quick.
Oh, wow.
That was cool. GameCube
number five. How many
GameCubes is it going to take?
I suck at this.
Your room would be so hot right now.
You got like 30
GameCubes all plugged in, all running,
all spinning, and all making disc noises.
Can you imagine hearing
that typical like
I am
people that think I'm going to
stoop to save stating
in the middle of a level.
That's not going to happen here.
I have to beat it at least
on my own. Man.
That's so fucking weird.
It just rips you to the side.
I'm not getting any.
What the fuck?
I'm pulling as hard as I can
to the right.
What the fuck is this?
What the hell, man? That's actually
infuriating.
I'm rolling as far
to the left and right as I can.
I'm about to freak out.
Somebody just put my finger
in my belly button and moved it around.
That's what it feels like
if I put my finger in my belly button.
I push and move it around.
It takes too much.
End the stream? No. What?
Resign. Resign.
I can't end it. No.
I'm not going to end it. I'm not going to end the stream.
Fuck.
I'm losing my mind right now.
Not because of the game. Because of the shit that I'm reading.
Oh, no, no.
You don't understand.
I'm holding left
as hard as I can to the other side when I get up there.
I fucking hate this.
I can't even fucking do it.
Alright, I'm going to put it...
No, I can't use that.
That's an emergency break.
I'm not pulling the emergency break right now.
Got it! Oh, fuck.
No!
I can't pull the Rat Tatooie
emergency break. I can't pull it yet.
I stopped screaming. What are you, crazy?
I'm going to go as slow as
possible. Fuck, it just rips
you down. No, my God!
I'm not pretending. I'm not.
I swear to God.
Okay, stop. I'm going to relax.
I'm not...
Imagine having to be really self-conscious
about the fact that you promised to people
you're not pretending to lose
at a GameCube game. Fuck you!
Fuck you! Stop!
Stop! I didn't even do anything!
Pull back!
I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything.
I didn't even do anything. I was going
so slow. Yes, your
problem. No, if I go fast, it just throws
me right off.
Dude, I'm holding it as
tight as I can to the bottom.
I'm holding it as tight as I can, and I'm just
slowly falling down. Ah!
No!
Fuck! What is hard like?
What I want to know. This is advanced? What's the other...
What's the hard ones like?
Take this audio and put it over
me watching
like big moments in TV shows.
Like daytime TV shows, like soap operas.
Like when is the reveal that...
Wait! No!
I'm in the hospital and you're not the father!
No! Fuck no!
I'm just having
extreme reactions to daytime TV.
Like, settle down.
Cut that. Okay. This is where I
fuck it up every time. Stop and
fucking run!
Run up it! Oh!
Thank you!
What? God damn it.
Lore 16.
I'm not doing that one again.
Let's first try this one. What do you say?
I had it.
Imagine getting angry about silly monkeys in a ball.
Alright, dude.
I need to do it. I have to.
I don't care.
Check this link.
I need 100 bananas.
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing? What have you done?
No, it's not real.
It's not real.
But it's so stupid.
Miami Republican
Senator Dave State introduces Bill which
would rename Nintendo's GameCube to the
DaveCube.
That's so stupid. I can't even address it.
No, I'm not pulling the rat tattoo
emergency break.
This is really fucking hard.
Four and a half hours my ass.
No way this took four and a half hours for someone to beat the whole game.
The whole game?
You're just bad, OmegaLul.
Wait, that wasn't even an OmegaLul.
That was a regular lul. I increased your lul
for you.
That's not that bad.
I can't imagine people that can just scream through all these levels.
Like, holy shit, how?
Watch the speedrun. It's insane.
I can imagine. This is insane.
You suck, dude, OmegaLul. Stop.
Somebody said Conan O'Brien?
I don't understand this monkey ball thing.
I guess it's really hard.
Gaming with Conan.
Conan O'Brien level
of skill level.
That's so...
That makes me feel a certain way.
It does.
Look at this next part coming up. You shitting me.
There's no way.
There's no way I do this.
Don't tell me to fucking hurry up. I hate that.
It's too stressful.
These are easy. Just get here quickly.
This part that I fell off on.
Who cares about the 10 straight seconds
it's going to take to Conan that banana?
Goddamn it. Stripper is in the window.
What window?
I thought you were talking about my window.
That would be really weird.
He looked.
I was just trying to figure out what you were talking about.
I did look.
Now slow it down.
What are you doing?
I got 30 seconds to get through this. Just go slow.
Fucking no.
No. It's that last little turn.
Conan would have the celebrity
play this part.
If it was me, then we would
really be fucked.
So Jerma, how you doing? You having trouble with this level?
Yeah, I'm bad at the game.
Me too.
I'm sorry.
I'm supposed to be like a
streamer or something.
You're going to have to recut this whole thing and redo this whole thing.
Put a dog here or something.
I'm really sorry.
You can use that idea though.
If I get like 10% royalty from whatever
the advertising comes in that show
that day.
I'll give you the idea and set it up for you.
At least one of those bananas.
I'll be happy.
I'm starting to think you don't have a bunch of game cubes
with safe states.
Fuck no.
I can't not pay attention.
They would be
stacked up in the garage
at this point.
It would be in the bathtub
stacked.
In the toilets. In the fridge.
There would be no where to put them.
You know what I think?
Here's the other problem. I think it's the music that's doing it to me too.
Oh my god.
My fucking computer.
Yeah.
Put on a different soundtrack.
Put a different soundtrack on.
Put another soundtrack on?
Wait, is there a race? I'm racing somebody.
Yeah.
I'm not sure how much longer I can take.
Like the Sega Bass Pro Fishing soundtrack.
Why was that one hard?
Oh, this one looks elaborate.
These shortcuts, damn it.
Get out of here.
I need this.
So I don't have to save the thing that
the Senator was doing.
Stop doing that. Oh, it's irritating.
I even get irritated in the actual pinball machines
if this happens. I'm just like, stop doing that.
Shut up.
This, what's this, water level?
First try, let's go.
This one's not even that bad.
A dull submarine.
What are you? Dull.
I just wanted to get the bananas.
Insane aquarium? Oh, that's one of the greatest video games of all time.
I'm glad you agree.
Alright, so I have to stay really close and then
bang a right, right? That's kind of how this works.
Jesus.
Alright, I'm good. This one wasn't that bad.
Why do you speed run this one?
That would be very hard to do.
Bring back grandpa.
I don't know, man.
What? You don't have to go in that hole?
Where's the goal?
Oh, it's over there. Oh, shit, okay.
Bring him back from hell.
I don't really want to.
Oh, shit, that's going to be fucking hard.
I already know it. Bring back Bugleberry.
You will see him again.
Don't worry. Just at least get the
big one up here.
At least. Okay, go. I don't care.
Oh, boy, this one.
Halloween Bugleberry
stream?
Maybe. I don't think anyone that's
ever played this game has ever fallen through that one.
I don't think so.
I think I might be the first one.
I'm going to hug the left side.
Uh,
what's the map? Do I get the bananas?
I'm running out of time.
How do I get those?
Hold on, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Do the mandatory
ego boost stream when Bugleberry's on.
That's a fucking brilliant idea.
Fuck the bananas.
I want them.
I want it.
Oh, my God, this one. I don't like this. I hate this one.
Are you going to play Saw again? Yeah, I'm going to play Saw.
I'm going to finish Saw 1.
And then go to Saw 2.
Probably on the same day.
Get a bunch of speed running this thing. Just do it.
And now, what?
Go down?
Is this on a slant?
No, this is good.
Oh, I could have got those bananas over there.
Shit.
Oh, my God, click the funny link, Germo.
Uh, I'm not clicking any links.
Can you play Hylix?
I actually have that now.
I bought that a while ago.
Holy shit, this one's insane.
I only missed a banana. Yeah.
I'm fine.
I'll be good. Hylix OST
fucks.
Dude, how would you do this without
Oh, my God, don't
just forget about the bananas and just do it.
Do it. Just go.
Oh, by the way, let me just
make a comment on this.
This is not a Mario slide
game. The reason why
I decided to play this is because I was like, man,
I wish there was a game where it was only Mario slides.
This is not it.
Super Mario.
Wait, I might just be making
this up and somebody probably just didn't even say this, but
did somebody just say that there
was a Mario 64 ROM hack
with all slides?
Did I make that up?
Did I, like, take somebody's words and just
twist them completely?
There is. No, shit. Is it really?
Oh, that's awesome.
I might have to look into that.
There are so many. I'll have to give them a try.
That sounds fun. I love
Mario slides. Don't fall
into one of the small ones. Okay.
Not too hard, not too soft, just right.
Not too hard, not too
soft, just right.
Like that. Oh, shit.
This one's crazy. Oh, man.
This one's crazy.
Good commentary on the game.
Oh, man. This one's gonna be nuts.
Oh, boy.
That's already, I can already tell this is gonna be a
this one's gonna be a hell.
I just tried to do the whole thing in one go?
No, I'm not that good. I'm not that smart.
Whatever. Just go really fast.
How's my voice not get tired?
Well, it's from years of being
classically trained to
be speaking and singing in a way.
Like, for instance, I'm
contracting my vocal cords in a way that make it so it's not
so much strain.
Like it's, I've been trained
pretty well. You're taught
during vocal school to only use about
10% of your power level in your voice?
I wasn't paying attention. I was doing
pretty good.
Oh, fuck you. What would 20%
of your power level look like?
And they make a whole TV show about that?
She's using more than
10% of her brain and she can
fold cars in half with her mind.
That's the way the lady could like look at
people and fold them into a pretzel.
I'm not gonna get this right ever.
Stop. It was called Lucy
with Scarlett Johansson.
Yeah. We're on the Conan
OST. There's no Conan
OST. They just play
Does that mean I'm going max speed?
There's no Conan OST.
Why would there be a Conan OST?
The Conan OST is just
background jazz music.
I'm looking at chat and I'm not
looking at the game. Conan OST.
Oh, okay. Well, there's
a Conan the Barbarian OST.
Hold on. Let me just
play it, play it, play it.
Why are you looking at the QRS
clip?
What a fucked up stream.
I was drunk.
Like really drunk
on that stream.
Okay, slow down. Don't go
this fast. Here it comes.
Okay, I got it.
I got it. I got it. I'm good. I'm good.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Oh, I have to go
that way.
Did I Dave State this?
Fuck. Not good. Just fall off. Who cares?
What the hell? How am I?
Everybody said what is it? Dave
State? Oh, right. You might not have been
here.
I don't know. I need to go fast.
Yeah, but I went fast last time. I overshot it, didn't I?
Oh, fuck. Okay, I got it.
Dave Cube.
I got it. Yeah, that's the
kind of speed you're looking for. Yeah, it is.
But that's not going to work out, is it?
What a fun level.
It's fun. It's fun.
Fucking god. Oh, fucking god.
Listen to me. I said like fucking cool.
Oh, my god.
Is this a Dollar Tree streamer?
I'm trying to piece together what that means.
I think what you mean by that is
that this is
so the gameplay is not
high quality or something.
It's still good enough. You still use it?
I don't know. What does that mean?
Some high quality shit at the dollar store. I don't know
what you're talking about. You look like
you came from the dollar store.
With like a bag of groceries or something?
Like, who cares?
Like, oh, I have some stuff from the dollar store.
Wow, it looks like you really came out of the dollar store.
Yeah, I came out of the dollar store and I have some stuff
in a bag. I've got like a
baseball cap on and a t-shirt. What, is there
something wrong?
This is just Fall Guys flashback to that
stupid level that I don't like.
Oh, no. Okay. Is this the final level?
Can I go over there in one go?
Can I go for it?
I can. I can. I can. I can. I can. I can. I can.
Awww.
It's not going so fucking fast.
Dollar store strat.
That's not even funny.
Where's the humor there?
What's the joke?
I don't understand. Explain the joke to me.
Why did I go that way?
I know what it means.
Oh, shit. It's Frogger.
I have to get the rope. Okay.
Oh, please. Why did I get on that?
Dude.
Imagine being like a kid with
a GameCube controller in your hand right now.
And you have your memory card plugged in
and you get to here. This is a level of like
30. And you have to do this
bullshit like this many times
before you get it right. You have to play through the game
45 times.
Four and a half my ass.
Four and a half. Did I say 45?
Yeah, four and a half my ass. Not 45
my ass. I don't have to wait for a hole in the
cycle, I think so. Wait. I can get in this one.
There it is. Nice.
That's it.
I did it. We're free.
Wait, am I falling right now out of the sky?
Now to expert. I'm gonna
I'm gonna try it. Let's turn the music off
though. Oh, the sub thing. Right.
The sub bananas. Presented by
Sega. He's going to die so much.
Okay. I don't care.
The name doesn't even matter. That was
advanced mode. We're now going to move
on to expert mode.
I'll try GonGon.
Expert. 50 stages.
This is gonna be horrible. Was there some
weird link we wanted to click on? Alright.
Fake Trump
suite.
I've just heard about DaveGate.
The American people shouldn't tolerate
this name change. From Game
Cube to DaveCube. As a gamer
myself, I will not let this
happen. Senator Dave needs to
resign immediately. Right now.
Here we go.
Biggly.
Biggly Choo.
Expert time. Nothing. Alright.
Let's get the yo.
It's not. Why are there two
goals? What's a red goal do?
Holy shit. That's a lot
of bananas. I'm gonna get
them all. I just jumped to
floor five? I just skipped the floor.
Holy shit. Okay. I've jumped.
I skipped it. I can
see how 13
or 14 year old me would have played this game.
A million times. Even if I lost
every time. I would just be
after school with like a peanut butter and fluff sandwich.
And I would get sticky fluff
hands all over the controller and I would not clean it.
It would never be cleaned. It would just
cake on there. You know
what fluff is? Oh right. Fluff is
a New England thing, isn't it?
It's like marshmallow cream.
Kraft has a wicked shitty
version called like Jet Puff.
This stuff sucks. Not the same.
Everybody has fluff?
No they don't. That was
stupid. That was stupid, Jeremy.
Why are you doing stupid things?
Uh. Uh.
Don't you fucking crash on me.
This one sucks.
I haven't even played it yet. Can I skip?
We have fluff in the south. We call it
peanut butter and fluff. Fluffernutter. Yeah.
Me too.
A lot of places don't have it though.
That's hard. Why continue?
We already have infinite continues.
You're never going to beat this by the way.
Hold on. You say I'm
never going to beat this.
Never. The answer
the answer is never.
Shit that was so fast.
Never. Ever.
Not ever. Oh man.
You're too old.
Well. Hey.
How about this. I'll tell you when I'm going
to give up. Not the other way around.
Vod Watcher is skip.
Well that's the beauty of being a Vod
Watcher. You can watch
every portion of the stream you want. You can rewind
this ten times. And watch
me do this right now.
Fucking God. You didn't.
Okay. I was misled.
German Monkey Ball is like a Mario
slide game. No, no, no. It's a balancing beam
game. Very different.
And very much not in my wheelhouse.
Alright. Easy.
Okay. Oh.
Yuck. Yuck.
Balancing beam bullshit.
It's not a Mario slide game.
It's a balancing beam game.
Oh. I'm sorry. That hurt.
You're playing the wrong one.
How could they be a right monkey. Aren't they all fun
and all like this?
Although, wait. There probably is one
Super Monkey Ball party game.
Where it's just like Mario Party but it's
Monkey Ball. Okay.
Go fast maybe? Just run.
Am I going to fall through that?
I'm going to try to go very fast.
Holy shit. It worked. Boy.
My God. This is so hard.
No way.
Dude.
Not a chance.
In hell. That's so hard.
That's so stressful.
Somebody said there's like
one slide.
Why did it work the first
time?
Stop.
He's never ever ever going to win.
Okay. Settle down.
I'm fine. Okay. I'm at that point
in this room where I can feel like
the criticism. I can
hear it. I can feel it. It's like
in my nose. It's itching.
I can hear what you're saying.
Why did it work the first
time? Why did it work the first time?
Why did it work the first time?
Thank God I have infinite lives.
Right now, my
pants are sagging down to
my ankles. At the arcade.
Because they're just so, there's like
12 pounds of coins.
In both pockets.
I have infinite coins.
Let's
go to the arcade
with a diaper on. Full of coins.
Okay. Is the diaper on
over your jeans?
Because that would be okay.
Wouldn't it? If you had
a pair of jeans, like you had underwear
pants, like a pair of jeans on, and then you had
a diaper on over it. And that's what you
filled with tokens.
Is that okay? Like what's
wrong with that? Stop
you motherfucker. I swear to God.
What do you mean worse?
Hold on, you said you would get arrested
for doing the Doug funny?
That's, you'd get arrested.
Okay, so if I like brought a
diaper into a store and held it in my hand,
and I was like fully closed,
I would get arrested.
Why are diapers illegal
to own? Okay.
I'm starting to believe that they're, I'm starting
to believe the people when they say that I'm never going to beat it.
I almost, okay. Should I
slow it down here? Okay, I've failed this
over and over and over again by trying
to run past it as fast as I can.
So I'm just going to do it
the way that I think I should be doing it.
Oh my God.
You don't have the time to do that.
That's probably true. Probably right.
Seven out of fifty.
Yeah, but look,
this is one of the hard ones. This is the gear check.
If I can get past this
one, then I'll just skip to like level twelve eventually
with one of those skippers.
Okay, here we go.
I don't get it. I don't get it. I don't get it.
I'm going to save state there. I don't care.
I'm going to save state right there.
No, no, no, no, no. Yes.
Yes.
I got it this time.
Somebody just said, oh, yo, dude, I came into the stream.
You're playing this on the DaveCube, right?
Yeah, that bill passed.
It turns out nobody actually gives a shit if that's
changed or not.
This console hasn't been relevant in twenty years.
No one cares.
No, please.
Why?
I'm one of those people in like the shooting games
that pop up that they go, don't shoot
me.
I'm going to get real angry here in a minute.
I'm going to save state there.
Use the baby. Why?
Baby smaller?
Wait, is that real? Am I making this
harder for no reason? Am I?
I can't change characters in the middle of this.
Fucking my god.
What am I going to do here?
I have to get out of this. I have to get out of this level.
What the fuck are you doing?
You can't do this to me. You can't just
fuck up and. God damn it, Dave.
God damn it, Dave.
Why?
It's the fucking music.
I got to turn the music off. It's the music.
The music's going off. No!
That's not good.
Put it into mono? I'm not going to put it into
mono. Okay.
No, I don't want to just do
this.
What is this?
I don't care.
I really don't even care.
You could scream in my face if you
want. You could grab me and pull me and
scream in my face.
I'm not even going to need it.
My hands are so
greasy.
My hands, it's unbelievable.
Oh my fucking god, what am I doing? Stop, stop, okay.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Eventually.
Oh shit.
I ran out of disc space
for the save states.
Don't do that.
Okay, don't be a fucking idiot, man.
I almost just save stated while I was going
down.
I have to use one hand.
Ow, my chest.
I can't.
Oh, the time.
There's no time.
What?
Get it.
Fuck.
That one was fine.
How can you imagine
how, think about all the
times to start over
and get to the amount of times that I have
pressed F1, just on that
beam, and do it all every level
over again, and that's how many times it takes.
No!
Okay, so we're fine. No, that's not the right one.
That's the save states not doing anything.
Oh, sad is deranged
Jeremy now. Wait, what?
I feel like this one's my wall.
I really do.
Oh my fucking god. I am going to
blow through the rest of this whole
thing. Once I get past this
level, I'm going to destroy the rest of the game.
This is the wall. This is the dumb wall that I have.
Oh my god, my whole world
is blending together. The whole world is together.
I can see everything.
How the fuck do people play this game?
It's so ridiculous. The amount of
coins. I'm going to need five people to come
into the arcade with me, all filled with diapers.
All having diapers on.
Take a break. In a minute.
I'll go pee in a minute
and get some water. Okay.
Let's not screw this up.
Easy. Let's get it right. Don't
even if I fall, it's okay. I can do it again.
You idiot!
I don't think there was enough
there wasn't enough time anyways.
There wasn't enough time anyways, even if I got to the end.
Oh my fucking god, you've got to be
kidding me. I have to go much faster than that.
I've got to go so much faster.
Oh my god, this is bad.
Okay, hold on. Fuck you!
Are we really going to
hold on guys. Fellas, are we really going to pull off the
is he pretending line?
How badly I don't want to be on this level anymore?
I'm overthinking it.
Oh my god, I'm stuck here forever.
I'm stuck here forever, I think.
I don't think I'll ever get by this ever.
Put on the face cam?
No. Oh, I look horrible
today. All right, slow down.
Not bad, not bad time.
Not bad time. Not a bad time.
Let's go. I do that.
Can't.
Risky move, risky move incoming.
Risky move, I got it. Risky move.
Okay.
That was that, that was, I made it.
About 700 people left the stream.
So, welcome back if
you decided to take a break and come back.
I don't blame you at all.
In fact, I agree with you.
Okay.
That, nothing can be as annoying
as that one just was.
All right, it's still fine. It's fine. This one's not bad.
I think I thought that was gonna work.
Okay,
I'd stop doing that. I'm gonna keep crashing
the fucking console.
Is Microsoft Edge your default browser?
What? All right, where we going?
Where is it? Up?
It's not up. It's down.
What? How do I get down there?
Oh, that was
hidden. This was not even
in the...
I just hold the back...
Holy shit, man.
No human can do this.
This is a game not for humans.
What the fuck does this keep happening
for? Imagine the damage you'd be doing
to your GameCube right now if you just kept on opening
the lid and ripping
the power button and pulling the power, like just
you try to break your console?
Nobody just gave a bunch of money.
50 community subs from Freddy Dread. What's up, Freddy?
Thanks for the huge amount of money.
Holy shit.
50 more subs from Freddy.
On top of like the 8,000 he's given the channel
over the couple of years.
I don't care. I can at least beat it.
I don't care if I lose my pride.
It's still hard. It's still really fucking hard.
Did IGN beat this game?
I don't think they did. What does this game have
for a score?
It's just
balance beam the video game.
No customizable monkeys?
Fucking shit.
Your mama didn't beat this game?
No. My mother probably couldn't
get through 1-1 on Mario.
She didn't even care.
I think my mother's played
three video games in her entire life.
Jesus.
I have to balance.
It's not even
supposed to be a broken game. It's running fast and slides.
Mario slide game, yeah.
Doctors play this game before surgery?
It's hard to watch. It's hard to play too.
Incredibly
hard to play.
The fuck?
This is the first medical exam you have to do?
Stay on it.
Jesus Christ.
Slow down.
Holy fuck.
Holy.
I might just pivot to brushing my teeth on screen.
Until they're raw.
You gotta keep them like right in the center.
Easy.
Imagine picking
anything besides 0.5.
I don't know how you do
What the fuck just happened? Don't even fucking tell me
everything crashed.
I need these bananas.
Alright, so if I make it halfway,
do I get to clock out my gamer card?
No?
What's Aspect Ratio doing?
Water levels really just fuck up everything on the graphics.
What the hell is this?
You're right.
This technically is a slide map. You're right.
I'm gonna hold back on the
controller. I don't want to go too fast.
But then I can't see.
Damn it. It's okay. I'm still alive.
I'm off along. Stay right in the middle.
What was wrong with that? What the fuck happened?
That was okay. What happened there?
I went right through it.
Holy shit, man.
You can fall off the side too.
That sucks. Oh my god.
Don't move. Don't move.
50 floors.
There's 50 of these.
50?
Probably can't just sit there, right?
It's a waste of time. Shit.
The camera really fucks with me too.
The camera only moves if you move
your body. And if you have to turn.
Like I can't press
the right stick to move the camera.
Wait for another cycle. Don't be an idiot.
You have 30 straight seconds.
Oh, Jesus. Okay.
Where am I?
Are you aware that you're not moving the monkey?
Jesus blew my mind there, dude.
I am now.
Easy here.
Okay. Fine. Fine. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy.
Straight. Straight on. Straight on.
You fucking stupid idiot.
What? What?
What happened?
What was that wrong?
Am I not going fast enough?
I mean, I don't have a jump.
I'm starting to tilt.
I can't tilt right now. Relax.
Don't tilt. Just play.
We're good. That saved a bunch of time
right there.
Why?
You have to
go so fast. You can't go that fast.
How many times?
Press the jump.
There is no jump.
How many times do we have to go over this?
There's no jump button.
You gotta hold the
ground down while you go.
This sucks.
Let me see what happens. Don't go that fast.
Go fast enough.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Now what?
Not fucking around here.
Inball machine things here?
I know some of you guys are saying, dude, what the fuck?
Save states.
This stream would have ended an hour and a half ago
to have access to save states.
Shit, look at all...
This is so tight.
Get...
One of these times you're gonna lose the save state and that's when we
pivot to something else. AI dungeon?
Maybe. We'll see.
I'm still having fun with this.
God, dude, what the fuck?
You gotta stay so far on the left.
Dude, go pee?
I'm about to grab this ball
and just chuck it a hundred yards.
Where's the master hand that can come down
and grab this ball and just fucking shot put it?
I feel like
you guys are talking about the speedrunners that have
sped around this game that are like, oh yeah, I speedrun this.
Do they have any teeth left?
I feel like it's just a mouthful of gums.
Like just from mashing your teeth down, just grinding them down.
Gee, sorry.
They know how to jump for starters.
I'm gonna press every single button.
Ready?
Wait, what? This one's easy.
Just go straight on.
There we go.
Oh man, this one doesn't look fun either.
God.
There's 35 flows left.
I don't think I'm gonna beat this game.
What about the sticks?
I did. Let me at least just even see
what the hell. I think you have to go all the way up
from corner to corner.
See what happens. Ready?
I mean, kind of.
Holy shit, I have no idea.
Dude, Monkey Ball 2 is easier and it has
infinite lives.
Well, I mean, I'm already in expert mode.
This way there. You'll know when I'm done.
I don't get this one.
Hop across?
Like, the gap here?
Holy shit, okay.
Speedrunners do this game in 25 minutes.
Yeah, that's insane.
GTA 4 waiting room.
What are you talking about? When did I ever say I was gonna play
GTA 4?
I don't feel like Grim Fandango.
That's a good old game.
I played through it a couple times though.
Shit!
God, this is gonna make me sick.
What about The Neverhood?
I thought about playing The Neverhood a long time ago.
But this is before
Armacrog came out.
I was really excited for Armacrog because Armacrog was
by the same group that made The Neverhood.
It was a Kickstarter project.
And it was okay.
If I'm honest.
No!
It was okay. I don't think they could
capture the same kind of magic they had with The Neverhood.
Dude, how do you
turn the game board sideways
to go through that? How do you go through that thing?
Did they just turn it sideways
just to say fuck you, you'll never beat the game?
This is a...
What is this? Okay, this one looks awesome.
We unlocked a mini game.
Ooh!
Let's check that out. I'm gonna piss.
I gotta pee.
Alright, I'm good. Got some water?
Happy birthday! Hey, thanks a lot.
I appreciate that. Oh, by the way,
I'm not doing a
birthday stream.
I'm gonna take
tomorrow and probably the next day off.
I'll be back on Thursday of this week.
Thursday and Friday are gonna be
interesting because Thursday,
the Left 4 Dead 2
new community campaign
thing comes out. Gonna be playing that
with Joel
Tyler from Valve News
Network and Simple Flips.
That's sort of the plan tentatively right now.
I'm kind of rusty at Left 4 Dead, but I think I still got it.
And then on Friday,
Friday of this week,
I'm gonna be a guest on
Kitboga's stream.
I'll be messing around for a couple of hours.
That should be fun too. I don't know what the
exact plan is, but I just know that that's
gonna happen. It's a double pog
moment, yeah. Well, thanks for the birthday wishes.
I've seen some of the things people are already making.
It means a lot. Thank you.
But yeah, no stream as of tomorrow
or the next day. I'll be back Thursday
and then Friday. I'll probably stream on Saturday too.
Let's keep going. What happened? Where is it?
Did the game crash?
Yeah, it's crashed. When was the last state?
I don't know. Oh yeah, Left 4 Dead should be
fun. It's been a very long time since I
played it. That link is funny.
Is it?
Alright, let me slow down here.
Don't go that fast. Alright, you go much
faster than the thing spins.
AI dungeon?
Give me another minute. Still not done.
Jesus.
I don't think it should be happening like this.
I don't think it's supposed to be like this.
Wait, am I supposed to switch sides?
Oh, okay.
I get it. I'm going
the wrong way. Oh man,
that's gonna be so hard.
Okay, you gotta get in each individual
thing. This is tricky.
Ugh. Happy 39th
birthday? Not that old. Not
that old. Close though.
You are close.
Fucking game crashed again. 45?
No, not 45.
This is my own fault. I keep doing it to myself.
But, you know, anything to get through expert,
right? Anything.
It'll do anything to get through expert.
Where's the save?
No, not gonna happen. Get in it!
What the fuck, dude?
Are you looking both ways before
you cross the fucking road?
Ugh. I would've
already eaten the controller if I was 13 and I played
this. The controller would've been part of
a fucking soup. I would've chopped it up
into a bunch of pieces and put it into my stew.
Come on, dude.
What the fuck?
No! Stupid!
Ugh.
It's not- I already- It's already- I already blew it. If I blew it,
it's already over. I keep going backwards
because the save state was done and crashed
the game. Get in there! Gotta
reach into the diaper and get some quarters.
I do agree with you. That would be fucked up if I reached
into my diaper to get quarters.
But,
would it really be that big of a deal? If it was
over the pants?
Come on!
Alright, how do you- How the fuck you do this one?
It just dumps you.
Stay in the middle?
No, that's not gonna work.
Right up the side? Yeah, that's what I was trying to do before.
Just holding left?
Go slower?
I don't think it's slower. That wouldn't-
I can't- It's not gonna go slower.
Built the stage with the other
analog? I don't think that works.
Stay on it!
I just heard a crunch and I don't know
what it was. I'm trying to stay all the
way to the left, but it just dumps you.
Stay...
But if I get on the edge, it just falls off.
I can't even get on it.
Okay, it just- What happened there?
Why did he flip over? You don't-
You can't fall down and
tilt the GameCube.
Don't ever push right? I- I haven't once.
I'm only holding
up or left. Like I'm holding
left right now.
Hold right instead.
I'll try right side. You think it's broken?
I don't think so. I think it's just- I don't know.
I think it's just being weird.
Why do they- Is there a secret exit behind
the start? Sure there is.
Why did I listen to you?
There's nothing here.
You're lying.
You have to tilt
right or tilt left?
Like in the movie Cars?
Cars?
What are you talking about?
You remember in the movie Cars when
when
Flash Lightning
goes over the tutorial of how to play Monkey
Ball? Turn right
to go left.
You don't understand.
I can't go
faster. There is no faster.
Look at the real estate that I have.
I can't feel the speed here.
We tried to stop going full about just pushing
left. That's actually a good call.
That's not a bad idea.
Just hold right.
That might actually work.
Hold on.
I think you really do just have to
stay right on the edge here.
Once it starts to go that far up you just
can't go anywhere.
Start on the lower side and move
forward and towards the higher side to have
momentum upwards.
Like slide down and then up.
This is too much for my fucking
toddler brain to do.
Can you surf like a wave?
I don't know.
You can flip the board over if you stay on one side
then it will stay flat.
How much time does it actually take to go through the whole
cycle here?
See what happens?
It goes like dump!
Right at the end. There's like a little dump at the end.
There's a little more momentum right like at the end.
I picked the worst character
for this. I didn't know that the Monkey
Ball characters had different stats.
Isn't that not even right?
See if I try to pull
hard left.
It just doesn't matter. You go over or
it dumps you anyways. Just watch the speed
run. No, I don't want to be embarrassed.
Use the speed run strat.
What's the speed run strat?
I'm curious.
I feel like this one, I don't understand this.
Yeah.
So funny. You're making me
cry laughing right now.
It's absolutely hysterical
to me.
It is. Okay, it is. I'll be honest with you.
It is. It was pretty funny.
Shit. You're doing the same
thing over and over and you're expecting different results.
What else
am I supposed to do?
I'm trying to just hold. You can't.
I think this is
the end of the game. What if
I don't move at all and just hold left?
No.
Actually just stay in the middle.
Yeah, you can't though.
I feel like I almost had it.
Give me the link.
See how to beat this dumbass level. How do I beat it?
Super Monkey Ball. Expert 18.
Okay.
What the fuck is going on here?
Okay, so he, it's when
it starts to tilt over to the right.
He runs down
and then, let me try this
shit.
It's right when it starts to go down and then starts to move up again.
Here we go, like now. Fuck you.
You have to catch it like when it's coming back up.
Like,
now. No, I don't,
I'm doing what he's doing. I'm doing what he's doing.
It doesn't work. Okay, by the way,
the video starts like, he's
in the middle of doing something already.
He's like already on the move when the video starts.
He's already got like a bunch of speed.
Oh, what's the video?
All right, hey, look.
Watch, there's still a lot of rushes.
Check this out.
Like all the ads.
What am I doing wrong?
What did I just delete?
I just deleted something on my browser.
Oh, no, I deleted
the game.
I'm so fucking angry.
Hold on.
I'm pivoting to AI Dungeon.
I'm done. I'm done with it. I'm done with this game.
I'm done with this one.
Twitter, you get to see this.
They're spying on me. Get out of here.
That's what he did in the video.
He went like,
do a different monkey.
But how?
I have to quit the game.
How do we use a different monkey? That's stupid.
What, I go through half the game and then it's like,
well, sorry, you weren't the monkey you needed
to be this time.
Mangan is the worst.
This is literally a disinformation
campaign.
I came
here for monkey ball, not monkey bitch.
Okay, that person deserves a timeout.
I want that person to get a timeout.
Like for ten minutes.
That person deserves at least a five
minute quiet period.
It's alright. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna be...
No, I'm not.
You fucker.
Okay, here we go. That's it. That's it. That was almost it.
That was close. That was really, really close.
You gotta catch it
at the exact moment that it starts to come on
the momentum to go down to up.
Right now.
Stupid game.
No, you stupid game.
Come on!
Dude, that's... How the fuck do you
do this shit? Dude, was this like Mario
Maker? Did anyone in the office beat this level?
Or did they just make it and go,
that looks good. Did anybody do it?
No. Looks good though.
Put a hand cam on.
I'm not gonna put on a hand cam.
Hand cam tutorial
for this level.
You're not serious, are you? Are you fucking
kidding me?
This shit don't happen in my game.
This shit doesn't happen in my game.
I just fly off the edge.
I just fly
off the edge.
Okay, I'm gonna do exactly what this person...
So they land immediately when it's flat.
They go to the right. They tilt.
They stay on the right side. I've already been off the
left edge, by the way, at this point.
There we go. There is no
jump.
I'm trying to tilt with the...
You have to bind a key to jump.
I'm gonna freak out.
Dude, I'm holding up, holding le...
I don't matter. I'm tilting. I'm...
I'm finessing.
I'm tilting.
I fell off the fucking edge, dude.
All the way to the right.
Okay, I'm gonna do this frame by frame.
They're not even touching any button.
They're holding right. Okay, that's what I was doing.
And then they hold left
when it moves. Yeah, that's exactly what I'm
trying to do. I was gonna do the...
Okay, ready? Just go right. Do exactly what
they do.
I'm about to just rip the fucking
power button off of my computer.
You should hit triangle
to grind.
You have to go fast.
I'm trying to hold
left. Hold right.
I didn't even...
This is so ridiculous.
I didn't even mean to do that this time.
Hold left.
Okay, I don't fucking know. I can't do
anything else.
What do you mean, finally listen? That's what I've been trying
to do this entire time.
No, you piece of shit.
Alright, I'm jumping off and I'm holding
left and forward at the same time.
If I do that too quickly, I fall off.
It's dumping me.
Tilting. Just go forward.
It's not gonna do anything.
Just cap
the FPS. What do you mean, cap the FPS?
What?
Don't slow down. Guys, I am
holding forward.
I'm not hitting back at all. I'm
only going forward or left.
I'm not tilting the controller back.
Why do you think I'm doing that?
Try doing it backwards.
This is insane.
Imagine needing to do this
this many times. Turn the tilt
controls off. Use the
keyboard.
This may be a dumb question, but are you using
an actual GameCube controller? No.
I am not. Good luck
then. What do you mean, good luck then?
What do you mean?
What do you mean, good luck then?
What's that mean?
That's your problem. What?
No, it's not. There hasn't been a problem so far.
How long
have I been on this level?
Probably like 35 minutes.
Start by going left and turn right to get
momentum.
If I do that too fast, I just
go right off.
I got it, I got it.
I know exactly what to do.
Trust me, I got it. This is fucking the real one
right here coming up.
One of these. I know what I have to do.
Check it out. I'll get it in a
second. Wait, one second. Give me a second.
Shit.
Dude.
Come on. This is so
frustrating.
Just leave this game.
I can't do that right now. I have to beat this level
or else I won't be able to go to sleep tonight.
Is your FPS capped?
Would that even matter?
I don't think that would really matter.
I feel like the game is just forcing me down the fucking hole.
Cap the frame rate.
Cap the frame rate. To what?
Hey, I'm the one that said, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait. Hey, I'm the one that said Monkey Ball
was like Mario Slope Racing.
I said Monkey Ball 2, not this
piece of shit.
Hey, easy.
Easy.
Change monkeys for the love of God.
But that means I have to lose my everything
here, don't I?
No. Redo. Who cares?
Who gives a shit?
It doesn't matter. It's not the monkey.
I'm trying to do exactly what the thing does
in the video.
They go right here. And it's like boom.
Now they're tilting a little.
What did he say?
FPS cap in Dolphin SMB emulation has been
bound to cause significant issues down the line towards
the later half of the advanced levels.
What?
Physics are based on frame rate. Cap your frame rate.
Don't even fucking tell me this is all...
How do I do that?
Cap my frame rate?
How do I do that? Graphics?
Turn on V-sync?
How do I do that? V-sync.
Cap it at 30.
Anti-Ala-sync. He read my
comment out loud and he ignored it.
I did? Wait, wait, what do I cap
frame rate in, uh, fucking
Senator, uh...
Swordfish. Monkey Ball ran
at 30.
You ignored it again?
I didn't ignore it again. I didn't even see it.
Figuration, hold on. Okay, well how do I do that?
That's 16x9 gecko code.
I don't know what the fuck that is.
Gecko code?
Floor 18.
Original Monkey Ball ran at 30. 45
on LCD and 50 on a screen projector.
Go back
for fucking boots. Can somebody just tell me
what setting, what box
do I check? Read this!
The game carried none of the level
design to the sequel. 2 is a fun
racing game. This one is a bullshit obstacle course.
Monkey Ball Torture from Wikipedia,
the free encyclopedia.org.
Monkey Ball Torture, what?
Somebody has a tutorial here?
Let me see it. Title does not
need... Alright, I'm just gonna find
it. How do I cap my frame rate?
If I get it first try, after this I'm
gonna laugh my ass off.
Cap frame rate. Frame
limiter. Okay?
I can't seem to find the frame limiter for
this. Can somebody tell me? It doesn't exist.
Feature was changed to
speed limit. Speed limit.
Okay? Look at the speed
limit. Speed limit! There it is!
Alright, so it would be 50%.
That would be 30 FPS, right?
Is this the game I'm supposed to run?
Uh, I think this just
put it into slow motion.
Hold on a minute. I...
I'll get it.
I can't even do it at 30% speed!
Oh my god!
A bunch of drugs.
You piece of shit!
What the fuck?
I'm gonna get it! Get in there.
Don't go over the edge, little
guy! No!
Like, why?
I'll get it at 50%. I almost had
it last time. Give me the controller.
Actually, controller issue. What?
Read this. Read this. Read. Check. Wait. Wait.
Read this. Check your modular trombulation.
Your anti-aliasing is blasted.
What? Read this. Don't change
the frame rate. Turn against the
platform when it tilts. You keep trying to stay
on the edge the whole time
and that's why you're falling off. Go to the
falling side and then ramp back up.
Alright. Guys!
Guys! Guys!
I have to pull a plug. I have to rip the cord
out. I can't. What am I gonna do this
all day? You're gonna watch.
Watch. Watch. Watch. Watch. Watch. Watch. Watch this.
Watch this. Watch this.
Irma's Game Cubes. What?
Oh, okay. Hold on. Let me try one more time.
Fuck you!
Please. Please. Please. I'm too-
The chat is going so fast.
Sopranos, but-
It didn't help me.
It didn't help me. At all.
Actually. That was the worst-
That was the least thing that I needed.
Do it! Please read!
Tilt to the jump till you
kick smooth. The north?
What?
Watching paint dry. I'm- I'm sorry.
Trust me. I know. I'm trying to get
through this. It's tilting and it don't do
anything, man. Super Monkey Ball.
Wait. Turn this off or turn this
down. I need to hear this. Shut this
off. Somebody has an actual tutorial
for me. What does it say?
Cool.
Please.
A lot of people make
their, like, first major mistake is they don't
pick the right monkey. You need to pick the
stinky monkey.
Uh-oh. Stink?
You fucking
dick.
You just made this video.
Didn't you?
Hey guys. It's a stavedate from the
speedrun forums. His name is
stavedate. Dave state?
Beginner strats for floor 18.
So the main thing I see a lot of people
make their, like, first major
mistake is they don't pick the right monkey.
You need to pick the stinky monkey.
Uh-oh. I need- because somebody please
tell me how to do it. Like, somebody help me. Please.
Somebody help me. I want a real tutorial.
Make one.
Give me a frame by frame. This is
expert-
Okay, hold on. Pick the stinky monkey.
Let's watch this for a second.
All the way to the right.
That's the shit that I'm doing right there, man.
I'm doing that already.
He's getting really-
Okay, alright, alright. He gets all the way to top.
Like, he's gonna fall the fuck out.
Shit, this guy's good!
Holy shit, this guy's
really good. Hold on.
I'm so good, actually, now that I'm not
so good.
Okay. So, he-
Volume back up. Okay.
So he goes bang. He goes right all the way
to the edge. Just follow.
T-A-S. T-A-S.
I thought you were saying T-O-S. Like,
my dick was on camera. I was like, what the hell are you talking about?
Alright, I didn't do it. I'll get it.
T-A-T-T-
It's tool-assisted.
Whatever. It's still possible.
That's not a real person.
I can still do that.
Shit. That was kinda close.
Shit!
I believe you can beat this level.
I'm gonna try, man!
Do it! Fuck you!
This is embarrassing.
No, it's hard. It's really hard.
Here. I made this
for you. Okay, here's- let me see.
Level 18.
Expert tutorial. Simple.
It's part with extra reverb.
Thanks for making me open a bunch of tabs that I don't want.
Come on, man.
Man. It's right there.
It's so funny, cause that's like the
Just Do It meme, but I guarantee you
there are people that are sitting there watching this right now
just actually screamed at me.
That angry, too.
Like that upset.
Help me. Help me.
Help me, please.
I need help. I can't
be defeated by this. I can't.
I can't be defeated by this. It's too sad. I need to beat this.
This guy sucks. No!
Stop! I don't- do I?
I got maybe a little.
Fuck.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Read this.
Be in the middle when it's tilting against you.
Tilt to the higher side.
I tried that.
I tried that already.
Why does this look like a different game?
Swing bar?
Is this the right game?
Is this a different game?
Is this the right one?
My claw doesn't look like that.
This is a different fucking game, man.
Stay in the middle, idiot. I'm- all right, look!
You can't
stay in the middle, guys.
You have to be going really fast.
You can't stay in the middle.
God damn, I almost TAS'd it.
I ran as little as possible. I'm trying.
It's a waste to gain speed.
I just went to the clock.
Oh my god. It's been like
45 minutes.
In some of the videos, people are leading this to use
the big monkey. I think you need to change.
Suck up! What's the monkey ball?
Okay. Here we go.
This is an actual video.
It looks like a real video.
It was uploaded like five years ago.
This is not somebody fucking around.
Let's see.
That's what I'm doing!
Isn't that what I'm trying to do already?
This is a text tutorial.
Make your way as fast as you can
across the bridge and hold the uphill
direction whenever necessary.
Great advice.
Momentum glitch, level 18.
Monkey's in a circle, okay, whatever.
I'm doing everything that I'm- all right, I'm gonna turn the music off.
I'm just gonna try it like this.
The only thing you have to do here is tilt
to the side when it tilts to the side.
Okay.
Hold right to the side when it tilts to the side.
Except that doesn't work.
I'm holding right right now.
And it doesn't do anything, man.
Before it tilts.
That's what I'm doing.
Holding left, tilting. All right.
I'm not doing anything.
Forward right, forward left, forward right, forward left.
I'm about to put on a hand cam.
So you can see what's happening.
I'm convinced he's doing this wrong.
You can't be convinced! No, I don't want to show you my controller.
It's got a bunch of dirt all over it.
It has inputs on the screen. Yeah, I know.
I can't believe Sony made that fucking video.
That's so funny.
Money monkey gif. 100 gecs?
That was it. That was it.
Everybody relax. Nobody move.
I don't want anybody to move. Don't fucking move.
Shit!
Fellas! Boys and girls, he did it!
Okay, so like I look-
Clementines are so much easier to eat than oranges.
You know what I mean? Like-
Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have to do this? Please.
What are you doing, man?
What the fuck are you doing?
What's that record on that level? What's the record on that level?
I want it. What's the world record on that level without
current terms assisted bots?
I want to know what it is.
18 left. Actual world record.
No.
Was it? I don't know. Could have been.
Welcome to the next hour.
Wait a minute.
I missed the world record
by 0
by 0.02
seconds. Did I?
Shit. Alright, this one is
all over the place. So you're going to go run,
left, run, right. No you don't. Just run right
down the middle. Okay.
Weird. Is this an illusion?
It's kind of just an optical illusion.
Wrong monkey.
I get it. You have to-
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I get it. I know what you
have to do. You have to-
This is gonna suck ass.
It's gonna be hard, but you gotta just keep it right on the edge,
right on the edge, right on the edge.
Fuck you.
Edgy. Yes.
That is how you could describe it.
Why did you read that?
You know what that means.
Let's move on from that one. Pretending?
Yes.
Let's make it a clean yes.
Stupid.
Why am I? I'm addicted to this game now.
Once I overcame
tilt level, now I can't stop.
How many more levels are there?
Like, 30? Great.
I definitely will not get through this.
Even with cheating.
It's gonna be- Fucking idiot.
That's so annoying.
It makes it harder somehow.
That's gonna be way worse.
Remember, please wake up. We miss you.
It actually- You know what?
We just need it to be slower.
Fucking game, man.
This fucking game.
Ooh, this one's Sega.
World record.
I guess the time would be the same, right?
The time would be a record, but-
How do they miss that shit?
Talk slowly?
Make it seem- Hold on.
Super Monkey Ball!
Alright, so if I go this way.
I think I'll be okay.
I- I hit my head though, that sucks.
You can try it again, though.
The game's kind of fun.
I mean, two is probably-
People said two is gonna be better than one.
That makes sense, I guess.
I fell down again. Fuck.
I'm not very good, but
the games have their strengths and weaknesses, so.
One is more puzzle-oriented.
Two is more slide-oriented.
What's supposed to happen?
Well, I can tell you this is not supposed to happen.
It's not actually happening. Alright, stop fucking around.
This one's more Dave-oriented, yeah.
Why do they think I could do that?
One is more shitty-oriented.
Two is more puzzle-oriented.
There are a lot of Super Monkey Ball
original haters in here today.
I've noticed that.
There's quite a few of you guys. Is it really that-
Is it that accurate?
Should I go fast?
David.
Take all games at face value.
You get to go much faster than this. I don't know.
How do you get over there?
Shit, like that. Whoa!
I'm not soft-locked, I'm fine.
Shit. Wait, what just happened?
What happened? What did I just do?
Is it connected?
It wasn't connected.
How do I hop over from here to there?
Got it.
This one looks real
good.
This one, we can just brute force, I think.
I would say this one's brute forceable.
100 Gex.
Okay, much harder than I thought.
Unlimited.
Nobody wrote
Ultra Gamer Instinct.
It's like, how does he do it?
He's a maniac.
He can do anything. He's so good.
He's so good.
Okay, hold on. I have-
What's the world record for the next level?
I'm curious. What is it?
I'm gonna try to get the time world record.
Uh, what is the record here?
This one sucks.
I mean, it kinda looks like it.
Damn. No one's ever beaten this level.
Somebody jumps from the corner
of the map.
Wait, you have to jump? Like, there?
Alright, maybe not this one.
One that's way more complicated,
that's really hard.
That takes a ton of patience.
Okay, that turn is hard as shit.
It could be this one.
Really sharp right turn.
Don't be deceived.
This is not too bad, although I say that now.
Why does this one suck?
Everyone was saying, this one sucks, this one sucks, this one sucks.
Why? I mean, I'm just a fucking idiot.
That's why I fell off. That has nothing to do with how hard the level is.
It's just boring.
Yeah, I guess it kind of is.
Just go right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Uh, shit.
Time. Running out of time, running out of time.
Holy shit, you have to do this
so fast. You have to do this SO fast.
Even with the fucking cheating.
Admit it, he admits it.
Yeah, what do you think? My computer's broken?
I'm going way too fast.
Alright, I'm gonna do, I'm gonna just be
5% faster than I was last time.
I can do that when the speed is slower.
Take it slow, I'll be good.
I have way more reaction time.
And I fucking fell off. I knew it was gonna fucking happen.
I knew it was gonna fucking happen.
I knew it. I'm just gonna start save-stating. Fuck this level. This place sucks.
I just looked at chat. I just read chat for no reason.
Why did I do that?
Oh shit, leaked!
Get that off the screen!
Get that off the fucking screen, mate!
What are you fucking doing?
Bad world.
It's not even, why would I want to take that window?
It won't take this other window now.
Why?
Oh fuck, that game starts.
Okay, right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, look, we already went over this.
That was just, that was a screenshot for Dave.
He wanted me to take a screenshot.
You know, that was a screenshot
from Dave to me.
He's like, dude, hey, these are my list of things that I'm trying to get to work.
Can you help me?
I'm like, alright, man, like I will eventually. Maybe like a little later or something.
I don't know.
That was a screenshot from Dave to me.
Don't fucking leak it again.
My computer crashed. Leaked.
Where does this press play on mad world right now?
No.
There's a disc right behind me. I got
the controller, I got the system, and I, you know, I can
my, I, uh,
look, I own everything.
I own them all. I own everything.
They're in the house right now. They're right behind me.
I don't, what's with like the weird dust filter
that's on this? I don't like that.
I just have to get up there with an extra
five seconds left.
Man, I don't know much more. This shit I can take.
Bunker S. What?
What'd I say?
What'd I say? What'd I do?
Fucking hard turns, dude.
Oh, come on, man. Fuck this.
Oh, fuck this. Screw this. Fuck this game. Fuck this level.
Still here.
I'm still playing it. Whatever.
Oh.
What?
I just don't wanna. I don't wanna.
I have to put it on slow motion.
It's the only way I'm gonna do it.
It's the only way it's gonna happen. I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm sorry.
This has to happen.
I apologize.
The original game does not have slow motion.
Yeah, well, you didn't get
you a copy from a guy like that in the back
of his van. It was burned
onto a CD-R.
Oh, my fucking God.
You talk a lot of
bad game for a little guy.
How can I still screw this up?
Actual worst voice?
Isn't that what it was? Doesn't know what it does.
It's like, you talk a lot. Yeah.
Except people are giving me money.
Captain Squiggle, thanks for the ten
good meter days sub. Thanks, though.
Seriously. I do it every time
even in slow motion. I fucking swear to God.
I'm about to rip the game up. I'm about to pull the game out of the
theoretical GameCube.
Theoretically pulling the disc out of the GameCube
tray in my mind. What's a good
speed to do? Like 20 miles per hour? I think
20 is good. I can take corners
easier that way. If I stay at
20, we're good.
You're gonna stop underclocking
your GameCube. Dude.
Stay at 20.
Stop reading chat. Finish the level. I am.
You talk a lot of
bad game.
I'm so
so fucked up right now.
Dude, stop. I'm not doing anything. I'm just
fucking saying a word.
Can I say, oh, you talk a lot of
big game. Just as me?
Or is that off limits forever
now? Is this, am I even
still gonna actually be able to finish this?
Even with the super slow motion
going like 20? It's gonna be close.
I might get it. That turn.
Alright, then we're gonna full
blast here and then full blast here. No, I definitely
have it. Full blast.
Five, four, don't go
that fast. Still have to go through the
gate.
Doesn't it feel weird? Feels like the game's
wrong. This one's cool.
This one's cool. I like this one. I gotta do Tony Hawk
Momentum. Cool.
That one was just fun.
That one doesn't belong in expert. That one was just
fun. This is a Mario Sunshine
bonus level. I already hate it.
Okay. Holy shit.
The end is right there. Did I miss it?
That actually would have been pretty awesome.
Holy shit. I can get it.
Easy, easy. Slow, slow, slow, slow. Don't go
fast. Unnecessary.
I bounced so high.
Stupid asshole.
We can't cheat on every single level.
Not you. I'm not talking about you guys.
These are not as hard as the other ones
were. They really aren't.
Okay, we're going safe. I don't care about the bananas.
This is gonna be horrible.
Horrible, horrible, horrible, horrible.
Is this other side
better somehow?
Kind of. Slow down.
He's still playing this. Yeah.
Damn it. I couldn't put my hand
on F1 fast enough.
Jesus, man. What the fuck.
I almost just did it. I almost just pressed it. Thank
God I didn't. I pressed 1 instead of F1.
This is dumb.
No. Thank God.
You know, when this stream first started
I really, really thought you guys were just like
messing around. There was no way
he was going to beat this.
Like, not a single
solitary chance in hell.
I'm like, what? It's Monkey Ball.
This game's on iPad.
I had no fucking idea.
You're literally cheating.
I'm not saying this is a victory.
Wait, what?
What? Come on. I hit
the goal post?
What's wrong with my mic? I probably
fucked it up or something. Yeah.
What's the, hey, what's the world record on that one?
What's the world record on that one? Dude.
What the hell do I do here?
I gotta watch. Okay, this is gonna be
horrible. Okay.
Nope. No way. No way. You gotta stay on there.
Wait, it turns on?
Sometimes, wait. What is
going on here? Dude. I
don't, dude, I don't think this is
Oh no!
Alright, we're good. What? Did I hit
F1? What did I press?
I don't know what I pressed.
I pressed caps lock.
Wait. It's okay. It's alright.
It's okay. It's crashed, but we're good.
Okay. We're good. We're in a good spot.
I can't imagine playing this
legit. I'm enjoying this game solely
because I'm able to do this. The game crashed?
Yeah, I remember the GameCube games back in the
day. Yeah, they just crashed all the fucking time.
I fucked up, whatever.
That's why I lost the console war.
Good. Alright, we're on floor
30. Simple bonus floor.
Only, yeah, only 20 more
to go. I'll be surprised if I even get through
the next 10, let alone the next 5.
Floor 31.
Is there ice in this game?
Am I waiting for something in particular
or...not that bad.
This looks pretty bad.
I need to go that fast.
This is bad.
Is this ice?
Okay, I'll be honest with you.
I was just looking down at my chest.
I don't know why. I just looked at it.
Why?
Good jump spot?
Just jump. No, fuck it.
I can't jump. It might be time to turn
around to Gamer Instinct. It's almost Gamer Instinct
time. Yeah, it's gonna be Gamer Instinct time
here.
Alright, nice.
Look at how awesome that looked in real time.
Don't bump into anything. This looks okay.
Maybe not. Is that how he sees the world?
How the hell am I gonna do this?
You have to get tons of speed around here.
That's it.
Alright, I get it.
You just gotta fit inside like you're skiing.
I mean, that's easier said than done,
of course, right?
It's pretty easy, is it?
What am I doing wrong? Jump at the start.
Please jump. He didn't.
I think I can do it. Oh, fucking who cares?
Just try to do it normally. Get up there!
Come on! No!
Please! If you do this,
I'm gonna gift you 5 billion subs.
Uh, I don't- That would be
like- That would be like the entire
GDP of, like, New
Hampshire. So, I don't think you have that.
25 billion dollars
is the GDP of New Hampshire? I don't- Is it?
I don't know. It might be. Look it up.
I feel like it's, like, a small enough state.
Get up there! This sucks.
New Hampshire has a 69 billion
dollar GDP.
That was close. If you beat this level,
I will gift you 25 subs. Hold me accountable.
Okay. Corner. I know, I'm trying to get
to the corner. Remember, if you beat this level,
I'll gift you all my Tesla stock.
I don't- I really want it.
Oh, dude! That dude's about to give me the entire
GDP of Canada. I'll take it!
600 billion?
Remember, if you beat this first trial, I'll give you fucking 500 bucks.
Oh, really? Okay, dude! Thanks a lot, man!
Appreciate the 500 subs!
This one's gonna be horrible. 5 community subs
from Ecoleech. That's
not 500. You don't- Nobody actually
has to do that. I'm fucking around. Don't feel like
somebody has to do that. I guess you just have to
just wait. I'll take the 20.
Thanks, Goiki, for the 20 community subs.
I will definitely take them.
Appreciate it. Thanks a lot.
We kind of blew through the 30s here.
I thought I was gonna take way longer than this.
Eat shit, dude. This one was hard. Eat shit.
That one was hard. Not you guys
eat shit. Like, this guy in the
pamphlet ball. I don't know what just happened,
but whatever. Okay. All this with
one life remaining, by the way. I have to be very
careful that I do not
accidentally fuck up this save state.
In fact, shift F2.
Right? There.
Okay. Do we get a bounce?
We just bounce over in the
game. The game crashed.
If you could guess. The thing I have
both those save states, the game just crashed. Cool.
Remember when I elbow dropped off the top rope
in one of the Derma Rumbles a couple years ago in the
PS4, blue screened?
I was so disappointed. That was one of the worst things
ever. We had to do the whole Rumble
again, and it's like, oh, but the
outcome's gonna be different.
So bad. Holy shit.
I just did it. Did I do it?
I did it fast, but I did too fast.
That was fast.
Nope. Take it slow.
You don't have to be fast, you just have to be right.
Like that. I feel like I really
kind of went into a groove here in the 30s.
I want the camera to be facing this
way, please. Holy shit, they get smaller.
Damn.
Just close your eyes. I'll take
care of this. All right. Open your eyes. I did it.
This looks cool.
Oh, they go. How was I supposed
to do that? Wait.
Are they gonna slide behind me?
Oh. Did they stop?
No. That was a fun slide
level. Okay.
We've made it to the last 10.
It's 41.
Almost at it first try. One more.
That's it? All right. Good. Good.
Gotta beat the next level without looking. That's not gonna happen.
Guys.
One in the middle. Skips.
Just be slow. What's the rush? There is none.
We don't even need to skip. Fine.
Oh, okay. Wait?
Hurry up, dude. Oh, shit.
You gotta go fast.
Really fast.
Wait, I have an idea. That's gonna work.
Watch. Never mind.
Okay. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Fuck you. Ape Escape is a
superior primate game. It might be.
Sure. I'll play it eventually.
Where is it? Shit.
What the hell was I doing? You gotta catch it
right when it comes across.
One. Two. Three.
Four. Five.
One. Two.
Three. Four. I'm counting
and looking down. Do I need to look down at my fingers
to count? What the hell am I
doing? Game crash.
And then you go from here to the other one.
What's going on?
Am I dumb? Am I dumb?
Hold on. Wait. I have to
go on. Go on this one
and you run just forward. Okay. I get it. I get it.
I know what to do.
Oh, this game.
This fucking game.
Dude, what the fuck?
Where is it?
It's like right underneath me.
I had it too. Fuck you.
Little bounce.
Fucking physics. It's stupid.
This is 2001. Physics didn't even exist yet.
Why does it keep
turning me around?
Gravity didn't exist until 2006. Yeah.
I know. You get it.
Does this one work? This one's very easy.
Is it? Am I overthinking this one?
Whoa. This one's hard.
I had it right the first time.
Blank, blank, blank.
Blank, blank, blank, blank.
45, five more. We're getting to the end.
I'm going to beat this game and
everyone thought I wasn't going to do it.
What the fuck am I thinking?
Save states and slow down. Fake gamer.
Double fake. Whatever.
I didn't say I wasn't going to play without a handicap on.
What was the triple fake?
It was a triple fake? What was it?
No, I flew it. I fucking flew it.
Why?
has to be or 46 I mean I don't want to I don't want to put my own horn here but
it's been a while since I've activated gamer codes there's a goal there's a
goal what's the whatever the goal oh I'm an idiot
nevermind oh stupid idiot get stuck in the roundabout yeah it's like going into
the rotary or the roundabout you just keep going in circles you don't know
which exit it is take the third exit I don't know where that is shit I don't
want to activate any any codes yet not yet I don't need it yet I need momentum
first stupid fucking asshole I swear to God keep miscounting how many of these
there are there's two more after this I'm in trouble I which sides are I go
left no I gotta go right I can only go right do it fuck you gotta go one one
revolution here at least and then you got a slide up into there it's right
there I'm so fucking upset right now I hate I hate the ones that have like the
permanent tilt it's a permanent just like big tilt that I'd say it's the
word I fucking don't want it stupid was a slide game there's not a slide game I
have to go around you know it was a raid I don't see a raid where it was oh there
alright thank you master gear for the raid welcome everybody like the game
just crashed just a gear they say everybody's fucking name wrong even if
it happens a thousand times good acting one backwards alternate you dummy don't
call me a dummy you're a dummy oh super mate boy don't tell me to alternate
I'm gonna mess me up oh super frog that was it and I fucking messed it up a key
I don't I guess one's too big stop it's fine come on you're fine you're fine
switch sides on the last one I know I'll try it's hard I can't too hard I can't
do it after a week fucker no child under the age of 12 beat this game I have
refused to believe it you laugh at the monkey characters for the first ten
minutes of the game and when you got a beginner you're misremembering you think
you like beat the game on expert and shit that didn't happen you beat like
the first four levels on beginner and then you like had to go to bed and then
your your parents got rid of these satanic video games to get out of your
life they cut rid of them for you is they were bad for you I'm trying to do
it right did I do it right oh mama how do you get up this fucking thing guys
oh mama do the other ring yeah but holy shit I can't even get out of the third
ring I can't get out of it right this bring right here you stuck forever oh my
fucking god it's time to go gamer mode I think I'm turning on gamer mode what did
it I know how to do it not like that I feel like this shouldn't be on in one of
the last levels like yes what shit shit that was so easy and I just that's what
whatever this is the final three floors damn it I thought it was gonna be a
first try pissed off I'm tilted now I was about to be so proud of myself too
can you please like are you doing this to me I have three levels left in the
game doing this to me unfair it's not fair it's not fair guys I don't say it's
not fair fucking fair man fucking I'm just trying to cheat do things you're
not supposed to do in the game and like reload the same save file like a thousand
times why I want to do what I want I'm putting the engine through fucking hell
like what the hell dude stupid that was so solid too holy shit how did I do that
the first time that was unbelievable the first time I hate I so mad still live my
live hello I am what happened my chat oh my chats like broken on this other
screen okay well just use this screen I looked over at my I have chat embedded
over here I was wondering I was like holy shit no one's talking this must be
really boring I say you know all right it just like turned off for some reason
here we go damn it at first try first so good your
camera zone yeah do that fuck yeah making plenty of like tantrum noises
this dream too hey I don't want I hate that I'm like whoa yeah it's like okay
dude but really you're playing like GameCube right now you're not like
sinking in fucking quicksand like it's okay just relax Jeremy you're fine
you're good ah it's just a game cube it's just a game cube game it's just a
game cube game like your mouth is being filled with fucking acid this one is
actually really fucking hard tricky as hell there's not gonna be AI dungeon is
there um probably not at this point because I'm about to beat the game when
I beat it it's I'm going to I'm going to end the stream immediately second that I
crossed the goal I'm going to turn off screen what the minigames oh you know
you're right never mind try them get there first gamer sense activated even
with the fucking goddamn gamer sense this is why you never tell me to do
safe states because we end up it's just where it is like this whatever the word
is we end up in a situation where I it's impossible unless I do save states over
and over again then I get addicted to it because I have never ending continues
and I get trapped here forever easy easy come on dude don't go in okay two
more and we're done look at this oh this is an easy one I just do that okay what's
the record on that one the last level oh shit okay we're good actually really
not that are final floor what are you supposed to do here okay um it's going
too fast you just have to roll around okay I get it but beat the game game
over I win I only had to cheat four to five hundred times can unlock some more
minigames there is the doll trophy ray I did it it was fun that was a cute
little game what's in the doll isn't that the Donkey Kong in this way too I'm
the one that did all the work let me in all right super monkey ball all right
let's do the uh there come the subs no we're not doing I can just keep it
that's good you're gonna give subs again you've
liar no because I had a negative last time 29 subs what whatever it's the
first to be zero 29 all right now that's that's true you got me now you got me
that's true you got me let's play a couple minute games 29 right following my
own channel in that way you can all right let's do some gift a sub gift 29
subs here you go you ready you've given 901 gift subs to the channel so far
total oh wow this is kind of a lot all right here we go 29 subs and there they
go all right let's go and walk a couple of mini games mini games monkey
billiards monkey bowling or monkey golf you can only do two what I mean monkey
billiards I don't like billiards do monkey bowling first but you actually
bowl okay let's go here that's a strike that's a strike right there I'll take it
actually technically that's a spare let's do it again shit right spin tons of
spin too much spin way too much all right sorry I'll get the spare all you
have to do is to knock them all down let's go I was trying to spin it kind of
fun I get it now I see where they wanted you to do just a little bit so it'll
curve that too much the other bowling mode I want to do what the professionals
do this shit you know what I mean when they get it right on the edge and it
just curves right the fuck in and strike he's fucking dead I don't do ten I don't
know the full string here I want to do the thing I want to do at least once
shit I'll get it that's gonna do it one time it's not gonna do it right you're
right I can just I can turn on the gamers sense I should really get a
strike every time all right look at this is gonna be awesome it's gonna be like
boom strike okay what if I am or instincts don't matter okay gamer sense
might matter if I do this all the way over here have it go all the way to the
left tons of power and all the way spin to the left there it is oh that's a
beauty yes I would have been so cool little less a little bit less we'll go
all the way over here a little bit less power that's this should do it nice nice
feel satisfied now we can stop I'm done with this one we got golf number of
holes whatever 18 holes why would they make 18 holes it's part 3 it's just
mini golf oh this is awesome why can't I just have played this the whole time
let me try to get a hole in one and I'll be happy this is cute though this is
fine this is cute it's cute it's cool okay let's just gonna I'm gonna hit her
as hard as I possibly can just smash it how many times you do that at mini golf
by the way I remember going mini golf and then you do it a little too hard and
it would just bang bang bang bang bang would skip over into maybe another
family playing and you're like the turquoise ball would just roll down and
knock into two or three of their balls and ruin their day I was so bad at many
go if I hated it I always had too hard even if when I I hated it it drove me
nuts all the one I get a thousand points who hates mini golf it just
enrages me I don't know why to me it's the worst part about golf dialed up to a
thousand like hey you know this really difficult really impossible thing that
takes too much skill to do we're gonna put a windmill in front of you now you
give me you give me a two wood and driving range I can I could crush those
balls like happy Gilmore stuff I used to just drill balls at a driving range it
was such a flex too because you would go there with people that have no idea
what the hell's going on and they're like doing a weird form and the ball
rolls down like 20 feet in front of them it's embarrassing I get up there and I'm
just like these are all going like at least two to three hundred yards I'm
destroying them but anytime anyone wanted to do like a mini golf was always
I had something to do sorry I'm baking a cake with my mother I can't or it even
got to a point I think where I would go but I didn't want to play I wanted to be
the scorekeeper is after a while becomes a pain in the ass too when you get to
like hole seven or eight in mini golf aren't you kind of fucking over it like
an hour or two will go by and it's kind of over this and then you just start
dragging the ball with your club like oh yeah my turn okay there's like six of
us here my turn all right well just drag a little bit and let go I don't care
where it goes you like regular golf I only like the driving part that's it
I love just smashing balls like a bucket of balls and just watching them soar all
right that's it I uh that was fun that's where I'm gonna call it so let's go over
a few things a couple of important things Thursday is the next dream it's
gonna be left for dead to the big community update Joel be Tyler from
valve I'm shit valve sauce and valve sauce yes and simple flips we're gonna
be doing to the leopard head stuff should be a lot of fun that's the plan
for Thursday and then Friday I will be on kit bogus scream as a guest I'm gonna
get kind of implanted into that world for a day that is Friday I believe at
somewhere early afternoon I think I'm like two or three Eastern maybe and what
I maybe I don't think we've locked it down completely yet but it should be a
lot of fun then what the hell kind of golf course is this we're going full
power right here what time on Thursday the normal start time like around
probably around noon there are three other people that we have to kind of
communicate with those so that could change I would just keep an eye on the
sus over the next day or so I'll have a locked in time that's gonna be it you
can call it here I'll try for one more hole in one you know what oh wait what
about one of the party games monkey fight number of wins one we're gonna
battle on final destination monkey target is so good dude all right I'll
try it okay knocked off oh I got big oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy oh boy
all right even bigger holy shit this is huge it's too big should I lost I don't
want flight anymore it's I don't like it a monkey target wheel of danger what are
you looking for bomb safe safe kind of cool number of laps one AV hey am I going
the right way am I going the wrong way I'm going the wrong way shit I'm doing
the thing that happens when you're in last place is toad and all your friends
are laughing and you get so fucking mad that you just turn around and start
driving into him it's not even funny you're not making a joke you're actually
trying to ruin your friends night and eventually gets a point which like dude
that's like stop doing that that's not even cool man not funny I told though
cuz toad is always in last place that's in the game's programming I didn't make
that game I didn't make told the worst computer control player they did it's
gonna fun place in my end I was nobody done one lap yet one please go redo
target and do it right if the press a to fly press a for the speed boost I'll see
what happens keep it so he made a video with a fake tutorial that's the best
okay can I nominate that for best one guy moment I thought it was person you
somebody's the person a for the speed boost our clouds not safe okay I'm ready
why do they close it suffocating just like Mario right from aiming for the
target you have to close it okay I get it right here okay that's 10 maybe 10
rounds all right if I get it more than 10 right now I the game so I went
head into the pyramid didn't touch them game not over enough the baby just say
let's ago we have to go pretty low to get under these your career can't get
any lower yeah my monkey ball career I'm doing everything I'm doing fine what
you talking about I'm okay like what do you mean my career we put away what's
not my career we're talking about yeah that okay so very clearly I need to be
very odd when you close the thing it drops like a stone there is no forward
momentum the thing just drops like a fucking anchor okay what's wrong with
clouds you don't want momentum okay here we go it just closed a bunch of water in
there with them okay give me some points for God's sake actually I make my
descent I think it's time to make this sent well it's so fast look at the wind
oh there's wind is looked to the left of my screen see you Thursday that was fun
become the subs no they don't what is this this is not subs it's not the subs
at all actually I think I saved over the subs it's not good hold on a second
hold on a second hold on a second I can get it I'll see you Thursday guys for
Left 4 Dead I didn't what was the last time I actually opened Left 4 Dead well
I think it was pretty recently but actually played a campaign you probably
have to go back to one of the old YouTube videos that's on the channel
playing with friends from like 2012 2013 that's probably the last time I did it
all right let me make sure I can get this we go all right we're good prices
averted here come on the subs today I can actually get this to run oh they
come yeah there they are that's a lot you guys are fading in and out so fast
because there were so many stop doing that there we go I kind of like this
style a little bit because it doesn't just blow by you can actually see the
name pop up although I think I messed it up I have to make the font bigger that's
my fault though I screwed it up and move this no what are you gonna do for my
birthday I don't know I really have no idea I'll be going to dinner somewhere I
don't know though wow that was my name it's my name I think if my music back to
I gotta redo all my stream stuff I need a new computer at least a new graphics
card the 38 is any good anyone that has one of the eight that exist are they
good are they yeah we'll do a raid we'll do we actually are going to we'll raid
we'll raid kitboga bogas live right now I'll be like I said joining him as a
guest spot on Friday so go take a look and see a kind of what you can expect
it more for designers and creators less for gaming yeah but I feel like I could
probably with with a better graphics card a better CPU I could probably have
the stream be somewhere like around 900 p and then drop my CPU limit kind of
processor down so the stream will just look better that CPU preset I could put
it at slow probably if I got like a 3080 and a one of the new thread rippers or
something I don't know I have to look into it but that was super monkey ball
and that's the stream I am in very surprised actually beat I thought I was
gonna give up at like level 31 go say hello to kitboga and I will see you all
on Thursday for it left for dead have a great night everybody take care of
yourselves and thank you for the birthday wishes too I appreciate it an
old man once you cross that mid-30s now you now you got it now you're old see
you soon take care guys goodbye