Black man 99. A 99 man battle royale against players from around the world.
Let's do it.
Fucking forgot the wood. I'll be right back.
Okay. I got it.
Alright, so. It's this thing.
Okay, here we go.
This is what I'm talking about.
It's this weird like tree trunk.
And I'm not gonna smell it, cause it smells like my dog's mouth.
But when this is out of the package, brand new.
It smells fantastic.
Right out of the package.
It smells like this awesome wood smell.
This has been in my dog's mouth.
Here it is. I'm not gonna put it in my mouth.
Mustache Ark?
Why is that so cool? It's not.
Alright. Pac-Man.
Let's go.
I'm pretty rusty. I haven't played Pac-Man in a long time.
I have played this though. Maybe like once.
Stream snipe his ass.
I don't know how this works.
You look like every math teacher in America.
That's kind of like, I'll take this as a compliment.
Alright, I want to do speed.
Speed.
Go. Knockout.
I don't even know what that means.
Oh shit.
Get these, right?
Speed and knockout.
What do these little things do?
Get it. Okay, get it. Go, go, go.
Pac-Man master.
I bet you I make it to the top ten.
I bet you I make it to the top five.
Look at that cherry.
What place am I in?
Oh, it slowed up.
You're in last place?
I am not in last place.
I'm definitely in the top five.
Ah, it was risky.
I'm in trouble.
I'm in deep shit.
I'm dead.
Alright, I got to top fifty.
What did I get? I was top fifty?
That's still...
Hey, look, number fifty-one.
Alright, again.
Let's do it again.
I just had to warm up.
You suck.
I was fifty percent better than a hundred people.
What are you talking about?
I'm part of the curve.
I'm right in the middle.
You were bottom fifty percent.
I'm still better than half of the people that queued up.
Yes, I'm even including the people that queued up
and left their switch
and walked into the bathroom.
I did that at least a few times.
Alright, I'm going to do better this time.
Here we go.
I'm going to do stronger and...
stronger and...
and counter.
Alright, let's go.
I almost just fucking was the first person out.
That would have been embarrassing.
I need to get that.
Whoa!
Don't touch it.
I got to get all these guys.
There we are.
Alright, good, good, good, good, good.
Oh my god.
You can't even fuck with me.
I'm so good.
Damn it!
I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I had it, I got too cocky.
I have to finish in the top ten.
At least the top twenty.
Otherwise, I'm not allowed to leave the stream.
I need to get to top twenty-five
or I'm not allowed to turn off the stream.
Sound fair?
Sometimes you got to go for it immediately.
Knock out like ten people right now.
Alright, alright, whatever.
I fucked up.
Whatever.
It's alright.
Eighty-four.
Your license is going to get revoked.
I'm going to be fine.
I'm going to get top twenty-five right now.
I lost so quickly it took a while to get me another game.
I don't even really know how this works.
There we go.
Alright, good, good, good, good, good.
Go, go, go, go.
Come up here.
Follow me up here.
Go.
There it is.
Go for it.
Oh, come on.
What?
Guys, don't blow it.
Don't blow it.
Just chill.
Get it?
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Help me.
I need new ones.
Come on.
Where's my stuff?
Where is it?
Come on.
Give me my pill.
Where's the pills?
Where's my pills?
The strawberry.
I don't even know how this works.
You have to get the fruit?
You have to get the fruit.
What?
I had so many opportunities to get it.
I didn't even know that's how the game was played.
What does the fruit do?
This is the first time I've ever been to that point.
This is like the eighth time I've played this game.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
The fruit refills the board.
That would have been fucking nice to know 100 years ago.
All right.
I'm going to win.
Let's go.
I was just lost.
That would have been really embarrassing.
I only get the fruit when I need to, right?
Oh, what's with the fucking controller?
Why am I not?
I'm not getting like any stuff.
Where's the...
What's going on?
Oh, the fruit just refills the whole board.
I get it.
All right.
I don't get that.
I don't need it.
Holy shit.
They're going to turn.
This is risky.
This is risky, but I'm going to do it.
Get out of here.
See that move?
Did you see those moves?
Are you paying attention?
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Go down and get it.
Oh, I'm so slow.
Oh.
Come on.
I didn't know that's what that did.
I didn't know that's what that...
I didn't know the red ones where it could kill you.
I didn't know that's what that did.
I thought it was just the ghosts.
I always had a chance there.
What?
I didn't know that was what happened.
It's all right.
I win.
Oh, what?
Oh, my God.
I thought I could just walk by them.
I thought this made you extra slow.
Okay.
Now I know.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
I'm going to win.
I got top 25.
It sounds so different playing this game.
I'm talking like this.
I don't know why.
Gary Seinfeld.
Yeah.
Relax.
I'm going to get to first.
At least top 10.
Now that I understand how the game works.
It took me a little while.
That train over here.
I'm going to get my own train.
Check this out.
Oh, I just...
I think I just fucking messed up everybody's game.
I just knocked out like 30 people and I'm both...
Oh, yeah.
So many ghosts.
Ooh.
That was close.
I got to go up top right.
Wow.
This bit rate.
Is it bad?
Oh, that didn't last very long.
Now it does it.
Do it again.
Watch it.
He's going to turn.
Okay.
This is going to be a monster.
Oh, my God.
Out of my way.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
My finger.
It went down.
That stupid thing.
I didn't want it to go down that way.
It just like went down that way because the analog sucks.
Like it just...
I go down that way.
All right.
I'm good.
Fucking analog.
Oh, this game is actually pretty fun.
All right.
No more analog.
It sucks.
It never does what I want it to do.
Use the buttons.
I can't use the buttons.
You have to use the analog.
Well, that's unfortunate.
Every time you see me just like go to the left for no reason, it's because the analog
sucks.
I just want to make sure you're aware of that.
I can give myself an excuse to lose every time.
I'm building up this shit.
I'm going to destroy somebody.
Somebody is so fucked right here.
Wow.
Careful.
Again.
I want to go down.
It's not what I wanted to do.
Oh, fuck.
Down here.
Let's go.
Counter.
All right.
What do these do?
I have no idea.
Hopefully, it's good.
That was absurd what just happened.
That's all right.
Watch out for the red ones.
Here they come.
Oh, there's so many over there.
Careful.
Oh, I need a fruit.
I need a fruit right now.
Risky move.
Got it.
Oh, eat shit.
Everyone is so strong.
I need a fruit right now.
Risky move.
Got it.
Oh, eat shit.
Everyone is so screwed here.
Oh.
Going out of my way.
No.
Did I win?
Oh.
Top eight.
Damn it.
I got trapped.
Yeah.
Damn it.
This is fun.
This is a lot of fun.
Change of control scheme.
I'll get used to it.
This game really woke me up.
Good.
I got top ten.
Let's see if I can get top five.
Should I just do stronger speed?
I don't know.
What's the play?
I don't even know what the play is.
I'm going to do stronger.
This is a really bad idea, but I did it anyways.
Already?
Off already?
What are you talking about?
Dude, that shit is not lasting at all.
That's lasting not at all.
What's going on with that time?
Look at this.
Why is it lasting so infrequent?
Look at that.
What's going on with this?
Take off stronger.
Speed.
Oh, my God.
I'm not even looking.
What was going on there?
Because you're...
All right.
Before I do anything, what the hell does all this stuff do?
What is speed?
What does strong...
What does mean?
Should I just stay on the one I had on?
The right side is who you attack.
Yeah, I just keep it on random.
You need to clear the board to upgrade the stat on the left.
I'm keeping on speed down this way.
Clear the board before doing anything else.
So I should clear the whole board.
All right.
I cleared it.
Speed up.
Oh, okay.
I get it.
Shit.
I didn't want to do that.
Fucking analog.
My God.
The analog sucks.
Back to the drawing board, Nintendo.
An awful controller.
All right.
Everybody's dead.
Speed up.
What?
Get away from me.
I got to clear the board.
You're still alive.
You have to die.
No.
Fucking analog.
Watch it.
Wow.
And they moved.
I didn't know they moved.
What?
I thought they stood still.
Oh, my God.
If I only just knew the fucking rules, I'd be number one.
Clear the pellets, not the ghosts.
Oh.
Calm down.
Yeah.
All right.
I need to, like, honestly...
Like, I need to shut the hell up.
Wow.
Wee.
Like, what?
Would you fucking inject caffeine into your jugular vein?
Like, sit down.
What the hell am I doing?
What the fuck am I doing?
All right.
This is the one.
Get rid of these pellets.
All right.
That's a full clear.
Did I not...
Was it one of the...
Oh.
Fuck.
There's one on the top left.
Shit.
All right.
Stop paying attention to that and just be a good Pac-Man gamer.
Did that not work?
Am I losing my mind?
What's going on?
Oh.
Every pellet needs to be cleared, not just the big ones.
I thought you meant, like, the big pellets.
That kind of sucks.
Don't touch that.
All right.
Let's go.
Speed up.
Kill.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Oh.
You just totally screwed me here.
I'm in trouble.
Down.
Shit.
It's hard.
Is that the right one to counter?
Maybe.
This is the one.
All right.
I'm going to do...
I'm going to do 10 more attempts.
Okay.
This is attempt number one of 10.
Let's focus on getting huge ghost combos.
Yeah.
I wonder what the other ones...
If the other ones are better.
So, I'm doing speed.
What are the other ones?
Like, train?
I wonder what train is.
Should I do train?
I'm going to try train.
I like train.
I don't want to pick up the...
Groot.
Yeah.
How bad is the bitrate?
All right.
Speed up.
It's not on train?
Let's go for a huge train here.
I'm just going to try to survive.
I'm not going to go for, like, clearing the whole board.
I mean, I'm probably going to need it.
I know.
But after a couple of times, I'm just going to go for skill only.
Watch out.
Oh, mistake.
Big mistake.
I'm good.
Wow.
That was lucky.
That was very close.
Get out of here.
Jeremy!
The game bugged.
I just got a free...
I cheated.
I don't even know how I did that.
I don't know what happened.
I think I may have just cheated.
Huge train.
Let's go.
Oh, no, no, no.
Risky.
What happened?
Did I win?
Did I get to...
Did I just win?
I won.
What happened?
Oh, no.
I touched the red one.
It spawned on me.
Oh, come on.
No.
Oh, what?
Oh, that sucks.
Did it spawn, like, right there?
Damn it.
Oh, I thought I had that one.
Oh, no.
I thought I had that one.
Damn it.
That was a good run.
Number two, Victory Royale.
The red ones don't disappear, yeah.
That's true.
Oh.
That's what fucks with me more than anything.
I'm not...
What was train even doing?
Stay speed.
All right, that was...
That was a...
I really...
I kind of fucked that one up.
Sorry.
I'm still...
My nerves are up from the last run.
I'm almost winning.
My nerves...
I'm, like, still a little shaky.
All right?
It's okay.
I thought I had that, too.
All right.
We'll get the next one.
Poor thing.
He's shaking.
No, it's just when you come that close, you just, like, start to go, like, oh, shit.
All right.
Let's knock some people up.
These early levels, you got to build it up.
Let's go.
This is risky, but I'm doing it.
Now, you're not going to fool me with that one.
I'm the king of that move.
Whoa.
Jinda got that.
That was stupid.
That was really dumb to pick that up.
What was I thinking?
Clear it out.
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
That almost just absolutely just decimated me.
Get that shit out of here.
Get it out of here.
What the hell?
You just hit dad in the other room.
Dad, will you stop?
Relax.
I'm trying to study reused material.
Yeah, I know.
Big pellet freezes the red guys.
I'm learning.
Oh, my God.
You just joked me.
Whatever.
I, this is, I love this game.
This is a lot of fun.
What a fun game.
This is way better than the Mario one.
I played the Mario once or twice and I was just like, I don't like this.
Let's go.
Focus.
I'm just going to build up a huge train.
See if I can do that.
Am I good enough to build up a gigantic train?
Find out.
Just destroy somebody.
I'm about to fucking ruin somebody's lunch right now.
Here we go.
How do I have speed one?
When did I miss a pellet?
I'm in trouble.
All right.
Back up here.
Safety.
I need safety.
Here we go.
Why?
How do I send those to people?
This is the German that I came to see.
No, I'm not going to make those noises anymore.
I'm going to relax.
You need to put it on train.
So what happened in the beginning there?
I didn't, I didn't get the first speed increase.
Why?
What happened?
It wasn't my fault.
It's the game's fault.
The game is broken.
Let's destroy this here.
It's flying over me.
What was that?
Don't get collapsed on.
That's fine.
It's okay.
Don't worry about this because I'm going to kill everybody right here.
I didn't get everybody.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
I'm okay.
Down.
Just get it.
Fuck it.
I don't need the speed.
Oh, fuck.
Watch that red.
Don't fucking analog.
You piece of fucking dog shit.
Get it.
There's a.
Wow.
It was so fast.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
It was two seconds.
It wasn't even one second.
Oh, my God.
It was just like, there you go.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my God.
It was so close.
When I grabbed the pellet, it was like, oh, a full second went by.
Shit.
You don't have to use analog.
I know, but I'm so used to it now, even though I hate it.
Damn it.
This is too much.
Oh, my God.
You don't have to use analog.
I know, but I'm so used to it now, even though I hate it.
Damn it.
This is too much fun, and I keep getting so close.
Give me all the pellets.
Watch out for this guy.
All right, let's go.
I'm going to get that other side.
Come on.
Don't fuck it up here.
Get it.
I'm good.
Eat shit.
Down.
Down here, all the way around.
That was a risky move, but it was worth it.
Let's go dump this on somebody.
Shit.
I got to change the analog.
It's so bad.
It's painfully bad.
This could be the worst analog of any controller.
Didn't they just get sued for this shit?
Didn't they just lose a lawsuit about how shitty the analog was?
They did, right?
That happened, right?
Movement I want here.
How do I change this?
Turn on fucking vibration.
What is this?
1993?
Is this like 1996?
Why the fuck?
Turn it off.
Nobody uses.
Nobody cares.
All right.
Now I want to go.
What are you doing?
Movement I want.
This is strategy.
I'm so good.
This is the shittiest menu I've ever seen, by the way.
Let me fucking move.
I'm trying to move.
If you know, you know.
And you know.
A lot of you that play this game, you went to that menu and like, this menu sucks.
All right.
Let's go.
If you know, you know.
Oh, I got so close.
Okay.
New controls.
Let's see what happens.
Are we going to get two meltdown screens back to back?
No.
By the way, how many?
I said it was 10 more games, right?
No, I can't just like stream once a week and have like freakouts once a week.
I'm not.
No.
Well, that makes the game fucking easy.
This is a guaranteed win right here.
What should I have it on?
Where's the last one?
Where's the last little pellet?
I don't see one.
Where was it?
I didn't even see it.
Already got it?
Oh.
Heat it up.
This is going to be big.
Don't do that.
Got to kill that guy and the guy behind him.
This awkward movement there, but whatever.
I got it.
I'm dead.
Close.
Very close.
That was shit.
Don't make a risky move like that again.
My hand hurts.
Oh, no.
This is a bad idea.
Why did I switch from the analog?
Ah, that was risky.
I...
No!
Ah!
And you saw what fucking happened.
And I...
Oh, shit.
My hand.
That just threw me off so bad.
I have to change it back.
It actually hurts.
He's going to rage put and never play it again.
This is just...
This is just the insanity of Nintendo consoles.
This is the insanity.
No other console on Earth...
It's been almost...
It's been the last three generations of Nintendo fucking consoles.
You buy the console and then you replace the shit controller that comes with it.
No other console has this problem.
Well, just get the better controller.
So the Switch is not $249.
It's $310.
Because you got to buy the fucking pro controller.
Because it's the only fucking consoles that have this problem.
It's been like this for 25 years.
And it's crazy to me because the Nintendo 64 and the GameCube controllers were phenomenal.
They were the best controllers.
They were probably the best controllers.
Are we...
Am I wrong?
They went from making the best controllers to...
You got to buy another controller because these ones suck so bad.
What happened?
Fuck Nintendo.
Fuck the Nintendo network.
They don't have any good TV.
They don't have any good games anymore.
Mario Odyssey now.
I'm kidding.
I got to do the theme, right?
I'm like the guy that has the meltdowns once a week.
I bottle up all of my anger all week and I just lay it out on all of you guys.
Everybody that cuts me off on the highway, every time I drop a coffee on the ground,
you guys are hearing it.
This comes out once a week.
And before it was like three or four times a week and it was diluted over the course
of a week.
It's the evil mustache.
Toxic arc.
This is the one.
No more fucking around.
I'm going.
Oh dear.
That was dumb, but I did it anyways.
That was dumb, but I just did it anyways.
That guy was the guy that wasn't going to kill me.
Guarantee it.
Went up.
Down.
Round.
THE DRAWING CONS!
It's console!
It's the worst console.
They've got to make them little fucking hamburger slices.
Oh look, it's cute.
Oh, it's the switch.
Oh yeah, it fits in a baby's hand.
Collect them all.
Here's a bunch of colors.
No, I will not.
It's over.
I had to.
These actual meltdowns.
What happened to my speed increase?
No, I very much enjoy pressing all the face buttons with my one thumb.
I really love it.
It's awesome.
These things are smaller than chicklets.
Yay!
Alright, I'm out of here.
I'm done.
I am unraveling right now.
I'm unraveling.
No more unraveling, okay?
I'm going to play, and I'm going to try to get to top ten again.
Maybe this is motion controllers, Nintendo.
I'd be able to do it, right?
Put that in fucking everything.
We all wanted that ever since the Kinect.
Some streamers are like,
Oh man, I'm looking forward to going to that Nintendo mixer.
At TwitchCon, I go Nintendo.
I'm not invited to that.
I'm going to get side-eyed at every conference I go to now.
Like, right?
I'm burning every bridge in the bridge before the cement was even dry.
The work hadn't even been done on the bridge, and I'm already burning them.
Play smart.
Counter.
I don't even know how to select counter.
What did I do?
I made it out with that one.
Get off me.
Down here?
This is very risky.
I need the speed, though, otherwise I ain't making it.
Oh dear.
God.
I'm dead.
They're all coming for me.
No, it...
I spent $60 to play this game.
So you need the other controller.
I just got my microwave, my favorite one.
Could I survive there?
Well, yes.
You see, what I did was I pressed right on the Joy-Con.
What a fun name that is.
Joy-Con.
And when I pressed right, the character went down.
It's the mustache.
Peter.
Peter, it's the mustache.
Kill it.
Kill.
Pipe it.
That's enough speed.
I don't need to mind my size.
I sound so angry.
Go.
Hopefully I got it in time.
Wow.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Yeah!
It just keeps going.
Did I win?
Oh my God.
No.
I was so close again.
Oh, no.
I was so sad.
It's like you're bringing me up to the top of the roller coaster.
It's the most intense, fun roller coaster in the world.
And then right when I get to the peak where you're about to drop me,
you hit the brakes and you say,
Sorry, the ride is closed today.
Come back tomorrow.
And I keep coming back every day and you keep stopping me right at the top.
That sucks.
No.
That's not what I'm talking about.
What the fuck?
Okay.
I have to win.
Please let me just beat this.
It's because everybody that's number one is just like...
They're just unbeatable.
Everyone that's number one is always just unstoppable.
God damn it.
It's too fun.
I can't stop playing it.
Okay.
Buy me some time.
There's so many on me.
I should have just grabbed it when I had a fucking chance.
I thought that was the one.
I was moving.
I was dodging.
I was moving around.
I just burped.
That was like stress burp.
That's so ridiculous.
Clear.
Paint the dots.
Paint them.
Whoa.
There it is.
Good.
Just get it.
Don't be an idiot.
Round town.
There it is.
Oh my God.
Turn around.
Go back.
No.
Bad spawn.
Hmm.
Ah.
I can't get it.
Did you see that bullshit?
I couldn't go.
I couldn't.
It was touching it.
I need to calm down.
I am calm.
I just turn and just whip a glass into the back of the wall.
All right.
Ten more.
This is it.
This is one out of ten.
Ten more.
This is it.
Left that here for safety.
A huge train over there.
I'm ready to destroy it.
I'm going to do a monster train.
Ready?
Watch this one.
That one felt good.
Going for one more clear and that's it.
Go down.
Down.
I'm good.
Eat them.
Eat them all.
I enjoy.
I'm having lots of joy from these things.
I get so happy when I hit a direction and I go the other way.
Um.
You guys are doing predictions every round.
That's guaranteed losing points.
I can't believe you're betting for me.
Stat wise that's a very bad odds right now. Let's try to go through down three times
Just just just complain about things and don't like solve them even though you're in even though you're annoyed that you have to solve it
Just just keep making sure they understand the joy-con sucks Jeremy keeps saying it over and over again. Maybe they'll
Have they heard it yet? Oh
They couldn't you just just just repeat yourself a thousand times. Maybe they'll maybe they're here at one time
Load it up load it up too risky
It's a stupid move, but I have to do it
Good I'll go that way. Oh Jerry. This is gonna be big
The red thing on the left scared the shit out of me and I tried to stop betting for me you're gonna lose
Some of you guys are gonna end up with nothing left. Wait, he was for top 10. Oh
Okay in that case cool. I
Made this so stupid these the setup that I have here is so backwards
I'm teching. I'm tell let me tech first. I'm gonna I'm teching for a little while this shit out of here
Get rid of that guy go to the left move. Good move. Good move. Good move up. I just ate all those things
All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Perfect. That's actually perfect
Oh shit get over there. Don't screw me over. Just calling a pineapple. Don't do it. Where am I?
Did I win oh my god, what the fuck I just I lost track of where even was I was just surrounded by earth
There's so much shit. That's the third time. I've gotten to number two. What are they doing?
What test that guy that just went for drugs?
These can't like do drugs and they play this game so they get to first place every time
We should all of us that got into this game should have to do mandatory drug testing
So I sit there take to drop blood from all of us and then run it and see who's on drugs
Shit, I'm on drugs
No, I'm gonna get booted from the tournament
No, no, I know what I meant to say was only performance enhancing drugs
That's what I meant to say
That makes you like be able to like lightning reflect. It's me
Play like the curb your enthusiasm music. Oh dear. Oh my god
I don't even know I have to go over this way. I have really shit speed really shit speed
really shit speed
What was it supposed to do there? Nothing. I got locked in in every direction
I got I I went back like 10 games of chess in 10 seconds and I saw that I was checkmate at every single angle
Hmm. Oh shit. It's this wasn't playing Pokemon. I changed that whoops. We all know that would be impossible for you. I
I'm so close. I'm so close in another universe. I won one of those games. Let's go. Come on
That was this is a really bad start. Oh, this is a awful start. It's okay. I can make it work
Guys gotta die. Yeah, you would screw everything up. He would have and through this guy good
What does this mean when this happened? I gotta get these all before the next batch comes out. Oh shit
Don't go that way. Oh, I got trapped because the fucking
little white things I
Just had to go a little before the left and it slows you down so much
You didn't commit. Yeah, cuz I thought he was gonna beat me cuz I two of those little like white Pac-man's
like just for biting me and
Hi, I feel like I'm getting interrogated
What happened? He's alive. Let's go. I'm obsessed with this game. I just can't stop playing it
Because it's just that these dumb battle royale games
I know why they're so popular now doesn't matter if it's Pac-man fortnight pub G
They dangle a carrot in front of your face
forever
Chances are for the most part you're not gonna come in first place
You are not gonna be in first place ever it might not even ever happen one fucking time
But the carrot is just here. It's just dangling permanently in front of your face. I gotta clear these guys out
There my grandma come out this way. All right now go
Very risky, but I'm gonna do it for it. All right. I don't care about speed anymore. I don't I really don't
If I can get it, I get it if I can I can
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. This joy con. I'm in dead. Ah
I couldn't go that way. I couldn't go to the right. I couldn't go to the right
It was too blocked off and I couldn't I should have saved the pellet on the left side
I'm never gonna win the carrot will be there forever
Oh
Number two, it's so close
They consider getting the Nintendo switch pro controller I
Can't wait for the next Nintendo controller. It's an IV bag
That's gonna be real fun. And like when you shimmy in your seat
You can like move your character around so it's incredibly innovative
And the IVs in your arm and it's given I don't know like Nintendo slash
Nintendo, you know, and you fucking fuck me up. I was trying to explain myself
All right. I'm done after three more. I'm literally running out of this. I'm running out of my office
I'm sprinting as fast I can after three more
Okay, silver is gonna be more valuable than gold. Anyways, we're like two decades. I don't care about getting the gold. I got silver
That cherry, let's go. Come on
Let's make a train. It was sloppy. It was really sloppy. I'm not happy with this
Not happy with this at all. I can't I'm not gonna get this. I gotta go back around. I have to get it
I'm not happy about that. That was sloppy
Now I'm not gonna get the speed boost
Where am I going? Where am I? I got to kill these guys. Are they gonna make my life a living hell joy con?
joy con
Yeah, I was playing really well at the end there and they were just too many good players
Anybody else also feel like a lot of times you press I know. Okay. I just felt all your eyes
Rolling into the back of your head
if you guys ever like use the joy cons and you press buttons on the joy cons and they it doesn't do anything
It's almost like the wireless technology in these things is from like
Please correct me if I'm out of my mind
I don't think I am
Shitty carpenter blames his joy cons
No a shitty carpenter blames his joy cons until the company that makes the joy cons gets sued
Loses a lawsuit based on how bad the tools are
That what you meant to say?
I'm not doing I
Didn't play well in pac-man a pac-man. I didn't have any good games
I
Didn't even get the speed boost. Oh imagine how stupid that would be hate these fucking things
It's making me laugh I can't play
I'm trying to focus. It's so hard to focus when you're thinking about like it. I got it. I got it. I'm fine
You have to be over there. Why do you have to be over there?
Okay
I'm only at three speed. This is awful. I have to commit right now. Oh my god
I don't have anything left. No, I couldn't I keep thinking about like this
What would I work a homeland is somebody correct me here? What actually happened with the joy cons?
It's somebody like what?
Didn't did they get they had to like do something. What did Nintendo have to do? What happened? Tell me what happened
Was joycon drift and who like called him out on it. Did they actually like go to court for this you did?
Jail
Nintendo oh that would happen. That's what happened
You guys are fucking hilarious
Shale
All right, I'm done after this one I'm getting like crazy
Get your shit together. I am fine. Look at I'm number 63 out of a hundred. Oh
My god, that's so funny. Now. Let me clear the record. I I love Nintendo. I think they're a fantastic company
They just need to hire a new guy to make the controllers
This is like three consoles in a row
Least to
Backtracking I'm not backtracking. I
Would I'm literally playing in front of you right now. I'm playing the Nintendo switch in front of you right now
Right drop kick this out the window if I like thought I it wasn't a good console
That's called bad spawns and that's called
I'm gonna punt it out the window
Am I doing the two red spawned in the two places I could go I was screwed
This is the actually last one. This game's a lot fun. I love this game. I love this console
It's a great console sure you buy every accessory fucking need it
It's in my brain and just won't go away
It's got me it's got me I can't help it it's got me I can't stop
What the hell is what this skip bullshit get out of here?
That's quite a combo, but I don't care
You are you having a giggle? I am. Oh
That's bad. That's bad. All right. No, that's the list the last one. I'm not looking at chat
I'm not gonna laugh at people talking about how like okay
All right, this is it. This is the end
The end of the stream right here. My voice is a horse. What the fuck? All right. This is the end right here
This is the final one. Somebody's called me a fucking crackhead. This is the one. Let's be real closer
to be the one
Fuck I didn't want to pick that up. Yeah, that's bad. We're good save
Right
that
Yeah, I got caught up because I'm gonna blame the joy con again
I couldn't go to the left when I wanted to go left. I was desperately trying to push it
I was trying so hard now. This is the last one these things are so bad
These things these things are designed to high-five people in fucking Mario Party not to play video games with what were they thinking?
What were they thinking?
Okay, all right, this is it this no more like fucking around I'm gonna try as hard as I can good start not really though
Actually pretty bad. Not a great start
It went up on its own by the way, I didn't press up that one doesn't count that one
This is the last one that one is now
Refund this is not steam. I've been playing like two straight hours
Fuck this was somebody's first frame shit
Um
And I like break up a friendship an hour ago, I'm sorry about that
All right, almost done. Give me the speed. I need it
Good good. I gotta go up and around when I get there in time. Oh
It's gonna be rotten
It's gonna be rotten by the time I get there. It's gonna be rotten good
Go down
so
It's actually the last one this is truly the final one before I bite this analog off with my teeth and
Spit it into the camera
Fucking idiot Jesus Christ who decided to make the stupid yellow fucking circle the protagonist of a game
It never even listens to simple goddamn instructions
He would rather die than function according to his unintended was intended fucking purpose. There's a reason he's piss-colored
He's a giant piss ball that everyone should hate fuck Pac-Man
Don't count. No, I was reading check. Let's go early the end. This is it
No matter what happens. I can lose right now. I can lose right now
Build it up all of them this way eat them. Make sure they can't kill you
God
No more speed don't care just going for clear pressing down. Why am I going to slow?
God damn it. I just didn't fucking commit because the red was behind me
Give it second place like four times. Ha ha ha
I'm gonna we're gonna run the credit in the background. No, um, this last one. I'm fine. I'm fine. It's good. Everything's fine
I I hate this but I love this game so much. I can't help it. Okay, it calls me a crack at
They weren't kidding either. They were like mad. I'm sorry. I tried to go
I just tried to go up four times in a row. I couldn't go up. It wouldn't let me I tried
Terrible route I still did it. I still got what I wanted bad route, but I feel like it's getting worse
I feel like it's happening like 40% of the time. I try to move in a direction. I think it's getting worse
This is getting worse. I
Have enough time to get these before they come over here. I'll get collapsed on. Oh, come on. What's with that spawn?
Are you out of your mind? What the hell?
Dude, it put it right in front of me. If I play another one after this, I'm gonna delete my twitch channel
Okay, if I do another one after this I will delete my account on twitch if I play another one after this
I will delete my account really dumb way to do that. But I did it. Anyways, please get him
It was a good run. I'm fine
We go. Come on. I can get one more boost fuck out of the way get out of the way
Oh you give me a fruit. Give me a fruit God
It's blocked on all sides. It's blocked
Oh
So close so many times no, I'm not gonna sleep tonight. Oh
Anyways, uh, thanks for watching everybody. That's that concludes the weekly meltdown stream where you know
I just like I get a little crazy and on Saturday and just bottle up a bunch of fucking anger and just blow it all up
And here we go
Screaming Andy YouTube voice Andy. I know I I know oh
Damn it. Let me I gotta fix the record. I love Nintendo
I love the four games a generation they come out with that are really good. I like that. I love this company
I'm sorry. I'm just kidding. No, I love my switch. It's a great console. I just want to stomp on the Joy-Cons
Moon shoes, but anyways, thanks for watching. I'll see you next week. See you on Saturday
Maybe Saturday I will have
All the iPad stuff done and maybe we can play some iPad games
I'll try to get a good list of iPad games and I will see you guys on Saturday. Have a great week
I actually have a lot of
Medical stuff really coming up here this week. So I'm looking forward to it. See what happens. I will see you guys Saturday
Have a great week. Thanks for watching as always. See you guys on Saturday. I hope you don't miss me too much
I'll be missing thanks for watching. I'm kidding. Of course. I'm gonna miss everybody. I'll see you guys on Saturday. Good night. Goodbye
Thank you for all the subs by the way, even though I went down to it once a week
I've made majority of you guys are still subscribed
So I you don't have to do that if you don't want to stay subbed
You don't have to you can just drop it right now if you really want to
I don't want people to have to think that they need to keep paying this stream
$5 a month like four streams a month. So you appreciate it. Nonetheless, have a great night. Have a great week
See you soon. I might have some things to talk about on the next stream. So we'll see take care guys. Have a good one