Hello ladies and gentlemen. It's me, Santa Claus. I found my way into Team Fortress 2.
And it's going to be a very holiday, cheerful, and exciting video today. We're going to punch people in the bums.
It's time to see who's on the naughty list. Let me have some chocolate before I do this. Right from Prancer's ass.
That was gross. Why did I say that? Here we go. Get up there you fat bastard. Oh my god. What a fail. Oh my god.
Geez man, the chocolate bar is a piece of crap for trying to just heal yourself.
I got two targets right here. There's a sentry. They know the sentry's over here. It's okay.
Come on now. Here we go. Oh get him. Get him. Merry Christmas motherfucker.
You're doing a fine job over here, engineer. Good job getting rid of that sapper.
So you're kind of like one of my elves. Oh shit, he's dead. Oh boy.
There's a level two over here, level three. Oh my fuck me.
Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle all the way. Oh what fun it is to ride on a one horse open sleigh.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
On donner, on tancer, on prancer, on vixen, on prickson, on crickson, and Richard Nixon.
These are the horses that run on my sleigh. Punch that medic in the face, he's dead. Hooray.
There goes a soldier flying real quick. I wonder if I could punch this guy in his dick.
find out right now he's shooting me with the rocket jumper something tells me
you don't know come on let me get a random crit he of course he gets the
random crits we're pushing too fast get the what what the hell is that I can't
believe he actually lived it for as long as he did moment of truth here we go get
that sentry nice nice job nice job I can't believe it it doesn't matter
anyways I got him and it didn't even work and I'm gonna die I'm okay yeah I
got it actually got it nice forget the cart I need punches I can't even leave
this bond oh look what the hell is this guy doing and what maybe he just kind of
gave up that's what I figure maybe he was on fire didn't have a way to heal
himself doesn't doesn't know where the health packs are and it's just like you
know what it's just over I'm just gonna sit here and die
pyro coming around here he's gonna drop down whoo just barely come on come on
I'll show you the Christmas spirit yeah bump me in here yeah you want the
Christmas spirit fuck no he needed one hit oh I'm going up there you think that
the mini century is gonna save you from me punching you right in the back you
think that's gonna save you huh you think that's gonna oh you want to be
friendly what you just showed me some respect and then you came at me with the
sword all right well not sword it's like it's more like a chocolate axe he's dead
I don't know how you died oh Merry Christmas no no I'll do it again I'm not
even lined up shit what just what was that what what the fuck just happened
that was chaos I missed two times a guy's hand is on the ground I should can
I pick that up I'll give it back to him he probably needs it yet yet get here
we go here we go here we go here we go watch out Angie watch out Angie this is
the one oh you got no that that guy just blew himself up on purpose because he
knew it was gonna happen what fuck I I'm counting that one regardless that that
guy just freaked out and made sure hey you are a spy maybe not but you are no
you're not that was fucked up that was some serious there's a one can I get the
pyro as well I wonder I wonder give me that full health cat give me that full
health cat give me that full health cat you son of a bitch and I got back
snapped how did he blow up that far away over